Come, daughter!
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
Oh, guys...
It can't.
I have to take my daughter.
We're here...
You and Carol came
with the same hairstyle.
You're matching.
It's Pucca and big Pucca.
But, buddy...
Two Puccas!
It goes with the plant.
We always match!
You're beautiful.
We'll go to the same party.
The neon party.
- The fairy party.
- Let's not have a fashion show,
but just comment on what inspired you.
What inspired you?
Carol?
- Man, I...
- I love it.
I woke up like... in this mood...
I wanted to do a bun.
What about the green lipstick?
I saw the green pencil
and decided to put it on my mouth.
Stand up, turn around for us.
Do your dance moves.
What about your dance moves?
Wonderful!
Wow! What about Pabllo?
I'm a fairy who hangs out with Barbie.
- Naughty girl, right?
- No, a fairy!
I like to refer to cartoons,
I enjoy animes,
I can be who I want.
So can I! What am I today?
Jeez, you're always
very versatile, trendy, super...
And you, John?
I'm went for the "hetero top",
unusual for me.
I'm very discreet!
Look at him, so discreet!
I'm not in my milieu!
No, you came as Brokeback Mountain.
And you're the other guy.
So, let's go?
No, I don't know if I like you.
So, kiss me. Later...
What about you, Lexa?
- I came shining today.
- Versace!
I'm totally golden today!
Versace, girl!
Get up, give us a twirl, dance...
- Versace!
- That's it!
Now, Jerry...
came without a bag or a backpack
because his pocket can fit a house!
Stand up, Jerry!
- I'll fit in that pocket.
- It's rad!
He's very fashionable.
Girl, many things fit in there!
Everything!
You're full of yourself,
you'll end up on a catwalk.
Titto didn't dance.
I don't have to...
Give us a twirl!
Thanks a lot. I like funk music.
Episode seven.
I can't believe it, girl!
Oh, my God!
Carol is crying tears of arousal
in this... I mean...
- You're crying, right, Carol?
- I'm very moved.
I'm not ready to say goodbye to you.
No, guys, don't joke around!
I'll miss you!
I'm not prepared...
There's one more.
This is episode seven, right?
Girl, you don't understand.
Do you remember what happened?
Anna heard Renatinho having sex,
do you remember?
It was sad!
Are you guys loud?
I'm very reserved having sex,
I like something more...
You're banging and you say, "Ah."
No, I'm...
Like a belly ache.
No, girl!
I'd say, "What is it? Did I fart?"
No, my love, not like that.
I'm making the sound!
Bad breath?
You have bad breath!
- I did!
- I'm making a sound.
Jerry, are you loud?
It depends on how horny I am.
Jerry, what's your level of...
horniness, is it like "full of energy"?
I'm full of energy!
I like men that talk to me.
- Yeah, I...
- I like men
who spank me.
You like men who talk?
What?
- What?
- What did you say?
I like to be spanked...
I like them to...
Hit your chin...?
Who choke you?
Who choke me!
I like that too.
It's great, guys...
I like to be choked too.
To be fucked and choked...
I feel short of breath.
You faint...
It's a slight choking,
not a psycho kind of thing.
I like being cursed. "You unemployed!
You bum...".
I like being cursed at. I love it!
I don't like being tied up.
You're unemployed
and you have bad breath!
Out of the blue!
What?
I don't like being tied.
I don't like it!
God forbid it!
That's not sex!
But you can choose it.
Hey, Jerry, how's the voice you make?
I speak like this
when I have an idea and I have
to write a funk song.
Go, naughty girl
Look at John, man.
He's caressing his nipple, did you see?
Let's hit play!
- Let's see it!
- Let's go!
Did you kiss anyone?
I did, but there were few men yesterday.
You don't have problems finding guys!
Jeez, I did at the last minute. I swear.
It was difficult!
I had a company.
Do you see that mature relationship?
They're cool, talking...
- I'm loving it!
- That's it!
Totally, right? They are talking...
"I had sex with someone..."
Yes, but...
They can fall out of love for each other
and be just friends or...
No, I don't think so.
This is strengthening their bond!
I made up my mind about the party,
I'll take you to Stage tonight.
Let's go wild!
Nath, is Andrei going? Your hands...
Yes!
Fine!
Did Andrei stay?
Andrei stayed and is...
Renatinho's friend and everybody's.
They took him in well.
Yes! They did!
- I liked.
- But...
he is a nice guy.
Easy, I don't know.
That's a way...
of stopping Nath getting in trouble!
If Andrei is there, Nathália is tied.
Ramon didn't worry about him,
there was no joke.
Ramon... he just wants to hook up.
Ramon didn't waste time bothering,
he just had sex!
He had sex with everybody.
Ramon's hooking up with a lot of girls!
Guys, remember she was jealous
of Ramon in front of Andrei?
It's been quite a while!
- She's fine!
- But...
She's resentful, right?
Very.
I believe you're a Scorpio, too.
I don't know, I liked Andrei.
I don't know if I want...
God, the dream party!
Girl, the way we like to sing, girl.
Bro, look at the party they went to!
The way we like to put up a show!
They're in Lexa's concert!
Is it my concert?
Lexa, MC Carol and Pabllo Vittar!
I gave a concert there last year.
We go everywhere together.
You guys are a couple, girl!
Easy, it's intense, but...
She knows she's intense!
I'm that kind of friend.
That tells you, "Come on!"
My friends are all mine.
Are you jealous of them?
Obviously. My choreographer
started dating,
she was going to parties and being quiet,
then she stopped going to parties.
I said, "Look, girl,
seriously... you can date,
"but don't leave your sisters behind."
I agree with you, but...
if my friend were like that,
baby, I'd be like this
at the party, alone! Happy!
- So would I!
- I would resent her boyfriend.
I'd be upset at...
A real friend wants you to be happy!
If she's happy with someone, you'll say,
-"I'm happy for you!"
- Sure.
That's it, I'll go dancing,
but I'll hold this little grudge.
When that person breaks up,
she calls you and...
"I told you."
"Let's go out?" "No, I'm lying down."
My nickname would be Beyblade,
I would spin around everywhere.
- Beyblade!
- I like it.
I'm having fun...
But I didn't come here to date or...
I came here to have fun with you guys!
But what are you gonna do about it?
How is it gonna be?
I'm gonna explain the relationship...
Explain the situation.
I'm gonna say,
"I want us to work things out,
"but unfortunately,
now is not the moment."
Nath's moved talking about that.
That's too harsh!
Girl, you're kissing this guy at the party
that you met 2 days ago.
I thought they were just making out!
Do you think Andrei wants that from her?
I don't think so!
I'll be honest...
What she's doing,
she's being
emotionally responsible for him,
which is great!
If it was the opposite,
I think she'd fall for him.
No, I think you can be honest...
Nobody says
they're in love anymore, right?
No, they say they're "in love".
I always say I'm enjoying the person,
I never say, "I'm in love."
- Why?
- It's cheesy!
It's not cheesy at all!
If you feel it, it's not!
I don't say it exactly like this,
- but it means the same.
- Like?
"I'm head over heels...
"for you."
"I'm head over heels
for you, you know?"
"I'm head over heels for you?"
"I'm into you."
It's been a week
I've been going to your house,
every night, that frantic kind of thing.
Let's say I wake up,
bring you breakfast in bed,
and say "Good morning, Carol."
Then you say, "Let me tell you something.
"I'm head over heels for you."
I'm gonna tell you,
"Go see a doctor."
When you say you're head over heels...
That's one option, it really is.
Guys, where I come from...
when you say you're head over heels,
fuck, it means a lot.
It's like saying, "I love you."
- He thought that was a water fountain.
- Damn, he's thirsty!
Look.
Lexa 1.0.
Now comes next version of Lexa, look!
Lexa 2.0 now.
Drinking from a fountain!
- It's Lexa, man!
- It's me!
Jesus Christ, man.
Lexa doesn't make faces, he does.
I drink calmly, right, girl?
The drink makes faces for her!
She drinks a lot!
Look at Ramon, man.
He's wasted!
Pabllo's already seen me like that!
But I was like that too.
- You don't have...
- Jeez!
Fuck, dude!
Oh, my God!
I think that's when Ramon drank the most!
Ramon invited me to a party,
I won't go anymore.
- What?
- I can't go out with him!
- You'll take care of him.
- No!
Have you ever run into Ramon
after last vacation?
No, we arranged to go
to a funk party.
The same funk party we...
- We go...
- Can you keep up with Ramon?
You can!
But he can't keep up with you.
I may beat him.
I'm very discreet at funk parties.
Wherever I go,
I'm very discreet, I'm quiet.
To make it clear, at that party there...
there wasn't a pandemic.
I miss that time
we could sit next to each other!
- I don't!
- Help!
This Nathália...
Ramon's carrying Nath, man.
They're watching the sunrise,
- they're not doing it.
- But what do you call that?
No!
Yeah... Trigger warning.
Trigger warning for the first kiss.
There's a chance.
No, that was a minor trigger warning...
The sunrise, look.
Nath would mess things up
if she did that!
Nath would mess up or Ramon?
Nath!
Both of them, actually!
If I shook your hand,
we're brothers. You're with her,
she's a buddy for me, that's it!
I'm free!
Impressive!
Man, I didn't do anything.
I was asleep when Ramon did that!
Relax!
Talk to him.
- He's pissed!
- No, he's not!
When I was gonna hug him, he...
Andrei's mad at Nath.
Andrei's mad, bro.
Andrei went upstairs to his bedroom.
He doesn't have one!
The extra became the lead artist.
He's a guest who gets mad
in the host.
At this moment,
I feel sorry for Ramon
because I had a flashback
of the last vacation, of how they were.
He and Nath were...
Andrei's sleeping on the floor!
I said he didn't even have a bed!
I would leave.
He has a reason to be jealous like this.
- But nothing happened, bitch!
- Nothing!
But he has a reason, sis.
Reason for what, bitch?
I'm dating you
and your ex carries you...
It's complicated, girl!
But he has to understand
he's new on the block,
it had happened before...
But he was classy, he didn't argue.
That's what I was gonna say.
He didn't say anything stupid to her,
he went to sleep.
He just slept!
I'd be kind of upset too,
because of the situation,
and I'd talk to her.
The problem with those guys
is that they always get mad at the women.
If I were there, I'd say,
"What's up, bro?"
But he doesn't have to talk to the guy,
he has to talk to her!
If I were Andrei, I'd talk to Ramon!
"What's that?"
I'd do that,
but I think it wouldn't bother me.
But that bothered him!
They're not in a relationship!
No one knows what will happen!
You didn't like it? Go to bed!
Remember when she argued with Ramon
because of that girl?
Andrei was in the bus,
he noticed she has feelings for him.
So, he will be upset
with his girl, his affair,
not with the guy, he doesn't matter.
The guy's hurt, right?
He's falling for her!
I think he's bothered enough
to not sleep with her,
but not to leave.
They'll kiss...
To sleep on the floor like that,
- that's terrible!
- They'll be cool.
Can you tell me
why you got upset yesterday?
I don't know. I was taking care of you...
at the end and...
I was drunk...
But I was asleep.
It's not my fault!
I know!
But you got angry.
Yes.
Guys, can I say something?
I like that talk.
At least he told her the truth, you know?
-"Man, that's it..."
- I don't know!
He said he didn't get pissed...
I feel like going there
and comforting him.
-"I was sad."
- He's sad!
If I were Nath...
I would talk to Andrei differently,
like, "I know you were upset because
Ramon carried me,
"but I didn't do anything.
I'm sorry about that."
- To put herself...
- In his shoes.
"Yes, I know you got upset. I'm sorry.
"I didn't do anything to you,
I was sleeping.
"So, let's keep going today? Or else
that's okay, I'm gonna go to my party..."
That's it!
I didn't plan this...
To be in a relationship with someone here.
It's the first time
the four of us are single...
Last vacation we were all dating...
That doesn't mean
we won't see each other again!
I liked the talk!
Please, emotional responsibility!
- Sit and talk!
- He's sad!
I think she could have apologized
for the situation, you know?
Imagine if you were him.
But, girl, it's really not her fault.
No need to apologize.
He really got upset,
he said, "I'm gonna pack."
I said she could have apologized
for the situation!
Imagine you...
She didn't do anything!
The thing is, he had
a reason to be upset, you know?
She thinks
she could have done that differently.
She was right, she was straight, you know?
If he got upset, it's not her fault!
And I think she was influenced by Anna.
Yes...
Now you understand that everything,
all fights, apart from Luan and Bia,
wouldn't have existed
if they had that kind of talk.
- That's it!
- Yes.
I don't wanna see you
hooking up with another guy.
That's not gonna happen.
It'd never have happened.
I just didn't want to put a label on it.
- But I've never...
- We don't...
...left home wanting
to hook up with a guy.
We don't need anything else.
We have to be partners.
I'm gonna cry!
Kimberly.
Look at her joy.
Oh, what a good kiss.
Oh, what a big tongue!
It's been a while since
I've felt a tongue.
Carol, are you happy they're together?
Little Pucca doesn't even comment!
Oh, my God!
Another friend of hers!
Ítalo is dangerous.
Is that a kiss?
It's somebody she makes out with.
Look at Tay's face!
Look at Renatinho, "Ouch."
How's Renatinho? Because the guy
who just arrived is real handsome.
This is my guy from Rio.
Ítalo, Tay.
Bro, hit pause!
"This is my guy from Rio."
Do you remember
when Renatinho got in the house,
"Aren't you the guy
that hooked up with Milena?"
That's Milena!
What?
Don't you remember?
- Of course I do!
- That's Milena.
That's Milena!
Let me introduce. Nathália, Renato.
- Renato.
- Nice to meet you.
Guys, is it Milena's guy?
Hey, man. Jeez, dude.
How are you? I'm fine.
- Are you cool?
- I'm fine.
But when Anna talked about him,
it was like the relationship
wasn't that good.
Yes!
Anna hooked up with her friend's guy...
she's with the guy from Rio.
Yes...
Guys, we're going camping...
Let's go camping tomorrow!
Camping!
- Look at Nath.
- Have you ever gone camping?
I went camping in the Amazon forest once.
I just found out I was there
two days after.
Then I started to cry
because I remembered Anaconda.
I never went camping.
But I wouldn't sleep well, and I'm a big,
hot girl!
What's that?
I'm a big girl!
What happened?
Oh, let her speak!
Please, have you ever gone camping?
I haven't!
I was gonna ask you
to set up a tent with me,
but you don't like it!
I was gonna say something, but I'm...
I'm gonna be quiet.
Camping at the beach?
Never!
It's very good!
Fuck! He's my brother from Rio.
He's my fuck buddy!
Bro, relax. Look, enjoy.
Please!
Did you hear her saying
he's her fuck buddy?
Do you have many FBs?
I don't have time for this.
I travel a lot!
That has nothing to do with it.
- I don't have a fuck buddy!
- No?
I don't spent much time in one place.
You can have one in São Paulo,
when you are here...
She has people to call...
"This is FB."
No, it's not!
They change all the time!
My thing is, a lot of turnover.
I live in Uberlândia...
I don't hook up with anybody there because
I did them all!
Love, whore's love
Whore's love
- That's it!
- What about you, Carol?
I don't have that,
but there are some guys I hooked up with
and I know the sex is good...
Sometimes I stop by and...
"Hey, what about that day?"
So, we laugh, talk, and...
That's a fuck buddy.
Do you have many FBs?
FB!
Fuck buddy. I get it.
There's that person, right?
In another state,
that you have a nice vibe with...
John?
Man, I do, but it's...
I have all kinds of fuck buddies.
John has objects which are their friends.
Everything can be sexual for him.
I have FBs, BBs...
- What's a BB?
- Booty buddy.
Booty buddy?
Fuck!
Yeah, I'm jealous.
Friends with benefits.
Sometimes I don't care
seeing him with other girls,
but sometimes I do.
Yeah, right!
Meaning...
Look!
I'm gonna say something!
Hit pause!
If there's someone I like
at this moment, it's Nathália.
Nathália keeps everybody at bay.
She's unbearable.
She's closed!
But when she's honest, she's awesome!
Like, "I like the guy,
but I can't explain it,
-"I'm jealous..."
- She's honest!
I like that!
She's not being honest
saying she doesn't mind...
"I don't, but I do, and I wanna throw
my drink at the girl."
Titto, do you think she was honest?
She doesn't know what she's talking about.
She did like Anna.
She said she didn't mind,
but seeing Renatinho having sex...
That's it! Nobody is totally detached
not to give a shit!
You can't be 100 percent detached!
What they have is chemistry.
They have that attraction...
That's a chill of arousal.
Is that it?
- I think so!
- That's delicious.
Ouch!
Let's go to the sex room?
There's gonna be a gangbang.
The three of them?
Yes! That's gonna happen...
A threesome.
A homage?
Oh, my God!
Homage à trois.
I'm shocked!
Ménage. Oh, my God!
Fuck, he's really a friend!
Let me get this.
Milena went to brush her teeth?
No, she went to pop a pimple and left!
Milena was naked?
I think she was naked.
Guys, it happened!
There was a real ménage.
I'd brush my teeth before having sex.
But when Anna saw Milena at that party,
she said, "My best friend!"
Yes!
A friend you have sex with?
Yes, like us.
But I didn't get one thing,
Renatinho was left behind,
he didn't try anything...
Renatinho and Anna are tied!
She talked about Milena...
No, it was Brazil versus Germany!
Some people have many things...
Renatinho held his dick.
Held his dick!
Let me say,
the competition between them is ruthless.
I don't know who hooked up more!
Did you hear that?
If Renatinho leaves today,
he lived as if it were two seasons.
I wonder if he's going back to Nikiti,
will you meet him, Carol?
- Renatinho?
- No, I'm cool!
Have you ever done that, girl?
- What?
- Challenged a short man?
"What do you want?"
Girl, I challenge ugly men.
Sometimes I do it!
I look at the ugly guy and say,
"I'll do it to feel pretty!"
Short men. I go for it.
Jerry, how tall are you?
I'm 5' 9".
How would you hit on Pabllo?
Pabllo, stand up, please.
But make that voice
so she'll shake those big legs, okay?
- Look at those quads, guys.
- The difference is big.
She's not bullshit.
Let's see it, hear it, hear it.
- What's up, baby?
- Hi.
Oh, the famous big ass.
Fuck!
He didn't say anything!
Girl, hear Jerry's voice!
That's the 4:00 in the morning!
That's it!
Jerry, did you think it was difficult?
Life's simpler than we imagined!
Let's have a hot dog?
A hot dog!
Anna, look.
She tripped, I didn't do anything!
Okay. She really tripped.
I took two guys there,
- nobody touched me.
- Is it my fault?
You gave the opportunity.
Stop pretending is not your fault!
Anna, I said,
"Let's enjoy the hot dog."
And she did that.
Look how cynical he is!
Bro, look how cynical he is. Oh, my God!
Look at that cynical guy!
Girl, I'd send him back to his hotel
and say, "I'm gonna stay at the beach.
"Stay away!"
"Your vacation is over!"
I think, in my opinion,
that girl didn't know about anything!
No, it's his fault!
She said, "Let's go."
And held his arm.
She was just holding his arm...
just because!
Yes!
She didn't know he was with Anna!
And I think Anna is...
It's not the girl's fault!
She shouldn't know about anything,
but what about him?
Anna's overreacting!
He's a cynic.
Everybody agreed!
But she says she's a free girl,
a free girl all the time and so on.
He made a scene first.
Exactly!
He's mad 'cause
she didn't let him do that stuff.
He said he liked her a lot
in her ear!
I think he could've avoided that,
got it?
Because, man, you don't need to say that.
I can offer you a glass of water
and suggest a lot of things.
I can flirt with you
drinking a glass of water.
Seduce me by offering me a glass of water.
I won't say anything.
I'll drink the water.
Just drink and offer me.
What the hell?
Carol, take it. Take my wallet.
What does that mean?
The glass was salty, they washed it...
It means I wanna drink something
that's not this water.
Jeez!
Where's her milk?
Hey, woman, hey!
It'd be way easier if you enjoyed with us!
We are with you!
With us!
We took you in!
Okay, fine!
Look...
That's it...
Now it's Renatinho's fault.
Now it is Renatinho's fault!
Nonsense!
That's nonsense!
He can bring a girl. She's already...
He could bring a girl!
Thanks, Anna, for this!
Anna and Ítalo!
Come, Mu.
Look at that!
Look at the size of it.
Renato's last day!
That's beautiful!
That's it, bro!
Always.
That's it, guys.
There's no better place to say goodbye.
This place is nice for camping!
It's bad to start missing people!
When there's one day left,
you always feel bad!
Guys, the last episode is coming!
I'm feeling something.
Look who's coming.
Fuck!
She really woke up, right?
Look at Renatinho's joy
because Anna came back.
He's staring at her!
Kiss? No, get out of here!
That's a mistake.
Kiss?
I think this is
the most beautiful episode.
Look, Ramon's saying, "Don't kiss me."
I'm gonna miss Renatinho!
You've seen it,
the energy's running out...
and I can't get enough!
Lexa, hit play! Let's see what's coming!
The last episode's promising
because I'm gonna nail it.
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
Tonight is gonna be epic.
Epic!
"The debauchery's gonna begin."
He proposed to me
But I don't get it
I'm a fucking slut
I live in the moment
Ride
The judge's crazy!
Oh, damn!
- I don't wanna sit down.
- That's it!
John broke the couch!
I didn't get anything, girl.
Thanks, guys!
It's life...