- Oh, my God. Episode two!
- You guys are so anxious, man!
I missed this a lot.
Fells like we're at a party.
- She comes in singing.
- Jerry's gonna sit down, easy.
- Jerry's hotter each day.
- Damn, you're all dressed up today.
- For episode 2.
- Where did you come from?
Fashion week.
- In my bedroom.
- We are honoring last week's party.
I said she's dressed up, not you.
Get over yourself.
I'm not talking to you.
Go ahead.
- Get over yourself.
- I'm gonna send our chat history.
You wanna get back together?
No! Don't do this!
I want to see episode two now, guys.
I'm dying to know what happened
to Murilo and Tay.
Because they started like that,
and now what?
Exactly. Let me ask you guys this.
Do you think they can fix this?
Because Murilo hooked up with a girl
in front of Tay. Will she forgive him?
If I were her, absolutely.
A second pair of eyes never hurts.
She hooked up with a guy too.
She just dismissed him.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
Murilo...
- Murilo, are you busy?
- Yes, I am.
He's frying mine.
- Are you going somewhere? You four?
- Yes.
Go on. Enjoy!
I'm watching you.
If you betray me, there's no coming back.
We're going for a ride.
Bye, boys!
Kisses!
Great girl in a great car.
Cool girl in a cool car.
Girl, today you're driving our car!
I trust you, girl!
Go, princess.
From dumpster, right?
Go, Mother Lucinda.
Mother Lucinda.
- Who's Mother Lucinda?
- Who?
I woke up great this morning.
Course, you had sex... All relaxed.
I woke up great, I'm cool.
- You nailed it.
- Not saying anything...
- That's it.
That's it.
She said you were teasing her.
Getting close to the guy she was with.
Then I said...
When we got there...
I was the first one to say hi
to that fucking DJ.
When I was talking to him,
she hadn't hooked up with him yet.
What's wrong with this, bro? Fuck it.
Girl, after what happened yesterday,
how are you and Murilo?
- What are you gonna do?
- You guys aren't talking.
He's not looking at my face,
but, girl, I'm cool.
- He's very mature, right?
- No. I told you what was gonna happen.
I told him to wait for the first party.
The first party, he drank
and did what he wanted, you know?
Now I can do whatever I want.
Now, it's... Yeah.
Girl, do you think he really hit on her?
It's easy to say...
Kissing is not a big deal.
Girl, he had sex.
He had sex with her in our room.
This is over for me.
There's no feelings involved in kissing,
but sharing the energy of sex
is hard for me. This is hard, you know?
I didn't know he had sex with her.
If he cared about me,
he wouldn't have had sex.
Girl, wait. You had sex with others too.
Girl, it wasn't in the same house.
- Did you get the cover-up?
- Sun! I got it.
Murilo was with his chick. Nath was with
her boy who looks like a grandfather.
I don't know where you were.
I'm a mother now, show some respect.
Then Murilo started...
He was expecting you to do something.
Then you did, he did too. I saw that,
I didn't need to interfere.
- But you're wonderful.
- It seemed he was bragging.
Bragging. Obviously, they're like this.
I said, "Bro, I wasn't expecting anything,
man. You don't even know what happened."
It happened, well...
- We do worse stuff.
- Murilo, you waited for nothing.
- Be cool, I'm not talking to you, buddy.
- Waited for nothing.
I'm not talking to you, you know?
Be cool. You have no say in my life.
You know?
Oh, girl. I think I like the boys,
but they're stupid, you know?
They don't know
how to treat a woman right.
I think you really had to stand up for me.
As usual. Every one of them
thinks this way. Always!
I think you really have to interfere.
- Oh, girl, like...
- One for all, and all for one!
Let's leave? Let's dress up, right, guys?
Nothing in life is easy.
Hey, we're back.
Guys, they didn't even put
the catsup away.
Everybody's asleep. I'm gonna have
to work. Bro, that's impossible.
I'm here.
We're gonna work.
- Now.
- Really, why?
Everybody's gonna have to...
I'm gonna change and leave.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I imagined this was gonna happen.
The work is at night.
Murilo, the girls have to work,
today is our day off.
That's true. Wonderful.
I asked for whiskey and a hip-hop night.
To remember old times.
Yeah, I miss this. I think this is right.
Let's go. Everybody is beautiful
and full of colors.
- Come on, guys?
- Pay for our drinks, come on.
Pay for our sins.
Bye, pretty boys!
Honey!
You have to ask those girls, guys.
Do you wanna drink something?
- We ordered...
- For Tay.
The one with hair in braids.
Yeah, where's she? If you can find her,
it's been 25 minutes.
What did you order?
- We ordered three gins.
- Sorry, today is hectic.
- Actually, there's few people to serve.
- Yeah, just two.
Oh, no, two over here and two there.
- Aren't the boys gonna work tonight?
- No, they should show up later.
Girl, I'm sweating. My armpit is sweating.
- Who already made 20,000?
- Since you noticed they're taking long,
switch with them,
I wanna see this flowing.
Wait, I have to remember
how to fix drinks.
Ask them to explain this to you.
- Okay.
- But quickly.
- I asked for two gins.
- Take these for me. You're gonna switch.
- Who's this for?
- I'll show you.
The gin is for the last table.
A blond couple
and a lady wearing a white
long-sleeve blouse. Those two, okay?
Okay.
Let me take the beers, girl.
Fix the drinks.
I don't remember.
Girl, gin and tonic, for God's sake.
- It's caipirinha!
- Just squeeze some lime.
- Where's our gin?
- I gave you two gins, now two caipirinhas.
No. Two caipirinhas for her.
But we actually ordered three gins
and two caipirinhas.
I gave you two gins.
Two gins and two caipirinhas.
- But did you order from Tay?
- Yes, where's she?
- She's at the bar now. We switched.
- She knows.
She told us two.
- Okay!
- I'm gonna confirm this.
No problem.
Let me teach you a trick. Now you're gonna
pour the vodka and count to ten.
Take the dosing cup off.
Pour the vodka in there.
- Count to ten, go.
- One, two, three... eight, nine, ten.
Pour it. Close it.
Shake it and put it in the glass.
Jeez.
- Who took your order?
- Tay did, but she's ignoring me today.
- But who's making mistakes?
- They are!
No!
- I've already said it, I've just said it.
- Me too!
- Tell them...
- I even...
- Girl, I've already asked.
- Tell them...
Then come here, not there!
- Here, three beers.
- Tay...
Let me explain.
- You serve them.
- But come here. So?
What are you gonna do
if somebody goes there?
- You tell to look for them!
- Okay.
- They're serving the lounge.
- One gin and tonic and one gin with juice.
There are too many people
in here, Ricardo!
Serve right!
I don't remember who ordered three beers.
I'm waiting here for a long time.
Not you. For God's sake.
How's work going?
- Three gins and tonic for us, please!
- I want five sex on the beach!
- Let's drink.
- Dude.
- Look at that girl.
- The one wearing yellow.
Dude!
Thanks!
I'm mad at you, Murilo.
Why is that, man? Hey, what did they
tell you about me?
You're gonna make her cry...
- Yes.
- Look at me.
Are we pals?
We are. But wanna talk later?
No...
I didn't go to that house
to get in people's way, okay?
No! Never ever. That's why
we really have to talk. No problem.
That's it. That's cool!
Bro, we got here together,
we don't know anything
and we've already had a history.
Bro, sorry if we ever argued...
No. Guys, living together is hard.
Look, that's most important, bro.
We have to promise one thing.
Never go to sleep mad at each other.
- Booze drifts apart, food brings together.
- I said, "I'll stop eating." Remember?
"I argued with Murilo, I won't eat."
No way!
- I am...
- I'm cool. I am passionate too.
- To us!
- To us, fuck!
The problem is, is Ramon good or bad?
Really? That's the name of my father.
But the drunk Ramon is good.
Is it really the name of your father?
What's yours?
- It's Vanessa.
- Nice to meet you.
- Every Ramon is a good person.
- Yeah, my father is a good person.
I was thinking about doing
something bad now.
- Not to me, right?
- I didn't say anything.
Take this any way you want, Vanessa, okay?
Fuck, Ramon hooks up with somebody
everywhere he goes. Look.
He's a womanizer.
- Are you gonna stay here romancing?
- Who?
- The whole party?
- I'm gonna stay with you now.
I told him,
"Are you gonna stay here romancing?"
No, but even I would be here.
What's up?
- That's okay.
- What?
- We're tired.
- You worked, but you'd better improve...
One for all, and all for one!
- Here's the reward, you can have fun!
- Amen! Thanks!
Amen!
Where's the booze?
We saved for you guys, kid.
One for all, all for one!
Fuck!
Hey, Murilão!
Murilão, come here!
Hey, I'm gonna talk to Ricardão.
I'm gonna try to borrow the boat for us.
Like, I don't know when,
but at least one ride.
- Hey, do you want me to talk to him?
- No, just chill,
- I can do this.
- Just us?
Breathe. Easy, darling.
Hey, bro!
How are you?
How was it?
- Did the girls do well?
- It was a little hard at the beginning...
- It's crowded, because it's summer.
- Good.
- I wanted to ask you a favor.
- Shoot, that's why I'm here.
- Last vacation... Do you remember?
- I clearly remember everything you did.
I don't know if that's good or bad.
But I committed myself when I called you.
I picked up the phone to call you.
It was that one time I needed a boat
to enjoy one night with the boys
and girls, I'm not sure you remember this.
Yes, I do.
The girls, although they weren't great,
but I believe in them incredibly.
- If I commit to you...
- No.
- Why not?
- It's early, you barely started working,
- the girls didn't do so well...
- But what's missing?
Call this guy, tell him
I asked you to talk to him.
He can help. That's the best
I can do for you right now.
And I mention your name when I call him?
He'll help you, say my name.
- Thanks. I guess!
- Maybe the boat is not that big.
I'm gonna pray.
- She's a prick, man.
- That's what I've just told her.
Don't let her make you lose your mind.
Don't lose it in front of her.
No. She knows it.
- She's my friend, I know, but dive in.
- She knows I'm weak, but then...
I respect her as always... Fuck it.
I didn't have sex for three months.
- She knows I like her.
- Jeez, she knows it.
She knows I like her, bro.
I don't do this to her.
I've never done this to anybody.
- I'm being very honest with you guys.
- Now you're doing this to her.
Bro, come on, you know?
Putting up with this shit? Fuck you.
Man...
Tay is not sure about her feelings.
She's free, she does
whatever she wants with her life.
- I wanna talk later, right?
- I was very honest with her.
- Bro, look at season one, how it went.
- Stop crying, she's coming. Stop crying.
I'm not gonna stop it.
Because this is what I'm feeling...
- Come on!
- That's what I'm feeling, you know?
But there's no need
for this joy, you know...
It's about being honest and being cool
when you're having fun. Fuck it.
That's it. That's okay.
Let's go home!
- Bye, girls!
- Kisses!
Hit pause.
You know what's fucked up?
I love it, you know. He was expecting
Tay to make a scene about that sex event.
He's bothered by the situation,
like, she doesn't care about me.
But I didn't get that part
about her being not sure.
- I think that's on him!
- She's totally sure.
- I didn't get why he was crying.
- I didn't! At all!
He's annoyed because
Tay didn't do anything.
He doesn't get he's the one playing games,
he's getting a taste of his own medicine.
- I like Murilo a lot...
- I like him when he's sober.
I think he's being noble,
he's already apologized to Anna,
he admitted he was crying.
He's expressing his feelings, that's cool.
- But, dude, he had to do that to Tay.
- I didn't get it when he said "prick"...
- But he had to do that to Tay.
- Maybe he doesn't want to open up to her.
- No, Tay is smiling, look.
- He's blaming Tay!
- No! He's crying because he likes her.
- And Tay is playing games with him?
I don't think he's playing games,
I think he's sorry.
I think he's crying because
when we use our temple...
- Tears of arousal.
- ...our body in a wrong way, we suffer.
- Now she's a minister!
- Oh, Carol!
Go preach away from here.
Do you think he's crying
because he's sorry or...
Yes, I've been there. I liked a person...
and had sex with another. The thing ended,
and I was disgusted with myself, you know?
- This is called moral hangover.
- I spent all night crying.
- I think he's feeling this way.
- Do you think he's disgusted with himself?
- Yes.
- No, guys! He's blaming Tay!
I think he's crazy about her
and doesn't know how to approach her...
He's crying because he's sorry or because
he's seeing she doesn't want him anymore.
He's seeing... That's it.
I think, maybe he's afraid
she doesn't want him anymore, you know?
By the way she's acting. Maybe I missed
something, I think he's like that.
I think he likes her so much
that when he sees her kissing somebody,
it's the same as seeing her having sex.
But if he had seen her having sex
on their bed, he'd have freaked out.
I think he got involved in the game,
he got involved, he went overboard a lot
and is very sorry.
Tell me now, who's playing games?
Tay or him?
If she likes him,
like she said in the car...
But she said it's over, girl.
- She's doing what she said she'd do.
- Why did she hook up with the guy?
- Girl! For God's sake!
- Look, guys...
She doesn't like that guy, she hooked up
with that guy to tease him, guys.
And he hooked up with that girl
to tease her. That's obvious.
You can love one person,
but feel attracted to others.
Girl, you know when somebody
is determined to forget a person?
- She can fall back for him.
- Obviously, but in a relationship,
the point is finding somebody
worth waiting for.
- I won't wait.
- If you have somebody...
I won't wait, I'm a whore.
Go, Vanessinha, go.
Vanessinha, welcome.
- Thanks, baby.
- Home sweet home.
Rendeiras Av. ZIP 88062-400
Lagoa da Conceição
What?
- Let's talk?
- I don't get it.
Girl, what a drama, man.
- Stop thinking you're right.
- There's no right or wrong.
- There are two free people...
- That's right.
- ...who do whatever they want, got it?
- But what I told you in the van,
I'll say it again.
You made a scene about his actions.
- Girl, look, really...
- Oh, you'll say he's not in love?
If he was, he wouldn't fuck someone else
in the bed he shares with me.
He should have had sex in the sex room!
I don't have to see them having sex!
- He's sorry. He's very sorry.
- I saw it!
- They had sex, I was alone in the bedroom.
- Don't you think I saw that and left?
Okay, girl, you saw it. You saw it, but...
- He should have had sex here in the pool!
- You should put yourself in his shoes.
- I told you I wouldn't do it.
- I know, girl, but you're saying
- you wouldn't do it...
- Why are we talking about this?
Suddenly he wakes up today
and is in love with me.
It's easy to fuck some girl, take her
to our bed and feel sorry the day after.
"Wow, I'm very sorry", got it?
Girl, imagine what it's like, the boy
is in love with you, and you tell him...
- In love with me, my ass.
- He had the chance
- to ignore you, and he didn't.
- Girl, you have to embrace these feelings.
- I'm talking about the last vacation too.
- But we committed to each other.
- How do you think this is a lie?
- It was different when we got out of here.
Even at the table. Oh, my God.
It's family, right, man.
There's or... no.
It's great. I don't wanna say this,
but it's delicious.
What's missing, man?
Is there ice?
There isn't?
Tay is very stubborn, bro.
- Tay is very stubborn, bro.
- Because of our age, I'm 28.
She's 23. She has
to fully enjoy her life, she's right.
I'll send your regards to everybody.
I think they're all upstairs.
Let's see what he has to say.
- Hello.
- Daniel?
- Yes, that's right.
- I work with Ricardo at the beach.
- How are you?
- I'm fine, everything is great.
I'm calling for a special reason.
Yesterday, I talked to Ricardo
and asked him if he could lend me the boat
we used in our last vacation here.
Actually, he told me you'd call.
That's okay,
I'll negotiate the price with him,
- but this is happening.
- Deal!
You're the man!
Dude!
Hey, guys! The van is here. Let's go?
Let's go!
- Let's drink this champagne?
- Yeah!
- Fuck!
- Let's drink it!
To the best vacation in the world!
Fuck!
Look at this, there's nothing.
Totally unspoiled.
- No boy coming home?
- I have a handsome friend.
Renan.
- He's coming at night.
- Carioca, right?
- Inked.
- So, I'd like one
in the house.
Look where Luan is!
- Where?
- He's gone!
- He must have had Beatriz suck his dick.
- For sure.
- That's for sure!
- They must be having sex now.
Let's go home?
Let's go.
I see a gorgeous man, stretched.
Thanks, bro.
Jeez! I'm back.
I'm gonna put it right here.
- What are you gonna do today?
- So...
Bro, I guess everybody is exhausted.
What do you think about
having a barbecue here?
- Jeez.
- I swear to you.
It's the best thing.
Better than going out. Listen up, bro.
- Is there gonna be cheese?
- Hear me out...
We can invite other people.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
Do you know who you'll invite?
I'm gonna invite Vanessa.
There's Vanessa, the DJ...
I'm gonna invite Beatriz.
Man, if Ramon brings
all his connections, there's gonna be
- about 30 chicks.
- And he's gonna kiss all of them.
That's a lie.
- I'm gonna hook up with Nath tonight.
- No!
See? I was going to. I tried.
Now I'm gonna invite somebody.
- I don't want to, I don't feel like it.
- See.
Let me drink some more.
Is the barbecue here?
Damn, our guests!
Hey! Kid!
Now we're talking!
Nice to meet you, Anna.
Fucking rain.
What's up, bro? Are you good?
Are you cool?
Look who's here!
- You left without seeing your friend.
- Where were you?
How I missed you!
- I'm fine, what about you?
- Cooking.
Damn!
Hi.
No hard feelings.
- I still love you.
- You are the only one I liked.
- Girl, go for it.
- I'm a woman too, you know?
- I don't want any problem...
Never!
She asked if Ramon and I have something
going on. I told her to go for it.
- No more.
- I told her.
No. Didn't I say, "The only one
Ramon hooked up with I liked"?
My name is Nathália
and I don't hook up with the same guy
I'm gonna hook up with all guys
And Anna will follow along
Nath!
Come here, Nathália.
On the chair!
Don't get dirty.
It's too dirty. Go, Nathália.
- Come on, Nathália!
- I've already put it.
Sit down!
Come on!
You know...
Open your mouth.
Now make him lose his mind with the shot.
I'm not good at this.
Did you swallow? He does that by himself.
Not yet?
Is it gonna be me all the time?
- Tonight or forever?
- Forever!
- Easy, let's talk about tonight.
- Not about tonight.
- Is it gonna be me all the time?
- You had sex with a girl. Easy.
I heard her moaning.
- Easy, I'm still hurt because of that.
- Wait. What about me?
- Kissing is no big deal.
- That's it.
If you go to the bedroom
and see some guy making me cum...
You had sex. It's gonna take some time
until I want to kiss you.
- Shut up. Please. Quiet.
- Let me tell...
Just listen to me.
- Just listen to me.
- Okay.
We hadn't seen each other
for three months.
- Two months!
- Almost three.
We hadn't seen or spoken to each other.
Then I get here, we get along just fine,
we have a real nice moment...
If it were any other girl
that I had hooked up with and said, "Man,
"let's be promiscuous?" I'd say, "Yes."
- I didn't say that.
- But we have a history, you know?
- Don't put words in my mouth.
- We have a history.
But why am I gonna hook up with a chick
if I'm gonna be with her the other day?
Three days later, I'll feel like
hooking up with another one.
Then we shouldn't be together.
Tay, our time is gone, okay?
- Our time is gone.
- Let's stop it, get in there and have fun.
- Some conversation!
- Oh, no. I have to smoke here.
- Bro, you weren't supposed to be here.
Hey, stop being rude!
- Come here, Lô, leave him!
- He wasn't rude to me.
He wasn't rude to me.
I'm gonna throw Luan.
Hey, Luan, don't let me
mess things up again.
Bro, gag me, tie me, please, right now.
Man, tie me, please, tie me.
Gag me, please. Knock me out.
- Gag me, please. Knock me out.
- I'm gonna do it soon, you're gonna sleep.
- Please.
- What?
What?
Who?
Here. On you, right now, fuck!
Get fucking real!
What's this?
I want it too.
- His dick was bumping into your knee.
- He said Murilo bumped his...
Get fucking real! I was watching!
I was waiting. Get the fucking leg off!
Do you think I was feeling his dick?
- Are you... Oh, fuck you!
- Stop it, Luan!
What... Right?
- I wasn't feeling anything.
- No problem, Beatriz!
Stop it!
- This is bullshit!
- Do whatever you want, man.
No, I understand, but I don't...
No, really, I didn't even care!
- You play a saint all the time.
- Murilo was bumping his dick into my knee.
Girl, I didn't even notice.
Man, we drank a lot.
I'm drunk too, I'm not sober.
He's gonna bump his dick
into my knee, I'm feeling his dick!
- Fuck, into my knee!
- No. You're not feeling it.
- You're not normal, you're a saint!
- Stop it, Luan!
Stop it, Luan!
- Just pretend.
- It's no use pretending.
Do you need other dicks?
- Oh! For God's sake!
- Do you miss a dick?
What?
He went there to say, "Didn't you notice
the guy bumping his dick into your knee."
- In this case, Murilo.
- And why did he argue with her?
But that's because Murilo
- and Luan have this beef.
- But, buddy, you don't have to...
Did you see how he talked to her?
Why didn't he go...
The guy was bumping his dick
into her knee, but that's it, bro!
- Say, "Get your dick off my chick?"
- Exactly!
He wanted to play the tough guy
with her. What an ass...
He didn't go talk to the guy!
But that was obvious last summer's end.
When they had that fight, things got ugly.
He did nothing. When somebody
confronts him, he chickens out.
Which was Murilo.
Which was Murilo, the one he's accusing
of bumping the dick into her knee.
I would go talk to him and say,
"What's up? You're disrespecting my woman.
"Are you bumping your dick into her knee?
What's up, bro? Are you crazy?"
There was a similar situation
last summer. Murilo didn't like
what Luan did to Bia in the bus,
there was that fight.
When Anna argued with Murilo,
whom did she go talk to?
To Luan, who was supporting Anna
about Murilo's opinion.
So, they have this history,
but that doesn't justify what he did.
Regardless of what Murilo did,
if it was on purpose or not,
Luan's attitude was completely wrong.
He should have talked to Murilo.
He should have gone to talk to him.
Why did he have to argue with her?
She was doing absolutely nothing.
He didn't talk loud to her, he whispered
in her ear so Murilo didn't hear.
When Murilo was far away,
he started to scream at her...
If she wanted to talk and tell her friends
what was going on, she didn't know because
- she's lost and there's booze involved...
- Poor girl, she was completely lost.
I think his attitude is outrageous,
I think it's ridiculous.
Her friends must support her,
she must stand up for herself.
Regarding Tay and Murilo, he said
stupid things. Men got lost in that party.
They had the chance to get along,
to express themselves, they fucked it up.
I think Luan and Murilo
made a huge mistake.
Tay gave him a chance...
Tay gave him a chance, and he screwed...
He wasn't rational, he didn't get
she was letting him be free,
and he wasted it all, you know?
What I think about Murilo and Tay
is that they didn't have that breaking up
- every relationship needs...
- Sit down and talk.
They'll have it.
Like the breaking up Nath and Ramon had.
They don't have problems.
They don't have any problems. They need
that kind of breaking up to be cool.
In the past, they didn't get along well
because they always had a fight.
Now, Murilo always respected Tay a lot,
you know? So, this is mutual.
We're on episode two,
we still have a long way to go.
Let's see what's going to happen
on next, go.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
- Fuck!
- The guys fought, bro?
- Again? No!
Oh, my God!
- One guy went to hold the other...
- It's Murilo and Luan.
But you saw them leaving
with that angry look, right?
They had a disagreement at the party
and took it home.
Oh, my God!
Do you think they fought
or they're helping someone?
- No, it has already happened...
- No, the way Luan threw...
- Were they really fighting?
- I don't know...
There may be something there,
I don't know, maybe...
They had a disagreement in the bus!
Something happened at the party,
and in the house, Bia was crying.
Bia was crying in the house, man.
There was a disagreement at the party,
in the bus, and in the house.
I wonder if Luan and Murilo's fight
happened now. Like...
- That's for sure, girl!
- But I think they have a grudge
that started last summer. I love drama.
Relationships must have this drama.
- It's no good without drama.
- No!
If none of them cries,
what is it good for?
I just have to say, the next episode
will be, like, something out of control.
- Exactly!
- Girl, call the cab for us?
Girl, I'm gonna call it from my cell,
but I'm taking the glass.
Just don't call the bus.
There's only fighting in buses, guys.
- For God's sake.
- Come, cousin.
Carol, bring the popcorn, kid!
Guys, what a mess!