Guys, did anybody fall?
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
We got here falling
and knocking down everything.
- What's up, guys?
- Buddy, long time no see!
- Hi, guys! I missed you!
- Is everything all right, guys?
What's up, guys? Are you cool?
Jeez. John broke the set,
that's great.
Lexa, turn around, show off that look.
Girls' look.
Jeez!
Man, it's crazy how we always match!
Golden shades, really beautiful.
And Titto, right?
What's up, guys?
How are you?
- Oh, fabulous!
- Very happy!
Guys, today things are gonna get wild!
- Today it's gonna be a mess!
- As usual.
Like every day, always. That's normal.
Yes. Today we'll see
what we've been waiting for to happen.
I want a new party, a new story,
a new intrigue, another couple.
Bia did more things in one night
than in the whole vacation.
She looks like she's free, right?
I don't judge because I'd do the same.
No, you wouldn't, you'd do worse.
No, I imagined she'd hook up
with just one guy,
but she kissed two guys
in just one night. Guys, yummy!
She just hooked up with the other guy
because the guys created those situations.
I don't think so, because
she hooked up with a guy,
then she hit on that guy, you saw?
No, but I give her a round of applause!
She hit on that guy...
She's beautiful, single, free,
independent, why not?
I loved it!
No, I'm gonna call her Bandit Bia.
She's acting more like a thug than I am.
- Girl, I'm like her.
- I don't have the guts to do that.
No, don't say that, Carol.
- At this time, man?
- Carol!
- Look the guy in the eye and say
- You don't look, you say,
"I wanna tell you something."
Then, "Hey, give me your number."
I think now my nickname is gonna be Bia,
because I'm like her.
I saw it, I want it, I can do it.
It was nice because she broke free.
She needed that.
She broke free.
- She built her confidence.
-"She broke free."
She needed to get rid of Luan's energy.
Goodbye, Luan, move on.
Guys, what about that young guy?
Renatinho?
He had sex with Anna the first day.
He got there doing
what he had to do, right?
He was too eager.
Absolutely.
What's that, "He did it on the first day."
How long do you take?
- No, I'm a "right now" person!
- A look, a smile, and then sex.
If I see a guy, and I like him,
we do it the same day.
You never know
if there'll be a second chance.
This is how I see it. If I don't
do it now, when will it be?
I do it, honey.
I act quickly, you know?
But I have to improve the way
I approach the guy.
Last episode, we ended
on that misunderstanding
- between Murilo and Tay.
-"I wanna leave!"
If I were Tay,
I wouldn't go talk to Murilo.
- I'd wait for him.
- There are four episodes left.
I think they're gonna fight
and have sex a lot.
Are you ready? My chocolate milk is.
Should we hit play?
Hit it, hit it hard.
You can cry.
I don't need to tell you
to shut up, you know?
I'll never say, "Nath, shut up", you know?
Oh, Murilo, shut up
Oh, that's because you
wanna play the saint.
I wanna play the saint?
What bothered me the most was
that everything happened
in front of me, you know?
You were throwing yourself at Nathália
the whole time, helping her...
Obviously, that bothered me.
He just did that because he saw
Anna hooking up with another guy.
I don't know if he planned that,
but that's a bad thing to do.
I think so because he said...
Nath was next to Anna.
He was immature in that respect.
Imagine, you're with a guy
and he's hitting on your friend!
- Imagine their bad breath as they talk...
- It's something I never got.
Soap operas, I've worked on nine of them.
Who wakes up and kisses somebody
in the mouth?
When I wake up,
it's like I licked a dog's ass.
Jeez.
You wake up with someone and say,
"Jeez, did you eat a corpse, man?"
Wait, what kind of bad breath
does this person have?
I'm not saying I wake up
with no bad breath, but I brush my teeth
when I wake up
and before going to bed too.
You brush your teeth before going to bed,
you stay there with your mouth shut.
You wake up with bad breath.
I don't have that bad breath.
My mouth is...
Guys, my mouth is very clean,
but I'm picky about smell.
Buddy, sometimes,
morning sex is the best ever.
But you don't have to kiss on the mouth.
Morning sex is the best sex ever.
You're not ready for this conversation.
Morning sex really makes a lot of sense,
it's really good. But no kissing.
But then, Titto, like, you...
Let's assume you're single.
Then you hooked up with a chick
and went to the bedroom,
you had sex and woke up in the morning,
she's on top of you, trying to kiss you...
I'm gonna share with you one move
I've never shared in public.
We want to know if it's your dick.
- I'm kidding!
- The best move is...
I won't advertise the brand, but you take
some chewing gum, chew it. Leave it there,
in the corner of the mouth.
The pieces stay in the filling,
that's disgusting, Titto!
Here, in the corner of your mouth.
You sleep with the gum, the problem is
if the gum sticks on the chick's hair.
You sleep and wake up,
in the morning, you shake it and...
Oh, that's disgusting! No.
Titto, do you see why
I don't like kissing?
Guys, I love kissing at a party,
those great kisses.
I don't feel like kissing
in the morning like I do at parties.
- If I'm involved, I kiss the guy.
- You don't brush your teeth?
Jeez, guys, you stick your mouth
in worse places.
Exactly.
I just peck in the morning.
- No kissing on the mouth.
- Me too.
Cramp in the tongue.
In the morning...
No, they were just talking,
and we talked a lot here. Honestly.
I wonder if they're gonna be friends
or if they're gonna hook up.
What Titto said, they're working
things out... They're talking.
I think he'll say,
"Hey, I'm sorry for everything.
-"Let's move on."
- I think she's gonna test him.
She's not gonna hook up with him right now
and she's gonna watch his behavior...
It seemed, yesterday, he was here
for Nathália. And I was like...
She said, "Since I want to
hook up with Murilo, let's hook up.
"Since Renato wants to hook up with Anna."
I said that to Anna, "Let's hook up..."
- Who said that?
- Tay.
That's what happened.
I didn't get it.
You're whining.
You're a drunk, clueless.
Clueless!
She's getting pissed very easily.
- You were very jealous. You see things.
- Jealous of what?
- Do me a favor? Go talk to a shrink.
- I'm never...
- I've had two abusive relationships...
- You need help too.
I don't need a third...
- Abusive? When was I abusive?
- You weren't?
No, dude!
Murilo, you were the only one
who heard that.
- I was the only one?
- Yes.
She had to explain
what she's talking about.
No, seriously.
If I were Tay and I'm right,
I don't have to explain anything,
he's wrong.
But you are there, in front of each other.
- He's wrong.
- If you seek peace, you explain.
She's wrong because she didn't explain.
But I think she didn't understand
that he misunderstood.
She should have explained
why she said that.
- At this point he won't listen.
- I think she didn't get it.
She's saying this, "You misunderstood."
But she's not saying what it is.
I think... I love Murilo,
but I think he's totally wrong.
I agree!
It was his mistake, he misunderstood that.
Yeah, he totally misunderstood what...
But I think he didn't get that yet, guys.
- She didn't explain.
- Ramon got there...
there's always that friend
who makes things worse.
Oh, guys. I wish they worked things out.
You know what's fucked up, guys?
This. Gossiping.
If you gather everyone involved and say,
"Let's discuss all this!"
Yes, nobody talks,
then you go to the bathroom...
Then Carol tells me,
"Oh, Titto said you're a..."
If we gather and talk, it's over.
That's the thing about Murilo
and Tay's relationship,
- why does he listen to Ramon?
- Everybody was drunk and saw it.
It's like that worthless
Chinese Telephone game, you know?
But I think that, if he were
less defensive, she'd be too.
I agree.
Let's pretend
- we've never met.
- Thank you.
Oh, no, guys!
You see? That's what you get with pride.
That's fucked up
because she likes him a lot.
He likes her a lot... I also think,
the tone of a conversation is not the way
you talk, but the way you listen.
The interpretation changes everything.
Maybe he said something,
she understood differently!
- Go for it.
- Mind the step.
Renatinho had a slight disappointment.
His friend made him work!
He had to work too.
I'm from Rio.
I'm here on vacation. Doing...
"I'm from Rio, dude."
That old saying, "I'm from Rio, dude."
That accent is a killer.
Why are cariocas like that?
They boss around. The...
I love the carioca accent!
- I'm from Rio, dude!
- Are you?
- No, I'm from Bahia.
- Are you from Bahia?
Bahia. Hello, Canavieiras, Una.
Stop, that's enough advertising!
What's the deal with those chicks?
If the manager doesn't see...
Murilo said he can hit on whoever
he wants, but the manager can't see it.
He's just like me when I used to work.
"Don't let the manager see this."
Did you do that?
Imagine what Pabllo did
to keep a low profile at work,
being this tall. How do you do it?
When I used to work in telemarketing,
we spoke to the bitches on the phone...
- Did you hit on them while telemarketing?
- I just answered calls. I'm passive.
How did you answer?
I answered, no!
We were just connected,
we only pressed the button. Well...
Wait, I have a complaint. I'm calling.
- Hello?
- Good morning, Customer Service?
I want to complain about my coffee
on this show.
Is your coffee an espresso,
a latte or just black?
- Black, please.
- I'll connect you management, press five.
Let me tell you. What a beautiful voice,
do you only work there?
I just work here,
you know how it is, right?
I'm shocked!
The call is to talk about coffee
and ends up giving you milk,
I'm sorry, bad joke, but what happened,
Pabllo? Is that how you talked to people?
Obviously. Guys, I indulged my fantasy
of being at telemarketer.
The guy hangs up the phone with a boner.
I had to say my name, Pabllo,
I had to say the company name,
a credit card company.
Like this, "Good morning, Amazon Prime.
Pabllo. How can I help you?"
What was the most unusual thing
that happened in one of those calls?
A man wanted to know my address
to send me a gift.
And did he send it?
- I never got anything!
- But have you ever got somebody's number?
I couldn't because we...
They recorded the calls. I've been caught
a lot of times talking bullshit.
I'm not sorry!
Was there, like, a call about a complaint
and you had phone sex, like this?
You can't because there's
a lot of things, right? So...
A booth? Did you talk sexy
like this? Like you did?
I always talk like this, that's my tone.
- No, like...
- Always!
- I'm shocked.
- I'd love to be answered by you.
Yeah, you can't complain.
You call pissed...
Like people from Minas Gerais. They say,
"Go fuck yourself," you just go, "I go."
I swear to God, people from Minas Gerais
have a soft accent.
But the accent from Rio
is like a porn movie accent, right?
Oh, girl. The accent from Rio
and from the Northeast.
Just me. I'm new here, just me.
Ramon is approaching like that, look.
- His approach. Look at his face!
- Ramon really is from Niterói, man.
Ramon doesn't even keep
a low profile, bro.
Did you see his look? He did this.
It's like John when he gets here
and looks at me. Right, John?
Ramon's hooking up with everybody.
He's keeping a high profile!
He's drawing a lot of attention.
The three of them
want that girl very much.
Now, Murilo, I wonder if he...
- Oh, fuck!
- Where do I know you from?
Oh, bullshit! What a bad pick-up line.
"From some beach."
Yeah. In Praia da Daniela.
He pulled a fast one on his friend!
No, man. He met her at that first party.
He was trying to hook up with her
and wasn't able to.
He was stalling her and didn't...
Guys, what a hot girl, help!
Man, what a bad pick-up line!
No, he's really met her!
- Really?
- Yeah.
You realized he pulled
a fast one on his friend, right?
Oh, in the land of the eyes,
the blind man is king.
Are you okay, buddy?
Constant dripping wears away a stone!
Girl, all good? How are you?
Let me tell you.
I've just got here...
I told you, bitch!
A pussy was needed.
She's that friend she called yesterday.
She's coming to Floripa.
Oh, she's that friend who said,
"I'm coming tomorrow", right?
I said that's my dream,
doing that someday.
That call that Lexa wants
to make for a moment.
I wanted to make for a moment.
I'm gonna be careful with what I say now.
Renato selected...
That's it!
Oh, man!
The selection here is...
- You're done, baby.
- That's right!
It's possible to hook up.
- Don't do this, no.
- I'll take it.
No, you take it, not me.
- You'll take it.
- No!
I don't want it, bro.
- Ramonzinho.
- I don't want it.
But he's right too.
He doesn't fall for anybody.
Take it, let's take it.
- Did you see the size of my belly?
- I'll talk to you later.
- What?
- Where did you go?
That's all I needed.
No, hit pause.
I think he got into trouble by himself,
like John said before.
I think he got into trouble by himself
when he put his hand on his head.
When somebody does that,
- it's because they fucked up.
- He's already taking the blame, right?
He took the girl home, but didn't want it,
Murilo made him do that, he was forced.
Then he took her. And he went
to explain the situation to the chick...
I think he made a mistake in the morning,
at the bad breath moment,
when he expressed his feelings...
Then he...
Then he took the opportunity to hook up
with a girl and thought no one would know.
No problem with hooking up
with that girl over there.
But the boys took those chicks
to the house, and he had to deal with it.
I think that if he wanted
to avoid that situation,
he could've been honest with the chick
he took home, saying he had a girl...
- in the house and...
- But, Jerry... They apologized and...
..."I'm not gonna hook up with you,
but you can come."
That was his mistake.
I can't take those boys, guys.
Looks like...
They're all the same. They don't talk,
they just do it, they hook up and...
But, Carol, the way Anna reacted,
do you think she's fine or she's hurt?
She's hurt and...
we go back to that topic you were talking,
"Oh, if it were some outsider,
"Anna wouldn't get upset." She would.
Outsider or not.
Guys, I think Anna's not upset because...
I think she doesn't even know
Renatinho hooked up with somebody.
Oh, she was the first to notice when she
got in the house. She did this, look.
But I think she got upset because
Murilo and Tay had fought earlier, so,
there shouldn't be so many girls there.
It's about respect in the house.
Yeah, I agree with John too.
Pabllo said it.
Murilo did that because he wants
to watch it all burn down.
You know that kind of person that's like
your dog, at home, when it makes a mess?
That's Renatinho, man!
I think he's overreacting, you know?
Renatinho is raising
the "I fucked up" sign. He really is.
All I wanted was she hooked up
with that guy, you know?
But are you cool, dude?
Are you okay?
Do you fall for that bullshit
Renatinho is saying?
"I'm here to be free" and he's in pain?
He's already in pain, guys, come on!
He's deceiving himself.
- He's deceiving himself.
- His ego's hurt.
Anna... I think Anna didn't fall for him.
She got upset with that situation,
that's different.
She said, "Doesn't he just want
to have sex? So, I'll have sex at home."
Remember that thing I told you?
"Bro, don't fall for this", you know?
Don't fall in love, don't get emotional...
"Don't get emotional." That's it.
Miss Emotional got crazy.
Miss Emotional.
It's like me,
giving advice I don't follow.
- It's me telling everything I do.
- Wait, did you see? Murilo,
"Don't get emotional, don't fall in love."
Just a little take of Tay with other guys.
You can imagine what's coming.
I have friends who arrive at a party,
kiss and leave.
- But I'd rather that conversation...
- What do you mean?
Guys, look. I'm gonna be honest.
That depends on the time.
- Right? Doesn't it depend on the time?
- People talking.
I think talking is a phony thing.
Girl, it depends on the time.
Man... I lost track of men I had sex with
and I don't even know their names.
What do you mean, a phony thing?
I think it's all phony. People ask,
"Where are you from?"
They won't remember anything!
The person's not interested,
only wants to have sex.
Night-outs have a schedule.
At the beginning, you're patient...
I see the guy walking, crossing the place
and kissing, like, 4:00 in the morning?
My friends don't even ask
names, places, times.
I like to talk. But, for example,
I've met you at a party,
"Let's set a date
for us to go out and talk?"
Oh, come on! Finally, hypocrisy. No.
You go get laid?
No, it's not about getting laid,
I wanna kiss, dance...
I wanna...
But where are you gonna talk?
Pabllo, you're at a party.
Lexa, not now, but...
Everybody's at a party, everybody's free.
Hypothetically speaking, you're at a party
and a hot guy comes, a hot chick comes.
- Then you hook up, 4:00 in the morning.
- Let's play this out?
But I'm the woman.
Why are you the woman?
You can't get too close, here, look.
1:00 in the morning.
I'm the DJ.
Guys, we're playing this out!
Go, then I'm the MC, go.
Midnight.
What's up, babe? How are you?
Are you from around here?
- Yes. What's your name?
- Fernando.
Nice to meet you.
- Are you free today, at this party?
- With friends.
- But are you free for me?
- You're fast!
Get over here, come here.
- Midnight.
- Midnight. You do all this?
I don't play hard to get.
3:00 in the morning.
Well, are you free?
I'm fine, what about you?
- Let's do it?
- Yes!
At 5:00!
Just here, look.
- Like this?
- That's it!
We've just played that out. Thanks, DJ.
Thanks MC Carol from Niterói, that's it.
Cheers, fuck!
It's rad. It's just not centered,
but it's good.
Renatinho is kissing... is it Anna?
It's another one, Renatinho...
Oh, guys, that's it.
That's it, he's a player. Look at Anna.
That one is a thug, he fell in love.
Anna, no!
Anna!
She was joking, right?
She's joking!
She's joking,
but she wants to mark her territory.
- Let's beat her up!
- My love, look...
Guys, I'm like Anna 101 percent.
- I'm like Nath on that vacation.
- I'm Anna.
Good vibes, kissing everybody...
Bro, Renatinho is hitting
on another woman.
Look at Renatinho.
But Renatinho gets prettier every minute.
Renatinho is womanizing,
he's very loose. Look.
Hit pause!
Pause, Carol.
When you were free, were you
like that? You got to the place,
you didn't wait for people to get
in the mood, you didn't notice anything...
- Were you like that?
- Who? Me? No.
I gotta tell you,
I was married all my life, man.
I was a father when I was 16...
But you had to have
some history to be a father.
Answer, Titto.
I wasn't ugly, I was poor, man.
Titto's puberty was sad.
We are the ones
who are gonna explore the whole house.
Are you crazy?
Fuck, Renatinho is crazy, man.
Renatinho is like Carol
from Wild and Free: Florianópolis.
Now he's gonna be wrong
if he doesn't fulfill that. Got it?
She even pretended
she was crying, did you see?
Renatinho is really wasted.
Really wasted.
Everybody's at the same pace,
he's much faster.
Dude!
And Anna got closer to take a look again.
He said, "He looks like me."
Jeez.
Renatinho became Renatão.
- Triple kiss!
- What's that?
Bro, she's upset!
Renatinho became Renatão.
He's the one who's hooking up the most!
But, bro, go, let's see.
I sent her the sex...
Is it Anna?
- It's Anna. The dogs. What's that, guys?
- I'm shocked!
She nails it, you see? She does her thing.
Honey, Beyoncé is like this, shocked.
But I couldn't feel anything
seeing Murilo hooking up with others.
The love's over, guys?
I don't like him anymore. You know?
She whispered, "I couldn't feel anything.
I think I don't like him anymore."
This is good, because she's letting
that feeling go away.
"I think", to me,
is something very... I don't know.
She's not sure, right?
She's in that in-between.
Everything Murilo did in this episode,
taking those girls home,
he did to affect Tay.
If that's not working anymore,
if Tay doesn't care anymore,
Murilo is gonna suffer a lot.
She doesn't mean that, right?
She's incredibly beautiful,
she can hook up with anyone she wants.
But she decided to stay cool
and he went wild.
She said, "I'm in mourning,
when this is over, things will get ugly."
Maybe she didn't hook up with anybody
so she has a reason to nail it in the end.
"Baby, do you remember the summer
when you hooked up with everybody?"
Hit play, so we see
what's gonna happen, go.
This could be pregnancy?
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Fuck, bro!
- Oh my God, no, no!
- I had some very exciting sex, brother.
- The guy was very crazy!
- They're nitpicking, right, man?
I've never seen this
in any other reality show.