Let's go!
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
Everybody was dancing back there...
I'll just clap.
Hey... MC is missing.
Listen to my English!
You missed class at CCAA
Get away
How are you, guys?
We're great!
Great!
What is it? A drunk Colombian woman?
Why is everybody speaking Spanish?
Because my mood today's a Latin girl.
- What?
- I'm a Latin girl today.
A Latin girl?
Kisses to all
Wild and Free: Florianópolis fans
from Latin America,
we love you a lot. Kisses!
Go!
Everybody's anxious to see what's going on
in this episode?
Pregnancy, lots of stuff!
- To me, pregnancy is...
- Guys!
There's this possible pregnancy!
Remember that Renatinho arrived,
hooked up with everybody,
hooked up with Anna.
Will this couple happen?
They won't be a couple,
they'll make out a lot.
I think so too.
Anna was the last one I saw him with.
I think Anna and Renatinho
learned they're free,
so they're a free couple.
And they ended up having sex.
Oh, that's true!
Sex!
He ended up with Anna, true!
He ended up with Anna.
What about Murilo and Tay?
Do you think it's really over?
What do you think?
I told you they learned
they have to be friends because
when they see
each other with others they get...
I think as a couple they are good friends.
That's right, Titto.
Now she's detached.
Guys, from the beginning
to the middle of that vacation...
there were a lot of fights.
They need to be friends now.
They don't work well together nor apart.
In my opinion, that couple,
especially Tay, can't take it anymore.
- Yeah.
- She's tired.
But Murilo's trying something.
- So, are you ready?
Are you ready?
Yes!
We are ready!
I have the remote!
Delicious!
Come, Christian Grey!
Let's go!
I don't like your sickness, girl.
I don't understand either.
Do you think you could be pregnant?
Fuck!
Oh, my God! No!
Girl, we were afraid of Tay and Murilo...
- Guys, is it Luan's?
- Who would it be?
She only had sex with him.
Yes!
Luan left but he is still there.
But my rhythm method...
My rhythm method says it's Luan's.
Fuck, it's a child,
in a relationship that doesn't exist!
Give the child to the dad.
In Floripa!
Give it to the dad!
I'd do it!
A baby in the belly? It's very creepy.
That's crazy, man.
I'd be very nervous,
I'd say, "Guys, cut. Camera, cut."
Lexa? Have you ever been through this?
Sure, guys!
I've never had sex.
- Being in doubt?
- The holy virgin is talking.
I've been with Guimê for five years,
I had a few scares.
And I don't know how to explain.
What did you feel?
- What did you feel?
- I felt...
What happened was, look...
It scared me a lot.
- You were scared to death.
- Nothing happened. Nothing.
And you, Carol?
My test was negative, just so you know.
So, guys, I use condom, you know?
But I once had some really crazy sex, bro.
What?
He was very crazy. When I realized
he wasn't wearing a condom,
I said, "What's this?
Why did you do this?" But anyway...
I can't, Carol... Carol, I can't.
- Seriously, girl.
- How was it?
- The sex?
- No, I know how sex works...
How was the feeling after,
thinking you were pregnant?
Man, it was awful.
I called my friend Pataxó.
Hi, Pataxó.
Is he Bumba's friend?
He's indigenous.
No, nobody likes Bumba.
- He steals chocolate, but...
- Just you...
Then...
There's "Bumba meu Boi",
hers is "Bumba meu boy".
"Bumba meu boy".
Then, it happened...
I was desperate,
called my friend and said,
"Pataxó, I think
you're gonna be an uncle."
Then I asked my friend
to buy the test secretly.
I took the test
and I wasn't pregnant, thank God.
Everything's cool.
- And the dad?
- Who cares about a poor dad.
But if he were...
If he were rich...
it'd be totally different!
Good afternoon. Hi.
I'd like a pregnancy test, please.
- Guys, they're making me nervous.
- I'm uptight.
Bro, she's sweating.
I've never seen this in any other reality!
I've never seen this. That's bizarre!
I'll take the front seat.
Damn!
No way.
- I don't see a board.
- It's inside.
Let's take a look.
Do you have a big floaty?
We had arranged...
Oh, not the flamingo!
What a wonderful floaty!
- Girl, everybody fits in it.
- Everybody!
I'd rather they do that
than fighting, so that's great.
Put it on the high seas.
If God made it, we can carry it!
Bro, imagine people driving by,
seeing that and saying, "Fuck,
"I think there's a mutant in town..."
That's unbelievable!
This scene is awesome!
Look at the traffic jam they're causing!
There's a fucking flamingo!
I loved it!
Let's not judge them!
Let's go!
Life's crazy, some of them
are having fun in the jam
and others are solving big issues.
Her life might change after that.
They don't know about it.
I'm not saying her friends
didn't feel sympathy for her,
I'm saying people's lives are different.
They are having fun and she's worried!
- Not pregnant.
- Phew, amen!
- Amen!
- I was scared like that.
- So was I.
That chick has just lifted a huge weight
off her shoulders, man.
- Exactly.
- Bia!
That's cool, she had a heavy burden.
Heavy like...
the Corcovado in Rio de Janeiro, you know?
I felt that way when I checked my grade
to see if I had passed a test at school.
The only time I felt that way.
No! It was when I said,
"John, your nudes leaked in three groups."
"What, buddy? What happened?"
John's nudes
have been leaked, that's true.
- Just once.
- But it leaked.
Now people are gonna google it
and type "John's nudes" to see it!
Have you ever imagined
having sex on that flamingo?
When I moved in to São Paulo, I spent
one week sleeping on an air mattress.
Having sex on an air mattress is bad,
I'm six feet and four inches tall
and my body, like a Miss...
- What did Nath say?
-"Miss-Chievous."
Imagine my heavy body
on a floaty on the water!
What about you, Titto?
You and the chick are on the floaty.
Would you have sex or not?
- Come on, Jerry!
- Say it, Titto.
Answer the question!
I don't compromise myself.
I would!
Am I gonna say I wouldn't?
I wouldn't!
I'd, at least, play a little.
Of course. If that carries ten people,
imagine this little body?
- I have to talk to Anna.
- About?
There are some things that make me...
- Like?
- She wants...
to do things in her own time, you know?
She does things in her own time.
He's acting like he was
the victim, my love.
At the bar, working,
he hooked up with a girl before her!
I wanna have fun, you know?
No, she hooked up before him.
At the party.
But he talked about Nath too.
Oh, yeah, everybody's single.
If something happens after this.
Ramon isn't
the best person to give advice.
He just makes mistakes.
He really isn't the best one.
He was the calmest guy.
But Ramon harmed Murilo
and Tay's relationship indirectly.
It's very difficult to understand you.
- Why?
- Just because.
Sometimes you show some things,
then all of a sudden, you change.
Sometimes, I think you wanna be with me.
All of a sudden, you don't.
It's a little difficult.
He's opening up.
- I like that.
- He's opening up.
I liked it.
Sometimes, you don't know
what you're saying when you're wasted.
You just say it!
No, Mu, what happened there...
- You freaked out.
- No, I didn't.
Stop it!
He doesn't get it yet, seriously.
He looks like my connection, slow.
Let me tell you something,
that depends on Tay now,
if she comes clean...
I like that talk.
But he's still talking
- and blaming her.
- I like the talk. He's talking calmly,
- opening up...
- If he were drunk...
I feel Tay is unhappy about that talk.
She didn't express herself.
She barely reacted.
I think she has his vibe.
She has the vibe...
- of just listening.
- Yes.
- She's tired.
- She knows she's right.
Deep down, a woman knows she's right.
That's it!
Thank God.
Hey, John!
I'd hook up with him!
Girl, and you?
Sure!
Fuck, bro!
Get a grip!
What's up?
How are you, bro?
Fuck, bro!
And you, Carol?
Girl, I didn't like one thing.
- What?
- His casual shoes.
Those masculine casual shoes?
Who would notice casual shoes?
I would!
Carol didn't even see he had legs...
No, buddy, he's super straight.
I noticed...
He looks like he's been raised
by his grandmother, you know?
I'd hook up with him because...
I think he studied engineering in college.
Look, Andrei!
Her guy!
Do you think Nath
will continue to hook up with him?
- Dude, I think so.
- Me too.
She enjoyed that guy's vibe!
Nath's barely making out,
when she does, she does it with him.
I think he was cute going there.
Me too.
I think she'll begin to make out with him
and fight because of him.
If I were a waitress like that,
I'd love to see my guy
watching me working, man.
I think they're in a mature relationship,
Murilo and Tay.
I mean, too mature.
She invited him.
He did like those gossipers.
Anna wants to take a guy home,
she'll perform a fatality in Renatinho.
Murilo wasn't expecting it.
The best scene is Murilo's,
the scenic Murilo.
Murilo's like my gossiping friends.
It's Renato... Is it that girl?
How's the joke?
Fuck, Tay. Listen!
Oh, girl, I won't listen, girl.
It hurts, I know.
"It hurts, I know."
And Murilo is by her side!
Meaning, she likes him!
I thought it was crazy,
because I thought she was totally free,
but... she's not!
I don't think she likes Renatinho.
Come on!
She's crying because...
I think she invented
an imaginary rule in her head,
and he crossed this line!
You don't believe that!
No, it's difficult for "Dr." John Drops.
Guys, it's obvious, she's upset.
She's hurt, but I thought she was free.
I agree.
Hearing your ex having sex like this...
must be frustrating!
I think she's upset because of her "F.B.",
not because of him!
- What's "F.B."?
- Fuck buddy.
It's...
- John's theory!
- I agree!
She had a permanent "F.B." in the house...
- I agree.
- ...but outside they
could do whatever they wanted.
But he took the girl home.
And she's hurt.
She doesn't like the guy, just his dick!
- What?
- She doesn't like the guy!
- She just likes his dick!
That's it! She likes fucking him!
If she could detach his dick,
she'd take it?
Exactly!
Before hitting play, I wanna hear
somebody who almost said nothing.
- What?
- What do you think
about this situation?
If I were in her shoes,
I would handle it differently.
I'd just say, "I don't care."
I would let the guy fuck
and I'd be cool.
Or I'd do like Anna, hook up
and leave, but I think I would stay.
I wonder if we are too detached.
Oh, girl, I don't believe those things,
that, "We're all detached."
- Sometimes here, I pretend I am...
- You are!
...but deep inside, I also am.
You can't be totally detached, man.
Pabllo is the most detached person
I've ever met. For real!
I'm gonna hit play!
- Let's go!
- Play!
Someone wants to use it. Nath!
Turn around now.
- Look. She's testing.
- Fuck!
That's not possible.
Look at this, Ramon.
What about that woman? Hell yeah.
Wonderful.
"Look at this, Ramon"?
Go have sex, sister.
Wait! Rewind it!
She's showing it to Ramon!
She's making sexual advances
on Ramon! Is it him there?
- It's Renatinho. Ramon?
- Yeah!
And Renatinho with...
It's Ramon!
Fuck, it's Ramon, man.
But I think it's very clear to Ramon.
That is...
#YOULOSTRAMON
And Ramon's like that...
That's resilience, man.
Vanessinha is awesome.
Fuck, Ramon's taking pictures!
He took the picture!
- Guys, what's the problem?
- He was cool.
Yes, for God's sake!
Andrei!
Hey, man, what a shame.
Everybody got in the bedroom?
Where are yesterday's pictures?
Put them here.
I threw our picture away.
Fuck!
Throw these away too!
Why?
Throw them away!
Who threw it away?
Murilo's looking for trouble,
he wants to fight.
They're nitpicking, huh, man?
What an angry girl.
Why did she do that?
Because she's tired, girl. Tay's tired!
But she took the bait.
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not.
I was talking to you, and you...
I was really quiet. I don't know.
I don't know!
Guys, they're attracted to each other.
She knows she can't demand
anything from him.
I like his mouth.
- That's a trigger warning!
- Yes!
- I'm here looking at his mouth.
- I'm serious.
- Me too!
- I get you. I understand you.
I'm serious!
I want him!
That's not worth it, you know?
I made a mistake.
She's very sensible.
I love Anna!
She gets straight to the point.
She's very honest.
Anna's here, look.
Anna's way too evolved,
and Rena... Can I say it?
She admitted that it bothers her, girl.
It's an honest relationship,
and he talked to her.
They are starting to do this now.
He said, "We can start talking
what's allowed and what's not allowed."
He said it now!
- Let's establish something.
- They've always been honest.
They didn't get drunk before!
They're cool, talking.
That's the honest couple.
The most evolved couple there!
That's what I was gonna say. I think.
I agree!
The most evolved couple.
I think that's a reflection
of other couples.
They see things and wanna be different.
We'll want to kiss others.
We won't avoid this.
Like it or not!
I'm sorry for us!
- That's it!
- Fuck!
Anna nailed it in this season!
She nailed it big time.
What am I gonna do? There's no way.
- That's it!
- Honest talk.
Honest talk!
Jeez, I would fuck him,
you see, my sister?
Everything's all right.
What do you think?
I give it up for her!
I give him too, a lot of things.
- Wonderful!
- What about you, Carol?
Why, didn't you like it?
She said they should mind their business.
He laughed.
When the dick's good,
there's nowhere to run.
He was just being charming, Carol.
Nobody, absolutely nobody.
Carol, bro.
You know what's worse?
I feel like cuddling her.
I believe Carol's fanfics.
It took me a while to love Anna
because of Carol.
Guys!
Oh, my makeup!
Guys, Ray and my gay friend are here.
Your gay friend!
I missed a gay friend there!
I missed a gay friend.
They needed a gay friend there.
I agree!
Watch out, Matheus hits on them.
Now we're talking, Amazon.
- I loved it!
- We'll see a triple kiss.
I love it!
Let's see the gay friend,
let's see him nailing it.
I wanna see the gay!
The gay!
I'm counting on him!
You go, girl, nail it!
You know, right?
- I'm already loving the gay guy!
- I loved him!
I love gays who do that.
Matheus, love you, girl.
You're slaying it.
We fuck for free. Line up and come,
one at a time, baby.
I love this gay!
"Line up and come, one at a time."
I love that gay.
Next time, it's gonna be me.
I loved him!
Line up and come, one at a time
I love him!
Gays are always there for you, right?
Interacting with girls,
saying, "Man, that guy!"
We know how to choose, girl!
Girl, I loved it!
Don't do what they say!
Don't drink it, you'll die!
You'll die!
They're dangerous.
Nath's already gotten a guy, my love.
But she was stuck to Andrei, wasn't she?
I think she wasn't that stuck, right?
Andrei's here, where's Nath?
Andrei's here!
I love that partnership!
Andrei's here.
Oh, my God!
I love that partnership!
I think there's gonna be a mess!
- You think?
- Yes!
I'm sure!
Jeez!
Look at Anna pretending
she didn't know he was there!
Nath's awesome.
She hooked up with that guy.
Notice the difference
of a girl in a situation...
Look. Hit pause.
A girl in the same situation as Renatinho.
Renatinho was desperate.
Nath didn't give a shit, she hugged...
No, you can notice
the tension in her eyes.
Renatinho was in danger.
Renatinho would've shit his pants!
Nath talked!
She talked!
She's tense, I could see that.
She's tense, but she's not
as shocked as Renatinho.
It's because she is...
- already wasted.
- She hung in there!
The muse of this season,
this vacation, is Nath.
Nath is from Goiânia.
She's a straightforward woman.
There's no bullshit with her.
It's just us.
Hit pause, please!
Some random guy showed up,
"It's just us."
I know, no... It's all or nothing.
You know that party
where everybody hooks up with each other,
like, "Lexa, it's just us, let's do it?"
I'm like this.
Tay kissed the guy.
I applaud Nath with my feet,
laid down, doing somersaults.
I think Nath was fucking awesome.
Nath, you named this episode, I'm shocked!
Queen of Goiânia.
Tay also was free there.
I think, for her,
it's over for her and Murilo.
- For quite a while.
- I don't think so.
- I think so.
- I think it's over...
It's over and she got it.
Anna liked her guy too.
Guys, Anna is making out.
Will she take that guy home?
Anna's on the loose!
Anna has poetic license.
Tay too, because she and Murilo said,
"Pretend I don't know you, it's over,
that's it!"
That's what I think.
I think the girls will take many guys home
and the boys are gonna be insecure...
We're gonna see
what their reactions will be.
- Say it, Carol.
- My opinion.
It's my opinion.
When I am hooking up with a lot of guys,
actually, I'm feeling sad.
No!
And I'm doing this because...
To make it up for the need inside you.
Exactly. In the end...
I feel worse!
Sad, but horny.
For example, I hooked up
with three guys in 48 hours.
What about Jerry? How many girls?
I think Tay,
I think Tay doesn't want anybody,
doesn't like anybody,
she wants to take revenge
on something that made her sad.
I think she's gonna end up with Murilo.
I stand for that couple...
I can't believe she's taking revenge.
If she were taking revenge,
she'd kiss a guy at another party
in front of Murilo.
This is what we do!
You sum up. I wanna know
your overview, Carol.
You don't need to take revenge
directly on a person.
- She explained that!
- Could be indirectly.
But the girls would never tell Murilo.
Sometimes we think that if we hook up
with 30 guys, we'll forget that one!
What about when you just wanna have sex?
I don't go to parties!
- Where do you go?
- I make a phone call!
But you go out to pick up guys!
I don't go to parties to pick up guys!
- I go out late at night...
- Late?
What time do you pick up girls?
Carol, tell me, it's late at night,
I'm very horny,
what do I do to pick up guys?
To pick up guys...
I take a shower
and wear a lot of Prada to fuck.
- Wonderful!
-"I wear a lot of Prada to fuck."
I loved it!
Are you anxious to know
what's gonna happen?
I'm almost dying here!
I'm very anxious. I think Tay's sad.
- No!
- Yeah, right!
Kissing a lot of men.
And she'll look for Murilo
because she loves him and he loves her!
Here, to Murilo and Tay.
What do you think?
I think she's fine.
I believe she can score three points.
- You wish you were her, right?
- Sure!
But if later she wants Murilo, no problem!
No problem!
Hit play!
Let's see it!
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
You don't know what will happen...
What's that, Murilo?
Oh, my God!
Go, naughty girl
I'm a very big girl!
Hi...
Where's her chocolate milk?