Guys, did anybody stumble?
Oh, girls!
We arrived stumbling
and knocking over everything.
What's up, guys?
Hi, guys!
- I missed you!
- How are you, Lexa?
Are you okay?
What's up, guys?
How are you?
Fabulous!
Guys, today things are gonna get wild!
Really wild!
Today it's gonna be ma real mess!
Like every other day!
Exactly!
Yes. Today we'll get to see
what we've been waiting for, you know?
I'm very anxious.
I want a new party, story,
intrigue, another couple...
Bia did more things in one night
than in the whole vacation.
Looks like she's free, right?
Guys, I'm not judging
because I'd do the same.
- No, you wouldn't, you'd do worse.
- Guys...
I imagined she'd hook up
with just one guy,
but she kissed two guys
in just one night. Guys, yummy!
She's beautiful, single,
free, independent, why not?
Why not?
I loved it!
I'm gonna call her Bandit Bia.
Girl, I'm like her.
I don't have the guts to do that.
No, Carol, don't say that.
Titto, not like that.
Look the guy in the eye...
You don't look him straight in the eye,
but you come and say...
"Hey, give me your number."
That's what you do!
This is very good, guys. Help.
My nickname is gonna be Bia, I'm like her.
I saw it, I want it, I can do it.
It was nice because she broke free.
She needed that,
she broke free.
She built her confidence.
"She broke free."
She needed to get rid
of Luan's energy, baby.
Goodbye, Luan. Time to move on.
Guys, what about
that young guy? Renatinho?
He had sex with Anna the first day.
Yummy.
And he got there doing
what he had to do, right?
I think he was too eager.
Are you ready? My chocolate milk is.
Should we hit play?
Let's go!
Hit it, hit it hard.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
Whoever has feelings, cries.
Whoever doesn't have them, doesn't cry.
It's not about being tough.
Nobody was trying to act tough.
I'm getting this off my chest
because of you.
You don't know.
The reason I'm crying is you.
Why? Tell me.
Do you know what happened?
Shut up!
You think I don't know?
I don't need to tell you
to shut up, you know?
- I'll never say...
- Murilo, shut up.
..."Nath, shut up."
I'll never say that!
Because you wanna play the saint!
I wanna play the saint?
Like Luan says.
Play the saint? Me, bro?
Here's what happened.
Renato told me, "The first chick
-"who caught my attention was Nath."
- To me too.
Then Murilo came and asked
what was going on, and I said, "Mu,
"Renatinho wants
to hook up with Nathália."
And he said, "I know. Would you do it?"
I said, "I would. Tomorrow is a new day."
Was that the reason?
Then things got ugly.
Renato came to me and Bia and said,
"The first chick I saw was Nath."
No, hey...
Would you hook up with him?
Would you?
Not today, but tomorrow...
That's it, buddy.
He didn't understand the situation.
Those girls play dumb.
Those girls play dumb, buddy.
That's fucked up, bro. I'm starting
to understand this now, you know?
It was my first night out, I can't come
to a conclusion of something that...
You know?
Soon you'll get it.
Yes, I know. Absolutely.
Give it time.
Just wake up.
Let's talk about what we
were gonna talk about yesterday.
What do you wanna talk about?
You said you wanted to talk.
No, you apologized, I said,
"We'll talk tomorrow."
You're sorry for what?
For yesterday, you know?
I felt like doing whatever I wanted.
Just like us...
If you wanted to hook up with anybody,
like the guy you were talking to, yesterday,
that's no big deal for me, you know?
We talked about this.
You're not gonna spend
a lot of time here, obviously,
so maybe, it wouldn't bother me as much
if it weren't a girl from here.
Nath is a good friend.
And what bothered me the most was...
I don't know...
but everything happened in front of me.
You were throwing yourself at Nathália...
helping her, and I don't know.
Obviously, that bothered me!
I didn't react badly,
I just kept to myself.
You know?
But that bothered me because
she's my friend,
and you were throwing yourself at her.
You were very worried, like...
No, bro, like, that was not...
because of this, you know?
Bro, something, like...
I know, you were worried about her.
Anyway, I'll get up and put on my bikini,
or else I'll stay in bed
and sleep all day.
Yeah. So, we're good?
One hundred percent good?
I swear.
You swear?
I'm good.
Andiamo.
We're in this together, dude.
You can count on me for these things.
God bless you, bro.
You too.
I need...
Say hello to...
Bye. Kisses.
If I forget anything...
- give it to Renato.
- Thanks for coming.
No problem.
Guys, I got an audio message.
- Wanna hear it?
- Sure.
Girl...
Mu! I got an audio message, come here.
What's up, guys? How are you?
Today, the boys are gonna work at the bar.
I heard Luan left,
and we're gonna reinforce the team
to help Ramon and Murilo.
That's it. I'm waiting for you here.
See you.
Come with us, bro.
You've got nothing to do, go with them.
If I'm supposed to go and help...
Did you talk to Murilo?
It's because
I was bothered by something that happened.
When he hit on you?
When you said you'd hook up with Renato,
he said, like...
"I'd hook up with Anna big time."
- I don't want him drunk.
- You guys were drunk...
Using me to make mischief.
I didn't say that about Renato.
Did Renato talk to you?
He did. I still think the same way,
I told him.
I don't care if he wants other girls.
Sure.
Yesterday, I felt... Like, I told him,
I said, "Man,
"let's stay together,
"but if I feel like it,
hooking up with other people."
We're here to have fun.
He didn't come here to stay with me.
He left his house, he lives close to me,
to stay with me here.
Right, there's still Rio.
I said, "We're here to have fun."
If he had hooked up with 15 girls, fine.
The problem was...
You're my friend, you know?
I said, "Man, I just wish
you had told me."
Still, "I don't know if she wants it."
But if she wants, she'll do it.
Got it?
I bet you'd be upset if Ramon
- hit on me.
- Sure, I told him that.
And I'll tell you later.
I say, "Anna didn't hook up
because she didn't want to."
I thought you'd say, "Go, Nathália!"
I just wanted to be informed, you know?
It seemed, yesterday
he was here for Nathália.
Girl, he'd just fucked me.
She said,
"Let's hook up, me and you,
"Renato wants to hook up with Anna,
let's hook up..."
And I told Anna,
"Since Tay wants Renato,
"let's hook up." Like this.
Who said it?
Tay.
That's what happened.
I didn't get it.
Did I hit on you?
I came to you and said...
When I said this, I said it to your face.
You wanted Anna?
No, let me tell you. I said...
That you wanted Anna?
Did you tell me that?
No, I didn't tell you...
He said, "Didn't you tell me
you'd hook up with Renato?"
I was embarrassed.
You told her this.
Just like you, kid.
I didn't want to hook up with Renato,
you were wasted...
You were wasted
and you heard something, you know?
You couldn't interpret what I said.
You should've asked me,
"Did you really say that?"
I asked you!
You didn't ask me!
You know?
It was about Nathália!
You asked me...
You're whining.
It's not whining. You're a drunk,
totally clueless!
Clueless?
You were jealous!
You imagined things!
Do me a favor? Go talk to a shrink!
No...
I'm not jealous...
- You need help, babe.
- Abusive!
When was I abusive?
Oh, you weren't?
Only you heard that.
- Only me?
- Yes.
Okay.
There's no me and you.
Just give me my cap.
Okay, here.
Here, take your little cap.
Your stuff...
Let's pretend we don't know each other.
- Thank you.
- Fine?
Jeez, totally. I'm so grateful.
No, not grateful.
Let's go, people! Let's work!
I wanna work on a day like this.
The energy here is not so good.
Let's go to the beach after eating?
Let's bathe in the sea to purify?
That's all I need!
Let's go?
Talk to us.
I definitely want to.
I'm gonna put this there.
Let's go, girls?
Look at his style.
- Hey, boss?
- What's up, boys?
Hey, bro.
- I'm great. What about you?
- Are you cool?
- Nice to meet you.
- New blood.
Let me introduce you,
this is Renato, my friend from Rio.
- Cool.
- I brought him to help out.
If you need someone to help out...
He's a little short...
but he knows how to
get things done!
If you need someone, he's available.
It's up to you.
We'll settle the rate at the end.
You can start.
Great!
Welcome!
Ramon, Murilo, you know how the bar works,
you know people are waiting
to set up things.
So, let's put on the uniform!
Let's go!
Cool, it's being served.
What's up, man? Are you okay?
Let's test Renatão?
You bring the order
of those ten people there.
- Okay?
- Cool.
If you drop it, it'll cost you your pay.
Save the tray.
Don't fucking drop it.
Watch your step. Go slowly, dude.
I'm gonna run. Show some respect.
He'll fuck up.
Where are you from? Paraná?
- I see. What about you?
- And you?
I'm from Rio. I'm here on vacation.
Doing...
Vacation...
- He's serious.
- You're making fun of me.
I'm working, and you're making fun
of my accent, man?
I'll be back with your drinks.
Thank you!
What's the deal with those chicks?
Can I really hit on...
So...
You can do whatever you want.
You know?
Don't let the manager see...
What's up, Rafa? Is everything okay?
Give her some ice.
Rafaela, Murilo.
What's up, Rafa? How are you?
I've already seen you somewhere.
I think I've seen you too.
Were you at... What's the name...
Where did we go yesterday, bro?
There, we were at Rooftop.
Oh, Art's is cool too, it's downtown.
Tonight we're going to 300.
Drop by!
Come with us.
You're invited,
let's take her to 300 tonight.
- I've seen you somewhere.
- I said this too.
I'm new here, just me.
At some party.
Yeah, absolutely.
You know I know you.
Where do I know you from?
I think you know me from some beach.
The north of the island.
Daniela's Beach, Jurerê...
Yeah.
Yes, Daniela's Beach.
Maybe it was Daniela's Beach.
Yeah, I think so too.
I was drunk!
I was a little too.
You don't remember either?
Oh, sure I remember.
So, I'm not mistaken.
I kissed her.
I imagined... When you said,
"I know you." I got it.
I can't analyze the situation.
I can't see it.
I think they all have girlfriends.
I wanted those guys...
I know, there are more over there.
Maybe we go for a walk,
exercise at the beach.
I think we could go for a walk.
Did you get a message, girl?
Yes.
Girl, all good? How are you?
Let me tell you.
I've just reached Floripa.
Tell me where you are,
and I'm gonna meet you.
One more member is coming!
Hi! I love it, right?
- We're at Praia...
- Novo Campeche.
Come meet us now.
I'm gonna send you the location.
Bye.
Do you know how Bia met her?
Fighting with her on the floor, guys.
Yeah, actually her ex-boyfriend, right?
Is she a good person?
She's a great person. She's very positive!
She's mature as fuck.
She's a nutritionist and also a coach.
Imagine her body, right?
She's brunette, curly hair...
Can she come dressed?
If she wears a bikini,
we're fucked.
She's great, you'll love her!
She's great!
I think that's what we needed.
One more girl!
Yeah, the girls' team!
So it'll get even better.
Yes!
We're gonna have to kiss each other.
Right, Nathália?
I don't think she does that.
They're here. They're laying down.
Oh, great.
You're kidding! She came...
Get out of here!
I can't believe you two came!
Girl! Damn.
Oh, my God!
Guys!
Damn. Oh, my God!
My God!
Guys, Vic, Mikaella.
Nath, Tay,
- Anna.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Damn, girl, I can't believe it's you!
God!
Well, guys. Are you okay, Rafa?
Now the gig's over
you can talk about the sex shop...
Brother, now you can do anything.
Tell me. How are you?
How are you?
Now, my job is over.
- Yes, I'm free.
- And you were paid?
Yes.
Yeah, be careful with what you say now.
Renato selected...
That's it!
Oh, man...
The selection here is...
Are you gonna show up at 300 tonight?
Just because you invited me.
I'm gonna be there for sure.
- I hope so.
- And after?
After party!
So, parties never end?
You have no idea.
Let's go?
Don't do this!
Let's go? You'll take her.
- You'll take her.
- No!
No, I won't!
I don't want it, bro.
- Ramon.
- I don't want to!
You'll take her.
You're here, you're doing it.
Call the girl.
I'm gonna be honest with her, look.
I don't care.
I got here.
Luan...
He decided to become
the Latin American prince.
You know how I am...
Let's get to the point.
We were together,
everything was great, right?
With all of us, he became a prince.
He was respecting me.
I mean, as far as I know.
Luan's crazy.
He got jealous, it got crazy...
All the craziness...
The possessiveness...
First, he got jealous of me with Tay.
He thought I wanted...
One day, I was in a very bad space,
crying because of my relationship.
Bia was looking after me, guys.
He thought we were hooking up.
I was cool, then I realized.
"I'm gonna get over there,
and he'll be with her,
"I'm gonna beat him up." Swear to God!
That's my girl, look.
I was prepared to see him, you know?
I was gonna come over with him, you know?
I'm very cool,
but don't mess with my friends.
He'd already messed with my friends
before I arrived,
I already hated him.
We got in the house,
and there was a fucking fight in the bus.
Then he began to show who he really was.
His mask was slipping.
Then he began to get crazier and crazier.
I love him very much.
I'm afraid when he's drunk.
I got in a really bad shape, you know?
Fuck, I'm not that, you know?
I'm more than that.
I lost track of who I am.
The whole time I was with him.
But it's what I told you,
you lose your essence,
you try to fit somewhere you don't belong.
You're much better than this.
Other things happened and I forgave,
I stayed with him
and I wasn't embarrassed.
It was an inner conflict, you know?
How are we going to...
Take your stuff,
get ready and go to the house...
Then we warm up...
We dress up in the hotel and go there.
- Deal.
- Take everything!
Everything!
We're absolute.
One for all and all for one!
You said what I was gonna say, Bia.
I thought there was a sorority feeling.
A partnership between them, you know?
They're really very close friends.
Yeah, Nath, Tay, and Bia.
They'll add value to the group.
The girls got there,
they explained everything,
nice briefing.
Of course, we always do this.
I love it!
Bia needed to get things off her chest,
and admit she needed to be ashamed!
She needed to...
She slapped herself!
She's gonna get wild.
She had never talked
about the perception she had about
her relationship.
Does she understand now?
I think she was able to understand
and made things clear. It's...
That's good.
All that she's been through.
It was very cool she said that
and understood that.
She's out.
She was in a circle, now she's out.
I think it's really about understanding
the situation she was in
and being able to talk about it.
Maybe she was embarrassed
to talk about that.
Imagine that Anna
got there this vacation
and had to stand up for her friend.
So, maybe she could...
But it seems she's dealing with it well
and understands that it wasn't positive...
She invited her friends, you know?
Her good friends,
so she's more comfortable.
Also, one of them is a coach,
it helps.
Yeah.
Let's go!
We're here!
Just come.
I'm here!
Ramon, come to my office.
Are you in the corner?
If those chicks come back without men,
we're gonna be fucked.
Why?
- They're gonna be pissed!
- Why?
- I think so!
- At whom?
- At us!
- At me?
No, not at you. You don't care.
He's afraid of the chicks.
Oh, fuck you!
No, bro, I'm sure.
I'm sure!
Take it or leave it.
Three words, let's go.
I'm sure about this.
Did you get my purse?
- Yes.
- Thanks.
There are women in the house.
Who?
I'm gonna freak out.
- Are they here?
- No, it's a mirage.
What a good mirage!
There's no better mirage than that.
A mirage.
Are you done?
We went to the beach, honey.
Hi, I'm an intruder.
No way. Welcome.
The kitchen is clean!
I'm still a little drunk.
Was it cool?
Look, I worked...
Did you work too?
Then we drank, we stayed and I got drunk.
What did you do?
- We went to the beach.
- Beach?
What are you eating?
Who are they? I'm gonna kick your ass.
Bro, look.
Look...
Take it, let's take it.
Did you see my belly?
I'll talk to you.
What?
You're making fun.
That's all I needed.
Okay.
I know what you're doing.
Let's go. Bye.
Bye, later.
Girl!
Where are the guys?
How beautiful!
What's up, guys?
You're beautiful, guys!
Hey, girls!
- Where are the girls?
- Upstairs.
Look at the house!
Jeez. What a house!
So, let's get the bag and take...
That's great, this bag.
Girl, wonderful!
Hey, the bus is here. Let's go!
Let's see this bus speak.
Look!
- What?
- This party!
Did you feel it shaking?
Look at that dark-haired guy. There!
Look at them, just like us.
The boys.
They're talking
about us.
Girl, I'm sure.
It's like this, chew and swallow it.
You're gonna make out with Anna today.
Those...
You're gonna have rough sex.
Doesn't he just wanna have sex?
I'm not gonna have sex here, go away.
In the bus, with the door open.
In the bus, door open,
you make the woman...
You're beautiful,
right?
- Cute.
- No!
Good one!
Let's take a walk.
Let's go!
Here...
- Bro...
- Enough!
Bro, things are going south,
I'm not following shit.
Look.
It's all about debauchery.
Bro, look, that's all I wanted.
- Bullshit.
- I swear.
I swear!
That's all I wanted.
Bro, I wanna be free here, you know?
- You're free big time.
- Sure, bro!
She hooked up with that guy
and stayed with him,
you know?
But are you cool, dude?
- Sure, dude!
- Really? I want you to have fun.
Remember that thing I told you,
"Bro, don't fall for this", you know?
Enjoy the party, don't fall in love,
don't get emotional...
- Things are intense in here.
- I know.
We need to have fun!
Not to become attached!
I wanna have fun here!
But they're restraining this.
I know.
That's not gonna happen.
If I were in that situation...
I'd be there!
Waiting for an invite.
That's what they have to understand, bro.
That's it!
Now let's have a smoke.
This is Andrei.
Hello, how are you?
Nice to meet you, I'm fine.
What's up? How are you?
When are we gonna kiss?
Jeez, you're fast, right?
Honest. I like this way.
When they're not, I go away.
I don't know if I can do it.
Of course you can!
You can do whatever you want!
Hold this! Let go because things are wild!
Bebeto and Romário.
Romário.
Bebeto.
You're Bebeto.
I'm Neymar!
Why am I the worst?
Let's go to the after party?
So, get up, you're my guest.
No, let's go to the hotel.
What hotel?
We're in a mansion.
After, tete
Bro...
Let's fucking go!
Again, touch it for good luck.
Go, Bia!
Fucking go! Let go.
Oh, girl!
Wait!
There!
Go!
One, two, three...
One for all
And all for one!
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
Guys!
Look, tonight was the first night
we didn't fight!
Cheers to our night!
Fuck! Thank God.
Floripa!
Amen! Hey, Nath, hold that!
Is there champagne here?
Yes.
We had no trouble, brother.
Everybody, fill up your glasses.
Amen, go!
We had no trouble today.
Nobody fought!
Everybody's here and there'll be jacuzzi!
I'll show you around
our studio apartment. Come with me.
Go, everybody, get off the bus.
Honey!
Hey!
Where are we going?
Let's get to know the house, honey.
We're here. I missed this, family.
I wanna know who's gonna cook.
I can't stop laughing, damn!
I don't have much time.
Funny boy!
Go, dickhead!
Dickhead? Hey, are you jealous, right?
Of course, she sleeps with me.
No more, right? Enough.
Let's go!
Bye, pretty boys.
Oh, for sure.
He was sure he was gonna fuck me.
Bro, I love that you came here, I'm happy!
Oh, fuck.
Bye, guys, God bless you.
I love you!
Kisses!
Love you!
Thank you, okay!
Okay!
Say hello to the girls laying down.
Tonight, we're going to Acqua.
Do I meet you there?
Okay.
Yay.
So, I see you later.
Okay. Bye.
Let's go to Acqua?
Hey.
It's rad.
Look!
Cheers, man!
It's just not centered, but it's good.
- Man, I asked for that.
- Yeah.
Don't complain or you get nothing.
Anna!
She wants to grab you, look!
Hey, Renato, cheating on Anna, right?
Let's stick her!
Look...
This one had...
This one had her hair pulled...
Things have changed.
...this one's worried.
Let me see your hair.
You saw it, right?
Renatinho kissing her in front of me?
You kissed other guys too.
I open the relationship,
he closes it, honey.
Then he kissed her,
I stood behind him and said,
"Open your eyes, I'm here, okay?"
I told the girl, "Let me see
if you have hair I can pull."
He's a good guy.
Very. Girl, have fun.
No, girl, he's my pair! In the house.
My pair here...
- Oh, I got it. Me?
- No!
But he's a good guy.
Really good!
He gives me the freedom
I want, you know?
Renan didn't.
Treat me bad, I'll fall.
That's why he doesn't care about me.
What happened? Are you drunk?
How are you? Nice to meet you.
It's two kisses in Rio.
I got it.
Are the girls
in Porto Alegre hard to deal with?
No, just you?
You...
I'm really hard to deal with.
I love girls that are hard
to deal with, you know?
Yeah!
Even if the weather changes
She's the sun, summer
Look, girls!
I'll put my glasses on
because I can't believe this.
I'm fucked up.
I have to fill this up.
Hard to deal with?
- She is.
- A lot, right?
Because she... Lord.
She was defending you, okay?
Don't complain!
The girl had a bad look in her face,
she said,
-"I'll go there!"
- Don't go.
Don't go!
- Option two.
- There's no option two.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna...
explore the whole house.
Are you crazy?
Your day was yesterday, I said nothing.
I was there, wasted, lots of pussies...
You were wasted, that's why it was my day.
Not my fault!
Yesterday was your day, today is mine.
Yesterday was your day.
We're gonna play with style.
Guys! I got another box for us.
Inside.
Oh, that's bullshit! Really?
Let's go!
Now? Oh, man!
You're gonna get around
with everybody inside.
Holy shit!
He said, "He looks like me."
He did?
Hug your friend!
Let's fucking go!
Hey, Anna!
Girl.
You're crazy!
Be careful!
I'm gonna fall, motherfucker.
Girl.
Jeez, I'm very sexy.
I could've gone like this.
I didn't hook up today!
Look at her style. Filthy feet.
I'm gonna fall, motherfucker.
Get up, then. Go. You're heavy.
At the party... At the party...
Let me go.
At the party...
I'm gonna puke, motherfuckers.
With the blondie?
I sent her the sex code.
Yeah?
I didn't feel anything about Murilo...
I don't know if it's good or bad.
I might not like him...
You know?
The love's over, guys?
She whispered,
"I think... I couldn't feel anything."
My God!
She's letting that feeling go away.
It's good, but that "I think",
is something very...
She's not sure, right?
Everything Murilo did in this episode,
taking those girls home,
he did it to affect Tay.
If this is not working...
If Tay doesn't care, he'll suffer a lot!
And Tay, I'll tell you,
she's incredibly beautiful, if she wanted
to hook up with anybody,
she would've kissed everyone.
She said, "I'm gonna stay cool."
And Murilo went wild.
She said, "I'm gonna stay cool,
"I'm in mourning,
"but when it's over,
-"things will get ugly."
- Maybe she didn't kiss anyone
so she would have a reason
to nail it in the end, like,
"Remember that summer
when you hooked up with everybody?"
That's it.
Hit play!
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
This affects me...
Sometimes, I don't know what you want.
God bless, things get ugly.
Do you think this could be pregnancy?
Oh, my God!
Oh, I don't wanna be here!
Take the fucking flamingo!
Absolutely nobody. Me and my friends.
Anna got upset with Renatinho...
No!
"I wonder if it's pregnancy"?
To whom?
I think Tay asked, didn't she?
So, if there's any pregnancy,
there could be two possibilities.
Murilo got Tay pregnant
or Luan got Bia pregnant.
Or Renatinho got Anna pregnant.
There wasn't enough time, man.
I don't know how...
We watch this every week...
No. Whatever...
If I'm tired of your face in three weeks,
- imagine pregnancy.
- I want Murilo to be a father!
Easy, they're not a stable couple yet.
Why would you wanna get pregnant,
- Having a child in that relationship?
- It's a strong relationship, man.
Imagine getting pregnant on your vacation
in Wild and Free: Florianópolis.
And what will the child's name be?
João!
They'll have to name him after João.
Blond João.
Do a takeover.
- I miss Blondie.
- I'm shocked.
I wonder why Anna was like that.
Why?
Fear, this is called fear.
Have you ever carried out
a pregnancy test?
Baby, that's panic.
Maybe somebody felt sick, puked,
Anna didn't wanna see it
and they're considering a pregnancy.
Bro, what about that floaty, man?
What's that?
I won't judge.
Would you do that?
What's that?
That floaty belongs...
- to that house pool, guys.
- No, that's smaller!
That one is the size of a boat, bro.
That one belongs to the pool.
I don't get it.
I think Carol would be
the chick, the car owner,
with a lot of guys hanging in the floaty.
Wouldn't she?
Don't do this.
I picture myself on the high seas
on that floaty.
Drunk, on top of a flamingo.
Probably!
We'll wait one week?
Oh, in one week?
Girl, I need a ride again.
I'm anxious about that pregnancy
and that floaty story.
Are you okay, Lexa?
- Let's go!
- I'm anxious!
I'll give Carol a massage.
That's yummy... Damn!