- Oh, my God!
- The last episode.
The last episode!
- Are you gonna cry?
- Yes, I am!
Oh, my God, the last day!
- What's up, guys?
- What's this?
What's this, Carol?
- It's the last day, I'm very sad!
- Guys, everybody is so beautiful!
How are you guys? I'm very sad.
It's the last episode of this season,
and it's already so iconic,
but I'm sad it's gonna end.
- Me too. I'm already sad.
- What will you take in from this season?
A lot of things...
That I have to be more patient...
Actually, they're all single,
not sure what I can learn from them.
- What about you, John?
- I learned to be detached and free.
I think that's the motto of this season,
being free. And I'm gonna miss you guys!
- Carol, my friend!
- We learned to listen
- to each other this season.
- It's because Renatinho
and Anna showed us it's about
being nice, about listening, right?
- And always talk to the person.
- Exactly. Be honest.
I learned...
I learned we can't fall for anybody
while on vacation in Floripa.
Titto, what about you?
What will you miss besides me?
I'll miss the moments I had peace
and quiet, when you weren't by my side.
Really? I'm gonna say
what you told me before the show.
I think deep down,
you guys love each other very much.
We love each other so much
that we get lazy. Right?
- I'm determined to watch the next episode!
- So be prepared to hit play!
- Let me get the remote.
- Hit play with your heels.
- What?
I think I had...
Oh, bullshit.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
God bless you.
- Kisses.
- Kisses!
Bye, girl.
- Don't cry, Romário.
- Romário doesn't cry anymore.
- Oh, I loved it, girl, it was great.
- Me too. I missed you a lot.
Yeah, now you gotta see him again.
Jeez, Ramon, help me,
how am I gonna tell Luan?
Man, first you have to find out
how he's doing outside.
Okay, you can hate him all you want.
You didn't hate him before, did you?
- No, I don't hate him.
- There you go.
The guy keeps fighting for no reason,
it sucks. You get tired.
If someone is not with you
to join forces, he just gets in your way,
it's not worth it!
Let's go!
- Enjoy the last minutes.
- That's true.
- The last hours.
- Yes!
What do you think about taking a walk,
just the two of us, today?
- Sounds great.
- A little date.
- Yeah? Sounds really great.
- Deal?
It's a deal.
- Am I gonna drive?
- Yes.
Yay!
- We weren't talking outside, right?
- No.
So, I kind of didn't know
what was gonna happen.
Oh, me neither, that's why I said
I didn't wanna see you when you said that.
- It would be better for us to meet here.
- I wanted to see you.
I also wanted to, but I didn't think
that it was the best option, right?
As I said before,
sometimes, when we talked,
we would end up here together,
and I didn't want that.
I didn't want to be on holiday
in a relationship.
After everything that happened
I wanted to set you free and be free.
- But do you understand the term "free"?
- Yes.
- It's not...
- You label things.
I wanted us to be free,
to see how it was gonna be here.
- And your test went totally wrong.
- What I thought would happen, happened.
So it worked!
- Yes, nothing went well.
- Everything I asked the universe happened.
I wouldn't test somebody I care about
like that. It's not authentic.
It depends...
You did what you felt like doing.
- Not literally. Some things...
- That's it!
- ...other things, I didn't.
- That's what I wanted, you to be free.
Some things I did because I was angry.
Anyway, I made mistakes,
because I did that.
That's gonna last a little,
because I can't erase what I saw.
- It's not easy.
- It's inevitable, you know?
- And that's it.
- It was great, I think we...
talked and worked things out.
- We needed this, right?
- Yes, we were distant from each other.
It all happened for us to mature.
And I matured a lot.
I experienced and felt somethings that...
If this was horrible for me,
it was much worse for you.
But it's what they say,
that had to happen. It was meant to be.
You told me you were in Floripa before,
but you weren't.
No, it's wonderful.
Thanks for bringing me here.
- It's a walk, a peaceful walk.
- Discovering new places.
I've never come here either.
I'd only heard about it.
Three hundred and sixty.
Since you didn't say what we were gonna do
and we don't have bathing suits,
we'll have to get in the water naked.
But it's deserted.
- Will you forgive me?
- Okay.
I accept your apology,
but can't forgive you.
I understand.
Forgiveness takes time.
We've already talked about this.
And thanks for being
such a wonderful woman.
Beautiful, hot and all.
- I love you.
Hey guys, what's up?
Today I'm gonna need
Murilo and Ramon at the bar.
Since Renatinho left,
bring one girl to help you, okay?
I'll see you there. Bye.
My egg!
It must be the new girl,
she's the one who worked less.
Anna? Yeah, it's her.
- We have to work today.
- What?
Yes!
Anna...
you're gonna work with us.
Bye, girls! Kisses!
Bring home the bacon...
We gotta have a party!
Somebody has to work, right?
- To pay all...
- It's not easy!
Good evening!
You ordered another caipirinha?
Yeah, I owe you one, it's not personal.
I know you. How are you?
- It took a little while, but you got it.
- Thanks.
Now, I'm gonna drink it all.
And he won't see it.
You won't gossip about this, right?
Let's go!
I'm drinking tonight.
Ramon!
He's there, drinking.
- To whom? Oh, I know.
- I don't know.
That girl over there.
Ramon...
I saw you came back with half a drink...
I guess the client didn't like it.
Bring him a free drink. Okay?
I'll do it now.
There was no client,
I was the one drinking.
I'm gonna drink it again.
Keep the beat going
Let's go, we have to work, fuck!
I was saying this right now.
Way to go! The intake of drinks is high.
It's high, great. Right, Anna?
Give me a vodka shot
before Ricardo sees it.
No, Ramon!
Oh, Ramon, fuck you.
Seriously, that's fucked up!
- Fuck you, man.
- Give me one more, Murilo.
Hit the bull's-eye.
A toast to this night, to us,
and to the end of a wonderful vacation.
I love you guys very much.
Wait!
One for all and all for one!
Look...
One Sex on the Beach
and a beer for that table.
- For those guys there.
- Sex...
- Just a Sex on the Beach...
- I gave you lots of tokens, you idiot.
One Sex on the Beach and a beer.
- You go rest, bro. Get out of here.
- I wanna drink.
- You don't call the fucking shots!
- Get out!
It's too calm here!
I'd rather be with the gang and have fun.
Can we convince him? Call Ricardo
and convince him to let us go.
- Not sure. I'll try.
- I think it's worth trying.
"No" is guaranteed, so let's try, right?
I'm gonna say... I'm gonna say, "Boss,
"we're desperate for them, you know?
It's not the same thing."
Today is Friday. I'm gonna say,
"You're making a slave of my guy."
I'm gonna go downstairs
and try to convince him.
I think this is gonna work. I hope so!
- Stop laughing at them!
- Thanks. You're wonderful.
- Hello?
- Hi, boss, it's Taynara, how are you?
Hi, Taynara, I'm fine.
- Tell her I love her.
- Are you in a good mood?
- Why? What do you want from me?
- I need you to release them from duty.
You know the vacation's ending.
We are at Mess, a very cool place.
- But they're not done working.
- I am done.
- Let Ramon stay. Ramon won't go!
- Fuck you!
I want to ask you to let them go.
There's gonna be an order...
Hey, excuse me, I'm on the phone.
Can't you cut them some slack?
Reduce a bit their working hours?
Okay, since it's your last day,
everybody's free to have fun.
- Bye.
Holy shit!
- Thanks, Ricardo!
- These guys like kissing.
Kiss, that's crazy. It's over, right?
It's the last one.
- You worked a lot, guys.
- Ramon did a great job.
- Great job, he was excited.
- Rookie.
Take it or leave it!
The party tonight is gonna be awesome.
- You're free to go.
- Forget it!
- You wanna make another caipirinha, Anna?
- Another caipirinha and one more beer!
Thanks, little guy,
we're in this together!
No, I'm coming back, I don't wanna go.
- Let's go?
- Let's go, man!
- Please!
- It's over! I'm going home.
And let's party
Go, go, go, go, go
Look, since we're calling the shots here,
let's buy one drink for the guys.
I wanna see this!
I wanna see this.
I'm analyzing the situation.
We're rich,
we can buy the entire VIP box.
Go, Bia, it's your call.
Hi, how are you?
- Nice to meet you.
- I know you.
From here, right?
- From Rooftop.
- Are you enjoying Floripa?
A lot!
Hi! How are you?
- Nice to meet you, I'm Nath.
- Nice to meet you, I'm Rodrigo.
- Rodrigo and Rodrigo?
- Yes!
How are you?
Would you like a drink from us?
We're here to buy you a drink.
Oh, my God!
- Jesus Christ!
- A toast to you guys!
- Of course, we're absolute.
- Hello. Nice to meet you,
- I'm Rodrigo.
- I'm Taynara.
Nice to meet you, I'm Rodrigo.
I'm Taynara.
I'm André.
- It's not Rodrigo.
- I was expecting another Rodrigo.
Oh, my God, you're dancing forró music
with a funk song.
I can do all things
through He who strengthens me.
- Finally!
- This is Romário, whom I told you about.
- You did?
- Yes.
I missed you. The hot blondie
who arrives with Romário.
I missed you. I love you.
There are some pretty things here!
There are no hot guys,
but there's a lot of hot chicks.
Guys! Let's go to the afterparty!
Oh, that's delicious!
Who agrees that Ramon
will do the dishes until the end?
- I didn't work, just Murilo did.
- I doubt it, I trust Anna.
Yeah, but you said,
"I'm not gonna make the drinks."
- You nailed it, I know you did!
- Shut up. Stop being full of yourself.
Stop it.
- Stop it!
- Do you get one for me?
- What are you saying?
Stop it, girl.
- It's a fucking family!
- Fucking prick, impolite, rude...
stupid, ignorant. I'm not the only one
who thinks this way.
But I'm a woman
and have the guts to say it.
I have the guts to say it.
No fighting!
Everybody talks about you
behind your back, I have the guts...
I'm not talking about you.
- Who's everybody? Is it Tay?
- Everybody!
I don't say he's a prick to me.
He is to you.
Not to me.
As a friend, Ramon is different.
The same way Murilo was a prick to me,
but he was never to you.
- And she was a prick to me too.
- Exactly!
You had to accept this and improve!
Ramon's a big prick to you,
never to me, he never did anything to me.
I know! But you defended him
and didn't defend me.
You defended Murilo when he had sex
with that chick! You lent her a bikini!
Are you happy?
I did this, and you argued with me?
- Drink it, sit down.
- Drink, my ass!
- Drink my ass!
- Did I say your name?
- What's this?
- Fuck. Why are you hitting me?
Why are you throwing the drink?
When did I lie?
Damn, guys, fuck this. It's the last day!
- You're gonna fight on the last day?
- Relax.
I talked to him.
No, no, I'm aware, you know
I only said good things to you.
Jerk!
Right, girl?
Let's go!
That's crazy, I only respect
who deserves it,
not who wants it. That's it!
I understand you,
I understand Nath, you know?
But, dude!
That was unnecessary, that's it!
Any kind of violence is unnecessary!
What a funny house, man.
I'm thinking here...
Everybody thinks the same way,
but I'm a proud woman and say it!
You controlled yourself because
you're absolute. But I'm a troublemaker.
You know what's worse? She wanted
to put words in people's mouth,
and the others didn't agree with her.
Then she got pissed. When she said
Tay's name, Tay didn't agree.
Of course Tay wouldn't agree!
Then he started to play the victim,
"Oh, you're hitting me..."
She's not better than anyone.
She always bullshits.
She acts like a child.
Women don't act this way!
Girl, if he wants to be a nitpicker,
I can be much more than him.
I'm gonna be worse than him.
Because he's trash, he's a prick.
Everybody has the same option.
He taught me what I deserve and need.
And I don't need a guy like him.
You've always been honest
about not having feelings for him.
You fought with Murilo?
"Jerk, you're disgusting..."
- We dated, just to be clear.
- It doesn't matter. I defended you!
I feel you don't do this for me.
That's because I like him, and you
used to tell me you didn't like Ramon.
And I think you don't defend me.
Because you never told me you have
feelings for the guy, so, to me...
My situation's the opposite.
You've always known we had something,
- I never told you I didn't like Murilo.
- It doesn't matter.
- It's about respect. I respect my friends.
- I never said I didn't like Murilo.
I respect my friends,
but they have to be honest with me.
That's boring!
You can't compare with me and Murilo
because we work things out.
- No, it's not about comparing...
- You never dated...
- ...the point is, none of them...
- What's the point?
Me and you.
Tell me, "You hurt me when you make
friends with the girls Ramon dates."
Like Vanessa,
you were upset because of her!
We agreed we were gonna stick together.
- Men are friends with men.
- Together, but not hypocrites.
- Men defend men until the end.
- Not hypocrites.
If you wanna take their side,
that's on you. Hypocrite, my ass.
Girl, together, but not hypocrites.
If everybody thinks the same way,
or don't have the guts to say it, I do.
- Wait, what is this opinion again?
- You generalize everybody.
- Bia, don't you think like me?
- I wanna...
I wanna know
what you're thinking to say this.
Everything's funny as long
as it's happening to somebody else.
If Murilo hooked up with somebody,
I said, "Go, hook up with somebody!"
- Same thing.
- But I liked him.
It doesn't matter,
this happened on the first vacation.
I liked Ramon at the first party,
and what did you do?
"Look, Ramonzinho had sex with a girl.
Go, Ramonzinho!"
You don't even remember anything
and you remember this?
I remember what I do!
- It's totally different.
- It's good!
Great!
I've already admitted being a phony.
So are you.
- If I were, I wouldn't say it.
- Finally, right?
You hate that I'm friendly
with Ramon's girls
because you like him and won't admit it.
That's what it seems!
- Let me finish! Wait for your turn!
- I don't like him!
Let me finish? I'd be hurt by Murilo
because I love him.
So, it's different. You got here saying
you felt nothing for Ramon.
So, I'll make friends with Vanessa...
because I think you won't get hurt.
I told Ramon a lot of times
he was a piece of shit to you.
Did I say you weren't true?
I said you were honest.
I've never told you...
But when I start being true to Murilo,
don't complain.
When I start to say,
"Mu, hook up with her, Mu!"
Don't complain!
- Do I say that?
- It's the same.
"Jeez, buddy, that chick is real hot,
hook up with her."
What happened here was unexpected.
She was surprised too.
I think she could've said a lot of things
in a better way, tomorrow she'll admit it.
That depends
on how she'll feel about this.
But here is different.
Everybody has problems.
She can stay with Ramon,
she's just told him he's a piece of shit.
Hey, your Uber's here, buddy.
Bia, he's leaving, say goodbye to him.
- Bye, Rodrigo.
- Thanks, Rodrigo.
We're in this together. I'll walk you out.
Forget it, we're in Floripa together.
I'm very sad to see
two friends get to this point.
Girl, Nath's really wasted.
Yes! She's totally wasted!
The girls were trying to open her eyes,
but then they got it all off their chests,
stuff they might regret.
She called her a phony.
"You never remember anything,
how do you remember that?"
But I think Tay
is being reasonable, you know?
Nobody can give her some advice because...
She doesn't stop talking,
she never lets anybody talk,
she's never wrong. They can't help her!
And I think it's bad when she demands
people to take her side, when she's wrong.
It's not like this, a true friend
supports you in good and bad times!
Those who pat you are not friends!
Your true friend will scold you and say,
"Hey, you're fucking wrong!"
"When I start being true to Murilo."
It's all wrong.
Because you always have to be true!
- Always!
- That's it!
Did you hear the example she gave?
"Go get the hot girl!"
Then Tay asked, "What do you mean?
Do I do this with Ramon?"
Guys, I hold a grudge against her
since the very first episode.
Don't say this, she'll block you
on Twitter. Be careful.
She's wrong, everybody agrees with this,
but I think we can't be judgmental
because I was like this,
I had this attitude, I didn't listen
to anybody... And we evolve, right?
I'm judging her attitude,
but I've already done that.
Yeah, we mature, I hope she sees it...
My contract says "Judge".
I came here to judge. Nath is wrong!
She's wrong. You have to be honest...
All the time!
But, Carol, what do you think about
your dream couple, Murilo and Tay?
Guys, I'm very happy, I am, man...
I'm very happy with that wonderful couple.
I rooted for them
since the very first episode.
Girl, you're rooting for them
It's true, she's been talking about them
from the beginning, she's really happy.
- Fake gel nails applause.
- I wanna be at that wedding.
She's ready for this, we know it, Carol.
What did you think about the naked swim?
Do you think they had good sex?
I think they did.
I want them to have a baby.
Damn!
- That pregnancy test is enough, please.
- She wants to be the godmother!
- I'm kidding!
- I agree with Jerry!
Oh, my dream is to be an aunt.
I found that walk very cute.
I found it cute. I think they refreshed.
- They needed it.
- They did!
And that talk they had in the car, like,
"Let's talk about our vacation..."
"What you thought it was right..."
And they ended up having sex in the water!
And I liked Murilo's honesty, he said
he did what he did because he was angry.
I talked about this.
I think they matured a lot, right?
A lot of situations made him...
Made him improve a lot, right?
- Both of them are mature...
- I love what you said!
I think there's no pride anymore.
I think it's over!
None of them have that pride or are afraid
of apologizing, I think they're fine.
They had to put an end to that.
Having no fear of apologizing.
I loved what you've said about maturing
because Bia wasn't mature, right?
Bia said, "How am I gonna see Luan
after hooking up with five guys?"
- You can hook up with whoever you want.
- No, girl, I agree with her.
One thing is that vacation, and another
is the reality, the end of that vacation.
- But she's on vacation!
- Girl, she was in an abusive relationship.
They're gonna come back to their reality.
Back to work, to their families,
and she's gonna have to talk about it.
They'll both have to sit and talk.
- Because I think there must be an end.
- I wonder if Bia was so quiet, so...
She was so quiet because of that?
Because she'll have to talk to Luan?
- Bia hasn't had sex in two episodes.
- Girl, she took a guy home now.
Girl, one thing is taking,
I wanna see them have sex!
What, Pabllo?
Nothing, I wanna see people kissing.
I think she showed everybody
that being wild and free in Florianópolis
is not just about hooking up, it's about
having fun with your friends too!
Shut up, girl!
If you were free in Floripa, you'd be...
Me? I would suck a lot.
Am I a whore? I'm a whore.
Get a clue! Let's hit play!
Girls, can I talk to you?
Outside, with Murilo, Bi and Tay.
I wanted to share with you something
I thought. Earlier, I woke up,
went to the lake, I thought about life,
everything I experienced on this vacation.
About the history, I guess each one of you
has a history here,
wrote history like you do in life,
the way you think it's right.
I thought about my mistakes
and successes, about what I think.
I was true to myself, everything
we enjoyed, the fights, the drinks...
- It was crazy!
- And we enjoyed this
like everyone would like to.
There were people fighting, getting along,
saying "I love you", making peace.
We've already enjoyed
almost all the parties.
- Thank God. Amen, brother.
- Thank God.
But there's one party
we haven't enjoyed yet,
and I wanted to take you there,
which is the unknown,
almost normal,
fucking P12!
Let's get wild, let's get wild!
Tonight we're going to P12!
We're gonna bring the fucking house down.
The way only we know how to do it.
- Now?
- We're gonna be carried out of there.
- Can we drink?
- Order the fucking booze!
I thought we were gonna relax today.
One for all, and all for one!
TODAY I WILL ONLY COME BACK TOMORROW
What's up, Murilo? P12 awaits me.
Hey, tonight is gonna be epic. Fuck!
- We'll leave our mark.
- Fuck!
Let's get in the bus with the right foot
because tonight is our last night here.
Night and day.
Let's go!
Thanks, Floripa!
Go, Ronaldo.
One for all, and all for one. Yay!
Look at Grijó, fuck! You son of a bitch!
Debauchery! Let's get wild!
It's fucking Floripa!
Forget about me? Fuck!
"My boyfriend's here,
my boyfriend's here."
Who were your new friends?
- You fucked up. By the look on your face!
- No.
Really?
MAGIC ISLAND
That's how I like it.
I'll allow him. Do it, kiss more.
I missed you.
Oh, flamingo!
Flamingo tonight? Let's do it tonight.
Let's go see the flamingo tonight.
- Easy, the night's just begun.
- Yeah, but, look...
I promised him.
Excuse me, Renatinho.
Give a triple kiss, you three.
Fuck! We're in this together.
Fuck!
Couple!
Good evening, guys! I wanna see everybody
full of energy, partying a lot.
I present you, Kevinho!
Take a ride and I'll introduce you
The best funk party in Rio de Janeiro
You know the Complexo da Penha
Is a real whorehouse
Let's go to the cage, everything's fine
A thin mustache and a hair cut
She looked at me, I looked at her and said
Come with Kevin and Chris
Sit, sit, sit, sit sit, sit
What did I say? Jump, come on!
Sit, sit sit
Sit sit, sit, oh, damn
Sit, sit sit,
Put your hands up!
Now it's all mine
Your heart doesn't make lub-dub
Now it just beats like a butt
Lub-dub, lub-dub, lub-dub
Please, ladies and gentlemen.
Put your hands in the air, everybody!
Now it just beats like a butt
Your heart doesn't make lub-dub
Lub-dub, lub-dub, lub-dub
Now it just beats like a butt
- Kiss me!
- Do you believe it?
I believe it, what about you?
We believe it!
Give it up for Kevinho
who enjoyed, Floripa family!
Debauchery! Let's get wild!
Girl, I can't take this.
It's because of the booze.
We're in Floripa!
She wants to date
I know what's gonna happen
Maybe our kiss is a match
Maybe I get the chills
There's nobody home
I'm gonna turn the stereo on so
She can dance
She's gonna look at me
She's gonna tease me, all horny
Looks like a mirage, it's a dirty thing
This chick is gonna live on my mattress
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with you by my side
Let's go! Tonight there's an after!
Fuck!
Let's go!
Oh, fuck, it's the last afterparty!
I'm back!
This is gonna blow
- You missed me, right?
- It's the last afterparty!
Jump, Amanda.
WHERE'S THE AFTERPARTY?
#itsfriday!
Girl, you saw the awesome party?
- The afterparty was the best.
- I'm shocked!
- The first really good afterparty!
- There were naked people in the pool...
- It was like Carnival!
- It was a micareta!
- Everybody did whatever they wanted.
- I wanna see what happened after...
Man, seriously, I wish
I was at that afterparty.
I wish I was at everything, at the house,
at the party, at the afterparty...
No, the party was...
Guys, Kevinho? Imagine!
But I felt a really good vibe
at that party at P12, right?
- Looks like everybody let off steam!
- Exactly!
A New Year's Eve. It was fucking awesome.
Yeah, refreshed energy.
If they weren't cool, there was gonna be
the greatest fight of the year!
It was gonna be war!
Girl, don't you think a lot of people
had good sex at that afterparty?
We're gonna see them waking up now,
where they slept. I wanna see it.
- I wanna see that too, the next day!
- Hit play!
Guys, it's coming to an end,
but I need help with one thing.
Where's the next one gonna be?
Oh, bro, I can't believe this!
One for all and all for one!
I wonder if there's not gonna be
season three. Carol?
I hope so, I hope very much there is, man.
I hope you understand.
That my love...
Whore's love
I'm very nervous? It's been two summers.
I'm already spoiled.
You broke the couch
and now you're gonna leave.
- No, he really broke it.
- I really got pissed.
Guys, thank you. There's that saying,
"If you stay, take my dick,
if you leave, my father's."
I'm gonna take an Amazon's glass home.
Oh, I'm okay.
- Amazon, invite me to season three!
- I hope to see you guys next time.
Bro, the guy managed to break
the leg of the couch.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna miss this a lot.
I think there's gonna be season three.
I hope to God, and we'll be there, sister.
I wanna see if they swap everybody
and pick people like us.
Creative Supervisor