WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
- I'm here!
- Guys, I missed you.
You're spitting in the back of my head.
- I'm anxious.
- What an upgrade we got here.
- Yeah, it's true.
- It's beautiful, right?
Good!
- This is much better.
- I'm shocked!
I'm very anxious for season two.
Last summer I was on Titto's lap.
Thank God, I asked... I said I'd only come
- if you stayed away from me. Thanks a lot.
- I wish we were closer, but we can't.
I'm very happy to be here with my friends
for the second season
of Wild and Free: Florianópolis 2.
But now we have two wonderful additions.
My friend Lexa, wonderful, impressive.
And my dear friend Jerry Smith.
- Girl, are you ready for gossip?
- I am. I can't wait for all the gossip.
You're not ready for gossip.
Oh, Lord, that's the way I like it.
Jerrynho, baby,
have you ever been to Floripa?
- Yes.
- Have you?
No, not Floripa, but Santa Catarina...
I enjoyed myself a lot there.
Tell us more about it.
- Why did you go there?
- Do you like video games?
"Do you like video games?"
For those who didn't understand,
this is her pick-up line.
She invites guys to play video games
at her place and screws them.
- Yeah. Better watch out.
- Our studio's changed a bit.
We're following all guidelines
from health authorities for COVID,
but Titto is devastated. Right, man?
He thought he would kiss me and seduce me
this season.
We're gonna have to wait
until next season.
- But we'll exchange some nudes, right?
- What's this bullshit?
Right, honey?
- Are you sharing nudes during quarantine?
- No.
- What about receiving them?
- I don't do these kind of things.
- I just send out nudes.
- What's that face, Lexa?
A face of someone who wants to know
about all of her friends' gossip.
I see nudes all the time, anytime I want.
I've got my go-to guy.
But it's good having friends' nudes,
you know?
I like having my friends' nudes because
that's when you can exchange favors.
What do you mean?
I can't send nudes to a friend!
Like "Hey, dude, what's up?
Did you get my dick pic?"
What are the odds, man?
I said to Pabllo, "Good morning."
- I've sent them to Pabblo, before.
- My friends have some sexy pictures.
- And we exchange them.
- How am I supposed to help my friend?
Girl, after some booze?
I send them! It's like,
"Girl, look how wonderful this is."
- I love it.
- Yeah, when you're pointing north...
They say, "Fuck, your thing is huge, bro.
How is your thing?"
- You can send it, okay?
- Men never send them,
never send nudes when they're 'offline'.
Do you know anybody who sends
their picture with a limp dick?
Only if it's stiff.
It's sad when they send it offline.
- No. You can't send a limp dick.
- I like dicks, you know? Hard, limp.
- It doesn't matter.
- I like to see the worm grow...
I'm dying to know what they've been up to
the last summer in Floripa.
How I miss the times we were allowed
to get together!
It's good to remember that this vacation
was recorded before the pandemic.
They're not actors, there's no script,
everything is real here.
Let's talk less and hit play?
- Let's do it.
- Let's go!
- I'm dying to watch it.
- Here we go, Brazil!
Look!
And they're friends, right?
I've missed you.
You look beautiful!
"Back to the game," that's right.
Jeez, you look thin, right?
You... Look!
- That's me meeting Lexa today.
- They're like us.
- Jeez, girl, you're great!
- They're beautiful! Screw you, guys.
They're great now. I wonder
if they forgot the fights they had.
Never, girl! It's that thing, right?
We can forget, but we don't forgive.
- If you drink, the problem comes up.
- Yes, it does.
- Guys, where's Blondie?
- I don't know. She sent an audio message
- and I waited to hear it with you.
- Hi, Tay, how are you, girl?
I got caught up in work in São Paulo,
I won't be able to party with you guys.
Bye, girl.
No!
- No! I can't believe this!
- No, Blondie, no! Please!
Blondie is not coming.
Jeez, I'm glad Anna is coming.
Or our team would be left shorthanded.
- I wonder who Anna is?
- Carol,
- who's this Anna?
- I wonder if it's Anaconda.
-"Anaconda!"
- We've seen Anaconda in the first summer.
Ramon and I are friends.
Are you hooking up with each other?
I don't think so. I hope not.
- Nath was able to be friends with Ramon.
- Meaning there's some hope.
When you say, "Certainly not",
it's something... There's still a risk.
The way she said it,
it's like, "Certainly, we are."
Man, let me tell you, I'd never expect
this from Nath and Ramon. "Good friends."
- I think she's mature.
- I think it's fancy, cool.
It's like a game.
"We're good friends and we can kiss..."
Nath said she broke up with Ramon,
they're good friends,
but they fought so much that I thought
they'd not speak to each other anymore.
Girl, I think they're gonna hook up
with each other, you know?
I wanna see it, you know what?
When they go out, see somebody hooking up.
- Because they didn't see it.
- Yeah.
He went to Santos, I went to Vitória.
We tried to stay together.
Distance got in the way, you know?
We didn't like some things that happened.
We didn't like some things...
- That's it.
- Relationships are hard, guys.
Lexa, do you think Bia
and Luan will get back together?
They are, girl.
There's gonna be lots of replays.
I think forgiveness
depends on Luan's dick size.
- What, Carol?
- The size.
What size?
- Size doesn't matter.
- So, you won't forgive.
You know? If it's like this...
That's all forgiveness is about?
I think forgiveness depends
on the size of the dick!
"THE SIZE OF THE DICK"
But what's the size of your forgiveness?
- Twenty-three...
- Twenty-three?
In order to forgive...
Twenty-three, twenty...
- Look, I'm unforgivable, then.
- What about the average? Never?
- I'm talking about forgiveness.
- And with no forgiveness?
Twenty-two.
- I went overboard with twenty-three.
- But you aim too high, fuck!
Twenty-three! I didn't know
you were making love to horses.
For God's sake! Holy shit... The dude has
a forearm hanging there, for God's sake.
It's hard to find something with 17.
Imagine 23.
Not where I come from.
Oh, yeah? So... Look.
I have footage.
Does anybody want to drink?
Finally, right?
Oh, my God, It's Anna!
Fuck! She's so hot!
- Okay, honey, she came with a bottle!
- She came with a bottle.
I missed you, Floripa!
Enter the house with the right foot.
- Guys, where's João?
- I wonder if João is in another car.
I think João is coming
in a car with a loudspeaker.
- I wanna see the look in their faces.
- Where's Joãozinho?
Where's Na... Where's Bia, bro?
Bia got out of there too, see?
Look, Murilo and Tay! Acting like friends?
"How are you, man? Are you good?"
If an ex talked to me like this,
I'd kill him.
"Are you good?"
"Are you good?" is...
Oh. Trigger warning.
Trigger warning. I don't know about
you guys, but I felt something there.
- Shaking?
- Shaking!
I want that smell, he's shaking.
Guys, let me tell you,
something is going to happen soon.
It's gonna be in the first episode.
They have all hooked up
with each other, baby.
That's inevitable.
It's fucked up when your ex says,
"I can't forget your smell."
Girl, I'd hook up with everybody.
- Guys!
- Me...
- Let me tell you...
- That's a trigger warning.
It's all I've wanted now.
Dance, Jerry. Dance. Come!
That was too much!
- It fell down.
- Put it in your pocket!
I almost did that a few minutes ago.
The best thing is the rookies fucking up.
Who invited you? Fuck!
- Don't talk about love.
- Sorry, guys.
What's this, Beatriz?
Look at those big asses... What's that?
Your pussy was showing in the pic.
What?
- What did he say to her?
- Guys, no!
- He didn't say that, no. Oh, no, guys.
- Rewind! For God's sake.
Your fucking pussy is showing!
The pussy was showing in the pic.
'Course, such a big pussy.
Did he say her pussy was showing?
Then she said, "Of course not."
and he said, "Such a big pussy"!
- She said "Was it?"
- She was worried.
- Yes, but he...
- He worried.
- But this was mean, right?
- No, it was.
He wanted to set the mood for debauchery.
- I didn't like that.
- He wanted to touch her or...
Seriously, after what he did, brother...
I think he had to approach slowly.
And tell her,
"Baby, let me tell you a secret.
"Your cunt is showing."
But, Pabllo, if some boy told you,
"Your pussy... Your pussy is showing."
Girl, first of all, I'd laugh a lot
and go, "Cut it out, dude."
I'd say, look.
- Say it to me, Titto, please.
- John, let me tell you...
I'll get a lot of water and put it here.
- Say it.
- John, your... Your pussy is showing.
Pabllo, help me, it's slipping out.
- Oh, girl.
- He'd say, "Buddy, I don't have a pussy.
"Man, your asshole
can turn into a pussy."
Guys, let's stop talking about pussy.
- Oh, no, he touched it! No.
- He touched it! He's clueless.
Totally clueless.
Jeez...
Now, come here, it's the boys' turn.
No, you saw that... No, guys, I can't.
Bro, she was... She didn't allow him
to touch... They weren't together.
- Let me tell you, I thought...
- But what am I to you?
Why didn't you tell me?
Go fuck yourself.
Oh... Oh, no. Wrong!
He's all wrong, all wrong.
- Everybody! And why didn't you fix it?
- Go show your pussy outside.
Beatriz, do whatever you want,
you're free.
- Guys, out of the blue!
- He's gonna start like that, man?
I've never seen anybody doing this
at a party. "Your pussy is showing."
Seriously, if he hooks up with her,
I won't say anything.
As far as I'm concerned, they didn't kiss,
they didn't hook up... He complained
about showing it.
She said, "Why didn't you fix it?"
Then he said, "What am I to you?"
Then why did he touch it
and say it was showing? Be quiet.
If you don't own it, man,
get out of there, dude!
I think it's happening something like,
he wants her to say what they are.
Seriously. When she said that,
she made him feel important.
She just said, "If you're complaining,
why didn't you cover it?"
Buddy, maybe she made him feel important
in a way that she likes him, nothing real.
The worst of all is him telling her,
"Hey, you're free, do whatever you want."
If I'm free, I can show it off.
- And you're pissing me off, man!
- Exactly!
I think his approach was very wrong,
touching that girl, you see?
I think he did that to show other boys
he's with her, you know?
Jealousy, possession, ego,
and lack of respect, I think.
- Jealousy.
- But I loved her attitude.
- Like, "What? I'm not following you."
-"Why didn't you fix it?"
I think he lied.
She wasn't showing anything.
He just didn't like that situation,
he wanted to get her out of there.
What about you, Jerry Smith?
And there's another thing,
when the panties are bothering,
you can feel it,
you can't show it and not feel it.
- I know it, I wear panties.
- When it happens to me,
I just feel it the day after, baby.
I think there's gonna be some tension
and a fight in the bus.
- Hi, what's your name?
- Pedro.
Pedro, nice to meet you.
I love Anna!
Anna fixed that guy up with Nath.
Wonderful!
You can hook up with him!
In my opinion,
if I were to go to that house,
Murilo would be the one
to draw my attention,
So I see Murilo in the house.
I know he has a history
with that other girl.
I'm at a party.
I try to fix someone up with the chick...
So Murilo is free.
- Strategy, right? Great strategy, right?
- Yes. And I'm not like...
Say it again, I didn't take notes.
I liked that move.
- I've never thought of that.
- When I want somebody, I make my move.
- Then suddenly we're hooking up, kissing.
- I have a move!
Carol, if you were Nath,
would you notice it?
Oh, I'm a thug, man. I'm...
- What would you do to Anna?
- Why is she fixing this guy up for me?
Thinking the same way, according
to NASA's conspiracy theory from Carol,
she did all that, arranged all that.
Let's say she says, "Nath,
"since you hooked up with two guys,
I can hook up
"with the other?"
Nath still likes him, but...
- She's free. How about that?
- I don't believe in this theory.
- I'm for honest talk.
- Honest talk.
- Let's watch the episode!
Can I come in?
What did I tell you, fag?
What did I tell you?
Their first time was in the bathroom.
Mine is there too, I can do it.
- He's naked.
- I know he's naked.
There must be a jerk
for everything, right?
- Whoa!
- Anna said that?
Look!
Bia and that guy should sleep
in the sex room, right?
We can go to the bedroom.
There's whipped cream.
There's whipped cream...
I stained all my clothes.
Let's go to the room.
- Let's drink some more.
- We can drink tomorrow.
- Okay, but I wanted to have sex here too.
- So we're gonna have sex here.
Okay, but I...
Guys!
I'm shocked!
- Okay, honey, bathe in the seashore!
- Why are you crying, Mýkonos?
- Cry, Mýkonos. Cry!
- Why are you crying? Look!
- Nobody invited me to that bar.
- Bro, I'm shocked...
It's another bar!
- It could be Hard, instead of Soft.
- Guys, I'm jealous, I wish I was there!
- I'd go out wearing bikini, look...
- She's thinking, "Let's party",
- but she'll work. Look, he's there.
- Carol liked the manager!
Let's watch this.
I wanna keep it light.
You're not keeping it light.
This is good just when we have sex.
Okay?
- It's like this?
- I won't bother you anymore.
- Jeez.
- It's good just when we have sex.
- I'm not gonna bother you anymore.
- Fag! I'd slap his face.
She repeated, "It's good
when we just have sex."
Bro, he really said that to her?
Seriously. He said,
"I'm sorry, I made a terrible mistake.
I want you to be my children's mother."
The day after, he says, "It's good when
we just have sex." He's messing up!
Regardless of it being a man or a woman,
I think it's terrible to hear this.
Let's be honest,
now she has all the reasons
not to want to stay with him again.
I think so too, he started wrong,
because, bro, he started totally...
- After everything he did in...
- I can't help you anymore, Bia. Jeez...
There's no way to support her!
Man, I can't put up with what he said.
It's clearly a trap. Now, get lost.
Carol, what do you think? The situation
has gotten serious, everything is a mess.
Is she gonna hook up with him?
I think so.
I also think she will.
Because it's about the size...
- Carol sticks with this.
- Carol just talks about dick.
It's Murilo with the other chick.
Guys! Oh, no. Stop it, it's all over now!
Where's my couple?
Wait.
- I think it's over.
- I don't.
- I don't think so.
- I think this could be the definite end
or something to make them fall in love
and say, "I can't stay away from you."
- Something from their first fight.
- It'll be the trigger for a fight.
Or the first, remember.
Man, everybody is cool. They're
the only two kissing in the bus.
Exactly... Yeah.
No, there's a funny fact about Anna.
Because she's new.
- She observes a lot, you know?
- Very open-minded.
She gets to know previous stuff.
She's looking into everything, man.
Look at Murilo going upstairs
with that girl!
- Murilo, don't let me down, Murilo!
- They're gonna have sex in the room.
Don't let me down, Murilo!
- I said he wouldn't.
- What's that, bro?
Fuck! "Goodbye."
Tay is not, girl.
- She said goodbye to her boy.
- Whoa, she's going upstairs.
- What's that?
- She'll see Murilo.
But she scouted the area, right?
She looked both sides.
Oh, my!
Whoa, man, get your fucking man!
- But she was classy.
- Baby, she just walked away.
You think I'll sleep with somebody?
I didn't allow you...
- But if she did, it wouldn't be a problem.
- To whom did she say that?
I thought she'd sleep with someone.
I think Murilo might have deduced this,
"If she brought a boy home,
"she'll have sex, so I'll have it too."
- I think so.
- He might have thought so.
- I think this might have happened.
- It's just...
It's just people don't plan that much.
They were kissing
and looking at each other.
- They were.
- You guys make a lot of plans.
If she... He saw her hooking up
with some other guy and said,
"Fuck, bro, I'm gonna have
to hook up with another chick
"because... She's gonna take
that guy to the house and..."
But why?
- You're hooking up with another guy.
- So he can hook up too.
From the bottom of my heart,
I hope Mu had hooked up
with that girl because he wanted,
because he felt like.
I think everything is fine, he's free.
What is wrong about
Tay and Murilo's relationship,
is that they get other people involved.
- She doesn't give a shit.
- That chick with Murilo
- is not to blame.
- Actually, there's no wrong or right,
- everybody is over there, man.
- Everybody is free.
That chick over there...
Has nothing to do with this.
- If I were her, I'd be filing my nails.
- In my experience, I think they'll talk
when they're sober,
they're gonna apologize and all...
Apologize for what?
Apologize for that situation, you know?
You know that drunk talk...
And she realized what happened.
"Fuck, I brought the boy here, kissed him.
"Then got in the room and saw Murilo
with another girl.
-"What will happen to us?"
- I don't understand this.
No, I wonder if they'll remain friends
or if they'll say,
"We realized it was bad
seeing ourselves with other people."
I think there's gonna be some trouble
after what she said.
But there's gonna be a talk.
- I think there's gonna be a bad mood.
- They'll say,
"We realized we should be together."
I think she thinks he did that
on purpose to hurt her.
I'm gonna interrupt you guys because
I wanna watch the next episode's scenes.
And I'm gonna play it now.
I don't have to go in my bedroom
and see them having sex.
Now everybody is free.
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
Because she said, "It's her, for sure,
the second pair of eyes never hurts."
I think it's intriguing
to have sex on the board.
No, guys, really? I wonder if something
happened on that board.
It's hard to keep your balance
on a stand-up board.
Creative Supervisor