God, it's been one week.
- Hello, guys!
- We're back.
Doesn't she look like a cupcake?
This is the best "hello"!
The best "hello, guys".
Pabllo has a pineapple hairdo!
Oh, baby!
Sis, what's going...
Which beach were you at?
I'm not at her level.
Girl, you came from there?
From Ibiza!
I loved it!
I came like this to fit the mood.
How are you, guys?
Anxious!
Fine, thank God!
I'm shocked,
and there's been only three episodes.
You know what's worse?
The disagreement bus.
In the beginning
I wanted to ride that bus,
now I'm afraid of getting on and arguing.
Because even Tay,
the most even-tempered,
got so mad at Murilo
that she got mad at everybody in the bus!
- I'm really shocked!
- So am I.
I wouldn't take that bus!
If someone pulls my wig off...
Girl...
There's a curse...
And it must be broken.
Everybody is happy at the party,
then they get in the bus,
and it's mayhem.
I'm shocked with Tay
because she was even-tempered
and classy,
and she got everything off her chest
about Murilo, on that bus.
Also that kick that she missed,
but it did happen.
She missed that kick.
We saw scenes from next episode,
she broke a glass at the table.
All her class was gone.
It's over!
- I don't know what happened!
- Me neither.
I think she loves in a different way.
No, I think it's Murilo. She's just hurt.
In my opinion, she's just hurt.
And when we think we've seen it all,
we have Luan, who left the house.
I wonder if Bia will finally
enjoy her vacation.
I think she will!
Hit play, dude!
I have the remote today!
So hit play, honey!
- Can I?
- Sure!
Thank you, guys...
God, are you guys excited?
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
What will happen?
I have no idea.
We should go out.
Nobody will be able to sleep.
Let's go out.
Let's not stay home. It's bothering me.
Yes, we can't be sad.
I'd rather go out to blow off steam...
Just the fact of going out...
Guys, I also made a decision,
you know?
I asked to leave...
I'm kidding.
Jeez, motherfucker.
The beer is here.
Motherfucker.
Fuck!
Jeez, that's not funny.
If I had come downstairs
for nothing, I'd be pissed.
Tonight, we're gonna party, man.
Cheer up, life goes on.
Don't cry, Nathália. I know you love me.
She's crying.
Come here and hug her.
And apologize for that bad joke.
I could... What?
Come here, Mu.
I'm cooking, making my beef.
Let's go out.
And the afterparty!
We're already fucked up, let's party.
Come!
It's here!
Let's go!
Hey, dude...
We got it.
It's good here, girls.
One for all and all for one!
TODAY ONLY ENDS TOMORROW!
Guys, I want to make this toast
and tell you
I love you!
Thanks a lot for everything.
We're friends!
Look at me.
Are you enjoying?
I just got here...
All the guys are here.
I'm available.
Weird talk.
You smell good.
Oh, son of a bitch.
Where's the thing, brother?
That's bad.
Was there a problem?
- I love you.
- So do I.
Thanks, really.
Unfortunately, I think this is
a very good opportunity
to show the real Bia.
It's not about kissing others,
it's doing what you want!
You wouldn't dance if you wanted,
if I were near you.
No.
I'm happy for this.
I like you a lot!
Me too, a lot.
Enjoy!
Thanks for everything!
- Really!
- Have fun!
Thank you!
Enjoy this.
Let's have fun.
Smart. I think you should
hook up with that one.
What I'll say?
Anna saw the three kissing.
Tell me.
Go on, tell me.
If Murilo wasn't in my life,
you'd be the one,
but Bia is free, she wants it very bad.
But forget it.
She said, "I'm away from Renan
because I'm gonna grab him."
I said, "Wait, I'll fix this."
Let me ask you...
You want Renan?
That's what I said, Mu,
he's a nice guy.
Go!
There's Luan. Otherwise, I would.
Hey, there's no more Luan.
Fuck it,
the black dude is hot.
Kiss him.
Guys, they're gonna kiss.
I love it.
I told you so.
Love you.
I love you.
Baby, I'm here.
Now, I am...
That's what you needed.
Now I'm...
Let's go over there.
- You liked hooking up with Renan?
- Yes.
- Really?
- I liked it.
Was the kiss good?
Did I fuck up?
Of course not.
You're free.
I don't know
if I'm gonna fuck him, you know?
Fucking is something...
Fine...
- Take your time...
- Yes...
If you feel like it...
I learned one thing here,
just do it.
He's also hot, look.
- Who?
- You like older guys.
No!
The short or the tall one?
The tall one!
Then we're learning to deal with this now.
We're learning...
He's very hot.
I don't like older guys.
I'm almost a cradle robber.
Nice to meet you.
Beatriz.
How are you?
I'm fine, what about you?
- Did you get here now?
- No, it's been one hour.
You only live once, baby.
Let's go to the afterparty!
Let's go!
Let's leave.
There's inspiration here, right?
Yes.
You're a miss? "Miss Chievous."
There you go. Now she's against me too.
What goes around comes around.
Sorry if you wanted to be VIP.
It didn't happen.
Honey, let me tell you.
Be careful, you're a guest.
I can kick you out whenever I want.
You kick out shit.
- You kick her out, my ass.
- And you too.
You kick me out shit.
You don't kick anybody out.
Kidding.
She's my guest,
she leaves whenever I want.
Leave me alone.
That's your boss.
I'll take care of my boy.
There you go.
Get real.
That girl wants to argue with me.
You're tripping, Nath.
Get real! She wants to argue with me.
Honey, I'll kick yours.
You don't kick anybody's ass.
- Want to see it?
- Yes.
Want to see it?
Keep your cool.
Get your shit together.
I'll tell you.
You're tripping, bro.
Let me tell you.
You're tripping, Nath.
Tripping, my ass.
- Tripping, my ass.
- Tripping!
That chick wants to argue with me?
Not me, honey.
Want to argue with me?
You're in too much of a rush.
Relax, dude, for God's sake.
No. Man, relax.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back.
Do you miss here?
Kinda.
Just don't bump into me.
Don't bump into me.
I can't be mad at you, Tay.
How I wish I could, really.
Good. Being mad is a bad thing.
Honestly.
Thanks a lot for hitting me.
It's been a long time I've been hit.
Renan didn't allow me to hit you.
But I wanted to grab your bangs,
you know those bangs of yours?
My dream...
was grabbing those bangs
and rubbing your face on the ground.
Good one, dude.
Good to know you're here. Great to know.
Good you're gonna enjoy
the waterfall with us.
Fuck, let's rock.
Yeah, we're in the house kicking ass...
but I think you're gonna enjoy it too.
I'm waiting for you. Just fucking come.
Let's go!
Let's go.
That's funny, right?
Everyone...
There's no bed for me?
...would sleep on a bed, right?
Ouch!
Oh, that's great.
That's triggering.
I love that position.
It's makeup sex, right?
Now...
Finally, we agree. Nath made a mistake.
She fucked up.
What she did was nonsense.
She had to work things out with Ramon.
I was thinking, "Jeez, they're great."
Yeah, and Ramon too...
Ramon made a mistake too...
I don't want to cover up
for anybody, okay?
I won't do this!
But she still has feelings for Ramon.
Sure!
- It's there, repressed.
- Guys...
If I hooked up with somebody...
Guys, we don't have a relationship.
We've hooked up,
but I see you with another girl.
Sis, be happy,
I'll hook up with others too.
Yes, but if you feel something...
It's not like that.
Hey, Lexa, do you think...
Nath still has feelings for Ramon?
I think there's something in there...
There's something deep down there.
There's some feelings there.
Nothing like Murilo and Tay.
I think it's a mild feeling.
It's different.
Hey, Jerry. Do you think Ramon
feels the same about Nath?
Oh, he has a crush on her.
But I think he's way cooler than her.
That attitude of his...
made her feel that way about him.
Because...
Yeah, all that confidence... Damn, man.
He's hooking up with girls,
I think... He forgot her...
Go live your life!
He doesn't express his feelings, you know?
That's fucked up
because he doesn't express them.
We need to praise the new couple.
Anna and Tay. For God's sake.
They're not a couple
because she ended up with Murilo.
Girl, from the bottom of my heart,
I still think
that is friendship realness...
I want to make this fanfic.
What, Pabllo?
Friendship, realness.
- What?
- But I ship...
After two hours, Carol said, "What?"
Pabllo's great. Great!
What did you say?
They're friends with benefits,
like... Let's kiss.
I don't speak other languages. Sorry.
Let's talk about Bia.
For God's sake, she surprised me.
She kissed a lot!
- I was expecting that reaction from her.
- Me, too.
It was nice
that she hit on that second guy.
I thought that was wonderful.
Girl, she's totally like me.
Lexa is drinking wine on a chilly night.
Guys, I am.
In Campos, do... "I guess, honey."
What? Guys, I'm here
with wonderful people, watching...
watching that debauchery. I'm great.
Thanks for yesterday.
- It was great.
- Thank you.
I loved it too. Sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
Accept my apologies.
I loved it.
- Thanks for the night.
- Thank you.
Kisses...
Of course we'll meet again.
- That means you're leaving, right?
- Humiliating.
Okay, boy.
Two friends.
I'm very happy after last night,
my vibe was killed...
The guys are helping out here, bro.
Don't do this.
Motherfucker!
The prick was teasing.
This motherfucker said, "I am team Nath."
And I, "Fuck."
I'm team Nath!
No, you were cool.
You and Bia hold it together.
As far as possible,
you respected me.
You don't even exist to me, jerk.
Drink it!
Say it to my face.
I'm not talking about you.
Say it, repeat what I said.
You're full of shit.
- I'll say whatever I want.
- Keep talking shit.
Okay.
If you don't want to hear it,
block your ears.
Jerk!
You need to stop.
You two are the least...
You don't have a reason to fight.
Exactly, to me, he doesn't even exist.
If it were Murilo
hooking up with some girl, okay.
Hey, don't say my name.
The problem was his chick, so...
What did she do?
She was born.
- She breathed.
- Sorry.
He's a jerk.
He bleached his hair.
Do the L, Lacerda.
Come!
He bleached his hair, you know?
He bleached his hair!
Fuck, you're rad. I should hit on you.
Fuck, I wanted to come at level hard!
Blond boy!
Motherfucker.
It was a joke, right?
Sure. Whose idea?
Let me introduce. Bia, Renato.
- Renato, Bia.
- Nice to meet you.
Fuck, this is a thug thing.
Tay. Tay, Renato. Renato, Tay.
Wear sneakers to go for a hike.
I know it. Mu!
Mu, that's my good friend, from Rio.
- Renato.
- I think I...
This is that boy from the square, man.
I've met him, man.
Yeah, with Mateus.
Is Mateus your friend?
You son of a bitch.
I can't believe this, bro.
Where's...
Let me introduce.
- Renato.
- Nice to meet you.
Guys, is it Milena's boy?
Hey, man. Jeez, dude.
I know her.
How are you? I'm fine.
Fine.
- Which one?
- Bro...
I guess you haven't met.
Grow up, dude.
- I'll tell you later.
- Fuck!
Rio is a small city.
Fucking small.
Let's go to the waterfall?
Let's go!
All I wanted was to go for a hike.
It's beautiful, bro.
It's beautiful, man.
This is the waterfall.
I wanted to introduce you
to the waterfall.
Waterfall, Renan.
Renan's never seen a waterfall.
- Who put that water there?
- God.
I've met him,
he hooks up with my best friend...
Are you a grass cutter?
No, but...
We're at Vitrinni...
The same way she hooks up
with guys whom I hook up with too.
It's not a problem for us, you know?
You kissed Ramon...
Ramon can't kiss anybody else.
Because of you.
Did you get it?
With feelings, it's different.
Yeah, there are no feelings, guys.
I kissed half of Rio de Janeiro!
Hey, he is cute, right, guys?
You think?
I just think I'm desperate.
- I think so.
- So do I.
I started to dislike Renan now,
I hope to dislike this one too.
But this one's cute.
And he's nice.
There was one moment
I was short of breath.
He saw it, came back,
to check on me.
I can do better.
Because, "You hook up with good guys."
I just kiss them,
I get to know things later.
I don't ask the names.
Okay.
Fuck. I'll say, "What's your name?
How old are you?
"What do you do?"
There's those five-minute chats
before, right, Anna?
This.
Nice to meet you. And take this.
"I'm sorry, are you available?"
"Oh, I am."
You called me too.
People talk too much. I don't know why.
No, that's good. Later, you...
You know you kissed some guy
who said that...
No, after kissing, kissing well, you talk.
I get it.
If the kissing was bad, you say,
"My friend is waiting
for me in the bathroom."
Let's go!
Oh, fuck.
Home.
I'm still online! I don't want to know.
I'm still online...
My dot is green,
I said I'm "Ramonline" today.
Home!
I'm gonna take a shower, then sleep.
What?
Fuck! There's no food?
To the pool, baby.
Come here, pumpkin
Go dancing in the gang...
Guys, here's the thing.
I'd rather start too soon...
I said, "They're already sleeping.
I want to go to the pagode party."
You could have laid down, man.
It deserves more.
Come here, buddy. Yeah?
Going upstairs?
Going upstairs too?
Anna. Do you want to do this job?
- What do you want me to do?
- Moisturize my hair.
Then I'll cuddle with you.
I'll cuddle with you later.
It's a good deal.
I gotta get the thing.
- Get more.
- What, baby?
- I'm embarrassed.
- Why?
He said, "Moisturize my hair?"
Are you being cute?
- I am cute.
- When?
Now.
That's the first time.
- I really am.
- No complaints.
He might want help to take a shower.
Easy there, honey.
The soap
is here.
Tell me when you're done.
You're gonna have
to use this for five minutes.
- Five minutes?
- Yes.
I look like a beauty salon, okay, honey?
Fuck.
I'm gonna give you a little massage.
Wet.
Afraid of getting wet?
Leave... Do a...
Is that it?
It'll change.
Now you're gonna...
Squeeze it.
Put it here.
Jeez, under the arm is like
a hair stylist.
After you remove this,
you'll have to use the hair conditioner.
The conditioner is on the floor.
Okay, honey?
There.
Check if it's a conditioner.
Does it have a label?
Conditioner, soap.
Take the shower by yourself.
I can't. Why? I didn't get it.
You come here just to...
I'm a nice person.
What am I? I'll help you out,
then you give me a massage.
You make me sleep.
I'll lay over there.
You'll get the massage!
Please, that's the least you can do.
I'm gonna do like Nathália.
Are you counting sheep?
Bullshit.
So, start counting.
Let's fuck.
- Let's fuck.
- No.
So?
Jeez, I knew I'd hook up with you
because everybody said so.
They were right.
What's up, bro? I don't get it.
Tomorrow, we'll go to Ramon's
and stick our heads in a bucket.
Are you gonna bullshit me?
But there's a saying...
"It's better to apologize
than ask for permission."
Why?
Ramon, you're leaving tomorrow with Renan.
If you want it. You're the boss.
You're bringing people,
I hook up with one at a time.
Hooking up?
You're under the quilt.
That spoon thing is complicated, right?
No, he's trying to make me sleep.
- On his underwear.
- I'm good at this.
I trust the boy.
If one more of his friends come,
I'll leave.
That's the way it goes, I'm not jealous.
Are you okay, bro?
With your brother?
- I'm fucking great.
- Fuck!
What about you? Did you have fun?
Those guys are cool, right?
Yes, they're very cool, bro.
- Did you cum?
- Yes.
Okay.
That boy is skinny,
but he's got it, right?
They say skinny guys are...
Right?
Were you in the Tiger Room?
- What?
- Were you in the room?
- Did you cum inside?
- No.
Okay.
Why didn't you cum?
There you go.
Go for it.
- What?
- Go for it.
You nailed it.
You didn't want to cum, okay.
No, I wanted to, bro.
It didn't come out?
I was almost cumming... I had a cramp...
I swear. I had a cramp at the time.
The scene is ridiculous.
You had a muscle pulled?
Was she on all fours?
No, dude, I was seated
in the middle, like this...
That's good.
- I went a little harder.
- That position's great!
Dude, it just froze.
What was I supposed to do?
You keep going with the cramp.
This position is really great.
Somebody clear this up for me.
What are we gonna do tonight?
Today...
Like...
Say it. Yesterday was great.
- Amazing!
- Everybody's energy was fucking great.
We had a fucking blast,
we got fucking wasted.
But today...
think about something beachfront.
A penthouse. Just top notch people.
Top notch people...
The roof night!
My flight's in the morning.
Yeah, tonight must be the night.
Don't sleep.
Probably, got it?
Are you leaving too?
No. Renatinho just got here.
Girl!
What's up?
How are you?
Don't you want to come here, girl? Come.
I am... As far as possible.
I'm wonderful.
But some things happened...
Luan is not here anymore.
Seriously, girl.
I'll catch a plane.
Okay, girl. Hurry up.
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
I'm fine.
- I love you.
- Love you too.
Kisses!
Bye!
Who?
A friend of mine, Mikaella.
She's coming tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
Renan. Three words:
Let's go!
Renato must get in first.
It's two words, right?
Actually, it's two words.
MOLE BEACH
Renato. You step up.
Right foot, twice.
Put your tongue on it in a sexy way,
hump a little.
God blessed.
Right foot.
That's for good luck.
Fuck!
There's not gonna be enough girls
Are we okay?
Are we all okay together?
We're sisters.
So we can't do it.
Me too.
I'm doing nothing.
Listen up.
I wanted to talk to you.
Shoot.
Why did you two go different ways?
I feel she's hurt
because of what happened
between you two and stuff...
Bro, something that killed my vibe
is that she said something
about Fernanda, when she wasn't there.
She teased the girl.
She was a guest of mine,
she had to put up with jokes.
Nothing was cool.
I'm gonna work this out.
When you got in the house,
you said Nath drew your attention.
She did. We talked about this before.
If you feel like hitting on her,
talk to her.
I have nothing to do with her.
Renato, my brother,
and Nathália are another thing.
I don't know what's going on.
Those chicks are together, you know?
- I see they're friends.
- Before you...
You sound out to see what's going on.
That's what I'm doing.
I don't know.
You're my brother.
You've come a long way to have fun.
Enjoy this however you want.
Now I'm gonna talk
to that blondie over there...
See you in the rooftop in a while.
Look, I need your help.
Why?
Because it's you... Fuck.
You were supposed to control me.
What are you up to? Is it Nath?
Yeah. You knew... In the waterfall...
before I hit on Anna, I wanted her.
Did I tell you this too?
I told the boys, you know?
What do you think?
Wonderful. If Nath wants it,
you should go for it.
Renato came to me and Bia and said,
"The first chick who drew my attention
was Nath."
Then he just said, "What do I do?"
No, he fucked her,
and went to hook up with Nath.
Would you hook up with him?
He couldn't hook up with Nath?
Would you?
Not today, but tomorrow...
That's it, buddy.
Let me tell you something.
Do you know I hooked up with Anna?
But you were the first girl
who drew my attention.
I guess you don't know this, do you?
No, I get fucked up all the time, right?
I could've told her, "Fuck,
I used to hook up with Anna."
That's only said by drunk people.
It's not worth it.
But I get fucked up all the time.
Bia hooked up with Renan,
and I couldn't hook up with Luan.
And I can't hook up with you.
Why can't you hook up with me?
Do you know what Tay told me?
I told her...
She said something like, "Wait.
"I'd hook up with this guy tomorrow!"
It's over, honey.
What did she misunderstand?
We didn't understand why she was crying.
But all the problem was because Murilo
misunderstood everything,
He understood literally.
Like, "Tomorrow,
I'll hook up with the guy."
He misunderstood.
But, at the same time,
I understand his pain.
Because he likes her.
He misunderstood.
He asked her to put herself in his shoes
- and she did.
- Yes!
But then he misunderstood.
Did you get it?
I did.
Explain for us.
They were having a...
Hypothetically speaking,
they put themselves in those boys' shoes.
But he understood... Like it was Tay
- answering.
- Yes!
But it wasn't her.
Tay said she wouldn't do today,
just tomorrow.
As if she were Anna.
And he thought
Tay wanted him.
That's it.
I was cut off like this at a party.
Do you think that person will think
- about cutting off?
- I know, girl.
But I cut my leg because of this,
really!
One chick did this, bang!
She broke a bottle, it hit my leg.
Don't do this!
I wish I was classy
to fight at home,
take things, and throw them on the floor.
They must use plastic cups.
She got angry!
And threw the glass.
But I think she had an outburst.
Yeah, she did.
But, man...
I'm not standing for Tay,
but she was classy.
Even arguing with Murilo,
she was very cool.
I think she needed that.
It was a huge misunderstanding.
She tried to kick him in the bus.
I forgot about that kick!
Hit play, please!
One, two, three and...
One for all and all for one!
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
Take it or leave it. Let's go!
In front of me?
If you love me, I won't.
You're a clueless drunk.
Totally clueless.
Whoa!
You get what you give. See?
Jeez, guys. I've... I've seen it all.
Renatinho made an impression.
Took everybody to the sex room.
He got there to make an impression.
He nailed it.
But he's not wrong, brother.
Delivered.
In the end, we praised Anna a lot, but...
In the end, she got involved. What I said.
She'd get out of that, if she knew.
We'll only know if she got involved
on the next episode.
She was kissing another guy!
She hooked up because of him.
We don't know...
But it looked like that.
Yes!
And why is Taynara so pissed?
Why?
We're gonna have to wait another week!
It's over!
Guys, I'm glad it's over.
My drink is over. I'm leaving.
Let's drink at my place?
I'm cool, let's go.
Girl, give me a ride.
Let's go!
Now we're talking.
Let's play videogames, Carol?
- Let's play?
- Let's.
I'm gonna give you my joystick.
Let's do it.
Let's talk something here, the two of us.
Let's go there.