♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
So, Homer, what happened
in Capital City?
Oh, Barney.
Come on, Homer.
We're dying of curiosity.
Look, there's only one thing
worse than being a loser.
It's being one of those guys
who sits in a bar
telling the story of
how he became a loser.
And I never want that
to happen to me.
Please, Homer.
-Yeah. Come on, Homer.
-Well, okay.
It all started on
nuclear plant employee, spouses
and no-more-than-
three-children night
down at Springfield Stadium.
(distant police siren wails)
(panting)
Well, I think we lost him.
Hey, and we're at the ball park.
All right!
Two birds with one stone.
Okay, everybody out.
(cheering and yelling)
You know, boy, some of the
players you see tonight
may make it to
the big leagues one day.
What? Aren't we
going to see
any washed-up
major leaguers?
Sure, we get
a nice mix here.
I can't think of a better place
to spend a balmy summer's night
than the old ball yard.
There's just the green grass
of the outfield
the crushed brick
of the infield
and the white chalk lines
that divide the man
from the little boy.
(chuckles) Lisa, honey,
you're forgetting the beer.
It comes in
72-ounce tubs here.
I hope you'll space out
the tubs this year, Homer.
-What are you getting at?
-Well, last year
you got a little rambunctious
and mooned the poor umpire.
Marge, this ticket
doesn't just give me a seat.
It also gives me the right--
no, the duty--
to make a complete ass
of myself.
Hmm.
Ah, the Gammills.
Good to see you.
You're an inspiration
to all of us
in waste management, sir.
Well, take your mind off
contaminates for one night
and have a hot dog.
(chuckles)
Put a little smile
on his card, Smithers.
Already there, sir.
-(whispers) It's the Simpsons, sir.
-(scoffs)
Ah, well,
if it isn't the Simps.
Uh, Simpsons, sir.
Huh? Oh, yes.
Homer and Marge Simpson.
Oh, and these must be Bart,
Lisa, and expecting.
The card needs
to be updated, sir.
Well-- (sputters)
Oh, that's okay.
The baby's name isn't important.
Let's go, Marge.
VENDOR: Red Hots!
Get your Red Hots here!
BART: Oh, wow!
There's Flash Baylor.
I gotta get
his autograph.
He used
to be a star.
-Hey, Flash, will you sign my ball?
-No.
Lousy, washed-up
broken-down tub of guts.
Who does he think he is,
anyway?
-What's the matter, boy?
-He wouldn't sign my ball.
Well, he's a fine role model.
Bart, give me that ball.
Hey, Flash, check out the mature quail
headin' this way.
Well, hey, there,
little lady.
What can Flash do for you?
Here you go, Bart.
Hmm. "Springfield
Kozy Kort Motel, Room 26.
How 'bout it? Flash."
Wow!
Flash Baylor
came on to my wife.
-You've still got the magic, Marge.
-(giggles)
Hey, Dad, look!
You're on Jumbovision.
Whoa! Hey, everybody,
how you doing?
Look at me.
I'm Homer Simpson.
Heh heh.
(crowd laughs)
Homer. Homer, X-Y-Z.
Examine my zipper? Why?
Whoops!
Heh heh heh.
Thanks, everybody.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
throwing out
tonight's first ball
the man whose name
is synonymous
with our nation's safest
and cleanest energy source--
Mr. Montgomery Burns!
(scattered applause)
Oh, they
love you, sir.
(chuckles)
As well they might.
You know, Smithers,
when I was a young buck,
my patented fadeaway pitch
was compared by many
to the "trouble ball" of the late,
great Satchel Paige.
Spit on this for me,
Smithers.
One hocker coming up, sir.
(spits)
-Wuah!
-(laughter)
What a lame-o.
I think I could actually hear
the air being torn, sir.
Oh, shut up.
Hey, Burns!
Hey, rag arm!
You throw like
my sister, man!
Yeah, you throw
like me!
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
to honor America
will you please rise
for our national anthem
sung tonight by Springfield's
rhythm and blues sensation
Bleeding Gums Murphy.
♪ Oh ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ Oh, say ♪
♪ Can you-- ♪
I'm asking--
♪ Can you see ♪
♪ By the dawn's... ♪
♪ ...And the rockets'
red glare ♪
♪ The bombs burstin' ♪
♪ Shoot it off ♪
♪ Poppin' way up
in the air... ♪
♪ And.... the home...
♪ Of the... ♪
♪ Brave ♪
(everyone sighs)
Hi-dee-hi Springfield.
Dan Hoard, mikeside.
Tonight our Isotopes
take on
the pesky
Shelbyville Shelbyvillians.
The 'Topes are looking to
snap that darn 26-game
losing streak-- longest
in professional baseball.
How 'bout that? Our sleepy town is
in the record book.
Ah. Sitting with
the employees--
I guess this proves
I'm their friend.
You did get me something on
an aisle, Smithers?
I don't want to be
surrounded by them.
Let's go now!
Swing, batter!
We want a pitcher,
not a belly itcher!
We want a catcher
not a belly scratcher!
-Here we are, sir.
-Oh, no.
Oh, Marge,
sitting next to the boss.
The best night of the year,
and it's ruined.
Of all the lousy, rotten...
All this means is you can't
wave your fanny in public.
Oh! Yeah, rub it in.
Beer here!
Duff beer!
Beer.
Did you hear that, Marge?
Delicious, frosty beer.
Fat lot of good it does me,
sitting next to old man Burns.
Now, Homer.
I suppose you want a beer.
Me, sir?
Oh, no, not a chance.
Only idiots drink beer.
Actually I was wondering
if you'd join me? My treat.
Oh. Well, if someone
of your stature
can enjoy a beer,
maybe I'm all turned around
on the subject.
Wait a minute.
We're not having
a drug test tomorrow, are we?
No.
Vendor, two, please.
VENDOR: $2.50.
♪♪ (organ)
The hitter's off his rocker,
kissing Betty Crocker!
Ha ha ha!
Good one, sir.
Oh, well, I used to rile
the late, great Connie Mack
with that one
at old Shibe Park.
Little baby batter
can't control his bladder!
Mmm, crude,
but I like it.
What do you say
we freshen up
our little drinkie-poos?
-Don't mind if I do.
-(chuckles)
♪♪ (organ)
Well, Simpsy,
you up for another wave?
All right, Burnsy.
-Wo! Wo! Wo!
-Wa! Wa! Wa!
-Wo! Wo!
-Wa! Wa!
HOARD: Bases loaded.
'Topes have one out,
down by three.
Here's the pitch.
Swung on and missed.
Strike three.
Of course.
Damnation.
These banjos couldn't carry
Pie Traynor's glove.
Big Bill McCloskey coming up.
As soon as he pops out
we'll go right to
the postgame show.
C'mon, all we need
is a grand slam.
(muttering)
My one game of the year
ruined by pathetic
incompetence.
♪♪ ("Baby Elephant Walk")
What's wrong with you people?
Let's show some spirit!
Come on, get up!
Your team needs you!
Come on!
HOMER: As I got up
in front of them,
I felt an intoxication
that had nothing to do
with alcohol.
It was the intoxication
of being a public spectacle.
There's some nut
down in right field
dancing up a storm.
He's really got
the crowd going.
Let's see if he can
shake up mediocre slugger
Big Bill McCloskey.
Swung on and belted
to deep left field!
It's going, going...
It's gone!
It's out of here!
Oh, my God!
The Isotopes win a game!
The Isotopes
win a game!
The Isotopes win a game!
Wow. That was
certainly exciting.
Yes. Unfortunately,
Homer Simpson's shameless
display of exhibitionism
tainted the entire evening.
I want him banned for life
from all company outings.
(chuckling)
MAN:
Way to go, Homer.
Hey, thank you.
You're too kind.
HOMER:
Glad you enjoyed it,
but I can't take
all the credit.
The batter did his part, too.
Excuse me. You, sir,
the dancing fella.
I'm Antoine Tex Ohara.
I own the Isotopes.
Would you be interested
in becoming our official mascot?
Me? A mascot for
a bush league team?
HOMER:
I should have slept on it,
or at least stared blankly
for a while.
Perhaps if I had been unable
to think of a nickname,
all our lives
might have been spared.
MAN: Get on the bus,
Dancin' Homer.
Will you shut up!
I'm trying to think
of a name.
Well, I'm ready
to punch in.
Huh-ho, hey, cool, man.
Our lives
have taken an odd turn.
Did the team ask you
to dress like that, Homer?
Nope. This was
my own bright idea.
Come on, we gotta hurry.
Don't fill up on those
vegetables, kids.
Save room for your nachos.
KIDS: All right!
♪♪ (organ)
For the first time
in my life,
people weren't
laughing at me
they were laughing
towards me.
HOARD:
'Topes win! 'Topes win!
Two in a row! Two in a row!
♪♪ ("Baby Elephant Walk")
A Simpson on a T-shirt.
I never thought
I'd see the day.
Ooh, boogie, boogie,
boogie, boogie.
boogie, boogie, boogie.
Hey, knock that off
or I'll stick this bat
where the sun don't shine.
Oh, yeah?
And where might that be?
Oh.
(cheering)
Helen, I'm in a
Caribbean mood tonight.
How 'bout giving me
"Baby Elephant Walk"
with a little
reggae kind of beat.
♪♪ ("Baby Elephant Walk"
reggae style)
(Jamaican accent) Go, Dancin' Homer.
Git up man! Git up.
Lively up yourself,
Dancin' Homer.
(clapping)
HOARD:
Bases loaded. Two outs.
The good guys
trail by a run.
-(clapping)
-CROWD: "S!"
"P!"
"R!"
"I!"
"N!"
"G!"
"F!"
"E -E -L -D!"
Springfield! Yay!
HOARD:
Here's the pitch.
Swung on and missed.
Strike three.
'Topes lose.
'Topes lose...
You wanted
to see me, Tex?
Homer, now we both knew
when you began doin' this
you weren't gonna
be here forever.
Oh, oh, oh, I get it.
You can't fire the players,
so you fire the mascot.
You make me sick.
Homer, I'm not firing you.
I just got the word:
You've been called up
to Capital City.
-Me? In the majors?
-That's right.
Well, wait a minute.
Capital City has a mascot.
The greatest mascot
there is--
the Capital City Goofball.
Yeah, but he's
gettin' on in years,
and he needs someone to
fill in for
a couple of innings a night.
-Could be a big opportunity for ya.
-I'll say.
Why don't you talk it over
with your family?
Because they
might say no.
This was the biggest decision
the Simpsons ever faced.
I should have
listened to the kids
instead of my
big, dumb wife.
Oh, I shouldn't
have called her that.
Bite my tongue.
Bite my tongue. Ow!
I can't leave Springfield.
I was born here and
I thought I would die here.
It won't be so bad.
You'll die someplace else.
Well, what am I supposed
to do about friends?
Pfft! You'll make new
and better friends.
But, Dad, we're simple people
with simple values.
Capital City is too big
and too complex.
Everyone in Springfield
knows us and has forgiven us.
Homer, I'd be lying
if I didn't say that
this scares me a little.
But we all
have a calling--
a reason the almighty put us
on this Earth--
and yours might be
to dance on dugouts.
-You mean--
-Let's do it, Homer.
Yeah, let's blow
this pop stand
and never look back.
Whatever doesn't
kill me
can only make me
stronger.
It's not that simple.
I've got to convince
my supervisor
to give me
a leave of absence.
Sure. What would you like?
Four years? Five years?
So, Simpson, you're really
moving to Capital City?
That's right, Ned.
All this stuff
is for sale, huh?
I don't know how
to say this, but, uh--
Oh, knock it off, Flanders.
Don't start blubbering on me.
I'm gonna miss you too...
not.
I don't know, Bart.
I mean, I'm gonna miss you
and all, but--
Come on, Milhouse.
This way we'll be
friends forever.
-Well... okay.
-(spitting)
BOTH: Eww!
I'm gonna miss you,
spit brother.
I can't help but feel that
if we had gotten to know
each other better,
my leaving would actually
have meant something.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, right.
Well, we have
one quick stop
and then it's on
to Capital City.
I can't believe it--
our baby sister
in the big city.
-I'll call you every day.
-I'll call you, too.
(horn honking)
Look, he can
use a horn.
-(engine starts)
-(horn honking)
Oh, shut up.
(cheering, applause)
HOMER: Some may say
that I have been given
a bad break in life--
little education,
bald as a cue ball,
ten years on the same job
for the same salary.
But today, as I leave
for Capital City,
I consider myself
the luckiest mascot
on the face of the Earth.
(crowd cheering)
HOMER: With the fickle fans
already forgetting me
I was ready to take
the biggest step of my life.
D'oh!
HOMER:
Well, kids, there it is--
Capital City!
Look!
The cross-town bridge!
-Wow.
♪♪
TONY BENNETT:
♪ There's a swingin' town I know ♪
♪ Called Capital City ♪
The Penny Loafer!
♪ People stop and
scream hello in ♪
♪ Capital City ♪
Kids, look!
Street crime.
♪ It's the kind of place
that makes a bum ♪
♪ Feel like a king ♪
Wow!
That's service!
♪ And it makes a king ♪
♪ Feel like some nutty,
cuckoo super-king ♪
Look, it's Tony Bennett!
Hey, good to see you.
♪ It's against the law
to frown in ♪
♪ Capital City ♪
♪ You'll caper like
a stupid clown ♪
♪ When you chance to see ♪
MARGE:
Fourth Street and D!
♪ Fourth Street and D,
yeah! ♪
♪ Once you get
a whiff of it ♪
♪ You'll never
want to roam ♪
The Duff brewery!
♪ Capital City,
My home, sweet, yeah! ♪
♪ Capital City ♪
♪ That happy, tall city ♪
♪ It's Capital City ♪
♪ My home, sweet,
swinging home! ♪
ALL: Capital City. Yeah!
HOMER (softly):
C... A...
P...
Uh... I...
Mmm, come to bed, Homie.
Sorry, honey.
I'm just a little nervous.
HOMER: We would
talk about it always.
For the first time
in our lives
Marge fell asleep
before I did.
Okay, here are
your tickets.
They are supposed to be good.
You're sitting
with the players' wives.
And don't forget
to cheer for me.
See you after the game
when you're a big star.
Bart was strangely quiet.
Later, he explained
he was confused
by feelings
of respect for me.
It wouldn't last.
Wow.
(gasp) Oh, my God!
I don't believe it.
It's really you--
The Capital City Goofball.
Hello, Dancin' Homer.
Glad to have you aboard.
If there's anything
I can do for you--
-just squeeze the wheeze.
-(honks)
The fifth inning
will be yours.
Everyone is
settled in.
They've had
a couple of beers.
The game is official.
It's a pretty important inning.
Wow, the fifth.
It's also the inning
I wish I had a zipper
on the front of this thing,
if you know what I mean.
-(honking)
-Right, Mr. Goofball.
Hey, call me
plain old "Goof."
So, what exactly do you
have planned for us?
Well, I get up, I dance,
I spell out the name
of the city
all to the tune of
"Baby Elephant Walk."
Ah, Mancini,
the mascot's best friend.
Well, see you
on that field.
I'll set 'em up.
You knock 'em down.
(thud)
-♪♪ (organ)
-Well, hello again everybody.
Dave Glass talking at you.
We got great weather
here tonight under the dome.
Hmm, let's see.
Upper, upper,
upper mezzanine. Hmm.
Well, these must be ours.
-These seats stink!
-You'd think players' wives
would be a little closer
to the action.
Actually, this section is for
the players' ex-wives.
And then I found out
that all the while,
there was this bimbo
in Kansas City.
Throw at his head!
HOMER:
Who'd have thought it?
A free ticket to
a big league park,
but I was too tense
to enjoy the game.
Every ounce of concentration
I possessed
was focused on
the task at hand.
Red Hots!
Get your Red Hots here!
Ooh, Red Hots.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen
Capital City's
newest sensation,
Dancin' Homer!
Mmm, these do taste better
at the ball park.
Uh-oh.
There he is!
I was graceful.
I was witty.
Brother, I was something.
But they didn't care.
(yawning)
What is with
these people?
Why are they sitting
on their hands?
Mom, what's he doing wrong?
I don't know.
HOMER:
It was so quiet,
you could hear each individual
smart-ass remark.
Well, this guy doesn't
make me want to cheer.
Gee, I really pity him,
making a fool of himself
in front of so many people.
These cornball antics
may play in the sticks,
but this is Capital City.
The only applause I got
was for dragging my carcass
out of there.
Hey, Mr. Showmanship.
The owner wants to see you
in his office right now.
I'm sorry, young man,
you're just not ready.
Pick up your check
at the front office,
and for God's sake,
put some clothes on!
Well, I guess it's back
to good old Springfield.
But I can't go back!
Not after I've seen
the bright lights
of Capital City.
I'll wither and die
like a hothouse flower.
Now stop it, you two,
and don't look too down.
I'm sure this is hard enough
for your father.
(cheering)
Way to go, man!
All right, Dad!
Oh, what a family.
My wife and kids
stood by me.
On the way home,
I realized
how little that helped.
So that's it.
The costume's buried now.
As my son would say,
I'm one sad ape-like dude.
-Wow!
-What a saga.
Hey. You guys are hanging
on my every word.
I've become
the center of attention.
Yeah, it's riveting.
Tell it again, Homer.
Okay.
I wonder why stories of
degradation and humiliation
make you more popular.
MOE:
I don't know. They just do.
TONY BENNETT:
♪ There's a swingin' town I know called ♪
♪ Capital City ♪
♪ People stop and
scream hello in ♪
♪ Capital City ♪
♪ It's the kind of place
that makes a bum ♪
♪ Feel like a king ♪
♪ And it makes a king ♪
♪ Feel like some nutty,
cuckoo super-king ♪
♪ It's against
the law to frown in ♪
♪ Capital City ♪
♪ You'll caper like
a stupid clown ♪
♪ When you chance to see ♪
♪ Fourth Street and D,
yeah! ♪
♪ Once you get
a whiff of it ♪
♪ You'll never want to roam ♪
♪ From Capital City ♪
♪ My home, sweet
swingin' home ♪
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.