(clears throat)
Hello everyone.
You know, Halloween
is a very strange holiday.
Personally,
I don't understand it.
Kids worshipping ghosts,
pretending to be devils.
Things on TV that
are completely inappropriate
for younger viewers.
Things like
the following half-hour.
Nothing seems to bother
my kids,
but tonight's show--
which I totally
wash my hands of--
is really scary.
So, if you have
sensitive children,
maybe you should tuck them
into bed early tonight
instead of writing us
angry letters tomorrow.
Thanks for your attention.
♪♪
(screams and howls)
Ooh, what a haul this year.
I love Halloween.
Heh, heh.
Wait a minute.
Let's see what
the kids are up to.
...and the policeman on the
other end of the phone said
"We have traced the call.
"It's coming from
the floor below you.
Get out of the house!"
But it was too late.
End of story.
Yawn. I heard that when
I was in the third grade.
It's not scary.
-Is too!
-Is not.
-Is not!
-Is too.
Fine!
Then you tell one scarier.
Flashlight, please.
Here's a story
that's really scarifying.
LISA:
Oh, brother.
I call it...
(Bart laughing maniacally)
That's all of it.
Sign here.
There you are, my man,
and a dollar
for yourself.
A buck. I'm glad there's
a curse on this place.
Huh?
Well, it's all ours.
I still can't believe
how inexpensive it was.
Motivated seller, Marge.
Well, he certainly
must have been motivated.
Prime location,
18 bedrooms, moat.
We shouldn't be able
to afford this.
So we got a good deal
for once.
Quit fighting it.
It just seems too good
to be true.
Ow! Mom, Bart threw
a book at me!
-Did not.
-Did too!
-Did not!
MALE VOICE:
Get out!
MARGE:
What on Earth was that?
Hmm. Probably just
the house settling.
(Marge groans)
Hmm, this kitchen certainly
could use a woman's touch.
Homer!
What's this thing
in the corner?
-I dunno.
-It looks like a vortex--
a gateway
into another dimension.
Ooh, a vortex.
Catch!
Hey, pretty slick.
Huh?
"Quit throwing your garbage
into our dimension."
Mom, Dad!
Help!
(gagging)
MALE VOICE:
Get out.
Okay, boy, let's see you
talk yourself out of this one.
I can feel an evil presence
in this house.
-Evil?
-Quiet, Lisa.
You're scaring
your mother.
Children, get your coats.
We're leaving this house right now.
Now wait a minute, Marge.
It's only natural there
would be some things wrong
with an old house
like this.
It's a fixer-upper.
What's the problem?
We get a bunch of priests in here--
I'm not going to live
in a house of evil
just to save a few dollars.
Don't be so stubborn!
We're not talking about
a few dollars.
We're talking about
a few thousand dollars!
(screaming)
Ooh! It's got great
high ceilings.
(screaming)
Tell you what,
let's, um, sleep on it, okay?
All right,
but if anything happens--
What could happen?
Mmm...
MALE VOICE: They are all
against you, Bart.
You must kill them all.
They all must die.
Are you my conscience?
I...
Yes, I am.
Lisa. Lisa.
The butcher knife, Lisa.
They are all against me.
They all must die.
Marge.
Oh, Marge?
MARGE:
I'm in the kitchen, Homer.
MALE VOICE:
Die! Die!
Everybody, die.
(maniacal laughter)
(gasping)
What's going on
out here?
Homer, Bart, Lisa, Maggie,
stop it!
-Sorry. Sorry, Bart.
-Sorry, Dad.
Sorry, Mom.
Sorry, Mag.
Well, that does it.
Children, get dressed.
We're leaving.
Ah, c'mon Marge, you said
you'd sleep on it.
I don't care what I said.
This family has had its differences,
and we've squabbled,
but we never had
knife fights before,
and I blame this house.
Mom, Dad, look!
LISA: It's an ancient
Indian burial ground.
BART: Man, this place
has got everything.
An ancient Indian what?
Mr. Plute,
Homer Simpson here.
When you sold me this house
you forgot to mention
one little thing.
You didn't tell me it was built
on an Indian burial ground!
No. You. Didn't!
Well, that's not
my recollection.
Yeah, well--
All right, good-bye.
He says he mentioned it
five or six times.
Let's go, children.
-Aw, gee, Marge.
-Homer--
MALE VOICE:
You will die.
You will die slowly.
Your stomach will swell.
Your intestines
will writhe and boil.
Your eyes will burst
and some horrible stuff--
possibly your brains--
will start coming out
through your nose.
Shush! Shut up!
Quit trying to push us around!
Stop saying
those horrible things
and show some manners!
Look at me.
I've never been so angry.
My hands are shaking.
Better than
your eyes bursting.
-Do it again.
-What?
-Make the walls bleed.
-No.
Hey, man, we own you.
Let's see some blood.
I don't have to
entertain you.
Come on, man, do it.
Do the blood thing.
C'mon! Do it! Do it! Do it!
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Why are you
trying to scare us?
Are you trying to keep us
from getting close to you?
Maybe even loving you?
Leave me alone.
Don't talk to her
like that.
Hey listen, lady...
Don't call me lady.
My name is Marge Simpson.
This is my family
and we're not going anywhere.
We're all going
to have to live together
so you better
get used to it. Please.
Can I have a minute
to think about this?
Sure.
Hmm...
Life with the Simpsons.
What choice do I have?
(rumbling)
-HOMER: Wow.
-BART: Bitchin'!
It chose to destroy itself
rather than live with us.
You can't help
but feel a little rejected.
-(Homer shudders)
-LISA: That wasn't scary at all, Bart.
Oh yeah? Well, how about...
this severed finger?!
-Eww, baby spit!
-(laughing)
Well, that last story
was just a warm-up
for this macabre tale
which I call...
Homer, all these flies.
Not to worry.
I'll just turn on
the trusty bug zapper.
-(flies buzzing)
-(zapping)
Ooh, that was a big mama.
Heh-heh-heh.
(humming)
That should just about do it.
Man alive,
there's nothing better
than a hamburger grilled
to perfection--
Cool, man!
(gasping)
Your burgers
are getting cold, guy--
Holy moly.
(screaming)
Huh?
(quivering)
Greetings, Earthlings.
I am Kang.
Do not be frightened.
We mean you no harm.
You speak English.
I am actually
speaking Rigellian.
By an astonishing
coincidence,
both of our languages
are exactly the same.
Well, what are you gonna
do with us, man?
Kodos and I are taking you
to Rigel Four--
a world of infinite delights
to tantalize your senses
and challenge
your intellectual limitations.
Look, I know that to you
we Simpsons are
a lower order of life.
We face that prejudice
every day of our lives,
but we are happy
on our little planet.
We throw ourselves
on your mercy.
-Please return us to--
-KODOS: Dinnertime.
Hey, get a load
of that spread.
Here you go, Earthlings.
Take all you want,
but eat all you take.
Well, thank you
very much, mister...?
To pronounce it correctly,
I would have to
pull out your tongue.
Eww.
-Fried shrimp.
-Sloppy Joes.
Smothered pork chops.
Look Homer,
radish rosettes.
These are hard to make.
They're a very advanced race.
Come, Earthlings, eat.
Grow large with food.
There's something
not quite right about this.
The girl's right.
Let's get some applesauce
out here for these pork chops.
What are you
looking at, buddy?
Your wife is
quite a dish.
Ooh, thanks.
KANG: It is our great
pleasure to provide you
with unlimited
entertainment on your...
intergalactic journey.
On this cable system,
we receive over one million
channels from the furthest
reaches of the galaxy.
You get HBO?
No. That would cost extra.
And over here is
our crowning achievement
in amusement technology--
an electronic version
of what you call table tennis.
Your primitive paddles
have been replaced by an electronic--
Hey, that's just Pong.
Get with the times, man.
Marge and I played that old
game before we were married.
Well, we did build
this spaceship, you know.
Anyone from a species
that has mastered
intergalactic travel,
raise your hand.
All right, then.
Sorry.
Your game is very nice.
Dinnertime.
Hey, how come we
never see you guys eat?
Oh, we wouldn't
want to spoil our appetite
for... the great feast
when we land on Rigel Four.
Ooh, a feast!
Will we be invited?
Oh, you'll be at the feast.
I have a feeling
you'll be the guests of honor.
(ominous laughter)
Tell us more about this feast.
No, no, eat now.
When we arrive,
there will be
plenty of time
to chew the fat.
(laughter)
Very good, Earth boy.
(oohing and ahhing)
Excellent, Mr. Simpson.
Excellent.
(gasps)
This will give the humans
the perfect flavor.
(gasps)
Stop!
Don't you see
what's happening here?
They're fattening us up
so they can eat us!
Oh, come on, Lisa.
If you don't believe me,
then just look at this book
that I found.
(all gasp)
Look! She's right!
Humans,
you have stopped eating.
Listen, you big, stupid
space creature.
Nobody, but nobody
eats the Simpsons.
-I beg your pardon?
-Don't play dumb with me.
We found your book.
You mean this?
It's a harmless cookbook.
It's just a little dusty.
(sighs of relief)
Wait a minute.
-Aha!
-(gasping)
Wait. There's still more
space dust on here.
(sighs of relief)
Let me get this straight.
You thought--
They thought we were
going to eat them.
Good God, is this
some kind of joke?
No. They're serious.
Well why were you trying
to make us eat all the time?
Make you eat? We merely
provided a sumptuous banquet,
and, frankly, you people
made pigs of yourselves.
I slaved in the kitchen
for days
for you people and--
Well, if you wanted to make
Shiroc the Preparer cry,
mission accomplished.
SHIROC: You aren't the only beings
who have emotions, you know.
We offered you paradise.
You would have
experienced emotions
100 times greater
than what you call love,
and 1000 times greater
than what you call fun.
You would have been
treated like gods
and lived forever
in beauty,
but, now, because of
your distrustful nature,
that can never be.
For a superior race,
they really rub it in.
There were monsters
on that ship,
and truly we were them.
MARGE: Lisa, see what we mean
when we say
you're too smart
for your own good?
-BART: Way to go, Lise.
-HOMER: Yeah, thanks, Lisa.
(Marge groans)
(gagging)
Hello.
Something scary happening.
(gagging)
Hey, Poindexter,
it's Halloween.
Put the book away.
For your information,
I'm about to read you
a classic tale of terror
by Edgar Allan Poe.
Wait a minute.
That's a school book.
Don't worry, Bart,
you won't learn anything.
It's called...
"Once upon a midnight dreary...
NARRATOR: "While I pondered,
weak and weary
"over many a quaint
and curious volume
"of forgotten lore--
"while I nodded,
nearly napping,
"suddenly there came a tapping
-(tapping at door)
-(Homer shrieks)
"as of some one
gently rapping,
rapping at my chamber door.
-'Tis some visitor..."
-I muttered,
"...tapping at my chamber door;
Only this, and nothing more."
BART:
Are we scared yet?
LISA: Bart,
he's establishing mood.
(snoring)
NARRATOR:
"Ah, distinctly I remember
"it was in
the bleak December,
"and each separate
dying ember
"wrought its ghost
upon the floor.
"Eagerly
I wished the morrow;
"vainly I had sought
to borrow
from my books
surcease of sorrow--"
Hmm? Huh?
Sorrow for
the lost Lenore--"
Oh, Lenore.
"For the rare
and radiant maiden
"whom the angels named
Lenore--
nameless here forevermore."
Ah!
(teeth chattering)
"And the silken, sad
uncertain rustling
"of each purple curtain
thrilled me--
"Filled me
with fantastic terrors
"never felt before;
"so that now, to still
the beating of my heart
"I stood repeating...
'tis a visitor entreating
entrance at my chamber door;
This it is,
and nothing more.
"Presently my soul
grew stronger;
"hesitating then no longer
-Sir...
-"Said I...
...or madam,
truly your forgiveness
I implore;
but the fact is,
I was napping
and so gently you came rapping
and so faintly you came tapping,
tapping at my chamber door.
That I scarce
was sure I heard you.
"Here I opened wide
the door;"
BART:
This better be good.
"Darkness there,
and nothing more."
Huh?
BART:
You know what would have been
scarier than nothing?
-What?
-Anything!
"Back into the chamber
turning,
"all my soul within me
burning,
"Soon again I heard
a tapping,
-"something louder than before.
-(knocking)
-(screams) Surely,
-"said I,
surely that is something
at my window-lattice;
Let me see then,
what thereat is
and this mystery explore.
"Open here I flung
the shutter,
"when, with many
a flirt and flutter,
"in there stepped
a stately raven
"of the saintly days
of yore.
"Not the least obeisance
made he;
"Not a minute
stopped or stayed he
"but with mien of
lord or lady,
"perched above
my chamber door--
"Perched upon
a bust of Pallas
"just above
my chamber door--
"Perched, and sat,
and nothing more.
(laughs)
Though thy crest
-be shorn and shaven, thou,
-"I said,
art sure no craven,
ghastly grim and ancient raven
wandering from
the nightly shore--
Tell me,
tell me
what thy lordly name is
on the night's
Plutonian shore.
Quoth the raven..."
-Eat my shorts.
-Bart, stop it.
He says "Nevermore"
and that's all he'll ever say.
BART: Okay, okay.
Ooh.
(sniffing)
Hmm.
"Then, methought,
the air grew denser,
"perfumed by
some unseen censer...
-D'oh! Stupid censer.
-"...swung by Seraphim
"whose footfalls
tinkled on the tufted floor.
-Wretch.
-"I cried,
thy God hath lent thee--
By these angels
he hath sent thee
respite and nepenthe
from thy memories of Lenore!
Quaff, o, quaff
this kind nepenthe
and forget this lost Lenore!
"Quoth the raven
-Nevermore!
-D'oh!
Be that word
our sign of parting,
bird or fiend!
"I shrieked, upstarting--
Get thee back into the tempest,
and the night's
Plutonian shore!
Leave no black plume
as a token of the lie
thy soul hath spoken!
Leave my loneliness unbroken!
Quit the bust above my door!
Take thy beak
from out my heart
and take thy form
from off my door!
-"Quoth the raven"
-Nevermore!
Take thy beak
from out my heart
and take thy form
from off my door.
-"Quoth the raven
-Nevermore!
-Why you little--
-Uh-oh!
(grunting, shouting)
Come back here,
you little raven!
(grunting, shouting)
D'oh! It missed. (shouts)
(echoing) Nevermore, nevermore,
nevermore, nevermore.
(grunting, shouting)
(shouts)
Ow! D'oh!
"And the raven,
"never flitting,
still is sitting,
"still is sitting
on the pallid bust of Pallas
"just above my chamber door;
"And his eyes
have all the seeming
"of a demon's
that is dreaming.
"And the lamplight
o'er him streaming
"throws his shadow
on the floor;
"and my soul
from out that shadow
"that lies floating
on the floor
"shall be lifted--
nevermore!"
Heh, heh, heh.
Lisa, that wasn't scary.
Not even for a poem.
Well, it was written in 1845.
Maybe people were easier to
scare back then.
Oh, yeah.
Like when you look at
"Friday the 13th, Part One."
It's pretty tame
by today's standards.
MARGE:
Children, bedtime!
I guess I'll have no trouble
getting to sleep tonight.
(Homer shuddering)
Oh, no, Marge!
Come on, please.
Homer, I'm not sleeping
with the lights on.
They're just
children's stories.
They can't hurt you.
(quavering)
Heh, heh, heh!
Oh...
Oh, I hate Halloween.
(wolf howls)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.