♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
A dash of rosemary,
a smidgen of thyme,
a pinch of marjoram...
You know, Marge, you make the best
pork chops in the whole world.
Oh, now Homer,
they're nothing special.
The extra ingredient
is care.
A sprinkle of chervil
half a teaspoon
of turmeric
and a whisper of M.S.G.
Marge, I'm gonna
build you a spice rack.
You don't have to go to all
that trouble just for me.
It's no trouble-- I got a whole
garage full of tools I never use.
Hey, kids! I spy Itchy and Scratchy
off the port bow.
(chuckling)
-BART: Hey, down in front.
-HOMER: Shut up, boy.
♪ They fight and fight ♪
♪ They fight and fight
and fight ♪
♪ Fight-fight-fight,
fight-fight-fight ♪
♪ The Itchy
and Scratchy Show! ♪
I knew all this stuff
would come in handy someday.
Lets see now.
Ah, here it is--
The Complete
Handyman's Bookshelf,
Volume One: Spice Racks.
"Pick up a hammer." Hmm.
(mumbling)
(grunts)
It's not as easy
as I thought it was.
(mumbling)
Ooh!
(gasps)
Wow!
♪♪ (theme from
"Psycho" starts)
(gasps)
(screaming)
Hey, Dad, can you
move your head?
No, I can't.
It's broken.
Hmm. Where would
an innocent child get the idea
to attack her father
with a mallet?
(laughing)
(screams)
♪♪ (theme from "Psycho"
playing)
(screams)
No, Maggie! Bad baby!
Keep her away from me, Marge!
She's got that crazy look
in her eyes again!
MARGE:
So, television's responsible.
Hey, we were watching that!
Mom, what are you doing?
Well, you won't
be watching
these cartoons
anymore. Ever.
But, Mom if you take
our cartoons away,
we'll grow up without
a sense of humor and be robots.
Really? What kind of robots?
I heard about the cartoons.
-Tough break, man.
-Thanks, Nelson.
Hey, what if you watch
"Itchy and Scratchy" over at my house?
Hey, that's just
crazy enough to work.
You heard me.
I won't be in
for the rest of the week.
I told you.
My baby beat me up.
Oh, it is not the worst excuse
I ever thought up. Wise guy.
Hmm. I wonder why
Bart and Lisa
are so late getting home
from school?
(laughing)
Hey, how come you
can watch cartoons
but the kids can't?
-Because.
-Because why?
-Because I said so.
-Because you said so why?
-Homer, I'm trying to work.
-Oh. What are you doing?
I'm cataloguing the violence
in these cartoons.
I don't think adults have ever actually
sat down and watched them before.
(cries out)
What kind of warped human being
would find that funny?
(laughing)
(groaning)
This is the kind
of entertainment
they think is suitable
for younger
and more
impressionable viewers?
Yeah, but what
are you going to do?
I'll tell you
what I'm going to do.
I'm going
to write a letter!
"Dear purveyors
"of senseless violence:
"I know this may
sound silly at first,
"but I believe
that the cartoons
"you show to our children
"are influencing their behavior
in a negative way.
"Please try to tone down
the psychotic violence
"in your otherwise
fine programming.
Yours truly,
Marge Simpson."
Take a letter, Miss White.
"Dear valued viewer,
thank you for taking an interest
"in the 'Itchy
and Scratchy' program.
"Enclosed is a personally
autographed photo
"of America's favorite cat-and-mouse team
to add to your collection.
"In regards to your specific
comments about the show,
"our research indicates
"that one person
cannot make a difference,
"no matter how big
a screwball she is.
So let me close by saying..."
"And the horse
I rode in on"?
I'll show them
what one screwball can do!
Everybody's looking
at us, Marge.
That's what we want them
to do, Homer.
Oh. Hmm.
HOMER: Well, how long are we going
to have to be doing this?
MARGE: Well, I've never
changed the world before
so I don't know
how long it takes, exactly.
But if enough people
take an interest...
Hello, Marge.
Oh, what is S.N.U.H.?
-Snuh.
-Oh.
It stands for "Springfieldians
for Non-Violence
-Understanding and Helping."
-Hmm.
I've started a crusade
against cartoon violence.
-Mm-hmm.
-I can protect my own children,
but there are many others
whose minds are being warped
-every afternoon at 4.
-Oh.
That reminds me.
I got to get over to
Milhouse's and... play sports.
-All right.
-And I'm going to Janie's again.
We're going to be, um,
making the most
of our childhood years.
-Have fun.
-BOTH: We will.
(Bart and Lisa laugh)
And what happens when
a child grows up
with insanely violent
role models like these?
The answer is all around you.
How many of you were hit on the head
with mallets last week?
(crowd murmurs)
MAN: Yeah!
Yeah!
(cheering)
I didn't know they still made
TV dinners this bad.
-After dinner, can I watch cartoons?
-No!
-There's peas in my fruit cobbler!
-There's peas everywhere.
Well, I guess I'll just go
and watch some cartoons.
No! I'm sorry
about the dinners.
I'll make up for it
tomorrow night.
Hey, who's up
for some cartoons?
-No one!
-All right.
Hey, tomorrow night,
how about baking
some of your patented
pork chops?
Sure.
Oh, dear, I can't.
I've got three
protest rallies tomorrow.
D'oh! 20 million women
in the world
and I had to marry
Jane Fonda.
Hi, kids! (laughs)
Guess what, Sideshow Mel?
(whistling)
It's time
for "Itchy and Scratchy."
(booing)
Hey, settle down,
boys and girls
or Krusty will have to
bring out his old friend
Corporal Punishment again.
-(booing)
-Please, stop it!
What's going--
Who are you people?
What do we want?
Substantially less violence
in children's programming!
-When do we want it?
-Now!
No! You're ruining the show!
(angry chanting)
Stop!
Please, stop.
Oh, please,
please, be quiet.
I'm trying to earn a living here, alright?
Please, stop!
(nervous chuckle)
That woman,
That screwball
Marge Simpson,
we've got to stop her.
-But how?
-Drop an anvil on her?
Hit her on the head
with a piano.
Stuff her full of T.N.T.
Then throw a match
down her throat and run?
All your fancy degrees,
and that's the best you can do?
-You make me sick.
-(murmurs of agreement)
(crowd chanting) Substantially
less violence in children's programming!
-When do we want it?
-Now!
Substantially less violence
in children's programming!
Eh.
Hmm...
Heh, I'm so funny.
♪ Fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight ♪
(laughing)
You know,
some of these stories
are pretty good.
I never knew mice lived
such interesting lives.
So much needless brutality.
I don't know if I'm having
any impact at all.
♪♪ ("Take Me Out
to the Ball Game" )
Don't do that!
Hey! Don't do that!
(Homer laughing)
Take that,
you dumb squirrel!
(phone ringing)
Where do they get
their ideas?
What is it?
What? "Smartline"?
Yes, I've heard of your late-night
panel discussion show.
-Well, I'd love to!
-(slams phone)
MAN: "Smartline"...
with our local Emmy
Award-winning host
Kent Brockman.
Hello, I'm Kent Brockman
and welcome to another
edition of "Smartline."
Are cartoons too violent
for children?
Most people would say
"No, of course not.
What kind of stupid question
is that?"
But one woman says yes.
And she's here with us tonight.
Mrs. Marge Simpson.
There she is!
Also with us for this
"animated" discussion,
heh heh, are Roger Myers,
chairman of the Board of
Itchy & Scratchy International.
Thank you.
Krusty the Klown,
whose delightful program
brings us the antics
of Itchy and Scratchy
every afternoon at 4.
-Hi, Kent! (laughs)
-(horn honks)
And joining us live
via satellite from Vienna,
the home of Sigmund Freud,
the world's most famous psychiatrist,
to give us an insight
into the human mind,
-Dr. Marvin Monroe.
-Hiya.
Now, first, let's see what
all the excitement is about.
Here's an example of the work
currently being turned out
at I & S Studios.
♪♪ ("Funeral March
of a Marionette")
(screaming)
(chuckling quietly)
Hilarious. Now what in the world is wrong
with that, Mrs. Simpson?
-MYERS: There's nothing wrong with it.
-Excuse me.
Excuse me,
he was addressing me.
I know. There's nothing
wrong with it.
Excuse me, there is!
I think that it's a bad
influence on children.
Oh, give me a break!
I think that is a bunch
of baloney, and here's why.
In preparing for this debate,
I did a little research,
and I discovered
a startling thing.
There was violence in the past
long before cartoons
were invented.
I see. Fascinating.
Yeah, and there was
something called
the Crusades, for instance.
Tremendous violence,
many people killed!
The darned thing went on
for 30 years.
And this was before
cartoons were invented?
That's right, Kent.
-So much for your viewpoint.
-Hmm.
Dr. Marvin Monroe in Vienna,
would you care to
comment on all this?
Well Kent, to me, the hijinks
of a few comic characters
absolutely pale in comparison
with the crippling
emotional problems
a psychiatrist
runs into every day.
I'm referring here
to women who love too much,
fear of winning, sex-aholism,
stuff like that.
So you have
no professional objection
to "Itchy and Scratchy?"
No, not at all. In fact, one
of my guilty little pleasures
is to snuggle up with a big
bucket of buttered popcorn,
dim the lights, turn on "Itchy and
Scratchy," and laugh myself silly.
And what the hell
is wrong with that?
Not a thing.
Now, for another opinion...
(laughing)
Hi, kids!
(chuckling) Krusty, please.
We're giving you an opportunity
to participate
in a serious discussion here.
Oh, I'm sorry, Kent.
It's just when the camera
gets on me, I get--
Hey! Hey!
(laughing, horn squeaks)
-Krusty!
-(horn squeaks)
Well, it looks like we're not
going to settle this tonight.
Mrs. Simpson, in the nine
seconds we have left,
can you summarize
your position for us?
Yes. I'd like to ask
all the parents in Springfield
who are concerned
about this to write in
and let the cartoon makers
know how you feel. Thank you.
I don't believe this.
"I will never watch your show,
buy any of your products,
or brake if I see you
crossing the street."
Wow! That's cold.
MYERS:
"Dear sleaze merchant..."
Oh, come on, that hurts.
Gentlemen, the screwballs
have spoken.
(humming)
-(phone ringing)
-Hello?
-Is this Marge Simpson?
-Yes.
The Marge Simpson who fixed it
so cartoons can't be violent anymore?
Yes.
This is Myers.
I'm here with the writers.
Listen, you're so smart,
how do we end this picture?
Hmm, well, what's the
problem you're having?
Okay, here it is. Itchy just
stole Scratchy's ice cream cone, and--
Oh, make it a pie.
Pies are easier to draw.
Okay, a pie!
-Anyway, Scratchy is understandably upset,
-Uh-huh.
so we figured he could,
you know,
just grab Itchy and toss him
in a bucket of acid.
Oh, dear!
But then we remembered
that this might be
interpreted as violence,
which is morally wrong now,
thanks to you.
So what's your big idea?
How do we end this?
Let's see, um...
Oh, couldn't Itchy share
his pie with Scratchy?
Then they would both have pie.
It's different,
I'll give you that.
ANNOUNCER: It's a tool
that every home handyman needs.
It's a jigsaw. It's a power drill.
It's a wood-turning lathe.
It's an asphalt spreader.
It's 67 tools in one.
How much would you pay for
a machine that could do all this?
-$1,000.
-Oh, don't answer yet.
-Oh sorry.
-Because you also get--
HOMER: Hey, I was
watching that.
It's time for Krusty.
You mean we can watch
cartoons again, Mom?
Yes, dear, all you want.
-All right!
Turn it up.
KRUSTY: Hey kids. It's time
for "Itchy and Scratchy."
♪ They love, they share ♪
♪ They share and love
and share ♪
♪ Love, love, love,
share, share, share ♪
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy Show! ♪
(chairs squeaking)
Lemonade?
Please.
I made it just for you.
You are my best friend.
Itchy and Scratchy seem
to have lost their edge.
Well, I think it conveys
a very nice message of sharing.
I think it sucks.
-♪♪ ("Psycho" theme)
-(screams)
Oh. Hey,
thank you, Maggie.
Mmm, this really
hits the spot.
Hmm. Doesn't it,
though?
You make really good
lemonade, Scratchy.
(chuckles)
Thank you, Itchy.
Wasn't that funny,
boys and girls?
Well? Wasn't it?
Aren't you going to watch
the rest of your cute cartoons?
Nah, come on, Lise.
Maybe there's something else
to do on this planet.
♪♪
But the third bowl
of porridge was just right.
(playing Beethoven's
Sixth "Pastoral" Symphony)
(dog barking)
Hi, kids!
(chuckles)
Uh... is this Saturday?
So, what did you kids do today?
Me and the guys went fishing.
I almost caught
a catfish this big!
-Oh.
-And Janey and I went bird-watching.
-We saw a grackle.
-Oh, that's nice, dear.
C'mon, Lise. Let's go finish
our soap box racers.
Okay.
May we please be excused?
-Sure.
-(chuckles) Wow!
What great kids.
This is a golden age, Marge.
And the parents of Springfield
owe it all to you.
Hmm. I didn't really expect
things to change this much.
Well, I always knew you'd
change the world for the better.
This will be the art event
of the century.
The greatest masterpiece
of Italian renaissance.
Michelangelo's "David"
on a coast-to-coast tour
of the United States.
Sir, which cities will be included
in your itinerary?
-New York.
-Mm-hmm.
-Springfield.
-Yes.
And if we have time,
-Chicago, Boston, Los Angeles.
-Oh.
(angry chatter)
(snoring)
(knocking)
Marge, get the door.
What in the world?
(pounding intensifies)
Get dressed, Marge.
You've got to lead
our protest
against this abomination.
Hmm, but that's
Michelangelo's "David."
-It's a masterpiece.
-It's filth.
It graphically portrays
parts of the human body
which, practical as
they may be, are evil.
But I like that statue.
I told you she was soft
on full frontal nudity.
Come on, girls.
What is this all about?
What do you people want?
We want you to get your big
Italian butt out of here.
MAN: "Smartline," with our
local Emmy award-winning host
Kent Brockman.
Is it a masterpiece
or just some guy
with his pants down?
That's our topic tonight
on "Smartline."
Now, Mrs. Simpson, why are
you against this statue?
I'm not. I think everyone
in Springfield should see it.
Wait a minute. Aren't you
Marge Simpson, the wacko?
(groaning)
-Yes and no.
-MAN: Hold it!
How can you be for one form
of freedom of expression,
like our big naked friend
over there, and be against
another form
like "Itchy and Scratchy?"
-(groans)
-Good question.
Well, I guess I can't,
which is a shame,
because I really hate
those cartoons.
Oh yeah? Well, what
do you have to say
to all those Marge Simpson
wannabees out there
who wish to suppress
David's doodle?
Hmm, I don't know.
I guess one person
can make a difference,
but most of the time,
they probably shouldn't.
Well, I guess that
settles that.
I'd like to
alert our affiliates
that we will be ending
our show early tonight.
Join us tomorrow,
when our topic will be
"Religion: which
is the one true faith?"
♪♪ (playing sad version
of Beethoven's Sixth Symphony)
(screaming)
(laughing)
Well, there he is.
-Michelangelo's "Dave."
-"David."
Oh. What's wrong, Marge?
Ah, Homie. Here the kids have a chance
to see a great work of art,
and instead, they're home watching
a cat and mouse disembowel each other.
Hey, don't worry, Marge.
Pretty soon, every boy and girl
in Springfield Elementary School
is gonna
come and see this thing.
Really? Why?
They're forcing them!
(laughing)
Oh. Well,
isn't that nice.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.