♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
ANNOUNCER: Live from
the Springfield Center
for the Performing Arts,
the wrestling match
of the century.
Today, Rasputin,
the friendly Russian.
Didn't he used to be
the Mad Russian?
Yes, but I'm afraid
the forces of history
have changed wrestling
perhaps forever.
And the challenger from
the University of Heidelberg
Professor Werner Von Brawn.
That's Brawn with a "W."
Two titans at the height
of their careers.
Oh, if you ask me...
this is going to be
one hell of a match.
Oh Bart, I hope you're
not taking this seriously.
Even a five-year-old knows
that this is as choreographed
as any ballet.
Rasputin's got the reach
but on the other hand,
the Professor's got his
patented "coma lock."
If you ask me, this is
gonna be one hell of a match.
MOE: Oh, look
at that show-off.
-Kissing his own muscles. Bull!
-(burping)
Rasputin is spinning
the Professor
like an auto-gyro.
That's got to be
disorienting.
Hey, Milhouse, crank it up.
Hey, that's my seat.
Correction: was your seat.
But I only got up
to go to the can.
Hey, I don't see your name
engraved on this bar stool.
One... two... three...
four... five... six...
seven... eight... nine...
The ref is issuing
a warning to Rasputin.
-CROWD: Boo!
-(clank)
ANNOUNCER:
Oh, my, oh, my!
Why is the referee
permitting this?
-CROWD: Boo! Boo! Hiss!
-(bell rings)
Boo! Hiss! Boo!
Boo! Boo!
This Saturday,
for one night only,
your life will
be changed forever.
Saturday, Saturday, Saturday!
At the Springfield Speedway,
Speedway, Speedway!
Don "Crusher" Woodard!
John "The Skunk" Tremaine!
And the Team Kamaratsu
dirt-riding dunk-masters
at the year's biggest
monster truck rally!
One night only.
Plus the amazing
the astounding,
the unbelievable--
Truckasaurus!
Twenty tons and four stories
of car-crunching
fire-breathing,
prehistoric insanity!
-TOGETHER: Whoa!
-One night only!
One night only! One night only
at the Springfield Speedway!
This Saturday! If you miss this,
you'd better be dead or in jail.
And if you're in jail,
break out!
Be there! Be there!
(echoing)
Be there!
(tires squeal)
-Truckasaurus!
(glass clinking)
I have an announcement to make.
As a family growth thing,
Bart and I think
we should all go
to the monster truck rally
this Saturday.
Aren't you forgetting
something?
Uh... Monster truck rally...
growth thing...
No, I don't think so.
Lisa's recital
is Saturday night.
I'll be playing my first solo.
If you miss it on Saturday,
I'd advise you to start looking
for a child therapist on Sunday.
But Truckasaurus
is one night only!
Oh, cruel fate,
why do you mock me?
-(crying)
Now come on, you two.
What time does your little
truck game start?
8:00, but what does it matter?
Well, Lisa's recital
starts at 5:00.
-We can go to both.
-(gasps)
Marge, you're a genius.
People, let's have good
assembly manners, please. Hmm?
-People. People!
-(instruments tuning)
Quiet down now, please.
Don't make me flick
the lights on and off.
Thank you.
Ladies, gentlemen,
parents and music lovers.
Welcome to the first in a series
of Saturday evening concerts.
Series? Oh!
Tonight, Sherbert's--
(chuckles)
Schubert's Unfinished Symphony.
Oh good. Unfinished.
-This shouldn't take long.
-(groans)
-(tapping)
-Remember, children. Stay together.
Five, six, seven, eight...
♪♪ (Unfinished Symphony plays)
(saxophone solo)
-That was beautiful.
-(solo continues)
Can we go now?
-Sit down, Homer.
-Grrr!
How much longer was Sherbert
planning on making
this piece of junk?
Oh, my, Lisa was wonderful.
She certainly has come a long
way with her fingering.
Thanks, Flanders.
Big know-it-all.
-When's Todd's solo, Dad?
-Shh.
It's coming up, son.
It's coming up.
(violin solo begins )
(sniffling )
My son, my son.
Come on, Flanders.
He's not that bad.
♪♪ ("1812 Overture" plays)
(loud clanging)
(cheering and applause)
(Homer humming
"1812 Overture" and honking)
-I reached him.
-Homer, drive defensively.
HOMER: Sometime's the best defense
is a good offense.
Faster, Dad.
Truckasaurus awaits.
HOMER:
Damn, no spots.
Oh, I think there's
one over there.
(crowd yelling)
-Dad?
-Not now, Lisa. Come on.
-Homer?
-HOMER: What?
It's Truckasaurus!
Where? Where?
(screaming)
(screaming continues)
(roaring)
Pull! Pull, you dogs!
MECHANIC:
Well, let's see here.
Cracked windshield,
melted bumpers,
punctured radiator,
teeth marks on the trunk.
(chuckles)
On the plus side
there doesn't seem
to be any frame damage.
This check should take care
of everything.
-Thank you so much.
-Mrs. Simpson?
I'm Leo G. Clark, inventor, owner
and operator of Truckasaurus.
Let me just say that, Truckasaurus
feels very badly about what happened
and everyone here at Team Truckasaurus
would like you to enjoy
this half bottle of domestic champagne
for being such good sports.
Mmm. Well, thank you.
Gee, everyone's so nice here
at the Monster Truck Rally.
-Look Homer, champagne!
-(straining)
ANNOUNCER (on P.A.): And now,
Majestic Undercoating is proud to present:
Ms. Monster!
Wow, a woman mud-pull driver.
Another barrier broken.
Ride on, sister!
Let the destruction begin!
Hey, they forgot my corn dog.
Give me some nachos,
Homersaurus.
Here you go, Bartasaurus.
(both chuckle)
ANNOUNCER: For our last event
of the evening,
we have a special
surprise guest!
The world's greatest daredevil.
The man who's no stranger
to danger.
If he's not in action,
he's in traction.
Captain Lance Murdock!
(cheering and applause)
Ladies and gentlemen
and especially little children,
I'm glad you're all here
to witness
what may very well be
my grisly death.
Tonight,
my most dangerous stunt.
I will death defy
both nature and gravity
by leaping over
this tank of water
filled with man-eating
great white sharks,
deadly electric eels,
ravenous piranhas,
bone-crushing alligators,
and perhaps the most
frightening of all,
the king of the jungle,
one ferocious lion!
-Ohh!
Oh, and...
(laughing)
I almost forgot.
To add a real element of danger,
one drop of human blood.
And on chance I don't survive,
let me just say:
seat belts save lives,
so buckle up.
This is so cool.
Oh, I can't watch!
-(tires screech)
-He made it!
(cheering)
(gasping)
Bitchin'!
ANNOUNCER:
He's okay, folks.
(cheering)
(muffler rattles)
What a fun-filled evening.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
the ten-year-old
who's brave and bold.
When he's not in class,
he's risking his ass.
The world's greatest daredevil,
Bart Simpson!
(chanting)
Bart! Bart! Bart!
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
Bart, Bart.
-We're home, son.
-Huh?
Dad, I want to be a daredevil.
(chuckles)
Kids say such stupid things.
You're crazy, Bart.
You're never gonna make it.
Spare me your lectures, ladies.
-Ahh!
-(gasping)
Oh, no, he's hurt.
-Bad.
-Let's get out of here.
Oh, my little boy.
(kissing)
Come on Marge,
we're mad at him.
-Are you all right?
-Better than all right.
-I got stitches.
-TOGETHER: Eww.
Probably a scar too.
Mrs. Simpson, Bart tells me
he injured himself
training for a career
in death defiance?
Yes, well we saw
a daredevil last night,
and, well, you know,
monkey see, monkey do.
Hmm. I think I know something
that might discourage him
from this sort of behavior.
Bart, in this ward
are the children
who have been hurt
by imitating stunts
they saw on television,
movies and the legitimate stage.
This little boy broke his leg
trying to fly like Superman.
This boy's brother
hit him in the head
with a wrench,
mimicking a recent
TV wrestling match.
I won't even subject you to the horrors
of our Three Stooges ward.
Gee, I never realized TV was
such a dangerous influence.
Well, as tragic
as all this is,
it's a small price to pay
for countless hours
of top-notch entertainment.
Amen, huh, Bart?
Has Dr. Hibbert
made his point?
He certainly has, Dad.
I learned a real
lesson here today.
-Thank you, Dr. Hibbert.
-Mmm.
(grunts)
I did it.
-Wow!
-All right!
-(cheering)
-BOY: Cool! Way happening, Bart!
-Awesome!
-Aw, man, you're the king.
-That was so cool.
-Thank you.
How about a hand for
these brave little animals.
(cheering)
(snoring)
Huh? Huh? Oh...
Hi, kids. Thanks.
Okay, field trippers,
off the bus.
What's the matter, Bart?
Aw, I'm runnin' on empty,
Milhouse.
You kids get a kick
out of my jumps
and I love you for it,
but it's all too easy.
There has got to be a challenge
out there worthy of me.
Hello, children, and welcome
to Springfield Gorge.
BART: Wow!
Man, this thing's pretty gnarly.
I bet you could throw
a dead body in there
and no one would ever find it.
Otto, I'm going to leap over
Springfield Gorge
on my skateboard.
You know, Bart,
as the only adult here,
I feel I should say something.
-What?
-Cool!
-(wind blows)
-(birds chirping)
♪♪ (Otto hums "Purple Haze")
Hey, Otto, can I use
that microphone?
♪ Do-do-do da-do-do-do... ♪
Sorry, Bart dude,
it's for emergencies only.
♪ Do-do-do da-do-do-do... ♪
But I want to tell them
about my jump.
Oh. Okay.
May I have your attention,
please?
This Saturday, I'll be jumping
over Springfield Gorge
on my skateboard.
There is a good possibility
I will plunge
to my bloody death.
Hope to see you there.
Thank you.
Springfield Gorge?
Bart, you'll be killed.
Lisa, I don't know how
to explain this, but I get
the same thrill out of
jumping over stuff
that you do from... reading.
Please, before you do anything
there's someone
I'd like you to talk to.
Thank you for arranging this,
Dr. Hibbert.
Oh, anything I can do to stem the tide
of entertainment-related injury.
Now children,
you're about to meet
the world's greatest daredevil,
Lance Murdock.
-Lance, this is Lisa and Bart Simpson.
-(groans)
Bart is one
of your biggest fans.
It's an honor, Lance.
How you feeling?
-Uh, I-- Ow.
-(bone snaps)
Doc, I heard a snap.
Mmm. I'm afraid
the bone's broken.
Well, that's all of them.
-(gasps)
-Don't worry, partner.
I've broken that thumb
dozens of times.
Hey! I bet you'd like
an autograph. Nurse?
Who should I make this out to?
Just Bart will be fine, sir.
"To Bart.
Thanks for visiting me
"at Springfield
General Hospital.
"Your visit was
a ray of sunshine
"on an otherwise cloudy day.
Your pal,
Captain Lance Murdock."
Wow, man.
-Thanks, Lance.
-You're welcome.
Take this thing
out of my mouth now.
Mr. Murdoch, my brother
is thinking about
jumping Springfield Gorge
on a skateboard.
Could you leave me with
the young'uns, please?
Now, let me start by saying
good for you, son.
It's always good to see young people
taking an interest in danger.
Now, a lot of people are gonna
be tellin' you you're crazy,
and maybe they're right,
but the fact of the matter is
bones heal,
chicks dig scars,
and the United States
of America
has the best doctor-to-daredevil
ratio in the world.
-But Captain Murdock!
-Thanks, Lance!
You're welcome,
little partner.
On your way out, tell the nurse
I'm ready for my sponge bath.
Another fringe benefit.
Nurse?
HOMER:
Springfield Gorge?
I thought we settled
this daredevil junk.
-Squealer.
-I'm sorry Bart,
but if you got hurt
or died,
despite the extra attention
I'd receive, I'd miss you.
Bart, I forbid you to jump
over that gorge.
-You can't.
-I can and do!
Go to your room, Bart!
There, I've done it.
I'm glad somebody
finally stepped in
and put an end to this nonsense
once and for all.
Hey man, you can tell me
not to do it,
but there's no way you can
watch me 24 hours a day.
And the minute
your back is turned,
I'm grabbing my skateboard
and heading for that gorge.
He's got us, Marge.
There's nothing we can do.
He's as good as dead.
(weeps)
You're his father. You've got to
try and reason with him.
No, that never works.
He's a goner.
Come on, Homer. A heart-to-heart talk
with your son.
You've got to try.
Okay, okay. I'll try.
Bart? Bart?
-Bart! What are you doing?
-Nothing.
You were on your way to jump
the gorge, weren't you?
-Maybe.
-Look, I know I can't stop you.
The only thing I can do
is ask you to promise me
you won't jump the gorge.
-Okay. I promise.
-D'oh!
-What's the matter?
-You didn't mean that.
Bart, this isn't one of
those phony baloney promises
I don't expect you
to keep.
If you make this promise,
you have to keep it.
-Why?
-Because if you don't,
I'll never believe
anything you say
-ever again.
-Oh, come on.
-I mean it, boy.
-Well, okay, Dad. I promise.
I will not jump
Springfield Gorge.
That's my boy.
How'd it go, Homer?
You know, Marge,
we got a pretty good kid there.
Well, he's got
a pretty good father.
(chuckles)
Where is he?
I thought he said noon.
Aw, he's just doing this
to build the suspense.
-Whoa, what a showman.
-Look! There he is.
Hey, boy, want to toss
the old...
D'oh! Why, that little liar!
I shoulda--
I was going
to play pickle with him.
(crowd oohing and aahing)
(vehicle approaching)
(tires screeching)
Bart!
(both grunting)
-Boo!
Hey, what gives?
Boy, I tried ordering you.
I tried punishing you,
and God help me,
I even tried reasoning with you,
and the only thing left for me to do
is jump the gorge myself.
What? Why?
Because that way,
you'll see what it's like
to witness a family member stupidly
risking his life for no good reason.
But Dad, you'll never make it.
Don't you think
I know that?
-Good-bye, son.
-Wait, Dad! Don't do it!
I won't jump anymore,
I promise.
Oh, thank God, thank God,
thank God.
-I love you, Dad.
-I love you, too, son.
You know, boy,
I don't think
I've ever felt
as close to you
as I do right--
Huh? What? (shouting)
(screaming)
-Ooh!
I'm going to make it!
This is the greatest thrill
of my life.
I'm king of the world.
Woo hoo! Woo hoo! I--
(screaming)
Ooh! Ow! Ooh! Oh!
(grunting)
(grunting continues)
Ow!
Ow! Ooh!
(siren wails)
(Homer screaming)
Ow! Ow! Ahh!
(grunting, crying out)
You think you got guts.
Try raising my kids.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.