♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
HOMER: D'oh!
-MRS. KRABAPPEL: Bart.
-BART: Huh?
MRS. KRABAPPEL: There will be
no further interruptions
during Martin's book report.
MARTIN:
"You're killing me, fish.
"Never have I seen
"a greater or more noble
thing than you, brother.
"Come on and kill me.
"I do not care
who kills who.
"To catch a fish.
"To kill a bull.
"To make love to a woman.
To live."
I thank you.
Oh, absolutely brilliant!
There were moments
I truly believed
you were Hemingway.
Bravo, Martin.
Oh, please,
call me Papa.
A little ketchup
for your buns, Papa?
-Ooh!
-All right, class, all right.
I think we have time
for one more report.
-Bart Simpson?
-Oh!
Is your book report on
"Treasure Island" ready?
Is it ready?
Ha! What a question.
Fellow students,
prepare to be dazzled.
Well, as Mrs. Krabappel
already mentioned
the name of the book that
I read was "Treasure Island."
It's about these... pirates.
Pirates with patches
over their eyes...
and shiny gold teeth...
and green birds
on their shoulders.
Did I mention this book
was written by a guy named
Robert Louis Stevenson?
And published by the good
people at McGraw-Hill.
So, in conclusion
on the Simpson scale
of one to ten
ten being the highest,
one being the lowest
and five being average,
I give this book a nine.
Ahem. Any questions?
No? Then I'll just sit down.
Bart, did you read the book?
Mrs. Krabappel,
I am insulted.
Is this a book report
or a witch hunt?
Then perhaps you'd like to tell us
the name of the pirate.
(thinking)
Blackbeard, Captain Nemo,
Captain Hook,
Long John Silver,
Peg-Leg Pete, Bluebeard...
Bluebeard?
Sit down, Bart.
I'll see you after class.
Awww.
Your grades have gotten
steadily worse
since the beginning of
the term.
-Are you aware of that?
-Yes, ma'am.
Are you aware that there
is a major exam tomorrow
-on colonial America?
-Yes, ma'am.
Blah blah
blah blah blah...
-Yes, ma'am.
-Blah blah blah blah blah blah...
-Bart, you haven't been paying attention
-to a word I've said, have you?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Well then, what did I say?
-Uh...
Straighten up
and fly right?
That was a lucky guess.
Hyuh! Take that, granny!
Oh, hide in the closet.
Oh, no, deadly mothballs.
Ew! Granny's kissing me.
FEMALE VOICE:
You have reached the level
of ungrateful grandchild.
Try again, if you dare.
(granny giggling)
(evil laugh)
Just a couple more games
and I'll hit the books.
♪♪
(laughing)
Soup's on!
Hurry up,
or it will get that
icky skin on the top.
Ew, I hate that
icky soup skin.
Okay, right after dinner,
it's down to business.
Hmm. Marge, could you get me
another beer, please?
In a second, Homer.
Lisa has some good news.
He doesn't care, Mom.
Sure I do.
I just want to have a beer
while I'm caring.
-Marge?
-Homer!
-(gasps)
-Go ahead, Lisa.
Well, okay.
I got an "A"
on my vocabulary test.
(gasps) What?
You did?
Well, that's just...
Oh, what a glorious day!
Lisa, hand me your paper.
I'm just gonna take this
over to the refrigerator and--
Hmm... well,
as long as I'm here
I might as well kill
two birds with one stone.
What's the big idea?
You covered up my paper.
Heh-heh, look at those
funny little whiskers.
Ooh! That reminds me.
It's Big Gorilla Week
on Million Dollar Movie.
Come on, boy.
Uh, no, Dad.
I should really-- Hyuhh!
Ooh, Gorilla the Conqueror--
the granddaddy of them all.
(crowd screaming)
Oh, well,
maybe just one more hour.
(Homer crying)
It's so unfair.
Just because he's different.
Well, time
to hit the books.
(chuckles) Burning the candle
at both ends, eh, boy?
Go get 'em.
All right, okay.
Let's take care
of some business.
"Chapter One--
A dream of freedom.
"On September 15, 1620,
Puritan separatists
"from the Church of England,
some living in Holland,
"left Plymouth, England.
(yawns)
Their destination was..."
Psst! Marge?
Come take a look at this.
Oh, the little tiger
tries so hard.
Why does he
keep failing?
Just a little dim,
I guess.
MARGE: Bart, honey
you're going
to miss your bus.
Uh-oh.
Hey, Bart dude!
Ooh, you look freaked.
Hey, Otto man, I've got a big test
that I am not ready for.
Could you please
crash the bus or something?
Oh, sorry, little buddy.
Can't do it on purpose.
But hey, maybe
you'll get lucky.
Okay, no reason to panic.
Find an egghead,
pump him for some answers,
and boom! I'm back
on easy street.
Oh-ho.
Look at him.
I bet he didn't study again.
And now he's gonna try to
kiss up and get answers from us.
He's pathetic.
Good morning, girls.
BOTH: Good morning, Bart.
Say, who's up
for a little cram session?
I'll go first. What was the name
of the pilgrims' boat?
The Spirit
of St. Louis.
-And where'd they land?
-Sunny Acapulco.
And why'd they
leave England?
Giant rats.
Cool! History's
coming alive.
(girls giggling)
As a natural enemy,
I don't know
why I should care,
but the information
pertaining to
America's colonial period
that you've just received
-is erroneous.
-So you're saying...
A blindfolded chimp with
a pencil in his teeth
has a better chance
of passing this test
-than you do.
-(Bart groans)
-(school bell rings)
-Thanks for the pep talk.
All right students, take one
and pass the rest back.
(thinking)
Think, Simpson, think.
Crisis brings out
the best in you.
(groaning)
(scoffs)
What is it, Bart?
Nothing.
Must... take... test.
Ooh!
(groaning)
(whistling)
What's the matter, son?
Sharp, stabbing pains
in my stomach.
Oh, dear.
I've heard of this.
Do you feel a shooting pain
in your arm?
-Both arms, ma'am.
-Mm-hmm.
Temporary loss of vision?
Who said that?
Come closer.
-(bell ringing)
-Yes, dear?
Ahh. Maybe, um,
one more dish.
Make it double cappuccino
chocolate fudge.
Ooh, your third bowl.
I think you may be
on the mend.
Is there anything else
I can get you?
Hmm...
Perhaps the TV?
Of course. Homer!
-What?
-Bring the television up.
-Bart's got his vision back.
-D'oh!
(straining) I wish I had
amoria phlebitis.
Everyone knows
you're faking it, Bart.
Well, everyone better
keep their mouth shut.
You're gonna have to fail that
history test sooner or later.
-I've got my bases covered.
-(phone line ringing)
Hey, Milhouse, what'd
I miss in school today?
Nothin' much. Lewis made Richard laugh
milk through his nose.
Oh, you don't say. What about
that history test, huh?
Piece of cake, huh?
Listen, what did you get
for number one?
Uh-huh.
Number two?
Oh, yeah, that sounds right.
Mm, mm-mm, mm, mm, mmm.
Ahh!
Here you go,
Mrs. Krabappel.
I think you'll be
pleasantly surprised.
Mm-hmm. Yep. Mm-hmm.
This test is worse
than Milhouse's exam.
Bart Simpson, I warned you.
This is the final straw.
Mr. And Mrs. Simpson, I think you know
our district psychiatrist
-Dr. J. Loren Pryor.
-Hey, Doctor J.
Hmph. I think what we have
on our hands here is a classic case
of what laymen refer to
as "fear of failure."
As a result,
Bart is an underachiever,
and yet he seems to be--
how should I put this--
-proud of it.
-Hmm.
One of his problems may be
his short attention span
which can lead to...
blah blah blah
blah blah blah...
-Uh-huh.
-Blah blah
-blah blah blah blah...
-Hmm...
Bart has failed his last
four exams in History.
Is there anything
you're not telling us?
No.
Every other student
in the class has shown
at least some form
of improvement,
and yet you
continue to struggle.
-Why is that?
-I don't know.
Look at these results--
Fifty-five,
Forty-two,
Twenty-six--
A 12 on state capitals?
Okay! Okay. Why are we dancing
around the obvious?
I know it. You know it.
I am dumb, okay? Dumb as a post!
You think I'm
happy about it?
There, there, Bart,
you're just a late bloomer.
Oh, I wish it were
that simple.
As shameful and as emotionally
crippling as it may be,
I'm afraid my recommendation
is for Bart Simpson to...
repeat the fourth grade.
What? You can't hold me back.
I'll do better. I promise.
-Promises, promises.
-Oh, sure. That'll be the day.
Well, maybe it
would help him
to be left back.
It won't be
so bad, Bart.
No, I mean it.
You can't hold me back.
I swear I'm gonna do better.
Look at my eyes.
See the sincerity?
See the conviction?
See the fear?
As God is my witness,
I can pass the fourth grade!
And if you don't, at least you'll
be bigger than the other kids.
(concerned groan)
Get off the bus, or forever
hold your peace, little dudes.
Otto, you know
I respect you.
I mean, you always
let us throw stuff at cars
and try to tip the bus
on sharp turns.
Damn thing never goes over,
does it?
So what's in your head,
little man?
Well, I been failing
a lot of tests recently.
-Yuh-huh?
-And now they're talking about
holding me back in the 4th grade
if I don't shape up.
That's it?
Hey, relax, man.
It could end up being the best thing
that ever happened to you.
I got held back in
the fourth grade myself.
Twice.
And look at me, man.
Now I drive the school bus.
DR. PRYOR:
I'm afraid my recommendation
is for Bart Simpson to
repeat the fourth grade...
(echoing) repeat the fourth grade...
All right, class.
The topic is world literature.
What was the pirate's name
in "Treasure Island"?
Bart Simpson?
Look, lady,
I got a peptic ulcer,
a wife hawking me for a new car,
and I need a root canal.
Will you quit bugging me
about this stupid pirate?
Psst.
It's Long John Silver, Dad.
I heard that, Bart, Jr.
I want to see both of you
after class today.
D'oh!
Thanks a lot, son.
(infield chatter)
Yo, little help.
I said, "little help."
Throw me the ball,
Poindexter!
Oh, I'm sorry, Bart.
I'm unfamiliar with
the rules of your sport.
I didn't want to interfere
with a ball in play.
(laughing)
Well, back to the forecastle
of the Pequod.
-Hmm... hey, Martin?
-You have your ball.
I have nothing else
of value.
I need you to help me
get a passing grade.
Well, you do need someone's
help to get a passing grade,
but I don't know why
that someone should be me.
Because I can make it
so the other kids
don't laugh at you so much.
They... laugh at me?
I'd always considered myself
rather popular.
You're not.
Watch. Hnh!
(laughing)
But my speed with numbers,
my years of service
as a hall monitor,
my prizewinning
dioramas--
these things
mean nothing to them?
Perhaps another
demonstration. Hnh!
(kids laughing)
Very well. You have made
your point, Bart.
Then it's a deal?
Yes.
Alrighty, let's have a look-see
at your study area.
-Study area?
-Yes,
your sanctuary from
the hurly-burly of modern life.
Well, there's a desk
under that junk over there.
MARTIN: Oh, no, no, no, no.
This won't do at all.
We're gonna have to
clean up this room,
and we'll clearly need
a few ferns in here.
No study area is complete
without adequate plant life.
-No.
-No?
Only geeks
sit in the front seat.
From now on,
sit in the back row.
And that's not just
on the bus.
-It goes for school and church, too.
-Why?
So no one can see
what you're doing.
Oh! I think I understand.
The potential for mischief
varies inversely
with one's proximity
to the authority figure.
Well, yeah, but don't
say it like that.
(tires skidding)
-(crashing)
-MARTIN: Ooh!
Nnymm.
Nyahh!
Uhhnng!
-Aaah!
Huh!
Pretty soon you will be ready
to try it with a real book.
(laughing)
Who would have thought
that pushing a boy into
the girls' lavatory
could be such a thrill?
The screams,
the humiliation,
the fact that it wasn't me!
I've never felt so alive.
Great, Martin.
Now the big test is tomorrow,
-and I haven't even started--
-Who cares about some test?
Life's too short for tests!
Hey, I thought we had a deal!
Ha, ha, ha!
The Martin Prince you made
a deal with no longer exists!
Come on fellows,
to the arcade!
Cool, Martin!
All right, Martin!
BOYS (chanting):
Martin! Martin! Martin!
♪♪ (humming
"Row, row, row your boat")
Bart?
It's past your bedtime.
Okay.
This is hopeless.
Ohh...
Well, old-timer, I guess
this is the end of the road.
I know I haven't always
been a good kid
but if I have to go
to school tomorrow,
I'll fail the test
and be held back.
I just need one more day
to study, Lord.
I need your help.
Prayer, the last refuge
of a scoundrel.
A teacher's strike,
a power failure, a blizzard.
Anything that will
cancel school tomorrow.
I know it's asking a lot,
but if anyone can do it,
you can.
Thanking you in advance,
your pal, Bart Simpson.
♪♪ ("The Hallelujah Chorus")
(groaning)
Wake up, Bart.
Rise and shine, little guy.
Time to wake up.
Oh, no, no.
Wake up and
look at the snow.
Huh?
Whoa!
Good morning world!
MAN (on radio): Rise and shine,
Springfield residents.
It's the Bill and
Marty Show. He's Bill.
-He's Marty.
-Two grown men
who can't get
enough of each other.
BILL: And it looks like
we've got some snow-formation
-for all those flake-lovers out there.
-ALL: Shh!
-MARTY: Mm-hmm.
-BILL: Springfield electric,
gas and water plants
are closed for the day.
MARTY: Oh, now don't forget
the nuclear power plant, Bill.
-Please, please, please, please--
-That's closed, too.
Whoo-hoo!
All right!
Now, for all you youngsters,
you toddlers,
this is what
you've been waiting for.
Springfield County
schools are--
I can't read it.
I'm too excited.
Uh-oh. Springfield County
schools will be...
-Please, please, please...
-Closed!
-All right, man!
-Yeah! Woo-hoo-hoo!
(children cheering)
-Wait, come back--
-Your hat!
-You're supposed to eat break--
-Wear your galoshes!
Cowabunga!
Remember to take a break
if your arms go numb.
-Hey.
-I heard you last night, Bart.
You prayed for this.
Now your prayers
have been answered.
I'm no theologian.
I don't know who
or what God is, exactly.
All I know is he's
a force more powerful
than Mom and Dad
put together,
-and you owe him big.
-(door slams)
You're right.
I asked for a miracle
and I got it.
I got to study, man.
I'm not missing anything.
Frozen earlobes.
Trudging up that stupid sled
hill over and over again.
How good could it be?
(children cheering, laughing)
(laughing)
I haven't had
this much fun in years.
-Aah!
-(laughs) Got you, Burnsie.
(chuckles)
Why, you young ragamuffin.
I was never one to back away
from a snowball fight.
Smithers,
you may fire at will.
Certainly, sir.
♪♪
I hereby declare this day
to be "Snow Day--
The funnest day
in the history of Springfield."
(cheering)
♪ Sleigh bells ring,
are you listening? ♪
♪ In the lane,
snow is glistening ♪
♪ A beautiful sight,
we're happy tonight ♪
♪ Walking
in a winter wonderland ♪
♪ Gone away
is the bluebird ♪
♪ Here to stay... ♪
Got to study, got to study,
got to study!
"Chapter Six--
Four Days in Philadelphia.
"The first
Continental Congress
"faced a difficult job.
"Could the delegates agree
on recommendations
that all Americans
could support?"
We hold these truths
to be self-evident...
"We hold these truths
to be self-evident."
...that all men
are created equal.
"...that all men are
created equal."
That from that equal creation
they derive rights,
inherent and inalienable--
Hey, look everybody--
it's snowing!
-In the middle of July?
-It's a miracle.
Fellows, I've invented
something fun. The sled!
(excited chatter)
MAN:
Hey, look, everybody!
John Hancock's
writing his name in the snow!
Do you want to be
held back a grade?
Concentrate, man!
(slapping continues)
Later, Mrs. K.
Please turn in
your exam, Bart.
Class is over.
Do you think you could
grade it now, please?
Well, all right.
Let me get "old red."
Mm-hmm.
Yup.
Well, Bart, it's a 59.
That's another "F."
Oh, no.
I can't believe it.
I know, I know.
Another year together.
Oh! It's going
to be hell.
(sobbing)
What's the matter?
I would think you'd be
used to failing by now.
No, you don't understand.
I really tried this time.
I mean, I really tried.
There, there.
This is as good as I can do
and I still failed.
Well, a 59--
it's a high "F."
Who am I kidding?
I really am a failure.
(sobbing)
Oh! Now I know
how George Washington felt
when he surrendered
Fort Necessity
to the French in 1754.
-What?
-Oh, you know, 1754,
the famous defeat
to the French. (sobs)
My God, Bart, you're right.
-So?
-You just demonstrated
applied knowledge,
and due to the difficulty
and relative obscurity
of the reference,
you deserve an extra point
on your exam.
Hey, it's only fair.
You mean, I passed?
Just barely.
(gasps)
I passed.
I got a "D-".
I passed!
All right! Mwah!
(singsongy) I passed, I passed,
I passed, I passed!
I got a "D-"!
I passed!
I got a "D-"! I passed!
I got a "D-"!
I passed!
I passed! I--
Kissed the teacher!
We're proud of you, boy.
Thanks, Dad,
but part of this "D-"
belongs to God.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.