CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(shrieks)
(Legos clicking)
Woo-hoo!
D’oh!
MARGE:
Okay, Maggie.
Say your "good nights."
Good night,
Teddy Bear.
Justin Timberwolf.
Good night,
Bedtime Krusty.
(honks)
(recorded voice):
Don’t let he bedbugs bite!
Krusty’s Anti-Bedbug Spray
sold separately.
May contain poison.
Good night, Maggie.
(whines)
Come on, sweetie.
Everyone’s going to sleep.
HOMER: ♪ You know
you make me wanna ♪
KIDS:
♪ Shout! ♪
-♪ Throw my hands up and ♪
-♪ Shout! ♪
♪ Kick my heels up and ♪
♪ Shout! ♪
♪ Hey-ey-ey-ey-ey ♪
♪ A little bit louder now ♪
♪ Hey-ey-ey-ey-ey... ♪
(crib squeaking)
(groans)
(squeaking)
(sighs)
All right, I’ll make you
another bottle.
(sighs)
Maggie’s so clingy.
Homer, hold her
while I pour the milk.
No problem.
(grunts)
My, you’ve grown.
-(shrieks)
-Whoa!
Wha...?!
Spilled milk?
(crying)
(sobbing):
All over the floor.
(tires screech)
Hey, Apu, what happened
to all your milk?
I sold it all to teenagers.
There’s a rumor you can mix
milk, Mentos and Lotto scrapings
to make jetpack fuel.
Does it work?
(jetpack puttering)
Kinda.
(tires screech)
(panting):
Hey, Moe!
Got any milk?
It’s either milk or paint.
(slurping)
It’s paint.
Or is it?
(gulping)
Yeah, it’s paint.
Well, then I’ll have
to charge you extra,
depending on the color.
Uh, stick out your tongue.
Eggshell? No.
Malabar ivory? No.
Mediterranean ecru? No.
Ah! Here it is-- white.
Ooh, that’s gonna cost ya.
LISA:
There must be a Web site
that can help you deal
with a clingy baby.
Oh, I don’t want to bother
the Internet with my problem.
Aw, come on, Mom.
We’ll help you surf.
Click that one, Mom.
-No, go up.
-Keep going--
up, up, up!
-The blue ones are ads.
-That’s the toolbar.
Now you’ve opened Word;
close it.
Close it.
Do-Don’t save it.
-Stop clicking.
-Don’t go there!
Why are you
buying a freezer?
Don’t click the cart
or you’ve bought it!
Aw, you clicked
the cart.
If you’re so smart,
you do it.
(groans)
C.R.I.E?
What does that stand for?
"Creative Responses
for Infant Edu-loving!"
Ooh, "edu-loving!"
They come to your home to help
you raise "independent,
self-actualized children.
The counselors can come
day and night
because they have no
families themselves."
Okay, I’ll sign up.
You just bought
another freezer.
Well, maybe I wanted
another freezer!
HOMER: I’ve got
to find milk somewhere.
(sighs)
(gasps)
Aw!
Hmm?
(gasps)
(rock and roll plays)
♪ Oh, yeah! ♪
♪ On the dark side ♪
(saxophone plays solo)
♪ Oh... yeah! ♪
You want milk?!
I got your milk right here.
Phew!
At first I thought you were
pointing to your crotch.
You thought, huh?
Yo, everybody! Get a load of
"Beautiful Mind" over here,
-with the thinkin’.
-(patrons laughing)
Listen up, ya humps!
Which one of youz parked
at the bank?
’Cause they’re towing
your sorry ass.
(shrieks)... That’s my car!
Yo, Angelica.
Get over here.
(moaning)
This don’t mean nothing.
Ah, please! Give me a break!
I’ve been driving all night,
looking for milk for my kids.
I’ll tell you what.
I’ll give you a ride
to the impound lot.
Okay, let me just grab
my registration.
(clanking)
Mm-hmm!
(loud rock music plays)
I can’t believe your boss
lets you listen
to rock music
while you work.
My boss?
(chuckling)
I don’t think my boss has
a problem with anything I do.
Oh, I’d really like
to meet this guy.
Well, he’s in this truck
right now.
But it’s just you and me.
(gasps):
That must mean...
I’m your boss!
I’m sick of you! You’re fired!
No, you dumb Dominick.
I’m my own boss.
Shut up!
When you call in sick,
who do you call?
I don’t call in sick.
I work when I want to.
Sometimes you want to work?
Hey, I get to drive around,
eat what I want,
eyeball the highway honeys...
-(honks horn)
-I’m your aunt, stupid!
...and lasso the street cattle.
Street cattle?
The cars I tow, I got
all kinds of names for them:
She-atas,
Hebrew canoes,
spam cans,
Swedish speedballs,
and of course,
stretch lame-os.
Some of those were pretty funny.
Check it out.
We already got
a "whine line."
When can I get my Beamer?
I can’t be out in this
neighborhood!
My jewelry’s real!
You can’t tow a hybrid.
My blow better still be
in the glove box.
Wow, you make
people miserable
and there’s nothing
they can do about it!
Just like God.
Man, oh, man, you got
the greatest job in the world.
You know,
if you’re interested,
we could use
another hook jockey.
The Springfield territory’s
wide open,
since Flatbed Fred
got killed
in that murder-murder-
murder-suicide.
I would love to!
Oh, but I don’t have
a tow truck.
For 500 bucks, I’ll sell you
this old bucket.
Hmm... I’m not sure
my wife will go
for this naughty
mud flaps.
Not to worry. These...
are the ones you show at home.
Ah, that’s still
too sexy for my wife.
No problem.
Man, you work as a silhouette
model for one day
and it haunts you
for the rest of your life.
Now just remember two rules.
One, stick to Springfield.
If I catch you on my turf,
I’ll rip off your head,
vomit down your neck,
pull out your heart,
show it to your head,
then shove ’em both down
your neck hole,
to which I previously alluded.
"...which I previously
alluded..."
Are there two "L’s"
in "alluded"?
Rule number two, always keep
your hook pointed out.
Why? What happens
if I point it this way?
Oh hello-o!
-Hello!
-Hello, Captain Hook!
Oh, spoil sport.
Oh, you’re no fun.
(tires screech)
Ah, my first tow.
I think it goes... here.
D’oh!
Ah, my first tow.
Stop. Stop.
I’m entitled to park there.
Really?
What’s your handicap?
Pogonophobia--
fear of beards and mustaches.
(snorts)
Well, I guess I can call a cab.
Stay back! All of ya!
(two gunshots)
MAN:
Ho, ho... (groans)
♪♪
(laughing)
Faster!
More dangerous!
Whoa...
(laughing)
(gasps)
(both laughing)
Marge, your codependent
hyper-nurturing
has infantilized your baby.
You’ve made her queen
of her "clingdom."
Ooh, did you hear that,
Maggie-wags?
You’re a queen.
Marge, you’re reinforcing
a negative.
I’m what?
Allow me
to demonstri-care.
Actualize!
And now you are free
to live like a human being.
(Maggie crying)
Maggie’s crying.
She’s not crying,
she’s celebrating
her independence.
Don’t crash that party.
-Oh... one hug can’t hurt.
-(crying continues)
Yes, it can-- hugs are drugs,
and your daughter’s an addict.
(sighs)
I guess it’s time to let
my little girl grow up.
(grunts)
(gasps)
You see?
Now her childhood
can begin-ualize.
Huh. Thank you, CRIE.
I’m, huh, I’m sorry
about the kick.
I’ve never done anything
like that before.
Yeah, well, I’m glad your first
time was such a success.
What the hell are you doing?
I’m doing my job.
You’re hovering over a hydrant.
♪♪
You’re in the sky now--
my domain.
(screams)
(laughs)
I’ve got tow dough
-I’m looking
to blow, Moe.
-Huh?
I’m buying a round
of the fanciest drink you got.
Four "Lobster-politans"
comin’ up.
(humming)
-Hmm.
-Huh.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Here’s to Homer
and the cars he towed.
(slurping)
With those jerks
out of the way,
I was able to park
right outside.
Outside?
That’s a one-hour parking zone,
and you’ve been here
a good 81 minutes.
Correction:
a great 81 minutes.
’Cause nothing beats hangin’
around with old friends,
drinkin’ lobster-based
designer drinks and...
-(whirring)
-Huh, good joke, Homer.
(nervous chuckle):
You can unhook my car now.
Uh, looks like
he’s driving away with it.
(nervous laugh)
No, he’s just moving it
so it won’t get towed.
(sighs)
Maggie, what can
I get you for breakf...?
Oh...
You did everything yourself.
-Hm.
-(humming)
Homer, where have you been?
Marge, when you’re married
to a midnight towboy,
you might not see him
for days on end.
I don’t want to live like that.
Hey, when you married a man
who would, years later,
without warning, become
a tow truck driver,
you knew what the deal
would eventually be.
Well, no one’s
disputing that.
Guess what, boy?
Last night I towed
your principal’s car.
Oh, awesome.
How’s he getting around?
(wheels squeaking,
Skinner grunting)
You can’t impound
my spirit.
(laughing)
Top of the mornin’,
Tow-mer.
It’s Homer, idiot.
(chuckles):
So it is.
I’m just here
to pay the fine
for the Sunday
School bus.
You towed it with
the kids still in it.
(chuckles)
I guess I’m more powerful
than God now.
You know
what they say:
"With great power comes
great responsibility."
Who said that?!
I’ll kill them with my power.
(cheering)
Take that,
you tow-talitarian.
Doesn’t that joke make
light of totalitarians?
Yeah. Stalin put my grandmother
in a forced labor camp
for 20 years.
Look, I was insensitive,
and I’m sorry.
But what this is really about
is a bully with a winch.
If I’d wanted the laws of this
town enforced to the letter,
I wouldn’t have hired fatty here
as police chief.
Hear that, Ralphie?
The mayor knows Daddy.
All right, listen up.
I know a thing or two
about tow-Joes.
I married three of them,
and they’re real territorial.
Now here’s the plan...
Get in here, Mel.
I don’t bite.
I might gum ya,
and you might like it.
SIDESHOW MEL: Must we all wait
behind this bush?
I have theater tickets.
MOE:
Ooh, theater tickets, huh?
-(paper rips)
-Now ya got nothin’.
(gasps)
(sighs sadly)
Maggie’s completely independent.
At least you need me,
sack of potatoes.
("Rock-A-Bye Baby"
music playing)
(sobbing)
(gasps)
Oh, my God...
multiple tickets,
handicapped spot,
parked by a hydrant,
incomprehensible
vanity plate.
If my life as a tow truck driver
were a teleplay,
this would be the end
of act two.
(humming)
(humming continues)
(mechanical whirring)
I told you to stay off my turf!
What? I’m still
in Springfield.
Wha...?!
Okay,
I made a mistake.
Why don’t you give me
two demerit points
in a point system
we work out right now?
D’oh!
Put me down, you lousy--
-(tires squealing)
-Wee!
Okay,
I’m warning you--
Wee!
I’ll kill you, you son of a--
All right buddy, that’s it,
I’ve had--
Wee!
(thud)
Oh, wee...
(grunting):
You... let go!
(grunting)
All right,
Just... let... go.
Oh, a trap door.
What’s down there?
Your Meatball
collection?
-Goodbye.
-I thought
we were friends!
I was kidding you
in a friendly fashion!
(thump)
Who are you guys?
We’re just like you--
tow truck drivers
who got greedy.
Is Louie keeping you
prisoner here?
No. We’re waiting for him
to give us a timeshare
presentation.
Actually,
we’re an a cappella group
and we’re gonna sing
"Under the BoardWalk."
The truth is, we’re just waiting
for each others’ hair to grow
so we can braid it.
(all laugh)
Okay, I get it.
I’m not stupid.
It’s number two, right?
♪ Under the boardwalk ♪
♪ Down by the sea ♪
♪ On a blanket with my baby ♪
♪ That’s where I’ll be ♪
♪ Under the boardwalk ♪
♪ Out of the sun! ♪
It sure is great not
having Homer around
to tell us where we can
or can’t park.
Yeah, without the crushing
rule of law,
society will do a better job
of regulating itself.
(both laugh)
(tires screeching)
Of all the nerve!
Now to buy some soft luggage.
(phone ringing)
Dad?
Where are you?
Do not worry.
I am working.
Working? Where?
Ask no questions.
And do not call
the police,
or I will kill me.
You sound weird.
All is well.
Goodbye forever.
-(dial tone)
-(sighs)
-(horns honking)
-(clamoring)
Get out of the way!
That’s my space.
I was here first.
Avast, ye sky whale!
(victorious laughter)
I need a camera battery!
-(train whistle blowing)
-(metal clanging)
All the Transformers
transformed
back into trucks and cars.
The end.
-Oh, that’s great.
-Great story.
Okay, we’ve got time
for one more.
Oh, yeah. All right.
Once upon a time,
there was a hilarious ogre
named Shrek Three.
He lived in medieval times,
but sometimes he’d say things
from today times...
Got one!
We can say these swears
any time we want
because they’re
in the Bible!
I don’t think "Leviticus"
is a swear.
Shut the hell up,
you damn ass whore.
MARGE:
Bart?
Uh-oh.
I’m starting to worry
about your father.
Well, I know he seems
to get dumber every year,
but lately he’s plateaued.
He hasn’t been home
in four days.
(grunts)
Well, I guess he told me
not to worry.
Where are you, Homie?
(yelps)
(cats meowing)
Yah!
Yah, yah, doggies!
Yah! Yah! Yah!
Go, go, go!
And if elected president
of our small community,
I will determine
once and for all
how far we can go
without being gay.
Maggie!
(door opens)
(door shuts)
We’re free!
Maggie!
You did all this?!
And to pay you back,
I’m returning your nose.
Here’s your nose.
-Daddy’s putting back
your nose.
-(giggling)
That’s your--
Oh, wait.
That’s Lisa’s nose.
Homie!
You’re all right!
Thanks to her!
Really?
Look at you...
so grown up.
Well, I’ve moved on, too.
Are you sure?
Hugs are dr...
Oh...
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem