CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(saxophone solo)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screaming)
(gasps)
(Marge humming)
Wow, Bart!
Lookin’ good!
(chuckles)
Well, I have to look good
for tomorrow.
Right...
tomorrow.
Homer, you do know
what tomorrow is.
Think. Think.
I’m not thinking. You think.
You have to think,
it’s your job!
(mocking):
You have to think,
it’s your job.
Why you little...
(grunting)
Homer!
Lisa is receiving
the Student of the Millennium
Award at school.
To be fair,
the millennium
just started,
so it’s not
that big a deal.
But they’re giving it to me.
(giggles)
You have
to be there.
You miss way too many
precious moments
in the childrens’ lives.
What?! Name 12.
Well,
just this week,
there’s been
field day,
picking me up
from the airport...
And the Father-
Daughter Dance.
Lisa, if you like,
I’m certified
to conduct a mock
father/daughter conversation.
Just dance.
Homer, you cannot miss
Lisa’s big day.
And you have
to come sober!
American sober or Irish sober?
Point zero eight sober.
Point one five.
Point zero nine.
Point one zero with a stomach
full of bread.
My final offer.
(grunts) Deal.
Goodnight, sweetheart.
-(ringing)
-(moans)
Can’t be late
for Lisa’s big day.
(hums)
I’m gonna make it.
I’ll be on time
for Lisa’s thing.
Ooh, an awesome accident.
Easy, easy...
I’ll just take three seconds
to gawk.
Aw, everyone’s okay.
(tires squealing)
Gonna make it.
Whoo-hoo!
(grunts)
An hour and 54 minutes to spare.
With my free time I can finally
work on my Superman novel.
"’Make way for Superman,’
said Superman as he punched
everyone at the Coffee Bean.
Chapter Two..."
Oh, man,
they just keep kicking off
awards season
earlier and earlier.
Yeah, the whole thing
is just a scam
to sell ad space
in the school paper.
JIMBO: That’s the place
that did both my Grandmas.
DOLPH: I did
both your grandmas.
Shut up!
KEARNEY: Shall we look
at the next one?
Willie.
He’ll buy beer for you,
but he’ll make you
drink it with him.
(boys chuckling)
(meowing)
Darn these long bank lines.
Although it does give me
a moment with my thoughts.
Ooh...
(grunts)
Darn these long bank lines.
(frustrated grunting)
(continues grunting)
That old man over there
isn’t even making
a transaction.
He just wants
someone to talk to.
Before this was
the Bank of Springfield,
this was the Midwest
Savings and Loan.
And before that,
it was an abandoned theater.
it was a theater.
Where’s Dr. Kevorkian
when you need him?
Well, if I know doctors,
he’s probably golfing.
(both chuckle)
Excuse me
for a moment.
Everyone down
on the floor, now!
(gunshot, glass breaks)
(grunting)
This is a robbery!
Uh, not a separate
robbery--
we’re together.
You mean
like a couple?
-No!
-Yes!
Oh, great.
We’re being robbed
by Johnny and Clyde!
(patrons laughing)
(cries out)
Stay away
from that button!
(alarm ringing)
Damn it!
(Skinner clearing throat)
Hm...
Well, Marge,
who’s the unfit parent now?
(chuckles)
You know, a principal’s dream
would be to have a school
with nothing but Lisa Simpsons.
Unfortunately,
the rest of you exist.
From her grade-grubbing
to her apple polishing...
(phone ringing)
ROBBER:
She’s got a cell phone!
We didn’t plan for this, man.
We didn’t plan for this.
Ol’ Gil’s here for his first day
as security guard.
Oh, boy...
(gunshots)
(screaming, glass breaking)
Oh, no.
Now it’s murder, man.
It’s murder.
(screams)
Uh, Chief,
looks like we got
a 64-G in progress.
Armed robbery with a gun.
(groans)
Come on, Chief, you know this.
Oh, a shooty-stealy.
And now the reason
we’re all here today...
Lisa Simpson!
(cell phone playing)
Oh, hello, Marge.
I’m at the most important event
of our daughter’s life,
and you’re totally late.
Am I disappointed? Yes.
Am I surprised? No.
(whispering):
Homer.
I’m a hostage
in a bank robbery.
What?! Oh, my God,
my sweet Margie!
Okay, listen very carefully.
Don’t do anything they say,
remain panicky, and above all,
try to be a hero.
Homer, I have to go.
If I don’t make it,
feel free to remarry--
from anyone on the list in the
bulletin board in the closet.
(sobbing)
Goodbye, my love!
Okay, this isn’t the way
I planned it,
but you can make it
out alive
as long as there’s
no funny stuff.
Don’t worry about me.
I was voted America’s
least funny clown.
Worse than Scuzzo, Scummo,
Oopsie, Carlos Mencia,
Stinko, Blumpy.
Even worse Sergeant Serious!
How could I do worse than him?!
I stole all his jokes!
(Homer panting)
Chief, you gotta
do something--
my current wife
is in there!
Maybe you should
take over,
’cause I got no
stake in this.
This isn’t even my bank.
I’m over at First Federal.
(moans)
-(explosion)
-Oh! Dye pack!
Man, that stings.
-(explosion)
-Oh. Damn it!
What are you looking at, huh?
(explosion, screams)
Oh! Is anyone else a dye pack?
Tell me now,
and I won’t shoot you.
I... Ooh!
You said diabetic, right?
(sighs)
Finally, the help we need--
a DVD of The Negotiator.
Hmm, hmm.
Which chapter
should we skip to?
"Meet Danny Roman,"
"Trouble Brewing,"
"Off the Case,"
"My Baby’s in There,"
"Enter Niebaum,"
"Take the Shot,"
"Sabian’s Choice,"
"Check and Mate,"
"Friends At Last,"
"Closing Credits"?
Oh, man, oh, man.
What the hell’s
taking them so long?
They must be getting ready
to kill me!
It’s no fair.
I shouldn’t die.
I just came here
to check the date!
(sobbing)
(clears throat)
Dwight, use your noodle.
If you surrender now,
you’re only looking at
a few years in jail.
I’ll tell them
you’re a good guy.
Marge, I can’t
go back to prison.
I’ve got no wife,
I’ve got no family.
I’ve got nothing!
(guns cocking)
If I give myself up,
will you come visit me
in the joint?
Hey, if I can say yes
to Chinese toys that kill kids,
you can say yes to him.
Okay, I’ll visit you, Dwight.
(Marge groans)
Oh, Marge, I was afraid
I was going to lose you!
(sobs)
Now let me help you
make your slow transition
back to society.
I just want
to go home.
You have a new home
now with us.
(Marge groans)
See ya soon, Marge.
Real soon!
Just like you promised!
(maniacal laughter)
(chuckles nervously)
Hmm.
Sweetheart,
what’s wrong?
I promised
that bank robber
that I’d visit him
in jail,
but I just
can’t do it.
You don’t owe him anything.
Moe was in the hospital
for three weeks,
and I didn’t visit him once.
You said you visited him
every night.
Moe the tavern,
not Moe the person.
Well, promises
mean more to me.
Okay, you gave your word.
You’re going to visit him,
no excuses.
Ooh! Shlomo’s Judaica
is having a blowout on dreidels.
(tires squealing)
All right, this time I’m going.
I’m really going
to visit a bank robber.
A man who held a gun on me.
Going to see him in prison,
where guards will frisk me,
paw through my purse, and...
Ooh, there’s apple picking
just up the road!
I’m getting
a visitor today.
I’m so nervous
it feels like
I keistered
a bunch of butterflies.
Dude, I highly doubt
you’re getting a visitor.
People don’t like you.
You come off needy and bug-eyed.
You’re wrong.
Marge is coming. She is.
Easy, bro. It’s not like
she’s your mother.
I wish she was.
My real mother abandoned me
in an amusement park.
All I have left is a caricature
from that day.
Ooh. That is harsh.
Hey, baby.
Listen carefully.
Someone’s been editing
my biography on Wikipedia.
I want you to kill him.
No problem, sweetie.
I’ll dump his body in the same
lake as your lousy lawyer.
(gasps): Then when you get out,
we can have a picnic there!
Aw, that’s so sweet.
Anyone for me?
I really shouldn’t show up
without an apple pie for Dwight.
In fact, I really shouldn’t
show up without an apple pie
for everyone at the prison.
Oh, my, it’s 5:00.
I missed visiting hours.
Perfect!
Look, Lisa.
I put new filaments in all our
burned-out lightbulbs.
Your father,
the millionaire,
thought we should
throw these away.
Mom, I think there’s something
you’re trying to avoid.
Or someone.
(laughs)
Don’t be silly, Lisa.
In fact...
(phone ringing, Marge screams)
(grunts)
(grinding,
phone continues ringing)
(phone continues ringing)
Damn these sturdy,
foreign-built phones.
(phone ringing)
Hello. Hello?
MARGE: Hello?
-(phone rings)
-Marge?
Hello, this is Ted Nugent,
the Motor City Madman,
urging you to vote no
on Proposition 87.
If we outlaw crossbows
in our public schools,
who’s gonna protect our childre
from charging elk?
Thank you for your time,
and as always...
(loudly):
I say Wango!
I say Tango!
MAN: (on TV): We now return
to A Kiss Before Frying.
(Irish accent):
It’s almost midnight.
They’ll be coming soon,
Johnny.
Coming to take you
to the electric chair.
(gasps)
I ain’t afraid
of old sparky,
the hot seat,
the kilowatt couch,
the death davenport,
the electric lap,
the crook cooker,
the scorch stool!
I ain’t afraid, see?
No, Johnny, I don’t see.
You’re going straight to hell,
you know.
I ain’t afraid,
’cause my sainted Ma
is comin’ to visit before I go.
And when I sit down
on the jolt throne,
I’ll be lookin’
into Ma’s sweet face
as my tongue explodes
in my mouth
and the goo boils in my eyes.
Oh, poor Johnny Stabbo.
(thunder crashing loudly)
(coughing)
Damn it!
(sobbing)
Ma! Ma! Where are you, Ma?
Don’t give up hope, Johnny!
Give up hope, Johnny.
Your Ma ain’t coming.
Now, if I may do the honors.
Ma. Ma. Ma...!
(electrical crackling)
(screaming)
(prolonged):
Ma...!
(crackling stops)
-Ma...!
-(electrical crackling)
(thunder crashing loudly)
(maniacal laughter)
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show ♪
("Take Me Out to the Ball Game"
playing)
You’re out.
ITCHY:
Psst, psst!
(cash register rings)
(camera shutters clicking)
You’re disgracing
America’s pastime.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
What the...?
(rapid gunfire)
(screaming)
(screams)
("Take Me Out to the Ball Game"
playing)
(camera shutters clicking)
We interrupt this Annie
Award-winning cartoon
for an important bulletin.
Convicted bank robber
Dwight David Diddlehopper
has escaped from
Springfield Penitentiary.
The escapee left a note saying
he will turn himself in
after he takes care of one
unfinished piece of business.
The police have issued
a statement saying,
"That seems more than fair."
(gasps)
♪ Who can it be now? ♪
♪ Who can it be
knocking at my door? ♪
♪ Make no sound ♪
♪ Tiptoe across the floor ♪
♪ If he hears,
he’ll knock all... ♪
(music stops)
Oh, hey, oh.
Oh, wait, this ain’t
where I go to vote.
(chuckles nervously)
Hello, Marge.
(groans)
Man, these cars
look all alike.
Now drive!
Dwight!
(chuckles nervously)
I-I was just on my way
to see you in prison.
Really, Marge?
-Look me in the eyes
and say that.
-Okay.
They’re so buggy, I can’t.
Dwight, please,
don’t do anything crazy.
-Just pull over there.
-Huh?
Um, what are we
doing here?
This is where my mom
abandoned me.
Oh, that’s so sad.
Ya think?
Marge, can you please give me
the day my mother didn’t?
Ride some rides,
eat some cotton candy.
Then I’ll let you go home.
Okay, but I’d feel
better about it
if you got rid
of the gun.
I’d like to, but then
you’ll leave like she did.
Can you at least
put it in your jacket?
Fine, but I’m still gonna
make that pointy shape.
Krusty.
I haven’t see you since
that terrifying day.
Uh, you’ll have to be
way more specific.
We were hostages
at the bank.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry I offered your
life for my safety.
(laughs)
Look, it’s Marge!
With Dwight!
I said there was
a spark between them,
and you said, "No way."
I saw it, I just didn’t
feel like talking to you.
Wait, something’s
screwy here.
I’m calling the cops.
Don’t bother, they’re
right over there.
Easy, easy.
Line up your shot,
then squeeze it off.
(gunshot)
Uh, Chief, I think we got a
hostage situation over there.
Can’t a man spend one minute
with his stuffed monkey?
One minute?
(to self): Monkey would make
a better chief.
What did you say?
I said the monkey would
make a better chief!
He’s a good monkey,
all right.
Hm...
(gasping)
The Viking boats!
This is where I lost
my first mom.
MARGE: Oh...
Well, this mom is not
gonna say bug-eye.
I mean, goodbye.
Damn it!
Boy, I really feel like
a Viking in this thing.
I’ll show them which monkey
would make the best chief!
(Wiggum grunts)
(screams)
Stop the boats!
(snapping)
(Spanish accent):
Sorry, Mister.
(Wiggum groans)
Are you kidding me?!
Ow!
Dwight, do something!
Okay. For you, Ma.
(Wiggum yelling)
-(cracking)
-WIGGUM: Great.
Dwight?
Are you okay? Dwight!
He’ll be fine.
Not you and me fine,
but fine.
Hey, leave
the comedy to me.
Okay, funny man,
make me laugh.
Huh. Uh-uh.
Instead of a carnival ride,
what if he was run over
by a Zamboni
with a moustache?
-I don’t see how.
-Then I got nothing.
Dwight, that was the most
unselfish thing I’ve ever seen.
I’m sorry I didn’t
visit you before.
HOMER: Hey, Marge.
Look at us,
the four amigos.
They’re gonna let me do some odd
jobs for them on the outside.
Listen, outside my cell,
I saw one dandelion growing.
I picked it for you.
Aw!
Then I pressed it
in my Bible to dry.
Oh!
I carved a frame for it
out of a bar of soap.
-Aw!
-Read the inscription
on the back.
"You chat up the guard
at the gate,
while I knife the guard
behind me."
I can’t do that, Dwight.
I figured
you’d say that.
But you can
keep it though.
Aw, thank you.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem