CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeps)
(beeping)
(saxophone solo)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(shrieks)
D’oh! D’oh! D’oh! D’oh! D’oh!
D’oh! D’oh! D’oh! D’oh! D’oh...!
(shrieks)
(buzzing)
(roaring)
(yells)
(animals screeching)
(hooting)
(wind whistling)
Hey.
Did you bring
the milk?
(sighs)
LOVEJOY:
This concludes our service.
Go now in the peace
of the Lord.
HOMER:
So long, suckers!
Move it, move it,
move it!
Do you want to be second
out of the parking lot? Do you?
(grunts)
-Leave her!
-We left her last week,
and she didn’t make
it home for dinner!
(tires squealing)
You’ll never
catch me, Lord!
(Homer laughing)
Oh, man, that church
service was so boring.
I did a whole book
of Find-A-Words.
Dad, all you circled
were the "I"s and "A"s.
Those are words.
Well, where should we go
for brunch?
Griddler
on the Roof?
Thank God
It’s Fried Eggs?
Luftwaffle’s?
Bodacious Frittatas?
Buffet the Hunger Slayer?
I want to say one.
Be my guest.
Denny’s.
(groans):
Oh!
Every place has
such a long line.
Don’t worry.
We’ll just go home.
Your mother
can cook.
I just want a simple salad
with pine nuts,
haricots verts,
seasonal heirloom tomatoes...
Forget it! One day a week,
I should be able
to put on nice clothes
and have someone
bring food to me.
There’s a place...
with no line!
HOMER:
Woo-hoo!
Bart, that’s not a restaurant,
it’s somebody’s house.
Lisa’s right, son.
Your mom is way too classy
a lady to crash a private...
I’m not cooking!
And you can cut
your own meat!
(groans):
Oh!
Everyone just act cool.
If anyone asks,
tell them we’re plumbers,
and then start plumbing
until they go away.
Hi...
you!
Dude! You don’t think,
you know me, but you do!
Oh Homer, you’ve got to try
this roast beef au jus.
Mmm! Au jus!
Not quite gravy,
not quite blood.
Look at the crowd
around that table.
(gasps): It must be a make-
your-own sundae bar!
Watch it.
Oh, I can’t wait to
taste that hot fudge,
and caramel
and crushed nuts
all slathered
over a delicious...
elderly corpse?!
(gasps):
We crashed a funeral!
Oh, my God!
Quick, everyone,
put on their long faces.
Longer!
(whispering):
We should get
out of here.
Come on!
Where’s Bart?
Mahogany.
Great movie,
great casket.
I miss my Pop-pop.
I miss him, too.
What’s your name?
-Donny.
-You’re Donny?
Pop-pop said that
after he died,
you should give me
ten bucks a week.
Starting now.
Okay.
Um, listen, I’m out
of town next week, so...
Come on,
we’re leaving!
Ooh. After one more
mini-quiche.
(chomping)
Excuse me.
My brother twisted his ankle
setting up the chairs.
Will the tragedies that stalk
this family never cease?
(crying)
Would you like to
be a pallbearer?
Of course.
(grunting)
I thought
she said polar bear.
Please, sir, a little
respect for the dead.
Oh, yes, of course. Whoa!
(thudding, grunts)
(groaning):
Oh, my back!
It hurts, and not in a good way.
Well, time to move
on with our lives.
(chuckling)
(spitting):
Oh, stop it!
(spits)
(Homer sputtering):
I’m down here.
HIBBERT:
Homer,
you have
a mild back sprain.
And you also ingested
a dangerous quantity
of grave dirt.
Well, you’re always telling me
I should eat more dirt.
Not dirt. Vegetables!
Which grow in what?
Oh! Look, I just need
to make sure
your vertebrae
are properly aligned.
This should take
only a minute,
and cost about
a thousand dollars.
♪ D’oh! ♪
That doesn’t sound
like Homer’s usual
annoyed grunt.
Hmm.
♪ D’oh! ♪
(lower note):
♪ D’oh ♪
Fascinating.
When Homer’s on his back,
his stomach lodges perfectly
under his diaphragm,
giving him a powerful
singing voice.
Is that
a real thing?
It is!
Tenor Andrea Bocelli
recorded an entire
song on his back.
You know, Homer,
your singing could help
alleviate patient suffering,
and save us a fortune
in Demerol.
My pleasure.
♪ If ever I would leave you ♪
♪ It wouldn’t be in summer ♪
♪ Seeing you in summer ♪
♪ I never would go ♪
♪ Your hair streaked
with sunlight ♪
(beeping)
♪ Your lips red as flame ♪
(crying)
♪ Your face with a luster ♪
♪ That puts gold to shame! ♪
♪ But if I ever leave you ♪
(Homer’s regular voice):
♪ It shouldn’t be in autumn ♪
(operatic voice):
♪ How I’d leave in autumn ♪
(Homer’s voice):
♪ I never will know ♪
HIBBERT & HOMER:
♪ I’ve seen how you sparkle ♪
♪ When fall nips the air ♪
♪ I know you in autumn ♪
♪ And I must be there. ♪
Ah, nothing lifts my spirits
like shopping.
Let’s see,
I’ll take his liver,
a case of Adam’s apples,
that motorcycle man’s
moustache.
Oh, the money you’ve
contributed
to anti-helmet laws has
really paid off, sir.
Well, young people
are my future.
HOMER (singing):
♪ And could I leave you ♪
♪ Running merrily
through the snow... ♪
(gasps):
That beautiful voice!
It’s making
my heart race!
(steam whistle blowing)
-♪ Knowing how in spring... ♪
-It’s coming from down the hall.
To the Betty and Herbert
Weinstein Pavilion!
♪ Oh, no! Not in springtime ♪
♪ Summer, winter or fall ♪
♪ No, never could
I leave you...
♪ At... all! ♪
Excellent, excellent!
The Springfield Opera House,
of which I am founder,
artistic director,
and standing ovation
starter,
is producing
La Bohème.
I want you
to sing the lead.
But I can only sing
lying on my back.
Uh, we’ll cover it
with a rewrite.
Places, everyone!
Oh, oh, I just have
one question:
what is this movie about?
For the last time,
it’s not a movie!
Excuse me, "film."
It’s an opera
and you are in it!
Muah!
Good luck.
(applause)
♪ Rodolfo, perché lete
che vi trovate gio? ♪
♪ Ho danneggiato
il mio piede. ♪
♪ Nei cieli bigi ♪
♪ Guardo fumar dai mille
comignoli parigi. ♪
-Homer’s fantastic!
-Yeah.
But these seats
are terrible.
(sobbing)
♪ Mimi! Mimi! ♪
ALL:
Bravo!
(cheering)
Encore!
My boy, you are a star.
Woo-hoo!
-An opera star!
-Oh.
Dad, you were great!
And you contributed
to our culture!
Well, I didn’t mean to.
No, no. It’s a good thing.
Oh, good.
This makes up
for me showing up drunk
to the father-daughter dance.
The dance isn’t
till next week.
Sorry, Lisa.
Can’t change
the future.
(trumpeting)
♪ And the home ♪
♪ Of the... ♪
♪ Bra-aave! ♪
We’re free!
(sinister laugh)
(applause)
♪ Figaro, Figaro, la, la, la ♪
Nice set, Homer.
That was a hot one.
Wow, praise
from Placido Domingo.
Just call me P-Dingo,
Eh, I’ll think about it.
You know, Homer,
there’s one thing about opera
that has always bugged me:
everyone sings
instead of talking.
But you made
me believe
I was in a magical world
where singing
is talking.
Thanks!
You know, of the three tenors,
you’re my second favorite!
No wait, I forgot about
that other guy.
Sorry, you’re third.
Wait, Homer,
before you go,
there is a new note
I’ve been working on.
Tell me what you think...
(sings operatic note)
Hmm...
what if you gave it a little
more of this flavor...
(sings operatic note)
Like this?
Keep reaching
for the stars, kid.
(sings operatic note)
(sings a groan)
Happy anniversary,
sweetie.
You know, it might be
a little more romantic
without your entourage.
But I need my childhood friends
to help me keep it real.
Would you have me keep it fake?
Homer,
can’t we please be alone?
It’s our
anniversary.
We’ll move
to another table.
Yoko.
See?
Isn’t it nicer,
with just you and...
Excuse us.
Would you mind signing
autographs for my mother and me?
(chuckling):
Oh, my pleasure.
To the hottest girls
in the room.
(chuckles)
What is he saying?
I said you look hot!
Hot!
-Ay Chihuahua!
-Ay chi-what?
(screaming):
Hua-hua!.
I want you to stop
flirting with women.
No problem.
Sir, may I say
I thoroughly enjoyed
your performance.
May I say
I’m enjoying the calm waters
of your deep, blue eyes?
Oh, well...
(chuckles)
What?
That’s how guys talk.
(growling):
Oh.
You are out
of control!
The late nights,
the eating!
You’ve actually
outgrown your cape!
Oh, Homie...
I miss our
alone time.
I miss you.
Need some help, H?
Want us to take Marge shopping?
You guys go on,
we’re gonna walk home.
Great call, H,
walking’s the best.
I really want to
hook up with Homer.
Now we both know
that ain’t gonna happen,
but, uh, I’m right here.
(radio clicks on)
(Jane’s Addiction’s
"Superhero" plays)
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah. ♪
Marge, when I’m onstage,
I can only sing
those love songs
by picturing
your beautiful face.
So in a way,
my groupies are really
our groupies.
Aw, you’re sweet.
WOMAN:
Oh, my God, it’s him!
(women screaming)
Use your opera
glasses, Dorothy.
DOROTHY:
Switching to thermal imaging.
Target acquired.
(panting)
Oh, we’re trapped.
Your fans will
rip us to pieces.
-Not me, they love me.
-(groans)
(ladies screaming)
Get on.
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
Sir, thank you
for saving us.
Do you want
to come in for coffee?
That’s right, I’m a woman.
A lady motorcycle driver?!
What is this,
The Twilight Zone?
It’s a shame a few
out of control fans
can make the rest
of us look bad.
I couldn’t agree more, Julia.
Listen, I love opera,
but I hate the way these people
treat your husband.
Why don’t you
make me president
of Homer’s fan club
and I’ll keep the
crazies in check.
That’s a great idea.
To celebrate, I’ll go whip us up
some Chex Mix pie.
So did you see
the show tonight?
Remember the part
where I forgot the words
and I just sang
"Uh-oh Spaghetti-os"?
I’m hoping
they send me a case.
(unzips)
Now listen, Homer.
You can have me
anytime you want me.
Marge!
But if you say
one word to your wife,
I’ll tell her you attacked me.
MARGE:
What is it, sweetie?
Um... everyone’s
wearing clothes in here.
That’s nice.
(on phone):
Mr. Simpson will
send you a photo
if you send him
a self-addressed envelope.
-(clicks)
-Mr. Simpson cannot
sing at your daughter’s
birthday,
but he will come for cake.
-(clicks)
-Dedicate your shopping center?
What’s the anchor store?
I don’t think so.
She’s perfect!
For the first time
since you became
an opera star
I can finally relax.
Well, uh, I’m not sure
she’s working out.
(Homer shrieks)
(Mozart’s "Don Giovanni" plays)
(screams)
(shrieks)
That’s it!
Let me make
something very clear:
my heart belongs
to Marge and you can
never, ever have it.
This opera’s over
when the fat man sings.
All right, Homer.
I understand perfectly.
You shall never be mine.
That’s good.
You’ve calmly accepted
that you will never have the
only man you could ever love.
Now, I think it would
be best if you left.
-Julia, wait!
-Yes?
Before you go,
could you hire your
own replacement?
But make sure
she’s not crazy like you.
(Mozart’s "Don Giovanni" plays)
(screams)
Die, you stupid cobra!
Die! Die!
(giggling)
Dad, I think someone’s
trying to kill you.
Who could it be?
A disgruntled former employee?
Whoever it is, the cobra
is their symbol.
HOMER (singing arpeggios):
♪ D’oh, d’oh, d’oh,
d’oh, d’oh, d’oh, d’oh ♪
♪ Woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Stu, stu, stu,
stu-pid Flanders ♪
Why the crescendo,
my dear, old friend-o?
♪ Get lost you waste
of a moustache. ♪
Okily-dokily.
Chief, I think we should
cancel the performance.
No can do, Marge.
My first duty is to the
season-ticket holders.
But don’t worry,
I’ve got the entire
opera house on
a complete lockdown.
I got sharpshooters
on the gargoyles,
inflatable Homer
decoys in the seats,
and to take out
the biggest threat of all,
we’re pre-crashing
the chandelier.
(glass breaking)
("Se Il Mio Nome Saper Voi
Bramate" begins)
♪ Se il mio nome ♪
♪ Saper voi bramate ♪
♪ Dal mio labbro
il mio nome... ♪
(groans)
I’m so tense.
I can’t enjoy Count Almaviva
serenading the intended bride
of Dr. Bartalo.
I just can’t.
I don’t see anything suspicious.
Except someone is loudly
unwrapping their candy.
It ain’t candy, it’s a lamb chop
wrapped in foil.
Hey, Mom, do all
conductors carry
poisoned blow-darts
in their pocket?
Well, Arthur Fiedler used to,
but I’d better take a look.
(gasps)
Chief Wiggums!
The maestro is the killer!
All right, I’m going in.
(horns blasting notes)
(moaning)
Allegro! Allegro!
-(orchestra plays faster)
-I mean, andante. Andante!
-(playing slower)
-Ah, yeah.
(grunts, thuds)
Snipers, take the shot.
(gunfire)
(crashing)
Okay, that’s a wrap, people!
Luckily, the sniper bullets
stopped her heart
from pumping the poison
through her body long enough
for the chandelier
to squish it all out of her.
With any luck, she’ll be up
and stalking within a week.
(chuckles)
I’m sorry you got hurt,
but you learned
an important lesson.
One comes between
me and my Homie.
(surly):
I’ll get you for this, Marge,
if it’s the last thing I do.
(normal voice):
Oh, and I scheduled
the cable guy
to come on Wednesday
between 10:00 and 2:00.
Oh, but Wednesday’s
not good for me.
(surly):
I know, Marge. I know.
(evil laugh)
Let’s go, Hagliacci,
or should I say,
Madame Butterface?
-What? What?
-I had two.
Well, that’s it.
I’m retiring from the opera.
It’s just too popular.
And I know something
much more fun
I can do on my back.
Singing opera made me
good at painting.
-Is that a real thing?
-No.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem