To the Navajo, the earth and its creatures
have great influence over our existence.
The stories, passed from
generation to generation...
...help us to understand the reason for
our tears of sadness and tears of joy.
Animals like the bear,
the spider, and the coyote...
...are powerful symbols to our people.
When the FBI man, Mulder,
was cured by the Holy People...
...we were reminded of the
story of the Gila monster...
...who symbolises the healing powers
of the medicine man.
In this myth, the Gila monster
restores a man by taking all his parts...
...and putting them back together.
His blood is gathered by ants...
...his eyes and ears by Sun...
...his mind by Talking God and Pollen Boy.
Then lightning and thunder
bring the man back to life.
At the end of the ceremony,
when the FBI man had been healed...
...we heard the news from other
Native Americans in the northern plains...
...that a great event had taken place.
Like the Navajo, these people
have their own stories and myths.
One of these stories tells
of the White Buffalo Woman
who came down from the heavens...
...and taught the Indians
how to lead virtuous lives,
and how to pray to the Creator.
She told the people
she would return one day.
Then she turned into a white buffalo
and ascended into the clouds...
...never to be seen again.
But on this day, when the Holy People
had given the FBI man a miracle...
...a white buffalo was born.
And every Native American knew,
whether he believed the story or not, . ..
...that this was a powerful omen.
And that great changes were coming.
I've got the digital tape.
You're lying.
I've got it in my pocket.
I took it out of Mulder's desk.
(footsteps)
Drop your weapon!
- Put it down, Scully!
- No way.
- I said put it down!
- I said no!
- You're setting me up!
- I'm trying to help you!
- Then put your weapon down!
- Not a chance.
- You're not here to kill me? Prove it!
- I'm not here to have a gun in my face!
Damn it, Skinner!
Drop your weapon!
- Back off!
- Put it down!
What the hell is this?
- You OK, Scully?
- Yeah.
Get his gun.
Give her the gun!
- Give it to her!
- All right.
Now I want an explanation.
I was warned that somebody would kill me.
Someone I trusted.
I'm gonna reach into my coat pocket
and end this charade. All right?
I presume you both know what this is?
Now I want an explanation.
Your cigarette-smoking friend killed
my father for that tape. Then he killed me.
- What are you talking about?
- I was a dead man. Now I'm back.
What is on this tape?!
Defense Department files
that reveal the truth
about our government's involvement...
...in the global conspiracy of silence about
the existence of extraterrestrial life.
- Give me that tape.
- It stays with me.
Give her the tape.
If what you say is true, if the information on
this tape is valuable enough to kill for...
...then it's the only leverage we've got
to bring these men to justice.
It's not gonna do us any good
if it falls back into their hands!
Then you'd better make sure it doesn't.
- Come on, Scully. Let's go.
- Where?
There are truths out there
that aren't on that tape.
- Mulder, I...
- Whatever you're...
I went to your father's funeral.
I told your mother that
you were gonna be OK.
How did you know?
I just knew.
My daughter was brought here.
- What's her name?
- Dana Scully.
- Melissa Scully?
- No...
That's her sister.
We just had a Melissa Scully in surgery
with a cranial gunshot wound.
Missy?
It's Mom.
We took drastic precautionary measures
due to the nature of the wound.
We've induced coma to try and
relieve the trauma on the brain.
- Is she gonna be OK?
- We've done everything we can.
We'll be monitoring her around the clock.
Nurse, why don't we get Mrs Scully
a comfortable chair?
That's my father on the left there.
- This was taken when?
- About 1973.
Amazing. Langley, take a look.
Do you recognise any of those men?
Are you familiar with a post-World War ll
project known as Operation Paper Clip?
The US government provided
safe haven for Nazi war criminals...
...in exchange for their scientific knowledge.
I know who this man is.
Victor Klemper.
The man next to your father
is one of those criminals...
...though not the most famous of the bunch.
Wernher von Braun,
designer of the V-2 rockets...
...may be the most notorious,
but Klemper takes the prize...
...for the most evil Nazi
to escape the Nuremberg trials.
- What did he do?
- Experimented on the Jews.
Drowned them, put them in pressure
chambers... All in the name of science.
Together with von Braun,
Klemper helped us win the space race.
Using his scientific data we were able to put
astronauts on the moon before the Soviets.
One giant step for mankind(!)
What would he be doing
in a photo with your father?
I don't know.
- Do you recognise anybody else?
- No.
Operation Paper Clip was supposed
to have been scrapped in the 1950s.
- But if this is 1973...
- What happened to Klemper?
He's still here, living very well at
the expense of the American taxpayer.
(door opens)
Unbelievable!
We thought you were history!
You'll have to wait for my video collection.
(Langley) Where were ya'?
At DC General,
scanning the police frequency
when I heard the report of a shooting.
Agent Scully...
- What is it?
- Your sister's in critical condition.
Scully!
Scully, wait! Scully!
I have to go there, Mulder!
That bullet was meant for me!
If they're trying to kill you,
that's the first place they'll look.
Those bastards!
I'll call someone who can help.
The only thing you can do for her
right now is to try to crucify them.
This is a serious mistake.
An innocent woman's been shot.
- Can this be traced?
- This is your man.
There was a mistake. It will be rectified.
BY Whom?
By whom will this be rectified?
Your ridiculously ineffectual assassins?
They're professionals.
This is not a profession
for men who make mistakes!
My God, you presume to make us believe
you can simply fix it with enough bullets?
No.
This woman... Scully.
I know she believes her partner is still alive.
Mulder's dead.
I took care of it myself.
And the computer tape containing the
stolen files you tell us was recovered...
You can show it to us?
I wasn't aware that my honesty
was in question or doubt.
Do you have the tape?
Of course I have it!
I think I'd like to see it.
So would I.
I have vouchsafed it for reasons of security.
I'll have it here for you tomorrow.
By which time this whole matter
will be cleared up.
(door opens)
- Victor Klemper?
- Yes.
My name is Fox Mulder. This is Dana Scully.
- Your name is Mulder?
- Yes. I think you knew my father.
- What's this about?
- You did some work for our government.
I'm old now. History bores me.
Because it escaped you?
Or because you escaped it?
Freud, Salk, Crick, Watson...
These will be the names they celebrate
at the end of the millennium.
Great scientists.
But Klemper? He will be remembered
only as a butcher.
History may be the onlyjustice you'll know.
Do you know my work?
Do you know what we accomplished?
As a Nazi? Or for the blood money
we paid you?
We were young men caught in a fervour.
But our experiments changed the world.
- For a lot of innocent Jews.
- Progress demands sacrifice, and I...
I have confronted my demons.
And soon I will die too.
Like my father. They killed him
and I believe you know why.
I believe they would kill anyone
if it is in the best interest of the work.
What is this "work"
that my father was involved in?
- I have no answer for you.
- You knew him! Was he a murderer too?
Some things you don't have to know.
No, I need to know!
I need to know the truth!
Isn't that what you want?
For the truth to be known?
Do you know the formula
of Napier's constant?
Yes. Why?
The photo was taken at the Strughold
Mining Company in West Virginia.
That is all I will tell you.
The rest you can find out yourself.
Let's go, Scully.
(ringing)
Hello?
Yes. One moment.
It's for you, sir.
- Yes.
- It's Klemper.
Victor!
How are you, old friend?
- It's been far too many years.
- What is it, Victor?
I was just paid a visit by the son
of one of our old colleagues.
What did you tell him, Victor?
I told him that you were
the most venal man I've ever met.
Beyond that, I told him nothing.
Mulder is alive!
I think it's time to call our friends...
...who will handle this matter
more satisfactorily.
- Are you expecting visitors?
- Is it Dana? ls Dana here?
No. It's a man.
He says he was asked to come here.
My name is Albert Hosteen. I was asked
to come and help with your daughter.
- There must be some mistake.
- Is your daughter the FBI woman?
- Dana?
- Yes.
She's very sorry she can't
come here to comfort you.
- You know where she is? Is she OK?
- Yes. I believe so.
- She is weak.
- She's getting better.
She has the best doctors.
They're watching her around the clock.
If it's all right,
I would like to pray over her here.
What would your father
have been doing here?
I don't know. He never came home
wearing a miner's cap.
Mulder, take a look at this.
- What do you think?
- I'd like to try door number one, Monty.
I'm trying 27828. It's not working.
- Nor here.
- Are you sure it's the right number?
Napier's constant is the basis
of all natural logarithms.
With a crowbar and a small nuclear device,
I might be able to get through one of these.
Mulder!
No, wait. Hang on a second.
Whatever we find in here,
you haven't had time to process everything.
- I'm OK.
- You couldn't go to your father's funeral...
...and if something in here was to cast doubt
on the kind of man he was...
I just know how it would affect me.
You called me.
Yes, I did.
About?
I may have located the digital tape
you're looking for.
You may have located it?
Yes, although it may fall
into the hands of people...
...who might use it
for purposes not your own.
You wanna work a deal?
Is that what this is?
Let me tell you somethin'.
I don't work deals.
I thought you should know
of certain potentialities.
- Do you have the tape?
- As I said, I may have located it.
Do you have the damn tape?!
- I'll know more when we next meet.
- I do not negotiate. Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
- I don't think you do.
I don't think you understand at all.
No, I'm quite aware of your policies
in those regards.
Then I hope your next
course of action will be more...
...cautious... and informed.
Mulder, look at this.
(Scully) It looks like they're storing records.
(Mulder) or what?
Of medical files, by the look of it.
They've got names, alphabetised.
Lots of files.
Lots and lots of files.
- What's in these files?
- Standard medical forms.
Birth certificate,
smallpox vaccination certificate...
- And then there's this.
- What is this?
It's an old tissue-collection cassette.
The new ones are plastic.
- Do they all contain the same materials?
- Yes, exactly.
- What year was this person born?
- 1955. All these files are 1955.
- What year were you born?
- 1964. Why?
Let's go find 1964.
You're looking for a file on me?
Dana Katherine Scully.
What?
It's a recent tissue sample.
What the hell is going on here, Mulder?
I don't know, Scully.
- That's your sister's file.
- Yeah.
- What are you looking for?
- I don't know.
Look at this.
- This file was originally mine.
- I don't understand.
(high-frequency tone)
- Wait here, Scully.
- Mulder, where are you going?
Mulder?
(hissing sound)
(shouting/guns being loaded)
There!
Find the woman too!
Scully?
Mulder!
Mulder, I'm down here.
- You OK, Scully?
- I heard gunshots.
- I've been looking for you.
- What happened?
We got a small army outside.
I think they got us trapped.
I think there's a way out down here.
This place isn't even on the map.
You'd be surprised what's not on the map.
And what our government will do
to keep it that way.
- How's that?
- Last night we were chased by a hit squad.
Driving what looked like CIA fleet sedans.
I may be able to negotiate a deal
that would guarantee your safety.
What kind of deal?
I'll turn over the tape
in return for your reinstatement.
- No, sir. I need that tape. I need those files.
- I'm talking about a way to save your lives.
And I'm talking about
an elaborate conspiracy.
Do you know what we found last night?
What?
An elaborate filing system
of medical records.
Locked inside a mountain vault.
- For the purpose of?
- I don't know.
But the answer's on that tape. In those files.
- Is that answer worth your lives?
- It's obviously worth killing us for.
What do you hope to find, Agent Mulder?
Why they killed my father.
And what happened to my sister.
And what they did to Agent Scully.
I think we should let him
make the deal, Mulder.
Look...
Those answers mean nothing
if we're hunted down like animals.
We are operating so far outside of the law,
we've given up on the very notion of justice.
We have turned ourselves into outsiders.
We have lost our access and our protection.
What makes you think
there's any such thing as justice?
Then what good are those answers
to anybody but you?
- What we found last night...
- Look, I want exactly what you want!
But I need to see my sister.
I suppose you already tried
to make a backup of the tape?
It's copy-protected.
I couldn't get a hard copy to print either.
What makes you think
they'll honour this deal?
Because if they don't...
...I'll go state's evidence and testify.
Or they'll have to kill me too.
It's up to you, Scully.
I told Skinner to make the deal.
But not to hand over the tape
until you agreed to it.
- I'm sorry about your sister, Scully.
- I just need to know she's gonna be OK.
(car starts up)
(Albert) For two days I had prayed
for the FBI woman's sister.
Her doctor said she was getting better...
...and her mother, who would not leave
her bedside, was able to sleep.
But word had come from my brothers
in the north that did not give me hope.
The white buffalo calf had survived...
...but after a day it would no longer
drink its mother's milk.
On the third day, the mother buffalo
laid down in her stall and would not get up.
They said the men could do nothing for her.
That night she died.
My father taught me when I was a boy
that this is how life is.
That, for something to live,
another thing must often be sacrificed.
This was my fear now for the young woman.
I'm here to see Melissa Scully.
My name's Walter Skinner.
I'm an assistant director at the FBI.
I'm very sorry about your daughter.
Dana asked me to deliver a message.
- You've been in contact with her?
- Yes.
I wanna know where she is and if she's OK.
She's OK, but she's in
a very serious situation
which prevents her from being here.
What kind of situation?
One that we hope to reverse
so that Dana can come back to work.
That man you just saw,
he's been very curious about this room.
Who are you?
My name is Albert Hosteen.
I was asked to come here.
Albert, do not leave this room. Understand?
Yes.
I could use a beer.
Do you want anything?
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
(Mulder) Mr Klemper?
Mr Klemper?
Hello again, young lady.
- Where's Victor Klemper?
- Oh, poor Klemper.
They found him yesterday.
Apparently, his heart had given out.
You killed him, didn't you?
You're one of the men in this photo.
You knew my father.
Yes, since we were young men.
You were involved in this project.
You know why medical data was collected.
Yes, I do indeed.
In 1947 a spacecraft was reportedly
recovered in New Mexico.
No doubt you know of this, and of the
reported recovery of a body at the site.
These incidents coincided with
not only the end of World War ll...
...but an ignominious project which brought
Nazi scientists and war criminals...
...to this country to exploit their knowledge.
Operation Paper Clip.
Yes, you know of it already.
And you must also know
the work of Dr Josef Mengele...
...the Nazi "Angel of Death".
He thought he could produce a super race
through genetic engineering.
As did many of his colleagues
at the Institute
of Hereditary Biology and Racial Hygiene.
- Like Victor Klemper?
- Poor Victor.
He loved his orchids.
Did you know he was able to create
some of the most beautiful hybrids?
Klemper was trying to create
an alien-human hybrid.
That's what I saw in the boxcar.
He was using human subjects.
- Mulder, wait!
- My father was involved in this?
The technology wasn't there! DNA wasn't
even identified until 1944! This is all a lie!
When your father realised what
the medical data was being used for...
...he objected strenuously.
He collected those files?!
With the threat of nuclear holocaust,
the government instructed
men like your father...
...to gather genetic data
on the general populace...
...for the purposes of
post-apocalyptic identification.
The vaccination records.
They took tissue from everyone
who had a smallpox inoculation.
Hundreds of millions of Americans.
So Hamper had access to a DNA database
of nearly everyone
who was born since 1950.
This man is telling you
everything you want to hear.
But it's a fabrication.
It is pure science fiction.
- There were no experiments with aliens.
- Why would I lie to you?
Like you said before, to protect yourself.
And the continuation of the Nazi agenda.
Human tests.
Why was your file there, Scully?
- I don't know.
- There were current records!
- Yes, but records of what, Mulder?
- Of abductions!
Of abductees!
They took my sister.
Why?
They took her as insurance because your
father threatened to expose the project.
Why her? Why not me?
It's not for me to say.
But your life is in danger now too.
You also threaten to expose the project.
You have become your father.
- Why are you telling me this?
- It's what you want to know.
Isn't it?
Is there more?
More than you'll ever know.
(ringing)
Yes.
Yes, he's just arrived. One moment, please.
You have a call, sir.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- I'm alive.
Ain't that a surprise!
Yes! Good! Good, good. Where are you?
Somewhere you'll never find me,
you double-crossing son of a bitch!
Are you sure?
I'm sure of this.
If I so much as feel your presence...
...I'm gonna make you a very,
very famous man.
You understand?
Yes, thank you. I'll report that to the group.
I've just received confirmation that
the digital tape containing the stolen files...
...was destroyed in a car bomb explosion...
...which killed Agent Scully's
would-be assassin.
What about Mulder and Scully?
I've a meeting with the FBI.
They wanna make a deal.
For what?
For nothing.
There'll be no deal.
There's no deal to make.
Fox? What time is it?
It's after two.
- Did you drive up here? Why didn't you call?
- I needed to see you in person.
I need to ask you something.
Something that happened a long time ago.
Oh, Fox, I don't remember anything.
I told you before.
Mom, listen to me. When Samantha...
Before she was gone, did Dad ever
ask you if you had a favourite?
- Did he ever ask you that?
- Fox, please!
Mom, did he ever ask you to make a choice?
- Don't do this!
- Mom, listen to me! I need to know!
Did he make you make a choice?
No. I couldn't choose.
It was your father's choice!
And I hated him for it.
Even in his grave, I hate him still.
Now...
...you wanted to see me?
I have the tape you've been looking for.
Really?
I'm prepared to hand it over, or destroy it,
in exchange for Mulder and Scully's safety.
- And for their reinstatement.
- What did I tell you, Mr Skinner?
I don't negotiate.
Especially with punks like you
who think they can bluff me.
- Bluff you?
- You haven't got any tape.
You haven't got any deal.
You can't play poker if you're
not holding any cards, Mr Skinner.
You ever wondered what
it would be like to, uh...
...die in a plane crash?
Of botulism? Even a heart attack's
not uncommon for a man your age.
You think I'm bluffing?
I'm not finished yet.
Albert.
(speaks Navajo)
What is this?
This is where you pucker up
and kiss my ass!
- Listen...
- Listen to me, you son of a bitch!
This man's name is Albert Hosteen.
Remember that.
If Mulder and Scully
come down with so much as flu...
...Albert will recite chapter and verse, file
for file, everything on your precious tape.
It's a nice try, Skinner.
You're thinking Albert is an old man...
...and there are plenty of ways
you might kill him too.
Which is why, in the ancient oral tradition...
...he's told 20 other men
the information on those files.
So, unless you kill every Navajo
living in four states...
...that information is available
with a simple phone call.
Welcome to the wonderful world
of high technology.
You're bluffing.
Am I?
It happened three hours ago.
She went into surgery. The damage to her
brain was worse than they had hoped.
Her blood pressure started to rise and...
...she slipped away.
She died for me.
I tried to tell her I was sorry,
but I don't think she'll ever really know.
She knows.
Melissa knows.
You were right.
There is no justice.
- I don't think this is aboutjustice, Scully.
- Then what is it about?
I think it's about something
we have no personal choice in.
I think it's about fate.
Skinner told me that he talked to you.
That you were insistent
about coming back to work.
If Melissa's death is...
I need something to put my back up against.
I feel the same way.
We've both lost so much.
But I believe that what we're
looking for... is in the X-Files.
I'm more certain than ever
that the truth is in there.
I've heard the truth, Mulder.
Now what I want are the answers.
(Child) I made this!