There is an ancient Indian saying...
...that something lives only as long
as the last person who remembers it.
My people have come to trust
memory over history.
Memory, like fire,
is radiant and immutable...
...while history serves only those
who seek to control it...
...those who would douse
the flame of memory...
...in order to put out
the dangerous fire of truth.
Beware these men,
for they are dangerous themselves, ...
...and unwise.
Their false history is written in the blood
of those who might remember...
...and of those who seek the truth.
Let's go)!
Get down! Get down!
Don't move!
On your knees! Hands behind your head!
- I wanna know where Mulder is!
- I don't know.
His car is parked outside! He was here!
I want Mulder and I want those files!
You will find nothing here.
What happened?
There were men.
They were looking for your partner.
Where is he?
Mulder!
Out of the car!
Come on!
Hands on top! Spread your legs!
- Where's Agent Mulder?
- Turn and face away!
Where are the files?
In the trunk.
- We need the DAT copy.
- I don't have it.
Who has it?
Agent Mulder.
Let's go)!
It is the recommendation of the
Office of Professional Conduct...
...that Special Agent Dana Scully
be given a mandatory leave of absence...
...until the full detail of her misconduct
can be calculated.
This summary action is justified
under the OPC articles of review...
...and Agent Scully will complete
her suspension of duty
without pay or benefits...
...due to the nature of her insubordination...
...and the direct disobedience
of her superior agents.
We will have to ask that you check
your weapon and your badge...
...before you leave the building,
Agent Scully.
Make yourself available to answer further
questions on Agent Mulder's whereabouts.
I've told you everything I know. To the best
of my knowledge, Agent Mulder is dead.
Don't think this hasn't
been difficult for everyone.
Agent Scully!
Who are these people?
They're doing their job.
They're putting an official stamp
on the perpetuation of a lie!
They're following protocol,
which you and Agent Mulder did not!
And the people poisoning Mulder's water?
Whose protocol was that?
- The investigation...
- Will be an exercise!
The men who killed Agent Mulder
and his father aren't meant to be found.
We will find them.
With all due respect,
I think you overestimate your position
in the chain of command.
Where were the safeguards against this?
These files were never to be seen.
Forty years of work.
The damage could be incalculable.
- The damage is done.
- Gentlemen, we have control.
The files have been recovered and the men
involved in the theft have been removed.
There is a matter of concern with the FBI.
We'll handle that internally, as usual.
The media attention will amount
to a few scattered obituaries.
The Mulder problem.
Special Agent Mulder is dead.
His body will not be recovered.
He'll be listed as missing until
the matter can be resolved quietly.
And we've recovered the copy
of the stolen computer files?
Yes.
Then the pertinent parties
should be informed
and we can continue with our work.
- Dana!
- Hi, Mom.
What are you doing with your shoes?
They started to give me blisters, so...
You walked here at this time of night?
Oh, Mom...
- What is it, Dana?
- I've made a terrible mistake.
Dad would be so ashamed of me.
The men who had come and threatened us
did not return to our house again.
But the following day
some of the boys from the reservation...
...came to tell us they had seen buzzards
flying out near the quarry...
...where Eric had first encountered the men.
The buzzard is a large but cowardly bird.
It does not work for its prey,
letting others provide the kill.
When I see them circling in the desert...
...this can only mean
that something has died
and they are going to pick its bones.
Or that death is close...
...and they are waiting for it
to do its work for them.
We did not see what they saw...
...but I remembered something
I had seen as a younger man.
Just as my grandson had done...
...I too had found a body at the quarry...
...in a hole, half buried under rocks.
But even the buzzards,
who will eat anything...
...would not touch it.
This spot is where we found
what the buzzards had come for.
We could not tell at first who
or what it was,"...
...but I knew what the buzzards knew:
that the smell of death was upon it.
The desert does not forgive man
his weakness.
Weak or strong, it takes no mercy,
and can kill a man in less than a day.
(speaks Navajo)
To survive, one must develop
skin like leather...
...know where to find water
and when to take shelter.
The FBI man would have surely died
had he not stayed underground...
...protected like the jack rabbit or the fox.
Even so, death was near.
In accordance with our ancient traditions...
...we put four oak twigs
on the beams of the hogan...
...to summon the Holy People
and tell them that a ceremony will be held.
It is called the Blessing Way chant.
Only the Holy People
can save the FBI man's life now.
He is in their hands.
(doorbell)
Frohike.
I know it's late, but I heard the news.
Maybe I should go.
Pardon my presumptuousness.
How much have you had to drink?
Do you recycle?
He was a good friend.
A redwood among mere sprouts.
I guess this means
he's passing you the torch.
I'm afraid not. I'm soon to be out of a job.
Those sons of bitches!
They're rigging the game.
And, like rats,
they just scatter back into the woodpile.
- The rats that killed the cat.
- What's this?
It's a news item about Kenneth Soona,
aka The Thinker.
The man who hacked the MJ files.
The ones he gave to Mulder.
"Kenneth J Soona
was killed execution-style...
...in what appears to be
a professional murder...
...his body found in the Trenton city landfill."
What's the date on this?
This was the day before yesterday.
This is after Mulder disappeared.
Could they be so stupid?
This healing ritual called the Blessing Way...
...has been passed down
by our ancient Navajo ancestors.
Its songs and prayers must be followed
just as they have been for centuries.
Or the Holy People will not be summoned.
I watched my father perform
the chants as a young boy...
...and saw their healing magic.
But my fear for the FBI man was that
his spirit did not want to be healed.
That it wished to join the spirit
of his own father who had died...
...and did not want to return
to the world of the living.
His body has become tired and weak,
and it searches for rest.
(chanting)
If the struggle to continue is too hard...
...or the wish to join his ancestors
too strong...
...the body will give up.
But if the desire to resume life
burns brightly enough, ...
...the Holy People will be merciful.
The days and nights now will be long
and difficult for the FBI man...
...as the Holy People come
and help him to choose.
I was first struck by the absence of time...
...having depended on it so completely
as a measure of myself and my life.
Moving backwards into the perpetual night,
it consumes purpose and deed...
...all passion and will.
I come to you, old friend,
with the dull clarity of the dead...
...not to beckon you...
...but to feel the fire and intensity...
...that still live in you.
And the heavy weight of your burdens,
which I had once borne.
There is truth, you know, friend,
if that's all you seek.
But there's no justice orjudgment,
without which truth is a vast...
...dead...
...hollow.
Go back. Do not look into the abyss
or let the abyss look into you.
Awaken the sleep of reason,
and fight the monsters within and without.
(panicked screeching)
(screeching continues)
Hello, son.
I did not dare hope to see you so soon.
Or ever again hope to broker fate...
...with a life to which I gave life.
The lies I told you...
...were a pox and poison to my soul.
And now you are here because of them.
Lies I thought might bury for ever
a truth I could not live with.
I stand here, ashamed of the choices
I made so long ago...
...when you were just a boy.
You are the memory, Fox.
It lives in you.
If you were to die now...
...the truth will die.
And only the lies survive us.
My sister...
Is she here?
No.
The thing that would destroy me...
...the truth I felt you must never learn...
...is the truth you will find...
...if you are to go forward.
(tour guide) OK, step through
the metal detector and we'll begin the tour.
This facility is the J Edgar Hoover Building.
It was finished in 1974 and built on
the site of the original FBI headquarters.
There's a display on the "Ten Most Wanted".
You might see a few of your relatives there!
If you have any questions,
I'll do my best to answer them.
Makin' you come in the front door
these days, Agent Scully?
For now.
(Dew)
- Are you carrying your weapon?
- No.
- Sorry to have to run you through this.
- That's OK.
That was weird.
I've had a stray pin left in a shirt collar set
this machine off. But you can go on through.
Thank you.
Scully, come in, please.
You said you needed to see me
concerning the investigation?
Yes, sir.
I came across a news article. A man's body
was found and I have reason to believe...
...he was killed by the same man
responsible for Agent Mulder.
Can I see it?
The date of death postdates
Agent Mulder's disappearance.
Now you already have the ballistics data
from Agent Mulder's father on file.
I'd like you to run it against
the ballistics from this man's case.
To try and prove what?
Well, if both men were killed by the same
weapon, Mulder didn't kill his father.
And it could help us find the men who did.
You've been relieved of
your investigative function.
Yes, I know that, sir.
I just thought this might be helpful.
I'm afraid not.
This case would have been handled by
the Trenton PD. They're on our database.
If there was a match on the two slugs,
we'd know by now.
You don't wanna check?
Miss Scully, I think you underestimate the
duties and responsibilities of my position...
...as Assistant Director.
I was trying to cooperate
with your investigation.
And enhance your chances
of reinstatement.
- No! I just want answers.
- And so do I!
I wanna know why I was asked to execute
a search warrant on your apartment...
...to look for a digital cassette.
I don't have it.
Is this tape what Agent Mulder died for?
I believe so.
You wanna bring me a smoking gun,
Scully, you bring me this tape.
Otherwise I would ask you to go home,
sit tight, and let us do ourjob.
Is that all, sir?
Yes, that's all.
Did you ask her about the tape?
She says she doesn't have it.
Is that what she says?
Yes, that's what she says.
Well, that's unfortunate for everyone.
Back again?
I'm curious about something.
Can I go through here again?
Come on through.
(Dew)
This thing is more sensitive
than a toothache.
Would you mind running the wand
over me one more time?
Sure.
(alarm)
- Are you wearing a necklace or somethin'?
- No. Not today.
Then what the hell is that?
- What do you think it could be?
- I don't know. It's embedded in soft tissue.
Looks like maybe a piece of buckshot.
I don't know how it could've gotten there.
I can feel it just under the skin.
And now that I'm looking at it closely,
there's a tiny scar over it.
If you want,
I could do a local and pull it out of there.
Yeah.
Thanks for coming down here so late.
No problem. You were probably wounded
in the line of duty and didn't even know it.
For three days the Blessing Way chant
was performed.
The FBI man suffered great fevers...
...and his body burned like fire.
There was doubt that he would recover.
But the spirits were in attendance.
Because, on the night of the third day,
he opened his eyes and asked for water.
The ritual bath must be given
outside the hogan before sunrise.
The FBI man was weak from his journey
and did not wish to speak.
But, like a rising sun,
I sensed in him a rebirth.
Still, it will take time to regain his strength.
Well...
...it's definitely not buckshot.
I, uh...
I know what it looks like to me, but, uh...
...I couldn't tell you how it got there.
Take a look.
It looks like a computer chip.
That's what it looks like.
I don't even know
how long it's been in there.
I have absolutely no recollection
of it being put there.
God, it's frightening!
Dana, this is very serious.
You gotta find out what this is.
I don't have access to the FBI labs.
I'm talking about access
to your own memory.
You've buried this so deeply,
you can't consciously recall it.
- Melissa...
- I know someone...
No!
What are you so afraid of, Dana? That
you might learn something about yourself?
You're so shut off to the possibility
there could be any other explanation...
...except for your rigid,
scientific view of the world.
It's like you've lost all touch
with your own intuition.
You carry so much grief and fear that you've
built up walls around your true feelings...
...and the memory of what really happened.
Just do this for me, as your sister.
Please.
I'll induce a non-ordinary state...
...a modified form of hypnosis
which involves Holotropic Breathwork.
This will quiet your interpretive mind
so we can cut through the interference...
...with your memories and perceptions.
Now, what I want you to do
is to maintain a focus on your breath.
Relax your breathing.
Now I want you to close your eyes...
...and think of a place where
you've always felt comfortable...
...and safe.
You told me of your experience
of being taken away and losing time.
Do you remember how you felt
just before this happened?
I was afraid.
Do you remember what you were afraid of?
That I would die.
But you didn't die.
Someone must have cared for you.
Do you remember who that someone was?
There were men.
A man took me.
There was a light and...
...loud sounds. My, um...
- My ears were pounding.
- They performed a procedure on you.
- Do you remember any pain during this?
- I'm trying...
The sound is all screwed up.
There was an alarm.
I remember, um...
They wanted to know if I was all right.
Maybe you trusted them not to hurt you.
Could this be possible?
I don't know.
At the FBI you work with people
you must entrust with your life.
Could it have been one of these people?
I had to trust them...
I was powerless.
I couldn't...
I could not resist them.
If this is too painful, I want you to go back
to that comfortable place where we began...
- ...and try again.
- Uh! No!
I'm sorry.
I'm trying, I'm trying.
I don't think this is working.
I don't think we're getting anywhere.
Thank you, but you'll have to excuse me.
You must be careful now
to end the ceremony properly.
If you leave, you must not do any work,
change clothes, or bathe for four days.
That's gonna cut into my social life.
(laughter)
The boys have a gift for you.
You asked for them
during your worst fevers.
During my fever,
I... I left here and travelled to a place.
This place.
You carry it with you. It is inside of you.
It is the origin place.
It wasn't a dream?
Yes.
We are done now.
(ringing)
Skinner.
(Scully) You came to see me today.
Excuse me?
You came to my apartment.
I assume you wanted to see me.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I saw you come out of my building.
You've obviously made a mistake. I'm sorry.
I need some air. Excuse me.
(Mulder) I have been on the bridge
that spans two worlds, ...
...the link between all souls by which
we cross into our own true nature.
You were here today,
looking for a truth that was taken from you.
A truth which was never to be spoken
but which now binds us together...
...in dangerous purpose.
I have returned from the dead
to continue with you.
But I fear that this danger is now
close at hand. That I may be too late.
So we are here to mourn
the passing of William Mulder.
To join in our grief for our loss.
To share also the memories of a man
whose life was rich and full...
...and who made his family's and his
friends' lives richer and fuller as well.
Sadly, I've been informed today
by the mother of William's children...
...that his son, Fox, could not be here
to join us in this time of sorrow.
- Mrs Mulder?
- Yes.
I'm Dana Scully. I work with your son.
Um...
I know what you may have heard
from the FBI...
...but I have a strong feeling
your son is going to be found.
Oh, my goodness gracious!
- I think he's still alive.
- How do you know?
I just have a very strong feeling.
- I'll let you know as soon as I do.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
Hello.
I see you're a friend of the family.
So am I.
Do you think we might speak?
- About?
- A very serious matter.
Please, can we find someplace
away from the others?
I couldn't help overhearing
your conversation.
- You think the son is still alive?
- Who are you?
I'm a member of a kind of consortium.
We represent certain global interests.
What kind of interests?
Interests that would be threatened by
the tape you are no longer in possession of.
- Threatened enough to murder?
- Oh my, yes!
- What do you know about Mulder?
- That he is dead. Cui bono.
- You're lying.
- I'm not here to tell you lies.
- What are you here for?
- To tell you your life is in danger too.
- Leave me alone.
- They'll kill you one of two ways.
They'll send someone, possibly two men.
They'll kill you at home
with an unregistered weapon,
which will be left at the scene.
Using false documents,
supplied by associates of mine...
...they'll be out of the country
in less than two hours.
- You said there were two ways.
- Yes.
He, or she, will be someone close to you.
Someone you trust.
They'll arrange a meeting or come
to your house unexpectedly.
Do you have someplace else
you might stay?
- Why? Why kill me?
- You want something they don't.
Jusfice.
And because they are now certain you don't
have the copy of the files they're looking for.
Why are you protecting me?
I feel my colleagues are acting impulsively.
Your death will draw unnecessary
attention to our group.
- You're protecting yourself.
- Why should that surprise you?
Motives are rarely unselfish.
- What kind of business are you in?
- We predict the future.
The best way to predict the future...
...is to invent it.
Good day, young lady.
Mom...
My God!
Fox!
I can't believe it. I'd expected the worst.
I need your help, Mom.
I don't have much time.
They said something terrible had happened.
I'm OK.
But I need your help.
I need you to remember.
I need to know more about Dad.
Who these people are.
It was all so long ago.
I need you to try to remember, Mom.
These pictures were taken in 1972. Where?
I don't know.
Dad worked for the State Department.
He'd go on the road. Where?
- I don't remember, Fox. Please!
- Look at the pictures, Mom!
- Don't do this to me!
- Look at them!
He must have talked about the men
he worked with. Were they ever here?
Yes.
But I don't remember their names any more.
What does this have to do with, Fox?
I think it has to do with Samantha.
I think it has to do with
what happened to my sister.
(ringing)
Hello?
Dana, it's your sister. Where have you been?
I had to go to Boston, for a funeral.
- I was worried about you.
- Why'?
I haven't heard from you
since you saw Dr Pomerantz.
Missy, something strange
happened to me today. I'm...
I'm a bit freaked out by it.
I'll come over.
Are you gonna be there for a while?
Yeah, I will.
OK. I'll see you in a bit.
(phone rings)
Hi.
(caller hangs up)
(Scully dials)
Come on, come on, come on!
(ringing)
Hi. This is Melissa.
Sorry to have missed your call.
Leave a message and I'll call you back.
Have a really nice day.
(Dew)
Missy, it's me. Please pick up.
Missy?
Missy, pick up...
I'm coming over to your place instead.
I'll look for you on the way. Bye.
(car starts up)
Scully, get in the car.
- I need to talk to you. It's very important.
- I was going to my sister's.
I'll drop you there.
I need you to come with me.
- Where are we going?
- To a place we can talk in private.
After you.
Eyes forward.
Put your hands where I can see them.
Don't turn around or I'll blow your head off.
- Don't think I won't do it, you son of a bitch.
- I believe you. Just stay cool. I'm with you.
Take two steps forward.
Now move slowly towards the couch.
Turn around and sit down on your hands.
Are you gonna let me tell you why I'm here?
I know why you're here.
I wanna know who sent you.
Whose errand boy you are.
No one sent me.
You've got the rest of your life
to give me answers.
(gunshot)
Oh no!
Damn it!
What's wrong?
Let's get outta here.
How high does it go, Skinner?
Who's pulling the strings?
You can kill me
but you'll be doing their work for 'em.
Forget about your job and family.
You'll spend the rest of your life
behind bars.
There isn't a judge they couldn't persuade.
What's the alternative? Let you kill me now?
I didn't come here to kill you.
I came here to give you something.
I've got the digital tape.
You're lying.
I've got it in my pocket.
I took it out of Mulder's desk.
(footsteps)
Subtitles by Visiontext
(Child) I made this!