He's got me overseeing
the satellite launch
out of Tanegashima.
- Good for you, bro.
- Can't keep a good dog down.
Bill told me
as part of the handover
where some of the bodies were buried.
If it does come out while
I'm in charge, I'm dead.
I'm tired of this. Come in.
I can see through you and this
transparent little offer to buy me off.
Maybe, I should just let them
come for you.
If this is the way things
are gonna go then fuck off, Dad.
Shiv gave me a hall pass.
And what?
Shiv has that same arrangement?
I don't know, Greg.
It's not a competition.
I don't think
it's a good idea for him
to come to the wedding.
How would you like half a bill
for your share of Waystar?
Why don't we talk this over with Sandy?
Sandy Furness?
He's already in on Waystar.
I have the shell company attached
to his private equity fund.
Keep your money. Bring me in.
We go fuck my dad together.
Leverage buyout. Hostile.
- What's your end?
- CEO.
And you're sure you got the stomach?
Yeah. I'm good.
Here they are!
What's he do... What's he doing?
Come on, it'll be fine.
It'll fit!
I'm afraid he's not gonna drive through.
- He says it won't fit.
- Well, clearly it'll fit.
What is he, vehicle dysmorphic?
The bridge has a three-and-a-half
ton weight limit,
and he's worried about his mirrors.
Well, which is it, Charlotte?
The story keeps changing.
Hey, hey! Come on down!
This is not my intended welcome.
We will... We will sort it, Tom.
Hey!
- Morning!
- Hey, good to see ya.
We can just get buggies and...
Buggies? How the fuck long
will that take?
We just need to round up
the buggies and...
I work in hospitality, Charlotte,
so I can smell bullshit.
- Mom!
- Honey!
Hey! Hey, Daddy!
Hey, Tommy, it's great to see ya.
Couple of hours?!
It was wonderful
just sitting there.
We liked watching the planes.
Your father thought he might
have seen the man from U2.
- OK.
- And Arthur Laffer,
of the Laffer Curve? Are they coming?
Well, uh, could be. It's mostly
rock gods and economists.
Hey, hey, it's the Fly Guys!
- Good to see you!
- You made it, man!
Tommy, your mother's a little thirsty.
- Mommy, you thirsty?
- A little thirsty.
I don't want to be a trouble, Tom.
It was my fault.
Grab a bag, and then we'll go...
I'll follow you up.
I hope you're happy now, Charlotte,
'cause my mother is dying of thirst.
And I've just picked up a bag.
I'm carrying a case on my wedding eve.
All right. I gotta go.
But I'll see you there, OK?
I managed to change
the time for the embassy,
and...
- Sorry. Are we OK?
- Oh, yeah.
Gil, you don't
have to come to the wedding
if you're too busy. That's...
We've just been doing
the media monitoring.
Motherfuckers. I'll fucking kill him.
I'll take them to pieces!
He's not sleeping.
It's what's-his-name.
Got under his skin.
Screwdriver-face.
Oh, the bit...
The bit where he implied
he murdered his wife.
Yeah, for some reason
that's somewhat irked him.
Gil, you don't need to focus on this.
We can hit it.
I know. I'm focused.
I'm X-raying this briefing
for salient facts.
I mean, I don't want to make
a big thing out of this,
but is it possible your father
is the worst human being who ever lived?
Uh, I... I don't think that's...
Is it true he's not
coming to the wedding,
out of... what, spite?
Well, it's complicated.
I want to take him out.
I want to destroy ATN.
I'm not sure that's wise.
And if I said it was wise,
would you have a problem with that?
No.
In the end, Gil,
I'll do whatever you want.
Siobhan, look. If there's something,
anything, you can get me,
I'm in a fuckin' knife fight here,
I'm holding a dildo
made out of American cheese.
So this is really
gonna happen, yeah?
You know I don't want ICBC as
part of the syndicate, right?
Uh, 75 to 150 basis points,
and point two percent commitment fee.
Then, uh, then, yeah. Fuck yeah.
- I feel good.
- Holy shit.
Without them we're good to go.
Let me call you back.
Um, has your sister
ever heard of Lake Como?
Has she ever heard of Venice,
St. Barts, the Maldives?
Has she heard of these locations?
She must be aware of them.
I got the call. You get the call?
I got the fuckin' call.
Shall we go inside? Come on.
What? In here?
Brother, we are putting
together a hostile takeover
of one of the largest media corporations
in the world.
I think we can brave
some non-vintage champagne.
Wow. Um, can we get some champagne?
A bottle, please? Thank you.
What are we talkin'? Like ten days?
Then we go in for the kill?
- Yeah.
- Can't keep it on lockdown
for more than about ten days, right?
- Yeah, that's about it.
- John?
- John? John!
- So, like...
Have you got any that champagne?
The 19th for the bear hug?
- Yeah. Good. One little thing.
- Good.
The Canadians, there seems to be
a little static on some details.
- Like what?
- Like... you as CEO.
What do you mean?
Relax. OK?
This doesn't happen without you.
It's normal co-investor bullshit.
- Frank knows those guys. You want me to...
- I'll handle it, dude.
No leaks. Please.
Not to Frank, not to anyone.
Why are you so jumpy about this, Ken?
Why am I jumpy?
About fucking Rome,
fuckin' Shiv and Connor,
probably blowing what's left
of my dad's fuckin' brain?
About taking the company
out of family control, forever?
I don't know, Stewy.
Why would that make me jumpy?
Look, I don't give a fuck.
But, I mean, do you want me to ask?
I'm just curious to see
if she's gonna come begging.
- Because I can ask.
- I don't want to ask.
If she wants to ask, she can ask.
'Cause I can physically see her.
Gerri, I don't want to ask.
OK.
She comes crawling,
then I'll think it over.
- Fine. OK, I get it.
- Who's there?
- Um...
- Have you seen Caroline?
Is she still with
that chinless hippie prick?
I thought we might miss the rehearsal.
We don't need to rehearse.
We're gonna kill it.
Did you think again about your dad
and whether we want to reconsider...
- Fuck him.
- Right, right.
And did you think again about
whether we want to go Wambsgans
or Roy-Wambsgans or, as I said,
I'd be willing to just drop traditional
and go Tom Roy,
in fact, for myself, if...
Um, hey, I wanted to ask you something.
Uh-huh?
I could do with knowing
about the bad thing in Cruises.
You know, the thing that meant
you couldn't sleep?
Uh-huh.
- No?
- Uh... I...
No, I don't...
No, I just think, yeah,
I just think, you know,
church and state and...
and AC/DC and...
ebony and ivory
and never the twain shall meet.
Yeah, right, but you always
wanted to make it public.
- Didn't you?
- Yes. Yeah.
- In my bones, I did.
- Exactly.
But I did then destroy
all the evidence, so...
I guess... you know, if it's bad,
the longer you leave it,
the worse it'll be when it comes out.
Yes, unless
it never comes out. You know?
I bet it's not even that bad.
Uh, it is quite bad.
It's quite bad.
- Oh, fuck, here we go.
- Look, honey.
This is where it's happening.
Ooh.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
- It's exciting!
You spoken to the Wicked
Bitch of the West yet?
I just got here, Shiv.
Is this gonna take long?
Shall we?
- Saddle up, soldier.
- Oh, come on.
She can't be that bad.
Yeah, just don't look at her directly.
Hello! Hello, hello!
- Hi.
- Here you are.
I knew you'd arrive eventually.
Tom. Remember Tabs?
- My mom.
- Hello!
- Tom.
- Hi.
Gosh, look at you.
You're very plausible.
Oh. Thank you.
Exactly.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, Kendall.
Tabitha, have you guys met?
- Have you all...
- Bro.
Ruff ruff! Ruff!
So, shall we go and play happy families?
Yes. Great.
Mm-hmm.
Well done on Tom.
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Tell me again why you're marrying him.
- Mom. Come on.
- Joking. I like...
- I like him!
- OK.
And I want to say
I hope this can be nice.
I really appreciate
your coming over here.
OK. It's no worries.
My travel agent
specializes in guilt trips.
Hey! Hey!
Apologies. Did I miss anything?
- No.
- Happy day.
Caroline Collingwood.
Pleased to meet you.
Likewise, your excellency.
Gregory Hirsch.
Greg!
- You're Greg Egg.
- Excuse me?
You're Greg the Egg!
When you were born you looked
like a little misshapen egg.
I... did... Yeah, I did hear tell of...
Oh, God. And your dad used to try and
sleep with all the men in Sausalito.
How's your mother?
Uh, good. OK, yeah.
Solvent, currently. Debt free.
Great. Come on in.
Come and see our little church.
These are all my disreputable
slave-owning ancestors.
Very nice.
- Oh, my God. Tom, did you see?
- What, Greg?
- Did I see what?
- That's the girl from Brooklyn.
From your bachelor party.
Who sucked your dick and
made you swallow your load.
Greg, that's not very wedding-y.
- But that's her.
- I know.
Greg, her name is Tabitha,
and she and Roman are dating.
Which is cool. So please, do not
act like an unsophisticated rube.
- OK. Wow.
- Yeah.
He really liked her, and it's fine.
It's just one of
those weird urban things,
like when you go to see standup
and the comedian is your dentist.
- OK? Yeah?
- Yeah, yeah... Oh!
- Hey!
- Hey.
- So,
- we should, uh, get going.
- Yeah, let's do it.
I'm Willa, by the way.
I'm Connor's partner.
Fantastic. And what do you do, Willa?
Oh, um, I'm a playwright.
- Wow. Fantastic.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- America.
And what do you do, Connor?
Well, um...
Connor doesn't really do anything.
Do you, Con?
I think they're all
gathered now, Patrick.
- Shall we?
- What?
What?
Shit.
Just to get things straight,
am I right that the father...
I understand the father...
Couldn't be bothered.
He's... He's not well. He's not well.
Yeah, that's the story.
Everyone remember the story.
So, uh, I will be performing
the father role.
Great.
Listen, I didn't mean you
don't do anything. Just...
Well, that's a shame,
because that's what you said.
No, you know, I mean, nothing
like my writing. Nothing...
Safeguarding 30,000 acres of
wilderness, that's nothing?
Being on the verge of setting up
a podcast on Napoleonic history
with a considerable level of
investment interest, that's nothing?
- No, sure, it's...
- Crackin' the nut of happiness
like a modern day Thoreau,
well, that's nothing.
Con. You're great, OK?
You are. I...
It was a dumb thing to say.
Well, here we are.
The ancestral home
Caroline didn't inherit.
The thorn in her side,
the fishbone in her throat.
When we were kids, she wouldn't
even let us look at it.
What do you think?
I mean, it's massive!
I hate it.
- Hey, so, listen.
- Mm-hmm?
You know the Canadians, right?
Yves, et cetera?
The pension fund guys?
- Yeah.
What do they think of me?
How do you mean? What's the context?
I can't give you context.
OK. That's very interesting context.
- Look, as a pal...
- Uh-huh?
Say there was a situation
where private equity
was trying to buy out
a major media company
and install a new CEO.
- How would they view me?
- Are you serious?
Fuck. So what, they're co-investors?
Come on, you know those guys.
Behind closed doors,
are they of the opinion
I'm the real deal,
or in training?
And would there be room
to wet the beak of an old pal
- in such a situation?
- Frank, too soon. Too soon.
Get your hard-on out of my soup.
OK.
- So?
- Well...
I think they have a lot of time for you,
but there may be certain questions.
- Oh, shit.
- Well, you know,
they think they're hot shots.
They make hard jokes.
As in?
Well, sometimes when you were absent
they used to refer to you
as "the calamari cock ring."
I don't even know what that means.
I think it means they think
of me as a cock ring
made from calamari, Frank,
it's pretty self-explanatory.
- So what do we say?
- Well, I thought
we were gonna say "illness."
No, I don't like illness. Plays weak.
OK, we can say "busy."
What prick's too busy to attend
his own daughter's wedding?
OK, "family rift."
But we background brief that
Gil's campaign is like a cult.
"What is this grieving senator's
mysterious hold on Shiv Roy?"
We sprinkle some of that.
It makes her look weak.
And it makes me look like I'm...
None of my kids have gone round
the bend, or offed themselves.
We've always pushed
that you're a good dad.
- Because?
- Because you are a good dad.
Huh.
So, if you don't want to say, I mean,
work or illness or...
rift, do we just...
Fuck it. There's no way out.
I mean, if you want to go...
I don't want to go.
But there's no other fucking way out.
We can do whatever you want us to do,
and I'm so sorry if you think
we've done the wrong thing,
but they literally just called
and told us he was coming.
- Who's coming?
- Dad. And Marcia.
- Wait... Dad's coming... here?
- Yeah.
I thought you didn't want him to.
I don't.
I mean, it's your wedding, so...
Yeah. I don't want him here.
He's never apologized.
But Marcia called Tom, and...
And obviously I had to ask Shiv.
Meanwhile, she's already
called Charlotte,
- and they're on their way.
- Dad's coming?
Is it about the launch? Is he concerned?
Yeah, I'm sure he's
thinking about that 24/7.
So, I mean, what are you gonna do?
- You could just say no.
- Yeah. I could.
But what, just get security
to fucking stop him?
- Hold on.
- I could do that.
Yeah you could, but it might
cause a funny atmosphere,
because he did pay for all this.
If he's got the stones to walk
in here, what are we gonna do?
Put the dogs on him? Tell him
there's no seat, he's gotta stand?
He's given us no choice.
So now I hear he is coming.
- Yeah.
- Well, that's wonderful.
- Oh, come on, Mom.
- No, no. It's fine.
I just hope you won't forget about me
when your father arrives
with the head of his
Middle Eastern operations.
- Marcia?
- Yeah, Marcia.
Do you still find her
a bit...? You know.
Actually, we became quite
close during Dad's illness.
Oh, well.
What a sweet little scene
that must have been.
Very touching, I'm sure.
- Actually, it's quite good.
- Why?
Just your being the second-most
important person at your wedding.
Take the pressure off.
Mm. Oh, this is delicious.
Well, I'm very glad you like it.
Because it cost a pretty penny.
Well, it's delicious. It tastes like it.
- Um, sorry. Just a second?
- Oh, no. Of course.
- Hi. Excuse me.
- Hi there.
Got any protein for us to use?
Protein? I'm not a fuckin' hen
to lay you eggs.
- I'm a strategist.
- I know. It's just... Gil.
- What?
- He'd like a word.
OK.
- Hey. Hey!
- Hey. How ya doin'?
I gotta say, you knocked it
out of the park with the wine.
It's delicious.
Gil.
Listen, I don't mean
to be overly dramatic,
but I was assured when I accepted
that your father wouldn't be here.
I know. Plans changed, I was ambushed.
This is not OK from my POV, Siobhan.
This compromises me.
And you were very eager
that Gil would come along.
I mean, it's...
Well, yeah, when I invited you
I didn't realize
it was gonna be a chore.
He's just weighty, Shiv.
He carries his gravity.
He's not a man, he's a fucking planet.
Look, there's no press,
and there's no pictures.
We got jammers and a fucking
hawk to take out drones.
It'll be like it never happened.
I hear you might have
something explosive
I can use.
Yeah, maybe. I'm working on it.
But just not yet.
Let's destroy ATN, Shiv.
Wouldn't that be a nice wedding gift
to the American people?
Oh, yeah, sure,
I'm just concerned
about collateral damage.
- Tom.
- Tom?
- He'll be fine.
- Says the man
who has literally no idea
what he's even talking about.
Shiv, come on.
I have all the arguments
on monopolies, and news,
and the coarsening of the public sphere,
but I kind of start falling asleep
when I hear myself talk.
Give me something salty, Shiv.
Get me a stick of dynamite
I can shove up his fuckin' ass!
OK, I get that.
Come here. You know Gil.
Yeah, sure.
Pleased to meet you, Senator Eavis.
Likewise.
How are you finding it
outside the evil empire?
Oh, fine. I'm fine, thank you.
And how do you like it
here in the lion's den?
Oh, I've been to zoos before.
You like drinking our champagne?
I'm a "champagne for all" guy,
not a "gruel for all" guy.
Hey, you know Senator Eavis.
Sword of the dispossessed
and lover of vintage champagne.
I guess technically,
I should take a swing at you.
Technically, I should
call you libelous scum.
Are you gonna calm the shit-talk down,
or are we gonna have to ramp things up?
Is your dad gonna stop poisoning the
discourse of our great republic?
Have you got a laptop?
Do you see the shit out there?
We're the fucking good guys now.
Join in, by the way. Feel free.
No?
Shiv? I mean, your guy here
is shit-talkin' our company.
Oh, yeah, we don't talk about that.
That would be a conflict of interest.
Oh, lies!
Oh, 'cause you... Yeah, the lies.
Can't wait for the big one
tomorrow. Right?
Well, these hands
aren't gonna fuck themselves.
Nice to meet you, Senator Beavis.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- Nice to finally meet you.
- Tom Wambsgans.
Obviously. Nate.
Uh-huh. Right.
Right.
I just wanted to say
thanks for having me.
I'm Tabitha.
Hi. Well, I've heard
very little about you.
What can I say?
Best man won.
Ha ha. As in?
You won the Shiv-off, pal.
Good luck.
Right. And who... who are you again?
Nate? Sofrelli?
Did she never... This is embarrassing.
- Are you a pal of Kendall's?
- Yes.
- OK. Ah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Shiv and I, uh,
back in ancient history we...
Oh, right. Oh! Oh, I see.
Oh, OK, maybe she did.
- Right.
- Maybe she did.
Ah. The best man won.
Maybe.
There was an uncle who ended up
living in Gibraltar with a monkey,
and he swindled my mom's grandpa.
We used to come here as kids.
She lives nearby.
Oh, very good. Keep the
wound fresh and all that.
You know what, I'm gonna split.
I can see my husband-to-be
talking to my ex,
and it's making me feel
like I want to hurl.
- So, great to meet you.
- Yeah, fair. You too.
Have a good night.
Just to say...
so kind of your parents to have
paid for all this delicious wine.
Oh, not at all, not at all.
They wanted to make
a contribution, so...
So clever the way they're letting
every single person know.
Oh. Oh, good...
You OK?
Yeah, I think I just
got stabbed by your mom,
but I'm not completely sure.
Oh, yeah, that's how it works.
You'll bleed out in about an hour.
Can I... Can I talk to you
for... two seconds?
Uh, yeah.
So I just wanted to get you up here
to talk about the table plans.
Oh. And have you thought
any more about... Ow!
Whether you want to tell me
about the secret thing?
And I just wanted to, uh, say...
that I, uh, I did meet Nate.
Oh, you...
You've met Nate before. I think.
No? Oh.
Uh... Oh, well, he's a...
you know, he's a good colleague,
and, uh, he's a friend of Kendall's.
They ran around in Shanghai together.
And he's a dick.
Well, he's OK, but he has
a certain dickish quality about him.
- Uh-huh.
- I think I've mentioned him...
to you before.
Look, Shiv, uh...
Is this real?
What do you... What do you mean?
Am I... Am I a total jerk?
- Uh...
- Do you really want to do this?
'Cause we don't have to.
Do this?
- All the people are here.
- Yeah.
And... besides, I want to.
I do... I do want to.
I mean, is this...
W-What level are we on?
Are you fucking around on me?
- Tom.
- Honestly?
This Nate...
you know, I can...
I can... There are vibes.
Oh, Tom. What, as soon
as two colleagues are close...
D.C. loves gossip.
No, sure.
Sometimes there are rumors,
and people, you know,
they're not fucking.
But sometimes they totally are.
Honestly?
This is real.
I'm not fucking around on you.
Well, I trust you.
Good.
Thank you.
And that put... puts my mind at rest.
So...
You know, when...
when we met, I was in such a mess.
I need you. Hmm?
I do.
I...
If you want to know
about the secret stuff,
the cruise line stuff, I'll tell you.
Because we have to be able to trust.
Right?
Yeah?
Yeah, that'd be great.
- Hey. Hey. How ya doin'?
- Hi.
- Where are the kids?
- They're upstairs.
- Cool.
- They're sleeping.
- Yeah. Right.
- I saw Shiv.
How are the happy couple? OK?
Good, you know, maintaining the veneer.
Mm-hmm. You OK?
I'm fantastic. I did, like,
120 push-ups this morning,
so, yeah, I think I'm OK.
Wow. Wow. You did 120 push-ups.
Rava, I just have
a lot goin' on right now.
It's not...
not one of your
more relaxing interludes?
Yeah. It's not.
I'm, uh, I'm a big fuckin' stress knot.
What can I tell you?
I probably have a tumor
eating me inside-out.
You want another drink?
Your lawyers have gotten
a little quiet on me,
so I'm just wondering if that's...
Oh, yeah, I don't know about that.
Can you maybe give them a little nudge?
Sure.
I'll give them a nudge.
Ken. Ken.
Hmm?
- I know you...
- Oh, yeah, you do?
- Yeah, I know you.
- Really.
And if you want to talk, I am here.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I'm good.
Hmm.
Yeah, you know what,
the truth is my lawyers are stonewalling
because your lawyers
are trying to fuck me over.
So shall we just leave it to them,
and then you and me can just flirt
and you can do your whole
la-dee-fuckin'-da smile
and we can just be all chummy and
everything because I love all that shit?
Have a fuckin' line
if you need one that badly.
Yeah, I will, OK?
- Fuck you.
- Thanks.
Everything isn't what you think.
You know?
You can't see inside me just 'cause
I've told you the occasional...
Sorry.
Well, well, well. What the
fuck's going on here?
This looks mighty fucking cozy.
Um... hi. Hi, Kendall.
- Hi.
- We were just...
well, we were just saying that I think
that the first time I came here
was back when you guys
were kids, like...
maybe 1986, I think?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Right.
- Remember that?
Right. Great.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I should, uh...
circulate.
- OK.
- All rightie.
- We'll see ya later.
- Yep.
Well, I'm happy to tell, but
do we have to do it tonight?
You know, 'cause it's about the
corporate cover-up of crimes
and institutionalized sexual abuse.
Oh, fuck.
Well... bad for Dad. Great for Gil.
It's not very "wedding-y."
Yeah, still...
OK. So...
there were payoffs,
there was...
legal and semi-illegal intimidation...
And do you personally
have plausible deniability?
Yes, I think so. Yeah.
Digital deep-clean,
and I shredded the paper material.
- Great.
- An outside team.
And inside, signed
the paper out... Greg.
- Greg.
- Yeah.
Just thought family would be safest,
and Greg's expendable. You know.
What, you'd... kill Greg?
No. But you know, he's family, right?
- So we shut him up.
- Yeah, OK, right.
What are you gonna do with this?
'Cause if I give you the details,
it could really hurt me, Shiv.
You're not gonna let me get hurt?
No.
I'll need specifics.
OK.
So...
So.
Keep him away from me.
Your father's making a
subtle entrance... as I see.
Hey.
Come on. Forbidden fruit.
Nate.
Has the chicken laid the egg?
Uh, no. Not yet. No joy.
Look at you.
I'm desperate to make you concentrate
on nothing but me for just 15 minutes.
You think I used to concentrate on you?
Nate.
So, Greg Egg.
- Ah.
- How long do you give it?
I'm sorry?
The marriage. How long do you give it?
Oh...
Is there doubt afoot?
I mean, I for one think
they look solid as a rock.
But there you go,
I'm just an old romantic.
Yeah, yeah!
- Here we are.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- Hey.
I'm feeling... much better.
He's much improved.
Great.
Though you weren't actually invited.
Maybe I can get them to make you
an omelet and find you a chair.
I think usually the ones who
are paying get a chair, no?
Oh. I didn't realize
you'd contributed, Marcia.
So rude of me. Thank you.
Let's get to the fuckin' room, shall we?
How is the big man? Well, well, well.
It's good to see you. You good?
All good. Everything is
good, acquisition-wise.
All we have to do is shut down the voice
of the fuckin' people over there.
Oh, there he is.
- Will you excuse me?
- Absolutely.
Kendall.
Hey, Dad.
So, what about it, son?
You want to jump out of the
trenches and play a game of soccer?
Can I bring you some corn
to get you through the winter?
How ya doin'? What's the news?
Oh, keepin' busy.
You need a reference for your résumé?
Relatively punctual.
Prone to bouts of insubordination.
Yeah, well, you know.
So...
how long are you gonna
fuck about on the outside?
Uh-huh. You recruiting?
What, new Head of Being
Continually Thwarted?
How would a TV network suit you? Huh?
One of the big guys when I land it.
Could that work?
You feelin' the heat on your own?
Yeah? A little?
You want me back? Like to...
Like to put that in a press release?
I'm just a lovely guy.
Can you top me up, please?
So? What was all that about, cocksucker?
Oh, he was just telling me what
a sensational job you're doing.
Fuck you.
Did he mention the launch?
Does he know that I've accelerated?
Say something fuckin' funny?
- Hello.
- Oh.
Caroline Collingwood.
Mother of the bride.
Oh. Hi, I'm Stewy.
So, how long do you give it?
Uh, I'd say forever.
Or until Shiv goes away for the
week, whichever comes first.
Excuse me.
You... beast.
Hi. Mom. I hear you're asking
"how long you give it."
Just a cheeky icebreaker.
OK, well, it's pretty fuckin' horrible.
It's not all about you, Shiv.
Other people need something to say.
OK, well, can you ask them about
the price of fucking fish instead?
I like your girlfriend, Ro.
Oh, thank you. I met her at a sex party
where she was giving the groom
a blowjob.
- You should marry that one.
- Excuse me?
And Shiv, stop taking
everything so seriously.
I'm trying to sparkle.
When people ask me how long
I give it, I say forever.
- OK, well...
- It will be forever.
- Well, thank you.
- Or it'll feel like forever.
She says she's being impish.
She's being a stone cold bitch.
Hey, you want to meet up
later tonight? All together?
- At the place?
- Yeah.
So, uh...
you talked to the white whale?
What'd he have to say?
Nothing. I mean,
he's just shoring up his position.
It's not real. He's under pressure.
Are you good? No wobbles, right? You OK?
I'm not gonna get coldcocked here, am I?
'Cause I heard from Frank
the Canadians might
not be too keen on me.
You talked to
the fucking grandfather clock?
Has he signed anything?
No, that would just be rude.
I mean, he... he... he...
he used to give me flying lessons
in his fuckin' Cessna.
Come on, man.
You're not a little prince anymore.
Don't rely on Sir Talky
of Fuckchester, please.
He's good, Stewy.
Are we working upstate, or...
Ah. Mr. Fuckhead, I presume.
Logan Roy, Logan Roy, Logan Roy.
Are we allowed to talk?
I've nothing but admiration
for you personally, Mr. Roy.
Oh, really?
It's the sort of thing
you say, isn't it?
Ooh. Classy.
So, what is it you've got against me?
You're the one making it personal.
I'm just trying to do my job,
think of everyone, not just myself.
The interest of each is the good of all.
That is the whole of the law.
You don't need to remind me
of my Adam Smith.
- I taught economics.
- Where? Kindergarten?
What about "From each
according to his ability",
to each according to his need"?
What about, and this isn't me talking,
but what about me, Mr. Fucking Ability,
busting my chops
in my auto shop
so that some needy fuck
from the projects
can jack off on my time?
That's the issue, I'm afraid.
Well, I find that a very
reductive view of human nature.
I didn't make human nature,
but I do know what they read
and what they watch.
I make my nut off
what people really want.
Don't tell me about people.
I'd go flat broke in a week if I didn't.
Nice to meet you, Senator.
Yeah.
Sleep well, Dad.
- Night.
- Thank you.
Might be your last good one
for a decade or so.
Hmm?
The cruise situation.
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
Yeah, sure.
Well, you might soon.
Unless...
You could afford to be
un peu plus agréable, Siobhan.
You don't understand, Marcia.
Well, I know when I see a spoiled slut.
Excuse me?
Tu m'entends.
What the fuck? Who are you?
Apart from a machine
for gathering power?
You don't know how vulnerable
a human being can be.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Have you ever had a fucking
grapefruit without an agenda?
He made you a playground,
and you think it's a whole world.
Well, va te faire foutre.
Go out and see how you like it.
Fuck off.
Well, you two seem to be
the best of friends.
Don't.
Aw, come on. It's OK.
Hey. Pinky.
Someone will be in touch.
Great.
Mmwahh.
Hmm.
You know, you're fuckin' great.
Thank you!
You're not a head fuck.
Or a bitch or a leech.
You say such pretty things.
You never once asked to stay over...
or how it works with my dad,
or the trust,
or what my stake is, you know?
I'm just pathologically incurious.
What if I was prepared to marry you?
Hello?
Hiya.
- Right.
- What?
Shiv's getting married,
Kendall got married...
I see. So, how about you
come down off of Mt. Olympus
and propose to a mere mortal?
Yeah, what if?
- No.
- No?
- Crazy.
- Why is this crazy?
Because this isn't
a normal relationship.
Why?
Well, um, for one thing,
we never fuck.
Oh, yeah, we do.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah, come on,
yeah, we do,
we've been busy, that's all.
No, you, like, kind of
jerked off near me, once.
There's no need to be disgusting.
To be honest, Roman,
I've had more sexual contact
with the groom than I have with you.
I asked you not to talk about that.
I've slept with a lot of guys,
Roman Roy,
and if that is gonna be a
problem, you better say.
It's not gonna be a problem, it's Tom's.
You want to get married or not?
Babe.
Do you think this is the way
to get someone to stay?
Hey-hey, Gerri.
Thank you for meeting me here.
Uh-huh. What is this?
Uh, just a chat.
Right. It's your wedding;
Why do I feel like
I'm about to get fucked?
OK, it's late. Here's the situation.
I know all about the cruise
division horror show.
And the cover-up.
And Gil wants to go to town on you,
but maybe I can get him to hold off
if ATN stops the personal stuff.
Gil's wife.
You want us to stop attacking him?
Poor liddle fwagile
pwesidential candidate.
No, keep attacking him
all through the primaries,
fire up our base, and then just back off
for the general.
They're journalists, Shiv,
not remote-controlled little...
Yeah, sure they are. I just
feel confident that, you know,
a little public comment or two
from my dad, an email,
and the minions realign pretty quick.
So you are, um...
just to be clear...
Oh, yeah. No, I'm bullying you.
Yes. I'm blackmailing you.
I'm threatening to destroy my father,
- however you want to put it.
- And you're happy with that?
Oh, come on, it is what it is.
You used to be such a nice girl.
- And Tom needs to be clean.
- Oh.
Move him on, move him
up... maybe abroad.
Clean hands.
You're very pushy, missy.
Thank you, fairy godmother.
And if I was authorized to accept,
can you get Mr. Smith
to fuck off back to Washington
and not pull down his pants
to show off his amazing morals?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I can
persuade him that a dirty LBJ
gets more done than a clean McGovern.
OK, well, good night.
Hey.
No marriage advice
from my dear old godmother?
I don't know. I was never
very good at all that.
My husband died.
Don't let him die?
OK, what is this? I was in the
middle of a conversation.
Dude, I am super-sorry. Jess,
could you give us a second?
No. Stew? Seriously.
Ken, I got... I got Sandy on the line.
Sandy?
- Fuck.
- What is it?
He can tell you.
You can say, Stew.
What's with the theatrics?
Can you hold for Mr. Furness?
He was just there. Where'd he go?
You're not gonna say? Seriously?
Is this the coldcock?
I think it's just best that he tell you.
That's all.
You're such a pussy.
Is... Is it... Is this,
uh, Canadian shit?
Um... it's about that bear hug letter.
- Starting the takeover?
- OK.
An acceleration.
No, no, no. No, no, no. Fuck off.
This weekend.
- Hello, Sandy?
- At my sister's wedding?
Are you insane?
What do you want this to be,
One Wedding and Four Fuckin' Funerals?
Hello?
Hi. Yeah, he told me already.
No, absolutely not,
no way, no. No! Fuck this!
Listen, but you
told Frank Vernon.
I t... I...
That has... I... I hinted.
We've been contacted by a reporter,
and they know something's cooking.
We have to go tomorrow or risk a leak,
which kills us.
No. N... We're all together, OK?
This is... This is not a good time.
Well, it really is a good time.
Your dad's out of the loop in the UK,
we catch him off-guard.
No.
I... I need to, uh, you know, pr...
p-p-p-prepare.
Uh, I... I...
Sandy, I need...
prep time.
OK? F-For the approach.
You can't make an omelet
without breaking some dicks.
Look, I'm sorry. OK?
We'll be in touch with the letter,
and let's close-coordinate
on the minute it's presented.
OK? Thanks, kid.
Motherfucker.
- Hey. How ya doin'?
- Hey.
Where's Con?
- Uh...
- Did...?
- Con? Was he invited?
- Did you tell him?
- Oh... Come on. What?
- Oh.
You want me to get him? I told Willa.
Uh... my...
Fucking hell!
Why did you get in the boat?
No, I'm good. I got shit to do.
What?! Why are we here?
I thought this was for old times.
- Uh...
- No?
What about you, you wanna smoke my jay?
No, I got shit to do too.
A lot cookin'.
What the fuck! Really?
All right, one hit.
There we go, motherfucker.
Diss.
- Intercepted.
- Old times.
So listen, guys, um...
I do have something I need to tell you.
Um... I was at Mom's earlier,
she had me going through
her papers and stuff,
sortin' through some shit,
and it turns out, uh, Shiv...
you're adopted.
And Ken? You're adopted.
And Connor is obviously adopted.
And so all that shit's comin' to me,
so you can fuck off.
I'm sorry, I don't know why
I asked you down here.
No, it's good.
Congratulations.
I'm happy for you.
Thanks.
It's gotta not be so easy for you
to be on the outside,
seeing me do big shit.
Yeah.
Big of you. Thank you.
Yeah, well...
uh... can I suggest a hug?
- You serious?
- What is it... What?
- Yeah. I'm serious.
- Why?
Just... come on. Bring it in.
- You know you want to.
- I'm goin' butt-first.
Here I come.
- Here we all are!
- Ahh!
Ow! I think I cut the nipple right off!
I don't know, I mean, like,
I think I owe it to him,
but I don't want to be
the one to tell him.
You know?
I mean, like, what if he
finds out that I knew?
Like... I either...
I either owe it to tell him...
owe it to him to tell him,
or I don't owe it to him
to totally t... not tell him.
I think tell him.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Maybe don't?
I don't fuckin' know.
Right.
Well, no we can't do that
because that'll trigger
the disclosure...
Oh, shit. That's him.
Wait. Stop. Stop.
Great night. Th-Thanks for the ride.
- Hey, Tom!
- Hey, hey!
- Hey, wait up!
- Morning, Greg!
Look, Tom, uh,
I... I, uh, didn't know...
like, exactly how to tell you this,
and I've been up all night trying
to think exactly how to...
broach...
So I want to just say that... that...
I think that Shiv is, like...
No. N...
I think she's having an affair.
No. You're wrong.
No... No, I'm... I mean, not...
Shut up, Greg. Shut up.
Well, no, because I s... I...
- You are. You're wrong.
- Maybe I'm wrong.
You are wrong, so we're all good.
- OK. G-Good.
- OK? So, good.
Thank you for your time.
Yeah. And you don't want to hear...
I don't want to hear anything, Greg,
because it was a misunderstanding, OK?
- I saw what I saw...
- Shut up.
I just said shut up. Shut the fuck up.
All right,
but I think you should know...
No. Shut... Shut the fuck up, Greg.
- I'm trying to help you.
- Shut up, will ya?
- Fuckin' shut up.
- Dude! What the hell?!
I told you to fuckin' shut up!
Get off of me!
- Just shut up!
- What the fuck, man?!
- Yeah, I...
- Shut up!
You know,
I was quite outraged
when she suggested this.
I don't like being outside the U.S.
for too long.
Doesn't sit well.
And there's a mercilessness I miss.
I'm not used to
these squalid little deals.
Yeah, living with the safety catch off,
fuckin' without a rubber.
Everywhere else feels so soft.
I mean, look at this fuckin' place.
Yeah, well, it...
it's all quite refined.
Refined? Ahh.
Slaves. Cotton and sugar.
This country's nothing
but an off-shore laundry
for turning evil into hard currency.
Is this where you tell me you're
working for the communists?
And now it just lies here,
living off its capital,
sucking in immigrants
to turn it and stop it
getting bed sores.
I was looking forward
to taking you down.
You've got a very persuasive daughter.
But doesn't a deal feel so much better?
Handshake?
I don't think either of us
want to get dirty, do we?
Yeah.
You want to game it?
Sure.
Deliver the letter,
he calls emergency board...
we go public, world blows up.
The arbs dive in,
he tells the world some fairy tales,
talks poison pill, other defenses,
board says, "Hang on,
we don't want to get sued."
Thank you.
Dad says, "Fuck the shareholders,"
he calls analysts, calls hedge funds,
tries to find a white knight,
calls us, tells us to fuck off.
He's a good man, Pinky.
He's a good man.
Price rockets, because everyone
knows we're gonna win.
You think there's a
chance he'll just do a deal?
Have you met my dad?
Nope. He'll never retreat.
It'll be hostile, hostile, hostile.