There's a potential opportunity
for some acquisitions.
Local TV?
No one watches TV, Dad.
Why shouldn't we do all the news?
Well, Kim Jong-Pop,
because that's not how
things work in this country.
It's really happening!
We're getting married.
That is a very romantic
way of looking at a prenup.
He's actually acting kind of strange.
Like inviting me to Thanksgiving?
Dad?
He kept pouring, and
it just went everywhere.
It was like he didn't even see.
Dad! Hey! Whoa!
All you have to do is do
a little bit of shredding.
Don't make it a big
deal. It's okay. It's a job.
Shooting bolts into cows'
heads is a job, but I... I...
It's not how I wanna spend my Thanksgiving.
You just invited me into the chicken coop.
I'm gonna eat you all. One by fucking one.
I wondered if you could do me a favor.
Well, that might cause some ethical issues,
'cause there's a world
where my guy and your gal
ends up wrestling for the
Democratic nomination.
You lost, Grandpa.
Are you all right?
Take your hands off him, okay?
I've seen all I need to see.
So, are we doing this?
Don't ask me. He's your father.
I'd be doing it for him.
This is fucking impressive.
You hooked this shit up, friend.
Hey, brother, I just wanna
say you killed that shit.
My man. Absolutely killed that. For sure.
What's up, bro? Good to see you.
You're fuckin' imperial right now, OK?
I think American Diablo is your best album.
Thanks, guys. Much obliged.
All right, man. All right...
Are we supposed to follow him?
What's gonna happen?
Just be cool.
So, this guy's your boy, right?
Yeah. Hey, listen,
can I talk to you about something?
Mm-mm, sure.
Um...
Oh, here she comes. What's up?
So he's just decompressing, apparently,
but he's really down to connect.
Oh, he's decompressing?
What from his voyage
to the bottom of the fuckin' rap ocean?
His show was a shitty show.
But the label got a room for you guys.
Right here.
I'm sorry, what's your name?
Jess.
Jess. Sorry.
Can you just remind him
he's the guy that owns the company
that owns the company that owns the label
that pays his fucking ass?
Absolutely.
Yeah, just don't say those words.
Oh, my gosh, look at this.
Shrimp. Huh?
Look at this.
Warmed in this airless box for like,
what, let's say six hours?
And this goo? Is this
delicious fucking goo?
Look at that. Mmm!
So, listen, I need to say something,
but once I've said it I'll have said it,
and while it's not a
big deal, it's delicate.
What is it? You fucked the company?
I haven't fucked the company.
Uh-huh.
Scientology? What is it?
Look, we're friends,
we go back, I can trust you.
Right?
No.
Sure, but on money stuff, I can trust you?
Because we're calling a vote
of no confidence on my dad.
What the fuck, man.
It's the best way forward right now.
This is fucking terrible.
Bro, you're gonna fuck the company.
You're fucking with my money, Ken.
Look, I'm telling you, it's just cleanest.
He's lost it.
He's going to D.C. tomorrow
to piss away our political capital
and position us
permanently in a dying sector.
Do you think you can win?
Of course.
It's finished. I'm informing
you, not courting you.
Because I have to work with whoever's left.
Right. With me.
So are we good?
Can I count on your vote for Team Future?
I can promise you that I am spiritually
and emotionally and ethically
and morally behind whoever wins.
What's the matter?
I'm pissed because I
have to come down to him
like a fuckin' FedEx guy.
Why can't he come to us?
Well, I guess he's the president.
Fuckin' Californian shrunken little raisin.
I've seen ten of 'em.
He's basically a fuckin' intern.
Are you OK, Karl, on all this?
Yeah. Sure. Yeah.
On the law?
Yeah.
Gerri walked me through it too, so...
I wish she was here and not you.
Well, thank you.
She has to stay in the city
for board meeting prep, so...
It was a joke, Karl.
And I'm guessing if I
say cortado with almond,
you're gonna look like
I'm some kind of jerk, right?
I will have a black coffee,
please and thank you.
Is this safe?
I don't think we're gonna
bump into anyone here.
So how'd it go with Stewy?
It went great. He's in.
OK. Well, that's great.
Yeah. So I think we're all good.
Uh-huh.
Shall I just... run it one more time
before we open our kimonos in public?
Logan.
Once the vote is proposed,
he's recused... out of the game.
So we have Kendall, Roman,
Frank. Three votes in favor.
And Asha. Your pet. That's good?
Rock solid. Already floated and noted.
Right.
Paul, Dewi, Datu...
They're old guard, they'll go Logan.
Yeah, well, sure. I mean... but sure.
OK, Uncle Ewan, uh,
he's still a possible, right?
Um, you could maybe
stoke the old resentments?
Lady Macbeth, gettin' your
little fuckin' screwdriver in.
It's not a fucking teddy
bear's picnic, Roman,
it's a massacre.
Lawrence?
Dad would sell Vaulter for parts.
Lawrence would be
crazy not to vote with me.
Except Lawrence hates you.
We have three for Logan,
five against, three unknowns.
Come on, this is bullshit.
Look, we push, Lawrence is ours,
Ewan could be ours, Ilona could be ours.
Gerri can't vote, but she can
talk for senior management.
This is done. There's being cautious,
and there's being fucking time-wasters.
If you want me to do this,
you gotta look worst case.
Lawrence, Ewan, Ilona, all in play.
One more makes us sure winners.
Yeah. We, uh... we hit Lawrence.
I got the call. The nuclear
reactor is sealed off.
The infected have been shot.
Oh, that's great.
That's great. Thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
We're good.
OK. OK.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Yeah. Goodbye forever.
Hope so.
Three men
to own half the wealth of America.
I have just been given the all-clear.
Ohh! I feel I can breathe again.
Honestly, honey, it's
like this 900-pound gorilla
has finally stopped fucking me.
Now, is this the thing I
don't want to know about?
Yeah. And it's gone.
Poof.
I think I'm good. I think I'm good.
Greg. Me. The circle's tight.
He's good.
He's my little R2 unit.
I don't know.
Arrgh! I don't... This...
I don't fucking know!
Should I stick with her?
Is that a president?
Maybe. I don't know.
Now, not to be Groomzilla,
but can we talk about menus?
'Cause I really, really love Lake Como,
but I'm worried about the fog.
One thing is, people don't change.
You know, a candidate can't change.
You can primp and plump and repackage,
but if you want to change
someone fundamentally,
forget it.
So, should we go...
very old New York classy?
Oh. Yeah. Uh, I...
Sorry, I had a pretty shitty phone
call with my mom the other day,
and just to smooth things
over I said that we might
have the wedding back in England.
You what?
Yeah.
Is that a biggie for you?
Excuse me, Shiv. Fuck.
Tom, it's just a wedding.
The planners will figure it out.
"Just a wedding"? Shiv.
Yeah.
It's our wedding!
Oh, Tom...
It only happens once.
I can't do this right now.
Tom.
OK. No...
I'm trying to think about work.
And I'm looking forward to it,
but I just can't get
into it all, all the details.
I mean, the wedding might
be in England, but it might not.
OK, OK, sorry, sorry.
So, I'll take Lawrence,
and you firm up the others,
yeah?
That's OK. I got him.
No, I know the guy.
I see him at every fucking fakers party,
phony soft opening that I go to.
We're like two peas in
a metrosexual think pod.
Look, are we doing this?
Are we running a fucking
company together, or what?
Just 'cause I like a joke
doesn't mean I'm a fucking clown.
Look, Rome, I'm just trying to...
I got it.
I know you're not a clown.
I'm not.
It's delicate.
Oh, it's delicate? I didn't realize
it was delicate, the little nuances.
Lawrence fuckin' hates you, man, he does.
And he likes you?
Yeah.
He likes me. People like me.
I look like a matador and
everyone wants to fuck me.
I see him around. I know the guy.
Trust me.
OK.
Gerri says there are multiple indicators
he wants to be sympathetic
to our expansion.
You think so?
If he waves this through,
he gets hundreds of local TV stations
most amenable to talking about
what a great fuckin' guy he is.
He just needs to be prepared
to take a little political heat is all.
Four more years, we're
Proctor & Gamble of the news.
Hey. Tom. Uh, I'm heading to Washington.
Do you mind if I miss dinner? I
need to figure out about Joyce.
No, sweetheart, that's fine.
If you need to think about
your commitment to Joyce,
then go, do it. Go to Washington.
Yeah, I just wondered if
I picked the right horse.
No, I get it, I do. Yeah.
Slide her under the X-ray machine, baby.
OK. Love you. Bye.
You, too. Bye.
Hey hey, guy.
Hey hey.
Hey. Everything OK, Greg?
Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
Sure?
Good.
Good good.
You know, you can, uh,
you can talk to me about
anything. You know?
Oh, yeah. Well, I... Thanks.
Fantastic... resource.
OK, OK.
So, Shiv is going to Washington,
so why don't, tonight,
why don't I take you out?
No?
What, for real?
I thought you were gonna say
"take you out and
beat the shit out of you,"
or "take you out and put a bullet
through your dumb fuckin' brain,"
or something else, you
know, funny like that.
No, Greg, I'm not some beast.
Well, actually, I finally got paid...
Attaboy. OK.
It's like they're not
paying the light bill here,
but, um, but I actually got paid,
and I was thinking about
maybe going to, um,
have you ever visited
California Pizza Kitchen?
No. Dear Lord, no.
It's pretty delicious, Tom.
No. No, it isn't, Greg.
I mean, you might think
it tastes delicious, but...
They make a Cajun chicken
linguini just how I like it.
But that's not how
you're supposed to like it.
OK, you probably have
quite an undereducated palate.
So, let's go out, and I'll teach you.
And I'll show you how
to be rich. OK? It'll be fun.
He'll be just along the
hallway here, Mr. Roy.
I have been here before,
and I do know how hallways work.
Someone will be with you shortly.
What a fuckin' song and dance, eh?
Ah.
Mr. Roy. I am so sorry,
but the president passes
on his sincere apologies.
He's currently dealing with a
matter of homeland security.
He's sure you'll understand,
but he's going to need to offer
an alternative face for this discussion.
"Alternative face," what
the fuck does that mean?
If I drop my pants, I can
show you an alternative face.
How does that sound?
Have I been snubbed?
Find out if I've been snubbed.
I don't think you've been snubbed.
Is this a snubbing?! Just fucking find out!
Holy shit. Wamsgans!
A fuckin' black eye?
You should see the other guy.
The guy who jammed his dick in your eye?
Let's just say, uh,
I was in bed, with Shiv, so...
What? She punched you?
No.
Things just get a little hot and heavy.
A little freaky-deaky. So...
Fuckin' our sister? That's cool, man.
Yeah, it's kinda weird
when you talk about that.
No, I think it's really cool.
Like, what's it like,
like, to bang our sister?
So what's goin' on? Clue me in.
Uh, we just finished, bud.
Yup. Yeah, I'm gonna go, uh,
eat a fucking elk or something.
See ya later.
Oh, hey, Tom.
Just to say I know
you've been eating a lot of shit for me
that I don't know about,
and I appreciate that.
I like you.
You're Team Kendall, man.
Lot of stuff goin' down,
but you're on the team.
Thanks, brother.
Here's to us.
To us.
Uh, so I do need to ask something,
but, um...
we're cool, yeah?
Like, we're fuckin' disruptors, Yeah?
Yeah.
But, um...
what would you say...
what would you say if I told you
that there was gonna be a
vote of no confidence tomorrow?
Kick out the old man,
in with the new guard.
Romey and the homey.
You and Kendall are
thinking of killing your dad?
Well...
That's a little Greek tragedy.
Yeah, Oedipus.
Did I say that I was going to fuck Marcia?
No. Although I definitely
would, 'cause she's hot.
But that's, you know,
that's like phase two.
Hey.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Yeah, no. No worries.
This place has changed.
Uh... yeah.
I mean, well, e-everything changes.
We've changed.
What's this? Shiv Roy goes soulful.
Does not suit you.
It's like you're wearing a
turtleneck and a stick-on mustache.
All right, yeah.
Well, I do have feelings.
So, uh, congratulations on Senator Miller.
Thank you.
Not exactly the fuckin' Southern Strategy,
gettin' a bunch of Jews, blacks,
and media studies professors
to vote in a Democrat in
New York state, but still...
Fuck you. You've seen the numbers.
Yeah, there's a number of
ways of analyzing the numbers.
I did a fucking good job,
in the teeth of a scandal.
At this point in the cycle, I
knocked it out of the fucking park.
So here's to me.
How's everything in the
People's Republic of Gil Eavis?
Amazing.
So, go on, Shiv, what is this?
OK, uh, well...
I want you to think about joining us.
Me and Joyce.
Why?
Because I need a piece of shit on the team.
What do you think?
Is it a good idea? You and me?
Uh, yeah. Why?
Historically speaking,
we found it quite hard
not to fuck each other.
It's great to see you...
on such short notice.
Shush. Eat.
I finished most of 'em, Grandpa.
Your mother says you don't have any money.
Until recently, but actually, um,
my pay came through.
And now I'm incredibly rich.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Well, uh, I'm sure you're
going to be very happy.
Thank you.
She also told me to feed you,
so eat up.
Whew. Honestly,
I think my stomach might have shrunk
during my... my period of poverty.
The waste in this city is obscene.
Finish it.
So, how come you're here... You're in town,
uh, if I may ask?
Well...
you're a grownup, allegedly.
So here's what grownups do.
Kendall is gonna call for
a vote of no confidence
against his own father
at the next board meeting.
S-Sounds like a huge deal,
but it's just procedure or...
It's a wanton act of egregious selfishness.
In keeping with everything
else I've come to loathe
about this rat's nest of a family.
Right. Right.
So are you gonna tell Logan?
I'm gonna keep my snout of the trough,
thank you very much.
Paddle your own canoe.
Hmm?
Hello?
Kendall?
Marcia.
I was wondering, if you're not busy,
if you don't mind joining
your father for dinner?
Did he ask to have dinner with me?
Yeah.
He's home alone,
and I have something I cannot miss.
Um... just him and me?
Yeah. Is it a bad time?
Do you have something planned?
Uh, no. Of course.
Um, no, I'm... I'm around.
Thank you.
I've left some steamed fish.
Merci beaucoup.
OK, su...
Mmm.
Exactly.
When I had their monkfish, I thought I
was gonna shit, puke and cum all at once.
That sounds... delicious.
Although I don't actually
have much of an appetite.
Well, you better find one quick,
'cause this is one of the most
exclusive popups in the city,
and we're having the full tasting menu.
Uh-huh.
How come the... the wine
list doesn't have any prices?
Because they're obscene.
Look, here's the thing
about being rich, OK?
It's fucking great.
OK? It's like being a
superhero, only better.
You get to do what you want, the
authorities can't really touch you,
you get to wear a costume,
but it's designed by Armani,
and it doesn't make you look like a prick.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
If I was going to come in
with you, what's your vision?
Well, it's me and Kendall.
Fuck Kendall. OK?
You. What's your vision?
You know what?
I ended up in a book shop the other day,
and I just started laughing.
OK.
I was looking at all the books
cramming up all the walls,
and I just thought, you
know, about the olden days,
all the fucking monasteries and the Bibles
and the sermons and the "Did Jesus
say this? And "Do you mean that?"
and all the words and what have you.
All gone.
No one gives a fuck.
You're saying we're going post-literate.
People are gonna read,
but the old world, it's gone.
Papers, gone. News, gone.
"Tune in to ABS at nine
to be told what to think."
No. Over.
It's all about the morsels, man.
Feed me the fucking tasty morsels.
Keep me interested. That
is where we're headed.
Tasty morsels from groovy hubs.
Tasty morsels... from groovy hubs.
Um, look, man,
I'm dumb, but I'm smart.
I'm too dumb to know how to fix our whole
company. I don't have the attention span.
This is probably the most interesting thing
that's happened in my whole life,
and I'm thinking about six other things.
But I am smart enough to
know what needs changing,
and I'm smart enough to spot the people
who can help us, Lawrence.
So are you in?
Well...
I'm on the side of change.
Yeah, you are.
Sorry... Oh, fuck.
Mind if I take this?
Go ahead.
Sorry, fellas. Keep it sexy.
Yeah?
Marcia asked me to have dinner with Dad.
He knows. Does he know? I don't know.
Did he mention me?
What did Lawrence say?
Uh, he's in.
For real?
Yes, for real. Fuck you.
Nice. OK.
OK, great. Thanks.
Oh, Jesus.
What... What now?
Ortolan.
What's ortolan?
It is a deep-fried
songbird. You eat it whole.
Oh, my God...
This is a rare privilege.
And it's also kind of illegal.
Oh, I have a...
For the head.
The exact purpose is debated.
Some say it's to mask the shame;
Others, to heighten the pleasure.
Oh, my God.
That is so good.
Did you eat it yet, Greg?
Not yet, no.
Eat it, Greg!
Um, it's a rather... unique flavor.
Yeah, it's the gamy, brainy hit, my friend.
Oh.
Can we have some more wine, please?
You trying to seduce me, Tom?
Yes, I am! Yes, I am, Greg.
All the things we've seen,
all the things we've done...
We're in this together, man.
OK. Is that...
Is that what this is,
this is about the thing?
We have a bond.
You do?
Yeah, sure.
I was an outsider once.
Young guy from St. Paul, alone
in the big city, and it was hard.
And you create this
kind of protective shell,
but underneath, we're
all just little... nudie turtles.
OK.
I gotta level with you,
because if I eat any more
songbirds, I'm gonna hurl.
My grandpa already
bought me dinner tonight.
Your grandpa? What's he doing in New York?
He's come down for this vote of
no confidence in Logan tomorrow.
Did you know about that?
What? You serious?
Yeah, he's come down especially to vote.
It's a big deal, right?
Yeah. Hold on. Hold on.
You say you want me...
but really, you don't.
It's so exciting when you
know more about me than I do.
You want me for my edge,
'cause she's not edgy enough.
You should be workin'
for a winner like Gil.
You know I'm a considerably more successful
political strategist than you are.
Shiv, you work with what you got,
and what you got is... bleachh.
I've been grooming Joyce for three years.
Appeals to everyone.
Exactly.
Which is a little like
appealing to no one. She's nice.
That is a horrible thing
to say about anyone.
Look, Kendall told me
how you're marrying this...
guy, this corn-fed basic from hockey town.
Yeah, Tom. He's a great guy.
Sure.
Great guy with the square head.
And you're workin' for the nice black lady.
What are you trying to prove?
You're such a fucking prick.
You should be with an
exciting bastard like me.
I tried playing with you, and you broke.
Sir. Your father's on a call in the den.
He asked if you'd wait a moment.
Oh, sure.
Tom? Uh, hey, can this wait till tomorrow?
You're gonna want to
hear this. Ewan is in town,
and he knows, and he's come to vote.
What? Hold... Hold on.
Who's your source?
Uh, I can't reveal my sources.
But it's Greg.
OK. Uh, Tom,
you do not breathe a word of this, OK?
My lips are sealed.
All right. Thanks, Tom. I appreciate it.
It's not a big deal. Team Kendall.
My God. My God! It's actually happening.
It's happening.
The troops are taking Saddam's palace, man.
This time tomorrow, you and me...
I could... I could be like the...
I could be like the third most
important guy in the company.
I mean, it's the storming of the Bastille.
Let us eat cake. I mean...
I don't know what we're talking about.
Thanks, Richard.
Hey, Dad.
Hey.
You shouldn't eat this shit.
You're not the boss of me.
Did you want to talk? Marcia
said you... wanted to see me.
Marcia.
Yeah, she's got her own game goin' on.
What does that mean?
You know what it means.
You've got your game goin' on.
I've got my game.
What... What's, uh, what's your game?
Everybody's got a game.
So what's goin' on?
What's the action? What's the story?
What's goin' on?
You heard about my meet?
You heard it was a snub?
What? Uh... Oh.
Yeah, I heard, um...
Uh, I heard real security alert,
but who knows, it's tough to read.
Oh, fuck.
I could do something about this.
OK?
Haven't had one of these in, uh...
I don't even know.
You gonna eat it?
Yeah, I'm gonna eat it.
Hey, good.
Cheers.
Oh, fuck!
Every fuckin' time!
Thanks, man. Thanks.
Should I get us some beers?
No, no. No need. Bottle
service. I ordered vodka.
Come on.
Whoa! Go ahead, man.
Hey! So this is what you do?
You, like, go to a club,
and then you come to, like,
this other part where
the club sort of isn't?
Yeah! Yeah, that's it!
This is 2,000 bucks a pop.
Why?
No reason! We're being totally ripped off!
Is this gold... Is this gold leaf?
Uh-huh. Drink the gold, my friend.
And then later you and I
can have a 24-karat piss.
Any news?
Um, we have Lawrence.
That'll make our sleep easier.
If I can sleep. Which I won't.
I think I'm just gonna call Sarita
and check Ilona's out of the action.
Oh, do we need?
You're not worried that could stir things?
Just to cover all the bases.
Hey, Frank?
Listen, is... is this...
Is this, like, objectively... horrible?
You know, w-we could hold off.
We could put this together next quarter...
Ken. You made this happen.
It's hard enough to get five
people together for a fuckin' dinner.
You might never get another shot.
And it's the right thing to do.
Strength.
You're a good son.
Night, Ken.
Goodnight.
Hello?
Sarita, hey.
Sorry to call so late. I...
You know, I was just,
uh, thinking, and... and...
It's nice to hear your voice.
Yeah, it's nice to hear your voice.
I don't know, I felt bad,
and I wanted to check in... on your mom.
Uh, I assume she can't make it
to the board meeting tomorrow, sadly.
No. I have to go, Kendall.
So, tell me more about Mr. Potato Head.
Tom?
He's a... He's amazing.
Well, I'm pleased.
Uh, but... It is great.
Shiv.
You're convincing me. You are.
It's the constant sort
of... weary repetition.
"Tom's great."
He is.
We're not gonna fuck tonight, right?
You know I'm getting married, too.
Oh, really.
Car model or failed actress?
Ouch. There she is.
She's actually a French doctor.
That's nice.
I mean, it doesn't mean
we can't do other stuff.
Uh...
Theoretically.
I'm getting married in March.
I'm getting married in May.
It's not a competition.
Sure. Yeah.
But only one of us is getting
married in lilac season,
and it's not you.
Come on.
What?
I have to say I am feeling...
You're feeling what, Nate?
I mean, we could
masturbate in separate rooms.
Oh, God!
No. It's quite modern.
No. Come on!
Or... Or...
Just, for old times' sake, last one.
Absolute last one.
I could just, you know,
the old traditional...
simply... stick it in.
Yeah. Like a gas station, right?
Just stick it in.
So a French doctor, huh?
She sounds far too nice
and interesting for you.
She's not that nice.
Deep down she's... statusand
money-obsessed. Like you.
This is nice.
This is like being friends.
You know.
It was Gil.
He's very interested.
I think you should do this.
You're hot, you're...
so hot right now.
Come on. Nate.
We should be good people.
Uh, I know.
Wouldn't it be nice to just
wake up in the morning and...
not feel like a fucking piece of shit?
Hey, Shiv.
Morning.
You know you're amazing, right?
Uh, yeah. I guess.
Come meet Gil.
He's not a pipe dream.
He's gonna go all the way.
OK.
So, we behaved ourselves.
They're gonna write songs
about how good we were.
Shiv? You're a blonde beast.
You should do whatever you want.
Bye, Nate.
I think it's gonna be tight, but, uh...
you know, all the variables swing our way.
Huh.
Whup.
Hey, what's up, Jess?
I have Ms. Shinoya on the line.
OK.
Sarita?
Hello?
Ilona. Ilona, hi. How are you?
God, it's great to hear your voice.
Y-You're up. Um, did...
did you get my gift?
Yes. So, my daughter told
me you don't want me voting
in today's board meeting. Is that right?
No, no, no. That's... That's not it at all.
That's, um...
C-Can I explain? That's...
Well, I'm letting you know
that I will be dialing in.
O-OK. Well, look, there's some issues.
I know you haven't...
Look, could I... Could I
come and talk it through?
Kendall, I will be dialing in.
I'll be there in an hour.
Great. OK, thanks, Ilona.
You're gonna go all the way
out to her? To Long Island?
Yeah, I can...
Is there time?
I can make it. I can make it.
I think...
I think I have to go.
Hey. You ready? Let's go.
Sorry, Mr. Roy, the skies are closed.
Temporary flight restriction.
There's a possible terror threat.
No, no, I need to go, pal. I'll pay
whatever fine they hit us with. Let's go.
We can't do that, sir.
FAA will pull my license.
Uh, OK, I'll handle the FAA.
Or... What is it? The AHS? I'll handle it.
Whatever you lose financially,
I'll make up in perpetuity. OK?
Sir, if we take off now, we
can be shot down by an F-16.
Yeah, but not really. Right?
Airspace is on lockdown.
There's nothing we can do.
Whoa whoa!
Yo!
How long to get to the
city? Financial district?
Man, we should get a round
of fuckin' shots going, right?
Make it happen.
Will do.
It's nice to see the war
criminal. Cleans up well.
Yeah, nice guy, lovely guy.
Whoo.
We good, then? Solid? Right?
I heard Logan started on time even when
he was airlifted in from
Aspen with a shattered femur.
That is true.
Yep, no.
That is correct.
Hey, is your phone working?
C-C-Can I get like a motorcycle courier?
Anything? Can you call your office?
Sorry, no bars.
They're evacuating five blocks
each way from the Stock Exchange.
Lower Manhattan.
NYPD has shut down
the West Side Highway...
Gerri. Can you hear me?
Hey, where are you?
Hey, listen, I'm... I'm...
I'm almost there.
The traffic's stopped. I need you to stall.
What? What's that?
It's a bad connection.
I can't really hear you.
Gerri?
I'm in a tunnel.
OK? Stall.
Well, how far are y...
Uh, I...
Shit.
What?
He's in traffic.
Don't. Don't do this.
He's asking us how long can we stall.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Great.
Oh.
It'll be all right. He's
not gonna be too late.
Here he comes.
Morning, morning.
Good morning.
Oh! Quite a turnout.
Yeah.
Frank, will you whip us through?
Uh, I... I just got word. I think
Kendall will be a few minutes late.
Request for a late start?
No!
No?
He can catch up. Fuck that! Where is he?
Stuck in traffic. That's all I know.
OK, come on, come on, let's go. Let's go.
Yup, yup.
It's twelve noon, and I'd like to call
the meeting of Waystar Royco to order.
Roll call.
What...? Roll call?
Logan Roy. Yeah. You're here.
We've never done roll
call. What is roll call?
We're doing it today.
Why are we doing roll call?
Because that's how we do it. Right, Noah?
So Logan Roy is here...
Huh.
Frank Vernon, present.
Kendall Roy, absent.
Roman Roy.
Yo.
Ewan Roy, absent.
Ilona Shinoy, absent.
Datu Kassma.
Present.
Dewi Swann.
Here.
Paul Chambers.
Happy to be here.
Asha Kahn.
Here.
Lawrence Yee.
Sir!
Stewy Hosseini.
I am here.
Mr. Chairman, we have a quorum.
Uh, we also welcome our
esteemed general counsel
Gerri Killman to the
meeting. Thanks, Gerri.
So everybody has a copy of the agenda
and the minutes of the last meeting.
Is that right?
Yes.
Do any of you have any questions
that have come to you
immediately after looking at them?
I know that I-I have a few thoughts...
we might have to take a look at.
What thoughts?
Just wait a second and I'll get to it.
OK. Who's this?
Ewan? Well...
you just can't keep away, huh?
Thought maybe I'd show up for once.
Watch the fun.
Great to have you.
They wouldn't let me in downstairs
without a passport.
Has it started?
Kendall. Hey, where are ya?
We've already started, man.
We've started.
Hey. Tell Jess to put me
through the polycom. Yeah?
So, let's move along
to item 3.1.
Frank.
Mm-hmm?
What's "Performance
issues?" Sounds fucking vague.
And why is it so high
on the fuckin' hit parade?
I don't know if we're actually gonna hit
those today. Maybe we can bump those.
Sorry, I'm gonna have to get back to you.
Can we bump 'em?
OK, then. Let's bump it.
Ohh. What the fuck's goin' on?
I think Kendall wants to make a comment.
He has a... a thing that
he's going to speak...
I think Ilona is going to phone in, too.
He's on the line.
I'm putting him through.
What is this? What the fuck is this?
Hi, Kendall?
Hey, guys. Can you hear me?
I apologize.
I will be there shortly.
Where are we at?
We are at your item.
Performance issues.
Uh... You want us to wait?
Where are you?
Fuck that. We're movin' on.
Gerri, Noah,
if we wanted to halt proceedings until...
We're not halting proceedings.
We're moving on.
No, no. It's OK. It's OK.
I can do this.
Dad, this is big.
Look...
I love my father.
OK? My father is a legend.
I worship the ground he walks on.
Nothing will ever detract from
what he's built and what he's done.
But he is currently unfit
to run this company.
Speak up. I can't hear.
Not only because of his
refusal to take the time
to recover from serious health issues,
but because every day he refuses to retire,
he is one day closer to
destroying his own legacy.
He took on levels of debt
that threatened the
very existence of our firm,
he is lining up dead-weight acquisitions
in a sector that he
has a historic regard for
but which is a non-growth area.
We face existential battles in scale,
and he is facing precisely
the wrong direction.
He is making decisions for a
future that he no longer understands,
and we don't have time for missteps.
What used to take ten... Two, three years.
Our entire ice cap will melt.
He is gambling our
last dollars at the track
on a horse that's ready
for the glue factory,
and I am calling for a
vote of no confidence in him
as CEO and chairman.
Bullshit. No.
I'm afraid since you are
the subject of the vote,
you need to recuse yourself, Logan.
Oh, Jesus Christ. Fuckin'
amateur hour at the fuckin' circus.
You don't get to vote, and you
don't get to comment, is the situation.
You really should leave the room.
OK, fine. Fine. Vote.
Would you mind?
Guys. Is he there?
Is he still in the room?
I'm sick. I can't move. Fuck that vote.
He can't be in the room. OK? Guys...
Let the minutes reflect
that Logan Roy was asked to recuse himself.
Let the minutes reflect that Logan Roy
shoved his boot up Frank's ass.
OK.
All in favor of the vote of
no confidence in Logan Roy?
Me. My hand is raised.
More in sorrow than in anger.
Oh, no shit, Judas.
Frank!
Nice to see you back.
Asha?
I see you.
And I see you, Logan.
Oh, Jesus, this is just
un-frickin'-believable.
Stewy? Stewy.
Me. OK.
Listen, as a major shareholder,
and in the absence
of any real clarity here,
I think it's the view
that this is a family matter and abstain.
Against.
Strongly against.
We have Ilona on the line.
Hello, Logan. Yes.
After consulting with my family,
I am voting in favor of the motion.
Thanks for nothin', Ilona.
Fuck off.
Ewan?
Go ahead.
What are we on, 4-2?
Go on.
Yeah. Join the rats.
Let's finish this, huh?
I vote with Logan.
I think we should take the
time to consider this properly
when all parties are here.
Datu, we're voting now.
Logan, please, can you
stay out of the conversation?
In which case, Logan.
I stick with Logan.
Kendall, you counted right there?
You all right?
Four against four, this is your best shot?
Lawrence?
I don't have a dog in this fight, Kendall.
I abstain.
So, currently
we've got four votes in
favor of Logan to remain,
four of stepping down, two abstentions.
Uh, Gerri.
Do you want to say anything
to speak to the senior
management teams' attitudes here?
Shut the...
Well, you know,
I'm an independent observer,
non-voting, a general counsel,
so I'm not sure that's appropriate?
Right. Thanks.
Very...
professional.
Hey, Roman?
Roman.
Put your hand up, bro.
Roman, can you hear me?
Uh...
Is your hand up?
Kendall, yeah. Hey. Are you there?
Roman...
Uh, you're kind of cuttin' out.
He's off the line.
Come on, son.
Roman.
Come on. Come on, come on.
You better be smelling
your fuckin' armpit, Romulus.
Um...
I think it's a tough one, you know?
I think, uh...
It's tough, but maybe...
Roman for me.
I'm not sure we can count that for you.
Roman?
Against.
He s-started to vote, I'm
not sure he can change that.
He can fucking change.
You shouldn't be here,
you shouldn't be speaking here,
you should be out of this room.
This is illegal.
Whatever.
If you count 'em out, deadlock.
Continuity prevails. I'm chairman.
Casting vote. I win. It's fucking over!
What's the vote?
My son.
That was your best shot.
You lost.
I think there's some doubt
as to whether he lost...
And Kendall, Frank, Asha, Ilona,
off the board, fired with immediate effect.
I don't think you're able to do that.
Security!
I am in the middle of
turning a fucking tanker.
Frank, you're fired.
I have some doubt...
I'm in the middle of
turning a fucking tanker!
Do you hear?!
Frank! You're fired.
Without exit package.
Asha, goodbye.
Somebody send a telegram to Ilona
telling her she's no longer required,
and my best to her cancer.
I think we all need to take a beat.
Meh meh meh fuckin' meh.
Logan, stop.
Is it wise to fire the board
with the share price this weak,
heading into a political fight?
Take it like a fucking man. You're out.
You're fucked. You tried
to kill me, but you failed.
And you're dead. Now fuck off!
Oh, go on, cry me a river.
Get the fuck out.
Straight out! Passes canceled.
We'll send along personal belongings.
Just need to get some things, OK?
No goodbyes! Thank you!
Get your fuckin' hands off me.
And what the fuck am I gonna do with you?
I don't know, Dad.
Jesus.
Can I just get some stuff?
No. No.
Thank you.
OK.
He-e-ey!
God, that was the journey from hell.
Spent 30 minutes in a cab not moving.
Honey?
Tom?
Hey. Hey.
Hey. You OK, sweetheart?
Yeah. I think somebody poisoned me.
I'm working from home.
Oh, someone poisoned you?
Hmm.
Oh! With booze?
Hmm. Hmm.
Aw.
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
Mm.
OK, I got you something.
Oh, thank you.
I missed you.
You only been away, like, 14 hours.
Yeah, well, sorry for missing you.
Oh.
Yeah. What?
What the fuck?
What? What's happened?
Well, more. T-Tell me more.
What's happened? Did it happen?
OK, call me right back.
The world's blown up.
Oh, fuck!
What do you mean, "has it happened"?
Did you know?
What? No!
Fuckin' Kendall!
Has it happened?
Did... Has it happened?
Wait!
Kendall? Call me back.
You knew?
Yeah.
I think too much "abolgoll" hurt my tummy.
Connor. You heard?
Yeah, Kendall called for a
vote of no confidence on Dad.
Kendall? Who the fuck else knew about this?
Roman did.
Roman knew?
I don't know why you'd
expect anything different.
Not a single one of them told me
about this. It's complete bullshit.
Oh, Shiv, you know I
don't like to take sides.
But I'm on your side.
Fuck you.
You knew?
Yeah, I tried to call you.
Not hard enough.
I did!
He's fired half the board.
What about Kendall?
Fired. Frank, Asha, fired.
What?
The rebels are getting
shot in the town square.
I'll talk to you later, Tom.
Are we the rebels?
Yes?
I have the White House.
The president will join once you're on.
They're very apologetic.
Tell him I'm on.
Yes, sir.
Yes, he's on.
Hello, Mr. President. He'll
be with you momentarily.
He'll be right there.
Thank you.
Mr. President.
Oh, much, much better.
No need for an apology.
Well, you really had a terrorist problem.
I've just taken down a terrorist myself.
My son.
♪ From all of you good workers ♪
♪ Good news to you I'll tell ♪
So, can you help me with
this FCC red tape bullshit?
♪ Which side are you on? ♪
Good.
And you, Mr. President.
♪ My daddy was a miner
♪ And you. Thank you.
♪ And I'm a miner's son ♪
♪ And I'll stick with the union ♪
♪ Till every battle's won ♪
♪ Which side are you on? ♪
♪ They say in Harlan County ♪
♪ There are no neutrals there ♪
♪ You'll either be a union man ♪
♪ Or a thug for J.H. Blair ♪
♪ Which side are you on? ♪
♪ Oh, workers can you stand it
♪ Oh, tell me how you can ♪
♪ Will you be a lousy
scab or will you be a man? ♪
♪ Which side are you on? ♪
♪ Don't scab for the bosses ♪
♪ Don't listen to their lies ♪
♪ Us poor folks haven't got a chance ♪
♪ Unless we organize ♪
♪ Which side are you on? ♪