I'm not letting you neanderthals
in to rape my company.
Daddy's boy.
How can we salvage this?
Do we need to sweeten the offer?
- Do you want to call your dad?
Everybody, this is cousin Craig.
- It's Greg.
- I'll... I'll answer to both.
I changed my mind.
I'm staying on as head of the company.
You fucked me.
On the family trust,
I'm gonna add Marcy to myself
and you four.
I'm gonna have to talk to my lawyers.
What're you thinking, son?
She's very smart.
- Family first.
- Um, sure.
But I want to run the damn show.
And until it opens up,
chief operating officer.
We stick to the plan, I takeover.
- And you two, under me...
- Under you?
Can we think about it?
- Yeah, of course.
- I thought about it. Fuck you!
Sorry the other offer fell through.
But we fattened the goose nice...
I'm gonna eat you all.
One by fucking one.
What do you say, kids?
Our position is, this
doesn't quite work for us.
Dad?
Dad? Dad?!
Kendall. Dad is in the hospital.
Rava. Hey.
Uh, my dad's...
My dad's in the hospital.
Yeah, he had, I don't know,
I don't know what.
But, uh...
Yeah, I don't know if he's gonna be ok.
It's... yeah.
So... I don't know. I'm here with Jess.
We're just trying to get there...
What the...?
Can we just find a way
around the traffic, man?
Just... just...
Just figure it out. Please!
Where's the icu?
Blood pressure...
Tests...
What's the situation? Can somebody...
Excuse me.
They're working on him.
What is this part of the hospital?
I mean, is this the best section?
Excuse me? Doctor,
is this the best part of the hospital?
Sorry. You know, we just...
We need to know.
The icu is the icu. This
is the best place for him.
Is this where you would
take your father?
I'm sorry. Can the team
have some space? Please?
Hey, here's an idea. Why don't
you worry about the medicine,
not the fucking feng shui?
Let's let the gentleman do his job.
Thank you.
- Let's do this for dad.
- Thank you.
Sorry.
- Synced and corrected by shazi89 -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Do they know who we are?
- I don't know.
- Are they sandbagging us?
- Do they know who he is?
- I don't know.
- Shall we call mom?
- What?
No. There's like
a million people to call.
She's probably just make it
about herself, anyway.
Come on. Your mom's a maniac,
she's not a monster.
Folks, we need you
to wait through there, please.
Hi. I'm sorry.
We're getting mixed messages here.
We have no clue what's going on.
We will be with you
as soon as we have an assessment.
Ok, well, that's not good enough.
We need to know what's happening. Now.
The socio-economic health
of multiple continents
is dependent on his well-being.
The socio-economic health
of multiple continents?
Kendall. Everyone.
We have an area we can go to.
They'll keep us posted.
So, look, take me
through what happened exactly.
Uh, I don't know, exactly.
It was weird. Um, it happened fast,
- we were just sitting there...
- We were just talking.
We were talking, shiv kind of started
- hard-balling dad a little bit.
- I wasn't hard-balling him.
A brain hemorrhage doesn't come
from some chit-chat, asshole.
So it's definitely a brain hemorrhage?
Is that what they said?
Somebody said that, right?
- Somebody said hemorrhage?
- Or stroke? I...
- The ambulance...
- A stroke is a hemorrhage.
- It is?
- Yes.
Did someone say "hemorrhage,"
or is it just us who said it?
It could be an aneurism.
Why aren't we chasing this?
I'll chase.
Hey, uh, is there any...
Did dad ever talk to any
of you guys about cryogenics?
You're insane. Look, I don't want
to be given the runaround
by doctor-fucking-suny purchase
medical school here.
We need to know
who the top players are, ok?
Who's the top dog in this hospital?
Have you talked to dad's neurologist?
Kendall, stop acting like
the king of the hospital.
We're all trying to do our
best, so just fuck off.
I'm on it. Ok?
According to this,
it sounds like a stroke,
but it could be
an acute subdural hematoma.
Great. Get in there
and operate, doctor Google.
He once talked to me about cryogenics.
What? Wouldn't that just be typical?
All the other billionaires are
strolling around in new bodies,
but not dad, because we were too
embarrassed to actually discuss it.
He didn't talk to you about cryogenics.
You talked to him about cryogenics
because you're obsessed with cryogenics.
- I'm not really, Kendall.
- And what he didn't tell you,
and what I'm telling you now,
is that you are an idiot.
Sticks and stones, Kenny.
Yeah, I know.
And on his birthday, too?
It's so shitty.
So what's happening now?
Are you staying at the hospital?
I guess.
I mean, I think I've got a job,
but I don't know.
Logan said I did,
but marcia was the only one to hear it,
so... and then he tragically,
you know, like, whatever.
Well, what sort of job?
Is it a good job?
I don't know. Like,
could be anything.
And I have, like, 20 bucks left.
The world is so fucked up.
I am not sending you
any more money, Greg.
Step up.
I'm not asking you to send me...
Look,
just make sure about the job.
- All right?
- Yeah, I know.
Hey, do you have cash?
Yeah. Uh...
No, just my last twenty.
That's fine. Thanks.
Um...
I just got mugged by shiv.
Born in humble
circumstances in dundee, Scotland,
shortly before the outbreak
of the second world war,
Logan Roy grew up in poverty,
but died one of the richest
and most powerful men in America.
His widowed mother took the decision...
It's an atn obituary.
They want us to ok it
in case they have to run it.
Is it nice?
I mean, it's made by
his own news division.
Doesn't say he was a prick.
You want to watch it?
No.
I would really love to see you.
Yes, it's appropriate. It could
hardly be more appropriate.
Ok?
Yeah, ok. Ok, good.
- Hey, Jess?
- Mm-hmm?
There's nothing in here about our mom.
Or Connor's. They need to be included.
Yeah.
Pj says Aziz kahn at Mayo
clinic is the best there is.
Sarah says Ann wieman at nyu.
Ann wieman? Is that...
That's not who I have.
Well, it's the name I have.
Can you tell Sarah to give her a call?
- Sure.
- Hey, Rome.
- Do you have regular?
- No, I've got...
Now I'm strapped.
Was there any change at all?
- Hey, you guys.
- What?
Could I have the change?
What is this? People are
sending shit already?
It's from Lawrence yee at vaulter.
Call him and tell him that
is not fucking appreciated.
Mm-hmm.
- Kendall, I'm so sorry.
- Thank you, Gerri.
Can you give me five?
We need to talk.
Over here, ok?
Obviously the nominating
committee, the board,
has a plan in the event
of Logan's incapacitation.
Sorry, do I need to hear this right now?
You do.
In the event that we, uh,
continue on our trajectory
of his current consciousness,
we're gonna need to announce a plan
by around 6:30, before the markets open,
in order to avoid
a lot of funky chowder.
Did you say funky chowder?
We've set up down here.
What have you set up?
You're gonna want a place to just be,
and chill, you know?
We talked to some of the
trustees of the hospital,
so everybody knows who's who.
Yeah. It's not a war room yet,
but, um...
But if we need one, it's available.
Jesus.
Uh, so there's a bathroom
through there...
- Hi, karolina...
- Hi.
Thank you, guys.
So I have dewi and asha
from the nominating committee
on the line.
Kendall's here,
and you're on speaker, guys.
So sorry to hear about the news.
Likewise.
As you know, our standing plan
in the event of Logan's...
Absence, is to separate
his ceo and chairman roles.
You'll become acting ceo,
frank stays on as coo.
We'll need to act fast.
Stabilize the stock price.
Dewi? Dewi?
I'm sorry...
My dad is my focus right now, ok?
Of course, it's just that
there's a problem
in terms of the optics
if what happened earlier today
between you two gets out.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Sure. Well...
And then there's the problem with frank.
- As in?
- Logan fired him
and promoted Roman.
Roman?
Jesus.
Look, I'm sorry, I...
I can't get into this right now, guys.
No, of course.
You are in no fit state.
But here's my take, ok?
My dad got sick today, right?
I don't know, I mean, nobody knows
when he started acting out of character,
but, like, he didn't seem great
from the morning on,
and there's no paper
on any of the moves made today.
- Right, Gerri?
- Uh...
Nothing meaningful.
Yeah, it was words.
Words are just, what?
Nothing.
Complicated air flow.
So, I mean, if I was saying
what actually happened today,
it would be nothing.
Well, that certainly
makes things simpler
from our point of view.
Do you think you can get
the family behind it?
Yes.
And frank?
Sure.
Dude, can't we just talk here?
You know Connor's invited Willa down?
Ugh. What?! Here?!
What's the deal with their deal?
Unlike me, he has
no sense of boundaries.
What the fuck?
It's stale, but it's empty, I think.
- Hello?
- You wanna do a play?
No, I, um, just wanted to...
I've been thinking
that maybe this might be
really tough on marcia.
Yeah, you're thinkin' that?
What, will she put all her
inheritance into gold or oil?
No, I just... no, I...
Look, I know that, like, the
trust only comes into play
if certain things happen...
Ahem. Yeah, he's dead, or brain dead.
Yeah, but I was thinkin', like...
Wouldn't it be nice for dad to wake up
and for all of us to have signed,
like he wanted?
You know, like a nice gesture?
And if he doesn't wake up,
we've basically signed over to marcia
the power to choose the new dad.
So... ok. So, for the record,
you are declining to sign
on the change of trust?
- For the record?
- Yeah.
What the fuck is this, mccarthyism?
I'm not declining, I'm just not...
I'm not "clining." What the f...
Ok. No. Ok, just, you know,
that just seems very shitty
under the circumstances.
What circumstances?
Well, you did make
her husband's brain explode.
- Fuck you, man!
- Ow!
- Ohh!
- Wait...
- Stop it!
- You shit!
What, are you fuckin' insane?
No! No!
He...
He doesn't deserve this.
It's just so unfair.
He's a great... man.
He, like, let me
come to his birthday lunch.
And he offered me a job.
Right?
He doesn't deserve this.
And... so, if there's
anything that I can do,
let me know.
Actually, there is something.
- Ok.
- Can you go to the apartment
and get his bed things and slippers?
The ones with the dark checks.
You don't mind?
No, no. I'd be...
Respectfully, uh, somberly willing.
Thank you.
- Now?
- Please.
Ok. All right.
Marcia, we get can get Colin or the
driver to go and get his things.
I don't need this
fly buzzing in my face.
Slippers, slippers, slippers,
slippers, slippers.
Yeah, don't fuck it up.
Fuckin' long legs. Greg! Hey,
I need a favor from you.
What's up?
Dad had some papers
he wanted us to sign,
and they're in some envelopes,
just pick 'em up at the
house, and bring 'em.
- Yeah. Where are the papers?
- Yeah.
They're in the house somewhere.
In envelopes... they're
just in the house!
- You got it?
- Ok. I was imagining...
Oh, you're fucking tall. This
is hurting my goddamn neck.
I have to go. Ok? Just find the papers,
and bring 'em back.
Papers, and... and...
They're gonna be just...
I am so done with this conversation.
- Just handle it, ok?
- All right. Yeah.
Better not fuck this one up.
I don't want Logan Roy's newspapers
goin' through my trash cans.
- Oh, my god! We've killed...
- Logan.
We're bastards!
Turn that off.
Roman, no. Turn it off.
- We've killed...
- Logan.
We're...
What are they saying?
Just rumors, you know.
He was taken to the hospital,
some of Twitter says he's dead,
and also a good deal of, um,
of rejoicing at our father's
potential demise.
Can we find out who these fuckers are
and, like... report them?
Or just, like, screen grab their shit.
- Ok.
- So we know? Yeah?
So, I don't know
where Kendall is, but...
Hi. Really sorry, you guys.
Thanks, Willa.
Why don't we sit over here.
Oh, there's Ken.
It's gross.
Hey.
News is out.
Ok, right. Well...
So, um, listen.
I don't even want to think about this,
but I just spoke
to the nominating committee,
and, uh...
The thing is that the plan
is to announce that I
take over from dad.
- Well, no.
- Excuse me?
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
we're waiting for
the results of the scan.
It's a pointless conversation.
Ok, well, let's talk about it.
I can't talk about it. I'm upset.
Hey! I'm upset too.
Oh, not too upset to go and fucking plot
- with the suits.
- Fuck you! Ok?
I could hardly hear them for
the blood rushing in my ears.
Isn't there a plan anyways? Like...
Yes, there's a plan.
That's what I'm fucking telling you.
The plan is that frank and I
will take over...
- Frank was fired. So..
- Yeah.
Ok. Well, I mean, let's d-discuss
and just see where we are, right?
I'm not doing this.
If dad dies, I don't want to be
talking about this shit when he dies.
He won't die.
Yeah, this is great. Thank you.
Hey, man.
Sorry, I'm... I'm really sorry,
but I don't have any money for the cab.
I'm sorry, sir, do I know you?
Yeah, I-I was here a little earlier.
I got assaulted a little in there.
So can you pay for the cab, please?
She was supposed to call,
but maybe she didn't
because there's an emergency,
uh, happening.
Sir, I'm sorry,
I don't know who you are.
Um...
Sss...
Ok, so he's not gonna lend me the money.
So, I don't know, um...
You know, he... pretty much,
he owes you your money.
He owes me the...?
You better give me the money, dude.
You guys need to work
this out for yourselves,
because basically one of you
guys hasn't got $14, ok?
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, Mrs. Roy?
Knock knock.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
It's so weird.
I actually like hospitals.
Lots of people don't. But they're safe.
The weird thing for me
is that I was, well,
I'd been intending to talk to Logan,
you know, and make a... make a proposal,
a very decent proposal, to shiv.
Actually been meaning to ask
for his blessing for a while,
but, uh... now it's very difficult.
You need to find the right time
for these conversations.
Right.
The weird thing I'm thinkin' now is,
do you think Logan
would still like to be asked?
You know? I mean, I know he can't reply,
but would he appreciate the gesture
if he was told about it later?
Or even in the case...
In the case of the worst... case,
would it have been nice
to have asked his body?
Rumors continue to
circulate about the health of...
Hey, hey. They're ready.
They have the results.
Ok. Fuck.
You ok?
Yeah. Yeah. He'll be fine.
He's probably in there eating
a fucking chicken bucket
and yelling at someone.
He's had a hemorrhagic stroke,
a bleed in the deep right hemisphere
that put pressure on the
thalamus and the brain stem,
and that's what caused
a loss of consciousness.
So, what, do you operate?
We don't do that with deep bleeds,
especially in older patients.
- He's not an older patient.
- Dude, he just turned 80.
But physically, he's, like, still in
his 70s, and he's in great shape.
The evidence is that operating
in situations like these
isn't worthwhile.
So, then, what do you do?
You can't do nothing.
We will carry out regular observations,
and hopefully we'll see
some improvement soon.
That's not good enough.
Right, Dr. Judith? That's...
It's an excellent department.
Well, thank you for your input,
but you'll understand
if we check out our options.
My assistant's been in touch
with Ann wieman at nyu,
and we might move dad there.
No. He stays here.
He gets better here.
Well, we can discuss.
We'll discuss and get back to you.
No. No discussion.
I am his next of kin. I am his proxy.
I am in charge. Thank you.
Good. Well...
We'll move Logan
to a suite in Greenberg.
I'll show you the way.
I'm sure you have some questions.
Feel free to ask me on the way up.
- I'm sorry, Ken.
- Thanks for coming over.
Ok, so look.
We don't know what's going on.
He could be fine; He could not.
Either way, he's not
gonna be back tomorrow,
so, long story short,
will you carry on as coo,
step up on the board...
- Become acting chairman.
- Yes.
- No.
- What?
He fired me, Ken.
He... I...
Look, I don't know if he even
knew what he was saying...
If his brain was working.
His brain was working fine.
Well, whatever else,
there's no proof, legally,
- that yesterday even happened.
- That's not the problem.
- So what's the problem?
- I don't want to be chairman.
I am just an attendant lord,
here to swell a scene or two.
What the fuck does that mean?
Come on, don't do that.
We could do great things together.
So what do you need, frank?
A jazillion dollars in unmarked bitcoin.
I don't have a price, Ken.
- Frank, I don't understand.
- Ju... we'll talk.
There's a lot of mess
to be cleaned up, Kendall,
but you can do it, son.
You can.
And there's nothing I can say
to change your mind?
I'm sorry about your father.
And good luck, Kenny.
Yeah?
I told Greg to bring
the change of trust.
- What?
- And when he does,
I think we should sign it.
I... I'm not doing anything
without my lawyer present.
Ok. Well, I'm going to sign it,
I'm getting Connor to sign it.
It's gonna make you look pretty
fucking heartless when you don't.
Don't give me a fuckin' scary look.
You hit me, I will fuck you up.
Ahh, fuck.
Yeah.
God, you're so annoying.
Shut up.
- Hello?
- Greg.
Hey. Did you find those
contracts Roman asked for?
Uh, I... yes, I got 'em.
Oh, I think you have the wrong ones.
Uh, ok.
Um... right.
What, uh, what shall I do?
Look, there's a lot of confusion.
'Cause if you have any doubt,
maybe you can't find them,
and that might be simplest.
But if I do,
'cause I...
I think I have the right ones here.
Don't bring them in.
Did he change his mind?
No. I'm just telling you:
Don't bring them in.
Ok. Ok. S...
All right, I get... I get it.
So, who's the...
Like, what's the chain of command here?
Are you the more senior sibling?
Greg,
it's simple.
This is a favor
I'd like you to do for me,
and I'd like you to be discreet.
You stay for a while,
you can't find them,
you come back. Ok?
- Ok.
- Thank you.
This is better.
Um...
Look, so, I know you don't
want to talk about this,
I'm just informing you,
Roman as a board member
and shiv as a shareholder,
I'll be taking temporary charge
as ceo and chairman.
Frank is not interested
in the position at present.
No. I'm sorry, but even
if we were talking about this,
which we are not,
it wouldn't necessarily be you.
I'm sorry, then
who the fuck would it be?
I don't know. Anyone.
It could be me.
Are you insane?
- Dad made me coo.
- I don't think so, dude.
Dad wasn't thinking straight.
I think he was.
You? The chief operating officer?
- Yup.
- I mean, if that wasn't a sign
he was loco in the coco,
I don't know what is.
Well, I don't see it that way.
Come on. It was
a negotiating position, Rome.
He was fuckin' playing you
to get you to sign the change of trust.
Do you even know
what it fucking involves?
I mean, he conked out mid-game.
Are you calling me a dipshit?
No. I love you, man, but
you're not a serious person.
All right, fuck you. He's alive,
you're not the fuckin' boss.
All right! Come on. Let's
not throw shit around.
We're in the middle, so let's
just sit tight. No sudden moves.
We need to move. The markets are gonna
want to know who's behind the wheel.
We need to control the narrative.
"Control the narrative." You
probably yell that when you cum.
"Oh! Control the narrative!
Oh! Control it...
Control the narrative! Uhh..."
Fuck you. We're in a hospital.
Everyone knows.
We have to say something.
No. Actually, we don't. 'Cause
no one knows how serious it is.
So we don't have to say anything.
Actually, we do. The sec. There
are rules, there are laws...
Oh, no. The law?
Well, we can't break the law.
Hey, karolina?
Has a ceo ever been out of action
and people haven't been told?
Um, not that I can think of.
There was apple, but that...
Right, but if we...
Wanted to drag our feet on this,
until we figure the moves...
Well, once we do know,
there's a duty to shareholders
to let people...
Yeah, but I don't...
I don't know what we know.
I mean, this could be
an allergic reaction.
- It could be the flu.
- Oh, come on.
Look at the fuckin' orchids.
This is out there.
It's like we're being held
hostage in the Honolulu airport.
But if we wanted to say something,
you know, other than...
It's called a lie, shiv.
When you say the thing
that's not, that's a lie.
We'll need to make a holding statement.
Of course, I'm open to your suggestions
on how to... finesse it.
Perfect. We'll make a decision
and get back to you shortly.
Ok.
Logan Roy, ceo and chairman
- of waystar corporation...
- So, what do you think I do?
Well, I don't know. What did she say?
Roman said bring in the papers,
shiv said don't bring in the papers.
Well, I guess you need to decide
which one of them is more important?
I guess Roman's... in the company,
but shiv seems like,
I don't know, more bossy?
All right. Well, can you just
take some of the papers?
Plus, I don't know about these slippers.
Like, they're all plaid.
Does "checked" mean plaid?
'Cause then there's gingham,
there's tartan...
It's like a crisscross
fuckin' minefield.
Oh, fuck the slippers, Greg.
You have to strategize.
I'm trying to strategize, mom, with you!
But you won't strategize.
Hey. What's up, Kendall?
You mix me up with your sponsor?
Listen, I'm just calling
to issue a reminder.
Your pecker's in my pocket, ok,
dickless dickleby?
You do what I say.
Let others say what they want,
but we stay dark.
You get me? No reporting
on what went down yesterday,
the turmoil.
Well, I can do whatever I want,
because vaulter and our satellite sites
have editorial independence...
As set out in
that piece of paper you signed.
You know what
that piece of paper is to me?
Nothing. Ok?
I'd jerk off on that paper and
send it to you as a greeting card.
"Mum's the word,"
motherfucker.
Hey. Sorry to bother you so late.
Hey, let's put something together
about the Roy family shitshow.
So, and I don't want to get into this,
but maybe we should just
cut off the whole Kendall ceo thing
so that it doesn't get painful.
Well, I mean, I'm not looking for it,
but I guess I'm already coo,
so one more step...
It's not gonna be you.
- Because?
- Come on.
- I don't know what that means.
- Yes, you do.
Well, it doesn't matter who does it.
It's just temporary, so anyone will do.
Yeah, sure. Anyone.
- Tom.
- Tom?
Ok, fine.
Karl.
Bleahh.
Prick. Eva?
- Cunt.
- Ok.
So, who?
Someone dad trusts.
But dad doesn't trust anyone,
except frank,
and he fired frank
for shits and giggles.
- Gerri?
- Uhh...
I don't love Gerri.
But I don't hate Gerri.
So, Gerri.
I'll talk to her.
How ya doin'?
Oh, I'm fine.
This is where they brought
baird, so it's a little...
Baird?
Yeah, baird. My husband.
Shiv's godfather?
Oh, does he, um... with the tortoise?
Yeah.
Fuck yeah, of course.
- How is he?
- He's dead.
I know. I know. I remember... you...
So, uh, Gerri, uh,
just wanted to say thanks for
captaining us through this shitstorm.
Um, you do a good job,
Gerri, you, uh,
you're, um, you're a real good job-doer.
I suck at the whole
corporate flirt thing.
You know, I just...
I like to lube up and fuck, you know?
- Ok.
So, um... for me and shiv,
the whole Kendall thing doesn't work.
So we were thinkin'...
General counsel...
You know where the bodies are buried.
You probably buried 'em yourself.
So...
You would have the family's support
to step in and take the reins.
That's a very generous offer,
but I'm going to have to decline.
Um...
Ok. Can, uh, can I ask why?
Why I don't want the job
that makes your brain explode?
Ok, but, um, uh...
G-Gerri, excuse me,
but I... I've always thought of you...
And I mean this
in the best possible way...
As a stone-cold killer bitch.
Who says you don't know how to flirt?
Ok.
Hey. Can I get a moment alone
with you, do you think?
- I...
- Have you seen this?
I'm so sorry about your father.
Thank you. Would you give us a minute?
Yeah.
- Thanks, Willa.
- Mm-hmm.
Tom, would you mind?
Oh, come on. I'm not the same as her.
Ken.
Vaulter's running a story about
how the company's in turmoil.
Don't we own him?
"Shit show at the fuck factory"?
Yeah. Uncertainty, discord.
That is not a good story.
"Family gets behind
other member of family,"
that's a good story.
Oh, fuck them.
I mean, when jobs was dying,
apple didn't say anything.
We're in a hospital, shiv.
Everyone knows.
We can't just prop him up
and wave his hand
and say he's fine like they did
in the politburo or weekend
at fuckin' Bernie's.
I like the sound of that, though.
Look,
you can't put a value on a human life,
except in our case,
you rather precisely can
because when trading opens tomorrow,
we're gonna drop like a stone.
The only question is, what's the bottom?
I think I'm the best option.
I just want to say that, uh,
if you need me to...
Go get sandwiches or coffee
or step up from regional parks
and run north America, I can,
and I will. And that's
just an offer on the table...
- Fuck off, Tom.
- Fuck you, Kendall.
- Don't talk to Tom like that.
- It's ok. It's fine.
I was about to be announced.
I mean, how can I not
be the logical choice?
Because you were about to be
announced, Ken, and then you weren't.
I mean, the only thing we know for
certain, like for absolute certain,
tonight, is that dad didn't
want you running the company.
So if there was a list of 7
billion people on this planet
that dad would choose to be boss,
we know you would be last.
Dad fired you, man.
No, he did not fire me.
He said it was just
gonna take a little longer.
But he said that to be nice.
What I think he meant to
say was that he wished
that mom gave birth to a can opener
because at least then
it would be useful.
You're a dick.
- That's...
- Too far?
Look, the board are offering this to me.
I don't actually need your backing.
You actually really, totally do.
I think you do.
Without it, after what dad did to you,
I mean, we could probably
take any appointment to court.
Jesus, shiv, we're talking
about court now?
Fuck you!
I didn't even want to talk
about this, remember?
What do you... what do
you have against me?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Oh, you want me to actually say?
- Yes, I do.
- You lack killer instinct,
you're wet, you're green,
you're intellectually insecure,
bullshit.
You're not emotionally strong enough,
- you have addiction issues.
- That's enough!
I don't think all that, I'm
just trying to be dad's voice.
Bravo. It was an excellent impression.
I just want to say
I'm not getting involved.
Good. But shiv's right.
I'm not saying I would make
a better ceo,
that's unsaid...
It's not unsaid when you say it.
No, I'm saying I'm not saying it,
so, in fact, it is unsaid.
Hey, pal, why don't you
go help Willa with her homework?
Ouch. Asshole.
Listen, why don't you decide everything.
I don't care. I just observe.
I'm a un white helmet. All right?
Guys...
Who else are you gonna get?
I think shiv would be great.
That's what I think.
Thanks, honey,
but... no way.
I mean, she doesn't work in the company
and has no experience of the company
and the markets would freak, but
apart from that, I agree with you.
I mean, we have options.
Sure. You could all ask for morphine
so you can stay in your
painless fucking fantasy world
where the orchids dance
and the company is run
by a magical fucking unicorn!
Fuck your options.
Hello, this is Greg on Greg's phone.
- Greg. How ya doin'?
- Yeah, I'm just, um,
not dawdling.
You're still at the fucking apartment?
You've been there forever.
Uh, just, um...
I know you're picking up
pjs and all that shit,
just grab a sweater,
maybe, also. My dad's, ok?
- Ok. Which sweater?
- It doesn't matter.
Not something washed.
Something that he's worn, maybe.
- If you find one.
- Ok, yeah.
If he's worn it, if his...
How am I gonna know if it's worn?
Just smell it. Ok?
Jesus! I just want something
that smells like him, ok?
I just want that.
Is that enough for you?
Dude, that's really nice.
I would want that
if this was my situation, too.
So I'll sniff some stuff for you...
Just... whatever. And if you
tell anyone about this,
I will... cut your dick off.
And don't forget those papers
I told you to bring.
And, uh, thank you.
Fuck off.
Yeah.
I... apologize if my bell summoned you.
Hey.
It's, um...
- It's like 4:00 A.M.
- yeah, I couldn't sleep.
Put the kids to bed and thought
I was missing all the fun, so...
How are they doing?
- The kids?
- Yeah.
Um...
They're ok.
Maybe you could bring them by tomorrow.
So they can say their...
You know, say their... hellos.
- Yeah.
- Ok.
How are you feeling?
Good. Yeah.
Yeah. How am I feeling?
Fuck. Ask me another?
- Jesus, what a day for you.
- Yeah.
The nominating committee
want me to be the big boss.
Really?
But shiv and Roman won't back me
because of what dad said at lunch.
Jesus.
- Yeah.
- Ah, your family is so...
Fucked.
I'm sorry, but... wow.
I'm sorry.
Um...
Ken, I...
What can I say? It's... I don't know.
Adrenaline.
It's just my body.
Hey.
I'm glad you're here.
Yeah. I can tell.
- Hey. Look. Stop. Stop.
- No. I'm not in the mood.
There's something I have to say to you.
- What?
- Siobhan Roy...
Oh, my god.
Will you marry me?
What... the fuck? Seriously?
I love you.
And I wanted to do something
to make all this better.
And I thought while your
dad's still with us,
wouldn't that be a nice thing?
We can get a quick wedding.
What is it about my dad dying
in a sterile environment
that screams big
romantic gesture to you?
Well, it's a horrible day, I thought...
Thought it would be a nice... thing.
Tom, you can't balance it out like that.
I'm not gonna... give you a
blow job when your dog dies.
Right?
Yeah. Ok.
It's fine. I misjudged it. I get it.
No, I'm s-sorry. Honey, I'm sorry.
I'm... this is...
Let's just not have this as the moment.
Why don't you do this again
properly another time.
No! Exactly. This is not the moment.
This didn't happen. Abort. Abort, abort,
good. Ok.
But so you know,
yeah, whatever.
- Yes? Yes?
- Yeah.
When it happens, yes.
Yes? Yes!
- Really?
- Yeah. I...
Yeah.
- It's such a shitshow.
- What is?
My family.
Our family.
- Our family.
- Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey.
So I got the slippers.
Thank you.
Yeah, I finally found 'em.
Can you put them in there, please?
Yeah.
So, you got the slippers.
I guess that makes you prince charming.
I guess so.
You saying you want to fuck marcia?
What?! No. Wh-why would you say that?
That's what you just said.
No. It isn't.
You said you were prince charming.
- No, you just said that.
- I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
Ok.
Do you know that, uh...
Do you know that he gave me a job?
What job?
- I don't know.
- Ok.
- Do you know when I start?
- No. Obviously I don't know.
- Why would I know?
- I don't know.
I thought you might know 'cause
I thought everybody's talking
and, like, might be talking about me?
No, everybody was talking
about you this whole time.
Everyone was only talking
about you, cousin Greg.
I get it.
Hey. Hey.
When you, uh, figure all this out,
come in and see me. Ok?
And, uh, and I'll look after you.
All right?
I'm serious. I will.
- Sure.
- Thanks, man.
That's ok.
All right, later.
Take it easy, Greg.
Yo, come here for a second.
So, listen.
I've been thinking...
We got for it. Me and you.
Ceo and coo.
- Oh.
- Me and my homey romey.
I thought I was a fuckhead.
Uh, dipshit, and you said that.
You said I wasn't serious.
- Sorry. It's been a long day.
- Yeah.
But dude, seriously.
Me and you, bro.
Like, I could teach you.
And you could, you know, teach me.
And shiv?
I mean, you know what shiv's like.
Ultimately she's a daddy's girl. Right?
I mean, she wants to play it safe.
We're the ones with the nuts
to fuckin' revolutionize.
Ok, I'm not uninterested.
All right, then, let's fuckin' do it.
Here's the thing. Gerri just
turned down the top job.
So does that mean something?
Are you fuckin' with me?
Nope.
Who asked Gerri?
It was broached.
- It was broached?
- Yeah.
By who? Did you broach?
You broached it, didn't you?
Don't pin the broach on me,
ok? Everyone was broaching.
Just want to make sure
we trust each other.
Everything up front, ok?
All right.
Ok.
Shake on it or something?
Official?
Oh. Ok.
Hi.
Oh, come on.
Hey. Hey, knock it off.
Thank you, Willa.
So, listen, I've asked Roman
to be acting coo...
- Actual coo.
- To my acting ceo.
- And you said?
- I said why not?
- Snake.
- Sis, please,
I'm trying to bring everyone
together here. I'm mediating.
- Well, I'm saying no.
- Me too.
I thought you were
a fucking white helmet.
Sometimes a peacekeeper has to go
shoot a maniac on the perimeter, ok?
What the fuck? Why would you say
no to this and yes to Gerri?
Gerri has been with the company
for 20 years. Dad trusts her.
She's older. She's wiser.
She's a mature person...
Such as myself.
Uh-huh. Well, she doesn't want it.
Ok, so in my opinion,
we should find someone else.
- Temporary.
- Ok, like who?
I don't know, someone neutral.
Eva or... American psycho, what...
- Karl.
- Karl. Yeah.
And what if it isn't temporary,
what if he uses his position
to make it permanent?
Because he wouldn't do that.
He's nice! He brought coffee.
Oh, he brought coffee.
Then we should definitely let him
take control of the company.
Dude, he's not gonna
Look, it's a gamble.
It's either me and Roman
and us as a family,
or it's Eva and Karl,
or some fuckface suit from the
deep state of the company.
They could take the company
out of our hands,
and we'd never get near it again.
If dad wakes up, and he's frail,
and he's looking at the end game,
you want to be the one who tells him
his family business
isn't family-run anymore?
I mean, maybe you
could get away with it...
- You know, his favorite.
- Oh, fuck you.
But maybe you wouldn't stay his favorite
if you gave away the firm.
Look, we need a statement by 6:30.
So you just have to think...
Like, bullshit aside...
Who do you think, really,
dad would prefer?
What's up, fam?
Oh. Yeah. Um... did you get the papers?
- What?
- The pap...
The papers in the envelope?
I called you?
Dude... oh, my god. I'm so sorry.
So no, basically?
I was thinking about your dad,
- I was up there...
- Hey, don't worry about it.
My head was just messed up.
Ok. We're gonna have to announce.
Where are we at?
While dad is ill, the family proposes
that Kendall run the company
with Roman as coo.
I hereby concur.
Ok. Ok, uh..
I will let the committee know
the family's position,
and pending board approval,
we can announce.
- Congratulations, Ken.
- Thanks, Gerri.
And Roman, congratulations.
This is all very exciting.
Difficult decision.
For the record,
I personally believe this
to be a total fucking disaster.
Ok, good.
Kendall, um, listen,
we need to talk.
I'm sorry, I just need to...
I just need a conversation
with you in private.
- What is this?
- Um...
There's a few things you should know.
Um......
Ok, there's no way to put this nicely,
so forgive me for stating it baldly,
but, um, there's a huge debt problem.
What are you... no.
- Yes. Three billion.
- No, there's not.
Fuck off. I'd know.
No one knows.
Well, me and frank.
What about... dad?
Yeah, your dad.
Hence the debt.
Gerri, what the fuck is going on?
Where did the money go?
In 1985,
Logan needed cash badly
for the expansion into parks,
so he took out a loan through
the family holding company.
He knew that besides frank,
none of the other boards members
could see what was happening.
And then he added that loan to the
company's already considerable debt.
Son of a bitch.
Ok.
We can deal.
Yeah, but Kendall, the thing is,
it's secured against waystar's stock...
And when the stock hits 130,
they can pursue repayment in full.
Which, if they decided
to do that, would eviscerate us.
Yeah, but there's no precedent for that.
They'll never do that.
They'll renegotiate.
- Well, that depends.
- On what?
Well, you see, the banks know
that the man they invested in
can no longer function,
and as far as they're concerned,
you're just some kid with nice hair.
You're making it quite fucking
difficult to savor this moment, Gerri.
I'm sorry about that.
Don't jump.
We had hoped to see a response by now,
but what we do know is
that he's stable. So...
If you want to grab some sleep,
this is a good time.
Night, dad.
See you soon.
corrected by Night_walker77