What if, after you die,
part of you goes to heaven,
part of you stays here?
Just to see how things turn out.
Wind Gap.
There was a murder there.
Another one's missing now.
Get me a story.
Hi, Momma.
Goodness, I didn't expect you.
The house is not
up to par for visitors.
I'm just in town
on business.
Camille, look at you.
I'm glad you're home.
What kind of person does that?
Hurt a child?
Doesn't help anything,
riling folks up.
You got two
mutilated girls on your hands.
Someone else is
doing the riling.
When you're here,
you're my daughter.
Everything you do
comes back on me.
I didn't come back
to cause any problems.
I can tell.
You hate this place, like me.
Someone in this town's
hiding something.
Momma says
I need to be careful around you.
Is that true?
Are you dangerous?
My dad's in the hospital.
I don't know
if he's gonna be okay.
What's the situation?
He's had a hemorrhagic stroke.
My assistant's been in touch
with NYU and we might
move Dad there.
No. He stays here.
I am his proxy.
I am in charge.
The board has a plan in the
event of Logan's incapacitation.
I'll be taking temporary charge
as CEO and chairman.
It wouldn't necessarily be you.
It could be me.
How can I not be
the logical choice?
Dad didn't want you running
the company.
We go for it. Me and you.
CEO and COO.
Okay.
Will you marry me?
Yeah, whatever.
Yes?
Do you know that he gave me
a job?
Come in and see me,
and I'll look after you.
There's a huge debt problem.
Three billion.
You're making it quite fucking
difficult to savor this moment,
Geri.
Don't jump.
There's a lot of mess
to be cleaned up, Kendall,
but you can do it, son.
Richard, can you get me
the price of the Waystar stock?
At close last night, please.
How is he?
Good. A little clearer.
He tried to put on a sock.
Hey.
Morning.
Hey, Mondale.
Wish me luck, buddy.
Wish me luck.
What's that? "Good luck, Tom!
Hope it goes well!" OK, so,
just wanted to say goodbye.
Have you seen the numbers?
Man, poor Ken. He's like
dysentery for the stock price.
You are walking
into a burning barn.
Still excited.
Still rarin' to go.
Mm...hmm.
Whoa.
I'm just paying homage.
What's that?
You miss me?
Well, I miss you too.
Maybe we should arrange a date
while she's not around.
You're weird.
No, you are weird! OK!
Goodbye.
Oh, Tom.
I'm gonna go see Dad.
If Marcia wants to be difficult,
so can I.
So...can you come with me?
Uh, I gotta stay in front
on this one, baby.
It's a hugie.
My first morning stepping up.
Just say you went
to see the big boss.
Don't make me choose, Shiv.
Please. Don't make me choose.
It's a man's right
not to choose.
Hey, Rava. Can you
give me 30 seconds?
Sorry, I'm just
getting the kids ready.
Oh, Luanne,
can you get...
Yeah? OK.
Hey.
Hi.
Uh, yeah, so...
this is... this is dumb,
but bank call this morning,
and I just wanted to ask...
Wait. What bank?
Our old joint account?
Um, no, no, Rava,
the bank.
ICBC, who have apparently
bankrolled the old man for years.
I'm sorry.
I'm... just in a rush. OK.
Just two minutes?
What's your read?
Do I go... do I go Hulk,
or Bruce Banner?
Well, K... Kendall,
talk to your people about...
I know, you're just...you're
always so good with this stuff, and just, uh...
The Hulk is the incredible one,
right? The Hulk.
We have to go. I'm sorry.
Why don't you ask Roman? OK?
Guys?
Roma... Rava. Come on.
Seriously?
I'm sorry.
Bye!
Bye, guys.
Bye...bye. I love you.
Out of ten?
Uh, seven.
OK.
You're in decent shape,
you're a little sloppy,
but I can get you tight as a drum.
Ah. Well, I trust Pax,
and Pax says you're the best.
I'm only gonna say
one thing, Roman, OK?
Go for it.
I take my shit serious,
that's why I have
the reputation that I do,
and I need you
to take it serious, too. OK?
Dude, I'm...I'm onboard,
so you can skip the whole
speech bullshit, OK?
I'm down.
All right. 5:30 every day.
Yeah, man, I'm serious.
I'm serious as cancer.
Fuckin' more serious.
Fuckin' money cancer.
You know, I'm COO now.
Mm...hmm.
Yeah.
That's Chief Operating Officer.
It's Waystar Royco,
so if it operates, I chief it.
Flip over on your belly.
Yeah.
Ahh.
But yeah, no,
5:30, that's perfect.
A. M. right?
Yup.
Well, good, because the other 5:30
I'll be at work, ya know?
Being an agent of change
and fuckin' firing people.
Thank you.
Ask her to wait there.
Oh! She's here.
It's the morphine.
It's not that unusual.
I know. I'm fine.
Is everything all right?
Hi, Shiv.
Hi!
Hi, Tom.
Hey. I'm afraid I can't stay.
Excuse me one second.
First day.
Hi.
What's the...
What's going on?
Nothing.
No?
Staff.
Good to see you.
Yeah. I know you said
that he wasn't great,
but I was passing by,
so I thought I'd just
drop in.
That is so sweet.
But you know, he's not
seeing people right now.
Yeah, but I thought
I could just pop up.
Even if, you know, he's grumpy.
I think it's best you don't.
Marcia, I've seen my dad
do the Master Cleanse.
I can take him
a little bit grouchy.
I'm afraid that
is out of the question.
Um, do you...
Might it be an idea
to check and see whether
he's changed his mind?
Yeah.
Perked up a little bit?
Of course.
What the fuck?
I know. I have to go.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, hey. Hello. Hi!
I'm Shiv.
Logan's daughter.
I just...I wanted
to say thank you for...
for all your work.
You're quite welcome.
Yeah. It's much appreciated.
Thank you.
And how does he seem today?
Good?
Oh... you know.
Actually, we don't.
We heard al about the sock.
Yeah.
It'll stabilize.
Mm...hmm. I know.
I know it will.
So... I've been thinking.
I've got a new game plan
for the call.
Uh...huh.
Hey. Can you try and not
look so fuckin' nervous?
I know what I'm doing.
I'm relaxed.
I just think it's a little late,
considering the gravity
and the need to get
the relationship right.
Sure. The...The new strategy
is really just a refinement
of all this great work.
It goes, uh...
Well, the working title
is "Go Fuck Yourself."
Uh...huh.
Hi, I have Mr. Polk.
Uh...huh. What do you think?
I think I need a little bit
more of an explanation.
My dad's a bastard,
they need to know I'm a bastard, too.
Right?
Right...
Great.
Hey, Mr. Polk.
Hi, Kendall, good to connect.
Likewise. Yeah, great.
So, you...you wanna go?
Well, why don't you go?
OK. Well, uh, sure.
We just wanted to make contact,
given where we are.
Mm...hmm. We are concerned.
Absolutely.
Now, obviously, look,
the main thing is,
we just handle this very calmly,
because the last thing
either of us want
is for this rather private
arrangement my father made
to, uh, you know, make waves.
Absolutely.
But I guess the issue is
we owe you 3.2 billion...
3.25.
Hey, I was rounding down.
We round up.
3.25 billion,
secured against
Waystar stock,
which is, you know, undergoing
some temporary turbulence
due to sector...wide factors.
Mm...hmm.
So, I guess, you know,
what I'd like to know is,
what your position will be
if we have a sustained breach
of the stock price
and we fall out of compliance
with our debt covenant?
OK, well, if the stock drops,
we're entitled to ask
for a payment in full.
Uh...huh, exactly.
Technically, uh, yeah.
So... what will we do here
in reality?
If it breaches 130,
you've broken the covenant
and we will want repayment.
Right.
I know.
But, um, like, really?
Seriously.
OK, I-I get it.
That's your initial position,
but we will want to restructure,
and, uh--
Look, here's where I'm at.
We're not crazy
about the media sector,
we're not crazy about
how your father has treated our relationship,
and our position
is to seek recoupment.
Oh, come on, man.
Fuck off.
Uh, hello?
I'm here.
Yeah. Yeah, come on.
Real world, can we start
to negotiate?
Listen, son,
that's our position.
If the stock drops below 130,
you're in breach
and we want our money back.
OK, fine. Let's keep talking.
Look, if you need
to talk to me,
maybe it's better if we
go through an intermediary.
I'm not a particular fan
of foul language,
and I don't like
to be insulted.
Thank you, good morning.
Oh, boy.
Fuck, that was brutal.
You were listening in?
Of course I was in.
I'm COO. Oof!
Are-Are they for real?
Would they squeeze us?
Well, obviously they could.
Yeah, but why would they?
Relax, man,
it'll be fine.
Uh, no, it fuckin'
necessarily won't. OK?
If this became public,
we could nosedive,
we could death spiral here.
Dude, I was only trying
to be nice.
That was a fucking shitshow,
and you handled it like a moron, is the truth.
Fuck off.
Gents.
Hello.
Uh, Greg Hirsch.
I believe I'm working here
as of today.
OK, what is your job
or job title?
Um, job, not entirely sure,
per se.
Uh... I'll find out.
OK, um, I don't
have anything.
I was actually personally
appointed by Mr. Logan Roy.
OK. Um...
Um...
Is there anyone else, maybe?
Tom?
Tom.
Last name?
Last name, uh...
Weird, I don't think
I ever got his last--
Uh, T-boss Tom...
Tom? Tom?
Hey! Hey!
Hey.
Can you help me?
Can you help--
OK, Greg. Greg Roy?
That's the--
I'm actually a Hirsch.
I'm not a--
My mom's a Roy, but, uh,
I'm basically a Roy
in all-all but my name.
Wait--
I'll be two minutes.
What? No. No. Shiv--
It has gotten weird.
OK? It has gotten very weird.
How is he?
I don't know.
He might have put on a sock.
Well, that's good, right?
Or he could be lying there dead.
I have no fuckin' idea.
OK, this is--
It's not a good time.
She thinks that
Marcia's poisoning him.
I do not. Apparently,
he doesn't want to see us.
Not including me?
Why would he say that?
Still pissed at you
for not signing up
to his corporate restructure
to make Marcia
queen of the castle?
OK, yeah.
Maybe she's pissed.
Look, did you see him
over the weekend?
No. I heard he wasn't
up to seeing people.
Yeah, no one has seen him
since we took him home from the hospital,
like, Thursday.
I think-Rome? You saw him,
right?
Uh, sure, yeah,
for, like, five minutes.
But he was, um...
he was pretty--
He wasn't really him him,
there were tubes and...
OK, but after that?
Nope.
No one apart from Marcia
has seen him
for the better part of a week.
Four days is not a week.
OK, the majority of the week,
and we're just accepting--
the whole world
is just accepting
this woman's word
that he put on a fucking sock.
Look, relax, OK?
I-It's a process,
we don't want
to rush the recovery...
Oh, right, because
you like playing boss?
That's not...
Please. Can you
go over there?
Shiv, this is--
I literally have something
unmissable.
Later. OK?
I'll try later.
OK?
OK.
Is everything OK?
No. We are on the brink
of total corporate collapse.
Oh, yeah.
Well, that figures.
Well, call me
if you go Lehman, will you?
Might want
some of these chairs.
Morning.
Here to help fix the Death Star.
"Grill on the exhaust vent,
guys,
grill on the exhaust vent."
So, my only concern would be,
to brief this meeting,
is it a little too aggressive
for a temporary CEO?
That is a good point.
Yeah, well, we've got
a very aggressive drop
in our share price, so I think
that's appropriate, good?
So brief this wide
and brief it fast, OK?
OK.
Uh, yeah. Great.
All right, all right!
Morning, morning, morning.
Hey, hey, hey.
My people.
It's great to see you all.
You know my brother and I,
CEO and COO...
COO.
Gerri, Karl, Karolina.
Um...
I'm actually gonna stand up,
if that's all right.
My back is fucked.
I have a new trainer, so...
So, I just wanted to
get the gang together early in my tenure
to say, uh... "Yo."
You're probably all wondering
about my dad.
He's doing OK.
Motherfucker.
We're hoping for
a full recovery.
He's, like,
a thousand percent better, though.
He's like a bull
in rhino hide.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Slow and steady.
This morning
he put on a sock, so...
That's right. Uh, this morning
he tried to put on a sock.
And welcome to Tom Wamsgans,
who was managing Resorts
South and Central
and is now sitting up
with the grownups.
Hey. I just want--
So, what I want to announce
to you all this morning
is a new strategic vision.
We have a great firm here.
Multifaceted.
Parks, cruises,
telecom, live entertainment,
sports--
but at the heart, media.
TV, movies, books, newspapers.
And what we're fighting for
is eyeballs, eyeballs which we
convert to our customer base,
eyeballs which we crate up
and sell to advertisers.
Right? And bottom line,
we're losing...
to monopolistic disruptors.
Alphabet, Facebook...
Internet.
Fucking game-changer, man.
That's right, the internet.
Internet.
But, uh, we are still just--
just-in a position
to leverage our brands into
something in the new landscape.
But if we don't,
we're gonna be like
the biggest fuckin' horse trader
in Detroit, 1909. OK?
We need
a more dynamic strategy.
Now, let's call it,
for the sake of clarity,
the Strategy
of a Thousand Lifeboats.
Vaulter is a lifeboat,
ATN Citizens is a lifeboat.
There are no bad lifeboats.
VR could be a lifeboat.
VR's a bubble,
but yeah. No bad ideas.
Porn could be a lifeboat.
Except that.
That's a bad lifeboat.
Hey, thanks, Rome.
Look, this isn't a brainstorm,
all I'm saying,
everyone's invited. OK?
I want each and every one of you
to be innovating, challenging,
being bold, being disruptive,
bringing me new, original,
multiplatform content.
Bring me more
in the interactive and digital space.
Bring me franchiseable IP.
Bring me a thousand lifeboats.
Bring me a fucking armada
of eyeballs.
Because steady as she goes
hits the iceberg.
All right.
Thanks, everyone.
Lifeboats! Whoo!
Just had to say,
that was great. Kudos.
Always here if you need
a friendly ear,
Lord Vader.
Just get shit moving
at Parks.
Yes.
Yeah, Tom?
It's stagnant,
so shake that fuckin' tree,
C3PO.
Shakin' the tree.
Shakin' it big time.
Uh, Fiona.
Walk with me.
Can you send flowers to Rava?
Nice, but, you know,
not ridiculous.
They should smell like flowers,
not desperation.
Oh, and Fi, talk to Jess,
I might want to throw
a couple of items up on the internal.
Not a big deal,
couple of TED talks.
Maybe a documentary
on the Epic of Gilgamesh, I'm thinking?
You know,
it's the first story, archetypal quest shit.
Because what are we
if not storytellers?
Hey. Talk to me.
Down three points,
and there's an AP headline
"CEO tells staff
Waystar headed for iceberg."
Not iceberg, lifeboats.
I said lifeboats, not iceberg!
Jesus! Karolina.
That's what we're pushing.
Push harder.
Will do.
I want to talk options
to you, OK?
I've got some thoughts
I've been working on for a long time--
OK, I don't want the sloppy seconds, Gerri.
I'm taking five to think big.
Ken, these are modeled
and thought through--
And rejected.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm talking a walk,
I need to get
some altitude on this.
I'll be back.
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
The thing about capitalism is,
yeah, sure,
it's got its issues,
but fuck me--
this is a piece of shit chain
on a stretch of nothing,
but this-this is the most delicious thing
anyone's ever fucking tasted.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
Thank you.
So dude, listen.
Mm-hmm?
I could do with a read
from someone without
a dog in the fight.
Actually, I gotta
talk to you about something, too.
This is tight.
This is absolutely
just us, OK?
Because a leak kills me.
Right.
This is about Rava.
For a pal.
Rava?
Yeah, it's a mutual friend,
and they want to know
is it cool,
or you still hankerin'
for a wankerin'?
I don't have time for this.
I mean, who-who's asking?
What?
I can't say.
But they just want
to know if it's an issue.
Like who, fuckin' Paul?
Well, if you're asking,
I'm assuming it's a fucking issue.
No, I mean, look,
we're separated, you know?
Whatever.
Free agents.
Yeah. No, I get it.
I'm gonna have another.
You know, if you
eat it fast enough
it actually burns off
the calories.
It's like a loophole.
Can I have another, please?
So, listen,
when I took over...
found out Dad
took out a huge loan
a decade ago. Secret.
Through the holding company.
Are you serious?
Secured against
the family's stake
in the public firm.
Fuck. Dude.
Yeah. Now the stock
is getting ready to breach,
and the bank are...
Yeah, I know, I saw the price.
It's brutal.
Who's the bank?
Mm-hmm. I'm just
gonna do this.
Dude...
we're not at Buckley
anymore. Jesus.
It's fine.
So, these guys
have your dick in a vise.
Yes. Thank you, Stewy.
Mm-hmm.
Can I have your take?
Well, number one,
you boost the price.
Yeah, no shit, Sherlock.
OK.
I'm trying.
How's it gonna play
for us to refinance?
Honestly? Not great.
Why won't your original bank
step up? Not good.
People don't love the sector,
and they don't love the fucking firm.
It's ramshackle, is the view.
And bro,
they don't love... you.
It's tough.
Ah, fuck it.
OK! I am open for business.
You know, one thing occurs.
Just blue sky,
wouldn't happen in a million years,
but what if
we came in,
took the whole thing
off your family's hands?
Uh, well, obviously no,
fuck off, how dare you,
I'm so insulted, et cetera.
Of course. But you
and Roman and Shiv,
you're gonna do that thing
forever? No.
You all have the chance
to be fucking...
fucking, like,
ugly petro-ruble rich.
You can do anything.
You can go into tech,
Shiv can do her politics
or whatever,
and Roman can, you know,
snort his body weight.
And you all live
unhappily ever after.
Uh-huh. Thanks, Stewy.
Just think about it.
Can I get the senior team
together tomorrow
for a reorientation?
Shakin' the tree, folks,
shakin' the tree.
Excuse me.
Greg? Are you kidding?
Hey, Tom.
Forgive me, but, uh...
we talkin' to each other
on the poop deck
of a majestic schooner?
Is the salty brine
stinging my weather-beaten face?
No?
Then why the fuck
are you wearing
a pair of deck shoes, man?
Oh-Yeah-No, well,
my credit card got maxed out,
I'm staying in a youth hostel
on, like, $80 a day--
Jesus. How squalid.
Dude, are you
carrying dog shit?
No-No, it's, uh...
it's free, right?
Is that cool? I mean,
I don't wanna be melodramatic,
but my body is growing weak
due to a lack of sustenance.
But in a dog poop baggie?
Yeah, I have
a bunch of 'em
from back home--
Greg, that's disgusting.
Not really.
It's not like
they pre-poop them
or something,
like, it's not like--
they're just bags, really.
It's just a mental barrier.
A pair of cap-toe Oxfords,
Crockett &amp; Jones, ASAP.
Lucinda, can we figure out
where we might put
the talented Mr. Greg?
Hey.
Nathaniel.
Siobhan.
How have you been?
Uh, yeah, good.
Busy.
Right.
So, is this...?
Work.
OK. Of course.
Yeah.
Wha-What?
Work.
A little work meeting
on the bed of a four-star hotel.
Get your mind
out of the gutter.
OK.
How's it goin'
workin' with... Joyce?
That tall glass of tepid water
from Albany.
It's great. Yeah.
How's the, uh,
poor man's Fidel Castro?
Senior senator from
the state of 1975.
How's that
workin' out for ya?
Better. Zing!
I wondered if you
could do me a favor.
Do I owe you a favor?
Yeah, 'cause I deigned
to date you.
You deigned.
That's nice.
And I thought
we were gonna be friends.
Sure. I wanna be friends.
Good.
I need a background check
on somebody.
Well, that might cause
some ethical issues.
'Cause there's a world
where my guy and your gal
end up in the mud wrestling
for the Democratic nomination.
No, it's not political.
I need background on someone
off the record.
Uh, Marcia.
Marcia.
The wicked stepmother.
Yeah.
It occurred to me
a few years too late
that I don't really
know anything about her.
So... just due diligence.
OK?
Well, um,
I know a really horrible guy
who's incredibly expensive.
OK. Yeah,
that sounds great. OK.
All goes through you?
Yes, milady.
OK.
"Deigned."
Yeah.
Did you see the women
I dated after you?
Yeah. They only dated you
because you dated me.
They were like,
"Oh, I guess he must have something."
Waystar diversity
and harassment policy.
Waystar Royco has worked hard
to develop a tolerant
and respectful workplace.
The company
is strongly committed
to making employment decisions
based on valid requirements
and without regards to race,
religion, national origin,
ancestry, gender,
gender identity,
gender expression,
sex preference,
sexual orientation,
physical or mental disability,
military status,
marital status,
or any other status as is
protected by applicable law.
Where the law requires
affirmative action programs,
the company will strive
to comply with the provisions of those laws.
Thank you for your attention.
Welcome to your new future
at Waystar Royco.
Feel it!
Hey. Where we at?
Hey.
We're down two more points.
Fuck.
Listen, Sandy Furness is here.
What do you mean?
I mean, he's here,
in the building.
He can't do that.
Fucking Pepsi doesn't just
drop in to see Coke.
Put him where
no one can see him.
South tank. I'm right here.
Sharks are circling.
Your father
would shoot him on sight.
You know, I don't need
to hear what my father would do right now.
OK? He's not here.
Right.
I'm gonna handle it.
He's not here.
Mr. Furness, what a surprise.
So kind of you to drop by.
Oh, not at all.
I just came to say
how sorry I was to hear about your dad.
Well, it's so kind of you
to do it in person
when you could have just called.
Thank you.
Well, I hope I didn't send
the birds a-tweeting,
what with all
the uncertainty and whatnot.
We'll make sure people know
it's just friendly.
And you'll give your dad
my best, tell him I stopped by?
Of course. Sure.
Maybe when that news is, uh...
less likely to kill him.
OK, well,
thank you. I do--
I appreciate this.
Oh, and just to say,
if, um, I can give you
any advice,
I'm just watching
the wheels nowadays,
so if you want to
run anything by me
as an honest broker,
use me.
A mentor.
That is a very kind offer.
Well, there's probably
a million options with our two firms.
Swaps, acquisitions,
cooperative interactions.
You know, smart stuff
only a young man like you
can conceive of.
Well, Sandy,
you've been pretty smart.
Smarter than the regulators,
anyway.
Tell you what's smart:
Vaulter.
I don't care
what the wise apples say.
Well, uh, I've got a thing.
Hey, Jess, will you
take Mr. Furness down?
Look at you. Right in the eye
of the raging storm and...
and cool as a cucumber.
Stay strong.
Stay in touch.
Um...
Yeah.
What happened?
He said I was
dead in the water without him
and tried
to finger-bang me.
What'd you say?
Said I'd rather
eat my own shit.
Have you heard?
What?
Stock's gone below 130.
You know sometimes
you leave the party
and you wonder what everyone's
saying about you?
With me it's usually
"Who's that young Han Solo
and how do I get his dick
in my ass?"
Like, I know
what they say about me.
What?
That. See that?
That's how much
people don't like me.
Hey, that's me too.
Don't leave me out.
The truth is,
we call their bluff,
which may not be a bluff,
and the debt becomes public,
and we lose control.
Or we get the stock up,
which we can't,
because we can't "magic" that,
or we pay the bank back,
which, I mean,
to realize that much cash...
stock sell-down,
which is horrible.
There is no good option.
Can I suggest something?
Yeah?
Can I suggest we all
take our shirts off?
OK. Kendall?
They can write
a fucking algorithm
to run this place,
but that's not the answer.
That's not us.
So... break shit up.
Like, just disrupt.
What are you doing?
Takin' my shirt off.
That's all.
Ken, make him
put his shirt on.
I don't-uh, I don't--
I don't fuckin' know. I--
Shirt off.
Shirts off.
How about your jacket off?
Come on, man.
Yeah, all right. All right.
Good.
That's all. Let's go.
OK.
So...
worst position, we sell down
the stock, we survive.
Maybe we cut a title or two
from physical production,
newspaper-wise.
Online only.
I like that.
That is a $20 million solution
to a billion dollar problem.
Yeah, but it's the right
direction of travel.
That feels right to me.
If you want stuff that works
for the price: layoffs.
Yum-yum. Blood! Yes!
See? Shirts-off shit.
I guess it could be a package.
Layoffs, sell-offs.
Structured retreat?
Well, yeah,
but with a philosophy.
OK.
Yeah.
OK? I mean,
OK.
I guess we just have
to ask or, you know, tell Dad.
Hey, guys.
Finally.
Hi.
Hey, sweetie. Hi.
What's up, slugger?
Hey.
Thanks for joining us.
Actually,
I can't stay long.
Apparently goes for us, too.
Aunt Marcia
won't let us see Grandpa.
Right, kids?
Huh.
Hey, Marcia.
Kendall.
How are you?
Good.
How's he doing?
Is he OK?
He's improving.
He's really improving.
Great.
Yeah.
'Cause I should probably
let him know something.
He's resting.
I'm sorry,
it's not a good time.
OK.
Well, it's just
when my assistant called--
She spoke with Joan, not me.
Got it.
Yeah.
Well, uh, let him know,
will you, that I stopped by,
wanted to talk to him,
keep him abreast of moves?
If you like, you can tell me,
I'll pass it on.
Um...
will you just tell him
that we're...
um, we're retreating,
tactically.
Well, that doesn't
sound right.
Not retreating, quite, but...
It's hard to explain.
I'm sure you're doing
the right thing.
OK, thanks. See you soon.
See you.
So, Stewy?
Mm-hmm?
You know how, like,
everyone hates you?
Well, no, that's not
something I'm aware of.
Oh, sure. They do.
Private equity,
getting your meat hooks in,
chiseling your profit
like a vampire locust fuck.
What is this?
Is this a roast?
Because I have shit to do.
I've had an idea.
OK.
How about instead of taking us over,
you give me $4 billion?
I stay boss,
you stop raiding
shitty companies for scraps,
you invest, for once,
in a blue-chip corporation,
one that is currently,
you know, undervalued
because of some
unfounded concerns
about its leadership, i. e.,
Little Lord Fuckleroy here,
the story twists...
happy ending for all.
Oh ho ho!
OK. Full disclosure?
Yeah.
I have a hangover.
And it's bigger than normal.
Why don't we do what we did
back in the day,
let's go to the bathroom,
have a little sumthin'-sumthin',
just knock out a few ideas,
just bash 'em out.
No. Not for me.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Do you mind if I have, like,
just like a taste of it?
Really, dude?
Ooh.
Yeah. Mm-kay.
Are you done?
Uh, no.
Obviously, I don't generally
take a minority stake in a public company.
Yeah, obviously,
because you're a parasite.
Mm-hmm.
How about for once
you make things bigger?
You know,
with your old pal?
Are you done?
Yeah.
Well, I can't even begin
to think about this.
But if I could...
to sell it,
I'm gonna need voting stock.
As long as the family
maintain control?
Well, effective control.
I'm also gonna need a board seat.
Oh, I'd force it on you,
dude. For the optics.
Shit hot new CEO
has some hot shit new money for investment.
New generation.
I keep the debt
out of the news.
Fuckin' sisters doin' it
for theyselves.
I'm not necessarily
totally opposed to this notion.
That's right, and luckily
I speak Stewy,
and that's Stewy for
"I have a fuckin' raging hard-on for this."
Greg. Come on, buddy.
First meeting of
the senior management cadre.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, come on.
Uh, great. Great stuff.
Great.
You know, I was lookin' through
employee emails,
which, by the way,
is totally legal,
and, uh, does my breath smell?
Honestly?
No, no. No, I mean,
it smells of breath,
but--
You know, there's
too much drift in Parks.
I'm gonna shake that tree.
I might punch-bag you
a little, is that cool?
Sure. As in,
like, punch-Yeah.
Morning, people.
Kick-off. Ahem.
Here's a question.
Here we are, out in
the Theme Park Division,
but tell me this:
if you could really do anything,
professionally,
and work anywhere,
where would that be?
Excuse me.
Uh-huh. Oh, no. Shiv.
I'm in the middle
of the first m-meeting.
Well, it's hard--
Connor's flying in?
OK. OK.
All right, bye. Right.
Fuck!
You background checked her?
Yeah, no need to tell Ken.
Is that legal?
You don't need to know.
Um, hey...
can anybody do that on anybody?
OK, so, first husband,
Lebanese businessman.
Yeah, I remember.
Right.
They had the high life in Paris,
lot of parties, with pols,
and writers, and also
a lot of shitbags and slimeballs
and arms dealers, oil guys.
Wow.
And further back?
Well, further back...
further back is complicated.
There's no leads.
What?
Yeah.
Is that...
Weird? Yes.
Ominous, yes.
Yeah.
It's apparently
a little weird.
And there are
two possibilities.
Either she came
from kind of nowhere,
Tripoli, Lebanon,
turns up in Paris,
age 31,
a publishing assistant,
and then just marries this guy.
Fine.
Or.
Or... cleanup job.
Oh! Hey, Marcia.
Great impression of a cuckoo.
Door opens, and there you are.
Hello, everybody.
Hi.
Yeah, hi. This is Connor,
Logan's firstborn son, you remember him?
And this is Tom, my partner,
and together
they're over 12 feet
of We Would Like To See Him, Please.
Are you trying to force entry,
is that it?
Oh, boy. I thought
we were just stopping by.
I usually try to avoid confrontation.
Let's all breathe.
He simply isn't
up to visitors.
Is this about me signing
some pieces of paper? Or...
Oh, please, Shiv.
It's very difficult as it is.
Oh, the fuckin' waterworks?
Is that it?
You're gonna cry now? Please.
Siobhan.
I can't believe
you would try and stop me seeing my father.
And I can't believe
you will try against his wishes.
Hi. Dad.
Hey.
Can you?
How are you feeling?
Uh, uhh-uhh--
Yeah?
You're looking good.
You're-You look better.
So, hey, Tom and I
are gonna move here, we think.
More permanently.
Less time in D. C.
Oh, and we're engaged.
Um, he wanted to ask you.
I love you.
I love you too.
Ohhh.
I'm gonna...
go get Joan. OK?
It's-It's fine.
I-I'll be back.
How is Mr. Roy?
Yeah. He--
Ohh.
Everything OK?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
He's looking better.
Morning isn't usually
a good time.
You know, the morphine,
he gets confused.
He doesn't like you all to
see him when he's not himself.
Uh-huh. Yeah,
he wasn't himself.
Right.
So...
Shiv, I'm a private person.
Not all of us
are born into good ease.
OK.
So if you want to know
anything about me,
just ask me,
and I will tell you.
Uh-huh.
Hey, Siobhan,
how's Pop?
Yeah. Yeah, no, he's good.
OK, bye.
He's tired.
Good afternoon.
Thanks for making time for us,
Mr. Polk.
Not at all.
We've been looking
at the terms we can offer,
I think you've seen
what we've put together.
I have. I have.
It's a very brutal structure.
Well, these are the terms
we think we can offer
right now.
I mean, I don't know,
the margin you're making,
you might even say you were...
well, I mean,
"extortion" is an ugly word,
but, you know, so is
"buzz saw castration."
Look, I think we should
keep things professional, don't you?
Uh-huh. Sure. Sure.
And professionally,
we're going to repay.
As in...?
We're good.
Everything's golden.
We don't need you.
This can all stay private,
and I'll be looking elsewhere
for a banking partner
as we go supersonic.
Good-bye.
Mr. Roy--
And fuck you.
Have you been here?
No.
It's super-good.
I'm thinking...
tout le lapin...
"all of the rabbit."
All of it.
Well, that's my question,
is when they say
"all of the rabbit,"
do they mean, like,
all of the rabbit?
I mean, it can't be,
like, all of it.
So, is this the Stewy money
we're celebrating?
Because I saw the news.
Well, I wouldn't say
that I'm the man,
but if there were a man,
hypothetically,
he might look a lot like me.
Yeah, I solved the debt issue
with private equity money.
I'm very happy for you.
Yeah. Well...
...the thing is, all of that,
it's made me
think about everything,
and, um...well, you know,
like, here's where I'm at.
I love you.
OK.
Well, thank you. Noted.
That's it? Come on.
That's--
"And... I..."
Uh, Ken.
OK. Uh, I'm not sure
that I love you.
Yeah, you do.
Fuck you.
Look, you want us
to live separately, right?
We don't know why right now,
you say you do.
Now, that makes me unhappy.
On the other hand, you claim,
and of course
I don't believe you,
that us being together
will make you unhappy.
So one of us
is going to be unhappy.
I just don't see
why it has to be me.
Wow. I-I cannot argue
with that logic.
No, it's, like,
impenetrable logic.
It's the argument
of a psychopath.
A psychopath who might,
hypothetically, be the man.
Who loves you.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck you.
We are not breaking up.
Yes. We are. I--
Yes, we are.
Sorry.
We are not. Not.
Yes, we are.
No!
Yes! Yes!
We are not breaking up.
We fucking are.
Good mornin'.
So, did you want
to work out down here?
Want me to take
my car to the park,
we can parkour it?
Well, here's the thing, Brex.
I can't do shit, really,
because my back
has been fucked
since Monday.
Fucked how?
Well, I assume
you're insured?
I mean, I do big,
big shit here,
every day,
so losing even
a quarter of a percent
of my operating capacity,
that has million dollar
implications.
So I'm thinkin'
maybe a test case,
I throw three or four dozen
white-shoe lawyers at you
and see what it would be like
to actually physically
destroy someone.
Dude, I don't know
what happened,
but I'm sure I can fix it.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck you.
Oh, fuck you, dude!
Jeez, look at you.
Look at your face!
You're a piece of shit.
Yeah.
But, uh, no,
I'm just sayin'
you need to take this
more seriously.
OK.
I have to go.
What about Malaya,
can't she--?
No. Iverson will freak out.
Hey, Rava.
What?
Why don't we just do it all?
You know? Back together?
Uh... let's talk later?
What does that mean?
Hey.
That was nice, right?
Nevertheless.
What?
Look, I, um...
I-I don't know.
I don't know.
Maybe it's, um, um-
Shit. It's like-
It's like you're moving on,
and maybe that makes me feel OK
about moving on too.
No. I'm not moving on. Rava.
That's bullshit.
I got a lawyer.
He's nice.
Let's just keep this all
really, really nice, OK?
Marcia?
Everything all right?
Kendall, you father
would like to see you.
...a dozen troops swarmed
the drugs farm from the air,
descending from helicopters,
while another unit
entered on foot.
It's claimed
the drug trafficking ring
had been in existence
for over three years...
Hey. Look at you.
Sitting up.
Fuckin' watchin' the news.
It's good to see you, Dad.
Well...
you understand
after you went down,
the stock tanked.
I mean, you should be flattered,
I guess.
We had some
pretty shitty options.
I mean, you took a gamble
on that loan.
But I found us
a private equity solution.
So...
I tried consulting you,
but-
People like the shape of this.
Karolina says there's
positive analyst noise.
We are at 36%,
with effective control,
plus a war chest
to make some moves.
We're-
We're in good shape, Dad.
You just keep
getting better.
I got this.
Fuginidiot.
Dad?
Hey, can I get you something?
You...
are...
fuh...
...fucking idiot.
Hi.
I think, uh...