- I'm laying out. You coming?
- The UV index is 10.
Jesus, we don't do anything.
We don't eat.
We don't go out.
God knows we don't do anything else.
Is that all you
ever think about, sex?
All I ever think about?
You haven't fucked me in over a year.
Blood sugar, I told you,
the weight loss.
Good, fine.
Skin cancer.
What's up?
Thing we talked
about at the wedding.
Rusty.
You made the call
to Italy.
Our friend over there's
gonna fit him for a suit.
She's sending over
two of her best tailors.
So I should meet 'em
at the airport?
No, they're gonna call
you when they arrive.
Now you hook 'em up
with a third party, huh?
Get 'em some scissors.
This is smart, Ton',
the more I think about it.
Glad you approve.
Anybody taking a look,
there's nothing linking us to it.
- Hey, good seeing you.
- Hey, there he is.
How are you?
Listen,
come here a minute.
About the other day...
I'm fine.
A couple of stitches.
Yeah? My fucking
temper, you know?
No no no no,
it's okay, really.
Take it.
Thanks.
Look, Ton',
I don't remember slamming
the refrigerator door,
but Carlo told me
and my dad,
I never should have raised my hands
to you. I'm sorry.
As long as
you realize.
It basically became
the same thing every day.
Coffee,
couple lines of meth,
smooth that out
with a shot of Jameson.
And that was just
to drive the kids to school.
Then one day I fell asleep at work
and forgot about Gracie's recital.
Human frailty, it makes
me sick sometimes.
- Chris, right?
- Should I know you?
Kevin Mucci, Yonkers.
We met at the Trotters.
Sal lacuzzo's cousin.
- Right. Hey.
- Hey.
Yonkers,
what are you, lost?
My ex's birthday over
at the Red Robin in Clifton.
I figured I'd need a meeting
to make it through that shit.
I hear that.
So I saw my cousin
this week.
It turns out he ran into a friend
of yours, the big guy, Vito.
And...
He was in a fag bar,
dancing with a guy.
Get the fuck out!
Right, Joey, use your head.
You are not gonna
fucking believe this.
Vito Spatafore's
an ass-muncher.
- Oh! What?
- What did you just say?
I'm sorry, it's true.
We ran into this kid. Vito was spotted
in a fag bar in New York.
By who?
The kid's cousin.
Allegedly.
Probably bullshit.
- He's a married man.
- With a goomar.
All right,
back up a second.
What did the kid
say exactly?
- The kid's cousin Sal lacuzzo...
- From Yonkers, I know him.
Sal was at this place in the city,
supposedly on business.
He saw Vito holding hands
with a guy in nipple rings.
You're leaving out
the best part.
He was wearing
a motorcycle outfit,
like the guy in the Village People
with the leather hat
- and the vest.
- Chaps too.
I don't know.
Fucking slander, ask me.
All right, let's take this
in the back.
- Yeah, that's what Vito did.
- You can go.
Tell you one thing, if it was me this
kid was spreading rumors about,
he'd have something up
his own ass.
And it wouldn't be
no cock, either.
That's the point,
though.
This guy Sal,
I know him.
- He's a friend of ours.
- I fucking called it, long time ago.
You knew Vito
was a recchion'?
- Yes.
- When?
I never said it,
but I knew.
Get the fuck out.
Enough of this rush to judgment.
For all we know, this fucking Sal guy's
got a hard-on for Vito.
Oh, you think
this is funny, huh?
There's a man's reputation
at stake here.
A married man,
with kids.
Nah, that don't mean shit.
Elton John was married.
Yeah, Rock Hudson too.
I think.
So what do we gotta do, Ton',
actually see him take it in the ass?
Get Vito
on the phone.
You know, he called me
the other night.
3:00 in the morning,
after the wedding.
And?
Honestly, it was weird.
He wanted to know what was going on.
He was fucking fishing,
see if we heard.
Straight to voice mail.
Ton', I mean,
he represents us.
I'm not gonna condemn
the man off the word
of some fucking douchebag
from Yonkers.
- I could care less, basically.
- Yeah? Maybe you're a flambe.
Fucking nauseating.
It was up to me, I'd drag Vito behind
my fucking car right now.
Will you take it easy over there,
fucking Judge Roy Bean?
One of my bar girls
knows his goomar.
We'll check with her. Maybe she's seen
him and knows where he is.
Loren.
Think about it,
though, Ton'...
sudden weight loss.
- AIDS?
- Nobody's got AIDS.
I don't wanna hear
that word in here again!
The Federal Prosecutor's office won't
tell you why your son's being held?
Or where. It has been four days
now since he's been arrested,
and we have no money
to hire a lawyer.
- How did you hear about the law center?
- You will write the...
Habeas corpus?
I'm not an attorney yet.
I'm a volunteer assistant.
One of our attorneys will file the writ.
- He is a good boy.
- The FBI went to his school
and took him like a criminal.
This is America?
It's not easy
to be Muslim now.
They wouldn't let Afaf skate
at the local rink
- unless she removed her headscarf.
- You're kidding me, why?
They said it was
for insurance.
It might fall off
and someone could trip.
If she had been wearing a yarmulke,
it would have been a different story.
You can bet.
They're these poor,
hardworking people.
- Finn, you're not eating?
- Coffee's good.
The government is just completely
fucking this family over.
When did it start she could use that
kind of language
in this house
with immunity?
I'm telling Mom about these people
that came into the office yesterday.
Let me guess, was it a crack
whore trying to get her kids back
for the welfare money?
Actually, it was a family from
Afghanistan who fled the Taliban
and sweated out
Visa lotteries
in a refugee camp,
and hold down three jobs.
You think it's funny? The FBI
snatched their son off the street
like we're some
third-world dictatorship.
Pretty scary.
There must have
been some reason, Meadow.
- Like he's a terrorist, maybe.
- 9-11, 9-11.
Bush is using it as an excuse to erode
our Constitutional protections,
- and you're falling for it.
- Well, I voted for him.
Right, well, you don't
relate to black people clinging to logs.
You oughta chill out
about some of this.
Hey.
Let me ask you
something,
those two Arabs
with the credit cards,
Fazool and whatever his name is...
Yeah?
you think there's a chance
they could be...
I don't know, Al-Qaedas,
something like that?
You know at one point
it did cross my mind.
Yeah, and?
I don't think so.
They're gun nuts
but the smaller guy Ahmed,
when those Danish cartoons
got published,
he was very upset,
but at the protestors.
He said he hated
the cartoons
but that the rioting shit would just
bring bad attention to all Muslims.
And the other guy
Mohammed, his brother's
a government interrogator
in Lebanon
or Syria.
Plus Mohammed and his
girlfriend have a dog,
a springer spaniel.
I'm gonna get a coffee.
Vito, what the fuck
you doing?
- Tony's looking for you.
- For me?
He's been calling
for fucking days.
My goddamn phone, Jesus. Everything all
right?
You tell us.
I'm good.
Tell Tony I'll call him.
It's better you come in.
Sure.
You go ahead,
and I'll follow you.
What?
What are you doing?!
Motherfucker!
Fucking finook.
Lying piece of shit.
Better not come
around here no more.
Hey.
You speak Ital, right?
Some friends
coming over from Naples,
paying a visit to a guy
from New York.
- Who?
- The little guy in Ozone Park.
That's pretty high up.
You should provide 'em
a couple of dumb gats,
guidance on where
to find him.
How do I get
ahold of them?
Just leave your phone on.
Part two when it's done.
I hear fat Vito's been riding up
the Hershey Highway.
- Where'd you get that?
- Come on.
Somebody started a joke.
I won't mention any names.
There's no truth to it.
It's a fucking captain
you're talking about.
People went to see him.
He was down the shore with his goomar.
So it's bullshit then.
As soon as he saw 'em,
took off like a bat out of hell.
Fuck.
You didn't hear it
from me.
It could be
a mid-life thing.
Sucking a cock?
Mr. Spatafore, hey.
Marie's still at the hospital
with her mom.
- Kids asleep?
- They went to sleep about an hour ago.
Fuck!
Hi.
How are you doing?
I need a room
for the night.
I don't have anybody down
for a reservation.
The sign said "Vacancy."
Oh, we have rooms. We usually don't
get walk-ins. Come in.
Glad to have you. Slow around here until
the leaf peepers show up.
Let me show you
where we serve breakfast.
I just want to go to my room.
No problem. It's $140,
breakfast included.
- MasterCard or Visa.
- I'll pay cash.
We accept that too.
But you can take care
of it in the morning.
I'm just beat,
that's all.
My car broke down.
On a night
like this too.
You know, my stepson
runs the tow service.
You want, early morning, I can have
your rig brought to the Mobil.
Yeah?
Black Cadillac.
Route 228.
This is for you.
Have a good night.
Franklin Pierce room.
Up the stairs, first door to the right.
I was just over at the house.
Everything is gone.
- Which house are you referring to?
- The spec house.
The PVC,
the shake-roof shingles,
even that expensive
lock on the shed is missing.
That's awful, Mel.
You don't know
anything about this?
You left it there
to rot.
I don't believe this.
- With my husband on his deathbed...
- Oh, Sarah Bernhardt.
...you went over there and you picked
through the place like a vulture!
You said you'd straighten out the
permits with the building department
- and you never did.
- That is beside the point!
Carmela, what happened
to my bundt pan?
It was your fault the permits
were denied in the first place.
You're a broken record, for God's sake.
That's what you are.
Carmela, wait.
No, let her go.
I've had a lifetime of her bullshit.
Gimme a coffee.
National directory.
City and state?
Peterborough,
New Hampshire.
The number
for Angelo Di Piazza.
- Double "Z."
- No number listed, sir.
How about
Roberta Di Piazza?
Nothing for
Roberta Di Piazza.
- Huh?
- Nothing, sir.
Could you try
Roberta Spatafore?
S-p-a-t-a-f-o-r-e.
I don't have anything
for that listing, sir.
Look, I'm trying
to find my cousin.
Could you search
the whole state?
Searching.
I'm sorry, sir.
- What's good?
- First time here, try the johnnycakes.
What's that?
Pancake made with white cornmeal.
New England specialty.
Where you from?
Scottsdale.
Well, they're delicious.
Little butter, local syrup.
Okay, and gimme some
of them Jimmy Deans.
Our sausages are
made in-house.
Hey, boys, how'd you guys
make out in the storm?
We lost our lights
in the middle of "Cold Case."
We thought we were gonna have to talk
to each other or read a book.
The usual, guys?
- Are we boring?
- Yeah yeah.
Here's your johnnycakes.
I gotta warn you,
they're addictive.
They look good.
- You want more coffee?
- No, I'm coffeed out.
You don't say hello
to your uncle?
- Hi, Uncle Sil.
- Vito.
Well, he ain't
gonna show.
I'll just
leave him these.
He said he'd be back
from Vegas today. I don't know.
You and Vito,
how are things going
with you guys?
We have our ups
and downs.
And in the romance
department?
Excuse me?
What's this all about?
It's awkward.
No offense, I really don't want
to talk about this.
Vito's a good father
and a loving husband.
But his mind
is elsewhere.
He takes these
unexplained powders.
He's got a goomar.
I know all about it.
It's nothing.
Forget about it.
You hear from him,
tell him I brought him
some Blood, Sweat and Tears tickets.
Backstage passes too.
I'm telling you,
my business,
I'm around a lot of women.
That one ain't
getting laid.
- Hello.
- Vito?
- You got him?
- Who?
- Put Vito on the phone, asshole.
- Fuck you, motherfucker.
What, are you sucking his dick?
Put him on.
How about I kick
your ass, you fucking faggot?
Yeah, that's right, telephone tough-guy.
Put Vito on the phone!
There ain't no Vito, man. I found
the phone on the side of the road.
- What?
- Hang on a second.
Where'd you find the phone?
Hello.
Hello!
Oh, you motherfucker.
What happened?
Bob at the marina
where Tony docks his boat
says he'll donate
a sunset dinner cruise.
- I paid $300 for that?
- Yeah.
I got seasick in Bermuda
on one of those.
- Oh, Angie, finally.
- Sorry.
I had these sales reps
in my office.
We're just going over
the list for the silent auction.
- We're already up to about 7500 bucks.
- Oh good, Artie.
- Ladies.
- A silent auction again?
- Why not get a live auctioneer?
- I got sea bream, beautiful.
Porcini-dusted ravioli,
huh?
I hate to be a pain,
but I gotta get back.
- Can we just let him cook?
- Sure.
Great, go for it.
Where were we?
Jesus Christ.
He's always interrupting.
People enjoy
the silent auction.
I thought our goal
was to raise money.
I say we get 'em liquored up, let 'em
tear each other's throats out.
- Well...
- It's just an idea.
Anyhow, put me down for $2,000
worth of bodywork and/or paint.
2,000? Madonn', Ange.
So, did you hear about
Vito and Marie? Separated.
Oh, sorry, I gotta take this.
Hello?
They were just at the wedding.
They seemed fine.
What'd I tell you?
Is that a beautiful fish or what?
Oh, for God's sake,
all right!
Can I just get some
prosciutto melon to go?
I'm sorry, guys.
I gotta get back.
No, the quarter panel
from the LeSabre, I said.
Oh shit.
You didn't know
he was gay?
Actually I had him pegged
the whole time, but...
He a close friend?
Not only that, he's one
of my most valuable guys.
He's ambitious,
he's focused.
When I was in
the hospital,
he helped Carmela
tremendously when we were strapped.
You've implied you have
millions of dollars.
Your hospital stay
was actually that costly?
Well no, but, uh...
Huh?
Is that the issue?
You tell me.
What is the issue?
He's a fa-ag!
And?
Now what am I
supposed to do?
About what?
I know what.
They're born that way, right?
It's not their fault.
Frankly I think they
go about in pity for themselves.
I don't think they
see it as a fault.
In your circle I'm sure
you got all kinds
of gays
and trans-whatevers
of all stripes.
But not where
I come from.
You personally...
how do you feel
about homosexuality?
I find it disgusting.
Men kissing men,
holding hands in the street.
Every fuckin' TV show now,
they rub your nose in it.
Although, that...
the lesbian thing
with the, uh...
Jennifer Beals,
it's not bad.
She a dyke in real life?
I don't give
too much of a shit
what people do
behind closed doors
with the consenting
adults.
Although don't forget:
I'm a strict Catholic.
I agree with that
Senator Sanitorium,
who says if we let
this stuff go too far,
pretty soon we'll
be fucking dogs.
I hear a lot
of ambivalence.
This guy that
got outed, look,
the guys that work for me
are asking for head.
His head.
What the fuck?
You know, him and me,
we're in the construction business.
Now some of these
union old-timers, the contractors,
they're not gonna want
to be seen with him.
And I'm talking huge deals,
major fucking dollars.
A lot of your circle
must have done jail time.
They can't be strangers
to male-male sexual contact.
You get a pass for that.
Well, that's nice.
Well, what are
you gonna do?
There's no women there.
You're there
five, 10 years.
Just for the record, my incarceration
was very short term,
so I never had any need
for any anal... you know.
So this fellow who's been outed,
what's he saying?
You think I'm lying,
don't you?
About when
I was in jail.
I've given you no indication
I think you're lying.
What the fuck, I suppose
something inside me says
God bless, a' salut'.
Who gives a shit?
I mean I had a second chance.
Why shouldn't he?
Part of your new outlook?
Maybe.
I salute it, then.
Tall fuckin' order,
I'll tell you that.
How so?
You can talk about every day being
a gift and stopping to smell the roses,
but regular life's got a way
of picking away at it.
Your house,
the shit you own,
it drags you down.
Your kids,
what they want.
One bad idea
after another.
Just trying to work a cell phone menu
is enough to make you scream.
There's some cold pasta.
No, I ate already.
What's all that?
For the silent auction.
My busy little beaver.
Not really.
Look, Ton', I haven't
wanted to bug you,
but before you
got hurt,
you said you would get
that building inspector
to cut me some slack
so I could get back to my business?
Oh yeah, right right.
I will, later.
Come here.
No, uh, I'm still not
ready for that.
Last time I thought I tore something
from tensing my muscles.
No, I got something
for that scar.
Vitamin E.
My facialist said
it will help get the red out.
You were right
about my uncle, Carm.
All along.
It doesn't give me
any pleasure, believe me.
I should have cut him
out of my life.
I brought this
all on myself.
You did not.
Don't ever think that.
All this, you never once
said "I told you so."
Accentuate the positive.
I wanted you
to get better.
You know my shrink...
told me that, uh...
I stood by Junior through
all his jealousy and shit...
trying to prove
I'm a good guy...
and that my mother couldn't
hate a good boy like that.
Imagine laying
next to a guy 15 years
and all the time he's been playing for
the pink team.
Who told you?
Tony swore me to secrecy.
I'm not gonna
burn my sources.
Anyway, it's all over
the place.
Those children, imagine when they
find out their father's a finook.
God, she's such a bright girl,
Marie Spatafore.
You think she and Vito
had some arrangement?
I just hope she
gets herself tested.
Still, Vito? He'd be like the last
one you'd suspect.
Suspect of what?
Wow, such a young lady!
Yes, she's working
two jobs.
Days she's interning at Gendler,
Lookstein, Abruzzo & Abruzzo.
What about Vito?
Nothing. Him and Marie
are having some problems, that's all.
- I can probably guess.
- Excuse me?
Huh-uh, I'm not
going first.
Do you know
something?
Okay...
he is possibly...
gay.
Finn saw him giving
some guy a blowjob.
What?
When Dad got him that job
in construction?
Finn showed up early
one morning and he saw Vito
in a car going down on some
security guard.
- Oh my God!
- He saw this?
He had Finn all freaked out.
He still does.
Why didn't you
say something?
Because Vito
warned Finn not to.
You gotta hear
what Meadow just told us.
- Mom!
- The cat's out of the bag, Meadow.
Oh, it's "Dr. Yank 'em,"
the painless dentist.
How you doing, kid?
Hey Ton'.
Hey...
Unfortunately, Finn here
has got some bad news,
so, uh, listen up.
Sit down.
Go ahead.
Tell 'em
what you saw.
Don't be scared.
It's all right.
All right, if we can just
head over and have lunch.
Good morning.
Let me ask you
a question.
Before he cornered you
in the porta-potty,
when the security guard
was sucking him off...
Whoa one sec, it was
the other way around.
What?
Vito was blowing
the security guard.
Son of a bitch!
Catchin', not pitchin'?
He's not gonna know
I told you?
You ain't gonna have
no problem from Vito, believe me.
- What are you gonna do?
- It'll be okay.
Get him to pay
for some therapy.
Look, why don't you...
why don't you go out front,
get yourself a sandwich,
any kind you like, huh?
Soda.
When we're done here,
somebody will take you back.
All right.
I wanna kill
the fat faggot myself.
Be a fuckin' honor.
Cut off his pisciatil'
and feed it to him.
There can be
no mistake now.
I can't believe
I stuck up for him!
I feel like I've been
stabbed in the heart.
We can't have him here
in our social club no more.
I mean, that much
I do know.
Social club?
He's gotta go!
I wanna think about it.
Yeah, I don't know.
What the fuck?
What is there to think about?
- Sit down.
- Fuck that! I'll say it again!
What the fuck is there
to think about?
You gonna take care
of his kids, huh, after he's gone?
It's true.
They didn't do nothing.
Poor little guys.
Now sit down.
I'm sorry if I yelled, T.
It's just...
how much more
betrayal can I take?
Vito, a fag.
Big construction tycoon.
Ton', when he was always talking
about "greasing the union,"
who knew that's
what he meant?
All right, this stays
in these four walls.
Am I understood?
- Phil, oh my God.
- You poor kid.
I know. I can't
believe it myself.
I keep waiting
for him to call.
How long am I supposed
to tell the kids he's away on business?
That fuckin' shitbag.
I get my hands on him
I'm gonna tear him
limb from limb.
- Oh, Phil, don't say that.
- You're my cousin he married,
making a mockery
of the whole sacrament.
But what do we
really know?
I mean, maybe there
were signs, but...
Vito Spatafore
is a good man,
and he's
a wonderful dad.
Somebody sees something one time
and he's tossed aside like garbage?
That's why
I'm here, honey.
There's been confirmation
through the grapevine.
Vito was seen
in a car with a man.
I don't want to get
graphic beyond that,
the idea of it
repulses me so much.
What confirmation?
Who?
The witness has
no reason to lie.
No...
We can't be in denial
no more, much as we love him.
Where do you think
he might have gone, honey?
So we can get him back here,
get him to do something about it.
Excuse me, Angie here?
In the office.
We can get you anything
you want, sweetheart,
air bags,
chrome rims...
- Oh, hi.
- Carm, hi.
I'm sorry.
Am I interrupting something?
I'm here for the free
bodywork certificates for the auction.
- Oh, that's right.
- But if you're busy...
This'll just take
another sec.
Okay, sure.
They were doing something
behind closed doors.
Well you know Angie's
put money on the street.
How do you know?
- Angie told me.
- She didn't tell me.
Probably 'cause of Tony.
Aw, maybe he didn't want you
to know something like that.
Me and my big mouth.
She's got enough money
to do that, huh?
Well, she's pretty successful with that
body shop, so...
Our grandmothers did it.
Those were harder times,
but... a' salut', right?
She's one of us.
Now it's like she's one of them.
- You wanted to see me, Ton'?
- Yeah.
Hey, Carlo.
Sit down.
Putting you in charge of
all construction business,
replacing Vito.
Holy shit!
Guys respect you
across the board,
you done real good
real with the ports...
Thank you, Ton'.
Jeez, I don't know
what to say.
We'll have a drink.
Congratulations.
A' salut,
a' salut.
Listen, Ton'...
since you think enough of me
to give me this responsibility
I might as well be
the one to say it.
All right,
skip the preambles.
The guys on Vito's crew,
they say if he
was to come back,
they refuse to take
orders from him.
Oh, they do?
Not only that,
a couple of the other captains
won't talk to him,
and I don't disagree.
Paulie especially.
Now that he's
accepted it, hey...
he's the most out
for Vito's scalp.
Yeah, you should hear him, Ton'. He's
goin' fuckin' mau-mau on the subject.
It's not their fucking decision
who they work with.
Let me tell
you something...
fuckin' Vito,
through sheer hard work,
turned himself
into my best earner.
I don't even know
if I'd have the new boat without him.
He's a come-from-behind
kind of guy.
That's true, but...
So I'm gonna burn
that kind of dedication?
It's hard to believe I couldn't get
something more out of him,
if he were to come back.
Stocks, offshore shit,
I don't know.
Well...
these other guys feel
an effort should be made
to find him and put him down
for the honor of the family.
Oh, please, huh?
You know, certain people,
they love the high drama,
like fuckin' high school girls.
And others I could name,
they just can't wait to
whack somebody, anybody.
But some people feel it's against
our principles, Tony.
A sin.
Carlo, let's be honest
with ourselves here.
We all know Vito's
not the first.
Well...
we're gonna do
great things.
Aw, Jesus, thanks again, Anthony.
Thank you.
What?
It's 2006.
There's pillow biters
in the Special Forces.
Let me just
ask you, Ton'...
sake of argument.
Let's say he shows up.
You gonna kiss this guy
on both cheeks?
Take Paulie, okay?
You know perfectly well
guys like him never kick up their full
percent to you.
You look the other way,
price of doing
business.
But you cut Vito slack now
that he's "out of the closet,"
just the excuse people need
to go off the reservation
and start withholding
serious money.
Let me read
in peace, will you?
Having fun
with all this paper?
I can't believe
this is just one case.
Rafaella Martino.
I'm the lead attorney on this mess.
Meadow Soprano.
- I'm Michael Kardish. I work with Rae.
- Hi.
Ms. Soprano came
highly recommended.
Columbia Dean's List, volunteer
at the South Bronx Law Center...
This is really
interesting too.
Of course it's different than the kind
of thing we see at the law center.
Clients there are so
trampled and abused...
Welcome to
white-collar fraud.
I need the e-mails from box 44
and 45, July and August.
Pull them and leave them
with my assistant.
Okay.
Tony Soprano's kid.
Tony.
Building my
lats back up.
Did you by any chance talk to
the building inspector about my house?
Shit, I forgot.
The sorting's tedious,
but some of the cases...
this guy was
pretty clever, really.
He set up all these
phony investment firms
and then just siphoned
the money out:
- $80 million.
- Whoa.
Yeah, he's out on bail.
Then you look at
my father's friend,
federal marshals
dragging him
out of his own
daughter's wedding.
He hasn't even
been tried yet.
You're innocent in this
country until proven guilty.
Yeah, but Johnny Macaroni
was indicted for murder.
They couldn't let him
stay 15 more minutes?
You better put
your pants on.
You know why
they did that?
To humiliate him
in front of everyone.
Metal detectors,
frisking,
my father
with the shoes?
It was pure
harassment.
Yeah, but the guy's lucky
they even let him out.
Oh, so white-collar criminals
can destroy people's lives
and steal their pensions
and it's no big deal to you.
You know what?
Bad subject.
Let's talk about
something else.
No, let's talk about it
so we can stop
with the "macaroni" cracks.
Weird, since you're
part Italian yourself.
Please, my dad
is so deracinated.
Yeah, the way he prefers it.
All those hysterical jokes
about Italian cheeses
and smelly feet.
Why are you
picking a fight?
I'm not, but you're slamming my family.
I don't know.
This is good shit.
It's amazing.
You weren't there for
the "grand inquisition" about Vito.
I knew it.
I'm picking the fight.
I was in the back
of a butcher shop
with your Uncle Paulie,
ratting out a guy
I don't really even know.
I mean what do you think's
going to happen to Vito for being gay?
And don't give me any of that "poverty
of the Mezzogiorno" bullshit.
We're in fucking
Caldwell, New Jersey,
and you're on your
high horse about justice?
They are gonna
mete it out themselves.
This is untenable.
This is nice,
this pot.
Yeah, that's a Baneda,
Arts and Crafts Movement.
Yeah? I really don't know
much about this stuff.
Well, you've got
a good eye.
That's the most
expensive piece in the store.
You're a natural.