[Chanting]
Chug, chug, chug, chug!
You know, I don't really think
this rally girl thing
is for me.
If that's the way you feel,
cool.
I'm someone
who loves Texas football.
I don't know, I love the game.
I'm gonna find some
extracurricular things
for you to do after school.
Hey, guys,
I'm Derek Bishop, head T.A.
- How 'bout I buy you a coffee?
- Okay.
[Overlapping chatter]
Hurry up there.
You guys got that?
Hey, come on, listen.
Pipe down!
[Whooping]
[Rockabilly playing]
[All chanting]
[Whooping, cheering]
♪ Somebody took my picture ♪
♪ hope I didn't smile ♪
♪ told me I was gonna be here ♪
♪ goin' down for a while ♪
♪ one day, I was walking
down the street ♪
♪ when I shoulda been
walkin' down the hall ♪
♪ I heard a voice
callin' out says ♪
♪ hoo, where you goin',
y'all? ♪
[cheering]
[Music continues in background]
[Chanting]
Tink, Tink, Tink, Tink, Tink!
Tink, Tink, Tink, Tink!
[Cheering]
[Song ends]
Yeah!
Thank you, everybody.
Give it up for Gary Clark Jr.
and the Old Fat Tribe.
Give it up also
for the big victory tonight
by the East Dillon Lions!
Let's hear it!
Way to go, Lions!
I want to welcome you
all out tonight
to the grand opening
of Buddy's.
I have the game balls,
the first two victories
by the East Dillon Lions.
Each week, we're gonna
take the game ball,
put the score on it,
and we're gonna mount 'em
in the trophy case.
There will be a lot of balls
in this case
by the end of the year, folks!
I'd like to bring up
two of my dear friends,
the great coach Eric Taylor...
And his wife Tami!
Come on up!
Crowd: [Chanting]
Coach, coach, coach, coach!
We are going to let the coach
and Mrs. Taylor
install the winning balls
into the case.
[Whooping]
[Yelling, cheering]
- Hey, ma.
- Hey, baby.
What are you doing up so late?
Oh, I'm just doing
some cleaning.
You know,
that was a damn good game.
- That was a good game, babe.
- Thanks.
Defense was all over me.
They switched up to a 3-4,
and they couldn't stop me.
[Giggling] Yeah.
Place looks nice.
Thanks.
You wanna tell me what's up?
Well, um...
[Clears throat]
Your father's getting out.
He's gonna be paroled.
- He's getting out.
- Actually, I was hoping
that you'd come with me
to Huntsville to go pick him up.
W-wait...
Where's he gonna live?
I don't know, babe.
I just...
I haven't thought about that.
I just want you to go with me.
I can't do that.
I'm going to sleep.
[Door thuds shut]
Sync by honeybunny
[cheering, laughing]
That's Dallas Tinker.
Luke Cafferty.
And Vincent Howard.
Apparently, it's some type
of a rally girl initiation.
That is awful.
This thing has had 2,000 hits.
And I've had about
that many irate parents call me.
- I have got to do something.
- Like what?
Well, parents
want these boys expelled.
- Which boys?
- Football players.
- The ones they see.
- Wait a second, now.
Listen, this is
a horrible thing, I agree.
I don't like seeing
what I'm seeing one bit.
There's a lot of boys there,
and they're not all
football players.
Well, the storm that's
gonna rain down on me is gonna
be about football players,
and they're your players.
Levi, just don't go expelling
my football players yet
until I can look into this.
Oh, this is because you have
a game coming up, huh?
It's because I'd like to know
the truth behind this thing
before you start throwing
people off my team.
Okay.
But you owe me one.
[School bell rings]
I mean, 2,000 hits?
I'll talk to my players.
I'll get to the bottom of it,
find out what I can.
And you know what?
These girls have got to be
dealt with too.
- Understood.
- I mean, that cannot happen.
We didn't do any of this crap
when we were kids.
- All right, I'll see you later.
- Yeah.
If any of you have
a problem with your grade,
don't go crying
to Professor Nevins.
He didn't grade them.
I did.
And believe me, I was much
nicer than he would have been.
All right, you guys are done.
I'll see you next time.
Office hours tomorrow
if you need me.
I don't even know him.
It's been like five years.
I get it.
Like that...
That's just really weird,
you know?
Yeah, I mean,
the way he treated my mom.
The reason why she was,
you know, messed up
for as long as she was.
It's hard to come back
from something like that.
Don't even know how I feel.
Doesn't even matter.
You think, though,
maybe people change?
You changed.
Yeah. I don't know.
I ain't go to jail.
Listen to me, I am telling you.
Buddy junior
is in real trouble.
His grades are terrible,
he stays out at night
all night, and I...
Pam, stop.
Just stop yelling.
He's a teenager.
He's just going through
a phase.
He's gonna come out of it,
just like all the other kids.
This is not a phase, Buddy.
Let me tell you something else.
You know what?
I think he's smoking marijuana.
You think or you know?
I can't believe
I'm saying this.
Maybe you should come out here.
Oh, oh, you think
he needs his father
after all this time?
Yeah, I been trying to
tell you that for years.
You know what,
don't give this to me right now.
This is about our son, Buddy,
and he's in trouble.
- We are losing him.
- I know that.
Just calm down and quit
acting like a crazy woman.
Oh, acting crazy?
I don't think you understand.
I've gotta open the bar.
I've got some things to do.
Oh, you've gotta open the bar.
Yeah, you go do that.
- You open the bar.
- I'll take care of it, Pam.
How do you feel
about that video?
[Snickers]
I didn't put it
on the Internet.
That's not really
the issue, is it?
Actually, it kind of is,
'cause...
If it wasn't in the Internet,
I wouldn't be sitting here
right now
because nobody
would know about it.
Does it matter to you at all
that you know about it?
[Laughs]
You let that happen to you.
You let those boys
do that to you.
It was just a party!
We were having fun!
Didn't look to me
like you were having fun.
Looked to me like you were
passed out cold.
Have you ever been to a party?
I sure have.
I usually try to stay awake.
It's a lot more fun that way.
[Grunting]
You move your ass!
Nobody told you to slow down.
[Coaches shouting]
You move your ass!
Nobody told you to slow down.
Y'all enjoy
that party this week?
Y'all see the video?
I know everyone else
in town did.
Including that girl's parents,
including her church members,
and her classmates.
Bring 'em over here, coach.
Bring it in!
Now, now, now!
Let's go!
You know what it is, fellas?
It's just damn shameful.
That's what it is.
And it's not gonna happen
out here again.
You act like a bunch of thugs,
it reflects on all of us.
I'm not holding you
to a higher standard.
I'm holding you to our standard!
Why you keep putting
everything on us,
like we were
the only ones there?
Coach, the whole school
was at that party.
If you two don't know
the answer to that,
you're dumber than you look.
Is there anybody out here
that doesn't understand
what our standard entails?
No, sir.
Y'all look at me
right in the eye.
Anyone, and I mean anyone...
Who breaks our standard
will be off this team,
and that is a promise.
Get 'em back to it, coach.
Let's go,
back in your lines, let's go!
- Come on, let's go!
- Come on!
[Muffled conversation]
[Laughter]
You remember that, huh?
- What you got up in there?
- Got some dressing...
[Man laughing]
To put up on this...
Okay?
[Man laughing]
Like old times?
Like old times.
Hey, baby.
- Oh...
- Um...
Look at you. Ha.
Say hi to your father, babe.
What's happening, little bread?
I ain't so little no more.
Ha ha, no, you all grown up.
All right,
no more little kid names.
What's happening, Vince?
What's up, man?
Um, so listen, babe, Vince,
I got us some chicken,
like old time's sake.
What else we have?
We have some greens.
Let's just do like we...
You know, like we used to.
- I missed your cooking.
- I know that's right.
- What the hell is this?
- What?
- What's that?
- That's my suitcase, man.
You didn't tell him.
She didn't tell me
you were staying here.
Uh, baby, just...
just go wash your hands.
Baby, please.
Vince. Vince.
Let's talk about
what happens in your body
when you consume alcohol.
One or two drinks
can impair your reasoning
and emotions,
which means you can decide
to do some dumb things
like drink more.
[Girls chattering]
As more alcohol
is consumed in the body,
your vision and speech
are impaired,
as well as your reflexes
and balance.
Alcohol is a drug,
and it affects your brain,
- Your heart, your lungs...
- 'Scuse me, Ms. Rene.
Can I just interrupt you
for one second, please?
Y'all, I need to ask you
to put away the brush,
put away the cell phones,
and pay attention.
Mr. Burnwell
has brought this woman here
to give you information
that you need.
I know y'all...
at least some of you...
have seen that video.
It is sad, and it is disturbing.
I'm sure you will agree.
It's sad to see a girl
throwing up her guts.
It's disturbing to see a girl
being passed around at a party
like a rag doll.
You think that's funny?
I think that's awful.
This discussion is part of...
- Boring!
- A larger conversation...
Excuse me?
What was that?
You don't deserve to have
this conversation.
You can leave.
You need to take care
of yourselves.
'Cause one day real soon,
there is not gonna be
anybody else to do it for you.
I suggest you take
this opportunity and you listen.
- Guys, guys, guys...
- Look at me, I'm a puppet!
Look at me flappin' my arms!
Let's go.
Back in your group, let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
- [Laughing]
- Hey, hey!
What the hell are you doin'?
What the hell is that?
You not hear what I said
yesterday?
Was I not clear enough
Jacob, you ever known me
to break a promise?
Wade, you ever known me
not to keep my promise?
Grab your helmets.
Get off this field.
Now!
Get on the 50-yard-line
right now.
Call it, coach!
Two groups.
Spread out.
It's a C-minus,
and I really have no idea why.
What's wrong with it?
There's nothing wrong it.
I just feel like I've spent
a little time with you now,
and there's more
to your thoughts
than you managed
to get on the page, that's all.
Is it badly written?
Is it unclear?
It felt safe.
I think there's a very
interesting mind in there.
I just want you to feel
comfortable exercising it.
Take some chances.
So that's what college is for.
First semester.
Look, it can take a while
to get your bearings.
You will.
Okay.
Hey, Julie.
I've got an idea.
Professor Nevins
holds these weekly salons
for promising students.
I think you'd be great for it.
You interested?
Um...
Sure.
Y'all get on to
class now, okay?
Hi, Jess.
Hey, Mrs. Taylor.
Hey, I'm sorry about
all of this today.
Oh, you know...
And if it means anything,
I was listening.
Well, I'm glad.
It does mean something to me.
- Thank you, Jess.
- Okay. You're welcome.
- I tell you, these rally girls...
- Eh...
And then I can
kind of understand them.
'Cause everybody just wants
to feel a part of the team.
Hey, Jess.
- Come here.
- Yeah?
I know coach is lookin' for
an equipment manager
on the team.
Mm-hmm.
How would you like to be
equipment manager?
Really?
You serious?
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
- I'd have to ask him.
- I'd be great!
I'd be better than anyone else!
I think you would.
I'll tell him that.
Okay. And tell him, too,
I'm really good with technique,
'cause I, like, worked
with Vince over the summer.
I'm not making any promises.
I don't know.
Okay. You're...
Thank you!
[Laughs] Yeah, you're welcome.
All right.
We got everyone in here?
Boys: Yes, sir.
Go ahead,
take a knee if you want to.
I'm not so sure
there aren't a few more of you
that ought be kicked
off this team,
maybe even
kicked outta the school.
Maybe even the state of Texas!
People are watchin' us.
And it's just as important
what we do on the field
as what we do off the field.
Y'all know that.
Tell you what we're gonna do.
We're gonna have a clean slate.
There's gonna be a few rules.
No more jerseys on game days.
It's gonna be coats and ties.
[Grumbling]
And there's gonna be
a little community outreach
plan goin' on.
Is everybody all right
with that?
Boys: Yes, sir.
Y'all better say it
like you mean it.
Boys: Yes, sir!
How you doin' today, sir?
This is one of our schedules,
the East Dillon Lions.
Sir, East Dillon Lions.
Come out and support.
Hey, how you doing, ma'am?
My name's Dallas Tinker.
I play for
the East Dillon Lions.
Mind if I help you
with your groceries?
You may not recognize me.
Have you seen my face?
Number 79?
Come on, defensive lineman.
All right, you have a nice day.
Hey, dude,
how much longer
we gotta be out here?
It's hot, I'm burning up.
Can't you see I'm baking?
I can see you want bacon.
Hey, Vince, hey, bro,
they not taking
these schedules, man.
I'm fixing to bounce, bro.
I don't know why
y'all lookin' at me.
I ain't the police.
Do what you want.
- Hell, yeah, Q.B.
- Hey! Hey, let's bounce, man.
I'm outta here.
Let's go, bro.
Where y'all going?
Hey, man, I'm out.
They not supporting us
no way, man.
Why should I be here?
- Vince, say something.
- What you want me to say?
I don't know, "come back
and pass out the damn flyers"?
Luke, look around you.
Go home.
It's done.
- No, Vince...
- Vince...
- Everybody's gone.
- Vince!
I don't wanna push
no tractor tires!
Team left, so why don't we
be with the team. Go home!
I'm dreaming about tires
in my damn sleep, come on!
I mean, Eric,
he's barely 15 years old,
and he's turnin' into
a pothead.
Ha.
Course,
it shouldn't surprise me.
He's out there with that Kevin,
that hippie, Kevin.
He's probably the one
givin' it to him.
I knew this was gonna happen.
And Pam,
she calls every 15 minutes
with some new disaster.
I am 1,500 miles away.
It's 1,500 miles away.
What can I do 1,500 miles away?
What am I gonna say?
What am I gonna do?
She's the one
that wanted the divorce.
She's the one that wanted
to raise the kids,
to give 'em a great life
'cause I was such a...
And you know as well as anybody
- that it tore my heart out.
- I know, I know.
And I wanted those children.
And now here it is.
What am I supposed to do?
The going gets tough...
And Pam, she just gets to punt,
just send Buddy junior...
You know what, Buddy,
maybe it's not about you,
and maybe it's not about Pam
as much as it is about your son
who happens to need you.
Nobody said being a dad's
gonna be easy.
Hell, we're both fathers.
Both know that.
Maybe you should look at it
as an opportunity.
I'm just sayin'.
[Soft rock in background]
♪ ♪
Don't you need
an equipment manager?
Billy is the equipment
manager, sweetheart.
Well, I'm sure Billy
could use some help.
Everybody could always use
a couple extra hands.
- No.
- Well, I just think
it might be nice to give this
girl an opportunity, you know?
It's something
that she really wants,
and we keep talking to these
kids about self-esteem
and all that... Let's put our
money where our mouths are,
you know, make some changes.
We gotta get this school
out of the '50s,
for heaven's sakes.
Honey, we're talking about
my quarterback,
who's a boy.
His girlfriend
happens to be a girl.
I don't need 'em both in the
locker room at the same time.
That's a bad idea.
You don't know that.
You just don't know.
No, I do know,
girls in locker rooms
are bad ideas.
I just think it's
something to think about.
Tell daddy to think about it.
- Don't you dare.
- Think about it, daddy!
It's not like
I'm getting my hopes up,
but Mrs. Taylor did say
she'd talk to him.
Ten seconds.
That was good.
So what would you be doing?
She said he needs, like,
an equipment manager.
You know,
start somewhere like that.
What?
Nothing. I mean,
I'm happy for you, just...
Just got a lot on my mind
right now.
Did you talk to your dad?
Yep.
How'd it go?
[Lively dinner music plays]
[Overlapping chatter]
You know,
"Caesar was everyone...
every woman's man..."
"And every man's woman."
Yes, you've used that quote
five times in the past week,
every time we go out.
Well, no wonder
you stole my line.
I did not steal your line.
Unless you are the 17th century
Earl of Oxford.
Oh, de vere?
Oh, please.
He is such a poser.
13th folio?
Maybe in his dreams.
[Overlapping chatter,
dinner music]
Anyway, I just adore Alison.
I hear she's doing
such wonderful work
on her sabbatical in Boston.
- Yes, she is.
- You must be so proud
so have such a distinguished
wife, yeah?
There's Professor Nevins.
I'm gonna tell him about...
[Voice fades]
[Overlapping chatter]
You're gonna want to get
real familiar with bleach,
'cause that's the one thing
that's gonna keep these
- staph infections from going...
- Hey, Foxy Brown.
Keep it in your pants, Tinker!
There's staph infections
in here?
Yeah. It's a locker room.
Okay. All right.
Hey, everybody listen up!
This is Jess...
Merriweather.
Jess Merriweather, all right?
She's the new equipment
manager with us.
I expect y'all to treat her
with the same respect
that you do me, all right?
What's that?
Hey, you mean none?
[Laughter]
Shut your face, Moreno!
You're good.
Thanks.
So this is you
on the team, Laundry?
Well, yeah, because
I'm the equipment manager.
This is the equipment
that I manage.
Thanks!
Hey, focus, focus.
This isn't gonna work.
I just... I just don't...
I don't see this...
I get to wear
a uniform and hats
and, like, stuff like y'all...
Isn't that cool?
Mm-hmm. You can't wait
till everybody leaves?
Can you take those off too
so I can get your uniform
going, baby?
But I'm gonna start on this,
because I gotta lot of stuff...
I don't know about this, Jess.
Okay, mwah, babe.
I'll see you later.
Later, babe.
[Kissing sounds]
[Girl giggling]
Excuse me.
Oh, God!
[Laughing]
- Good lord.
- Oh, man!
[Laughing]
Fancy meeting you here.
Hi!
[Laughing]
Let me just give you
a little perspective
about something.
You were in a supply closet.
That's where they keep mops
and brooms
and computer paper and...
There's some rats in there.
Isn't that romantic?
This is gonna get around
now, too.
And before you know it,
you're gonna have yourself
quite a reputation.
Is that what you want?
'Cause I happen to know
you're smart
and I can see
that you're beautiful,
and this is a time right now
for you to choose
what your future is.
And it's not just gonna be
people around this school
talking
and your friends talking.
It's gonna be parents talking.
It's gonna be college
admissions officers talking.
So really think about
what you want, all right?
- What's happening?
- Where'd you get the car?
Friend of mine.
Gotta get it back
by midnight, you know.
'Fore it turn into
a paddy wagon.
[Chuckling]
I must have
just missed you earlier.
You know, I went down
to get some tickets
for your game on Friday.
- You went to my school?
- Yeah, man.
Don't be going down there
lookin' for me.
Hey, hey, come on, now.
Your mama said you were
like superman out there.
I want to see you play, son.
I'll be a'ight.
Hey, hey, come on.
Hop in, hop in.
We'll go get your mama at work,
we'll get something to eat,
some ray's barbecue.
Come on, man.
Y'all go ahead and enjoy that.
Come on, son.
You gotta eat, right?
I'll be a'ight.
You know,
I'm in this position where
everyone thinks
that I'm married,
but I don't feel like I am.
Is that why you don't
wear a wedding ring?
I'm sorry.
You know what?
This is none of my business.
- This is none of my business.
- No, you know what, it's okay.
It's kind of liberating
to talk about it,
to hear it out loud.
You know what,
we have some issues.
Everyone in my life thinks
that we're happily married
and that everything's great,
but she's been gone
for six months on sabbatical,
and how are we supposed
to work on our issues
if we're not even together?
I probably shouldn't
have said any of that.
I've had too much to drink.
It's okay.
I promise that
I will not tell a soul.
You're an awesome girl,
Julie Taylor.
In a different world,
different time...
Suffice it to say,
I feel very comfortable
around you.
I hope it's okay
that I said that.
Yeah, it's...
It's flattering.
[Laughs]
Good.
Okay.
Good night
to you.
Good night.
I'm gonna try that again
and see if I can get
my legs to work.
[Giggles]
It's been a lovely evening.
You know what you said about...
Taking chances?
Yeah.
The short part of your tie's
a little long, man.
You learn about ties
in the joint?
Uh-huh. You must have
took a tie class.
That's where your ass been
the last few years. Ha.
Don't worry about
where I learned it.
I learned it.
- I don't care.
- That's enough, Vince.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
Come on.
Say what you need to say.
You don't get it, do you?
We been doing just fine
without you.
And you come in here
and you expect us
to act like everything's cool,
but it's not.
You ain't been here for us.
And if I had anything
to say about it,
your ass wouldn't even
be in this house.
Hold up.
You gonna drop bombs?
- Oh!
- I got this.
You gonna drop bombs
and run like a little kid?
Your house?
You want to talk like a man,
we can do that.
A man don't leave his family.
Is that talkin' like a man?
And don't come
to my game tonight.
Vince, wait.
Wait!
Give him a chance.
Okay, we give it a chance.
Then what?
He starts robbing.
He starts stealing.
He'll end up
right back in prison.
Okay, then do it for me.
Give him a chance for me.
Okay?
Let's be a family.
Baby...
[Whooping, clapping]
[Clapping, shouting]
[Overlapping comments]
[Players chanting]
East side, East side.
East side!
Coach is lookin' for you.
- For what?
- I don't know.
Didn't say.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
What's up?
You left the grocery store
early. Why?
Why not?
Go ahead, say it.
Say what's on your mind.
Well, first of all,
you didn't ask me
how I felt
about Jess bein' on the team.
Being in the locker room.
I don't run personnel
decisions by you.
And all these new rules.
They're stupid.
This shirt, this tie,
and whatever high standards
you're lookin' for,
this ain't it.
Close that door.
When I first met you,
you were climbing out of
a police car.
People said you were a punk
and you'd never last
on the field.
You know
they still believe that?
Screw them.
I work hard
for everything I've done.
I know you do, and you
oughta be damn proud about that.
I am.
I'm proud of you.
Your teammates are proud of you.
It's about character.
It's about striving to be better
than everybody else.
Coach, my dad
just got out of prison.
He's staying with me
at my house.
And I can't stand him.
My mom,
she asked me to forgive him.
To be better.
And you're asking me
to be better.
I don't know how to be better
'cause he never taught me how!
He never taught me
how to be better!
- He's not around!
- Hey, coach, we're going out.
- Ten minutes.
- Fine, coach.
- I'm supposed to be better!
- Close that door.
Listen to me.
I've said you need to strive
to be better
than everyone else.
I didn't say
you needed to be better
than everyone else.
But you gotta try.
And that's what character is.
It's in the trying.
I'm gonna give you a few minutes
to gather yourself up here.
47 tiger x tracer fade.
Hastings beat it.
I'm gonna hit you
on the second window.
It's coming in hot.
Be ready.
Let's do this, a'ight?
On one. Ready?
All: Break.
Late in the fourth quarter,
the Lions down by a touchdown.
But they are still
in this game, folks.
Howard to the line, looking
to get something started.
Vince Howard
is taking no prisoners
and finding Hastings
for another Lions first down.
- Hike!
- Howard takes the snap.
Looking for a receiver.
Oh, he's gonna
keep it on a scramble.
- Take him out!
- Right there!
Breaks the tackle.
Gain of 12, and the Lions
are knockin' on the door.
Howard drops.
He throws.
He's got Russell.
Touchdown!
An unbelievable pass!
It's the Vince Howard show,
ladies and gentlemen.
With a minute and a half to go,
the Lions
have tied this ball game.
Defense!
[Chanting]
Defense! Defense!
Comin' down to it, folks.
Dillon needs a stop.
There's the snap.
Dragons are back.
Cafferty's got a lane.
Big lick... boom!
Ball is out.
Fumble!
Yeah!
The ball is loose.
I don't know who's on it.
Looks like Tinker fell on it.
[Blows whistle]
It's official, folks.
Lion's ball!
Under a minute to go, folks,
and there is life!
There is life in East Dillon.
Okay, watch him, watch him.
Let's go, guys.
Ready!
Set!
Hut!
Howard in the pocket.
He's got 88, Ruckle,
open over the middle.
Complete.
That is in bounds.
Time's still winding.
The Lions are gonna
have to hurry.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Here we go, on the 20.
40 seconds left,
and Vince Howard has been
carrying this team
on his shoulders all night.
He's got one last shot.
Let's go!
Pick it up!
Ready. Set.
Hut!
Pick it up!
Touchdown, Lions!
Lions win!
Vince "get the hell
outta my way" Howard
has lit up this field tonight.
What a show by this young man.
The Lions are 3 and 0.
What do you know?
They call that
the Tinker shuffle.
Gets 'em a flag
for excessive celebration,
but you can't really
blame these kids.
Another big night.
Another big win
for these East Dillon Lions.
Hey.
That was a hell of an effort.
Hell of an effort.
I ain't got nothing left,
coach.
That's character, Vince.
3 and 0!
3 and 0, man!
We got it!
Let's go!
[Cheering]
East side, baby!
East side!
Give it up.
You see it?
There it is.
[All chanting]
3 and 0, East side!
3 and 0, East side.
[Telephone rings]
- Hello?
- Pam.
Yeah.
This is what I've decided.
Send Buddy junior
home to Dillon.
He needs his father.
Are you sure?
I've never been more sure
of anything in my life.
Send my son home, Pam.
Thank you.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah. Feelin' good.
I'm really sorry.
There's nothing
to be sorry about.
No, no, there is.
I mean, I shouldn't
have let that happen.
I'm a teacher.
You're a student.
It wasn't a good idea.
Right. No, I-I-I
totally agree with you.
So we're good then.
Yeah.
Okay.
See you in class.
I went to your game.
I know you didn't want me to.
But I did.
Look here.
I-I want you to know, um...
I know how much
of your life I missed.
I really...
I did some bad stuff.
And I was gone.
Time I'll never get back.
Look at you.
You only 17 years old.
And you already better
than I ever was.
And you were right.
It's your house now.
And you the man here.
I didn't ask
if I could stay here.
That was wrong.
Sorry.
[Chuckles] Tonight...
For the first time
in my life...
I knew what pride felt like.
Ha. I mean, boy, you...
That was crazy out there.
[Laughs]
You... you the man for real.
Leaping over players
in a single bound, boy.
[Chuckling]
I'm proud of you, Vincent.
[Door opens and closes]
Hey, so, uh,
so where you gonna be?
I'll be around.
Sync by honeybunny