- Where do you keep these things? Bank?
- We have our own treasury.
- Wine cellar.
- And a tunnel under the river.
My guess is they've turned one
of the cellars into a strong room.
Did you find someone, Arthur?
Stefan Radischevky.
- And he speaks Russian?
- Yeah.
He works in the house for four
weeks, keeps his ears open.
All right?
I have a bright future too...
mapped out.
But you want to try things first?
Michael...
why does a pen pusher who
sits on his arse all day
want to fire a gun?
There's going to be a vacancy
at Shelby Company Limited.
No revolvers, all legal.
Get me a meeting with someone
from the Soviet embassy...
♪ Look up here, I'm in heaven
♪ I've got scars that can't be seen
♪ I've got drama, can't be stolen
♪ Everybody knows me now. ♪
He was in the war.
He was in a tunnel collapse.
He won medals.
Take care of him.
♪ Look up here, man, I'm in danger
♪ I've got nothing left to lose
♪ I'm so high it makes my brain whirl
♪ Dropped my cellphone down below
Here he is, Mr Shelby.
Thank you, nurse.
Tommy...
I need to speak to you about the priest.
I know things about him.
Hmmm.
From when I was a...
from when I was a boy.
I will shoot him myself, Tommy.
Just teach me how to shoot.
It's easy, Michael.
Just point... pull the trigger.
He asked for me today, Mary...
.. not his mother...
.. for the first time.
He missed you.
Where is he? Is he in the kitchen?
Yes, he's with the girls and Johnny.
Did you remember your medicine, sir?
Do you ever read the Bible, Mary?
Sometimes.
Do you ever read it out loud while
standing naked, next to my bed?
Cos... when I take the morphine the
doctor gave me, that's what you do.
I'm wide awake but you are
standing there naked, plain as day,
reading from the Book Of Leviticus.
Do you want to know what happens next?
No... neither do I.
That's why I pour the medicine away.
Go and get Johnny, Mary.
Without the firing pins,
the guns won't work.
And there are no replacements?
They don't make these anymore,
these are the end of the line.
We had the foreman take
out all the spares.
Take the pins, they'll never fire a shot.
Nobody will know until they unload
the bloody things in Tbilisi.
Or until they are facing
our guns at Kutaisi.
Take them all out and give them to me.
Come on, boys, no fucking about.
I will tell the Soviet
Ambassador that there is no longer
a need to blow up the train.
I will tell Tommy, you accept his plan.
You know, some mornings I
wake up, I think I've died
and this is heaven, Tom.
I mean, the wives and the
kids camped out by the valley,
not being moved on.
Sure, me, meself, I'm surrounded
by maids and food and booze.
See that line, there?
No.
That's the edge of heaven.
The border between
Birmingham and paradise.
And today, my friend, you're
going to step over that line,
back into the world.
You mean you have something
for me to do, Tom?
Have you ever heard of
Hampton Court Palace, Johnny?
No. I can't say I have.
You and three families of the
Lees are going to set up camp
100 yards from the gates of the palace.
You won't be moved on because
I have just bought the land.
You'll be joined by
some old friends of mine
who are going to open a hole
underneath your tents and caravans.
You see this blow to the
head you took, Tom...
And for allowing the hole to
be dug, you will get £5,000.
Which you will split between
the three Lee families.
I take a lot of this money is to
do with not asking questions, Tommy?
Dead right, Johnny.
And when the hole is filled in
again, you can go back to paradise.
Mr Shelby, your brothers are here.
And there's someone who described
himself as, "the wandering Jew".
Will you take the Jewish
gentleman to the drawing room
and take my brothers to the
kitchen and give them tea and rum?
Yes, sir.
Good morning, Mr Solomons.
Yeah, it is.
Nice little place you've got here, Thomas.
What is it?
A foreclosure of a gambling debt
from some poor young lord who
you pumped full of opium
in one of your casinos?
Or is that just tittle-tattle?
No. Drink?
Nah, I don't touch it, mate.
Your housekeeper said you're
not allowed to drink. Eh?
She said, you are suffering
from so many ancient injuries
from your sporting life
that your head is like some
sort of smashed vase what's been
stuck back together by an horse.
Now... word in London
is that you can be found
wandering the streets of Birmingham,
stark naked, throwing away money.
You talk to dead people.
Also, that you believe that you
are powerful enough to summon up
Jews of a very particular standing
up to the gentile wilderness
wherein you live in order for them
to do your fucking bidding, mate.
And still, you came.
Yeah, well, you know...
I was passing, weren't I?
Do you know something, Alfie?
This morning, I tried to read the
paper and I realised that the
only consequence of my terrible
accident is that I now need glasses.
Right...
Right, well, I know a man...
.. who can make you a pair of these,
he is a magician, mate.
He is a magician.
So, not only will you be
able to read your newspaper,
but you will also be able
to see into the future.
Now, I know this, right, because
he made this pair, here, for me.
So, you don't have to
worry about telling me
what this is all about, do you?
Because I have already seen it.
You're fucking about with
Russians, in't you? You silly boy.
Right, you've got two choices, Michael.
You fuck off to America with
Arthur, join the Apaches,
or you marry the girl.
This isn't a joke.
Arthur, are you really going
to live with the Apaches?
- Told her father yet?
- No.
He'll fucking shoot you, man.
Are you sure the kid's yours?
I wish I hadn't told you.
Then think of marriage
as a beautiful road...
flowers all the way down it.
Is he joking?
It's hard to tell these days.
Do you, er...
Do you love the woman?
Fucking what?
Go and marry her, like the rest of us.
She doesn't want her family to know.
She doesn't want to have the baby.
- We know a woman...
- Shut up, John.
Same woman who helped you out twice.
They weren't my women.
That's why you had them fixed, Arthur.
Charlotte will want the best.
- She is the best.
- The best.
Used to be a nurse.
20 minutes, done.
Don't have to go in, or wait outside.
You go to the Garrison,
drink whisky, have a laugh.
Remember, John?
Then this kid walks in, no shoes
on, and says, "It's done".
Second time we was in there...
same kid, this time he's
wearing shiny new shoes.
And he shouts, "It's done, Arthur."
And what?
She bought new shoes...
.. with the money I gave her.
It was for a good cause.
Arthur... If you're going to get
on like this with the Apaches,
they'd fucking scalp you, boy.
Tommy said when that bell rings
we've to all go to the big room.
Come on. Tommy has a plan.
Arthur.
Arthur, come here.
Shalom!
Arthur, shalom!
Alfie.
Shalom. Come here. Come on, listen...
I owe you a little something, don't I?
I do. Come on. Sit down.
Come on, sit down here.
There you go.
Right...
Listen...
Arthur...
I want you to know, right?
That whatever happened between us, yeah?
Back then... that was business.
It was just business. All right?
And I also want you to know
that I have made my apologies
via my own God for abusing a very
holy day to get you clinked up
and battered, which I did.
And now, I would also like to extend
my personal apologies unto you.
All right?
I hear that you have allowed
Jesus to come into your life.
You heard, then?
Yeah, that's beautiful. That's wonderful.
Now, that's lovely, isn't
it? That's... that's lovely.
But I was wondering, how
does that work for you on a
day-to-day, considering
your line of work, mate?
Your apology's accepted.
Cos I hear you're a right
fucking nuisance with it.
Hello...
You see, all I'm saying is that
every man, he craves certainty.
Don't he? He craves the certainty,
even if that certainty of yours, right...?
Well, I mean... it's fucking
fanciful, mate, in't it?
Eh?
I'm Old Testament.
Fucking hell. Look at that. Now, that...
.. that scares me more. Yeah.
Congratulations, Tommy.
You now have the finished
article right there, don't you?
See, that man, right, he
will murder and maim for you
with God on his side.
Yeah.
You don't want to let him go.
If we're going to do business with
this fucker, I demand to know why.
Right...
While I was in the hospital,
I formulated a plan
and this is how it's going to work...
So, the Russians cannot
be trusted to pay us.
we are going to take what is ours.
We need to see what's in their treasury.
And that's why we need Mr Solomons.
Right boys, just remember
they are fucking insane...
and dangerous.
And drunk on stuff we've never heard of.
And they're worse than
us for spirits and ghosts.
And today, they're going to test us.
Fuck them.
The Russians all turned and ran.
The Cossacks didn't run, Arthur.
Mr Shelby, welcome.
How is my car?
I think I'm in love with it.
And I, yours. So, we should
keep what we love, yes?
Excuse the reception.
Whenever we open the treasury,
the Cossacks are on guard.
'In Russia,
'men on the other side of the law
decorate their body in tattoos.'
- Right.
Now, some of these tattoos are
proof of allegiance to underground
organisations, which are the sworn
enemies of the Royal household.
So, it's customary in Russian
Royal households to check for such
tattoos before engaging a man in business.
And as we approach the
allotted day, these ladies here
would like to make sure that you're
not assassins or infiltrators...
No, we're all good.
So, they'd like to check your skin.
They want to check our skin?
Yeah. Now my body's already been checked.
Although, at the time, I
wasn't sure that was the reason.
And now it's your turn.
Come on, boys.
Take your clothes off.
Fuck off.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Obey.
That's it...
Obey, Arthur.
No, I won't be obeying nobody.
Get out of my way, I'm leaving.
Arthur, come here...
Come on, Arthur.
Shut up, John.
I will have a maid gather the
buttons and sew them back on.
Right. Fuck it.
There you go, ladies.
Made in fucking Birmingham.
All right, I think we've seen enough, eh?
Tatiana...
Your face, Arthur, is a fucking picture.
Sometimes assassins hide their
allegiances behind their balls.
You pass the test, soldier,
with flying colours.
You see...
He wants to be a good man.
But there now.
There.
Inside every man, there is a devil.
The real diamonds, eh?
It is traditional to seal the
successful examination with
vodka and music.
Holy fuck, Tommo, what was that?
Well done, boys. Eh?
Well done, Arthur.
Now you know what you
have to do next. All right?
One last job.
Make contact and play nice.
Five minutes.
I brought Michael because as chief
accountant, he has to be witness.
Ada, can I... can I use your phone?
Michael, business first.
Michael, stop looking at your watch.
Ada, whilst you're reading this,
can I go and use your phone?
Who's the lucky girl, Michael?
Her name is Charlotte and
Michael cannot breathe
if he does not talk to
her every two hours!
Ada, please...
Phone's in the hall.
Dial nought for the line.
Thank you.
And keep it quick, I pay the bill.
I will.
Not for long!
Think about it, Pol,
together we can take control.
With two of us in the company,
we can straighten things out.
What about the politics?
You and me fighting together
and winning, that is politics.
That's a new kind of politics.
It's just this way, I get paid
and Karl gets a nice Christmas.
Good. Welcome to the Bourgeoisie.
My name is Smith.
My girlfriend is... is pregnant.
And, er... we'd like you to help us.
We need to fix a date.
Welcome to Shelby Company Limited.
Shelby Company Limited.
Limited and unarmed.
Michael, would you like to welcome
Ada, our new Head of Property
and Acquisitions.
Congratulations. Where do I sign?
Ada, have you got... um... whisky?
Yeah, Tommy.
I've already told him.
He's becoming too like his cousin.
I thought that was the idea.
Yeah, Tommy but with a bit
more fucking charm and class.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that'll help(!)
Yep. Where am I sleeping, Ada?
- Michael...
- In the room next to Karl's.
- Good night!
Oh. Heartbroken, poor love.
So how shall we celebrate?
Well, with Michael in
bed, I thought I might...
.. go for a little drive.
A drive? Where are you going to drive?
Polly?
Things have begun to develop with
the man who's painting my portrait.
Polly?
It's when you stand there in the dress...
.. you just find yourself talking
about every little thing.
- And have you...?
- No.
Not yet.
But he called me two nights ago to
say the portrait was finished and
I said I'd go there in the morning
but he said, no, he
wanted me there tonight.
Ada, you don't breathe a fucking
word of this to the boys.
- OK, but is he nice to you?
- No. No. I mean it, Ada.
Is he rich?
His friends write the papers, Ada.
Tommy would try and close him down.
So go.
He's like a tiny bird pecking at you...
.. and I think he's given up on me.
So bloody go.
Why should the boys have all the fun?
♪ Baby did a bad, bad thing
♪ I feel like crying
♪ I feel like dying... ♪
More vodka.
♪ Baby did a bad, bad thing. ♪
Don't move.
Wait there.
You're doing good, Stefan.
- It's a fucking mad house.
- Yeah, I know.
The Prince wants me to suck his cock.
And how much would you need to say yes?
That's on top of the day
rate for the arse slaps.
When am I out of here?
Soon.
What you got?
The strong room's not
guarded at night, but
they said they would kill the three
brothers in the "uglya dvor" --
coal yard.
The Duke was talking about
using a sword but the woman,
she was talking about using machine guns.
It's a fucking mad house, John.
We're doing up your pub in Nechells.
It looks a treat.
Keep your fucking head up, Peaky boy, eh?
Fucking mad house, man.
We are almost there. This way.
This treasury was built
200 years ago to protect
the King's jewels in
case of French invasion.
We are now underneath the River Thames...
Your jeweller.
I don't think they trust me, Tommy.
Mr Solomons is the only
jeweller I trust in London.
Yes, trust. Yes. Might have to
add that on the old invoice.
Thank you. Thank you.
As we agreed, your jeweller
will now select items
to a total value of £70,000.
When you have selected your chosen items,
they will be put into a box and stored.
When you have fulfilled
your part of the deal,
the box will be delivered to you.
May I just start, right, by saying
that I may choose to stay here
and just starve to death
and choke on sapphires
rather than ever go back
to the fucking world again?
Yeah, well, there is a good reason
for that, you know, little man.
Because my shop, right, is just
above a rum house, so all the...
- You speak Russian?
- I do, yeah. I do.
Cos of me mum. Yeah, my mother.
You people, all right,
you hunted my mum...
with dogs...
through the snow.
Yeah.
But today, right, is for
forgiveness, ain't it?
For selection.
So, now...
Hello...
Right. I think it's
fair to say, yeah, 1,500.
1,500?
All right, I'll give you 1,800.
I know the current market value. 18 it is.
That's very gracious of you.
Right, then. How about
say we look at this.
This is a nice little bit
going on there, isn't it?
Oh, but that was a gift
from Tsar Nicholas.
I ain't asking you, though,
am I? I ain't asking you.
All right. I come here to do business,
offer my professional services.
If you keep interrupting me,
I won't be able to focus and
do my job, you understand?
Mr Romanov, let me remind
you, we were told to come here
and choose what we like...
and now we have chosen.
Tsar Nicholas give you
that? I'll give you four.
Five... with the royal provenance.
Done.
Right, Rumplestiltskin, let's go over here
and have a look what's in these boxes.
Two. That's much nicer. Ten.
That there is definitely a five.
Are you keeping score?
- Yes, I am.
- Another five.
- Seven. - Six. - Let's call it six, eh?
- Beauty. Look at that.
- Beautiful, isn't it?
- That is splendid. - Splendid,
yes. - Beautiful, is it not? - It is.
- It's a work of art. You recognise
this work, do you? - Immediately.
I'm guessing, right, that all the
bad ideas around here, they're you.
They are you, aren't they? Hmm?
What do you mean?
Yeah. Tommy, see this, right?
It's got paste in it. That's paste.
Let me tell you something, son.
Somebody comes into my shop
with some paste like this,
usually what I make them do, right,
is fucking swallow it.
Eh? What game are you playing?
- Eh?
- Mr Solomons...
- .. shall we, er... shall
we clean it up? - Be careful.
Eh?
Mm?
Yeah. Yeah.
Right, what we got?
37,600.
Well...
Do you have any eggs?
I am simply asking...
Faberge is not part of the deal.
We would not offer you Faberge eggs.
Mr Romanov, my jeweller here,
he advises me to insist...
on Faberge.
It's a deal-breaker, Tommy.
Oh...
I brought that from Crimea myself.
Fucking hell.
With the provenance of that being
laid by such a delicate beauty...
.. that does indeed bring the
entire selection to £70,000.
- Good man. - And now, Mr Shelby,
you will join your brothers and
Mr Solomons will take his leave.
I demand absolute honesty.
- Oh, sorry. Can I...?
- I insist.
There.
A woman of style and substance.
I'm a student of silence. Is
this good silence or bad silence?
It's good.
- It's very good.
- No. It's still wet.
I know it isn't saying much in
the grand scheme of things but
this is the best work I've ever done.
I'll miss Sundays.
There will be more Sundays.
Sorry.
Sorry, can you not do that, please?
Can you just not do that, please?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry.
- It's all right. - I'm sorry. - It's
all right. No, honestly, it's all right.
Vodka!
I sewed your buttons back on.
I wanted to see if I did a good job.
Yeah, you did.
You did a good job.
Sir?
No.
I didn't.
My aunt only employs the best whores.
How did you feel when I held him?
You were jealous.
You wanted to kill me.
Or him.
No?
Why do you play games with people...
.. when there is no benefit to you?
In Russia, because we were bored.
In England, because...
.. we don't know how to stop.
At least there are silly
games and orgasms.
So let's fuck.
Here?
No.
No, in a darker place.
You still love her, don't you?
You want her?
Why would you fucking say that?
Why would you fucking say it?
- Just tell me. You love her.
- What are you fucking saying?
You want her? You want her.
Who the fuck are you? Eh?
Hm?
What are you fucking saying?
You want her...
.. tonight?
Watch...
In the palace in Tbilisi,
there was a priest...
and he would put his hands here.
And with that strangulation
there was also ecstasy.
It's called Khlysty, a Siberian prayer.
You are almost hung over.
You are almost dead, but in that moment...
Women who had lost men
in the war would lay down
and they would fuck...
the ghost.
You want her.
You want her, don't you?
♪ If you are the dealer
let me out of the game
♪ If you are the healer
I'm broken and lame
♪ If thine is the glory
mine must be the shame
♪ You want it darker
♪ Kill the flame. ♪
Now you should drink this.
It's holy water.
Keep that fucking away from me.
There.
I opened up another treasury for you.
You should call this painting...
.. Fuck Them All.
I will.
The parish...
.. the King...
.. the copper.
Yeah, the copper in particular.
Do you want to hear the
wildest story of them all?
Yes.
I killed a policeman...
in cold blood...
- .. with a gun.
- Really?
She did it.
♪ There's a monkey on my back
♪ Makes me talk like that
♪ Makes me act like that
♪ There's a monkey on my back
♪ Makes me talk like that. ♪
I tell you what...
I tell you what, I swear at one point...
at one point I looked down,
I got the top of her head,
and I thought she was going to
pull me cock off in her hand
and fucking throw it out of the window.
Oh...
She sucked me dry, I swear to God.
Like fucking spud water at the end.
We've had worse nights.
You're quiet, Arthur, eh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Fuck off.
How was your night, brother?
- You got all your buttons back, eh?
- Yeah, all right. Fuck off.
Yeah, what's God going to
say about it, Arthur, eh?
Fuck off, both of ya.
He tells Linda everything.
Every single thing.
Yeah, well, we'll see.
We're going to miss you
when you're gone now, Arthur.
Just drive the fucking car.
Private Letso reporting
for duty, Sergeant Major.
At ease, Private.
Good to see you.
Seven left...
out of 50.
Should I get them tea?
Get 'em beer, Curly.
They used to run on it
like cars on petrol.
Give them the Black Country stuff.
It's in a barrel with the tack.
They're going to fucking clean me out.
Whatever they take, they'll
put back. They're good men.
John, Arthur.
You remember these boys?
Well, if it ain't the Tipton
fucking Clay-Kickers, eh?
- Clay-Kickers.
- Come here, you.
This is William Letso, from the
South African Native Labour Corps.
Sent to Flanders from the
Bloemfontein diamond mines.
The best tunneller I ever met.
So there's three cellars
underneath the house.
Wine, kitchen, septic.
There's a tunnel here that
runs from the house underneath
the river to an underground strong room.
Now this used to be the Palace treasury.
The tunnel runs directly west and
it's separated from the house
by three iron doors
with locks we can't open.
We need our tunnel to run from here
and hit the strong room direct.
Primrose Hill, 23. Ada Thorne.
Ada?
Is Michael still there?
Right, would you tell him
that I've taken the car?
He can take the train.
Try and find out why he's
been so bloody sour lately.
Shouldn't go looking through
other people's private things.
He's my son.
The bullet was mine. I never
got a chance to fire it.
And the gypsy rules say
it must be passed on.
It's not about rules, Pol.
It's about he asked me.
It's about he told me
why he wanted to do it.
Now, if I tell you,
I can't take the knowledge back.
Better off without it.
So this is when he was with the parish.
Better off without it, Pol.
This is when he was with the Fathers...
This is when he was in the
care of the Holy Fathers.
Michael wants it so you don't know.
- That priest...
who was there...
when he was taken in...
and who is still walking
the fucking earth.
Fuck.
He asked me, Pol...
and I said yes.
And I said,
"You put a bullet in
that fucker's brains...
".. by order of the Peaky Blinders."
No.
Not my son.
He'll still be as dead if Arthur does it.
And part of him will always stay dead.
I swear to God...
In whose house it took place.
.. if my son pulls the trigger...
.. I will bring this whole fucking
organisation down around your ears.
♪ On a gathering storm
comes a tall, handsome man
♪ In a dusty, black coat
with a red right hand. ♪