Ho! Ho! Ho!
Happy birthd...!
_
Mm.
D'oh!
- Sync and corrections by ByDem -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪ Pickin' up trash ♪
♪ Put it in the bag ♪
♪ Kentucky chicken bucket ♪
♪ Makin' four cents an hour
and free cigarettes ♪
♪ Oh, yeah! ♪
You have done a beautiful job, ladies.
I think we're ready to move on.
Homer!
I'm awake! I'm awake! What?
Oh, I wish you hadn't done that.
Someone adopted this highway.
Not so loud.
The highway doesn't know it's adopted.
But we love it just the same.
Well, at least you rented
an SUV for this trip.
Now I don't have to clean up the mess.
I'm starting to get carsick.
Quick, stick your head out the window!
No, no, no, no, it's a rental.
Aim inside and blast away.
Anyone want a caramel apple?
- It's a rental.
- No, thanks.
Shave the dog?
It's a rental.
Thank you, no.
_
Get me candy.
What's so funny?
Ha! You checked this out
with half a tank,
but now it's three-quarters full.
I'm callin' you Santa 'cause you
just gifted us one-quarter tank.
Nobody, and I mean nobody,
calls me Santa.
What are you doing, Dad?
I'm gonna burn that quarter tank.
Wasting gas while sitting on my ass.
It's the American way.
Whoo-hoo!
Amazing, son!
Unfortunately, your left foot
just grazed the sideline.
Incomplete pass.
Dad, I've got to pee.
Huh? Huh?
I know it's a rental,
but I'd rather go in the woods.
Maybe I should come with you.
Dad, come on. I'm ten years old.
I can pee by myself. It's easy.
You just shake it when you're through.
You do what now?
- Sketch what you see.
- Hmm?
_
Bart, where are you?!
- Bart!
- What is it?
Bart...!
Bart!
I don't know, but I can't shoot it.
Looks like it's pregnant.
Ah, let's wait till they're born,
and then we'll, uh, shoot 'em all.
Where the heck were you?
Where's Bart?
Okay, this is the hardest news
in the world for a mother to hear.
Just ease her into it.
Um, you know that
sewing room you wanted,
but we could never figure out where?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What? My special little guy.
Don't worry, Lou.
If there's one thing I've mastered,
it's consoling distraught parents.
Ma'am? Ma'am?
Can you describe your son's skeleton?
Ooh! You incompetent...
Look, look, your boy's gonna be fine.
Now we laid out a grid
and have search teams
fanning out over the forest.
I'm sorry, but, uh, because of the grid,
we have to suspend the search
and bring in some ambulances.
Where is my son?!
Where am I?
Hmm.
_
Huh.
Welcome to Strategic Air
Command, Springfield Station.
If you're watching this tape,
half the world is doomed.
Says you, General Dead Guy.
Behind you is a Titan II missile,
key to a mighty line of defense
that will reduce our casualties
to an acceptable 200 million.
Dud.
Ay, caramba!
- Bart?
- Bart!
Now don't worry, I have the best
dang bloodhound in the county.
Uh, does your boy smell like a fox?
- No.
- We're of no use to you.
Come on, Bart. You made your point!
The whole town is looking for you.
Even that scary old man from the
house with the broken windows.
Bart broke my windows!
It used to be a normal house!
All right, listen up.
We have a boy-comma-missing,
and you maggots...
you're gonna help find him.
I thought we were ladies.
- You're lady maggots.
- Now see here, Sergeant.
You haven't fed us.
We're pretty close to riot mode.
This is the boy.
Never seen him in my life.
_
We all get tattoos we regret.
I will find that boy,
and I will toast you with his blood!
What'd I tell you
about blood toasts, Bob?
To do them, but not brag about them.
Ask now what
your country can do for you
is what you can do for your country.
Doesn't sound like any president I know.
_
Freedom!
Oh, I can smell Springfield!
Aw.
Nothing good ever comes from trying.
Private Homer,
you fat stack of mop buckets!
You find something funny about this?
How about I wipe that smile off
your fat face?
Not my Homie!
Avert your eyes, ma'am.
A phone?! Please.
Dial tone. Dial tone.
Oh, thank God!
I'm looking for a Miss Culls.
First name Tess, middle initial "T."
Uh, just a sec. I'll check.
Uh, Tess T. Culls. Tess T. Culls!
Uh, come on! I know you're
hangin' around here somewhere.
Why, you little...
When I catch you, I'm gonna
stick a beer tap in ya
and pull till the foam
comes out your ears!
Oh! Oh!
Oh. I give up.
If you find Bart,
give me his lunch money.
Well, I'm never giving up.
Why not?
Because searching forever is much easier
than me finding a new friend.
I could be your new friend.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
Shut up!
His lucky cap!
Bart? Bart? Are you down there?
Milhouse!
I have never been so glad to see you.
Thanks for not noticing my new haircut.
Just give me your phone.
I'll go get help!
You can count on me!
I lit these for our son.
Marge, honey, he's never gonna come back
if he thinks it's a church.
With 78% of the search area reporting,
Channel Six is now projecting
that Bart Simpson is dead.
That's right. Self-proclaimed
underachiever Bart Simpson,
dead at the age of ten.
Now let's look at the districts
where he's deadest.
Lisa, I have news about Bart.
We already know.
Oh, Milhouse, you were his best friend.
What did you come here for?
Um...
I came to tell her he's alive,
but this feels almost as good
as hugging Harry Horse.
I came to comfort you
in these uncertain times.
Aw.
It's over!
We're callin' off the search!
- Did they find him?
- No, he's dead.
No! That can't be.
Lord, why do you kill things
that I want to kill?
Take me now, vile rake!
_
I think you should look
at Bart's death this way, Bob.
You're free. You're totally free.
Oh, this slipped off.
Have you ever thought
of how your life could've gone
had you committed
to good instead of evil?
Evil isn't a choice.
Mm. I see.
Why don't we try a little
psychological exercise, Bob?
If I unshackle you, will you behave?
Try me.
Cut out Bart's picture.
And by so doing,
cut him out of your life.
Don't listen to them, Bob.
I'm alive.
Are you okay there, Bob?
I won't believe he's dead
until I've made soup from his bones!
Why do I keep giving them scissors?
Hello?
Hey, Mom, it's me. Still married?
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
He's alive! And sassy!
Um, one for the road?
It's a long road.
I'll see you soon.
Hello, Bart...'s friend.
Bart's alive!
Lead me to Bart.
You'll have to kill me first.
But if you kill me,
you'll never find Bart.
Hmm. A conundrum.
How to break you?
Tell me, do you like light operetta?
Oh, how light?
And a-one and a-two.
♪ I have a song to sing, O ♪
♪ Sing me your song, O ♪
♪ 'Tis sung to the moon ♪
♪ by a lovelorn loon ♪
♪ Who fled ♪
♪ from the mocking throng, O ♪
♪ The song of the knell ♪
♪ of a churchyard bell... ♪
I give! I give!
I'll take you to Bart!
♪ He cracked like an egg ♪
Please stop!
♪ And began to beg ♪
You promised.
♪ As I sang this song-o ♪
♪ It's a song of a popinjay, ♪
♪ bravely born ♪
♪ Who turned up his noble nose ♪
♪ with scorn... ♪
Can you at least stab me in my ear?
No.
Okay, we'll split up and find Bart.
Thanks for lending this to us, Ned.
And I'll do the three things
that help the most:
pray, pray, pray.
What about me?!
I ain't ridin' in that!
No, you're pulling it!
Lousy, no good...
I couldn't pull you when you were eight!
Mm-hmm.
Hmm. Hmm.
Hmm. Angry dad, wise-ass kid.
Now, there's a formula that never fails.
Okay, boys, we're gonna
sing a nice little song.
I want to play cowboys and Indians.
Calvin, put down that tomahawk.
Calvin. Calvin.
Calvin!
You look funny, Dave.
Dave? Dave?!
♪ God bless America ♪
♪ Give me back my tomahawk... ♪
That's where he is.
But if you jump down,
you can't get back up
and you'll be caught.
So, uh, I guess that's checkmate.
We're not playing chess.
We're playing a game called After You.
After me?
If you insist.
_
Oh, God. I am so sick of these.
Twelfth time's the charm!
Sideshow Bob?!
That's right. I found your hidey-hole!
You found my heinie hole?
Ah, yes.
Always the back-of-the-class wit.
Well, today you're going to be
a real blast.
I don't like the way
he really hit the word "blast."
_
Uh, Bob, it takes two keys.
That way, no nutcase
can do it by himself.
Well, no one ever said
launching two boys
on a 50-year-old missile would be easy.
Wow! For a 50-year-old missile,
it's in terrific shape!
Shut up!
I'm a kid who appreciates
things that last.
Come on, boy.
Get a good whiff of his scent.
Did you find anything?
Uh, we found Bart's sock drawer.
Get back out here!
Well, you can't shoot
her. You know that's a woman.
Oh, this is the last
time I hunt with my lawyer.
Son, I can't go no further.
I want to just lie down and die.
Dad, you can't die here.
You have to die in a nursing home,
where your body falls apart
as you burn through your savings
till you're a worthless vegetable.
You know, with dignity.
You're right, son.
We're here on a mission.
Now, let's pick out that Christmas tree.
We're here to find Bart.
Right, right. But we got
a nice eight-footer over here.
She's got a bare patch,
but we'll turn that to the wall.
That's it. I'm not listening
to another word.
Help! Help! Help!
For this, you can thank my time
at Cirque du Soleil.
More like Cirque du So Lame.
Yes, they are pretty much all the same.
Just a little further...
Oh, wait, wrong key.
Five minutes to launch.
Bob, why are you doing this?
Well, it's perfectly obvious.
Uh, it's...
Give me a moment.
It's an ICBM.
I Commit Bart's Murder!
That's your justification
for killing two kids?
I... Hmm?
Dad, look! It's either
Sideshow Bob or Shaq.
Not me. I'm going that way.
Boy, am I lost.
Shaq, can you help us?
I'm not Superman.
You have a Superman tattoo on your arm.
How do you know so much about me?
You're scaring me.
I don't have any money.
Have you ever thought
of how your life could've gone
had you committed to good?
It is true. I had talent.
I was on Zoom. Just send it to Zoom!
Box 350, Boston, Mass.
♪ 02134 ♪
You don't want to do this.
You're losing it, Bob.
I don't know what's real
and what's hallucination.
_
Hello?
Hello, Doctor. Bob Terwilliger.
Did I catch you at a bad time?
Oh, Bob, how thoughtful of you to call.
Most prisoners rarely follow up
after leaving me to die.
_
I just need to know,
should I kill these children?
Sounds like someone's got a case
of the shoulds.
If you're calling to ask,
it means you already know the answer.
T minus two minutes.
Clear blast area.
Just tell me, please!
He's not allowed to talk.
Hmm, that sounds like
the ignition sequence
of an LGM-25C Titan II-II
ballistic missile.
I've had just about enough
of your nonsense!
All right, I owe you one.
So, why'd you save us?
Because I realized I don't want
to kill you anymore.
Milhouse, is there a knife in my back?
Not that I can see.
Milhouse, is there
a "kick me" sign on my back?
Not that I can see.
Aw!
I just can't get a clean shot.
Also, you don't have a gun.
I'm useless, all right.
_
What a brilliant conceptual piece.
Who's it by?
"Norad."
More like Snore-ad.
Wait, is it ticking?
_
Sooner or later,
it all comes down to mopping.
_
Doctor, I'm happy.
And when I'm released,
after three consecutive life sentences,
I think I'll open a flower shop.
Oh, that's great, Bob.
Not all my patients are this successful.
Well,
I won't be needing his file anymore.
And if you're interested,
tomorrow's 9:00 appointment
just opened up.
And a 10:00.
_
Your New York Magazine, sir.
This is The New Yorker.
Totally different.
One is the gossip rag of the glitterati.
The other, an asthmatic dinosaur
that hasn't been relevant
since William Shawn breathed his last!
Can I go now?
I've got 15 other lighthouses,
and every one's a weirdo.
Not that you are.
Fine. Leave me.
I'll just polish the bulb
and ponder a wasted life
as I walk along the shore.
_
I rewrite it
every time the tide goes out.
Listen to me!
Life is short.
Don't spend it
on foolish, empty revenge!
If you buy a mailbox, I wouldn't
have to talk to you anymore.
Fine.
- Sync and corrections by ByDem -
- www.addic7ed.com -