(Bart choking loudly)
♫ ♫
(exclaims)
(school bell rings)
(burps)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeps)
♫ ♫
(playing arpeggios)
- (horn honks)
- (Grampa yells)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(grunts)
♫ ♫
(knock on door)
(wind whistles)
("America the Beautiful"
playing)
(old-timey piano music playing)
(man groans)
(lively jazz music playing)
(upbeat rock and roll music
playing)
(The Simpsons theme playing)
(warbling electronic music
playing)
D'oh!
♫ ♫
Great birthday trip.
One more thing to remind me
of my insignificance.
(Grampa groans)
Two adults, one student,
one boy who just phones it in,
and a senior citizen veteran
on his birthday.
Oh, and I'd like to apply
my astronaut discount.
I'll need to see your diaper.
Typical cheapskate Homer.
Taking all the fun
out of turning 87.
Get this stupid
party hat off me!
What the...?
Oh, I'll fix it.
(Grampa groans)
Woo-hoo! 182!
Homer, that's your weight
on the moon.
(shrieks)
PLUTO (distorted):
I used to be a planet.
Then one day they called
and said it was over.
It's over when I say it's over!
So sad.
But I'll be back.
I'm working on some stuff.
Let's just say you might not be
seeing Halley's Comet no more.
(orchestral music playing
faintly inside)
Losers.
(orchestral music playing)
NARRATOR : Forged in a nanosecond
in the Big Bang,
our universe is so enormous,
every NFL stadium
could fit inside it.
And their parking lots.
(crowd oohing, gasping)
When's this show gonna start?
It has started.
(stammers) How can it have
started if I'm talking?
Wouldn't that bother everyone?
Quiet!
I can't hear the Big Bang!
NARRATOR : Approximately
13.8 billion years ago...
- (gasps) Billion?
- ...the universe consisted of
a tiny singularity
of enormous mass,
which suddenly burst forth
in the greatest explosion ever.
Fire in the theater!
No! Your pupils aren't
ready for Earth light!
(crowd screams, gasps)
Damn it, I was developing film!
(jazz band playing
"In the Mood" over stereo)
Turn it up!
I can't hear it!
Louder!
Keep it down!
(tires screech, music stops)
Mm, happy birthday.
I never want to hear that again!
♫ Happy birthday ♫
♫ To you ♫
♫ To you. ♫
Say my name, you cowards!
Make a wish, party pooper.
Okay, I will.
(man groans)
That was a coincidence.
I got you
the one birthday present
you can really use.
A call girl that kills me after?
- A hearing aid.
- A hearing aid?
Forget it. People will think
I'm old, dadgummit.
You are old.
You've lived long enough
to see your prejudiced attitudes
come back into fashion.
Lousy Greeks.
- (bird chirping)
- (Grampa gasps)
(wind whistling)
(bingo balls clacking)
(needles clicking)
(man snoring)
(loud dripping)
(chirping)
♫ ♫
(laughs)
Thank you.
Bart! Bart!
Wake up.
- Yo. What's up?
- Listen.
The planetarium said
the universe is
13.8 billion years old.
But I turned in a paper
where I said million!
What do you want from me?
(snake rattles)
I was just wondering
if you were planning on breaking
into the school anytime soon.
You know, like, maybe tonight.
Nope. Not till next month.
Please.
I'll do your homework!
Sounds like you can't even
do your own homework.
- Ouch.
- Yeah, you think about that
while I'm breaking you
into the school.
LISA :
Hmm.
MARGE :
Who's breaking into the school?
Bart's just talking
in his sleep!
MARGE : I believe that.
Trust you. Good night!
How did you know
this door was broken?
Eh, Willie keeps me posted.
I keep him in licorice.
(grunts)
Willie's riding
the red pony tonight.
(moaning)
Look who's got pumpkin stickers!
Bart, those are for Halloween.
Also Thanksgiving,
if there's some left over.
Whoa! Where has this been
all my life?
Come on, let's go!
Okay. You fixed
your stupid paper,
and I scored
the teacher's nicotine gum.
She does that so she doesn't
smell like cigarettes, you know.
Yeah, and she should also
get some booze gum.
(mechanical buzzing)
What's that?
Maybe it's the ghost of that boy
who had to climb that rope
in gym until his heart exploded.
(gasps) You're making that up.
Am I that creative?
No.
(mechanical buzzing continues)
Oh, God.
(gasps)
Principal Skinner.
Are you living in the school?
Absolutely not.
And you have no proof.
(groans)
Seymour, why are you
living here?
You have a house.
With 30 pizzas on the way.
30 pizzas.
I can finally send mama
back to Italy! Mwah!
It's not my house,
it's Mother's.
But after what I just found out
she did, I can never go back.
They say it's better to talk
about it, but I never will.
- Okay.
- We understand.
Seriously, don't ask
what it was.
- Are you asking?
- I was stretching.
Then why'd you only
stretch one arm?
It's the only arm
that needed stretching.
Fine, I'll tell you what it was.
- You don't have to.
- Really, it's okay.
We believe you.
Ever since I was a kid,
I-I wanted to be a drummer.
- In a rock band?
- No.
Marching.
I would've given all I had
to be the dot on that "I."
It's also called a "tittle."
Don't you think I know that?
I did everything I could
to make that band.
In my application, I sent
songs and choreographies.
(lively marching band music
playing)
I'm a shoo-in!
Then the fateful day came.
Son, you got a letter from
Ohio State University.
I'm too nervous to get up.
- Do you want me to read it to you?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
You were rejected.
Uh, seems kind of thick.
Well, they gave you
a lot of reasons
why you weren't good enough.
♫ ♫
That's so sad.
There's more I have to tell you.
I was going to surprise Mother
by papering her drawers,
then I found this.
I was accepted.
She lied.
That's so sad.
- (Bart chuckles)
- What makes this really tragic
is there was also
a personal handwritten letter
from the Director of Admissions.
(sniffs)
What's that smell?
I'm making spaghetti
and kick balls.
Does it get worse than that?
How could it be worse than that?
May I see the letter?
(scoffs) I must say your
sympathy is a pleasant surprise.
No, this is just the only
college acceptance letter
I'll ever hold.
Mm.
So it's for all these reasons
that I will not be seeking
a seat in the U.S. Senate.
I will now take a few questions.
Let me tell you the wonderful
present I just got.
Dad! What a surprise!
(under breath):
What's he doing here?
Didn't we just
see him yesterday?
GRAMPA : That's what they're
saying under their breath?
How awful!
I want to hear all of it.
Maybe if we pretend we're tired,
he'll go home.
(all yawning)
Thank God he can't hear us.
And I'm glad these fake yawns
are something we can do
as a family.
What?! You, too?!
Good-bye!
Dad, wait!
What's wrong with the old coot?
I mean, what's wrong with you,
you sweet old coot?
I got a hearing aid,
and I heard everything you said.
We didn't mean
the mean things we meant.
We just said them
because we meant them.
(stammers angrily)
I am gone forever!
A little mall walk
will cheer me up.
Uh-oh, old guy.
Don't make eye contact.
Rubbing them is like
working dry lasagna.
Old guy! Here he comes!
He'll want to try
all my lotion samples.
I'll have to explain
what "send" is on a cell phone.
Come in! Come in!
Well, that's more like it.
(screams)
(Lisa gasping, groaning)
I had to cheat.
I was doing it
for the bell curve.
And with 99% of the vote in,
the next president
is Lisa Simps...
Wait a minute.
I'm being told she cheated
on a paper in second grade.
She is disqualified,
making our next president
Kenny Hitler.
No!
Hey, welcome to
Bob Hope's USO Show,
or as I like to call it,
Christmas away from Dolores.
(rim shot, cymbal crash)
Oh, that could've been me
on those drums.
I would've gotten to rehearse
at his house in Toluca Lake.
Toluca Lake!
What'll it be?
Can an old vet have a beer
and tell you his troubles?
Sure.
(no audio)
And that's how
I opened the orange.
So, uh, (chuckles) my mother
didn't tell me I got in.
That's all right.
You can enroll now.
- Can I?
- No!
This is a school,
not an '80s comedy.
That, uh, letter you sent me...
is that something
you send every student?
No, I only sent that once,
to you.
When you didn't show up,
that was the second worst day
of my career.
What was the worst?
The day the Big Ten expanded
to 14 schools.
What are we, morons?
We didn't even notice till
Northwestern pointed it out.
Oh, I'm sorry, should I not have
told you about the letter?
Uh, no.
It's actually good,
because I'm no longer sad.
I'm angry!
It's time for a furious
self-guided tour of this campus.
♫ ♫
I've never seen someone
walk the oval so many times.
He's got to be dizzy.
I switch directions
every other lap.
- Oh, uh, Michigan sucks.
- What?
That's how we say "excuse me"
around here.
(bells chiming melody)
CHOIR (to melody):
♫ Loser, loser ♫
♫ Missed opportunity ♫
♫ All over now ♫
♫ You poor bastard. ♫
Et tu, Brutus?
Hey! (grunts)
Okay, Mother, it's time for
an unpleasant confrontation.
(school bell ringing)
Class, I'm going to hand back
your astronomy papers.
LISA :
Keep calm. Keep calm.
No one knows
you did anything wrong.
Lisa Simpson, come to my desk.
(gasps)
Miss Hoover, I have to confess.
I changed my paper.
It said million,
but I knew it was billion.
(sobs):
Oh, please.
Maybe I can start a new life
in the other second grade class.
(sobbing)
I know you changed your paper.
I don't care about your grade.
Where the hell
is my nicotine gum?
(sniffles)
My brother had it, and he was
hanging around the class pet.
I'll get you some more gum.
You do that.
♫ ♫
Can I help you?
What are you doing here?
Your mother rented me your room.
You rented my room
to the town drunk?
I am also the state drunk.
(burps)
What do you want?
(gasps) You know?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Oh, son, forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
I just couldn't bear to lose you
like I'd lost everything else.
Oh, I would've arranged for you
to live near me in the dorm.
Oh, I can't live
in a college town.
Can't control myself sexually.
What you did to me was the worst
thing anyone could do to anyone,
much less a mother to her son.
I really don't know
what you could say.
Son, I guess when
you get right down to it,
I've always felt marching bands
are a colossal waste of time.
The music and the walking
both suffer.
You may have a point.
And you'll always be
my little tittle.
- Is that a tear?
- Maybe.
(both sigh)
Please, I beg you.
Will you move back in?
There are gonna have to be
some changes.
What kind of changes?
Well, I want the parental
controls taken off the TV.
You'll just watch
booby programs.
If I'm in the booby mood,
yes, I will.
Welcome back, son.
Looks like I got
a little brother!
He's not staying, is he?
You boys work it out.
We sure will, Ma.
You still haven't found Grampa?
No. But I found this guy
who's willing to take his place.
(Spanish accent):
I am Grandpapa.
Gather the grandchildren
that we might play
the Hungry Hungry Hippos.
I don't think anyone can
replace our Grampa.
Are you sure?
Your husband...
she looked through
hundreds of grandpapas.
This was my third callback!
Make a choice.
- (phone rings)
- Yello.
Is this the no-good ungrateful
son of Abraham Simpson?
- Speaking.
- I'm gonna send him back to you,
and I don't want
to see him here again.
This place is really depressing.
And he does not help.
There's a pathetic old drunk
peeing himself in the bathroom.
That's a mirror.
And it's not the bathroom.
BART : (sighs)
When is Grampa gonna get here?
GRAMPA :
I knew it.
Still bad-mouthing me
behind my back.
LISA : I can't believe it,
but I miss him so much.
(confused grunt)
BART :
I love him, too.
I just can't say it to his
beautiful shriveled turnip head.
Aw.
I love how he knows
what every building used to be.
And Maggie says...
(mechanical voice):
U. R. A. D. Light.
(sobbing)
Come get your Grampa,
you sweet slices of melon.
- Aw.
- (all sigh)
Aw, we love you.
Woo-hoo!
D'oh!
(dramatic orchestral music
playing over TV)
What are you watching?
It's a booby movie, isn't it?
It's Emmy-winning premium cable.
Do they show boobs?
Not since they started
winning Emmys.
Very disappointing.
Well, I guess
I'll watch with you.
What's that thing?
It's a raven from
the Lannister's Maester.
What's a Lannister?
What's a Maester?
House Lannister
is the wealthiest fa...
- Is that a dragon?
- Yes.
This is stupid.
♫ He walks down the street ♫
♫ He falls in the hole, man ♫
♫ Everyone knows Hans Moleman! ♫
Who?
Nobody knows Hans Moleman.
Next.
I was here first.
(scanner beeps)
♫ In the checkout line ♫
♫ He doesn't even scan ♫
♫ Nobody knows Hans Moleman. ♫
I just need my heart pills.
Shh!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
^.^.^.^.COLORED by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com