Water a soup again?
Now it's crow soup
I call an eye
Me too
Me three
And Maggie gets the beak
Your hovel got in the way of my horse
Kiss his hooves in apology
Please forgive us noble steed
Our nostrils are not worthy of your
mighty stench
are those new horse shoes
Oh they look good on you;
Lousy nobles
We serf are starving while they're feasting
and jousting and posing for tapestries
where they're friends with a unicorn
as if any unicorns would like them
unicorns like nice people
I am a nice person
Young lady
that kind of talk is anti fearless
and i wont have it
without feudalism
we wouldn't have this hovel
or bountiful filth
or my awesome buboes
Ohh
I'll lance you later
Bart
They just stuck new severed heads up
on the city wall
Oh, can we go mom
can we, can we?
That's a lovely idea
And we can bring my mom
I hope she is doing okay
in her new nurshing home
which one is your mom's web
Son, is that you?
No
You ruined my nap
just like you ruined
my daughter's life
That's her
They didn't skimp on the tar
That's the secret of long lasting heads
There's Ned Flanders
It's always nice when you know someone
Those were kind of sideburns
i was saying you should grow
Pretty sharp
pretty pretty sharp
See how the heads of rich people
get the tallest pikes
with the best view
It's so unfair
I told you to lay off feudalism
It's the only system we know
We have no choice about it
therefore it's the best
The system is designed to keep us down
That's not true
In a great country like ours
a poor girl can grow up
to be anything she wants
A wife
Or a harlot
And that's it
I wanted to be a harlot
but it's all who you know
it's never too late
everyone is somebody's weird fetish
Mom, what's wrong with your skin?
It's blue
and ice cold
This could be a serious disease
Homer, she needs a medical attention
pretty, pretty sharp
It's never easy to say this
You've got genital snarf
La la la la la la
we've got our new home
Doc,
Is there any way to control
the occasional flare-ups?
Nope
Now what'd have we here
progressive frozen mortification
this can only be the bite of
an ice walker
An ice walker?
Mom, how did this happen?
I dated a ravenous wight
who abhors the warmth of the living
And?
He got fresh
I am sorry baby
I know I am a screw up
But you've gotta give me another chance
I love you
She's nine hundred years
younger than you
you pervert!
I like 'em young
That ain't no crime
Is my mom gonna be okay?
I am sorry but a week from now
your mother would be a frozen solid
Noo!
No that can't be
she's barely into her hag years
All you can do is give her
leeches for the pain
Here's an organizer
So,
So there's nothing we can do to save her?
Well, there's one treatment
All we have to do is buy this amulet
my mom is saved
Yeahhh...
but a hundred GP
I mean that's more than
a tenth-level fighter makes
in an entire campaign
Don't worry
We'll figure it out
Hey, sweet young thang
what time they'd cut you down
Oh, baby
Okay, we just need to come up with
a hundred gold pieces
How much do we have in our savings?
Let me think
What are savings?
Well then we can sell our possessions
the pig
the spoon
the gelatinous cube
has to be worth something
Is this because of what happened to the cat?
I told him not to nap on me
Soo,
That's on him
Look, honey
I love your mom
As crones go she's tops
but does it make sense
i mean total sense
to spend all that money
so a really old lady can get
a little bit older
this is my mom's life
This family would do whatever it takes
to keep her alive
is that understood?
Of course, of course
Good
All i am saying is...
Homer Serfson
You're the most selfish jerk
in the entire Tri-Kingdom area
I should've listened to that witch
and married my twin brother, Markery
Always here if you need me, sis
get lost freak!
She chose me
You get that money to save my mom
or never set foot in this hovel again
good things come to those who wait
Is Marge still sore at you Homer?
Yeah
It's not like i want to kill her mother
I just wanna let her die from neglect
If i dont get money for that amulet
I'll be sleeping on the iron couch
Now let's see here
An urgent message for Milady Gwendolyn Partz
Uh, Milady Partz?
Hey, has anyone seen Milady Partz?
Ah come on
Somebody grab Milady Partz
That depends
How big is your dowry
You little craven
If I ever get my hands on you
I am gonna slice you open
and drain all of your humus
Blood
Black bile
Yellow bile
And phlegm
Okay
Break's over
Uh, Lord Montgomery
I've had some unforseen family
medical expenses
And I was wondering...
could i get an advanced on my salary
Uh, but first
can I have a salary?
Peasants
Serfson, you've pushed that wheel around
and around for twenty years
Did you ever wonder why?
Mostly i just pust it
Have you ever noticed
that the wheel isn't hooked up to anything
The rumors were true
But you work does produce
something very special
Human misery
which when collected,
ground into a powder and snorted
gives rich people tiny wings
that do nothing
So if you help me,
it reduces my suffering
which means less wing powder
for my betters
I am glad we had this talk
But I really need the money for...
Flit-flit
Thank you for your time
Hey, Azzlan
Marge, my child
I've come to offer solace
in this difficult time
you mean, convert me to your religion
when i am at my most vurnerable
No, no, no, no, no!
I am just here to ask you
an important question
Have you heard the news?
Yes, yes
I would be saved
thanks so much for stopping by
I am just gonna leave you with
this literature
in the buffet, God...
I can't go home and face your mom
without the money for that amulet
In here
Do you have your lucky lead nugget
Always
A lead-lick a day keeps the doctor...
Gold
Sweet sweet gold
Why didn't you ever tell us
you could do magic
Because if the king finds out
He'll take me away and forces me to be
one of his evil wizards
You necromancing nitwitzs
I wanted an all-seeing eye
Not this
No daughter of mine is gonna end up
in the hex trade
Let's go buy that amulet
And don't worry,
Mum's the word
Did you say the word
Hey Azzlan
Twelve nothing
my serve
You know, eventually
you're gonna run out of us
I said, my serve
Mom
I've got a surprise for you
Thanks to who?
I said it when i was eleven
And I'll say it now
You're the greatest husband in the world
Where'd a dirt-poor loser like you
get all the gold for that?
Well...,
Let's just say
I strangled the Leprechaun
I am not wearing that
but without it you'll die
fine by me
What!?
I want to die
Oh, typical
I wanna live, I wanna die
just make up your mind
they're both terrible
I've lived a full life
I saw a drawing of an ocean
I watched my daughter married an Ogre
I am not an Ogre
My father married an ogre
after my mother was eaten by
a different ogre
you're my mom
I can't bear the thought of saying good-bye
you want me to live, I'll live
Let's celebrate
I'll roast a hobbit for dinner
Bet you've a packet of South Farthing
pipe weed
she picks me, Gaffer
Hush now, lad
the big folk will choose who's tastiest
and no mistake
How do you know you got them from me?
We miss you
We miss you, too
love you
love you, more!
is it really so bad for grandma
if she dies?
wont she spend enternity
in the field of Bliss?
Yeah
We're all going to the field of Bliss
where the days are passed
in frolic most joyous
Just frolicking?
That's it?
Sometimes you wave ribbons through the air
but mainly frolicking
Doesn't that get old?
Did I mention the ribbons?
cause there's ribbons
Field of Bliss?
Nonsense
the afterlife is an eternity of slaughtering
and being slaughtered by your enemies
Oh yeah
You both wrong
after death you spend all day
counting goblin Jesus' money
And it better all be there
Seventy one mermaids
somewhere the fish is the top part
Mushrooms
Everywhere mushrooms
Frolicking and ribbons
Yeah, but...
What if after we die,
that's it
we're just gone
So just poof?
Really?
Poof and then just super nothing?
Well, it's clean
I'll give you that
Oh yeah
This is way better than death
Come on, mom
There's so many things we can say
to each other now
Oh really?
Okay then
Say then
I am waiting
Well...
what about you guys?
What do you want to ask your grandma?
I've got nothing
I am gonna take a stroll
and enjoy the golden age of cleavage
Lisa?
Uhmm...
Grandma?
Tell us your most ardent swain
I dated a little shape-shifter once
I thought i could keep him from changing
I was wrong
Love is a fairy tale
Every moment with her is a precious gift
Yes, yes it is
All that matters is that we're family
and we're together
Sorcerer-intended Chalmers
Your daughter has been detected
using a witchcraft
Under the magic the gathering act,
She is hereby property of the crown
What?
My daughter isn't a magician
Oh I am terribly sorry but she is
Yes, the moment that she transmuted
lead into gold
our palantirs they just went bananas
I've never seen palantirs go so bananas
It was the only way
I just don't want you to be sad
about grandma
Oh no
This is all my fault
Don't blame yourself honey
We're all at fault from doing
whatever it takes
to make you happy
Help!
You can't nap my kid
that's kidnapping
Toenail Imprisonum!
D'oh!
Lisa's magic?
Maybe I am a magic too
Abra-carumba!
You just grab a stick
and say a funny word
That's not insulting to us at all
Please don't take my daughter
She's only trying to save her grandmother
She sounds like a wonderful kid
Now please say good-bye to her forever
Take a present leave a present
She's gone
Lisa's gone
Clip me out of here Marge
I am gonna rescue Lisa
if i have to kill every noble
in that castle
But dad
Serfs can't rise up against nobles
you'd be attacking the system itself
And nobody loves feudalism more than you
Son,
feaudalism is a beautiful vision
The bill of no rights
One person no vote
But I am willing to betray all that
to get my daughter back
Hey, you mind if i dissolve those?
Uh, just checkin
better to ask
Better to ask
Peasants
Peons
and distinguished beggars
Are you tired of the nobles taking
the wheat we sow?
the yarn we spin and the wine we steal
from travellers we murder on the road
They even take our children
And not just the worthless Bart
but the magical Lisa
If we can put a moon-spangled hat on a man
why can't we kill a bunch of rich jerks
and take their stuff
How are we going to get over this walls?
Walls cannot stop us
The trees would fight with you
We would never forget your sacrifice
Sacrifice?
We could've torn down the castle walls
in five minutes
Trees can't talk silly
Lisa: Mom, Dad
Help!
Milhouses, save your girlfriend
Lisa, lisa, lisa
Okay
No, I am just a friend...
who is a girl
It's something to build on
You peasants are a drag-on the economy
Oh, I get it
because he's riding a dragon
My love for worldplay is undiminished
Oh no, we're losing
We need to talk
Now?
Yes now
It's time for me to
Go
Life's about moving forward
Girls want to be women
Women want to be mothers
Mothers want to be grandmas
And grandmas want to know what comes next
But what if I am not ready?
I wont leave you if i dont know
you'll be alright
Okay Mom
I understand
Maybe I was born a peasant
but i am going out an ice queen
Ouch
Now we won
My mom gave her life to save ours
Take comfort, Marge
Now she's in the field of Bliss
No, she is in Goblin money heaven
The afterlife is snake chewing your eyes
but it feels good
This is our heaven
Or...
As long as grandma lives on in our hearths,
then she's never truly gone
Until we die
then it's like she never existed
And someday,
No one will remember you
Or anybody
All is well the nobles are defeated
the dragon is dead
And I have a daughter
who can turn lead into gold
Uhm actually,
I can't anymore
Dragon's fire is the source of all magic
And granda killed the last one
Everything wondrous
and extraordinary about our world
is going to fade
But maybe now we can use science
to improve our world
With new technologies,
we can put an end to poverty and disease
Sure it would be hard work,
but far more rewarding than waving your hand
over a rock to change it into gold
I mean
Please come back magic
live damn you, live
I am risen
But what about science?
Oh sweety
Who would want to live in a world
without magic?
It would be so boring
People would have to make up fantasy stories
Most of them poorly-written pretenses
for explicit sex and violence
Just to escape the tedious real world
That does sound awful
Look, the dragon is burning our village
I love our lives