I've travelled the whole world.
He's in there
trying to discredit me and what I'm doing.
Are you for real? Where the fuck…
I'll show him my Instagram right now.
I'll go in there and show him
my fucking Instagram right now
and say, "What the fuck is your problem?"
Alex is saying I purchased my followers.
That's a fucking shit go.
He's trying to ruin my business
that I've worked very hard for.
It's not on.
You're a bully and bullies
need to be fucking called out
and that's what I'm going to do.
Just so you know,
something's about to happen.
There you are.
-I was talking about you.
-We were.
-You were? How coincidental.
-Yeah.
-What is your problem?
-Your response is very aggressive.
Alex, you tried to manage me
so many times. I have the emails.
-Come on.
-Babe!
You tried to gain me as talent.
I said, "No."
-Pull the emails up.
-100% you know.
-I will.
And guess what? I'll show everybody.
It's pathetic
what you've done. It's disgusting.
I have followers all around the world.
-You're coming after my business?
-I'm asking you a question.
I told you what my response was.
I'm not satisfied with it.
Well, guess what?
All the talent you have have done
jack shit compared to what I have.
Guess what you should do?
You should take your talent to Turkey,
get 1,2 million followers from Turkey
so they can do what I've done.
You're a disgrace
on behalf of you, your talent.
-You're a waste of time--
-Don't say that. That's mean.
Sarah, don't get involved.
-He's my friend.
-Don't get involved.
You literally told me
you met him two weeks ago.
-Yeah.
-He's not your friend, sweetie.
-He's not your friend.
-What's the benchmark for being friends?
You met him two weeks ago.
-We're friends.
-Don't be aggressive.
I want to defend him.
Don't be aggressive.
You keep repeating that,
but it doesn't mean we're not friends.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
You're going to be the most hated person
and I didn't want that for you.
Guys, honestly,
we're taking away from Cai's event.
This should be about Cai
not you two arguing. So, let's cut it.
That was heated.
Jade's up here. Living his life,
doing his thing
and this person is a hater.
Why is he so concerned
with everyone else's businesses?
Build your own fucking business.
He's a toxic person
and doesn't really have many friends.
Sarah is Alex's only friend
in the group at this point.
But I think that's going to
bite her on the ass.
-Sarah.
-She was defending Alex.
-That was awkward.
-No.
You've been friends
for two weeks, step aside.
To be honest,
I don't know Sarah, I've met her twice.
Said hello. Does anyone know her?
I've seen her so much
but I didn't have a connection.
And I felt nothing towards her.
-Hannah, do you like her?
-Yes.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Wait, you've been hanging out, have you?
I just think she's new to Byron Bay.
She's trying to fit in.
There's a difference between new and fake.
Yeah.
Sarah, she's just moved here.
I don't believe in excluding someone
without even knowing them.
I actually thought Sarah was super sweet.
And then she said, looking at Nathan,
"He took me out but I was wearing
underpants. So, it wasn't a date."
There's obviously something
a bit tweaky going on.
She said,
"I have underpants on." That's cold.
She kind of sounds tacky.
Honestly, there's something fake there.
I know where my standards and values are
with my friends I associate myself with.
And that is not resonant
with my friend group.
-Hello!
-Hi. How are you, mate?
-I have your print.
-Oh, my gosh!
Thank you.
What's cracking, beautiful human being?
Off the back end of my exhibition,
I sold quite a few works. I'm stoked.
-Beautiful place that you have.
-Thank you.
Me and Simba went over to Alex's place
to drop off the prints he bought.
Cai obviously makes himself
very much at home here.
Look at him. He's laying down,
having a little chill sesh.
I love this couch so much.
Not many people are even trying
to see his side of the story.
And Alex has been a good person to me.
He also is the reason
why I can eat food this week
because he bought my prints.
So, the least I can do is be a G for him.
I just thought I'd pop by
and see how you were doing.
-And make sure you were sweet.
-Well, I had the crystal out.
I feel there's a lot
of energy in this crystal.
And I need it at the moment.
I need all the repairing,
healing I can get.
Healing after what? The exhibition?
Oh, my God. After your exhibition. I know.
I did feel bad about that. I did not plan
for it to be some huge explosion.
I think maybe I misread Jade,
because I thought that
he wanted to have a conversation with me
and give me the benefit of the doubt.
And he was being sweet.
So, I thought that,
my question in that environment…
He'd go, "Thanks for giving me
the benefit of the doubt."
"Let me tell you X, Y, Z." That's the
response I thought was going to happen.
Holy shit.
The fucking tsunami that came at me.
I went and talked to my Nana and Pop.
They were standing quite close to you.
And my Nana comes up and goes,
"I think they're fighting
about something about followers."
-"What are followers?"
-So sweet.
How are you feeling?
It upset me to see how upset he got.
Because deep, deep, deep, deep down,
-I'm a nice person. It's just buried.
-Yeah.
You could basically drill for oil
before you find the nice person.
I hope that kind of all works itself out
because Byron is a small town,
we're all in the same industry and stuff.
Yeah.
There's a lot of negative vibes
going around right now
and it's causing
a lot of disharmony in the group.
So as a holistic health
and spiritual coach,
my mission in life is to heal others.
I think it could be a really
good chance for me to step in,
bring everybody together,
and heal their grudges.
I made a really awesome plan.
Just to bring a few people together.
And create a space for a bit of
a deeper spiritual connection together.
Getting to the bottom of things
that are slightly in the shadows.
And bring them to the surface.
I've seen what you've done.
I've talked to people
that you've worked with and
the fire twirling and everything…
I'm so excited to be a part of this.
Fire is the primordial element
for creation and destruction.
It is that which burns away the deadwood
and makes space for something
new and beautiful.
And it's my way to help other people
with their health.
And inspire some level of emotion.
This is a beautiful thing
that I wanted to…
give to you. Almost as a gift, right?
-See, all that sounds great.
-Yeah.
But also terrifies me
because I don't know if you've noticed,
but I've pissed a lot of people off
in a very short time. So…
It's gonna be an opportunity
to come together,
and start this healing process.
Can't wait to be there.
I appreciate that Simba thinks it's gonna
bring Jade and I closer together.
But the only thing
that'll bring Jade and I closer together
is an answer to my question.
Oh, my God. Last night.
What a nightmare.
Literally, what a nightmare.
I knew there was something up
with that Alex guy from day dot.
And I feel that the way I handled myself
and went at him might've been aggressive.
I'm still gonna stand my ground
'cause like, "Don't fuck around."
I didn't think it was aggressive.
It was totally fair how you reacted.
He was trying
to pull you down to his level.
People do that. They get jealous,
they see your success,
they want to try and act
as if you got it handed to you--
That's why it upset me.
Because I felt he was trying
to take away how hard I've worked.
If Alex is gonna come for me, I'm ready.
I'm not going to be disrespected.
And I won't have my mood
and my energy affected.
I'm already talking
like a Byron Bay person.
Should have a crystal around my neck.
How do you feel about Sarah?
'Cause I was shocked
that she was so on Alex's side.
-I know.
-And he was so in the wrong.
But Sarah was telling you not to yell.
-And I judged her off that.
-Right?
Yeah.
Sarah's behavior just doesn't
go down well in a small town.
She needs to be careful.
She's going to
cause a lot of trouble for herself.
Hello.
Hi, babe.
-Hi. How are you?
-How are you?
Hannah is so great.
She's been reaching out to me and wanting
to spend some time to get to know me.
-Welcome. Thank you.
-This is beautiful.
My family and I are known
for our brand Bisque.
I wanted to put Sarah in some
Bisque clothes to help her fit in a bit.
You know when someone
is not from Byron, as in a Goldie,
it's like spray-on dresses, high heels,
fake eyelashes, big lips, fake tits…
So, I have my beautiful linens.
We can just play dress-up.
Okay.
This is
quintessentially Byron kind of vibes.
I keep hearing "Byron vibes,"
"that's so Byron." What is Byron?
Byron is flowy, quite a lot of neutrals.
You let the goddess shine.
That's nice.
So…
I was thinking to get you
in a gorgeous little--
-Does that go with that?
-Top and the pants.
-That's pretty.
-Yeah.
Don't know if it'll look good,
but I'll try it.
The clothes that Hannah picked for me,
it's not something
I'm vibing with at the moment,
but when in Byron…
Wear some fucking linen.
You look stunning.
Oh, my God! You babe!
-Do I look like a Byron girl now?
-Yeah!
You look just beautiful.
Really?
Thank you!
I jumped in and told Sarah
what the girls were saying at Cai's
'cause I felt sorry for her
and that she needed to know the truth.
I wanna hear from your side,
'cause I was talking to the girls later.
-I heard you were taking Alex's side.
-Yeah.
He's my friend. So, I feel like I want
to protect him if he's being attacked.
This is the thing with those girls…
they tend to take sides.
They've become better friends with Jade
and with you sticking up for Alex,
they're basically being like,
"We can't trust her."
If people don't like me now
'cause of me trying
to just diffuse that whole situation,
what do I do about that?
Yeah.
I don't know what to do here.
It's high school bullshit.
Well, I appreciate you reaching out to me.
I think it's really nice.
You're my only Byron girlfriend.
It's my pleasure.
-Here you go.
-Amazing.
-Thank you.
-Hey.
-Hey, mate. Just in time.
-Hello.
Just what the doctor ordered.
Came right at the perfect time.
Couldn't have thought
of a better person to come try a cocktail
than the "Party Boy" himself.
So good to see Saskia and Frimmy.
They've always got my back.
I appreciate that about them.
They're like family.
What's been happening?
Man, I've just been cruising.
Kind of just relaxing after the…
-After Cai's event.
-Yeah.
I seen you drag
-Sarah over for a word.
-Yeah. We had a chat.
She actually said that Elias said
I'm a fuckboy. I've got no substance.
He apparently just fully rinsed me.
Fuck.
He's actually really, really annoyed me.
I'm so confused.
I thought you and Elias were friends.
I don't get it.
Honestly, when I was speculating
who planted that seed in Sarah's head,
I was like,
"There's no way it would be Elias."
"He would have my back."
Who knows what his motive is.
He's threatened by you.
He wants
to steal your thunder any way he can.
I just find
the whole situation really immature.
It feels constantly like
Sarah causes drama. I feel like…
I don't know why she's doing this to
two guys who are meant to be friends.
She told me that
on the night of Cai's exhibition.
After all the drama between Alex and Jade,
I'm like, "I won't bring it up here."
-Yeah.
-I was like, "I'll let it run for now.
"But I'll have to say something to Elias."
I reckon Elias has an issue with me.
It's because he's jealous
and he wants Sarah to like him and not me.
And honestly,
I think he's pathetic and insecure.
I'm not going to stand for this shit.
Dude, this place is so beautiful
every time I come inside.
Simba really wants
to have this night with everyone
to bring things up to the surface
that've been bubbling up.
Hopefully get to a point
we can let them go.
What can we help you set up now?
There's all these cushions
and blankets over there.
It feels like Sim's very tuned
into everything that kind of goes on.
He's seen a lot of energies
and he wants to re-ground everyone
or find a way to help do that.
-Yeah.
-Koby.
My man.
I talked to Nathan the other day.
And he's pretty…
I think he's a little bit upset with you.
-Why is he upset?
-'Cause he talked to Sarah.
-Yeah?
-And…
Sarah told him
you said the "Fuckboy" call.
Is that true?
She asked me if he's a bit of a fuckboy.
And?
I was just like, "Yeah."
-It's Nathan…
-Shit.
I don't want Sarah
being hurt or fucked around.
He's pretty upset.
-I don't know why…
-He was upset when we talked.
It's his behavior.
If you're upset by your own behavior,
and people calling you out
for something you do,
then maybe you should change
your behavior as opposed to
trying to pose as something else.
There's nothing wrong with being
young and promiscuous.
When you've kind of
stepped on people to do that
and then try to portray
this "sweet boy" thing it's a bit weird.
Fuck! Preach Lord! That's pretty hardcore.
There's obviously so much shit
between these two.
Shit. First Alex and Jade,
and now we've got you two.
I feel kind of protective over Sarah.
I don't want to see her get hurt.
So, darl. What sort of vibe
are we going for tonight?
It's a little bit different
from what you've seen me in.
Hannah took me into her shop
and gave me a bunch of outfits to try.
Obviously, I've put my little twist on it.
It's different for you. I can see
where Hannah stops and you begin.
It's cute.
Why did she feel
the need to make you over?
I don't know, but when I went to her shop…
she told me that all the girls
are talking shit about me.
Are you actually serious?
Hannah said the girls are shitty that
I took your side and stood up for you
when you and Jade fought.
And Elle said she thought I was fake.
I feel like I'm in high school again.
-I know.
-You know? They're trying to stir shit.
That's my role.
-I know. There can only be one bitch.
-That's my thing.
Bitches stepping on my fucking land.
What upsets me is Sarah is out there,
doing what she wants,
she's wearing what she wants
and power to her.
To be dragged down by these people…
Not about it.
But I have Sarah's back.
She had mine with Jade,
and I have no problem
going into bat for her.
If the girls come for Sarah at this party…
I'm coming for them.
Obviously, you're gonna see Jade tonight.
I'm gonna see Jade.
I have no idea what his response--
Are you gonna go in for round two
or leave it?
Far as I'm concerned, I asked a question,
I don't have an answer.
I get it's a sore point for him and
something he doesn't want to talk about.
But it's still the elephant in the room.
It's a Turkish elephant
in the room, really.
Although Jade may not see it like this,
I'm actually doing him a favor.
Because he's going to have to
address this sometime in his career.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on. We'll do some more in the car.
This is incredible.
-Hello! Oh, my God!
-Welcome!
This is amazing!
How are you?
Nowhere to be, but here.
Oh, my gosh!
-Oh, my God!
-What a pleasure.
I wanna let loose
and not have any negativity,
or anyone that will come in
and create drama and chaos.
So, just spread your arms out like that,
close your eyes,
drop into the presence of your body.
The sound of the drum.
Be right here, right now.
There's nowhere else to be.
If there were any demons on me…
Those demons are definitely gone now.
-Hello, my beautiful.
-This is beautiful.
-Thank you.
-This is magic.
Thank you so much for being here.
Is there any beverage?
-Have we got any beverages?
-Yes. We're going to have a cacao.
We're gonna have a beautifully brewed,
organic cacao I've brewed myself.
It increases energy,
grounds you, it opens your heart,
so you're able to connect
and move and be in the body.
Yes.
There's no bevvies.
I was so disappointed.
If I've ever needed a big, cold glass
of Savvy B in my life, it is right now.
Welcome, welcome.
-Hi.
-How are you?
I'm good. How are you?
In your body. Into your spine.
And turn around.
I feel repulsed.
-You okay?
-Instantly, my vibe is just ruined.
And I hate how I'm like…
-Yeah.
If Alex is going
to come for me, I'm ready.
I'll pop off from zero to 20
and I won't come down to one.
I'm not going to be disrespected
like that anymore.
Not happening.
Is that the dress you gave her?
Yeah!
She's turned it into Gladiator Woman.
I don't know
what she was thinking with that bra.
You can't take
the Gold Coast out of some girls.
Yeah. How you feeling about
everything since last week
and the run-in you had with Jade?
Look, I…
-Deep down, I don't like upsetting people.
-Yeah.
It wasn't my intention
to personally upset him.
-Yeah.
-It was a genuine question
coming from a genuine place.
I said, "I want to give you
the chance to explain."
You know. You've got a great audience.
You've built that up over time
and energy and effort.
How'd you feel if someone just bought
your audience and you lost work to it?
Elias is an example
of what an influencer should be.
And people like Jade, whose audience
aren't what they say they are,
makes people like Elias look bad.
Yeah, I get it.
I still don't think
you should just call someone out.
It's numbers. I spend all day doing this.
To qualify everyone.
Oh, my God. Here he is again.
He's talking about me.
Hey, sorry, I hear everyone's having
a chat about me.
I'd love to be involved.
And we're going to go again
because you just can't
stop fucking speaking about me.
Stop speaking about me.
It was mean,
it was hurtful and it was nasty.
Why did you say that?
Just a question.
It's not just a question.
You're smarter than that.
Come on, Alex. Don't be stupid.
Sure, it's a loaded question.
But it is still a question, right?
I've gone out of my way
to try and be your friend.
It wasn't a personal attack, Jade.
It was a question.
How can I not take that
as a personal attack?
-I don't know where--
-It wasn't.
I don't know where you come from
and what you think.
But if you're gonna go
throwing shit like that,
you're gonna have a big issue with me.
We're gonna have a problem.
Let's embrace
the good energy that is here.
-There's enough crystals for good energy.
-To heal fucking anything.
Let's absorb the good energy and try and…
-Okay.
-Be happy.
-Have a good night.
-Thank you.
Jade's response to my question
has been really emotional and aggressive.
Oh, my God!
I love you.
I fucking love you.
Look who it is!
-What's doing?
-What's happening?
You got the memo?
-Yeah, it's cracklin'.
-Shit.
Ever since I heard
that Elias said I was a fuckboy to Sarah,
I've been feeling really hurt.
I wouldn't do that to someone.
I don't know why he thinks
he can get away with doing it to me.
-Take a spot near the fire.
-Yeah. Beautiful.
-Relax and settle in.
-Thank you.
How's that?
Getting the drum beat by Elias.
It's upset you. So…
I think we need to get that sage
and smoke the shit out of you.
Bless each other.
Might as well talk it out and sort it out?
Yeah, just go.
-Yes, Mom and Dad.
-We got your back.
El.
Reckon we can have a little chat?
-Yeah. Is that all right?
-Yeah. Let's do it.
They're going. Okay.
At least they're talking now.
-How you been?
-Yeah, mate.
Look, we're friends, right?
I've got your back
and supposedly you have mine.
At Cai's exhibition, right?
-Yeah.
-I sat down and had a chat with Sarah.
And she's got this idea that I'm a fuckboy
and I've got no substance.
-Yeah.
-I asked her where she got the idea from.
She actually said that she asked you
a few questions, and you actually said,
"Yeah. Nathan's a fuckboy.
He's got no substance."
Whatever else was said.
She asked me a direct question.
She goes, "My initial read of Nathan
was that he's a bit of a fuckboy. Is he?"
I'm like, "Yeah, he is. He's promiscuous."
Oh, my God!
You are, by nature, since I've known you.
Oh, my God. You're fucking… Okay.
If you think I'm this fuckboy,
then stop being my friend.
Because the nights, for you,
seem to always go in one direction.
-You're a young dude.
-Oh, my God!
Being promiscuous
is not the worst thing in the world.
He's a known fuckboy
and this isn't any new information.
Dude, why are you constantly
running away from this thing
and constantly acting out that character?
Why do you kind of call people out?
What is your problem?
It's different when
someone asks you a question.
Let me live my life and you live yours.
If someone wants to get close to you,
what they're basing everything on is like,
"Is he like this or is he not?"
I won't be like, "No. He's not."
You know what? How about this?
I've got a true opinion of you in my head.
You're an egotistical fuck.
And I also think that you are
seriously, seriously insecure.
You're an idiot.
It's frustrating and it blows my mind.
I feel like he was trying
to get between Sarah and I.
He's never gonna apologize.
He lives his life
in the only way that he thinks is correct.
And is unapologetic about it.
You don't do this to people.
Are you okay?
Come here. What happened? I heard you.
No. It's actually…
-Well, you seem frustrated--
-No. He's got a real opinion of me.
-It's pissing me off.
-What is his opinion of you?
He's just hammering me with like,
"You are the fuckboy. You are…"
-He's saying that to you?
-Yeah, sitting there right now.
He's sitting there
saying you're a fuckboy?
If that's how you're gonna act
and what you do, roll with it.
Be the fun, party fuckboy.
Whatever you want to be.
Why go spend all this time
trying to paint another picture
and try to build this other persona
that's not in line with your actions?
How about you come and get to know me?
-That's not nice.
-You don't know who I am.
I'd rather have an enemy talk shit
about me than a friend talk shit.
No.
Do you feel like what happened
was tit for tat?
-Do you feel like--
-The whole conversation felt like that.
Both of you entered that space and--
Yeah and he said,
"I think you're egotistical and insecure."
End of the day, it shows how weak he is
and how insecure he is
and how unstable he is.
It took me by surprise
that he's going to throw something
so sensitive in my face, regardless
of the truth of the matter or not.
It's a dog act and he's a bit of a dog.
-Hey.
-Hello.
-How you doing?
-How are you?
There they go. Look at them.
Nathan and Elias go back.
They have history.
They're good friends
and since Sarah's moved to town,
I think that's changed
the dynamic of their friendship.
You guys all good?
No. Well, I just said,
"Hey, look. Apparently you think
I'm this, this, this and this."
And he was like, "That's what you are."
And I was like, "Well, we're friends."
You know what I mean?
"If that's who you think I am at least
get to know me on a deeper level."
There's been so much drama.
If you want to hang out,
let's go do something. Let's go have fun.
Let's go hang out.
I do care about you
and you know I want you to…
I want you to feel welcome here
and welcome in the friendship circle.
I think deep down the girls' real problem
with me is that they don't know me.
And I don't think they
can be bothered getting to know me.
But it seems to be how everyone
judges everyone here in Byron Bay.
I do feel bad, but…
It just seems like
she's causing all this drama.
Yeah.
I think it's sad that Nathan and Elias
are fighting over Sarah
because they've been friends for a while
and a girl shouldn't come between them.
Just go back to the Gold Coast.
We're being summoned.
It's time.
The tribal council is about to speak.
All right, beautiful people.
Let's all sit by the fire.
Make yourself at home
in this beautiful place.
There's quite a bit of drama
unfolding in the group.
I can feel the energy
not being completely balanced.
I want to bring people back together.
Thank you so much for coming here tonight.
The idea of this gathering
is to bring about a level of mindfulness,
groundedness and healing
that needs to be brought into the group.
We're here tonight,
surrounded by the fire elements.
It correlates
to burning off the internal deadwood.
There's no need for it anymore.
It can be burnt away.
And that creates space
for forests, for greenery, for diversity.
So, from my heart to all your hearts,
to the universe,
thank you so much for being here tonight.
-Thank you, Sim.
-Thanks, Simmy.
Go, Simba.
Simba!
My eyes are now just like…
This is just so powerful.
Simba!
-That was amazing.
-Oh, my God.
I haven't been able to be myself in Byron.
And I hate that because
I only know how to be myself.
It's made me want to go home.
I haven't been back to the Gold Coast
since I moved to Byron.
And it's crazy how an hour up the coast
can feel like a million miles away.
With all the shit that's going on,
I just really needed to come up here
and be where I feel the most comfortable.
Mom.
-Hi!
-Hi.
Bonjour, Sarah.
How are you?
-Are you hungry?
-Yeah.
-Let's eat.
-Yes!
My mom's from the Seychelles.
So, even though
she's lived in Australia for many years,
the Creole culture
is incredibly important to our family.
There you go!
I hope you like it.
-Thank you. You're the best.
-Okay.
I've felt like an outsider
so many times in my life.
And that's how I've been feeling in Byron.
And I know
that Mum knows exactly how I feel.
-It's so nice to be here.
-Coming home?
-Yeah.
-Move back home.
How's the move going?
Are you happy?
It's been a challenge.
So, I thought, moving to Byron,
I would work on my album,
meet some creative people,
be able to connect.
And… Yeah. It's just been pretty lonely.
I've struggled a bit to…
-Make friends.
-Make friends?
-Yeah.
I hung out with one girl,
Hannah, yesterday,
and she told me that the girls
have been talking shit about me.
Really? That's low.
-Yeah.
-That's not good.
I don't know. Some days are tough
and I think I want
to move back to the Gold Coast.
-It's sad to hear that, love.
-Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know.
-You want a hug?
-Yeah.
Come.
Poor thing.
They've been making
nasty comments behind my back.
It's so upsetting.
And it's just making me feel like
I don't want to stay in Byron.
The Sarah I know
wouldn't let all these
things happen to her.
Yeah.
I always admired you for the way
you stand up for yourself.
Yeah. I was much happier
when I took care of it myself.
I always admired that in you.
That's so sweet. Thanks, Mum.
Mum's right. The Sarah she knows
would never put up with bullies.
I've been biting my tongue
for far too long. Enough is enough.
I don't want to be this person anymore.
I want to feel like me again.
So, I don't know
how it's going to go down, but…
we'll see what happens.