-What did Nathan say?
-That you said I was fake.
Nathan would never say that.
-He did.
-It's not true.
Nathan's not a liar.
But he did say it.
I'm so sorry.
I don't care who told you what,
but right now this is Elle's event--
You can't out-grieve the widow.
You're more upset than Elle.
No. I'm upset because I don't want
this to take away from Elle's event.
Just leave.
I've had enough.
-I think at the end of the day--
-Let's go.
I'm sick of this shit.
-Can I just say something?
-Where's Nathan?
Nathan's coming here.
I need to talk to Nathan.
I always get in the middle
of some situations.
I mean, I'm friends with everyone.
I'm friends with Nathan.
I'm friends with Elle.
Whatever Elle's issue is,
she needs to sort it out
so everyone can move on.
-Dude.
-What?
You've been saying
that I called Sarah fake.
She felt like
she's not been included into--
-I don't give a fuck how she feels.
-Listen to me.
No. I'm gonna tell you right now.
She said that you said specifically.
I literally came in
with the best intentions
and I'm being made to feel like I'm crazy.
-Everyone's like, "He said this--"
-You're not crazy.
It doesn't make sense
why Nathan would say that.
If it's not true.
Hannah also said it.
It's the same thing.
It's that Elle is saying something.
There's a fight happening there now.
-How she can't be trusted--
-Fucking hell.
I think I need to leave.
Yeah. I need to leave.
-I'm gonna take this and go.
-Okay.
She poured her heart out
and said that all of these people
have been talking about her.
She doesn't feel liked.
I said, "I have to agree."
Then she goes, "Was it Elle?"
You have said stuff about her.
I've said specifically,
"I still don't know who she is."
I never said she's fake.
-Okay. But get this.
-Get me.
I feel like Sarah is driving
a wedge between Nathan and I.
And to be honest with you,
it hurts my heart a bit.
What's going on? Talk to me. Come here.
I feel like I should leave.
I don't wanna cause a bigger scene
than what's already happened.
I wanted to talk to Elle
because I've been hearing so much shit.
It's the first chance
I got to talk to Elle.
She flat-out denied it.
Now I feel super gaslit
and super blindsided.
I feel bad for Sarah
just 'cause she's not done
anything wrong to anyone
and people are giving her a tough go.
People have judged you
for the way that they perceive you
and that's why I'm here to back you up.
My whole goal here
is to make you feel welcome.
And you are very welcome here.
I think it's nice that he came out
to make sure that I was okay,
but Elle was incredibly convincing
and it's starting to make me doubt Nathan.
So I'm feeling, honestly, awful.
So I've said what I need to say
and I'm just done now.
I respect your decision.
-I wish you would stay.
-Sorry.
I got the door.
When I moved to Byron, I thought
I was gonna make new friends.
I realize more than ever
how isolated I am,
in that I don't have solid friendships
with most of these people here.
And I feel like nothing I do
would be good enough for them.
At Elle's fundraiser yesterday,
Jade and I decided we should
cut the crap, have a conversation,
see if we could move on with our lives.
Ever since Cai's exhibition,
things between Jade and I
have been awkward.
I am accusing him
of buying fake followers,
and every party I see him at,
he is throwing daggers my way.
It's a small industry
and it's bad for my business.
I'm nervous about meeting with Alex
because I don't trust Alex.
Hello?
-Hey.
-How are you?
You bought vodka.
This is kind of like the peace offering.
I've invited him into my home
and I just don't know
which way this is gonna go.
I was a bit nervous, with you coming here,
because I just really don't know
what's gonna come out of your mouth.
The reason I came up to you and said,
"Do you wanna chat one-on-one?"
is I wanted to have
a conversation away from everyone.
Just to see if we can just talk, I guess.
Obviously,
at Cai's exhibition I upset you.
And I feel like you wanted blood.
Like you were out to--
I was ready to stab you to the neck.
I was ready to go.
You should take your talent to Turkey,
get 1,2 million followers from Turkey
so they can do what I've done.
You look here, as a talent manager,
absolutely fucking pathetic. Pathetic.
You were trying to discredit my work
that I have worked so fucking hard for.
For ten years now, I've had my phone
every single second of my life,
doing everything
for my fans and my followers.
I took it as a personal attack
and I lost it because it hit me hard.
I don't think Alex could ever understand
what Instagram is to me.
My followers are my best friends.
These people give me joy.
These people make me happy.
You think you're the only person
trying to discredit my Instagram?
No. I've had enough of it.
I won't to put up with it anymore.
My whole life, people have done
what you've done to me
at Cai's art exhibition.
I come from a small country town.
All the time, people would
turn around and push me down
because I'm different. Because I am gay.
I didn't have any friends.
Weirdly, you and I
are the same in a lot of ways.
You know, going to the school,
I was like the fat, pimply, redheaded kid.
I look at the people around here
and instantly I'm like,
"I don't really fit in here."
I'll be honest,
my natural defensive mechanism
when I'm uncomfortable is to kind of
go on the offensive and poke fun at things
because that's my sense of humor.
It's like escargot, darl.
I'm a really acquired taste.
Pardon?
I don't know what escargot is.
-Snails.
-Okay.
He has a vocabulary
that is a lot bigger than mine.
And he 100% would have went to Year 12.
Wait.
This is my white flag.
-It's a tissue but that's the white flag.
-Okay.
I'm sure we can find some common ground.
Well, I hope so. Yeah.
After listening to him, I'm starting
to understand him a little bit better.
There is a little bit of humanity there.
But this is not peace, this is a truce.
And if Alex breaks the truce,
get ready for round two.
So, look, apology's out of the way…
-There we go.
-Just get smashed?
-No.
-Why not?
-I do not wanna get smashed.
-I do.
-What color are you doing?
-I don't know. What do you reckon?
-Pink. Do pink.
-Pink? Match your jacket?
-Yep. I reckon.
-We can do that.
I think with Nathan,
I feel sorry for the poor guy
after that little confrontation
at Elle's fundraiser.
Hello.
Look who it is.
How are you? Good?
-Hello.
How are things?
-Speak of the devil.
-Good.
-So, Elle's fundraiser?
-Yeah.
-Haven't seen you since then.
All I wanna do is just protect Sarah.
I really just want everyone,
particularly the girls,
to just see who she really is.
She's not fake
and she's not hiding behind anything.
She's just a bit scared at the moment.
Look, Sarah likes to come across
as a very strong, independent woman
-that doesn't give a fuck.
-Yeah.
But, at the end of the day, she does care.
When she goes home, she gets rattled
about what people think of her,
what people say about her.
She feels like she gets judged
before people get to know her.
I was like, "I hate it as well."
With Sarah,
I think you need to be careful.
We obviously care
about you, no matter what.
-We'll have your back no matter what.
-Yeah.
But I think… Just be careful.
You don't wanna lose too many friends.
It's so hard.
I'm torn between my best friend, Elle,
and my new squeeze, Sarah,
but I'm also trying to keep the peace
amongst all our friends.
It just sucks.
I can't believe I'm in this position.
How do you feel about her? You still…
I'm spending time with Sarah.
I'm getting to know her.
I think she's a great girl.
For me, can you just give her
a chance and get to know her?
She's just trying to make it down
in Byron. You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I haven't heard Nathan
speak about a girl like this before.
Maybe I misjudged Sarah.
Makes you want to get to know her more.
I mean, there's a lot going on
for Nathan right now.
Have you spoken to Elias
since the fundraiser?
No. I haven't seen
or spoken to Elias in ages.
And then he sent me this text.
He goes, "Time to hash it out."
"Meet me at the car park by the beach."
That's like a bike racks
after school kinda thing.
-Have you seen this?
-What?
-Wait for it.
-Here we go.
It's pretty funny. Wait.
"Just biding my time."
-Put a mouth guard in going to meet him.
-Then look at this next one.
-No.
-"But it's inevitable."
That's pretty heavy.
I mean, do you think that's about you?
-I don't know.
-I reckon that's about you.
-It probably is.
-Yeah.
Elias has said all this shit about me
and called me a fuck boy.
Then he's the one all pissed off.
I've honestly just had enough now.
I'm gonna go sort this out.
Byron. It is a small town.
So the moment you have bad blood,
you have to face it.
All of this drama has come about
because he talked
shit about me behind my back.
He makes it quite clear
that he thinks he's better than me.
I know there's
a clear difference in our morality
and when morals don't align,
there's always going to be conflict.
And all I've done, in saying
that he is in fact a fuck boy,
is kind of hit that nerve
right on the head
and he's reacted.
He thinks I'd do anything I possibly can
just to sleep with someone
and that's my only goal.
It actually really irritates me.
Obviously, I wanted
to have a chat with you.
-Yeah.
-About what happened.
I just wanna get
to the bottom of it all and understand
where these kind of feelings come from.
I feel like
there's definitely an underlying
feeling of resentment from you.
I didn't go and call you a fuck boy.
Someone asked me if you were, right?
I have my opinions about you.
I think that you might be arrogant,
but it doesn't mean when they ask me,
I'm gonna say you're this
and that. 'Cause I'm your mate.
I'm meant to be your friend.
Friends have each other's back.
You said, "Yes, I believe that of you.
Yes, I backed my actions in saying that."
-All I wanted you to do is say sorry.
-I gave--
I was transparent.
She asked a direct question.
-I gave a direct answer.
-Then you stand by and go…
You did say, "Yes."
And that's what you think of me.
And you said that to my face.
Why would I just go, "Fair enough, mate."
Shake hands. Sweet.
We're still friends. All good.
I think Nathan is gonna be someone
who's always going to try and rationalize
and justify anything he does
no matter how fucked up it is.
He will find a way in his mind
to make him feel like the bigger man.
This whole thing stems from you being
upset about this fuck boy thing.
Why is that an issue?
Why would a mate go behind my back?
Then Sarah's like, "I don't wanna
hang out with this guy anymore…"
What are you doing with Sarah?
Are you dating her?
What does it matter to you?
Because compiling actions lead
to my perspective of someone.
So Elias clearly has an issue with me
because he is into Sarah.
And that's because
he's jealous and insecure.
But fuck that shit.
Your perspective is fucking this big.
-You're so narrow-minded. You are.
-Yeah, right. Okay.
It's crazy.
I'm not the first one to realize that.
Cool. I said from the very start
of this whole thing
that by the end of this
we'll either be like best mates
or be fucking enemies.
Your opinion to me means fuck all
because I don't agree with you.
We don't see eye to eye.
We don't
and I'm happy to leave it at that.
That's it.
I can't even be bothered
with this guy anymore.
I've got enough friends.
I don't need him in my life.
The worst part about all of this is
Elias talked shit about me
behind by my back to Sarah.
I'm just hoping that Sarah and I
can move on with things
without all of this bullshit
going on in the background.
How've you been?
Really good.
Just decompressing after the fundraiser.
Totally.
I've been dying to see Elle
ever since her fundraiser.
Just to kind of see
what her take is on it.
But mainly for Elle to kind of own up
to what she said about Sarah.
How did the rest of your night go?
Yeah, it was good.
Obviously, I was super stoked
to raise the funds that we needed.
But at the same time, of course,
Sarah and her approaching us
for that whole conversation
really got me down.
It's ridiculous.
I've never said she's fake.
You kind of did say it.
-At Cai's.
-I've never said that.
Look, I always want to give
someone the benefit of the doubt,
but, honestly,
there's something fake there.
Elle did call Sarah fake.
You don't need it deny to me.
I was there. I heard you.
It's a tricky situation
because I think everyone
has said things about her.
But what I've actually said,
and I know I said
that she's not presenting herself
in a way that I think she truly she is.
And that's fine.
There's this level of authenticity
we're not seeing from her.
There's a bit of a difference.
She said, "Fake."
Just say the word "fake."
I don't know
why we're saying other fancy words,
which mean the same thing.
-I'm not saying she's fake.
-Yeah.
You did say it, but I was never
going to not have your back.
-So I was like, "No, no, no."
-No. I didn't say that.
Clearly she's trying to
create a divide between Nathan and I.
Nathan and I are super close.
When it's just us two in the house
we're like this really cute,
old married couple.
I had my concerns
about Sarah from the start.
She's from the Gold Coast.
It's all about
short dresses and fake boobs.
Just doesn't seem like
that's a good fit for Nathan
because Nathan is
a really authentic person.
Now there's been a massive disconnect
and his whole thought process
is that I haven't made an effort
to get to know her.
Which is true. But at the same time,
she hasn't made
the effort to get to know me.
You reckon that you're protective over him
when he sees a new girl or anything?
No.
-No?
-No.
To be honest,
I don't think Elle is being that fair
with Nathan in this new relationship.
Maybe she has feelings for him.
Elle was incredibly
convincing in telling me
that she hadn't said
anything bad about me.
And it's just made me really confused.
I don't know who to believe now.
-Hi.
-Hello. How are you?
-Good. How are you?
-Good.
I'm looking forward
to seeing Nathan today,
but I'm hoping he can ease my anxieties.
-This is nice.
-Yeah.
And that he can prove to me
that I can trust him.
-Cheers.
To another tequila.
Sarah and I have had some difficulties
since the whole fuck boy thing.
But now I need to make sure
that she knows,
when it comes down to it,
I stand by her and I'm there to back her.
I was cut that you had to leave
Elle's fundraiser so early.
Yeah. I couldn't have gone back in
after I had spoken to Elle.
It was just my time to go.
She basically looked me in the eye
and was like, "I didn't say these things."
-She's quite convincing, isn't she?
-She called me a liar.
She was like, "You're lying."
It was so intense.
Yeah.
I was like, "I'm not going to sit
and argue with you and a ruin your event."
It surprised me to hear
that you actually confronted Elle.
-That's a ballsy move. It is.
-Why?
'Cause you don't want to fuck with her.
She says this to me all the time.
She goes, "If you try to fuck me,
I'll fuck you ten times harder."
I'm like, "Oh, my God."
She's so hectic like that.
We had a massive blowup about it.
She was like,
"Why would you throw me under the bus?"
"Why would you do this?
And say that stuff?"
But I said, "You did say this stuff."
And she goes,
"No. I didn't."
And she denied it to me as well.
It doesn't make me feel good
that Nathan and Elle are fighting.
They obviously have had
a friendship long before I moved to town.
But to hear that Nathan is standing by me
makes me feel really good.
It's got to the point now where,
it's not really somebody
that I wanna be friends with.
Yeah. I understand.
And I'm definitely not gonna kiss her ass
and try to make her like me.
-Yeah.
-I'm just over it.
It's like changing
how I feel about the whole place
and the whole experience of being here.
That's not good to hear.
I don't like that.
I know for a fact,
and I've said this to Elle before,
you're a great person.
And, I swear to God, I'm in your corner.
I'm in your corner. Backing you hard.
I'm really grateful
that you've stood up for me
because there's not many people
in this town
that I've met that are genuine.
I want you to know that I appreciate that.
-It's all good.
-Okay. Thank you.
Nathan's got my back.
After everything we've gone through,
the fact that he's still
standing by me is fucking cool.
It's not the first time I've heard,
you know, someone like you
trying to move down to Byron,
to have a change of scenery and whatnot,
and completely feel like
you're being alienated.
-Yes.
-Which sucks.
Maybe we should go
and spend the night in the hinterlands.
-Get out of Byron.
-Really?
Really?
I mean, yeah. If you wanna.
It's freaking amazing.
-Yeah. Okay.
-Yeah.
Come here.
It means so much to me
that Nathan is in my corner.
I don't know why
Elle has a problem with me.
-Let's get out of here.
-Yeah.
I feel like she is kind of annoyed
that I've taken Nathan away from her.
Look at this day. It's gonna be so good.
Beautiful.
How's the surf looking?
-It's kind of big.
-Looks good though.
-It's good.
-Will you get out there?
Yeah, definitely.
This is standard Byron.
Amazing day,
amazing waves, drinks on the beach.
Reckon it'll put
everyone in the best mood.
Is that Sarah with Nathan?
Good day for skimming.
-What's that?
-Skipping rocks.
Yes.
Maybe we should do that instead.
There is tension between everyone
in the group at the moment.
But it is one good opportunity
to make a big effort to get to know Sarah.
It would take
so much of a load off Nathan.
If Sarah would give me a bit of time,
maybe I might feel the same way
and I might get along with her.
-Hello. How are you guys?
-What a surprise.
-Hi.
-How are you?
-Good. How are you?
-Good.
-This is nice. Your whole outfit.
-Thanks. You look cute.
Feel free, esky down here.
-Thank you for inviting us.
-How are you?
-Hello.
-Hello. How are you?
So who else is coming?
There's one person,
I'm not too sure if they're 100% coming.
I have a feeling
that Elle might be a bit jealous
because she's just not coping
with Sarah and Nathan dating.
I did try and get to the bottom of it.
But I think
I need to ask Nathan about that.
She may still be coming.
I just have a feeling.
It wouldn't surprise me
if she didn't come.
-Babe, did you want a rosé or something?
-I'd love a rosé.
Are you gonna have a rosé, Sarah?
-I'm all right with water for now.
-Yeah?
Yeah.
All right.
Yeah, boy!
-How are we?
-How're you doing?
Yay, team!
-Oh, my God!
-Hello!
-Hey, brother.
-How are you?
-Hello!
-Where's your surfboard?
-I can't surf for shit.
-More of a Lauren thing.
-Here's Elias.
-What's cracking?
-Simba!
-How are you?
I think it's good to have
a bit of it beach day like this.
Yeah.
Just hope everyone
has a chat and has a good time.
Yeah. Leave
everything out there in the surf.
-Pretty much.
-Yeah.
How are you?
-I feel awkward.
-Why? What's going?
I haven't seen everyone
since the incident.
-I don't really know how to be.
-You guys want some more?
Yes, please.
Be you, darl. You were never in the wrong.
I want to just get over it and move on.
But I don't know if Elle's coming today
and I don't know how to move forward.
I'm spending heaps of time with Nathan,
but he lives with Elle
and I'm hearing two different things.
Reckon she was looking into your face,
saying, "I never said it."
But actually did?
-Yeah.
-She is a psychopath.
How about I do a little groundwork?
I'll have a conversation with Elle.
Sarah deserves some
straight up answers from Elle.
If she won't tell me,
maybe she'll tell you.
And if you can do some recon,
I would love you forever.
Bit of barbeque action?
Do you guys need a top up of rosé?
Take all of that bathing suit off,
Elias, now, you sexy dog.
It nearly came off.
I needed this. Beach day.
-Hi, Ally.
-Hello, darl.
How have you been? Have you been busy?
Yeah, I've been all right. I love this.
Thanks.
I wanna find out
if Elle has said nasty things about Sarah.
When challenged on it,
Jess is the kind of person to come clean.
At the Save the Mermaids party,
there was a bit of tension
because Sarah's been
talking to me for a while
about people saying that she was fake.
Okay.
And she brought it up with Elle
and Elle just flat out said,
"I never said that."
But there was this story going around.
I think it was you, Lauren and Hannah,
discussing Sarah after Cai's event.
Is that something that happened?
So, I was standing with Hannah
and Elle and Sas around the fire.
And they were talking about…
Yeah, they were talking about that.
They were saying that they don't know her
and they think she's a bit fake.
Perfect. Now I've got you.
Elle, you called her fake
and now you're about to get called on it.
All right. Elle's here.
-Hey, hello.
-How are you?
-Good. How are you?
-Good.
What's happening?
-Hello.
-Hi, gorgeous. How are you?
-You good?
-Good.
I'm one of your best mates,
and I still don't understand this whole
situation with Elle, you and Sarah.
That threesome relationship
does not sound like
the good type of threesome.
That's pretty much it.
-Elle! Hi, honey.
-Hi!
Hello.
-Are you good?
-Yeah. Good.
How are you feeling after your event?
Were you okay? You and Sarah okay?
That was a really shit time
for her to do that.
You know, there's a time and place
for those sorts of conversations.
-My fundraiser wasn't the time to do that.
-No. Not at all.
She did actually really hurt me
because she spoke about Nathan,
saying that I said
those things about Sarah.
-Did you call Sarah fake?
-No.
See, we just talked and Jess said you did.
-Like…
-When?
Throwing me under the bus.
But, yeah. You said that she was fake.
But you weren't saying it in a bitchy way.
You were saying it backing Nathan.
Jess is meant to be a friend.
But Alex just dropped a bomb
between Jess and I.
This Sarah debacle
actually feels ridiculous.
All the girls were basically going around
saying that they didn't like her.
And I said I need
to get to know her more.
I don't know enough about her.
What she's done so far,
the way she's presented herself,
the comments she's made… I think--
I can't--
You think she's trying
to project something she's not?
Yeah. I don't know.
It's lazy to call someone fake
without knowing them.
The way she's presenting herself
isn't truly who she is. That's--
I don't know. The whole thing just
comes across as very Mean Girls to me.
-No.
-I feel like--
Sarah's my friend.
I'm not gonna listen to it.
It's very Mean Girls.
-You guys have your Mean Girls--
-But that's what you're like.
You're like that too, mate.
I didn't mean for it to be like that.
I didn't realize that was the situation.
-And I said--
-What do you mean you didn't realize?
-Of course you did.
-No. I didn't…
When we were talking
about it, it was casual.
I was really annoyed at Jess.
I think she handled that so poorly.
When I said "fake,"
I didn't think that was gonna
make you feel like I was telling Alex
all this shit about you.
'Cause I was not doing that at all.
Okay. That just happened
in front of my face sort of thing.
You think I was talking shit about you?
That was an innocent conversation.
He's just a drama queen.
That's not how it happened.
He's like, "You said Elle said this."
That's not what I said at all.
-We were having a conversation--
-You just did.
-No. I said--
-You just did, Jess.
How? How? How did I say that?
-How did I say that?
-Oh, my God.
Elle's trying to keep up
with this image that she's an angel
and she would never say
anything wrong about someone.
Don't make me out to be a liar
because you don't wanna
own up to what you said.
Pissed me off, definitely.
So what happened?
I was talking to Jess
about this conversation.
Jess said, "Yeah, it happened."
Elle called you fake.
They all called you fake.
I was like, "Well…"
-Elle's denying she's ever said that.
-Yeah.
So, when I was speaking to Elle, I said,
"Did you say this about Sarah?"
She goes, "No."
And I threw Jess under the bus,
"Well, Jess said you did."
I think Elle wants the world to believe
that she's a really good person,
and she's a perfect person, which is
a pretty exhausting title to hold up.
I think she just needs to be real with
herself and admit it when she fucks up.
What is it that I present
when you don't know who I am
that you think is fake?
I have no idea. I don't know.
I'm just sick of it, you know?
Grow the fuck up.
It's been really challenging not having
any close girlfriends in this town.
Just to debrief on everything
and have somebody close by
that understands what I'm going through.
No worries, darl. My hands are cold.
-But your heart is warm.
-My heart is warm.
Hey. So, Sarah?
-Yeah. I mean…
-Tell me more.
Have you seen her
since we saw you at the shaping?
Yes.
And?
-Well, I mean…
-Tell me. What happened?
Yeah. We had a little date.
It was cool and it was really nice.
-It was nice?
-Yeah.
We went for a couple of drinks,
and then we hung out
most of the night having drinks.
It was nice.
And then… Yeah.
Now we're just hand-holding these days.
You're hand-holding? Look at you.
-It makes me happy if you're happy.
-Thanks.
Come here.
Nathan does seem like
he has genuine, strong feelings for Sarah.
But I think there's a lot more going on
between Nathan and Elle.
I need to figure out
what the hell is going on.
What about Elle?
How is she taking it all?
She's not happy.
Look, I've tried to keep it a secret,
but we actually did…
Way, way, ages ago.
One drunken night we ended up kissing.
Really?
Fuck.
I should not have said that.
Nathan's playing with some serious fire.
So, if you and Elle do have history,
do you reckon she's jealous?
Yes.
I'm so excited. This looks very good.
You'll like it. It looks like a lot of
green and health, but it's actually good.
-Need a good green smoothie.
-I know.
This is what we need
from eating burgers and stuff.
-Now we need greens.
-A good detox from yesterday.
What happened with you and Elle?
-Oh, my God. It was so annoying.
-Yeah.
I was talking to Alex
and I briefly said to him
that we were all talking about Sarah
and how we don't get along with her.
He was kind of fishing. He kept bringing
Sarah up and then Elle walked over.
And then all of a sudden
he just throws it at her like,
"Jess told me that you said
Sarah was fake."
Then Elle, her face just like went…
-To the devil and she was literally--
-The daggers.
Yeah, she was ready to like take me down.
She was gaslighting me. She was trying to
make me look… And I, in that moment,
was like, "Am I making this up?
Did this not happen?"
That's how confused I felt.
'Cause she was looking at me
like I was just so out of line.
It's interesting. This happened to me.
So, I caught up with Elle
for a drink and I said to her,
"You called Sarah fake."
And she just looked at me and was like,
"I did not say that."
I was like, "But you did."
She's just
making us look like we're lying.
Lying. Yeah.
Elle is making Jess
and I look like idiots.
And I have all this juicy goss
that explains everything
about the way that she's been behaving.
So, just between you and I…
Keep it right on the down-low.
Nathan told me that
Elle and him have hooked up in the past.
-Yeah.
-No way.
The whole thing is all a little bit funny.
Just like a one-night stand?
What are we talking here?
So Nathan told me they had hooked up once.
When someone says that,
it's probably a few more times.
-They live together.
-Yeah.
It would have happened
multiple times for sure.
-Yeah.
-So maybe it's not like…
-A protective friend.
-That's the thing.
-It's not a protective friend.
-She's maybe a bit jealous.
She's 100% jealous.
It's all starting to make sense now why
Elle is lying about calling Sarah fake.
Because they are the love triangle.
It's not Elias.
It's Elle, Sarah and Nathan.
I feel like this just makes
so much more sense now.
It just didn't add up why she was reacting
so harsh to such a small, minor situation.
So, Elle's mad.
And I think it's like,
"I have feelings for you" mad.
And so think about it,
how does Elle's partner Stav feel?
-Oh, my God. I forgot about Stav.
-Yeah.
I don't think Stav knows
that they've hooked up.
-What the fuck?
-I know.
And also Sarah.
You know,
this triangle has just become so messy.
This will catch up with Elle.
Byron Bay is such a small town.
Nothing stays a secret for long here.
It's all just going to come to the surface
and it's going to explode.
So hectic.