It's been so long since I've seen ya
My body, oh, how I miss ya
I'm so tired of screaming
But I can't help feeling that
This could be us
But they're keeping us apart
I came to Byron to take my music seriously
and to build an audience.
Byron is like a hub for creative people.
Hello.
Hey. Where are you?
I'm on the way out to go see Sarah.
This studio address. Is this for real?
I'm driving through a paddock.
Definitely the address.
Why? What are you looking at?
Oh, my God. There's a fucking cow.
Sarah has a voice. She can sing.
I think there's potential
for her to make a lot of money
and I want to tap into that brand.
Louis Vuitton doesn't buy itself.
-How are you?
-Good. How are you?
Alex is gonna be a big part
of helping establish my career,
and I really think
that we're becoming friends.
So how are you feeling after the party?
It was a fun party.
I'm really sad you left.
-Who'd you like?
-Everyone.
But it's good you left 'cause you would've
rolled your eyes the whole time.
I had RSI from rolling my eyes.
I need to go see
an optometrist after this.
Do you know who I found fascinating
at that party?
-Who?
-Jade.
-Hannah?
-Hi!
When he walked in,
the light hit all that Cartier jewelry.
-It nearly blinded me.
-Yeah.
I was like, "It's a walking disco ball."
-He's a whole vibe. Yeah.
-He is.
He has a million followers on Insta.
-So I went on and had a look.
-Yeah.
Something weird there.
I think his audience is a bit bullshit.
He might not be buying them,
but I don't know.
I just get annoyed
when people have inflated numbers.
If it's all bullshit…
Sorry, darl. I gotta call you on it.
Fake followers piss me off.
If you go up against my talent
for the same job with your fake followers
and you win it,
that's money that my talent should've got.
Do you know who I thought was fun? Nathan.
How you going? I'm Nathan.
-Hi. You look amazing.
-Alex.
-Sarah. Lovely to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I think Nathan's a fun time.
He actually invited me out
to show me around Byron.
Out of everyone at that party,
I'm really glad that Nathan's the one
that you're going to go on "a date"…
We're calling it a date?
He just said he'll show me around.
So for all I know, we could just be pals.
How are you cooking the salmon?
Gonna sear it in the pan.
Salmon, brocc and then--
-Brocc to make you rock?
-No.
-That's the chef's tea towel.
-I'm a chefette. I can borrow it.
Elle and I live together.
We've lived together
for about six months now.
I got the kangaroo whip now.
And she's quite flirty with me.
-You want this.
-No.
You want this. I know.
No, I don't. No.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Love me.
I honestly think it's funny
when Elle gets kind of jealous
about me hanging out
or talking about other girls.
'Cause she's got a boyfriend.
-'Sup, guys? What's cooking?
-Hey, Stavie.
I guess Elle's boyfriend, Stav,
is in Byron maybe once every two weeks.
I heard a big smack upstairs.
What's going on?
Nathan whipped me with a tea towel.
Fun.
How long you around for, Stav?
I'm only here for a short while.
-I've gotta go back to Magnetic Island.
-Yeah.
You'd think that when Stav
comes back to town
that Elle would kind of like pull back
and not be so like lovey-dovey with me,
but she doesn't at all.
She still is like, "Love you… Oh, Nath."
Looking out the corner
of your eye and Stav's there.
Meet anyone interesting at the party?
There was Sarah.
-She was nice.
-Is she from Byron?
She's from the Goldie.
She's moved here though.
Do you like her?
From what I've seen, she's pretty cool.
I feel like Nathan can do
so much better than Sarah.
She's from the Gold Coast
and the Gold Coast
is all about fake boobs, big lips.
Nathan's not interested in that 'cause
Nathan is a really authentic person.
She's a singer.
That's pretty cool. Girl with talent.
Yeah.
So do you want to go on a date with her?
Yeah. I'll take her out
for dinner or something.
Yeah.
Why don't we crack out the wine?
My Johansen event is coming up
and it is my first-ever catwalk.
My business is all online,
so it's super stressful
because I'm trying to make sure
I represent the same image
that I have online, in person.
Oh, my God.
Jade! How are you?
-Babe! Hi!
-Hey! Look at you with all your clothes.
This is so pretty.
-Thank you.
-Hey!
-How are you?
-Good. Good.
I am Australia's number one
most followed male influencer.
I came to Byron to connect
with some other influencers.
We all just want acceptance and
it is so good to have a friend in fashion.
I'm stressed about what to wear
to the Johansen launch. I've no idea.
So the location is super cream tones
and jungle theme.
Perfect.
So I love this because
everyone's going to be in creamy colors.
-Perfect.
-You know, that kind of vibe?
-Thank you, baby. I was stressing out.
-You'll be okay.
You're gonna look amazing.
I would absolutely die if I walked in and
seen somebody in the same outfit as me.
I'd be so embarrassed I would leave.
That to me would just be…
You need to try on this puffer.
Let me grab it.
-This is the jacket.
-Oh, my God.
This is so you.
-Look at this. Yes.
-I love it.
By the time I'm done with you,
you're gonna be wearing
all of these clothes just 24/7.
-Yes!
-I love it.
I'm obsessed with this.
I need to pay you for this.
No. It's a gift.
I'll smash it on my socials then.
Let's get a mirror shot.
This is gonna sell out because of you.
-Babe, Hannah's Ibiza party.
-I know.
-Now, that was a whole new…
-Interesting, right?
Did you end up getting the…
An apology from her?
She ended up apologizing,
but it wasn't sincere.
So, yes, I…
-Sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-I am sorry.
You're sorry? Are you actually sorry?
I expected more from her,
like, "I've missed you."
And like, "I love you
and I want it to be better."
But it wasn't like that.
I don't know. I was disappointed.
-Did you invite her to the launch?
-Yeah.
In my heart, I want her there
because we were friends for so long
and she's seen me grow this brand.
She's seen how hard I work,
but I just don't want her making it
about anything but Johansen
and the brand, you know?
'Cause if she can be on her best behavior,
-I'm happy for her to come.
-Yeah.
I didn't work six years to have
Hannah do something at my event.
It's so weird because
she actually sent me a text message.
She's like, "J, darling.
So lovely to meet you the other night
and thank you for my crystal."
"You're so sweet. Would you like to come
to the Crystal Castle with me?"
Oh, my goodness.
No way.
I'm so nervous
about meeting up with Hannah.
When it comes to their feud,
I am team Jess,
but after the party, I definitely feel
that Hannah and I can be friends.
Maybe I might go.
Yeah. 100% go
and don't judge her based off me.
Hannah's a lot of fun.
Just don't get on her bad side.
All right. Let's move around.
Simba and I met at the gym.
Yeah. It's about a eight-year
bromance with Simba.
-I knocked all of the padding out of them.
-Did you?
Simba's like this larger-than-life,
whimsical shamanic healer.
Bouncy. All right.
Let's see which chicken leg will win.
Come on. Body shots only.
You think the face is the body.
On the surface, me and Elias
seem like an unlikely friendship.
Okay. One, two, three, four.
He's in this world of modeling and surfing
and I'm a holistic health
and spiritual coach.
I'm a bit more of a hippie,
bit more alternative.
I don't think I'm an influencer.
I think I'm an inspirer.
That was good, man.
What a day.
How'd you find Hannah's party
the other day?
It was good. Pretty chill.
-Did you connect with anyone?
-Yeah.
-What was that girl--
-Sarah?
-Yeah!
-Yeah. She's a cool chick.
I think it's a bit more
beneath the surface
than initially meets the eye with her.
I had this weird moment
when she was talking about this saying
that she resonates with,
"jack of all trades, master of none."
I was like, "No way."
I took my ring off like, "Look at that."
It was a trippy moment. I was like…
Very cool. Maybe she picked up
on some sort of innate, kind of,
you know, undercurrent kind of vibe.
Yeah. I honestly think she did.
I'm like a jack of all trades
and a master of none.
What does that say?
Stop! No!
It was good to meet Sarah.
I think she's a deep thinker.
Hopefully she's going
to the Johansen event
because she's someone
I want to get to know a lot better.
We had a couple
of cool moments there for sure.
Yeah.
We were chatting, her, me and Nathan,
talking about who has
the biggest energy or whatever else.
She's just like,
"I think confidence is quiet."
"I like that. It's cool. Interesting."
Nathan offered to show Sarah around town,
but, to be honest,
Sarah made it pretty clear that she's
more in tune with myself than Nathan.
Go.
I'm pretty keen to show Sarah around town.
When I do things, I go to the nth degree.
If I do it, I do it right.
I love curating an experience
with someone.
I think Sarah's great,
and honestly, my heart's racing
and I don't know what to expect from this.
Hi.
Hi, baby.
How you doing?
Hi. Good. How are you?
I'm good.
Good to see you.
-You, too.
-This is Neo.
Hi, baby. Oh, my gosh. She's so cute.
Got vegan treats
'cause I remember you're vegan.
That's so sweet. I love that.
That's so nice.
When I saw the picnic set-up,
it definitely took me by surprise.
I didn't pick Nathan
for the romantic type.
Nathan made me feel
really comfortable, really quickly.
Cheers.
To moving to Byron.
Moving to Byron.
How you settling in?
It was hard moving somewhere,
not knowing anyone.
Yeah.
Especially in Byron where people feel like
they have to protect this place.
-They're so cautious of people coming in.
-I get that.
The perception of Byron,
it's like this hippie town.
So loving and so caring
and you're gonna be sitting in a circle,
playing bongos, singing,
and everyone's gonna invite you over.
-It's actually the opposite of that now.
-Yeah.
But I came here to find my people
and I definitely did that.
It's like if you're in a bad mood,
you think everybody's death-staring you,
and in a good mood,
you think everyone's friendly.
You've got no idea.
You know me, the other night,
running around dancing, being crazy.
Everyone's like,
"This guy's the most confident guy."
But I'm the least confident guy.
-I just know how to act confident.
-Really?
I wouldn't tell that about you.
I know. No one does.
But I understand 'cause
I've been a performer my whole life.
So I get when I have
to be out in social situations,
to turn it on
and be a certain type of person.
Yeah.
I definitely think I got to see
the real side of Nathan a little bit.
It was nice to hear him share
that he was a little bit more vulnerable
than what he leads on to everyone.
-Hi, baby. You're all wet.
-Hey, girl.
She's like…
So I'm gonna ask something of you.
I brought my ukulele down here and
I thought, "I want to do a little song."
-And if you wouldn't mind--
-I would love that.
-You can say no.
-No. I would love that.
If you can film me.
-For my Instagram.
-I can.
-But I wanna see you in action.
-Okay.
-Okay. Cool. Thank you.
-100%.
All right.
You look good. This is good.
Serenade me.
So I pulled you up
'Cause you're shady
But you pull me close
And the anger faded
You give me faraway vibes
You light me up with a smile
You're gonna wreck my good time
That was amazing.
Thank you.
-I think I fell in love today.
-Did you?
That was really intense.
I got goosebumps.
-Really?
-No, honestly.
-It was so nice.
-Thank you.
I wanna give you a hug.
-There's…
-I'll stand up.
There's some feels in that.
Thank you for that.
-Thank you for filming.
-That was amazing.
You're the first one to hear that song
'cause I just wrote it.
-So congratulations.
-That was insane.
Holy crap. I feel honored and blessed.
Thank you.
I was about to kiss you.
Really? No, you're joking.
I don't kiss on the first date.
Is it a date?
I thought we were hanging out
and getting the grand tour of Byron.
That's the thing--
-This is better. I'm not complaining.
-No. But after that, I was like, "Shit!"
"Maybe I need to show you
around Byron more."
'Cause that was pretty insane.
I do need to be shown
around Byron. So, yeah.
-Yeah. Right.
-This is cute.
For the first time since I got here,
I feel like I might actually fit in here.
I'm feeling nervous meeting Hannah
because things are not fine
between Jess and Hannah
and I feel a really strong bond
and alliance with Jess.
But, you know, I'm new to Byron
and I do want new friends,
so I'm willing to give it a shot.
I hope I can
bring them back together again.
Hey, babe.
I feel someone's energy next to me.
Yeah. It's me. It's Jade.
Hi.
How are you?
When I first met Jade,
I felt like our energies
were just high vibing.
What is this?
So this is…
It's an amethyst, right? But it's a geode.
What does a geode mean?
It means… If you put them together,
they're perfect…
They stick back together perfectly.
Crystal Castle is very Byron.
Let's have a walk around.
It's a lot different to what
I ever experienced in the Gold Coast.
Oh, my God. It's a dragon egg.
A what? A dragon egg?
I'm like… Look at this though!
-Are you meant to get in there?
-You kidding me?
Yeah.
Oh, my God. Let's squish in.
We go in?
Okay.
-Okay.
-Nice.
Are you feeling it?
I personally
am feeling…
The buzz?
Yeah.
-Are you not feeling the vibe?
-No.
Honestly, if the word "vibe" was invented,
this would be why.
Sitting inside a 120-million-year-old--
How do they know
it's 120 million years old?
Because no one's
120 million years old in real life.
How do they know that?
It's like when they find
dragon bones and stuff like that.
-Where do they find dragon bones?
-There's some in Australia.
Okay.
Dragon bones are not real.
Hannah is completely in her own world.
She's a new level of different
I've never met before.
But I'm here for it.
The rose quartz crystals behind us,
looking at the view.
Perfect.
When did you move here?
I only just moved here
literally last week.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-You're even yet to ground into Byron.
Have you made any friends?
-I have made some friends.
-Who?
Jess and Lauren.
I would love to bring Jess and Hannah
back together again.
They've been friends now for years.
I seen that there was something going on
at the party with Jess.
-We're good now.
-You good?
Because I was speaking to her and she said
that she was a little bit concerned.
-Because she's having her launch.
-Yeah.
-For her collection.
And she didn't feel
when she spoke with you at the party
that your apology was genuine and sincere.
And she was a little bit worried.
She doesn't want anything
to go down at the event
'cause she's working so hard on it.
Shit. I really hope
that I haven't upset my new friend.
I just want you guys to, you know,
sort out whatever it is.
If she thinks
I'm going to mess it up, then…
That shocks me a little.
Because, in my mind,
it was all said and done and cleared.
I literally thought we were fine.
Jess' event, I've got to say…
I don't know
if I'm going to rock up. Who knows?
So, guys. Not to put pressure on you,
but this is my first catwalk ever.
For my brand image,
this is the biggest event I've ever done.
So I just want to make sure
it all goes really smooth.
You guys look amazing.
It's going to be amazing,
but just don't fall in the fucking pool.
Please don't fall in the fucking pool.
Everything needs to run smoothly
because there's a lot
of important people coming to the event.
Pose. Yeah.
I have some of my best customers coming.
Some amazing influencers
are going to be there as well.
So there's a lot of pressure.
Let the guests arrive.
-I'm so nervous.
-It's gonna be so good, Jess.
-Is Hannah coming?
-Hannah?
-Yeah.
-I don't know.
-Who knows?
-Did you invite her?
I did. But I just want her
to be on her best behavior.
I just don't want her doing anything
that takes it away from the show.
Oh, my gosh. You look amazing.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
How are you, fella?
Good to see you.
-Good to see you.
-You too.
-Oh, my gosh. Look at you!
-How are we?
How are you?
Hello!
You look beautiful.
-Thanks. So do you.
-I love this.
Look at us.
We're kinda twinning here, aren't we?
Hi! How you going?
Saskia and her partner Frimmy,
they're such a vibe.
What are you showing today?
We have our staples range,
our new collection.
It's kind of a combination.
-I'm not like normal brands.
-Into seasons.
-My God. Not at all.
-Lots of brands are moving away from that.
Saskia works in fashion as well.
She works in wholesale.
She's successful
and I think having Saskia at my event
could be a business opportunity.
And it's important to me
that she likes the collection too.
-Been surfing much?
-Yeah. A little bit.
-The swell has not stopped.
-It's crazy.
I've known Frimmy for a long time.
We grew up in the same area,
surfing the same waves,
and he's such a nice, genuine dude.
He's also got a good business head on him.
-What's your plan?
-We started up a tiny, little airline.
-No.
-Yeah.
You're getting a record player on there.
Cocktails on arrival.
-An old-school vibe.
-Yeah.
-Sick!
-We're gonna make it unique.
Frimmy's idea to do
a boutique little airline
connecting Sydney and Byron
is so outrageously cool.
Frimmy and Saskia are such a power couple.
They're so epic.
What about you? Are you seeing anyone?
Yeah, I met this girl called Sarah
at this last little party and I…
I said I'd show her around,
'cause she's new.
You're telling the boys about her.
You're digging yourself in a hole now.
-Hey--
-It's serious.
It's serious. It's a heavy energy.
Quick, get it in.
You're making me nervous, man. Stop it.
-Hey! How are you?
-Hi!
-How are you?
-You well, mate?
-How you doing?
-How are you? Good.
-What's going on?
-Nothing.
Thank you.
Cheers, brother. Good to see ya.
-Cheers.
Cheers to you.
Nathan and I shared a connection,
and I'm looking forward
to picking up where we left off.
-How are you?
-Good.
How was your weekend?
Yeah, it was crazy. It was crazy.
-What about yours?
-Same.
There are little smirks going on here.
Thank you for making it awkward.
-I love you.
-I like it.
Sarah's cute. She's a lot of fun.
I get a bit lost for words.
The heart starts racing.
I don't know. It's hard to speak
when your heart's running at 200 BPM.
Just a couple more of these
and then it'll all be all right.
Stop it.
This is an outfit.
-It's kind of a bit loud.
-Isn't it?
Yeah. It's great.
I'm not in Byron just for the acai bowls.
I'm here to find hot, talented people.
Fashion attracts creatives.
-I'm glad you're in color.
-Yeah.
I thought, "Everyone's in black.
It's a funeral."
Hello. I'm Saskia.
What about Nathan?
What about him?
Well, how did your date go?
It was really good.
And he was like…
We were just having a good time.
Yeah?
And it was a picnic on the beach.
Was it like a David Jones hamper or like…
No. He handmade
vegan rice paper rolls for me.
-Shit.
-And he brought the dog.
But since I got here, I feel like…
I don't know. There's a weird vibe.
There's a weird vibe?
Either he's trying to be cool
or he's like, "I don't like this girl."
'Cause it's weird.
Nathan's kind of talking to everyone
and not really talking to me.
And just acting a little weird.
Since I moved to Byron,
he's one of the few people
that made me feel really
comfortable, really quickly.
So I'm feeling a little bit disappointed.
That's cool.
-Hi!
-Hey.
Look who's here.
Hello.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-How are you?
Hello.
It's better late than never.
Welcome.
Hello!
How are you?
-Hi.
-Oh, my God. Go say hi.
-Hello. How are you?
-How are you?
I will definitely freak out
if she tries to bring drama into my event.
Last but definitely not least.
-Hello.
-I'm like, "You're last?"
-No.
-How are you?
-You look beautiful.
Nice to see you. Thanks for coming.
I got something for you.
You got something for me?
-Just a little something.
-What have you got?
"Sisters who slay together stay together."
That's very…
What…
Is that us? Which are you?
-It's Kylie and Kendall.
-I know.
Which do you wanna be?
"My beautiful Jessica,
I'm so beyond proud of you."
"I'm sorry. I love you."
That's nice.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
I appreciate you coming
and supporting me as well.
I have always been
one of Jess' biggest fans from the start.
I've always been so proud of her.
It's so great
that our friendship's back again.
-How've you been? Been good?
-Yeah.
I'm happy giving Hannah
the benefit of the doubt.
And now that we are friends,
we can move forward.
Okay. Maybe.
Looks like Jess and Hannah
are good friends again.
Success.
-How'd you find your party? You enjoy it?
-Yeah.
Well, my friend overheard two people
that are "new" to our scene,
Alex and Sarah,
call my family and I… It's pretty heavy.
The Handmaid's Tale.
As in, relating my family and I to that.
To a cult.
-Pretty much.
-Yeah.
Oh, my God, look at them.
Like something from The Handmaid's Tale.
-I don't think I can do this.
-What?
See you. Bye, babe.
-It's pretty--
-Disrespectful.
Like, majorly.
-And also…
-You know he's here?
-Yeah. I know.
-Yeah. He's here.
Are you gonna say something to him?
I think I have to.
Just don't smash glasses.
I've heard he's a bit sassy.
Fucking good luck.
Thanks, sweetie.
Thank you for today.
-You look stunning.
-Thank you.
Bye.
I think I'm losing it.
I guess, as the newbie at the party,
I found myself spending
quite a bit of time on my own.
It's been pretty lonely.
Nathan is completely ignoring me.
It's just left me feeling really confused.
I think I've got him all wrong.
Maybe he's a player.
At this point,
I'm just going to brush it off.
I just want to have a good day
and get to know everyone else.
-Hi! How are you?
-Good to see you.
-It's been a minute.
-Good to see you. I know.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
No. We're just talking about dubstep.
-Dubstep!
-Yeah. Big fans.
-How's your week been?
-Good. Thank you.
I'm leaving. So…
-Gonna go talk to Jess?
-Yeah.
About the event?
Maybe. I might go for a wander around.
I'm gonna go join him.
Everyone's leaving.
-Hey.
-Everybody left us. So rude.
-Yeah. I know.
-How dare they?
-It's fine. I'm not mad about it.
I won't be offended
if you relocate to the buffet.
I'm a patient man.
-Do you want to go eat?
-No.
-Are you sure? Okay.
-It's waiting for me. It's all good.
Are you a seafood fan?
No. I'm mostly plant-based now. So…
Yeah. I could never get around oysters.
I can put them in my mouth,
I just can't swallow them.
That's a bad position to be in.
You know.
Have you had a chance to see Byron yet?
Have a look around?
-Seen the sights?
-Not really.
A little bit. But not really.
That's a shame. We should do something.
-Show you around?
-Yeah.
Yeah. Pinky swear.
Now it's sealed.
Nathan is completely ignoring me,
and Elias wants to hang out,
and I'm so confused.
-Everyone's coming.
-What's going on here?
-Sarah!
-Hi!
-Hi.
-How are you?
You look so good.
You look so good. You look beautiful.
Elle and Nathan are flatmates,
so they're really close.
And hopefully Elle can help me
figure out what to do now.
Well, what do you think?
Because you know Nathan.
I don't know Nathan.
So you just…
Why not just explore both?
-There's no reason why--
-Is that rude? Is that…
Look, they are friends,
but you're just going out as friends.
-So it doesn't really matter.
-Okay.
I think that Sarah and Elias
might be a bit better of a match
than Sarah and Nathan.
For Nathan to be truly into someone,
they've got to be the whole package.
I mean, it's way too early
to just decline a date from another party.
Your date with Nathan was very low-key.
It was low-key.
It was probably 20% more romantic
than I thought it was going to be,
maybe 50%, but it was still low-key.
It was in the daytime.
I wasn't wearing heels,
so I don't think that counts.
It's not a date
if you're not wearing heels.
And I was wearing underpants.
What the fuck just came out of your mouth?
Honestly, who says that?
Is that how you identify a date?
Yeah. If you're wearing heels
and no undies, it's a date.
Oh, my God. What the fuck am I saying?
Okay.
That comment was totally trashy,
so Gold Coast.
Yeah. I'm going to go hang out
and do some more networking.
-More networking?
-Yeah.
When I get really nervous and excited,
I act really weird.
What else could possibly go wrong?
-Hi.
-Hi!
-How are you?
-I'm so good. How are you both?
-Very well. Thank you.
-Good.
So I wanted to talk to you guys
about something.
This is a reference to the show
The Handmaid's Tale.
-Yes.
-Someone said something about my family.
Are you saying
that we're like the wealthy people
getting other people
to have children for us?
Or am I the other person that's meant
to be giving birth to these other people?
No. You were the celebrated child.
When you were standing there,
your parents right next to you,
it was very dramatic.
-So it was a good thing?
-Yeah. Totally.
I'm making a pretty weak attempt
to dance myself out of this situation,
but it's working!
Felt like the light was hitting you
on a certain angle.
-Right.
-It was very poetic.
Okay. Well, good.
I think the show's about to start,
so let's just…
You guys are so great.
Stop it!
Guys, I'm so excited for this day.
Obviously, this has been
a lot of pressure for me,
and I'm super nervous, but I'm so excited
to spend it with you all.
My new friends, my old friends.
This has been six years in the making.
This day is super important to me.
So cheers, guys.
Thank you so much. I'm excited.
Enjoy. Okay?
Cheer them on.
"Six years in the making"?
It takes six years to do a fashion line?
Go.
It better be amazing.
Work it, baby. Yes.
You go.
This catwalk is a bit of
a make-or-break situation.
A lot of influencers are here.
Quick.
Jade has got such a massive following.
His Instagram blows up
every time he posts.
Gorgeous.
So I need to represent
the brand perfectly.
Sick. This coat.
I have that jacket.
What do you think?
Yeah, girl.
It's progressive for Byron Bay.
"Progressive for Byron Bay"?
It's neutral colors.
It's neutral colors
wrap-tied around a body, darl.
Gorgeous.
Yes.
That's a good vibe. That's cute.
It's very Pirates of the Caribbean.
I'd wear that.
-Would you?
-Yeah.
The hard work that Jess is putting in,
I can see that she will take it
to the next level. That's for sure.
I can see it being a global brand.
Come on, right?
Yes, queen!
You killed it, Jess!
Would that take you six years?
Darl, that will take me
a trip to Spotlight, I think.
Alex has a bit of bite to him,
that's for sure.
I was really shocked.
-Get it, Jess. Get it.
-Congrats!
-Thank you so much.
-Well done!
-That was beautiful.
-Thank you.
-Did you guys like it?
-I loved it.
-Thank you.
-Jess, that was amazing.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
This is 100% a proud friend moment.
She nailed it. And I'm gonna have
to tell everyone on my Instagram.
These are for you.
-Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
-I know.
I'm so excited for you.
-Jade, that is so sweet.
-Babe.
Thank you so much.
Do you guys know Jade?
I met him at the party.
Jade says he's the most
followed man in Australia.
Don't think that's true.
-Yeah. Right.
-Yeah.
Yeah. He's a honey.
He's an interesting character.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. Very interesting character.
No. He is interesting because how he comes
across on social media is not actually…
I don't know. He's such a sensitive soul.
-You know what I mean?
-Interesting.
I know Jade from Instagram.
I finally followed him.
His content's quite funny.
In the influencer world,
everyone's suspicious of everyone.
Is this whole place
just one big town filled with lies?
Potentially.
After the Johansen launch event,
I feel like a bit of an outsider.
So I'm so excited
to take Elias up on his offer
to just hang out
and get to know each other a bit better.
How are ya?
-How's it going?
-Hi.
-Good. How are you?
-Good.
-Gonna have a sit? Go for it.
-Yeah. If I can steal some towel.
How's it been?
-It's been hard, dude.
-Why?
-Just felt like a little bit…
-Just really…
Do you know what? I honestly thought
I'd come here and make heaps of friends
and have a little community and stuff.
But it just hasn't been like that.
Everyone's real funny towards outsiders.
It can be super cliquey.
It's always hard moving to a new place,
on your own especially.
-You don't know anyone.
-Yeah. I don't know anyone.
It's just been really hard
and I feel like I'm alone a lot.
Yeah. Sorry.
It's horrible
when you're trying to find friends
and people that you can connect with
in a place that you're trying
to make your home.
I know how that feels. Yeah, it's not fun.
You've been hanging out
with Nathan. What's the vibe there?
Yeah. I don't know.
When we hung out, he kind of seemed like…
I don't know. Like there's
a little bit more substance to him
and he's got a softer side and whatever.
-Yeah.
-And then at the launch…
-That's exactly it.
-Like two completely different people
when he's around everyone
and when he's one-on-one.
I don't know which version
is the right Nathan, I guess.
Exactly. That's exactly the same
kind of journey I've had with him.
Met him at a party.
And then later on, went for a few surfs.
A couple one-on-one things.
Like, "This guy's actually cool. I think
I vibe him. Maybe we're becoming mates."
But then we hung out a couple times
in social settings.
I was like, "This guy's not my cup
of tea. He's just a party boy."
-Really?
-Like superficial friends.
Someone you only go so deep with.
Then there's not really much more there.
So do you think he's a player then?
He doesn't really hide that.
Maybe he has to you.
But with the boys, he doesn't hide that.
Do you think he's a fuckboy?
Yeah. You're pretty bang on.
I'm not gonna lie on his behalf.
I'm not part of that lie.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Sarah had already shown
she was vulnerable.
It's impossible for me to say,
"He's a great guy."
And then he goes and fucks you over.
And you go,
"Why didn't anyone say that to me?"
It's like… I'm not gonna
back up anyone like that.
I'm here for you, mate. Come here.
That's so sweet.
That's really sweet. Thank you.
Hearing Elias' warnings about Nathan
make me feel betrayed
because I thought we had a connection.
Elias is a really down-to-earth guy,
and he might actually
really care about me.