Okay, mark it.
Yeah, so open it and slap it.
Ready? Go.
That was so exciting, you guys.
Oh, my God.
So heavy.
-Yeah.
-I'm sad.
Yeah, I'm gonna miss you too.
Well, you have a good time.
-Love you.
-Okay, bye.
Moving somewhere new is scary.
I don't know a soul in Byron Bay.
My name's Sarah, I'm from the Gold Coast.
And I'm a singer, influencer and pianist.
Byron is like the mecca
for creative types.
Every musician, artist,
anybody who wants to create,
collaborate, are so drawn to Byron.
And I'm just
really excited for this new adventure.
-Alex speaking.
-Hi, is it Alex?
-Yes.
-Hi, this is Sarah calling.
-Sarah who?
-The singer from the Gold Coast.
Okay.
I think I spoke to your assistant
and she set up a meeting for you and I.
I'm wondering if that was gonna go ahead.
Just confirm with her, please.
-Okay.
-Thanks, Sarah from the Gold Coast.
Okay, bye.
Finally here in Byron.
Yas!
There's such
a different bunch of people here.
These people are a vibe.
My name is Jade Kevin Foster, I'm…
Hey, babe.
I'm coming to Byron Bay
to make new friends.
I am obsessed with your dress.
You look gorgeous.
There are a lot of influencers
in Byron now,
and as the number one most followed
male influencer of Australia,
I need to surround myself
with likeminded people.
Being an influencer can be lonely.
And I'm absolutely terrified.
I'm terrified
about my life in Byron right now.
But I'm also excited as well.
Byron is one of the most
beautiful places in this world.
Look at this day.
It's gonna be so good.
This is why I live in Byron.
I'd love to
get lost in those hills someday.
It's actually sunny.
It's a surf town with hippies.
The energy is just incredibly beautiful.
It's got beautiful beaches.
Beautiful people.
It's got everything that I love
in life in one very small town.
Everywhere you look, everyone you look at,
it's like a postcard.
It's fucking beautiful.
That's why it's a mecca for influencers.
We're like a tight crew
of content creators,
but we hate that word "influencer."
-Hey.
-Hi!
Take all of that bathing suit off,
Elias, you sexy dog.
-Our crew of photographers…
-That was sick.
…fashion designers…
Amazing.
Gorgeous.
…spiritual healers…
Be right here, right now.
…we're all doing things.
-Good job, bloke.
-Thanks, baby.
Whether you've lived your whole life here…
This is just so powerful.
…or you're new in town…
You guys, today is the day.
I am just about to move in
to my new Byron Bay house.
…breaking into our crew can be tough.
I just moved here. I'm brand new.
There's a difference between new and fake.
I've got a true opinion of you.
I think you're an egotistical fuck,
and seriously insecure.
You gotta stop causing beef
between two guys.
-Do you have a problem with me?
-I do.
You're an absolute fucking disgrace.
Absolutely fucking pathetic.
It's just been really hard.
I'm confused as to who you are.
Just leave.
Byron Bay has this strong power
that if it wants you here,
it sucks you in,
and if it doesn't,
it literally spits you out.
That's gorgeous with the sun, Hannah.
Seriously, darling, it is beautiful.
Beautiful. I love that,
how you're bending your body.
-I don't know what I'm doing.
-It looks good.
Whatever you're doing, it looks so pretty.
I would describe my personality
as bohemian, eclectic
and a little bit strange.
Do a little dance. Do a little thing.
My family is known for our company Bisque.
Mum and I model the clothes
and whatever my mum
puts on, people just snap up.
All right, Mama.
Oh, my God. Look at you, you are so hot.
Does anyone ever tell you that?
You know I've only got one pose.
Give me a moment.
-Gotta compose myself.
-Yeah.
Our style reflects
the earthy vibe of Byron.
We're all relaxed and chilled and flowy.
I love the palm frond shadow
over your face a little bit.
Just go that way a little.
Okay, there we go.
Honey, I'm home!
-Oh, my God!
-Hey. There's my favorite family.
Nathan's rep around town
is that he's a cheeky,
fun, energetic party boy.
Oh, my God.
-You well? You look beautiful.
-I'm good.
What're you up to?
Nathan and I have hooked up a few times,
but it's pretty normal for Byron Bay.
You guys match really well.
I'm not gonna put on black.
-Look at this place. Of course.
-Did you dress for us?
People skills has always
been a strong point of mine.
I love connecting people.
And I just love to make people smile.
I heard about this party.
What's going on?
You want to get the best
in the business involved?
You're confident, I love it.
You guys want a drink?
I'd love a drink, actually.
I'm good with a booch.
-Yeah.
-A booch would be amazing.
Booch.
Feels like forever since I've seen you.
-I know. It's been a minute.
-Yeah, it has.
Yeah, so tell me more about this party.
Maybe you've got friends
that I haven't met yet.
And maybe they're coming.
Maybe you should invite some.
I'm single at the moment, so…
-Single's good.
-I know, it is.
I love being single. I love being fun.
I also do want
to settle down at some point.
-Do you?
-Not in the near--
No boys wanna
ever settle down in Byron Bay.
So for you to actually say
that you wanna settle down, that's…
I mean, eventually.
What's the guest list like?
Elias is coming?
Yeah?
-Elle, your roomie. Yeah.
-Beautiful. Amazing.
Is Jess and Lauren coming?
I am going to invite the Bell sisters.
It's…
-We've had things--
-Really?
Yeah.
There's definitely
some unfinished business
between Jess and myself.
I am throwing a party
to try to resolve things.
We're in the same friendship group.
So it's time to make peace.
-I'll stick to the dance floor.
-Stick to the dance floor.
No, it's gonna be really intense.
I need nine models
and we've only locked in four.
-Oh, God.
-I just need you to try on the stuff.
Show me what you got.
My sister Lauren and I grew up here
and we've lived here our entire lives.
-Do you like this?
-I love this one.
So I feel like
it needs to be tighter at the waist.
Byron used to be
a really laid-back hippie town,
but it has changed so much.
And there's a lot of competition.
It's full of designers, models,
and there's so many
fashion labels based here.
We're all hustling to make a go of it.
I love this.
Cute.
Cute! I love that one.
It's so cute.
-I designed this for you to wear.
-Thanks.
-It's extra. Do you want a photo?
-Yeah, I'll take a photo.
Social media is such a huge thing.
Cute.
We've been able to make $100,000
in the first hour of a collection launch.
So that's been
the key factor in my success.
I love this on you.
I got something to tell you.
Byron is such a hot spot now,
but it's still the same small town.
There's a lot of drama,
especially in our friendship group.
Hannah invited us
to her party on Friday night.
-What? What the hell?
-Yeah.
Are we gonna go?
I don't know.
I don't wanna be petty and not go.
-Yeah.
-She's made the effort to invite us.
So I feel like we should go.
I think that Hannah
invited me to her party
to brush things under the rug.
But I will be asking
for an apology the second I walk in.
I wonder if she will apologize.
I hope so.
-But you just never know with Hannah.
-Yeah, true.
-My man, how are you?
-What's going on?
-Mate. Just cruisin'.
What you got going on?
I'm trying to tattoo on pigskin,
but it's a little uncomfortable.
As a vegetarian,
I haven't been in a butcher for…
Don't think I've ever been in a butcher.
-So that was uncomfortable.
-I could imagine. Look at that.
We've got such a diverse crew
of characters in our friendship circle.
Cai's one of the coolest guys I know.
He likes to keep the peace
amongst all our friends.
And regardless of how different we look,
or how different we are,
we're such good bros.
Mate, these are so sick.
Thank you.
Been testing some images
for this exhibition I've got coming up.
This is unreal. I'm losing my mind.
I grew up here, I went to school
five minutes down the road from my house.
I am a photographer.
A lot of the work that I'm creating
is influenced by this area.
There's so much cool stuff
that's being created here in Byron Shire,
and it's awesome to be a part of that.
Mate, Hannah's having
a party this weekend.
You should come.
It's like a Ibiza
kind of style theme, so, like, white.
Sick!
You'll stick out
like a sore thumb in that place.
That would be so good.
-Okay.
-It'd be so sick.
I just don't have
any white clothes to play around with.
So I'll have to go op-shopping
or something.
It's gonna be fun.
There's a fair crew going.
I'll give you a warning.
The Bell sisters are coming,
and I asked Hannah,
and I think there's a bit of drama
between those two, I don't know.
I mean, Byron, there's always drama.
We're all very close.
So there's some very strong emotions
and feelings amongst all our friends
and no doubt there's gonna be
drama going down at the party.
Byron is just like
a breeding ground for creativity, I guess.
That's certainly what drew me to Byron.
I know I've got the talent,
but what I need help with
is finding the audience.
Well, look, if they wanna do it,
it's gonna be expensive.
Who?
Never heard of him.
Darl, they're very 2016.
You can't have Big W prices
and expect to get David Jones talent.
-Hi!
-Hello, how are you?
-Good. Thank you. I'm Sarah.
-Hi, nice to meet you.
Couple of years ago,
people started to care about
how many Instagram followers you have.
And I quickly worked out
there's good money in it.
-Hello! Hey, I'm Alex.
-Hi!
I don't just manage anyone.
The group of people
I manage is very small.
And to break into that circle,
you better be pretty amazing.
Let me just make a space for you.
Lots of crystals.
They're not doing anything,
still single, still poor.
Haven't worked.
Where are you from? What your life story?
-All the fun parts.
-Okay.
I'm from the Gold Coast.
I'm a singer and pianist, obviously.
So I'm, like, brand-new in town.
And I'm here to work on my album.
Why do you wanna be here in Byron?
I want to meet people
when I'm here and make connections,
find people to collaborate with.
What are your vibes about Byron?
I think the locals are very proud,
and they're their own
really fierce kind of community.
So it's a little bit
of a hard one to crack
when they know
that you're from out of town.
Yeah. Do you have socials at the moment?
-I use Instagram.
-Yeah.
And I have a Twitter account.
-Twitter, darl? That's very 2012.
-Yeah.
-If you wanna hear my music…
-Sure.
…I can play you something
just on the piano.
-It's here, may as well.
-Let's do it. We're here now.
You can try and fight but
You will always be the villain
In someone's story
Since I was really little,
music is all I've ever wanted to do.
My mum was born in Seychelles islands
and she immigrated
to Australia in the '70s.
Being Seselwa was a really
big part of my upbringing.
My mom taught me all these Creole songs,
so it was a really big
part of my childhood
and the main reason
why I wanted to be a singer.
Everything's a weapon
And now that I've gotten here,
it's so important that I make
some new connections with some people
to help me to get where I need to go.
-And then it'll have a big instrumental.
-Gorgeous.
It's gonna go in and I do
like a minute with kind of instrumental
which I haven't worked out yet.
Gorgeous. Great voice.
-Thank you.
-Really beautiful voice.
You can sing, but to be brutal,
there's a lot of amazing singers
out there who don't have a career.
So I think if we can build
an audience around you, then--
-So you can help me.
-I can certainly give it a shot.
There's this event on the weekend.
There's gonna be the typical Byron crowd.
Think, like, good-looking boys,
good-looking girls.
-Okay.
-I stalked Hannah's Instagram.
She's friends with a lot of
really hot Instagrammers as well.
So, if you're free,
do you wanna come with me?
If you really wanna be
successful as an influencer,
you need to know these people.
It's all about meeting people here.
That could be a way
I could really help expand your circle.
-Let's do it. I'm super keen.
-Okay. Cool.
-How good was that?
-Pretty fun.
There's a few.
Not too many people out today.
-Yeah.
-Frothy.
That one I dropped in on you,
that was good.
Haven't seen you for a bit.
Are you seeing anyone?
I'm single as a Pringle at the moment.
Same, man. I'm a recluse. So--
-You are.
-I need to come out with you more often.
Don't tell me
that not every mother and daughter
is DMing you on your Instagram.
-Don't think I'm an idiot.
-My mum DMs me, yeah.
-And my sister probably.
-You have a sister?
Yeah, no…
I work in digital content creation,
and I do some modeling as well.
There's more to me than meets the eye.
I'm a deep thinker
and I've got a spiritual side.
These are some things I don't
necessarily show through the 'Gram.
Are you going to Hannah's this Friday?
I heard she's having a party.
I'll definitely be going.
Who knows?
We might both find a wife up there.
Nathan loves socializing,
trying to chase that next thrill,
that better feeling.
I don't know what he's trying to achieve,
but, you know, it's working for him,
so good on you, mate.
You do all right,
you know, as a single man.
I like to make people laugh
and I think people like that.
Elias is probably one of
the best-looking blokes I've ever seen.
So what I do is I let Elias
draw 'em in and then I'll pounce.
See, he's the honeypot
and I'm Winnie the Pooh.
Everyone loves Winnie the Pooh,
but they want the honey first.
Every time I've gone up to Hannah's,
I just can't have a bad time. Like--
Yeah. There's been
a few good parties there.
I show 'em the good life, make 'em laugh.
That's me.
Should be sick. Looking forward to it.
Yeah, it's gonna be fun.
Stay with your breath.
Reach the arms up on the next inhale.
Byron Bay is built
on that hippie, Zen lifestyle.
We're gonna soften
the forehead into the earth.
You have to do yoga,
even if you're not good at it, like me.
Try and feel the way the belly
is expanding with the inhale.
-You can take your shoes off.
-Okay.
-Yep. Welcome to class.
-Thank you for having me.
Yoga is definitely not my scene.
But you know what,
I've come to Byron to make new friends,
so if that means putting myself out there
and doing something
I'm not quite comfortable with doing,
then, so be it.
How much longer do we stay like this?
This guy was so out of place at yoga.
Namaste.
-Namaste.
I suck.
I could just tell from the second
I saw him that he wasn't from Byron.
I just moved here.
-You just moved here. From where?
-Yeah.
-From Gold Coast.
-Cool.
Yeah.
I think the Gold Coast
is a very different place.
It's like a bit more of a,
mean to say, but tacky kind of vibe.
But a lot of good people
come out of the Gold Coast.
What do you do for work?
-I'm an influencer.
-You're an influencer.
Yeah.
-Byron's a perfect spot then.
-Is it?
Are you getting heaps of good content?
I am. I found a few spots around
my house that were really cool.
-Yeah.
-But, yeah.
I'm looking up on Google,
"Best spots in Byron to take pics."
I feel like they're all so basic
that everyone's thrashed the location.
-Yeah.
What do you do for work?
-I have a clothing brand.
-Cool.
Yeah. How good though,
you can live here with your career?
-I know. Yeah.
-It's easy to live anywhere.
-What have you been doing here?
-I've been binge-watching Kardashians.
-Have you?
-By myself.
-You love the Kardashians?
-I'm obsessed with the Kardashians.
Yeah, that was like
my break in my career was,
I had Kylie wear my clothes.
-That is so cool.
-Yeah.
That's so weird, that was
kind of my big break as well.
Because Kim came to Melbourne
and I attended her fragrance launch,
and then she posted
a photo of her and I together
and my Instagram just
blew up when she posted it.
-No way.
-Yeah.
In 2014, I had 11,000 followers.
After Kim Kardashian shared my photo,
I woke up in the morning
to over 200,000 followers.
Now I have over
1,2 million followers on Instagram.
I didn't get your name.
-Jade.
-Jade. I'm Jess.
You'll have to come
for a drink with me and my sister.
-You'll love my sister.
-That'd be fun to meet your sister.
I'm really hopeful
that I've found a friend in Jess.
She's beautiful, she's well-dressed
and she sucks at yoga,
so we're gonna get along great.
-Hello?
-Hi, babe!
-So nice to see you.
-I know, darling.
What are you making?
I just made you a ceremonial cacao.
Stop it! Oh, my God.
Yeah, so it's cacao,
cinnamon, ashwagandha,
some medicinal mushrooms,
some coconut milk.
-Yeah.
-Incredible.
So Elle is Nathan's housemate
and my close friend.
She is a spiritual person
and that's probably been
our connection from the start.
The connection to spirituality
in Byron Bay is quite a beautiful thing.
There are crystals
all throughout the mountains here,
and it helps you ground yourself,
especially when life
gets a little bit crazy.
I brought some clothes for…
You know how I'm having my party.
Amazing.
Nath came home yesterday,
and he told me that he'd gone to see you.
-We had some great chats.
-Yeah?
-He's a funny dude.
-Yeah.
You two hooked up a little while ago.
It's pretty standard
for my friends to possibly like someone
that I've already
hooked up with, and vice versa.
Byron Bay, it's a small town,
so the pool is quite small.
You didn't answer my question.
-Wait, what question?
-You, Nathan, did you guys hook up?
-Yeah, a few times. Yes.
-Okay. Right. A few.
Elle did seem pretty interested
that Nathan and I had hooked up.
Don't know why.
Well, I'm super excited about the party.
Who have you invited? Give me the goss.
I've decided to invite the Bell sisters.
Oh, my God.
Tell me what actually
happened with you and Jess.
It was a series of unfortunate events.
Hannah definitely dances around the truth.
And I feel sometimes I really
have to wedge information out of her.
So what situation specifically?
It was to do with
me feeling
underappreciated as Jess' friend.
One night in particular, I saw her out
and she basically
wanted to try to confront me
about the situation.
And she was getting…
-Aggressive.
-Bit more staunch.
Right, and so then you two had
a proper heated argument in the street?
Yeah, pretty much. It was… It wasn't nice.
I don't exactly still know what happened.
-I do hope that you can just sort it out.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Same.
No, it's time to. Yeah. Thanks.
Hey!
-How are you?
-Good.
Nice to see you again.
-This is my sister.
-Hi, Lauren!
Lovely to meet you.
-How cute is this?
-So nice, right?
You're so lucky to live here.
I just moved here.
-Lovely!
-Yeah.
We're gonna introduce him to a few people.
-Nice. Definitely.
-Please.
Is it like a crew you hang out with?
Yeah, we've definitely got
our, like, gang of friends.
-Like our girl gang.
-That's something I don't have.
That's one of the reasons
why I travelled down here
and wanted to move here is because
I just found in my life,
like, from school,
growing up, I just haven't had
that real good connection,
that good group of friends.
Jade is definitely different
to my friends that I grew up with.
I feel like he just connects with people.
He has such a good heart.
-Friday night, you need to come--
-Come to this party.
-Friday night? Yes. Cheers! Thank you.
-Yeah.
So, yeah, Hannah is a friend of mine,
so it's her parents' house,
but we haven't spoken in months.
We just had, like, a falling out.
-She just sent me these hectic messages.
-She got left out of a dinner.
But she didn't. She felt she did.
It was literally a dinner after work.
I went with a staff member and my sister.
And I'm getting
these abusive text messages
because my staff member posted
on Instagram that we were having dinner.
Hannah just lost her shit for no reason.
The last time I saw Hannah,
she was screaming at me.
And then she stormed off.
So how did she invite you to the party?
I think she's trying again,
which is good for her.
That shows good character.
But I'm going there
to try and sort it out.
I want her to apologize to me
'cause I deserve an apology.
I'm going there to make it better,
if she's not gonna make it better,
there's nothing there.
Be ready. We might leave
after ten minutes. Who knows?
Shit's about to get interesting.
-Does this look all right?
-Absolutely incredible.
Okay and here? What do we think here?
Maybe we should prop these lemons up more.
Oh, my God, the new cushions!
I don't like this one.
'Cause the whole thing
was meant to be really simple white.
Yeah.
For my party,
the house is looking… absolutely magical.
I'm excited for
a little get-together with close friends.
I am feeling a little apprehensive
with everything to do with Jess.
I'm trusting the universe will make this
the healing night that I am hoping for.
Byron is super tight-knit,
so I feel like a bit of an outsider.
But today is the day of Hannah's party.
And I can't wait to get in there
and meet some people.
I just hope they like me.
Oh, no.
I'm nervous. I'm very nervous.
I don't know what to wear.
Don't know what to expect
or who those people are.
I have tried
my whole life to be in a group.
It's a big deal for me. It is.
Hey!
Hi!
-Hello.
-Oh, my God!
I feel really good
to have that friendship backbone.
I feel like I've got
some extra level of support there,
and we can all do this together.
-What an afternoon.
-I know.
I want the D-floor to start.
-Do the boogie.
-Yeah.
So what's the running order?
I'm having my beautiful
sound healing lady play a little--
-You're doing a sound healing?
-Yeah.
Did you know that part?
-No, I didn't.
-I didn't tell you that.
Are you meant to drink
while you sound heal?
It's about music as it changes
the molecular cellular levels.
So what you're drinking doesn't matter,
'cause this doesn't, like…
It doesn't mix with your cells, does it?
-It does.
-Does it?
Well, then put the drinks down, people.
Hannah does present herself
as a spiritual person.
While she's really out there,
her "spirituality" is questionable.
What's crackalackin'?
-How are you? Good to see ya.
-How are ya?
Simba is my best mate and I'm super stoked
he's coming with me to Hannah's party.
I love dragging him along to these events.
I reckon he's gonna have fun.
How are you?
Good to see you.
-Good to see you too.
-I know.
That view.
-No way!
-There he is.
Look at the white.
How are you? You good?
I did my best. Are you proud?
-You look great!
-Look at him.
-It's like grunge swag.
-Hell yeah, I had to.
What the hell?
That sunset is honestly off the charts.
Oh, my God. It actually looks phenomenal.
-Are you kidding?
-My God, wait, I need one too.
Hold up.
Oh, my God! The coloring is incredible.
-Is that what I got?
-No. Yours is different.
Living in Byron Bay,
we're all like a tight group of friends.
We know each other so well that
it can be intimidating for the new people.
-Hey.
-G'day.
Hello.
I'm really excited to go
to this party Alex invited me to.
-Hi!
-Hi! Hannah.
I'm Sarah.
-Hi. Alex.
-Nathan.
Nice to meet you.
-Thank you for letting me gatecrash.
-My pleasure.
-You look fabulous.
-Thank you, so do you.
-How you going? I'm Nathan.
-Hi!
-Sarah. Lovely to meet you.
-Lovely to meet you.
I don't know if I fit in.
So I'm a little bit nervous,
but I'm excited to meet new people.
I just moved here. I'm brand new.
-Right.
-You guys are the first people I've met.
-So you're from?
-I'm from the Gold Coast.
-GC?
-Yes.
What about you? Are you local?
Yeah, we live in Southern Byron.
-Nice.
-Yeah.
Is that your partner?
-No. He's my new BFF.
-Friend.
As of 24 hours ago.
-Great. Fantastic.
-He's the BFF.
-Good.
-Yeah.
Everyone knows everyone in Byron.
When there's a new face in town
you want to know them.
I guess that's what
both Elias and I are thinking.
-Sarah.
-Elias. Nice to meet you.
-Elias?
-Elias.
-Where are you from?
-The Gold Coast.
Yeah? You moved to town recently?
-Yeah, like, a week or two ago.
-Really?
Yeah, I'm a singer
so I'm working on my first album.
Do you play any instruments as well or--
I play piano and I play ukulele.
I'm like a jack of all trades
and a master of none.
Hold that for a sec.
What does that say?
Stop! No!
Inside the ring, it actually says,
"Master of none."
Kinda made me feel like
there's bit of a connection there.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
That's so funny. Wow.
-Cheers to that.
I do not know anybody.
I'm trying to smile
and smize at everybody.
I was looking for Lauren and Jess
but they weren't there.
-Hannah?
-Hi!
My name's Jade. Lovely to meet you.
-Lovely to meet you.
-Thanks for having me.
-Hey!
-Hello.
I'm feeling so nervous right now.
The worst possible outcome
that could happen tonight
is me being rejected
or feeling out of place.
I bought you a gift.
-Yeah.
-Lovely.
Oh, my God! Hi, honey!
You're amazing. You smell so good.
Thanks, babe.
Okay, what have we got here?
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Oh, my God.
The very first crystal I bought myself
was hot pink. It was the same color.
And this is like…
-It lights up?
-Yeah.
-Lights up.
-It's a light!
Jade, are you kidding me?
I hope you like it.
Hannah…
is different.
She is a very nice girl.
Definitely always want to
give people the benefit of the doubt.
So hopefully,
Hannah and Jess resolve their issues.
Guys! Look at my new prezzie.
-Hey!
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Jade. Nice to meet you.
-Hey, I'm Alex.
-I'm Jade. Nice to meet you.
I know who Jade is.
His name has come up
a few times in the office.
But I'm very selective
with who I work with.
And that's the type of person
I run away from.
-See ya.
-Lovely to meet you.
Lovely to meet you.
-Yeah.
-You're never butt naked in the house.
-I'm always butt naked.
-Are you? Me too.
Even when you are there.
You're in your room and I, like…
No one's there.
Nathan is really cheeky.
I think he doesn't
take anything too seriously.
Which could either be
a lot of fun or a lot of trouble.
I'm liking what's going on.
Stop it.
Elle. She is my wingman.
-Yeah. Always.
-Or wing-woman.
Elle came across to me as maybe
a little bit territorial with Nathan.
I think she didn't really vibe with me.
I just want to fit in.
-I'm going to the bathroom.
-Okay.
-Nice to meet you.
-Lovely to meet you.
But I think it might take some time.
Thank you. Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Welcome to new friends.
-Grab your drink. We'll sit over here.
-Okay, great.
Thank you so much. Cheers.
-Okay, well.
-Back soon.
-All right, well, enjoy.
-Okay.
-See you guys later.
See ya.
-How are you going?
-Good. How are you?
I'm all right.
It's just they're… not my people.
-Like, it's not--
-No. Really?
There's like a Byron type, right?
Like they're very Byron type.
Hannah seems sweet
and she's got a lovely house.
But she's very, like,
talking like this the whole time.
Like, is this chick for real?
It's very Byron Bay.
Jade. He's an Instagrammer.
He's got a big following on Instagram.
You know when you click on someone's
profile and see their Insta stories?
I've been on Jade's account.
And I'll click on it,
and I'll see the dots come up
and like, "Nah."
Jade says he's
the most followed male in Australia.
But something is not right here.
-Nathan, baby.
-Hit me.
What have you got?
Have you seen any hot girls
you're interested in?
Yes.
You know how the world
wants you to be in a box?
And be like, "I'm this or I'm that."
And people get pissed off
when people go off the path.
-Your own path. 100%.
-Yeah, exactly.
-Now I think it's a bit more varied.
-Yeah.
I definitely think Elias could be
somebody I'd like to get to know better.
I kind of get the sense
that he is just really soft and gentle
and empathetic.
It's fun to hang out with him.
I love that's the way everything is--
What's up, my crazy humans?
-What's cracking?
-Hi!
Hey. How are you?
-So you're new to town.
-I am. Brand new.
I can show you around town.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Cool. Okay.
That's on.
I got a vibe then.
Got a vibe.
This is gonna be very interesting.
Elias and Nathan
could not be more different.
So this evening,
you said that you were
invited by the Bell sisters.
Yeah. By Jess and Lauren. Yes.
Jess and I are old friends.
-Old friends?
-Old friends.
But we had a little falling out,
and I'm not one to have
a falling out with people.
I know that shit's
going to pop off tonight.
Do you want to be
close with her again, or…
I think we'll be okay.
-You think you'll be okay?
-Yeah.
-And they just arrived.
Hannah owes me an apology because
she went crazy for absolutely no reason.
Saying sorry is powerful
and I think she should say it to me.
-I need a champagne.
-Yeah. Immediately.
I can tell she wants to make amends.
I think she's just holding back.
Like, it's hard for me because
I feel like I'm so upfront.
-You are.
-It's hard when someone isn't.
Yeah.
I'm not good
with any type of confrontation.
And Jess can actually be quite gung ho.
-Try not to get emotional.
-I'm fine.
You went really pale before.
I thought you were gonna pass out.
I know, in this moment,
I need to center myself.
Calm myself down.
I'm hoping that sound healing will help
the situation between Jess and I.
This is Ruby.
She's our beautiful sound healer.
And we're just going to experience this
for a moment of time.
Oh, my God, look at them.
Like something from The Handmaid's Tale.
I have made as much small talk
as I can with these people.
I mean, what cult is this?
I don't think I can do this.
What? No.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah. I can't.
-What are you gonna do?
-Go home.
See you. Bye, babe.
I've never been to a party
where there was sound healing before.
And it's really, really cool.
It's something else.
We are love
And the kindle is within
I find it really funny
Hannah's done a sound healing
the second I walk into the party.
Maybe it's so she can chill me out
so I don't go at her as hard.
How does everybody feel?
Fabulous.
-Great.
-Hi, guys.
Grateful. Blessed.
Hannah's in the wrong.
And I'm going to have a conversation
and get this apology that I need from her.
If you do something wrong, own it.
Do you want to have a chat?
Let's not fuck around.
-'Cause shit got really nasty.
-Yeah.
Should we get straight into it?
I do want Hannah in my life.
I don't want to deal with her bullshit.
If she doesn't give me an apology,
our friendship is over.
You obviously got me here tonight
to resolve this issue, right?
Yeah.
So I was out at dinner
with two people after work,
and I just feel like
I got attacked by you.
Well…
The messages… were rude.
Right? They were rude.
I felt like you went really crazy at me.
I felt disrespected by it.
When you sent me those messages,
I literally was like, "Yuck."
When I saw you out at the bar,
I could feel your anger.
-And you acted like a psychopath.
-I tried to run away.
You were out of line.
And I felt really fucking angry.
I know. I'm not going to deny it.
I did act a little crazy.
So…
Am I gonna get an apology?
Look, I was not myself during that time.
I did act a little bit crazy.
I wasn't in the best headspace then.
I was probably partying a little bit more.
'Cause my mind wasn't clear then.
Yeah. So…
Yes, I…
Sorry.
-I am sorry.
-Sorry.
Are you actually sorry?
I didn't find it very sincere,
her attempt of an apology.
So I just don't really know
how to take it from now on.
I feel like maybe
certain things weren't said,
but I'm glad we had a talk.
Coming to Byron,
it's a really tight-knit community,
but I just hope that
I might actually fit in here.
I love this place.
I'm going to enjoy being here.
Out of everyone I met at Hannah's party,
Jade stands out the most to me.
There's something off about him.
I need to get to the bottom of it.
I'm not going to let this go.