That can't be Cristal.
I refuse to believe that's Cristal.
Oh, my God!
As a talent manager,
I spend my days checking on influencers.
And there's something about
Jade's Instagram that just doesn't add up.
When it comes to social media,
I know what I'm talking about.
And Jade's content doesn't really align
with someone who'd have a huge following.
-You know, I've been doing my stalking.
-Yes.
Bring it over. I need to see.
There are programs which allow brands
to type in anyone's username
and see where their audience lives,
what interests the audience have.
The game is up. We can see everything.
So his top audience
so, where he has
the most followers is Turkey.
With 451,000 of 1,2 million.
-So, 37% of his audience live in Turkey.
-Turkey.
The other sus one is Iran.
When you buy audience it's from places
like Turkey and Iran and India.
They're where you get fake audience from.
I spent my career trying
to make influencers a real thing
and be taken seriously by brands.
But stuff like this
walks back all that work
that I've done
to make people take what I do seriously.
-Yeah.
-Because this is taking the piss.
What infuriates me
is there's so many online creators
who are building
their audience the right way.
That it takes time
and effort and creativity.
You can't buy your way in.
So, I know I'm gonna
have to confront him about this.
The reckoning has begun.
It's basically me rolling up
and going, "You're full of shit."
There's no easy way
to come back from this.
Look at this.
There's the ocean in the background.
Yes.
I feel like one of the best
things that I've done
is move down here to Byron.
I mean, the people that I've met so far…
And the energy is just
a total vibe and a half.
-Are you guys--
-Mommy's calling again.
-Mom's calling again?
-Yeah.
-Hi, Mama!
-Hey, Mom.
Hey. I nearly hung up on you.
-She's gorgeous.
-Nothing.
-This is my friend Lauren.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Hi to Lauren.
-I'm just going to go and talk to my mom.
-I won't be long.
-Bye. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
-We'll have a drink soon.
Yes.
Sorry. I've just been doing…
I'm just creating content with Lauren.
So, I'm sorry I haven't been
able to answer your call.
I look at Instagram
to see what you're doing
when I can't hear from you.
-So--
-Turn your head to the side again.
That is not a dollar sign.
It is.
It's a dollar sign.
What?
Why do you always
pay me out about what I'm wearing?
I have a really
complicated relationship with my mom.
We used to be best friends
when I was growing up.
And we were a solid, united front
and I wanna go back to that with her.
But, since I've become an influencer,
she's just been really critical of me.
I've been going to the gym a lot
and I've been choosing healthy options.
And when I have a little bit to drink,
instead of going fast food,
I will go a healthier option.
So, I hope you're proud of me.
Except for what I see on Instagram.
Too much drinking, too much bad food.
Growing up was tough.
I got bullied a lot about my weight.
It was a hard time.
So, I started Instagram to make friends.
My followers are there supporting me 24/7.
They mean everything to me.
Finally, I also have real friends.
-Okay. I love you.
-I love you too.
-Bye.
-Sorry, babe.
-That's all right.
What did you think of Jessie's launch?
-The launch was fabulous.
-Yeah.
-Absolutely killed it.
-Yeah. I think--
I heard they're at it again
with the whole fucking Alex bullshit.
-What?
-Apparently Alex turned around
and said, because Jess had mentioned
that she was working
on this for quite some time,
"Have you been in your room
selling this for six years?"
-Are you joking me?
-Yeah.
-Six years in the making?
Does it take
six years to do a fashion line?
Would that take you six years?
Darl, that will take me
a trip to Spotlight.
He's honestly the sassiest little bitch.
What the fuck? Who is this guy?
Alex has pissed off
a lot of people in town
and now he's come after
Jess and her business.
Don't come for my friends or for me.
He's gone and said that at Hannah's.
Now he's saying this now.
I've gone up and introduced myself
to him a couple of times
and he's been completely…
Doesn't wanna bother.
So, why is he staring at you
the whole time?
-Remember at Hannah's?
-I know.
I almost wanna ask him,
"What the fuck is your problem?"
-Yeah.
-But he needs to be fully confronted.
-Yeah. 100%.
-Yeah.
I just don't understand
what his motive is.
I just see Alex, right now, as a bully.
And I know that I need
to support my friends.
I really do wanna be there for them.
No matter what it is.
I'm making some chai. Want some?
Man, chai's my favorite.
These are sick.
Yeah. I was just actually
getting things ready for the show…
-Coming up.
-Man, incredible.
Look at this curious mind you have.
With this particular show,
I think that it would be
quite smart to get, you know,
some people who don't know my work
and see
what their reactions to the art is.
And that's where Simba's
really helping me out.
Breaking it down… This is the play on
the Byron Bay call of the blow-in.
So, I thought,
playing around with fabric and stuff
and this really symbolizes that
in more of an artistic way.
Someone's a blow-in if they've just
rocked up from somewhere else.
And then they're here now.
And they're calling it home.
Yeah.
Hey, boys.
-How are you?
-How are you, beautiful man?
-Good seeing you.
-Good. Yeah.
-I hope you don't mind I grabbed an apple.
-Is that from my fridge?
Yeah, brother.
-Hey, that's for lunchtime.
-It's for your recess.
How are ya?
-Whatcha doing?
-I was checking some artwork.
Sick. You should get Sarah
to sing at your event.
She sung to me the other day.
It was pretty sick.
-Really? That was a little bit of a flex.
-Yeah.
-That was a lowkey flex.
-"She sung to me on the beach."
-Yeah.
-That's pretty cute.
I'm psyched on Sarah playing.
I'm all about having
that sort of creative mix as well.
-Yeah.
'Cause I think if I can show this
as well as her showing off some stuff…
She also was saying to us that,
you know, she wants to
know more people
around the area and stuff.
-And this could be a good way--
-It'd be a great in.
Especially something that's creative
and she does something creative as well.
Cai's art is about the whole
blow-in culture with Byron.
I can understand where he's coming from.
The locals can make it so awkward
and make people feel so unwelcome.
And I would hate for Sarah
to have that feeling.
I didn't get to speak to her
much at the Johansen event.
Yeah, 'cause we were hanging out there
and I didn't really get to see you guys.
The whole thing was…
I wanted her to go out
and make friends and talk to people.
Be a bit more comfortable.
Exactly. And just get to know people here.
So she's got a friendship circle here.
-Yeah.
-For sure.
-Hey.
-Hey, gorgie bum!
-Hey, cutie. How are you?
-How are you?
-What are you having?
-Green smoothie.
-I ordered you an almond latte.
-Thank God.
-Thank you, sweetie.
-Only the best for my boo.
Thanks, darl.
I hear you're gonna perform
at Cai's exhibition.
-You think it's gonna be good?
-It's gonna be great.
-Okay.
-It's gonna be interesting.
-Why? I feel like you know something.
-Well…
-You know the whole Jade thing? Yeah.
-Yeah.
-The followers.
We have the software,
and we generate this report
and I looked at his audience
and it's not good.
He's going out to market
with his 1,2 million
and 550,000 of that is from Turkey.
Another 100,000 of that's from Iran--
He doesn't just have
a big audience from Turkey?
It's unlikely.
Jade claims to be
the most followed man in Australia.
And with that comes
a lot of responsibility.
You need to have a real audience.
And if you don't,
you need to be called out.
I have to have a conversation with him.
I don't know how he's going to take it.
I feel bad for him, but at same time,
I think, "Fuck you!"
"Fuck you"?
Are you gonna bring it up at Cai's?
-Yeah.
-My God.
What's going on with Nathan?
I have been dying to find out.
I haven't seen him since the launch.
Really? But you must've like…
-heard from him?
-No.
That is so weird to me.
I'm just really confused about Nathan
because after spending
one-on-one time with him,
I just don't understand
why he's acting really weird.
And then do you know what?
I was at the beach hanging out with Elias.
-We were chatting.
-Right.
I asked him about the Nathan thing
and he confirmed, he is indeed a fuckboy.
So, do you think he's a player then?
-I mean, he doesn't really hide that.
-Do you think he's a fuckboy?
Yeah, you're pretty bang-on.
I thought Nathan and I had a connection,
but it looks like I was wrong.
So, I don't know how
this is gonna go down when I see him.
-Is that Elias?
-No. Hannah.
No. Hang on. Hannah.
How is the handmaid?
No.
-What'd she say?
-"Hey, beautiful girl."
"Considering we may have started off
in not the most perfect light,
I thought it would be nice
to have a healing,
girly, nourishing
get-together to creative sharing."
"What are your thoughts? Love, Hannah."
-I don't get it.
-You have beef with her?
No, I didn't think I did.
What should I say? Should I do it?
It's kind of odd
getting a text from Hannah,
but I really wanna go to Cai's exhibition
feeling like I have some girlfriends.
-Do you want to do it?
-May as well.
Yeah. I'll do it.
-You should.
-Yeah.
I love spending time in nature.
Just breathing in the oxygen-enriched air.
Nathan and I are super close.
We're like soul brother and soul sister.
We do a lot of things together,
and we have each other's backs.
-It's good to get out of the house.
-Yeah.
I know that Nathan and Sarah
have been hanging out with each other.
I wanted to have a chat with him
and find out how he's doing.
What did you think of the Johansen launch?
It was good.
-Jess is obviously super talented.
-Yeah.
-It was really nice.
-I love her clothes.
Yeah.
So, I actually
wanna address something with you.
So, when I was talking to Sarah…
…she felt that you were
super cold at the party.
I wasn't being cold. I wasn't giving her
maybe the attention that she wanted.
I was just trying to let her do her thing.
At the end of the day,
are you even interested in Sarah?
She's really talented as a musician.
So, maybe I was a little bit starstruck
when she was playing uke on the beach.
I'm only telling you this
because I love you.
Someone's going around
and talking shit about you
and calling you a fuckboy.
And I have a feeling
it's gotten back to Sarah.
I just thought that was incredibly rude.
I really don't appreciate that,
to be honest. I hate that shit.
I really like Sarah
and I don't want her to get
the wrong impression,
because that couldn't be
any further from the truth for me.
I just wanted you to know.
Yeah, well,
maybe I'm gonna ask her about that.
From what I've experienced thus far,
I don't think
Sarah's a good match for Nathan at all.
And I just feel like Nathan
can do so much better than Sarah.
I think you should approach her about it.
Yeah.
Time to watch Nathan get bogged.
Let's see Nathan get bogged.
It's kind of stressing me out
that Sarah thinks that I'm a fuckboy.
But it's always good
to go down to the beach
and have a bit of time with the boys.
Because these guys
are like my closest friends.
I'm not trying to peer pressure you
into going faster.
It's just like, maybe turn the car on.
That'd be nice.
Are you guys excited for the show?
Yeah. I'm psyched, man.
-I'm pumped.
-That's sick.
I printed some stuff
on fabric and everything.
So, it'll look really cool.
And it's in a little bit of a shed.
But, I've invited quite a lot of people.
-Sick.
-Yeah. Up in the hills.
-Yeah.
-Amazing.
And you've also organized the musical
performance for the night, yeah?
Yeah. We heard about this yesterday.
So, what happened was,
Sarah played the ukulele
and sung to me on the beach.
And we went on this little date
or whatever you wanna call it.
-And--
-I think it's called a date.
-Right--
-Hang on a second.
-Is that your Sarah?
-Not my Sarah, it's the Sarah.
Actually bumped into Sarah
yesterday on the beach after a wave.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You've both been
on beach dates with Sarah?
I didn't go on a beach date.
Did she have a ukulele with her?
She didn't have a ukulele.
She had a lollipop and a…
-She had a violin.
-A hydro flask.
Sounds like a date to me.
I heard something the other day.
They all told me
that someone called me a fuckboy.
Yeah.
-Do you think--
-Did you do anything fuckboy related?
Is there an essence that you could be?
You know me…
I've been just hanging out with you guys.
Someone's kind of planted
this seed in Sarah's head
and that's why she's going around
asking people if I'm a fuckboy.
The only people
that really know me is the boys.
And they would never
say anything like that.
I don't know how this has happened.
I hate being called a fuckboy.
Because it's just like, in my opinion,
a fuckboy is someone with no depth
and they are literally just out there
to go and fornicate, basically.
If you guys wanna call me a fuckboy
just get it over and done with now.
Since I've known Nathan…
Obviously, we'd go out and party a bit.
The priority of the night for him
definitely seems to revolve
around sleeping with a girl.
That is the very essence
of a fuckboy, right?
Yeah. Let's stop talking about that stuff.
Let's go surfing.
I'm not too sure about Sarah,
considering she's good friends with Alex.
But I don't know
if she has any girlfriends in Byron.
-Hi.
-Hello.
How are you?
This is so cute.
So, I'm gonna meet up with her
and see if I misjudged her.
Welcome to my little healing magic carpet.
I'm finding it really strange
that Hannah wanted to meet up with me.
I'm having a hard time fitting in here
and perhaps she is just trying to help me.
I just thought I would bring you here
just to clear the air and start off
in a more positive note after that
ridiculously stupid
Handmaid's Tale comment.
I don't like to dwell on things.
I like to heal things
and move forward and, you know…
Okay, good.
I'm glad that you invited me here.
'Cause I haven't got to spend any time
-with any girls in town since I got here.
-Yeah.
It's nice to get
to hang out and get to know each other.
I know.
You're a Byron local.
You seem to know everyone.
What can you tell me about the rest
of the people that were at your party?
Well, I know you've been
hanging out with Nathan.
-Yeah.
-He's a ball of energy.
Yeah. He seems like a party boy.
He's a party boy, you know.
It's just who he is.
Elle lives with him.
What's she like?
'Cause she was really hard to read.
I can't…
-She is hard to read, though.
-Yeah.
She's a strong woman.
I feel like Hannah's confirming
everything I had already suspected.
Let's do a tarot reading.
Okay. Do it? Start?
-Go.
-Okay. All right.
I'm really nervous. Okay.
Two of Wands.
It says, "Hope for a balanced
future made manifest.
The labor of our hard work
come to fruition."
-That was good.
-Yes!
-Pick another?
-All right. Here we go.
Queen of Pentacles.
Interesting, 'cause she's pretty much
in the same kind of color tones.
I know. And she's got her boob out.
I'm just vibing with her.
She's my kinda girl.
Hanging out with Hannah,
I have definitely softened to her.
I respect Hannah for reaching out to me
and wanting to spend some time with me.
And I feel good
that I'm going to Cai's exhibition
with a little bit of support.
I'm so glad that we got to do this.
I feel so much better now.
-So, thank you so much.
-I'm really glad too.
We've broken through.
That makes you my first Byron girlfriend.
-Yeah.
-Oh, my God.
I wanna get a photo.
-I wanna get a selfie quickly.
-Okay.
All right. Gotta document this shit.
Man, it's so cool. Unsuspecting
characters all hanging out together.
It's a good crew, man.
-It's a weird mix of us.
-Yeah. I love it.
I think that a lot of people
are attracted to Byron,
not just from like one specific thing.
I think there's so many different elements
that are amazing about this place.
If you're a good person,
doesn't matter where you're from.
Before you came here it was a whole
different world you were living in.
And, you know, the person you are now,
how is that sort of different from before?
It's been a really, really tough,
difficult, turbulent journey, man.
Do you mind if I ask what happened?
One of my close friends who passed away…
A couple of my friends
wanted to do a psychedelic trip
with some psilocybin mushrooms.
Things didn't go as planned. And…
One of my close friends
ended up falling off the balcony.
And…
Yeah. It's…
Man.
Yeah, man. It's…
I can't even begin to comprehend
how that must have felt.
Man. Yeah.
Yeah. It kind of switched this level
of compassion or empathy in me,
which allows me to help
so many other people.
If that traumatic experience that you
went under has brought you to here,
I'm thankful that your journey has,
you know, brought you to this place.
Before I was in Byron,
I was in the corporate world.
It didn't feel authentic.
It didn't feel like it was me.
So, when I meet someone like Cai,
I feel very much at home.
I think it's good for us, as men,
to be a bit more open and…
Talking about this stuff.
Yeah.
The conversation with Simba,
it was quite intimate, you know.
And that's a hard thing
to find in a new person.
This community and this area,
that's where I grab
all my inspiration from.
And that's what I'm trying
to show at my exhibition.
Tonight's Cai's exhibition.
I'm hoping
I don't derail the entire night.
But there's questions
about Jade's Instagram
that need to be answered.
No one else is gonna ask him.
Hello, beautiful.
Cai!
How are you?
-Good. Thank you. How are you?
-Thanks for coming.
Good to see you.
Sarah is a creative,
a lot of my friends and me are creatives,
and we're going to be at this exhibition.
It's a great way for her
to sort of feel a bit more included.
-You ready?
-I'm ready.
Welcome. Think you're the first person
to actually see it.
-I love this.
-What do you think?
I'm obsessed with everything about this.
Yeah?
The fabric's a new style
that I chose to do.
It's just 'cause it was,
I guess, cheaper to make.
But I really wanted that photo
big in the middle.
This is unreal.
So, are you nervous?
-Should I be?
-No. Not at all.
All the people who are coming are friends
and family and they're all good people.
-Okay.
-But then, there's you know…
-I'm grateful you invited me to perform.
-Yeah!
Byron Bay is well renowned for
creative types coming together.
So, it's probably going to be a great
opportunity to show people who I am.
So, this musical number that you're doing…
-Yeah?
-What's it about?
You know when you feel
real kind of conflicted thoughts?
The lyrics to my song are
about feeling like an outsider in Byron.
I felt like I'm not really supposed to be
here and I felt really out of place.
-Yeah. Actually, let me hear this song.
-Sure.
I've been staring at the dirty spot
That taints my bedroom wall
For what feels like a year
It's been a minute since I left this room
And longer since I held on tight
To anything that don't give me the blues
They're going on around here…
Sarah was going to find out
the truth about Nathan sooner or later.
I'm keen to see how she interacts
with Nathan tonight
and how that kind of bubbles up
and unfolds.
So take the high road with the bumps
Yeah, well, I guess I paid the price
Sold my life and soul for fame
I said it once, I say it twice
I don't belong here…
I definitely do want to speak
to Alex tonight, because I feel like
he has a problem.
And I don't understand
why he's doing this.
I've been staring at the dirty spot
That taints my bedroom wall
For what feels like a year…
Tonight, I'm just gonna ask Sarah about
the rumors that have been going around
about me being a fuckboy.
And try and get to the bottom of it.
I can't let this one go.
And then I met you and you scare me
'Cause the only souls I met here
In this strange town, they're all liars
But you said you'd stick around
And I believe you
I really do
We're all liars around here
I'm home
And we're all liars around here
-Yeah!
-Yeah, girl!
That was amazing.
All right. How's everyone doing?
Yeah? You're good?
I really want to say thank you so much.
Friends, family, new friends, old friends,
thank you so much for coming.
I want to explain a bit about this
collection of work that I've put together.
So, I've shot these over the past,
I guess, maybe year.
The main focus from all the images
are different emotions.
That feeling of sort of euphoria
with this area.
It really works with the sort of
"blow-in" culture and that stuff.
There's a bit of that in here and there's
a bit of those blow-ins here as well.
We love them, you know?
We are the two biggest blow-ins.
We are the blow-ins.
Fucking love all of you new friends.
And I fucking love all of you guys
as well.
Cheers, Cai.
All right. Now go drink the free alcohol.
-There he is!
-Stay away from me!
-How's it going?
-Hi!
That was so beautiful.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Wanna come for a walk?
-Sure.
Do I… I'll leave that there. That's fine.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
I think after hearing Sarah sing,
it just struck a chord.
I think she's a really special soul.
-You wrote that song this week?
-Yeah.
Right. It was actually sick.
-Thank you.
-Your stage presence… Yeah.
-Just crazy.
-Thank you.
-I feel like--
-Your sass really comes out.
It would have been better
if I wasn't freezing.
-Want my jacket?
-Little bit.
-No. Then you'll be freezing.
-I'm not cold.
Look. Now they're just having a chat
and it's like…
Are you sure?
I feel really bad. Don't do that.
-I don't get cold that easy.
-I'll take it.
-You don't want to be into that.
-It's cool.
Typical Elias.
Straight after
she finishes playing her song,
he swoops in, grabs her,
he even throws his coat over her.
He's like… Man…
Oh, my God. This is really warm.
I'm gonna actually "put it on," put it on.
This is like a biker jacket.
-It's my riding jacket.
-'Cause you ride motorcycles.
This is good. You're cold now, aren't you?
You're pretending like you aren't.
Am I cold?
No, but you… Oh, my God!
Last time I saw you,
when you came out to surf,
you said we should catch up again.
We should.
-Okay. Let's do it.
-Yeah.
Oysters and champagne?
Oysters and champagne! You read my mind.
I'd actually really love that.
-That'd be so much fun.
-Yeah. That'd be cool. Let's do it.
Elias is cool. He's sure of himself.
And he's quite supportive.
-Go back in? Let's do it.
-Yeah!
It feels really good to talk to him.
I know I love your work.
It means so much
to have nana and pop here.
My sister. My friends and family.
They're all my biggest fans
and it's so great to see everyone
enjoying themselves and getting on.
What speaks to you, here?
This smorgasbord of bodies.
Did you say "smorgasbord of bodies"?
Fuck. What a Saturday night.
In a town full of posers,
it's nice to see someone
with some real creativity.
Cai is exactly the type of person
that I came to Byron to find.
I put my money where my mouth is.
So, yeah, I'm gonna buy some of Cai's art.
Is this what you would…
Is this your style?
I love the roller girl
and I love the other print
which has the sheets.
I'd love to have both of them
up on my walls.
It shows the anxiety side,
but also the freedom side.
I think you're on point.
I'm just hearing about
he's talking about you.
-You're hearing about what?
-Alex.
Alex has come in and talked shit
about my new friends.
Alex was slagging off the Johansen event
and I'm not gonna stand for that.
In your opinion, when you heard him,
was it coming from a mean place,
or was it actually like…
It was mean and spiteful or nasty?
I think he was being a bit mean.
It was.
So, where's Alex?
Come here.
Hey, Alex. Can we have a chat with you?
-Sure.
-Let's have a chat.
Let's go have a chat with Alex.
-Hey.
-Hey!
We just wanted to
privately have a chat with you.
I hear you're going around
saying stuff about--
-Jess's event.
What did I say at Jess's event?
You were being rude to her.
People heard you.
-During the show.
-Like made a nasty comment.
You were like,
"She spent six years designing this?"
Just talking shit.
It was a joke. She said,
"I've been designing this for six years."
I don't know fashion,
so, I said, "Does it take six years
to design something?"
Honestly, I have no idea
what Alex's problem is.
It just wasn't the night for anyone
to try and say shit to me.
Do you have a problem with me?
I do have an issue with you.
When I first came across you,
I was fascinated with you.
I still am fascinated with you.
You've built this audience
and your profile is full-on.
But one thing that kind of
rattled me… I was trying
to work out how you did it.
I knew the whole Kim Kardashian thing
and all that jazz.
But I ran your account through
our software at the office.
When it comes up with your audience
it says that
half your audience is from Turkey
and that you've got more followers in Iran
than you do in Australia.
If you'd done your research
into me properly,
you'd realize I've traveled
the whole world
and I've worked my fucking ass off
to get to where I am.
So, if you're gonna go as a talent manager
and question me and my authenticity,
sitting here as a talent manager,
with talent, you're a fucking joke.
Now let's get into your business.
So, you're a "talent manager," yeah?
Who do you "manage"?
I've managed all different kinds
of YouTuber credits.
All kinds of YouTuber credits?
What have they done?
Give me some examples.
They're not your size
or have a million audience.
That's why you don't understand
anyone of my size.
'Cause you've never managed
You obviously don't have that much talent.
You obviously don't have that much time.
And that's why you're here
trying to create this drama.
You're an absolute fucking disgrace.
Jade's response
is really emotional and aggressive.
I think there's a bit of guilt there,
but I'm not gonna back down.
My question stands.
Who do you manage here?
-No one.
-You don't manage anyone here?
Then what are you doing here?
Why are you yelling at him?
Have a go. You for real?
I came here to find talent.
That's why I looked into you.
You tried to manage me
so many times, Alex.
-I don't think that's true.
-You don't "think" that's true?
-Maybe five years ago.
-That's not true?
So, you're admitting it?
-Maybe five years ago.
-You admit it?
Maybe five years ago.
You tried to gain me as talent,
I said no to you,
and you're coming here and saying that
my "audience is from Turkey."
You tried to manage me so many times
and I said no to you,
and now have a go.
Look at you! You look, here,
as a talent manager,
absolutely fucking pathetic.
Pathetic.
See you, Jade.
Give me another drink.
He's a fucking joke.
Can I have another wine? Thank you.
-Is this white wine?
-Yes.
Are you for real? What the fuck?
Alex is coming for my business right now.
It feels very personal.
He's trying to discredit me and
my business that I worked very hard for,
for a very long fucking time.
So, it's not on.
-How are you doing, Sarah?
-Good. How are you?
I haven't seen you all night.
Man, I just… I just want to
find out what the goal is here.
If someone's planted this seed,
it's someone that has no idea who I am
and doesn't know me from a bar of soap.
Or it's one of my close mates.
Was it you that asked, "am I a fuckboy?"
Or was it someone that planted
that seed in your head?
It was…
Elias.
-You're full witch doctor on me?
-Yeah.
What did Elias say to you?
It was… The conversation
of "Nathan" got brought up.
-Yeah.
-And…
He basically just said,
"If you're worried that
Nathan is a fuckboy,
you're right."
And that you're…
not really a person of substance.
That's actually pretty ruthless.
Elias strikes me as a caring person
but Nathan's reaction to Elias'
comments about him
made me feel awful.
I think I've got him all wrong.
That burns…
hard when, I guess…
it comes from one of your friends.
Turns out Elias is the person
that really dug the knife in here.
And that fucking hurts.
I don't have a bruised
enough ego to be like,
"No. I never want to talk to you again."
It's all good. Honestly, it's sweet.
And I appreciate everything
you said as well, 'cause it means a lot.
He's tried to manage me so many times.
I cannot control my emotions at all
when someone comes for me.
And my business.
And something that I worked so hard for.
-'Cause he's a talent manager.
-He's a talent manager, right?
He sent so many emails out
to try and get me, to manage me
and I declined him.
But the thing is…
If the question was here,
the response was like up here.
And then him going,
"You tried so hard to manage me."
I don't really think
I ever did, to be honest.
Now he wants to go in there and say,
"Your followers are from Turkey."
I've traveled to Turkey…
I've traveled the whole world.
-He's tried to be your manager--
-Yeah. So many times.
You were right to follow your gut.
-100%.
-And not let him manage you.
Imagine if I said yes to him. Oh, my God!
-He'd be talking shit about you.
-Oh, my God. Literally.
I have literally traveled
around the whole world.
Where the fuck…
I'll show him my Instagram right now.
Literally. I will go in there and show him
my Instagram right now.
-Turn around to the clown.
-Do it.
And turn around and say,
"What the fuck is your problem?"
He didn't deny the audience
was from Turkey.
As I said, it's just a question, mate.
Where did the audience come from?
And he just went…
Just so you know,
something is about to happen.
With?
-There you are!
-Hey!