-Cheers.
-How cute are these?
-Very cute.
So who did you invite?
-Well, I invited Hannah.
-Yeah.
-And then, of course, Jade.
It can't be a girls' lunch without Jade.
-Gotta call Jade.
-If he didn't come, he'd kill me too.
And then…
Elle.
Elle. Okay, so Elle is coming.
I promised Saskia
I wouldn't tell anyone the secret
she told me about Elle and Nathan.
Nathan told me
that Elle and him
have hooked up in the past.
Yeah.
But it's a hard secret to keep
when Jade's your best friend.
-Hi.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Hello.
-Hi!
Oh, my gosh, don't you look so beautiful!
-Come give me a hug.
-I miss you!
-How are you?
-Nice to see you.
Come on, sit down.
I love you in a print.
-I love it on you.
-Love, love, love.
-Cheers!
-Isn't this so cute?
-Yes.
Gorgeous.
I was like,
"We need a beautiful lunch, the girls."
-Yeah.
-And I'm here, fucking living for it.
I love it.
-The girls are here, baby.
-I knew you'd love it.
I think there'll be
a big elephant in the room.
-Who's coming?
-Elle's coming.
No.
So, I organized this lunch
to bring all the girls together.
My real motive behind it
is to get everyone to talk. Let it out.
Be honest.
Get it out there and let's move on.
I wanted to be friends
with everyone again.
I know that there's been situations
and I do think we need to talk about it.
Everyone is against Elle.
And Elle is just constantly lying
and making us all look like idiots.
I mean, Elle called Sarah fake.
Honestly, there's something fake there.
And that is not resonant
with, you know, my friend group.
But Elle denying what she said
makes Jess and I look like liars
and makes Elle look like a saint.
I mean, everyone
has said something about Sarah.
Just own what you've said.
We all said
that we thought she was a bit fake.
-She's a bit standoffish.
-Yeah.
-You know, let's not lie.
-Exactly!
And we've all owned up to what we've said.
-Yeah.
-But Elle is saying she didn't say it.
I don't get it. Look, I just wanted
to bring her in because I think
if we're going to chat, let's all chat.
We're meant to be friends.
She would have to be
out of her fucking mind
to rock up to this lunch today
and look at you and I and Hannah
and say that she didn't say it.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey!
-How are you?
Good.
Are we sitting here and saying grace?
I'll be honest.
I think we all need to talk.
It started up with me.
Everybody here knows
that I've befriended Sarah.
We were talking about everything, and I…
She was basically just asking me,
"What's going on?"
Like, "Do the girls not like me?"
And I said that you said
that she was fake.
Hannah's thrown me under the bus.
Friends do not treat friends like that.
I think a good thing today
is for us to all own our part.
Let's just own our part.
I think she just needs to own it
to end the drama
between everyone in the group.
I just want everyone to move on
so we can all get along
and have a good time together.
You know, you probably all brought me here
because you're wanting me to admit
that I called Sarah fake.
I know I've told Sarah to her face,
"I don't feel like you're authentic."
All this time you've said
you didn't say it at all.
I said that I said
that she's not acting her authentic self.
-Which is--
-No, that's--
Let me finish.
One, I don't even use that word, "fake."
Two, I haven't called her fake.
I am far more eloquent
to just use a lazy word like that.
To be honest, it's a bigger picture.
I want to know why you're doing this.
-What am I doing exactly?
-Well, that you're denying it.
I'm actually not denying anything.
I said she's not
acting her authentic self,
which is effectively saying
someone is fake.
-Can I ask a question?
-Can I please finish?
-And--
-Elle, I get that you want to finish.
You keep saying that to Hannah.
"Can I finish?"
And I think you have anger towards Hannah.
I would really like to just finish
so I can actually answer your question.
She hates my guts.
Right now, in this moment,
I have the biggest problem with Hannah
because I feel like
she's completely two-faced.
I actually don't have time or space
or energy for any of this nonsense.
After hearing about
Elle and Nathan hooking up,
I think that there's a few layers
of why Elle is denying this.
I think, one, it's because she doesn't
want to get on Nathan's bad side.
Nathan's now seeing Sarah.
She said a negative thing about Sarah.
So she is prepared to deny it
to every single person in her path
to make her look good, like she's an angel
and everyone else is against her.
I feel like you said it
and then you regretted it.
-I feel like there's other levels…
-No, actually…
…that's not talked about.
There's other reasons
why you would want to deny it.
There isn't anything going on.
Elle's lying
about what she said about Sarah.
You know what? Elle's lying
about the fact she's in love with Nathan.
I understand all of your perspectives.
I really hope you can see mine.
I hope you have a beautiful afternoon.
-No, Elle, you shouldn't be walking away.
-Elle!
You should be taking responsibility
for what you said.
Just leave it.
God.
Her energy is just so scary.
And I think it's time for me
to stick up for myself.
This is the campaign we pitched on.
They chose the other company
'cause they were cheaper.
-Hello.
-Hi!
-Bookmark this. Let's slide it off later.
-Done.
-Sorry.
-Hey, gorg.
I'm in a tug-of-war
with my head and my heart.
And I just need to tell somebody
who really cares about me how I'm feeling.
Have a seat. Tell me what's been going on.
The usual.
-I've just been in the studio heaps.
-Yeah, right.
-I got my lips done too.
-They look great. Show me.
I got them done once. I tried
to tell people I had an allergic reaction.
No one believed me.
I looked like a pufferfish.
-But after a few days were you into it?
-Looked amazing.
Day one, you're always like,
"What have I done?"
-By day three you're like, "I need more."
-Yeah.
When I hung out with him at the beach,
it meant the absolute world to me
that Alex defended me to the girls.
But in the back of my head,
all of the gossip and rumors
are still there.
So what's happening?
Were you having a shit time?
I just felt a little bit weird,
'cause nothing has been resolved
with the girls.
It was kind of fine
but it was also awkward because…
I was just really aware
that none of these girls are my friends.
Yeah.
Out of all of the girls,
I feel like Elle is probably the worst.
Elle has said
a bunch of awful things about me
and, at this point,
I just need her to cut the crap.
And just admit it and we can move past it.
How do you feel about it?
You know, you came here to make friends
and to be honest…
-Are you happy?
-No.
I was so optimistic when I came here.
I was so excited to connect with people.
And day after day, week after week,
it's been the opposite.
I don't want to quit,
but at the same time,
it's bringing back a whole heap of stuff
from when I was little.
I've never explained this to you before.
We grew up where all of our school friends
were blond hair, blue-eyed, pale Aussie.
My mom's not from here,
so we had a different accent and food
and culture and all that kind of stuff.
And my sister and I
got bullied mercilessly for it.
And every day,
we were just made to feel… Sorry.
Every day we were made to feel like,
"Was something wrong with us?"
And I feel like that every day here.
Like I'm not good enough.
Yeah, it's just shit.
-Sweetie, it's not worth it.
-Yeah.
You're too pretty to cry, darling.
I've been thinking a lot
about just moving back to the Gold Coast.
Sweetie.
I could just pack up
and head home back to my friends
and back where I feel like I belong.
But the thing that's keeping me here
is Nathan.
We have a connection
that I just can't give up on right now.
Does Nathan know
how this is affecting you?
He gets it, but I don't want to,
every time I'm with him,
-talk about negative stuff.
-Yeah.
I feel like I'll give it one more go
to try to just resolve everything,
and then, if not…
Back to the Gold Coast.
I'm gonna have a go at him
because Sarah's my friend.
And if Nathan doesn't stand up for her,
she's gonna leave.
-Nath!
-Hey!
Mate, the front door's open,
so I let myself in.
-Mate, come in. How's things?
-Yeah, good.
-Good to see you.
-Yeah, likewise.
Sarah's in the middle of her own cyclone.
She's got a new boyfriend.
She's got the jealous housemate
of the new boyfriend.
It's great if she's Taylor Swift
writing a new album,
but this is no way to live.
And unless Nathan stands up
and does something, she's gonna leave.
I got weird vibes from Sarah yesterday.
-Really?
-She just…
I think this whole
Byron thing's getting to her.
Mate, I could… To be honest,
she's definitely had a rough go,
moving down to Byron.
Not everyone's been
the most welcoming, you know?
The one that I am a little weirded out by
that's coming for Sarah,
which I don't really get, is Elle.
I'm Elle's friend
and I'm trying to mediate here.
I'm trying to look out for Sarah,
but also, you know,
keep my friendship with Elle.
And how's that going for you?
Because I feel you're in a tough spot.
It's not going great.
Why would she just blanket
not want to give her a chance?
She's quite protective over me.
So if she gets
any sort of vibe from anyone
that they're not going to be nice,
then she's just like, "Nah."
Cut the shit.
Is Elle in love with you?
Because it doesn't make any sense to me.
Why does she care so much?
I get being a protective friend,
but it sounds like she's jealous of Sarah.
There's been some things said in the past
where she's like,
"We're really, really close."
Was she wearing a negligee at the time?
And she can't imagine life
without me and stuff.
There's definitely been comments
thrown around that I'm like,
"Yeah, it could allude to that for sure."
-Is that uncomfortable for you?
-A little bit, because she has a partner.
Which, you know, I'm friends with.
And Stav's here a lot.
And I would rather
just be friends with Elle.
Look, I'm no rocket scientist,
but Stav actually is.
So if he hasn't picked up
what I've picked up,
and the vibes that Elle's given me, then
maybe I should start working for NASA.
You've got to make a decision,
because if you really want
to have a future with Sarah and you want
to explore what a relationship's like,
it's never gonna happen
when Elle is staring over your shoulder,
judging you, guilting you.
-Fucking man up and do something.
-Yeah.
You can't live life with both.
You've got to make a decision on one.
If she doesn't get accepted
by these girls,
Sarah's, you know,
hopping on the Pacific Highway.
She's going home.
It's not worth it for her.
I really don't want Sarah to leave.
I need to show Sarah
how much I care for her
because, as scary as it is,
I'm actually starting to fall for her.
Are you alive, Jade? This is the most
quiet I've ever heard you.
I'm so relaxed. This is so good.
I feel like one of the best things in life
that I've done so far
is definitely moved out here to Byron.
The people that I've met so far
and the experiences that I've had,
and the energy
is just a total vibe and a half.
-That is just what I needed, right?
-Same.
-That was amazing.
-So nice.
I've been working so hard lately
and it's so weird
because I come here with you today
for a relaxing massage,
and just before
I walk out the door to leave,
you will never believe what arrived.
You've got the product here?
-I have the official packaging.
-Oh, my God. Show me.
So even though I do have
a wild, crazy, fun party side,
I am also quite a serious businessman,
and I'm just about
to launch my own product.
-Are you ready?
-I am.
I am so excited. Have a go.
-Oh, my gosh. I love it.
-Yeah. You love it?
I have been wanting to do
my own fake tan for so long,
but now my dreams are coming true.
How long have you been working on this?
Eight and a half months? Nine months?
-Wow.
-Yeah.
So how are you going to launch it?
What's the goss with that?
I'm so excited.
I put everything that I have into this.
This fake tan launch
is the biggest day of my life.
Literally. This day's so important to me
and it's so important that it goes right.
-We're going to go to the GC.
-My favorite place.
Yes, and we're going to do it
on a massive yacht.
This is the biggest yacht
in the whole of the Gold Coast,
and the whole of Nelly, Queensland.
Oh, my gosh. I'll get my tightest,
shortest dress and my highest heels
and I'll be ready.
Get those boots on, baby. We're going GC.
I am so excited.
This is going to be amazing.
-Yes.
-So who's coming?
-Everyone's coming?
-Everyone.
So I'm guessing Elle will be there.
Yeah. It's gonna be awkward though,
isn't it? Because…
Yeah. Now she's actually
going after Hannah.
Elle has serious drama
right now with Hannah.
This tan launch is gonna be so awkward.
It's so weird. And I'm like,
"What is actually happening," you know?
-Strange.
-It is.
There's so much drama going down
and there's only one place
for this to be settled:
at my tan launch.
This is going to be great.
This is so nice!
I pulled out all the stops today
because I want
to show Sarah that I'm worth staying for.
Jump in.
And ultimately tell her
how much she means to me.
-Cheers.
-Thank you. Cheers.
-Now you've seen the hinterlands.
-Yeah.
-It's so nice.
It's really pretty.
At this point, the only thing
keeping me here in Byron is Nathan.
Have you been into the hinterlands at all?
-Never?
-No.
This decision is so massive
because I haven't felt this way
about a boy in such a long time.
But when I make my mind up, it's final.
So if I leave,
it's over between Nathan and I.
There's a lot going on. How are you
feeling about everything like that?
I don't know.
No one's made any effort
to get to know me, and…
So no one knows the real me,
because I feel like I just keep…
Every time I hear someone saying stuff,
like, negative things are coming out
of people's mouths about me,
it just wears me down so much.
I just don't know who I can trust.
Right now, I don't even know
who Sarah should or shouldn't trust.
I trust all of these people, for me,
because they've never done
a wrong thing by me.
But I think that I've proved time
and time again that Sarah can trust me.
I've done nothing wrong by her
and I've always had her back.
All of this stuff
is exactly why I was like,
"I just need to get you
out of the Byron bubble."
I don't know
if this will surprise you or not,
but I don't always go out and do massive
spreads out in the hinterlands.
It's like me saying, "Love Byron.
Stay here. This is amazing here."
Yeah.
You're, without a doubt, the best thing
that's happened to me since I moved here,
and you've done stuff for me
that no one has ever done.
So, yeah. I'm really grateful
and I'm really glad that I met you.
You make me really happy. You really do.
And you need to know
that I will always have your back.
You can always trust me.
I'm never gonna break your trust.
It's a big decision I have to make
between going home
and being around my friends and my people
and staying here and falling in love.
But right in this moment,
I just want to stay here forever.
This is everything
I've ever dreamed of in my life.
Have a look.
Today is the biggest day
in my whole career and possibly life.
The influencer industry
is very competitive.
And now to have my own product
is just such a big deal.
And if this failed,
I really don't know what I would do.
I need everything to be so perfect
because everyone's gonna be doing socials.
My backdrops are everything, yeah?
Perfect.
I just want this to go perfectly.
I've literally come to Byron Bay
with zero friends.
And this is not a very Byron event.
This is definitely a Gold Coast event.
So I'm absolutely terrified,
because there is quite a possibility
that people might not turn up today.
Do you feel like
I need to do anything else?
Everyone's gonna love it.
-See, that's the charm of the Coast.
-Hello.
-Let's go get a drink.
-Okay. I'm down for that.
As soon as I step on the boat,
it's like cocktails,
half-naked men…
Jade's in heaven.
I love you.
I feel uncomfortable.
I'm sure a few people are a bit violated,
but it is what it is.
-Cheers. Thank you.
-Cheers!
This is such a massive boat. So insane.
-The shirtless guys…
-Shirtless guys. Can you get on that?
Thank you for coming.
Cruise onto the boat with Simba.
The place looks pretty epic.
It reminds of something from Ibiza.
It's definitely a very different
demographic to Byron Bay.
But I love Jade.
And obviously he's done well for himself,
so I'm all for it.
-Cheers, lords!
-Cheers with my claw.
-Yeah, we got it.
I have a deep, loving affinity
and appreciation
for entering Jade's world.
Interesting people that can't really
move their face or their lips.
It's just… It's Jade. I love it.
Have you ever used fake tan?
Give me 20 minutes.
I just pocketed one of Jade's.
We've both used fake tan. Bodybuilding.
We have!
We've actually used fake tan.
-We used to bodybuild.
-Bodybuilding shows.
And you just go… Show us some moves.
Do "hold the fence."
They glisten!
I actually did this one on stage.
I actually caught up with Nathan
the other day.
He was saying that
him and Sarah were hanging out.
I feel like it's important
that we have a chance
to speak to Sarah today.
Because Nathan does seem
like he has genuine,
strong feelings for her.
He actually likes her,
so why don't we make an effort with Sarah
and have a chat to her?
It makes me want
to get to know her a bit more.
Hello.
-Sorry, hello.
-Hey!
-Hi.
-Well, hello.
-Welcome to the Gold Coast!
-You're in the GC!
I'm so excited you girls are here!
-I know. It's so exciting.
-Yeah.
I think it's quite nice.
We can finally say how we feel
and open up to her.
I just think it'd be nice
to get to know you.
You're obviously dating
one of my good friends, Nathan.
He was like, "I'd love for Sarah
to make friends with my friends."
I want to be able to offer that to you.
I feel like we got off on the wrong foot.
Yeah, me too.
I think you girls are beautiful.
I would love to get to know you
and obviously Gold Coast boy.
It feels like these girls are ready
to give me a bit more of a chance.
You know when you pulled
Elle and I aside at Elle's fundraiser
and I stood by Elle's side?
I feel like a bad person
because I didn't say the truth
to your face, when I should've.
I stuck by Elle's side,
so I want to apologize about that
because I'm really upset
about how Elle's gone about it now.
-I mean, I--
-I appreciate you saying that.
-I'm sorry.
-I, personally, when it comes to it…
I have come in
and made friends with everybody.
When I'd seen you, I could see
that you were alone, by yourself,
which made me sad.
I was so confused as to
why you didn't come up and approach.
Off the bat,
I wanted to be friends with everyone,
but then when you hear that
people are saying stuff about you,
it just means that I come to an event
and I'm more reserved and not myself,
because I honestly don't know
where I stand with you.
I have the utmost respect
for everyone here.
I just need to get to know you.
There's all this other shit
that's gotten in the way.
Being on the Gold Coast has made me
realize I haven't been myself in Byron.
But now I'm in my element,
where I feel most comfortable.
I really want everyone to know the real me
and I feel like, today,
I can show that to them.
Getting to know you,
I'm sorry about speaking shit on you.
-It's cool.
-I spoke harsh shit about you, sorry.
And I've been so confused
about your relationship.
-I've been a bit of a dick too.
-That's so fine.
Let's… Who cares?
Let's all just be friends.
Let's all take off our clothes
and Naked Tan. It's Jade Kevin Foster!
It just feels so good,
and it's incredibly reassuring to me
because it's about time
people stopped blindly following Elle
when they know
that she's done the wrong thing.
Oh, my God, honey!
Hannah always kisses everyone on the lips.
-How weird was that lunch?
-A bit weird.
-How weird was it?
-Really weird.
-Very weird, right?
-Yeah.
I am a little bit nervous
to see Elle after that lunch.
But I feel like it's time for me
to stick up for myself.
Cheers, darling. Yes.
Congrats.
How's it going?
Good, actually. Really good.
I just had an interesting conversation
with Saskia, Jess and Jade.
And we just got to…
talk and iron everything out.
Oh, my God! You resolved something.
Jess and Saskia acknowledged
that they judged me
and they had opinions on me.
And they wanted to try to get to know me
because things are a bit more serious
with Nathan and I than they thought.
Saskia actually apologized to me,
which was really nice.
-And how do you feel?
-So good.
Today is going so well,
and I can't wait to speak to Nathan
and tell him what's been going on.
I just hope he's not with Elle.
Where is Jade?
-There she is. God damn.
-Is she coming over?
No, she's not coming over, but I just…
Hi.
-Look, we can hide over here.
-I'm not hiding.
-This is my home. This is my turf.
-True. She's on your turf.
I just want… I can… I'm happy.
I'm in my hometown.
I just want to have a good day
and I'm not gonna let Elle drag me down.
I moved to Byron Bay because
I knew that this would be something
good for me to do for my career.
And now I'm on this yacht
with my own product.
This is a pretty cool moment
for me right now.
Love it!
Hello, sexy people.
I'd just like to thank
all of the Naked Tan ambassadors
and my new group of friends
that I have made in Byron Bay
for being here today.
I love each and every single one of you.
Every time someone smells their body
after they put this on,
I want them all to think of me, baby.
Yeah, Jade!
Today is such a massive success.
I've made it. This, to me, is epic.
I'm gonna say hi to the rest of the girls.
-She's coming.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-How are you?
Elle walked all over Hannah
at the lunch yesterday.
They might have something
out for each other. It feels like that.
-How are you?
-How are you today?
I actually think it's time
for me to confront Elle.
And I'm here to back myself.
What did I do to you?
There seems to be a situation with us
and you're not taking ownership
for everything you've said--
I've taken ownership of everything.
You pretend to be Sarah's friend,
you talk about her nicely,
but you're calling me
saying, "I'm not vibing with Sarah."
-I didn't say that, darling.
-Yeah, you did.
Elle is very much wrapped up
within her own web of lies.
And I know why.
I actually have a little secret
about Elle and Nathan myself.
I may or may not have said "fake,"
yet you all want to hammer me for it?
Every time I even try to speak,
you just shut me down.
It's not my problem
that I have a big energy
and a strong presence.
How about you level up
rather than try and pull me down?
Elle, you seriously do not like me.
-And that's okay.
-She can't handle confrontation.
She wigged out.
I can handle confrontation,
but you totally don't like me
and that's okay,
but don't try and be fake nice
to my friends as well.
I'm not being fake nice.
I think that's a massive projection
from you, my dear.
I think you are very two-faced, Hannah.
I know that Elle and I really aren't
each other's biggest fans at this moment
and I've realized
I probably never was to begin with.
The thing about Byron Bay is,
I've heard so many Elle stories,
as in I am not fake
and I know people genuinely like me,
and the amount of people that have told me
or they have some sort of Elle story,
what does that say?
I could say the exact same about you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Really?
You guys, this is getting so nasty.
I don't fucking appreciate it.
I don't think it's good.
Typical Elle move. She walks off.
Elle is the quintessential
passive-aggressive spiritual human.
Nath, I got to chat to you.
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Hey, what's up?
Yo. Dude, I just had
the most hectic situation happen.
-Here we go.
-With our fucking dear friend Hannah.
I mean, I walked over
to say hi to the girls, really nicely.
Hannah's like, "You know what, Elle?"
"The amount of stories
that I've heard in Byron Bay about you."
And how everyone has an Elle story.
If someone's gonna come at me,
I will fucking show you
how shitty it is
to not be in my good book.
Hannah's behavior lately
has just demonstrated
that she is not just crazy funny
like what I thought she was.
She is proper crazy.
Rich.
I literally left for like two seconds
to show people my tan
and what just happened?
Elle walks away from every situation.
She does not take ownership for one thing.
Elle storming off like that
doesn't surprise me.
I mean, she believes her own lies,
and she clearly is not coping okay
with Sarah and Nathan dating.
I mean, I know that there's history
between her and Nathan.
I feel like she's really
holding on to that.
This is also why I don't think
Elle has taken to Sarah
the way that she probably should have.
Nathan told me, a little while ago,
it was late at night
and Elle said to Nathan,
"I want to kiss you.
Don't let me kiss you."
And there was this--
-What?
-Yes, even though she's with Stav.
Is this recently that Elle said,
"I want to kiss you"?
-Yeah.
-How did you find that out?
Nathan told me.
What?
I knew Elle and Nathan had kissed,
but I didn't know they hooked up recently.
I mean, the whole story
has completely just changed.
People are so fucking dodgy,
I cannot handle it.
I think Hannah's had enough of Elle's shit
and she is dropping truth bombs
left, right and center.
I'm just glad she has nothing on me.
I think Elle rattled your cage
really badly,
so now you're unleashing.
Maybe I'm finally feeling
like I haven't said enough.
I don't know, I just feel so good
and I feel relieved that
the air's been cleared with the girls.
Sarah's looking so relaxed.
And she's looking beautiful.
You can tell that she's in her element.
I've literally been sitting and waiting
and hoping and wishing for that shift.
But look at you.
I'm so glad that you're feeling yourself
and you're being the person
that I've seen in you.
I feel like Nathan seeing me
in my element, on the Gold Coast,
where I feel most comfortable,
is good, because I want him
to know the real me.
And I feel like I can show him
that side of me today.
Let's go show this boat
and all of our friends
who the real Sarah is.
She's on. Here she comes.
If I was in Sarah's position,
I'd say I would want to know the truth
between Elle and Nathan.
It's a vibe, right?
I love this boat.
Yeah, it's good to see you.
-You too. I know. It's been a while.
-It's been so long.
So did I hear
that you and Nathan are something?
-Yeah.
I did say to Sarah
that I would be her backup bitch.
And I will if she needs me.
So you know how
when you came to my shop and I styled you
and I said about what
we were talking about at Cai's?
They were calling you fake.
Elle was one of the main ones that said it
and she's denying and denying.
Yeah.
She met me, and she didn't like me,
and she said something.
So it's not the issue
that she said something.
The issue is she won't just say,
"I fucking don't like you."
Yeah.
And especially, the fact is,
you're with Nathan.
-They're meant to be close friends, right?
-Yeah.
-Meant to be close friends?
Are they not?
Hannah's being
incredibly vague and cryptic,
and I don't know why.
Nathan told me that him and Elle
had a little something.
Okay.
And he said that it was late at night,
and even though she's with Stav…
I was like,
"What? You're telling me this?"
"This actually happened?"
Okay, so Elle and Nathan
have a romantic history.
Well, that's what Nathan told me.
That was all.
But there's always something
a little bit more, so…
If they actually had a thing,
she might have feelings for him.
Then that makes so much more sense.
And if Elle wants to be with Nathan
and that's why
she's saying stuff about me,
then that makes sense.
Hannah has dropped this bomb on me.
My head is all over the place
and I'm so confused.
I'm starting to feel like a fool
for falling for him.
I need to figure out
who's telling the truth
and settle it once and for all.