When I moved to Byron,
I didn't bank on feeling
quite as isolated as I have done.
But things were going well
between me and Nathan.
I was starting to feel really positive,
and like I might actually
be able to make things work in Byron.
But everything
has just come crashing down.
Because at Jade's event,
Hannah drops this bomb.
What's been happening?
Just been hanging out in Byron.
I found it interesting
that at Jade's launch on the Gold Coast,
I've never seen you so happy.
You were so light
and full of energy and you were proud.
I kind of didn't really realize it too,
until I was back up in my hood,
that I've been trying to make this work,
and trying and failing.
What were you and Hannah talking about?
It was really weird.
I don't know whether
she was trying to warn me,
but she said Elle's talking shit about me
because she also likes Nathan.
Hannah said they've had a thing before
and something might still be happening.
-And then immediately after--
-Wait, whoa.
Whoa.
Did you talk to Nathan about that?
No.
Because when I saw Nathan,
he told me that Elle was in love with him.
-He did tell you that?
-He told me to my face.
To me, that makes the whole situation
of him living with Elle weird.
Wherever Nathan goes,
drama seems to follow.
And I think Sarah needs to be on her game.
I don't want to see her heart broken.
What does your gut say?
I've just had enough.
-Yeah.
-I've just had enough.
I don't want to get more
emotionally invested
until I know whether it's true that
something's going on with Nathan and Elle.
This news has just sent me in a tailspin.
Am I just flogging a dead horse
by staying here?
Because at this point, I don't know
who to believe, I don't know who to trust.
I don't know, like…
I just don't want to see you sad.
And I've seen you sad
the last couple of weeks.
Yeah.
You came here with a purpose, right?
You wanted to get inspired,
to write music, and I just can't stand…
If you're not doing that,
then what are you doing?
The last thing I want
is for you to go, but…
You need to decide
what's going to make you happy.
Yeah, I have a lot of thinking to do.
This decision is so massive
because I haven't felt this way
about a boy in such a long time.
I think I need to speak to Nathan
and Elle. I just really want them to admit
if something has happened between them.
Mate, honestly, Jade's tan launch…
That was such a well done event.
Some hunky dudes
giving us drinks and food.
Even Sarah was just
fully coming out of her shell.
Yeah, I saw that.
Yeah, she was like… I've never seen her
so in her element, so happy to be there.
But it was also a bit worrying
because I can understand why she'd want to
move back to the Gold Coast.
The more I'm hanging out with Sarah,
the more I'm starting to fall for her.
As scary as it is, I need to show Sarah
how much I care for her.
I've organized a party. In the hinterlands
overlooking the mountains and…
Shake up some cocktails for everyone.
Get all our friends around.
We're all going to get dressed up
as our best Byron selves,
which Sarah is going to nail, I know.
Yeah.
You're doing the right thing.
Being welcoming. And that's good.
I'm hoping that this is going to be
the turning point for Sarah,
where everyone shows her
that she is welcome
and she's actually gonna give Byron a go.
I'm still scared that
she's going to bail back up to Goldie.
Totally. The sense of home
is hard to get rid of,
you know what I mean, and that's her home.
That's her place that she loves.
I've never seen Nathan
like this with a girl.
This is a big deal for him.
He's putting energy into this one.
I really hope
he doesn't get his heart broken.
At this point, I'm doing everything I can
to keep her here
and get her to feel comfortable
and start to love Byron.
-And love the people in Byron, as well.
-Totally.
I feel like everything
literally hinges on this party.
Because I really want
Sarah to stay in Byron
and ultimately,
I want her to be my girlfriend.
There's a whale. Did you see that?
-What?
-I just saw it.
-They're jumping out. Incredible.
-So beautiful.
I can't believe
how amazing this view is. It's insane.
It's so nice.
Thanks for coming to my launch.
-It was so good.
-It was amazing.
So much fun.
My tan launch was such a massive success.
I could not have expected it
to go any better.
The topless waiters were hot but bulky.
-I was like, "Whoa!"
-It was a different type.
More Gold Coasty, I think.
-Yeah.
-They had bums.
-And like…
-"They had, like, bums."
If anyone's doing something extra,
it'd be you.
The tan launch in the Goldie was hectic.
I felt like we kind of got
trapped in a convo with Elle
and all of that shit happened.
And she doesn't really understand
why we're upset.
Yeah.
But I mean, with Hannah, it was ridiculous
what is going on between them.
Elle has a major problem with Hannah.
But Hannah was dropping truth bombs
about Elle everywhere on the boat.
Hannah just comes in like a Navy officer,
just had a full rig of
those belts with bombs,
just going bomb, bomb, bomb!
There was one point when she said,
"Nathan told me
that Elle wanted to hook up with him
and tried to, and he said no."
-Bomb!
-Yeah.
-My jaw…
-I know.
She said that, and I was like, "When?"
And she said, "Recently."
I just wonder if Stav knows.
-Yeah.
-No.
Elle was running around saying,
"Stav and I might get engaged."
Does Stav know that just a few weeks ago
you tried to hook up with your roommate?
Bomb!
Well, I would love to believe
that whatever happened
about the Elle situation was not true.
With her trying to hook up with Nathan.
But that came from Nathan.
I know.
-I feel sorry for Sarah, you know?
-Yeah.
Elle's relationship would be struggling
because of her feelings with Nathan.
It's pretty weird living
in the same house all together,
watching him with a new girl.
That would be driving her insane.
Wondering how it's gonna go down.
It just is a disaster.
-This is wild.
-So wild.
-It's nice to finally have you over.
-Thank you for having me.
-It's nice to finally see your house.
-Yeah.
This is the first time
I've actually been to Nathan's place
because it's so awkward around Elle.
-Is Elle here?
-Yeah, Elle's here.
-Does she know I'm here?
-Yeah, I think so. Which is fine.
-Okay.
-Is it not?
After all of the drama, the rumors
and gossip about Elle and Nathan,
I'm starting to second-guess
Nathan's character.
Everything went pretty smoothly
yesterday at Jade's tan launch.
-Yeah.
-And the girls were being nice.
-You didn't get a chance to speak to Elle.
No.
Yeah, there's definitely that fear element
of me not wanting to bring Sarah
over to my place
because Elle can make it so awkward
and make people feel so unwelcome.
And, honestly, I don't know
what to expect from this, you know?
-It's a chance for us all to have a chat.
-Yeah.
Clear the air.
To be honest, I really need to know
if Nathan and Elle
are romantically involved.
So I'm going to confront them and just
find out what's going on once and for all.
-Hi.
-Yummy.
I'm surprised to see you here. But happy.
I'm glad we get to sit down
and finally talk.
-Yeah, me too.
-Yeah.
It's good to have her around.
I know.
I didn't want it to feel like
it was awkward in your own house.
-But I know you guys will be all good.
-Yeah.
Yeah, I'm so sorry for all of that.
I totally understand
how all of that may have made you feel
because I am now sort of
on the receiving end of that same behavior
and everyone ganging up on me now.
I don't want to have
any animosity between you and I.
I don't.
But all the girls around me
are basically trying
to pin all of this on me.
I just do not want
to have anything to do with Hannah.
She's completely lost
all my respect. Completely.
Interesting that you say that,
because Hannah came up
and spoke to me yesterday
and had stuff to say about you guys.
Hannah said to me
that you guys have a romantic history.
Oh, my God.
And that something
might still be going on.
That's nothing new.
Every single day we go out.
We always rock up to the events together
because we live together.
We're always in each other's pockets
because we're such good friends.
People just say, "You guys…"
Like, they pin that on us all the time.
It's nothing new.
-And look…
-We're not…
-We're not a thing. I'm with Stav.
-Yeah.
Way back…
Way back when we first met,
we kissed one time.
You guys, you mean. Like, you guys kissed.
That's where she's getting it from.
Fuck. Like, nothing's happened
while Sarah and I have been together.
The fact of the matter is,
I don't have feelings for Elle.
I actually only have feelings for Sarah.
Even if Elle and I had history before,
like, why would that even matter anyway?
-You know what I mean? Like even…
-I'm in a committed relationship.
-Exactly. You know?
-Nathan's with you.
You have nothing to worry about.
I don't trust Elle one bit.
I just need to, like, process
everything that I've learnt today.
I really so badly want to believe
that Nathan is telling the truth.
All right, I gotta go home.
-I've got stuff to think about.
-You've got a lot to process.
But there is something about
the way Elle spoke to me.
I have a sneaking feeling that something's
still going on with Nathan and Elle.
I just…
I don't know where to go from here.
At Jade's tan launch,
there was a lot of tension.
You can be on this side.
You're in that green one.
I invited everybody over to my house
so Hannah and Elle can clear the air.
I got you… I got your flannel.
I recently went and did art therapy,
and that was super helpful for me.
So I am taking what I learned there
and sort of trying to
apply that to this situation.
I've got your canvas,
and we're waiting till Elle comes.
And then I'll explain
what we're about to do.
I love you, but this is going
to be really interesting.
What? We'll see, we'll see.
But I'm here to help, guys.
-Hannah is copping it from Elle.
-Hello.
Oh, fuck. She's here.
-She's coming.
Hi.
I hope that the art therapy
gets us all back together as friends,
but it's very awkward
having Hannah and Elle around each other
because they just go at each other.
Hi, hi, hi.
We all look cute.
-Yeah, everyone looks cute.
-I love your hair.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
I needed to get in the vibe.
-Let's do it.
-Yeah.
Cai had no idea what was coming.
Thank you for blocking me on Instagram.
-You're welcome.
-Yeah, that's right.
"Thanks for blocking me on Instagram."
And I'm like, "Hey, you're welcome."
All right, well, we're all here
to do some paint therapy,
so let's get to it.
Basically, we're trying to
get how you're feeling.
I want to see this tension on canvas.
And I want to understand why.
-All right.
-Yeah?
Okay.
I am one of the most generous,
loving, open-hearted people that I know.
But at the same time,
if someone dishonors me,
I certainly wouldn't want to be them.
So, going around the circle…
Elle, starting with you.
What color did you pick and why?
I needed to get the black paint
because I'm feeling hurt,
and I feel like the black paint
really emanates that emotion.
Elle has a problem with me
because she knows
that I can see through
her light and love bullshit.
Why are you feeling hurt?
I'm feeling hurt because I just feel
like friendships have broken down
all because of something
that was very miniscule.
Who are you referring to
when you say that?
Hannah.
You told Sarah
that I had some sort of
romantic connection
with Nathan in the past
and that we are still together.
But he brought that up
with me about you guys.
What? That we kissed?
You are two-faced.
I'm not two-faced!
-You are.
-You are!
You are.
And I just don't want to
associate myself with that anymore.
I'm happy for us to not be friends,
-but I will be civil.
-I'm so happy for us not to be friends.
I'm not someone to be fucked with.
Whatever. I'm just over it.
It just seems like this battle
going up and up.
We wanted to clear the air,
but it's just made things
a whole lot worse.
Hannah's news broke my heart
because I felt like I finally met
a guy who I could trust.
But I'm really starting to doubt myself
and my judgment of people.
-Hello.
-Hey. How are you?
Yeah, good. You look very nice today.
Thank you.
I'm going out to a party later.
I called Mom to get some advice
to make sure that I'm not
jumping to conclusions
or making a rash decision.
So, you know how I told you
I was going out with Nathan?
-Yeah.
-I keep hearing from so many people
that Nathan's flatmate Elle and him
have something going on.
I asked them both about it,
and he, like, flat-out denied it.
So I can't trust Nathan.
I just don't know what to do because
I really, really, really like Nathan.
What he's done for me since I moved here,
and the way he's treated me,
no one has ever done that for me before.
Like, ever. It's really hard.
I'm sorry that you're feeling
that way, lovely.
Yeah.
Do you think I should just come home?
Well, I can't really tell you what to do
because it's how you feel. It's your life.
-Yeah.
-But…
I think you should perhaps
go with your gut feeling.
If I leave, then it's, like, over.
Since I moved to Byron,
I've felt like an outsider.
-I'll talk to you again soon.
-Okay, love you.
-Okay, love you too. Bye-bye, love.
-Bye.
So, I just don't know
if it's worth staying here.
This is really hard.
-How are you?
-Hey! How are you?
Man, you've done a cracker job.
Thanks, bro. How is it?
-Looks sick, hey?
-It's amazing.
Mate, we've been slogging it out.
Thank God you're here.
Thank God I got the invite.
-Reckon everyone's gonna love it?
-Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I'm really excited for everyone
to get here, especially Sarah.
Today's about two things.
It's all about us all coming together,
having a good time,
and also for me to tell Sarah
how much she means to me.
-Looks like you put some time into this.
-Yeah, bro.
After the conversation we had with Elle,
I really need to make sure
that Sarah knows
I'm not going to do anything wrong by her.
Everyone I've talked to
is so hyped on tonight.
It's gonna be mad. Look at this place.
-Dude, this is ridiculous.
-I know.
He's done an amazing job.
He's really put an effort into this party,
so hopefully,
Sarah is going to stick around.
I'm so excited to test this
and test the dance floor a bit.
We're on again, aren't we?
We're on again. We're on.
Parties in Byron Bay,
they're definitely "anything kinda goes."
-Cheers, guys.
-Thanks for coming.
-How are you, brother?
-Good to see you.
How are you?
Hey, you.
This party is so lit.
I am so glad that I moved to Byron.
I am so glad.
This has been one of the best decisions
I've made in my life.
Before, I came here
with over a million followers and fans
who I love dearly,
but no real genuine friendships.
But now look at me.
Hello.
-Hello.
-How are you?
Good, how are you?
-You look so fuckin' hot, Hannah.
-Do I?
How was Cai's?
-Oh, my God.
-That was so funny.
It was actually so nice.
It was such a good day.
But it got a bit hectic.
-I wonder how Elle's feeling about it all.
-I was wondering about that.
How do you feel?
I want to be over it. I want us
to all be good again and to move on.
That's the same how I feel.
I don't want to be doing this anymore.
I reckon, when she comes in,
let's have a chat with her
and just say hello.
We don't want to fight with her.
-Yeah.
-And so…
Her and Hannah can figure their stuff out.
Hannah was dropping these bombs
about how supposedly Elle tried
to hook up with Nathan recently.
And I feel like Stav has no idea,
so I sort of just feel bad for him.
-Is Stav gonna be here tonight?
-I don't know if Stav's coming today.
I feel really great
about entering Nathan's event.
I'm just there to have
a great time with Stav.
So it's really important to just let go
of all the rumors about Nathan and I.
I love Stav.
He is an incredible human being.
Hello.
-How are you?
-Good.
-Hello.
-How are you?
Lovely to see you.
It's awkward.
Thanks for coming.
Here we are. Get into it.
-This is it.
-Get away. Get away.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-How are we?
-How's it going?
-You guys look beautiful.
-So do you!
-You smell good!
You know,
I want to move forward with it all.
She's a good friend of ours.
That is the cutest dress.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
Yeah. I'm really good.
-You feeling okay after yesterday?
-Yeah, I actually am.
You know what? I don't wanna
keep going on about this.
-We are all friends.
-Yeah.
And I do love you,
but I don't want to be told
that I'm ganging up on you.
Yeah, that's fair.
I guess it was more so just me speaking
about how I felt at that time.
I'm glad that everything is cool with us,
but I don't have an interest in building
or maintaining a relationship
with Hannah right now.
It is going to be very difficult for me
to ever form a new friendship with Hannah
based off the amount of lies,
deceit, betrayal
and two-faced behaviors
that I have experienced with her.
We'll all be good moving forward, okay?
We'll all be good,
and you and Hannah will work out.
-Yeah, you guys sort it out.
-In time.
I'm actually a big cuddly teddy bear
that is so affectionate
and wants to give everyone love
and spread my light everywhere.
But on the other hand,
you don't really want to fuck with me.
-Cheers.
-Is Sarah here?
-No, she isn't.
-I caught up with Sarah.
-Did you?
-She was at my house.
-How did that go?
I basically just apologized
for everything.
-That's nice.
-I said I just wanna move forward
in building a friendship
because she's with Nathan now.
It's gonna be awkward
if we don't get along
-and I wake up and she's in my kitchen.
-Yeah.
I was wondering how…
Yeah, no, that's good.
At the end of the day,
I just want Nathan to be happy.
He deserves to be happy.
It's still something
that I don't quite understand.
You and Nathan are in a good place?
-Yeah, we are.
-Good.
-That's good.
-And you and Stav are in a good place?
-Yeah, we're really good.
-That's good.
Being in love with Stav is like feeling
the morning sun on your face
and breathing in fresh air
every single day.
And it's been so great.
-We're in a really, sort of like…
-Yeah.
Good. I'm glad.
In all seriousness, with Sarah…
Like, obviously there's feelings there.
-I can tell.
-It's real, mate.
Like, that's the thing, we've…
Yeah, we've come a long way.
I've put myself out there,
and I'm at a point where
I've gotta throw it all on the line now,
because if she decides
that she needs to leave,
I need to know
that I've done everything I possibly can.
I think I've done enough.
Fuck, you've done even more
than I've ever seen you. That's love.
I love it! He's opened up!
-He's coming through.
-Thanks, bud.
Good to see you.
Thanks for coming, bro.
It'll be a good one.
I honestly cannot wait
for Sarah to get here.
I just wish she would hurry up because,
you know, she's running pretty late.
Hi, it's Sarah. Leave a message.
Hey, lovely. How are you?
Just wondering when you're coming.
Everyone's here.
So, I hope to see you soon.
Give us a call.
Coming to this town,
I had the biggest hopes and dreams,
and I really hoped
that this was going to work.
I just feel like this town has broken me.
That's not a party face. What's happened?
Don't cry.
-Sorry.
-Don't cry.
Apart from you there's not a soul
in this town that I can trust.
Is it Nathan?
When I'm with him, it's like, amazing.
But then I just feel like…
Something is just happening under my nose
that he won't acknowledge,
but everybody else seems to be
talking about it.
Like, there's just so much stuff
that people are saying
that's happening between Nathan and Elle,
and I just don't want to be
caught in the middle of it.
As in, the two of them are a thing?
I like Nathan so much.
But… sometimes feelings for someone
is just not enough.
I just can't, like, compete with…
a flatmate that has feelings for him
and the hostility, everything.
It's just… It's all too much.
I can't trust anyone in this town.
It honestly feels so crap to be
in the middle of all these hidden agendas.
Does Nathan know?
I feel like if I stay…
there's always going to be that…
little thing of doubt
in the back of my mind.
And I don't want to be wondering
what he's doing or anything.
-I just can't do it.
-Yeah.
I feel like I've given this town
everything I've got,
and I've tried so hard to make it work.
I don't want you to go.
You're the only friend
I've made in this town.
It's like I'm gonna lose my only friend.
-Not that I want to guilt you.
-I'm so sorry.
You've gotta…
This has got to work for you.
And if it's not enough for you
to stay here for him, I get that.
I don't wanna leave
and I'm gonna miss you
and I feel so bad, but…
-I love you so much, babe.
-Me too.
I really want you to be happy.
And I want you to just, you know,
do everything you wanted to do.
I feel like I'm in a tug-of-war
with my head and my heart.
This is not something
that I'm taking lightly.
Thank you. I fucking love you so much.
-I do too.
-I'm so grateful for you, honestly.
Because when I make my mind up,
it's final.
So if I leave…
it's over between Nathan and I.
Hi! It's Sarah, leave a message.
-Caiser.
-You good?
Where's Sarah, mate?
I kept an eye on you before.
So, did you try calling her just before?
I'm literally…
I've been calling her all night.
Everything's starting to become
pretty real now.
I've heard nothing from Sarah,
and, you know,
I'm spinning out of my own head
as to what's happened to her,
where is she,
and why she hasn't contacted me.
And it's actually, you know,
everything's starting to cave in.
I'm really struggling.
I've sent her a text. Nothing.
It's really shit to see Nathan like this,
because he's been working hard
on a lot of different things,
and I think, in his eyes, he sort of saw
everything coming together tonight.
And it's just not really working that way.
Sarah's not here and it's rattling him.
Don't jump to conclusions.
Maybe she's still on her way.
It's a good night.
All these people are here for you.
I know, bro. I know. I get that.
I get that, but she's not here, bro.
The one person…
Obviously, I love having you guys here,
but, like, I was expecting her
to be here by my side the whole time.
I genuinely don't know why she's not here.
I'm starting to question
what's been going on.
Hey, it's okay.
-Spirits up. Come on, bro. It's okay.
-I love you, bro.
Nathan's my homey. I'll always
be there for him if he needs me.
-Big teddy bear.
-Thanks, bro.
Do not do that. Do not…
Stav and I have
a lot of challenging mechanics
in our relationship
that need to be worked through.
Long-distance relationships
can definitely be tough.
-Well, you look beautiful tonight.
-Thank you.
-It's so nice that you're here.
-Yeah.
I know that we've had, like,
a lot of challenges.
Obviously, you know, me living in my house
with Nathan, and you not being there.
He's been a great friend.
I'm glad you guys have been
through this together.
-I'm glad I'm here now.
-Yeah.
I love you so much.
You're so cute.
-Elle…
-Yeah.
-I love you so much.
And there's so many opportunities
that we have in our future together.
I know.
And I cannot express my love
for you anymore
than I can do right now.
Elle, will you marry me?
Are you cheeking around?
They got engaged.
-What?
-They got engaged.
This engagement has come out of the blue,
and I don't know if we're ready for it.
But we're on a mission to save the world,
and what better way to do that
together with someone that you love?
Thank you, everybody.
I have asked this woman to be my wife.
And what did you say?
Yes.
Thank you.
Stav!
-So amazing.
-Surprise, surprise.
I'm so happy for them.
-They make a lot of sense.
-No you're not.
You're not. You're definitely not.
Stav, man.
Come on.
What kind of spell has she got you under?
-Breathe in, breathe out.
-I know that.
Terrific.
I cannot deal with that right now.
Personally, I wouldn't want to get engaged
where, like…
the guy who I've been hooking up with
is also there, but…
love is mysterious.
Congratulations.
You fucking cute people.
You're beautiful. You guys are the best.
That's probably one of my biggest fears
is dropping to the knee. It's huge.
Based on things
that have happened in the past
and things that Elle's said to me,
I don't know how long it's gonna last.
Good job. You've done well.
Nathan looked really shocked
by the engagement.
There's been a lot on my mind,
but that was the smartest thing I've done.
-Nice.
-Thank you.
Yeah, baby.
Nathan loves me, and I can only imagine
that it's a little bit difficult
for Nathan to not be
my number one go-to anymore.
But he's with Sarah.
Good.
But where is Sarah? Where is she?
I'm walking into Nathan's party
without my wingman, and it sucks.
Everyone is so rattled.
Hey, Mr. Margarita.
-Can I have a chat with you?
-Yeah, of course.
Thanks.
I'm not sure
how Nathan will react to this.
-You happy with how tonight's going?
-Mate, it's been going good.
But I'm fucking… I'm rattled.
Obviously, like, Sarah's not here.
And I've called her a bunch of times.
I texted her.
I had a very sad Sarah in my office
this afternoon.
-Yeah?
-Bawling her eyes out.
And… a packed car,
and she's gone.
She's just said she's had enough.
She can't do it anymore.
I think all of Byron's just got to her.
And look, I get it.
It's a small town,
and it is an insular environment here.
Like, you run into everyone.
It's tough to break through that.
You've been here long enough,
where it's not a thing for you.
But I think for Sarah,
it was such a strong thing,
she wasn't accepted by these girls.
And then the girls just turned on her.
And then, there's this rumor about,
you know, Elle and you,
and it's just compacted on her.
And she doesn't know what to do,
and, like, she was devastated.
She brought this up with me
and I quashed it straight away,
and I told her there's nothing going on.
And on top of that,
I've done everything I possibly can
to show her how much I care about her.
I'm really, really devastated
that Sarah's listened to whatever rumor,
and she actually believes
that Elle and I have something.
I really believe that she loves you.
I think that scared her
that she didn't feel secure
and she didn't feel
like she had a place here.
I guess this town just isn't a fit
for everyone.
It's still your party.
-Yeah.
-Let's get on with it.
Thanks for telling me.
The worst part about all of this is
I could really see a future with Sarah.
And I've literally stopped at nothing
to show her how much I care for her.
And now she's gone.
Where did I go wrong?
I feel like I've tried everything.
But this town just doesn't seem
to want to accept me.
I feel like I've had my heart broken.
It's so upsetting.
I just wish she was here.
And it fucking hurts.
Look, 90% of the time,
we're posting the good times,
but it's not always that way.
Nothing is perfect.
But at the end of the day,
all any of us want
is just to connect with somebody.