All right, ladies,
so coming into down stretch position,
so just draw your hips forward. That's it.
Good. Last one.
So nice, ladies. All done.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
-I'll see you next time. Thanks, ladies.
-Thanks so much.
God, my arms are shaking.
That last exercise kinda got me.
You guys are too good for me to be
doing this with you. I need new friends.
But I needed that. I needed that today.
-But how are you? Yeah?
-I'm good. I'm really good.
But I heard so much happened
at the Spirit Night with Simba.
Elle didn't make it
to Simba's Spirit Night.
She missed a lot that went down.
I heard there was a huge blow-up.
Yup. So Nathan went to confront Elias and…
-It went pear-shaped.
-Oh, my God.
Elle's quite protective of Nathan.
They live together,
they've been good friends for ages.
He was, like, boiling point.
It must've really got to him.
And look, Nathan and Elias
have been friends for a very long time.
So their friendship was solid
prior to Sarah coming to town.
To me, I think Sarah needs
to really take the reins on it.
Yeah.
Nathan feels like family to me.
And I just think there's unnecessary
drama going on because of Sarah.
Do you think she's doing it for attention?
Do you think she loves the drama?
I'm genuinely confused
about who she is as a person.
-And that's been my thought from day one.
-Yeah.
Such a shame that you weren't there, but,
what have you been up to?
I've just been absolutely under the pump
to deliver this epic fundraiser
for Beyond Coral
ocean restoration foundation.
I don't know if you saw,
I posted a photo of me being a mermaid.
Yeah, I did see that.
I'm gonna have
a sculpture of me on display
as a mermaid.
Why didn't I think
about a sculpture of myself at my event?
There is not one person I know
that could pull off being a mermaid,
other than yourself, Elle.
-She'll be Queen Elle. We'll stand around.
-Queen Elle, the mermaid.
I guess you could say I naturally have
people and tribes gravitate towards me.
And being a leader in this community,
I'm hoping to inspire people.
It's gonna be such a cool mix of people
going to the event.
So obviously you girls, the whole crew.
-So Alex, Sarah…
-You are going to invite Sarah?
Yeah, look, I am.
I think there's so much power
in being the bigger person,
and putting your own issues aside
for the greater good,
which is to save the oceans.
But at the same time,
if Sarah causes a stir at my fundraiser,
I will definitely pull her into line.
Since moving to Byron,
I've certainly felt like an outsider.
But I'm not gonna take
this bullshit anymore.
-Hi.
-Hey. There she is.
I'm really enjoying
hanging out with Nathan.
There's a natural connection,
and I hope he feels the same way.
-Thank you for coming.
-Thank you for inviting me.
It's been a minute since we hung out.
After being called a fuckboy,
and all the drama that happened,
I'm super keen to
put all the bullshit behind us
and just move on
in the direction that we left off on.
The day that we hung out,
it was so good, so sweet.
I had heaps of fun. I was like, "Sweet."
"I think we're onto something,
that we're gonna hang out a bit more,"
but it just turned
into a shit show for a while.
But it's really nice that you came.
You look beautiful, honestly.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
It's really nice
to have some one-on-one time.
-I was really nervous actually.
-Really? Why?
I don't know.
Just 'cause we haven't hung out,
then all the stuff happened.
It's the first time
that we actually get to sit down and talk
without anyone else around.
Yeah.
I appreciate that you got to know me
and we could hang out,
and you didn't listen
to everybody else's bullshit.
'Cause that happens a lot.
I completely understand,
and it's happened to me as well, you know?
All of the gossip and rumors
that I heard about Nathan,
I'm just not paying any attention to it.
You cannot win, hey.
Hannah told me that
some girls were saying shit about me.
That I'm fake and I don't fit in.
Honestly, there's been a few times
where people have put things in my head.
Was it Elle? Just tell me.
Because I've heard after Cai's exhibition,
Elle was saying some pretty, like,
not that nice things about me.
I feel like you just answered
your own question.
Nathan has confirmed that
Elle is going around saying that I'm fake.
I've been nothing but nice to Elle,
so it hurts a little bit.
But the last thing I wanted
was to let it ruin the date.
We should stop talking about serious stuff
and just do some shots.
You want some shots?
-We're at a tequila bar.
-I have to agree with that.
Can we get two tequila shots?
-Thank you. I can smell it. It's strong.
-Thank so much.
-Cheers.
-That eye contact.
You gotta…
No, it's fun. That was good.
Your necklace is tangled.
-Hold on.
-Thank you.
-I think it's the other side.
-Okay.
-Hold on.
It was tangled.
-Did you get it? Thank you.
-Yeah, I got it.
I don't know if that's his move.
But it kind of works
because it left me wanting more.
Honestly, thanks for coming.
It was really nice.
Tastes like margaritas.
-How's things?
-Obviously, Nathan, everything he said.
-He rubbed me up the wrong way.
-Yeah.
I've got a true opinion of you in my head.
I think you're an egotistical fuck.
And I also think that you are
seriously, seriously insecure.
No doubt, it upset me.
He feels hurt,
apparently about the fuckboy comment.
But he made some really low blows.
When Nathan came at me
with that final line,
"You're an egotistical, insecure fuck,"
it was like, "That's you, mate.
That is literally you to a tee."
Shut the fuck up.
So what do you wanna do?
What are you thinking?
I'm gonna wait,
bide my time, and get him one-on-one.
That how I need to speak to him.
One-on-one.
I think that's a good way
of looking at it because
you don't want him
to be in that space of ego and persona.
You wanna get him exactly
where he is closer to his authenticity
and confront him then, because I feel like
he'll just try to trigger you
and not listen to what you're saying.
Yeah, 'cause at the end of the day,
I can control myself.
-I don't know if he can.
-Yeah.
It's gone beyond rivalry.
I just wanna to have
man-to-man conversation with Nathan
and knock this out.
I just need to be ready to fight back.
Let's go hard.
Oh, my God. You look amazing.
Yeah. Surprise.
Honestly, you look phenomenal.
I'm so glad
that I've grown my hair this long
'cause I look like a legit mermaid.
Having my partner Stav
back in Byron is great
because the CHARM fundraiser is fast
approaching and there's so much to do.
We're about to turn you
into a sculpture now.
-Perfect. Let's do it.
-Perfect.
Ready, don't move. I'm gonna scan you.
It's gonna take about
30 seconds to a minute.
CHARM is our ocean conservation project,
and the scans that Stav is taking today
will be used to turn me
into a life-size mermaid sculpture.
Me being scanned as a mermaid
will bring about more conscious attention
to saving our coral reefs.
I just finished it up.
-All right.
-Wow. That is so cool.
Can you make my boobs bigger?
-Yes, we can do anything.
-Okay, good.
So many people all over the world
refer to me as sunshine.
I can help shift the consciousness
of people all around me.
I feel like a real-life Wonder Woman.
That's what Stav calls me.
You're an absolute weapon
in the business world.
And you're a weapon
in the engineering world.
I think with our powers combined,
there's so much great
we can do in the world.
And starting with the oceans,
that's just the tip of the iceberg.
There are a lot of important people
coming to my fundraiser.
Nothing is going to crush my day.
I think that it's gonna be a great event.
Cai is probably
the only person left on the planet
that at this age, its normal to have
a Slip 'N Slide at your house.
We're grown-arse men.
Far out. That thing was fun.
Oh, my God.
Man, it hurts a little bit.
-It's dangerous but that's how I like it.
-Yeah.
I mean, when you have a hill like this,
you gotta use it.
A lot's happened with you.
You went on a date last night.
-How do you know that?
-Little birdies told me.
-Word goes too fast.
-I'm a man about town. What can I say?
Yeah. Sarah and I went on a little,
I guess you can call it a date.
So what happened? Come on. Fill me in.
You're glowing a little bit. Like…
-Did you kiss?
-Yeah, we kissed.
-Really?
-We kissed.
My man had it in him. Okay.
That's good, man. I'm happy for you.
So how do you feel about Sarah now?
Are you moving forward with this?
She's actually a great girl,
and, in a way, I care for her
because I feel sorry for her
that she's being judged,
and then on the other side,
Elle's really protective over me.
And I can tell
that she's just like, "Nah."
From what Nathan has told me about Elle,
it sounds like she's got a crush on him.
And I think Elle's a little bit jealous
of Sarah taking up all Nathan's time.
All this stuff with Elle, does that mean
you're not gonna bring Sarah home?
Elle's pinging crystals at her.
-Sarah's sonic voicing her.
-"Eat quartz!"
We can write a comic book about this.
Oh, God.
I'm definitely in a bit of a hard place
with Elle not liking Sarah,
and Elle being my housemate.
It's definitely making things difficult.
So how was all that
fire action the other night?
Yeah, mate.
That kind of got out of hand a bit.
Elias and I aren't
really good at the moment.
I thought you and Elias
were not that type of friendship
for him to throw you under the bus.
-What he said.
-You'd think so, right?
Elias has just completely
disregarded my feelings,
calling me a fuckboy and all of that.
But things are going well
between Sarah and I.
So fuck him. I don't care anymore.
I bet you can't go all the way
from the top on the board.
-Standing up?
-Yeah.
-All right.
-Let's do it.
Yay! That looks cute.
-Yay! Let me see.
-Yeah.
These are cute.
-What about you send a couple to Nathan?
-I should 'cause we went out.
-Did you know we went out?
-Did you?
-Like a real, proper date?
-Yeah.
Did you pash or anything?
Oh, my God. You did!
I literally have not stopped
thinking about him.
He must've done something right.
-Did you go back to Nathan's place?
-It was the first date.
I wasn't gonna go back to his place.
No, I was a good girl.
-But he lives with Elle, doesn't he?
-Yeah.
So you couldn't go back to his place.
Yeah, it would've been awkward.
That's a massive roadblock.
She posts all over Instagram
about being a spiritual warrior,
woman connected to the earth
and full of crystals. A bunch of shit.
-Yeah.
-Take a mirror, girl.
Elle has nothing nice to say about me.
And Nathan told me she's called me fake
and I don't know why.
I think that's Saskia and Frimmy
up on a horse.
-You can smell the wealth, can't you?
-I'm not into it.
I knew Byron was a small town,
but you can't go anywhere
without seeing somebody you know
and it sucks.
-Hey, guys.
-Hello.
-Howdy.
-Hi.
As much as I don't
wanna see Sarah right now,
it is one good opportunity
for Sarah to take responsibility
for what's happened
between her, Elias and Nathan.
What have you been up to? What's new?
After Simba's the other day,
how did that play out with the two boys?
I know how Nathan feels
about the situation,
'cause I went on a date with him.
We had a good chat about everything.
-You went on a date with him?
-A date?
He and I get on really well
and it's just super easy.
We just ended up drinking tequila
and having D&Ms all night.
But you like Elias as well.
Yeah. The whole thing that started off was
I wanted to make friends
and get to know people.
Doesn't it make you feel
like you shouldn't maybe see Elias
if that's gonna cause
spanner in the works?
I don't know why she's doing this
to two guys who are meant to be friends.
I think it's immature.
I think she should be
addressing it herself.
You gotta stop causing beef
between two guys.
Hey, but you're not causing the beef.
-No.
-They have beef between themselves.
You are, without trying to.
Byron's a pretty macho place.
It's pretty small place,
and so you don't wanna jump
on everyone's toes.
I feel bad for the fight
between Nathan and Elias,
but Saskia's attitude towards me
is so unfair.
And I'm sick of being judged.
All right. Good luck with the horses.
-Thanks.
-We'll leave you to your horsy ride.
-Bye.
-Bye, guys.
What the actual fuck?
I don't know where Saskia's coming from.
Why's it Sarah's responsibility to resolve
a conflict between Elias and Nathan?
They're two grown-arse men.
Work it out yourselves.
So many things that they just said,
they were so judgy.
As if, like, "You've just come here.
You've caused all this drama."
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
What did I do?
I would never accost somebody on the beach
on a literal and figurative high horse
and start questioning
their motives and character.
And if this is
what they're saying to my face,
I can only imagine
what they're saying behind my back.
Okay, so I think that we should do
a silk set in this fabric.
-You love it, don't you?
-Yeah.
I'm obsessed with this.
I'm so excited I'm doing
a collaboration collection with Jade.
Jade doesn't really know
a lot about designing,
but he has the following
and that's all that matters.
We could do color
if you wanted to, on a T-shirt,
'cause guys wear colorful T-shirts.
-I think we'll leave the color out.
-Yeah.
We're not going Gold Coast.
You live in Byron Bay now, all right?
It's a different town.
A collaboration is where an influencer
comes together with a brand
and they put their own type of spin
on the clothing line.
This is a dream come true.
So what's been going on?
How do you feel about Alex?
He obviously doesn't want
to be my friend, so I'm cool with that.
Yeah.
I'm sick and tired of talking about Alex.
I don't have the energy for it.
I'm not doing it.
I saw Elle and Saskia the other day
and we were talking
about Elle's fundraiser.
Oh, my God. Okay. She's doing
a mermaid sculpture of herself.
-Hold on.
-Yeah, a lot is happening.
A sculpture of her as a mermaid?
-Is that what she's going for?
-I think so.
That makes more sense.
I thought you meant her as normal person.
At the door, there's another Elle.
I really don't know
what Elle does with her charity,
but having a sculpture of herself
at her event is so fucking extra.
In my head
I'm just seeing mermaids and robots.
There's a lot going on right now.
I'm there like, "Get me another drink."
Let's hope there's alcohol.
Do you think there's ever been
a robot mermaid party in Byron?
No, I don't think so.
This is definitely a one-off concept.
-Here they are.
-Hey.
-Hey, great to see you.
-Geniuses.
Hey, this looks amazing.
So who's in the guest list?
We've invited, obviously, all of our crew.
Elias is gonna come.
-Is he?
-Yeah.
-Have you spoken to him?
-I haven't said anything to him.
-Is everything good with you guys?
-I don't think so.
I really hope that Nathan and Elias
can leave their differences aside
because I can't afford
any issues at my event.
-Oh, my goodness.
-Hey, guys.
How are you?
The community of Byron are very
passionate about environmental issues.
And there's a lot that's riding
on this fundraiser,
so it's so important
to really impress these people.
-Oh, my God, mermaids.
-There's a merman as well.
Oh, my God, there's a merman.
-There's a merman.
-Oh, my God.
This is totally a Byron party.
This is one of the reasons
why I moved here.
-He's so hot. Hello.
-Give him a wave.
Naughty. Naughty boy.
Here's the troublemaker.
This is great.
I love the merman outfits.
They're a real vibe.
So what is today? Is it a fundraiser?
We've got CHARM the coral farming robot
here for the first time.
-There's a robot here?
-The robot is here.
We're also raising awareness about
how we actually rehabilitate the reefs,
with the mermaid,
which we'll talk about later.
-Okay, great.
-Yeah.
It's hypocritical
that Elle's trying to save the ocean
whilst serving tuna canapes.
Won't the mermaids get upset?
-Cheers, guys.
-Well done. To CHARM.
To CHARM. I love the name.
I'm so excited for Elle's fundraiser,
but I've kinda figured out
that Elias isn't coming.
I'm sorry to break it to you,
but I ran into Elias at the gym.
And look…
I should've probably called you but…
He just said, briefly,
that he might not come tonight.
He wants to talk to you. One-on-one.
-About a few situations… I know.
-I'm ready.
-But away from everyone.
-Absolutely. He hasn't contacted me.
In his position, I would have
come to the fundraiser, no matter what.
But if he really thinks he can't control
his anger and aggression that much,
that just raises another whole issue.
Done.
-So what's been happening?
-I actually went on a date with Sarah.
-Do you like her?
-She's cool. She's definitely cool.
-I like her. As in we've connected.
-Yeah.
-And we get each other.
-That's good.
-Not everyone has accepted her.
-That's the thing, right?
I'm not exactly sure
why Elle doesn't like Sarah.
-She needs to give her a go.
-She does.
And in some ways, I feel like she doesn't
want to give her a go for whatever reason.
I think there is a sense of jealousy
from Elle when it comes to Sarah.
I've heard of one reason in particular.
But I'm going to try to keep it a secret.
Oh, my gosh. Dave and I
went horse riding the other day,
and next minute
I see two stragglers coming up.
And it's Alex and Sarah.
And I was like, "Oh."
Sarah was chatting and she mentioned
that her and Nathan went on a date.
How do you feel about her?
Yeah, I was surprised.
I find it really weird
that Nathan hasn't told me
he's been on a date with Sarah.
I mean, Nathan tells me everything.
He can do better than her.
I don't know her very well,
that could be me, but anyways…
I wanna know about what it's for.
I went swimming in the reef
and it was fine, but I'm not sure.
Half of the reef is dead
all around the world.
Really? The Great Barrier Reef?
-Have you heard of coral bleaching?
-No.
You haven't heard of coral bleaching?
From people pouring bleach in?
No.
Wait, what?
I'm so sorry, I wanna know. I'm confused.
I had swam in the coral reef
and it looked beautiful.
I didn't know it was dying
'cause when I seen it, it looked fine.
Darling, I really wanna
show you Stav's invention.
-Coral farming robot. Come with.
-Okay.
-A coral farming what? Okay.
-Robot.
It's really important
that the guests understand
the intention of what we're doing.
I hope Jade would help spread messages
of social change to his followers.
So what we've got
basically is an invention
that can hopefully save the coral reefs.
-Like this machine here?
-Yeah.
-Look, there's little corals.
-There's little corals.
We're growing coral
and we're going to replant it in the reef.
-Does this regrow the coral?
-Yes.
I thought this collected something.
Sorry. See, already…
No, it's okay. So corals are like animals
and they have sex once a year.
This machine has sex?
That's why we call it
"husbandry" technology.
-Can she help me have sex?
-Potentially.
There's animals having sex
with this machine right now?
Not right now. Only one night a year.
Okay.
Sometimes when people speak smart to me
and I don't know what's going on,
I just nod and look like I understand,
but really I have no fucking idea.
Did you pass your 12th?
You did, didn't you?
Every smart person
that does this have done year 12.
I didn't do year 12. I missed out.
-How was your date?
-What date?
-Yeah.
We saw Alex and Sarah on the beach
and she, you know, explained to us
that you had a little date night.
Yeah, no, we went on a little date.
We went to Mexican.
That's cute.
Hung out, actually heard her,
where she's been
and heard her troubles
and her struggle, I guess.
She's just moved to Byron
and she doesn't really understand
how all of these friendships work
and who sits where and like, basically,
the lay of the land.
I understand where she's coming from.
She's confused
about who's friends with who.
But she hasn't given herself
the time of day to explain herself.
I feel like there's a part of her, which…
She's still playing two dudes at once,
at the end of the day.
The really reason I'm defensive
is because of you.
I'm pissed off because she thinks
that she can cause drama.
That's not cool.
I don't want to see you like that.
Saskia is on her mission
when it comes to Sarah.
Possibly, Elle has gotten in her ear.
You guys are more wound up
about this than I am.
-Everyone just have a drink, relax.
-You need to tell me more.
Cai!
Yes.
-Look who he's here with.
-Everybody looks so good.
I've agreed to go to Elle's fundraiser
for one reason only.
Elle and Nathan, they're really close.
So I'm going to try to make an effort
to move past all of our issues
for the sake of
my relationship with Nathan.
Hello. Hi, how are you?
-Hey, beautiful, how are you?
-Hi.
-How's things?
-Good. How are you?
I'm great. I'm great.
-You look beautiful.
-Thank you.
-Hello, Sarah. Stephen.
-Hi. Hey, how're you?
-Thanks for coming. You look nice.
-Thank you for having me. So do you.
So this is essentially
a fundraiser for the rebuilding of coral?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, I love that.
I'm all for saving the ocean.
I love the ocean.
I can't imagine Sarah would've
gone to an event like this before,
and I really do hope that she brings
her best behavior to the table.
I heard there was going to be mermaids,
so I need to see some mermaids.
-Hi.
-Can we get a photo?
Don't you splash me, you little devil.
I don't think Jade's gonna
offer me an olive branch anytime soon.
So as much as it pains me, I'm gonna be
the bigger person and offer it to him.
-You're so sexy.
-He vibes.
-Look how jealous Nathan is.
-Nathan, get one.
Do something crazy.
I need something crazier.
You look great. Sexy merman.
Hi.
Can I talk to you,
like a little turn on the daybed?
I was having such a great time.
Mood kill, vibe killer.
-How are you?
-Good.
I just don't want to have any drama
at Elle's event.
Yeah, I don't either. That's why
I wanted to have a chat with you.
I'd love to sit down,
have a conversation with you
outside of all of these people
just to say why I said what I said.
-Okay.
-Just no, like, judgment.
-Just a conversation.
-There was judgment at the start.
-Sure.
-That's why I'm…
I just want to see
if there's a way forward for us.
I'm determined to get to the bottom
of his follower situation.
But maybe my approach was a little off.
I want to have a conversation with Jade
one-on-one without an audience.
-Okay, well, next week? Yeah.
-Meet next week.
-Yeah.
-Okay, awesome.
-Thanks, Alex. Okay.
-See you next week.
Oh, my God.
I'm chatting with Alex next week.
-What did he say?
-He wants to have a chat outside of this.
Where does he want to go?
I don't know. I feel like
it was more authentic that time.
I love you.
-Love you.
-You cute little biscuit.
-You come with Cai?
-Yeah, I was nervous.
I hung out in the car park for ages.
-Why were you nervous?
-I'm just… I feel…
I feel a little awkward.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-You look beautiful.
-You look really beautiful.
-Your eyes look incredible.
Really? They just got extra green
when I saw you.
-I love this girl. Really cute.
-She's cute, eh?
So how are we?
Good, yeah.
-I'm just a little bit…
-The girls?
I haven't spoken to any of them,
and I don't want to cause a scene.
What's the vibe like?
I'm not gonna lie.
I know that Elle isn't so…
She's not a fan of yours.
I was quite surprised
that you were even here.
Yeah. She doesn't know who I am.
That's what I mean.
I get to know someone before I hate them.
-Much better strategy.
-Exactly.
Then you have a right
to be up on that high horse.
Otherwise you're up there
clip clopping, looking stupid.
-I know.
-Speaking of high horses…
-We did meet up with Saskia and Dave.
-Yes.
Maybe a little bit awkward,
but Saskia and Elle have definitely…
I don't really understand
why Elle and Saskia have an issue with me.
None of them have made
any effort to know me.
Should Sarah say something?
Do you feel comfortable
having a conversation with her?
I just don't want it to escalate.
I don't know
if I'm able to go all afternoon
and be nice to people
who have been talking shit.
-You gotta get it off your chest.
-Yeah.
You gotta have a conversation.
I've learned, get it out there.
-I'll be there.
-Yeah.
If there's fireworks, there's fireworks.
But you'll at least leave knowing
you said what you wanted to say,
with a clear conscience.
-You're gonna run into these people.
-Yeah.
I just want to have a chat to her
and talk it out,
and let's just see what happens.
Everyone, guys. We're doing speeches now.
Obviously, you've seen CHARM,
and that grows coral at scale.
But the question is,
how do we actually take that coral
that's grown in that aquarium
and rehabilitate reefs? And this is how.
Shall we?
-A mermaid.
-It's me.
-It's you?
-Elle!
-Yes.
What we've got
is an artificial coral reef,
and we can plant coral all over her.
And in a few months,
this will be a new coral reef.
That is so cool.
It's a very Elle thing to do
to tie a life-sized statue of herself
into saving the ocean.
So we want to invite some of you
to come plant coral on this right now.
Me!
Come.
We are helping change the world.
-These are the corals.
-Yeah.
You're gonna take one…
Shove that little pickle in there.
Is that fake eyelashes?
Did you put eyelashes on your mermaid?
I have this inner urge
to knock it into the pool,
just to see if it will swim
like a mermaid.
Everyone. Now we have a real-life mermaid
that is going to give
a little performance to us.
Show that life should be all about magic.
The mermaid performance reminded me
of when I'd try to show Mom
how long I could hold my breath.
-I'd love to. Right here.
-Okay, perfect.
-There we go. Perfect.
-Perfect. Thank you.
The best part, even though
these guys are little babies…
We got a new mermaid in town.
No, I didn't do that.
We think you're a mermaid anyway.
Don't need to jump in the water.
-We're acting natural.
-No…
-That was amazing. So exciting.
-You've done a great job.
I can't sit there and pretend
that everything is okay
when I have an issue or I'm upset.
So as much as I don't like this…
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Can we chat?
-Yes.
…I think I need to speak to them
because I just can't let it go.
I just wanted to pull you guys aside
because I heard a rumor that
Elle has been talking some shit about me.
-About you.
-Yeah.
Haven't been talking any shit
about you at all.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-So you didn't call me fake?
-Absolutely not.
I was infuriated.
Whatever I have said about her,
I will say to her face.
-I'll tell you exactly what I've said.
-Please do.
I still don't know anything about you.
And that I'm confused
as to who you are as a person.
You and I don't know each other very well.
But I've heard so many things
about you saying that I'm fake.
And I'm honestly sick of hearing about it.
It is weird
'cause it's coming from Nathan.
-What's up?
-I miss you.
-What did Nathan say?
-That you said I was fake.
Nathan would never say that.
-He did.
-It's not true.
Nathan's not a liar.
But he did say it.
I was absolutely gobsmacked,
but I did not want to make a scene
in front of all of our guests.
I'll tell you now, I never said
any of those things. Full stop.
If she's lying, she deserves an Emmy
because she is flat out
denying my reality.
It's tearing me down
to keep hearing this stuff.
Hannah told me, Nathan told me,
everyone keeps telling me.
I'm so sorry.
I don't care who told you what,
but right now, this is Elle's event.
You can't out-grieve the widow.
You're more upset than Elle.
No, I'm upset because…
I'm talking to my friend.
I don't want this to take away
from Elle's event.
Just leave.