I mean, there were rumors
that they were gonna
announce it next month, but they
must have gotten impatient. Okay.
Whatever they say,
we need to come up
with 10,000 possible responses
to 10,000 possible scenarios.
Okay, just to remind you,
I don't work for the National
Park Service.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How are those scenarios coming?
Okay, look.
Before we go in there,
you need to know something.
- He's here.
- Who's here?
The guy whose name you forbid
me from saying
out loud because it fills you
with rage.
Look, I don't know
who he's working for,
but I guess he's part of one
of the bidding groups.
Are you gonna be able
to be civil in there?
I'm perfectly civil.
He's the stupid garbage-head
doo-doo face.
Perfect.
Thank you all for coming.
I am Trevor Nelson, legal
council to the Newport family.
The Newport family trust intends
to sell a 25-square mile parcel
of pristine, undeveloped land
containing Lake Eagleton
and the Southern Indiana
foothills.
Why now?
The Newports have owned this
land for 100 years.
Thanks to the recent economic
boom in Pawnee,
real estate prices are at an all
time high.
And in the words of
Jessica Wicks-Newport, heir
to the entire Newport fortune,
quote, "It's time to trade
those dumb, old trees
for a butt load of cash."
It is.
It truly is.
This land is begging to be
a new national park.
And it's in my own backyard.
This could be my crowning
achievement.
I could retire.
I mean, I wouldn't.
I'm gonna work until I'm 100
and then cut back to four days
a week.
Oh, God, I'm already so bored
thinking about that one day off.
Maybe I'll go to law school
or something.
We will select the finalists
from a set of initial sealed
bids due at 5:00 P.M. tomorrow.
Good luck.
- Okay.
- Cool.
- There he is.
- What?
- Okay.
- He's here?
- He is coming over.
- I don't want to talk to him.
I should hide.
No, he should hide.
He should run.
He should run away.
He should hide his stupid face.
He shouldn't be--
Hello, Ms. Knope.
Hello, former strange person
I used to friend.
You're looking very...
Ron-like.
- You have your same hair.
- No, I don't.
I have bangs now.
I've never known what bangs are,
and I don't intend to learn.
Well, maybe you should!
I left the parks department
two years ago.
Now I work in
the private sector,
running my own building
and development company.
It's called very good building
I wanted to convey the quality
of our work
without seeming flashy.
So your company is involved
with one of the bidders?
Hell yeah, pimp!
He's on team Gryzzl now.
We, uh, hired his company
to help plan and build
our new Gryzzl campus.
Right here in town.
Oh, and that land?
Oh, my gosh.
It's perfect.
The trees and rocks and sky.
Yes, the land has good sky.
Sky!
He's so far out.
So norm-core.
You know that the National
Park System deserves this land.
Why are you trying to screw me?
This is like Morning Star all
over again.
This is nothing like
Morning Star.
And that was two years ago.
Well, you don't know
who you're dealing with.
I directly oversee 1,200 people.
I have a staff
of creative geniuses
that will not stop working
until we win this bid.
Leslie?
I-I couldn't find that file
you wanted,
but I did find a file called
bird census, 1980.
- And...it's empty.
- Get out of here, Ed!
- I fired you.
- Right.
If anyone wants to hang,
I will be at Subway.
He's very stupid.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Babe?
Just dropped off Leslie's
triplets with her mom.
All three of 'em.
Nailed it.
Look what she gave us.
Slow cooker.
- Great.
- Yeah.
Um, so hurry up and get ready.
The gala starts in an hour.
And don't forget, tomorrow we
have to go to that guy's office
to sign the renter's insurance
forms.
Get ready.
Go.
Everything is going great.
April's kicking ass at her
National Parks job.
Uh, I work there part time.
And I have my own TV show.
Welcome back to the
Johnny Karate Super Awesome
Musical Explosion Hour.
Morning, Johnny.
I have something for ya.
It's Mailman Barry.
Morning, Barry.
- I have something for you.
- Andy, no.
- Ninjas attack!
- No.
Oh!
That's my crotch.
Okay, guys.
Three more kicks a piece.
Uh, Jessica?
Hi.
I'm glad I caught you
before you left.
Just between you and me,
what do you think your land
might sell for tomorrow?
Trevor says it'll probably be
around $90 million.
Ah ha!
Woo!
- Oh.
- Oh--oh, wow.
I know.
I am just--I am so happy for me.
Would you ever consider giving
the federal government
a discount?
For a very good cause?
A national park.
Oh, Leslie.
I have always liked you.
Yeah, no, you haven't, though.
But I also like money.
And money pays for my lifestyle.
Leslie doesn't pay for my
lifestyle, money does.
So between money and Leslie...
Uhh.
- You see the bind that I'm in?
- Yeah, it's a tough one.
Well, thank you, Jessica.
You did and said exactly
what I thought
you were gonna do and say.
- And that's oddly comforting.
- Thank you, sweetie.
Who is Tom Haverford?
He's a mentor, a lover, a hero.
But who is my hero?
Simple.
It's me.
Five years from now.
Okay, I really only need
a correct spelling
of your last name.
You are looking at one of
Indiana Business monthly's
35 under 35.
I own Pawnee's
hottest restaurant,
two fast-casual eateries,
and the Tommy Chopper.
We serve chopped salads
out of a decommissioned
military helicopter.
I'm a mogul now.
Hey, Tom?
Ben Wyatt, city manager
of Pawnee.
Chamber of Commerce asked me
to introduce him
at a very fancy black tie gala
tonight.
One of the many area big wigs
who comes to me for life advice,
fashion tips.
Uh, you get it.
Write this all down.
So for the introduction,
I'd love it if you could just
keep it brief.
Like, stick to my fiscal
accomplishments.
Oh, wanna wake me up when you're
done boring us to death?
Am I right, Janet?
Write down that I'm funny.
Benji?
Relax, come on.
When's Tommy ever let you down?
Constantly.
I'm being honored at a gala
tonight because I'm in charge
of the Pawnee bicentennial
celebration.
It's my biggest project since
ice town.
So it really means a lot
that I'm being recognized
as a city leader,
instead of being yelled at
and pelted with things.
Wait, you don't think
this is all an elaborate setup
to pelt me with things, do you?
It takes like eight hours
to cook something in this thing.
I guess I could pick up
a brisket tomorrow
and start it for dinner
Thursday.
Oh, Thursday's no good.
I have production meetings
all day.
Then we've got dinner
with Joe and Donna on Friday.
Hey, you know, Sunday.
We can go
to the farmer's market,
put the brisket
in the slow cooker,
get a movie on pay per view.
The new Jason Bourne movie's
supposed to be pretty funny.
Andy?
We're planning our whole week.
Like old people.
We used to be spontaneous
and weird.
We used to eat cereal
out of frisbees
because we didn't have
any bowls.
You once broke a rib trying
to wrestle one of those
inflatable floppy guys
at a car dealership.
I won.
Now you sprained your shoulder
trying to clean out
the stupid gutter.
You even have a job.
We have a bank account!
That's it.
We've held out as long as we
could, but it finally happened.
We're boring.
We're boring people who will
bore each other by being boring.
No!
We are still fun.
I'm gonna prove it to you.
Tonight at the gala,
we are gonna do something
spontaneous and weird.
Okay.
Stop taunting me.
Get on the phone to Washington.
Call in every favor
that we have.
Dave, put Missouri on the back
burner.
This is top priority.
You all have 36 hours
to find me $90 million.
Go!
Whoa, $90 million?
Well, I only have $2 million
in the discretionary fund
and I've already used some of it
to make Thomas Jefferson sexier
in those Mount Rushmore
promotions.
Which, by the way, attendance
has been up.
That's not a coincidence.
Pawnee's rich and famous
will all be here tonight.
- Maybe you start there.
- That is a very smart idea.
And that tuxedo makes you look
like a sexy orchestra conductor.
- Here, wave this pen around.
- Focus.
Fine.
Let's go get that park.
That park is my dream.
I'm not gonna let it slip away.
Who cares if Gryzzl and Ron
have more money?
I have the most valuable
currency in America.
A blind, stubborn belief that
what I am doing is 100% right.
Ken Hotate.
Great bow tie, is that new?
Why, yes it is.
My son sells them on Etsy.
He is a huge disappointment.
Oh, well.
Now that we're chatting,
the National Park Service
is looking to buy
the Newport land.
But we're a little short
on funds.
- How short?
- $88 million.
What do you say you put some of
that casino money to good use?
You know, we have been
considering opening
a second resort.
No, it would be a donation.
The government would keep
the land.
So you would like the Wamapoke
people to pay
the federal government millions
of dollars to buy land
that was stolen from us
by the federal government?
And we don't even get to keep
the land?
Well, when you put it like
that, I see the irony.
So are you in?
No?
What if I buy some of your
disappointing son's bolo ties?
Damn it.
Hey, check it out.
I'm so crazy and spontaneous,
I don't even need this sling
anymore.
- Yes.
- Pa-dow.
Oh!
Oh, did you hear that pop?
Could you hear that?
- You wanna do shots?
- Yeah, I'd love to do a shot.
'Cause wine makes me sleepy now.
This is gonna be fun.
What do you want to do first?
Ooh.
I dare you to eat this entire
jug of olives.
Done!
- What are you doing?
- I'mma take a Zantac.
All that salt will give me
heartburn.
Oh, God.
You ruined it.
We--we have to figure something
else out.
Should I still take the Zantac?
Yeah, you always feel better
when you do.
Oh, my God, I hate us!
Let's go.
Now, I know all of you are off
doing your own things
and we don't see each other
as much as we used to,
but I need my old team back
for one last mission.
So hands in.
Defeat Ron on three.
- One, two, three!
- Ooh.
Actually, Ron promised me
I could build a restaurant
on the new Gryzzl campus so I'm
kind of totally on Ron's side.
Okay.
Tom's dead to me.
Donna?
Waiting for your hand.
Yeah, Ron hired Regal Meagle
realty to broker the deal.
And I'm gonna need the money
for my wedding.
Shia LaBeouf-designed wedding
dresses do not come cheap.
Oh, my God, you're getting
married?
That's amazing.
And you didn't tell me earlier?
How could you?
Joe popped the question
a few days ago.
I didn't post anything
on Gryzzlfeed
'cause I wanted to tell you
in person.
This is very beautiful.
And I'm furious at you.
How are you?
How are the kids?
Oh, they're great.
You know.
They're trying to destroy us.
There's three of them.
It's insane.
But they're great.
We gotta run, Les.
Sorry for totally crushing it.
And you in the process.
Later.
Well, never fear,
because Terry is here.
Yes, I go by Terry now.
Because there was a guy
at National Parks,
he was already named Larry.
So they suggested I go by Terry.
And then I said my real name is
Gary and they said, who cares.
So.
It's just a fun group.
Good evening,
and welcome to the Pawnee
Bicentennial Gala.
Not long ago, this town
was barely on the map.
Unless you were talking about
a map of the cities
with the most obese pets.
But then, one great man
came along
and he lifted all of us up.
And that man was me.
Tom Haverford.
Owner and proprietor
of the effortlessly chic,
celebrity-packed Italian
restaurant, Tom's Bistro.
And several other
establishments.
Ron?
How could you?
I simply took a skewer
for one shrimp
and added many shrimp to it.
They're long enough
for five or six.
First you try to steal my park
and now you steal my team?
I didn't steal them.
They're independent people who
have moved onto better things,
just like you did.
Bacon-wrapped shrimp.
I fit seven on this one.
It's a masterpiece.
Why don't you shove them all
in your dumb mouth
and then when I turn around,
you can stab me in the back
with the skewer?
People come up to me
and they say things like,
Tom, given all that you've
accomplished,
is it hard to stay humble?
And I say...not for me.
I'm pretty amazing
at being humble.
But, enough about me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome
Pawnee's man of the year 2017,
Mr. Ben Wyatt.
Thank you.
Thanks.
And thank you to Tom for that
moving tribute to you.
And thank you to the boys and
girls club for the incredibly
lifelike paper-mache statue.
You know, when I first moved
here--
Oh, uh.
I guess it's time for cake?
Okay.
Great.
Perfect.
Timing.
Oh, how about this?
We shut off the lights,
turn 'em back on, everybody's
fancy jewelry is missing.
Meanwhile, you and I are already
on a boat to the airport.
Let's put stink bombs
in all the vents.
- Yes.
- Wait, no.
I forgot.
I got rid of all the stink bombs
before you babysat
Leslie's kids.
Being responsible adults
sucks butts.
Butts, that's it.
I'll streak across the stage.
Yes, I love it.
I'm gonna get naked.
I'm gonna get up there.
Everyone is gonna see my weiner.
I mean, you've seen it.
You know how dumb it looks.
- Uh-huh.
- Perfect plan.
Why are you even here?
What have you ever done
for this city?
My company has stimulated
Pawnee's economy.
You're just still upset about
morning star.
I told you to never say
that word to me.
No one should ever say that word
out loud.
It's like Voldemort.
Or Ron.
You know what?
You don't deserve that candle.
- Gimme that candle!
- Let go.
- This candle's mine.
No, give me this candle.
You steal my team,
I steal your candle.
- I stole nothing.
- Guys?
- Neh.
- I want it!
- Leslie.
Stop!
It's okay.
Everything's fine.
Just wheel out the backup cake.
There is no backup cake.
Who doesn't bake a backup cake?
Okay, well that seals it.
Even Leslie is crazier
than we are.
They're still gonna serve
that cake, right?
And then I said, uh, you might
want to check with the penguin.
I get it.
You Gryzzl guys are a real hoot.
- And you have so much money.
- Thanks, Jessie.
And, hey, enjoy that new
prototype Gryzzl tablet, huh?
I will.
I just love it.
Thank you, Jessica.
I love you too.
I love your skin.
Give me your skin.
Oh.
There's still a couple bugs
with the A.I. software.
But, uh, maybe just turn it off
before you go to sleep.
All right, Donna.
Let's hit it.
- About to get some peddies.
- Okay.
Peddies on peddies on peddies.
Okay.
You're next.
Hello, Ron.
I just want you to know
that I am not sorry
that I pushed you into
a giant cake.
Well, I am sorry.
That I attended a public event.
Yo, Ron?
Come on, bud.
We're gonna go play some
video games
and we want you
to watch quietly.
After we drop off the renter's
insurance forms,
we need to stop by
the grocery store.
And then we need to sign
a suicide pact,
because our lives
are meaningless.
Babe, we are not boring people.
Would boring people get
renter's insurance,
even though it's not
legally required?
Where are we?
I have never once been to this
part of Pawnee.
It's the creepy warehouse
district.
It's mostly just raccoons
and old car batteries.
Whoa, hang on.
Pull over.
Look at that.
- This place is amazing.
- Let's go in.
What up, playa?
Just wanted to apologize
for my intro running long.
But, uh, you know.
When it comes to inspirational
Will Smith quotes,
how are you gonna stop at ten?
You know, when the chamber
of commerce asked you
to introduce me, I was a little
worried you would spend
the entire time talking about
yourself,
which is exactly what you did.
I'm sorry.
Truth is, they didn't ask me
to introduce you.
I asked them if I could do it.
I was gonna talk about how I owe
you so much.
How you stood by me through all
my failures and I stood by you
through all your terrible
outfits.
But when I got up there,
I got pretty emotional.
To make it up to you, I'd like
to read you the speech now.
I've known a lot of ballers
in my day.
But no man balls harder than
the man I'm about to bring up.
He's kind, he's intelligent.
He's a person I'm deeply proud
to call my friend.
Pretty good speech.
I mean, it was, um...
a little sappy, maybe.
I think I liked it.
Jessica, Mr. Nelson.
You are going to hear
a lot of bids today.
But this is the only one
that matters.
Is this a circle?
Or, is it an "O"?
Is Oprah involved in your bid?
It's a zero.
I bid zero dollars.
I have to say, that's one of
the lower one's we've seen.
Pawnee is celebrating its
200th anniversary,
and the Newport family has been
here since day one.
Through feast and famine,
transformation, upheaval,
celebration.
The Newport family is part of
the fabric of this town,
and not always in a good way.
Like when your hot fudge
pipeline exploded.
Oh, boo hoo.
It all ran off into the lake.
Well, yes.
Admittedly, it did make the fish
taste delicious,
but it was a P.R. nightmare.
My question is this.
What do you want the Newport
name to mean in the future?
If you donate this land
and you let me turn it
into a national park--
the Newport National Park--
your name will stand
for something good.
For generations to come.
- How much was her bid again?
- It was, uh...zero dollars.
Oh.
That's the part I don't like.
Just keep me in the running.
Give me a chance to prove
to you how great this could be.
Says here there are 12
closets, three bomb shelters,
five dumb waiters,
two and three eights baths.
No kitchens.
It's a fairly standard layout.
Cool, is that a staircase
to nowhere?
Yes, it is.
Good eye.
What was this place?
Remember the Pawnee doll head
factory?
- This was a doll head factory?
- No.
This was a holding cell
for people who went insane
on the assembly line.
What's behind this door?
Fire poll.
So this place has had
zero offers?
People seem to be scared off
on account of it being
haunted...
and disgusting.
After 47 years living here,
I decided to move
to Orlando to be closer
to Disney World.
We are responsible adults.
- You know what that means.
- I know.
We have money and we are going
to buy the shit
out of this house.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Who needs rental insurance?
We're gonna live here.
We now go live to the press
conference.
Good evening.
I'm attorney Trevor Nelson
with the law firm
Fwar, Dips, Winshares,
Gritt, Babip,
Pecota, Vorp, and Eckstein.
Legal counsel to the Newport
family.
Here to announce that the
Newport family trust
has narrowed the search
to two final candidates.
The Gryzzl Corporation
and the National Park Service.
Okay.
I'm in the game.
All I have to do is convince
them that it's better taking
no money than taking
$90 million.
Well, you did convince three
unsuspecting toddlers
that peas turn into cupcakes
in their tummies.
I started my career in Pawnee
by turning a pit
into a cool, little park.
And now, I have the chance
to give this town a massive,
beautiful gift
that they can use forever.
In the words of Jason Bourne,
"This is where it started
for me, this is where it ends."
Yeah, you know,
I still think Kevin James
was a weird choice
for the reboot.
Oh, I don't.
I think he nailed it.
So I'm thinking in addition
to the Tom's Bistros,
we have a hyper exclusive lounge
area called Tommy's Lounge.
Attention!
This is war.
You guys are going down.
And that's all I wanted to say.
Except Donna, Tom.
Hey.
I'm--I'm sorry I haven't kept in
better touch with you recently.
But I've just, you know, I'm a
little preoccupied with my kids and my job.
And also, prepare for war.
Because you chose the wrong side
and we are gonna smoke you.
And also, I made cookies.
But Ron is not allowed
to eat them.
And they say prepare for war
on them.
But the "O" in the word for
is a heart.
And...
I ate a lot of them on the way
over here,
because we're at war.
- Hey, Tom.
- Hey, man.
- Buddy, good to see you.
- How's it going?
- It's pretty good.
- Hey, Andy!
Let's go.
War.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com