CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(playing "Deck the Halls")
(tires screeching)
(bell clanging)
D’oh!
(screams)
Sir, we’re two minutes
from landing
at the Billionaires’
Retreat.
Ah, my favorite week
of the year.
Sophisticated
financial discussions
with my fellow plutocrats.
Food fight!
(excited whooping)
Take that, Ted Turner.
In your face,
founder of Facebook.
Skinny-dip!
Yay!
(giggling)
Yee-haw!
(guns firing)
(laughing, whooping excitedly)
Gangway!
(laughing)
(whooping, guns firing)
(snickering mischievously)
(humming)
"Men."
The room for me.
(women screaming)
(chuckling)
Nice prank,
Simpson.
I dare you to dump
that bees’ nest
on those second
grade babies.
Why would I want to?
Because I said,
"I dare you."
Kearney, can you
read it back?
"Nice prank, Simpson.
I dare you to...
dump that bees’ nest
on those second grade babies.
Bart:
Why would I want to?
Jimbo: Because I said,
’I dare you.’
Kearney, can you
read it back?
Kearney, reading:
'Nice prank, Simpson,
I dare you to...’"
The point is,
Simpson,
a dare has been placed
on your nards.
My nards accept.
Stingamajigs!
Save yourselves!
Huh?
Where are the bees?
No bees?
Dare annulled.
Can I appeal?
Yeah, appeal to other guys,
Captain Wuss!
(all laughing)
(chuckling)
Other than the birth
of my kid,
this is my
happiest moment.
All the bees are dead.
Aye, lass.
The bees are dyin’.
And not just here.
All over the world,
from Glasgow
clear to Edinburgh.
And no one knows why.
("Amazing Grace"
playing on bagpipes)
I’ve lost a lot
of wee friends of late.
(sobbing)
Willie, I didn’t know
you were an apiarist.
From context, I can tell
that means beekeeper.
’Tis a tragedy, Lisa.
No man should
outlive his bees.
They’re stinging
God now.
(sobbing)
(crickets chriping)
(chuckling, spraying)
And the call from the SEC
was coming from inside
their own brokerage house.
(screaming)
Jeff Bezos
wet his pants!
I did not.
That was apple juice
from before.
I fold.
I raise a million dollars...
and to sweeten the pot,
my assistant, Smithers.
If you lose me, sir,
may I say what an honor
it’s been to...
Bets don’t talk.
-They see and raise.
-(groans)
Well, if we’re betting people,
I got a whole herd of them.
My professional basketball team:
the Austin Celtics.
(chuckling)
Well, they’re hardly
worth a Smithers,
but we don’t
have all night.
Can you beat nine high?
Damn. Eight high.
So, I own a basketball team,
do I?
Take good care
of them, Burnsie.
Don’t let the forwards
mix with the guards.
And if they’re
acting sluggish,
slip some steroids
into their cocaine.
Mm-hmm.
Fortune Four
lotto numbers are: nine...
Pfft... knew it.
-seven...
-Duh.
-three...
-What?!
-and...
-Boring.
Dad, we have
to do something.
All the bees
are dying.
Oh, no, no bees?
Ooh,
now who will sting me
and walk all over
my sandwiches?
But Dad, bees
pollinate flowers.
Flowers: the painted whores
of the plant world.
No bees means
no honey.
(panting)
Synthetic honey.
Just like you remember.
Honey?
Thank you.
(slurping loudly)
(Homer screaming)
D’oh!
I never dreamed the future
could be scary.
Let’s go, Lisa.
We’ve got
some worms to save.
-Bees.
-Worms, bees,
ticks, fleas.
Let’s go, go, go!
FRINK:
I’m glad you
called me.
I know I’m not the first
scientist in the phone book.
That’s Associate
Professor Aaron Ableman.
How I hate him.
(gasps)
Thundering thorax,
it’s just exactly what I feared!
Hmm.
In there, close.
See these red dots?
This bee has been felled
by bee measles...
or, as I call it, "beasles".
Animals can get sick?
-I’m going to talk
to the girl from now on.
-You’re the nerd.
What we need to do now is find
enough uninfected bees
to start a healthy colony.
This pheromone
should attract them.
(spraying)
Marry me,
and I’ll support
you for life.
You’re not a bee!
This thing is useless.
(gasps, grunts)
(gasps)
There’s one on Lisa.
(buzzing)
Hold still, sweetie.
Daddy will kill it.
And this time, no screwups.
Stop, stop,
it’s an uninfected queen!
(gasps)
How do we catch her
without hurting her?
Uh, unfortunately,
the best method
is to allow her
to sting you.
-(screams)
-Yeah, much like that.
Now squeeze around the stinger
to keep her attached,
and a colony of bees
will soon form around your face.
(buzzing)
Now just keep them there
until the colony
is healthy and thriving.
How long is that?
Long enough
that you will be known
as Springfield’s
crazy bee girl.
(laughing):
She likes the stingers.
(humming)
Marge, remember
when we were talking
-about our worst fears?
-Uh-huh.
Mine was snakes,
and yours was...
Never being a grandmother.
Really? I thought it was Lisa
with a beard of bees.
Well,
whatever-- brace yourself.
President Lincoln!
You’ve come back,
and you got rid
of that hat.
You’ve got my vote.
Lisa, I don’t like this
at all.
It’s not for long.
But until they find
a suitable habitat,
this beard is the only hope
for these bees.
Relax, Mom.
I’ll mold them into
a shape you know and love.
(buzzing)
Stop Milhousing your sister.
(chuckling)
Now take it off
before they sting you.
Actually, bees rarely sting
when they’re in a cluster.
They only attack
to defend their hive.
I don’t know.
All it takes
is one troubled loner.
Please let me keep them
for just a little longer.
(buzzing)
(sighs) Okay.
One night.
So, let’s see
how my burly-bottomed
ball handlers
are faring.
(chortles excitedly)
Smithers, we’re leading
two to nothing.
Run out
the clock, boys.
Run out the clock.
(buzzer droning)
Oh, yeah, three points!
Big three in the Big D
for the Big C.
Mark Cuban-- that’s me.
Who is that man,
and why isn’t his enthusiasm
being punished?
That’s Mark Cuban, sir.
He’s the most flamboyant
owner in the league.
I’m out of my mind!
(cheering)
How odd.
His money seems to have
bought him happiness.
(playing an upbeat tune)
I’d like to meet him,
Smithers.
So, you made your money
in nuclear power?
I can’t remember how
I made my money.
If you’re really
a billionaire,
give me the secret
billionaires’ handshake.
Smithers, turn away.
(groans)
Yay!
So, tell me,
why don’t you recoil
from the public
like a normal billionaire?
Hey, why own a basketball team
if you’re not gonna
have any fun?
Fun?
Is that how it’s pronounced?
I’ve only seen it written.
Hold that thought.
No one’s paid attention to me
for ten whole seconds.
(chainsaw roaring)
(crowd cheering)
It’s time for this peacock
to show his feathers.
You know, the feathers
with the big eye
that trick them into thinking
that’s my front?
Said feathers
are what I’ll flaunt.
BART:
Uh, Mom,
maybe you shouldn’t have put
so much syrup on the pancakes.
(Homer chewing,
moaning in delight)
The secret is not
to swallow the stingers.
(spitting)
Dad, don’t eat the bees!
They’re just drones, Lisa.
They only live for,
like, five minutes anyway.
And they only have
haploid cells,
not diploid
like me and Bart.
Yeah!
Listen, Lisa,
I was trying
to think
of a way to
help your bees,
and I remembered
this abandoned greenhouse
outside of town.
Which used to be a beautiful,
thriving greenhouse
till I was hired to run it.
(chuckles)
Your bees will have plenty
of room in this old greenhouse.
Plus, there
are flowers,
and it’s near
a prison,
so they’ll have a place
to sting people.
Oh, Mom,
it’s perfect!
Go live your lives.
Get off my face!
(buzzing)
Oh, I miss them.
Now you know how I’ll feel
when you go to college.
You’ll always
have Bart. Always.
But he’ll be gone a lot
repairing refrigerators.
Always.
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your new,
fun-loving owner.
You’ve seen him on the cover
of the December 1943 issue
of Collier’s Magazine.
Montgomery Burns!
(cheering and applause)
(cheering, whistling
and hooting)
Silence!
Now, let’s make some noise
for everyone’s
favorite basketball team,
whom I have renamed
the Springfield Excitement.
I knew it!
Now I would like
to sing our National Anthem.
♪ My country ’tis of thee ♪
♪ Austria, Hungary ♪
♪ Obey your king... ♪
(whispering):
Sir, the Archduke is dead.
What?! The Archduke
is dead?
And the empire
is destroyed.
Then what happened?
-World War I.
-Then what?
-World War II.
-A postwar period.
-Then what?
-The Cold War.
-(whispers)
-Then what?
-(whispering)
-The European Union.
-The European Union?!
Good heavens!
Ladies, hold onto
your husbands!
It’s time for the saucy antics
of Springfield’s own
Basket-belles.
(ragtime music plays)
(cheering)
(crowd booing)
Enough of this vulgarity.
Back to your brothel, harlots!
Now, enjoy your game
and the madcap antics
of the free-wheeling
title-holder of this asset: me!
♪ Hiphop hooray ♪
♪ Ho, hey ♪
♪ Ho ♪
♪ You drew a picture
on my money ♪
♪ But you couldn’t make my... ♪
(gunshot, groaning)
Sir, were those
real bullets?
Yes.
Was that a real gorilla?
No.
I see.
(crowd shouting
and grumbling)
Uh, sir, your escapades,
while well-intentioned,
seem to be driving away
our fans.
We have to turn
this business around!
Time to think
outside the boxeola.
What would Mark Cuban do?
(engine revving loudly)
I’m out of my mind!
(explosion)
That’s not much help.
Build a new arena.
State-of-the-art!
New arena.
(buzzing)
(screams)
(whimpering)
(gasping)
That’s it, men.
Pave and tar the
way God intended.
Mr. Burns, you can’t do this!
I can, I shall,
and in the future,
I will have done.
I cannot be stopped!
Kill his acorns
and make him watch.
MAYOR QUIMBY:
First, one announcement.
I regret to inform you
we are not offering childcare
tonight.
I don’t know who that guy was
you were leaving your kids with.
Now, without further ado,
let’s get ready to referendum!
There’s only one place in town
where the bees can survive,
and Mr. Burns wants
to tear it down.
(gulps)
Please, people.
You didn’t listen
to me about the snail darter,
you didn’t listen to me
about the osprey,
and you didn’t listen to me
about the javelina.
The feisty pig
of the desert?
Apparently not feisty enough.
Future generations
will judge us
by how we cared for
the tiniest creatures.
I am not just asking you
to save the bees.
I am asking you
to save your souls.
(applause, cheering
and whistling)
Excellent speech.
Just excellent.
I no longer wish
to build my magnificent
new basketball stadium.
You don’t?
Heavens no!
No skyboxes.
No kiss cam.
Nor will we have the chance
to marvel
at number one draft pick
Muk Mu, the human North Pole.
(all gasping)
No, I’m afraid
he’ll be on the first
kayak back to Ketchikan.
ALL:
No!
Please, don’t take our freak!
I love you, Muk Mu!
CROWD (chanting):
Muk Mu! Muk Mu!
All those in favor
of building this decadent
monument to excess, say aye!
CROWD:
Aye!
(sighs)
Nay.
I know it’s not
your fault, Muk Mu.
You’re a gentle,
loving soul.
♪ ♪
What’s wrong with
your bees, Lisa?
Mr. Burns took away
their sanctuary,
and now,
they aren’t strong enough
to survive on their own.
I’m going home.
Give me the keys
to my bike lock.
-Are you sure?
-Give me the keys!
Okay, okay! Don’t know why
I had ’em in the first place.
(Lisa muttering
under her breath)
Oh, I’d do anything
to cheer up my little girl.
Really?
Listen, Homer,
in the back room,
I got these super-tough
Africanized bees.
I saw this ad
in a gentleman’s magazine
for excited African honeys,
and that’s what they sent me.
If we could combine them
with Lisa’s bees,
it would make them strong enough
to survive any environment.
But how are we supposed
to combine the DNA
of two strains
of the same species?
Actually, Homer...
(whispering)
(gasps)
You and me?
No, the bees!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That’s what I meant, too.
I have no...
inclination...
(buzzing)
-Got the queen?
-Yup.
And she’s ready
for a night
of anonymous sex
with multiple partners.
(chuckles)
Now, let’s give them
some privacy while they...
get down to buzziness.
♪ Come with me ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ To the sea ♪
♪ The sea of love... ♪
(sniffles
and sighs)
If they was me,
they’d be done by now.
(exhales loudly)
Wow. This must be
important, Dad!
I’ve never seen you walk up
an incline before.
Sweetie, I have a very
special surprise for you.
-(buzzing)
-My bees?!
(laughs)
Your bees died days ago.
These are their angry,
mutant descendants.
And they’re tough enough
to live in any environment.
They sound awfully mad.
Are they dangerous?
Hmm, I’m not sure.
Let me check.
Are you guys
dangerous? Ooh!
A simple yes
would have sufficed.
(yelling)
Don’t worry, Lisa.
Where else are they gonna go?
To that new stadium that
looks exactly like a hive.
(loud buzzing)
Welcome to the American dream--
a billionaire using public funds
to construct
a private playground
for the rich and powerful.
(cheering and whistling)
And now, so our skybox owners
can really enjoy the game,
I shall let in the sky!
(loud buzzing)
(whimpering and groaning)
Stop! I am one of you!
(loud chatter and clamoring)
We’ve been invaded
by a swarm of killer bees!
My microphone is no microphone
at all.
It’s bees!
Am I being badly stung?
Yes! And it hurts!
(yelling)
(loud buzzing)
(upbeat
instrumental music plays)
(yelling and groaning)
Our bullets are useless.
(gunshot)
Aah!
Okay, they’re useful on me.
(crickets chirping)
Oh, they’ve found a home.
You’ve won this round,
but when next we meet,
the beekeeper
will be the beekeepee!
(buzzing)
(chuckles diabolically)
(screaming)
Help me, Muk Mu!
(sighs)
So, that’s how I was outfoxed
by a little girl
and her half-wit companion
when my beautiful stadium
was declared a bee sanctuary,
and I had to take
a third-quarter write down
of $804 million.
Wait a minute.
Someone crunch
the numbers!
He’s only worth $996,036,000
-(all gasping)
-He’s not a billionaire
at all!
Wait, wait, wait. It’s only
a matter of four million.
I’m sure
I can find that somewhere.
I, uh... I have $50 here
in my wallet.
Mark, can you get me off
the hook for old times’ sake?
Can’t do it, Monty.
(gasps)
Aw, don’t worry.
You’ll feel a lot
more comfortable in the...
millionaires’ camp.
No! No!
Just kill me now!
(hillbilly accent):
Howdy do?
I own a minor
league hockey team.
(yelling)
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem