CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
("Deck the Halls" instrumental
playing)
(music fades)
ALL (sadly):
Ho, ho, ho.
♪ Oh, Christmas tree,
oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪ You’re on the curb
and dead now ♪
♪ Your Christmas lights
are in the box ♪
♪ In two months
we will change the clocks ♪
♪ Oh, Christmas tree, oh... ♪
(loud grinding)
Gee, they sure give
the Christmas spirit
the bum’s rush
around here.
And they’ve already started
exploiting the next holiday.
So, young man,
have you judged people
by the content of their
character this year?
Yes, Reverend Doctor.
Lunchtime!
Free at last!
Okay, remember our deal--
everyone gets to return
one Christmas present
with no hurt feelings.
I’m returning this
kitten calendar.
Um, I’m also returning
this kitten calendar.
Kitten calendar.
Hey, those are
15 month calendars!
That gives you
three extra kittens!
That’s the last time
I get you guys
a Christmas present
at the last minute.
Man, those are ugly kittens!
Mom, Dad!
Our mall got a Mapple store!
It’s so sterile!
MyPods! MyPhones!
(gasps)
A Brainiac Bar!
My question is the
following statement:
Operating System 4.2
has sloppier architecture
than a Tijuana anthill.
Did you get peanut butter
in your Ethernet port again?
No. I got mayonnaise
in the CD drive.
Hmm!
I see you’re
admiring our MyCube.
It’s fueled by dreams and
powered by imagination.
What does it do?
You should ask yourself,
"What can I do for it?"
Okay. What can I do for you?
Please, I’m begging you!
Sir, it’s not even
turned on yet.
But it’s glowing.
That light confirms
that it’s off.
I can’t afford any
of your products,
but can I buy some
fake white earbuds,
so people will think
I have a MyPod?
Sure, those are
called "MyPhonies."
Oh, and they cost $40.
Oh, I’ll never get
a Mapple anything.
KRUSTY:
I hate this MyPod!
I can’t watch movies
on a screen this small.
And the music today--
don’t get me started!
I said, don’t get me started!
(keyboards clacking)
(Mr. Teeny whimpers)
Come on, isn’t someone
going to get me started?!
Uh, let’s go, Teeny.
Maybe somebody at Old Navy
will get me started.
Here kid, you take it.
Thank you, Krusty!
Oh, don’t thank me.
Thank the Jewish Clown
Awards gift basket.
I’m a Mapple person!
We’re all
Mapple people.
Sorry.
MAN (over P.A.):
Attention, Mapple universe!
Prepare for a live announcement
from Mapple founder and Chief
Imaginative Officer Steve
Mobbs.
-Steve Mobbs?!
-He’s here?!
He’s a genius!
He’s like a god who
knows what we want!
(lisping):
Greetings, it is I,
your insanely great leader,
Steve Mobbs.
I’m speaking to you from Mapple
headquarters deep below the sea,
with an announcement
that will completely change
the way you look
at everything!
(all gasping)
And that announcement is...
BART’S VOICE:
You’re all losers!
(gasping, moaning)
You think you’re cool
because you buy
a $500 phone with a picture
of a fruit on it?!
Well, guess what?
They cost eight bucks to make
and I pee on every one!
ALL:
Eww!
I have made a fortune
off you chumps
and I’ve invested it
all in Microsoft!
Now my boyfriend, Bill Gates,
and I
kiss each other
on a pile of your money!
(shocked gasping)
(sobbing):
Traitor!
Your heart is blacker
than your turtleneck!
(glass shattering)
(grunting)
(laughing)
Who dares question the boss
we fired 10 years ago
and then brought back?
It was my
brother Bart!
Flay him with
your earbuds!
Flay him, I say!
MyCube, take me away!
-♪ Loving you ♪
-(birds chirping)
♪ Is easy
’cause you’re beautiful ♪
Get him!
-Get him good!
-♪ Making love with you... ♪
Stupid angry mob, chasing me
because I shine a harsh light
on modern society.
Now I know
how Dane Cook feels.
(sniffing)
Mmm, what’s that exotic aroma?
It smells like a hamburger
cooked at a rug store.
Hello.
Would you like some lamb?
Mmm.
Whoa! All these years I’ve been
petting lambs when I should’ve
been shoving them in my mouth!
-I’m Bart.
-I’m Bashir.
My family and I just
moved here, from Jordan.
Jordan. That’s on some
map somewhere, right?
Bashir, introduce me
to your new friend.
Bashir, you didn’t tell me
you had a sister.
(laughs):
Such a charmer.
Would you like to
stay for dinner?
Hey, I never refuse food
from strangers.
Okay, you’re new
to our school,
so here’s the deal:
we call Skinner, "Skin-rash,"
Mr. Wiener is "Mr. Whiner,"
and Groundskeeper Willie,
"Grounds-Creeper Stupid."
Ah, that’s
not clever!
And I have so many
aspects you can mock!
I’m poor, I’m dirty,
I can’t read or write,
I think movies
are real!
(laughing)
Okay, next, here’s the
food at the cafeteria
that will make you sick:
coleslaw, tuna,
all chowders and gumbos.
The only thing that’s
safe is the pork chops.
My religion says
I can never eat pork.
A different religion?!
Do not tell anyone that
because if the
bullies around here
find out that
you’re different...
JIMBO:
Who’s different?
What’s your name,
sweat stain?
Uh, Bashir.
"Bash here"?
I love a kid that
comes with directions.
Okay, Bashir.
Tell us where you came from
so we can punch you back there.
I’m going to punch
you extra hard
’cause I secretly
think you’re cute.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You can’t just whale
on him because he’s--
What religion
are you anyway?
-Muslim.
-Oh, boy.
You’re the reason I can’t carry
toothpaste on an airplane!
Ow!
Look, guys,
everyone’s different.
Jimbo, you’re Christian,
Dolph, you’re Jewish,
and, Kearney, your family’s
in that cult Moe started.
I had to join.
My mom’s doing the savior.
I mean, the one true Moe.
You’re the
one true mo.
(laughing)
(grunting)
Help me,
almighty Moe!
Can’t. I’m not
really a god.
I was just acting crazy
to get out of jury duty.
(Bashir and Bart laughing)
Look at Lisa Simpson,
over there by herself.
Not talking to us,
her best friends!
Do we hate her?
-Yes!
Lisa, we came to
tell you that we...
(gasps):
Is that a MyPod?
Yeah. I’ve already downloaded
so much incredible music!
Check out "Moon Dreams"
from Miles Davis’
Birth of the Cool.
(mellow jazz music playing)
Or, check out this
MyTunes exclusive
episode of
Itchy & Scratchy.
BOTH:
Ooh!
♪ ...and Scratchy Show. ♪
(classical music playing)
(music grows louder)
(screams)
(yells)
(whimpering)
(fanfare)
Ah.
Oh.
(explosion)
Why?!
(sad music)
(electrical crackling)
Stop!
(explosion)
(electrical crackling)
♪ I love the nightlife,
I’ve got to boogie ♪
♪ On the disco round... ♪
(giggling)
Marge, I installed
all the low-energy bulbs.
What have you done
with the old ones?
Disposed of them in an
environmentally friendly manner.
(fire crackling, glass popping)
(chuckling)
Salaam alaikum!
Milhouse is looking good!
He’s got contacts,
changed color,
got a cool new catchphrase.
Salaam alaikum!
Dad, that’s Bashir,
my new friend.
(doorbell rings)
Bart forgot
this, sir.
Sir?
That’s the kind of
respect you’d have to
strangle out of
an American kid.
You know, Bart
never told me
he had a handsome
teenage brother.
(giggling)
Oh, uh, I’m really 38.
38 waist I might believe.
(shrieking, giggling)
Hey, Carl, got any idea what
direction Mecca’s in?
Why don’t you ask Homer?
He ought to know, by dint
of his son’s new friend.
(laughing)
Hey, Bashir’s great.
If Derek Jeter married
Mariah Carey--
it wouldn’t last--
but I bet they’d have
a kid like him.
Homer, this
is serious.
This Bashir kid
is Muslim,
and therefore
up to something.
Oh, I can’t believe
that till I see
a fictional TV program
espousing your point of view.
All right.
For the last time, Fayed,
where did you hide
the nerve gas?!
Under your Statue of Liberty’s
dress!
And she loved it!
Oh, my God.
What can I do?
Well, if you want
to stop Bashir
and his war
on American principles,
you could discriminate
against his family
in employment and housing.
That’s pretty patriotic,
but I got a better idea.
Invite ’em over.
A little dinner,
a little dessert,
and then you
Jack Bauer ’em
into giving you
all their secrets.
(evil laughter)
I guess I have no choice.
Homie, it’s very
open-minded of you
to have Bart’s Muslim friend’s
Muslim family over.
Here’s the
plan, Marge.
You keep them talking.
I’ll be listening
and quietly judging.
(doorbell rings)
The doorbell will tell
you when they’re here.
So, how did you two meet?
(chuckles)
We met while studying
at Jordan University
of Science and Technology.
Ah, interesting.
Why, just the other day,
I was reading that science
is used to make bombs.
Now, bait the trap.
Why don’t I get us
dessert?
(chuckles)
I made us
a little cake.
Care to cut?
Watch this,
Lenny.
Not now.
I got soap in my eyes.
No, thank you.
What’s the matter?
Don’t like the taste
of freedom?
Dad, these people
are my friends.
Don’t fear them
just because they have
a different religion,
a different culture, and
their last name is Bin Laden.
Young man,
you do not respect us
by disrespecting
your father.
I like the way
you Italians think.
Shut up,
old man.
I think it is time
for us to go.
Mm-hmm.
That’s it.
Ruin a perfect evening.
You’re teaching Bart
a terrible lesson
of intolerance.
I’m sorry.
It’s just so
fun and easy
to judge people
based on religion.
Well, I want you to go over
to their house and apologize.
But we’re the more powerful
country for a few more years.
Okay, I’ll apologize.
Up-bup-bup-bup!
Don’t eat that,
sweetie.
It’s poison.
I am sorry I suspected you
of being soulless murderers
of innocent children.
I hope we can move
past this and...
(gasping):
Dynamite?
They are terrorists.
Must leave quietly.
(trash clattering,
leaf blower roaring)
(loud metallic clattering)
(clattering)
So far, so good.
Marge!
I was right!
Everybody is
whatever I think they are.
I saw them
unloading dynamite.
(sighs)
Homer, I’m sure you
didn’t see anything.
Go to sleep.
All right, sweetie,
but if I wake up tomorrow,
we’ll discuss it.
(wind whistling)
BASHIR:
Hi, Homer!
Hmm.
(gasps)
You rubbed?
You must like me.
You really,
really like me.
Good morning, Ramadan!
Come to Crazy
Fayeddie’s!
Our prices
are Hussein!
Here’s... Genie!
(giggles)
-Now do Flanders.
-No.
Now I will destroy your
decadent Western society.
(1940s-style music playing)
No...!
Hmm.
Usually that ends the dream.
(snoring)
The power of dreaming has
convinced me the threat is real.
(panting)
(doorbell rings)
Delivery for
Lisa Simpson.
(gasps)
It’s a gift from Mapple.
Oh, such beautiful packaging.
I never thought
a company could be my soul mate.
Oh, it’s my first MyBill.
$1,200?!
But I only downloaded...
1,212 songs.
(groans)
I got to prove
the genie was right.
Off to work.
Sometimes I wish you would
quit that awful business.
But I love blowing up buildings.
Oh, my God.
Safely and legally,
in order to make room
for new buildings.
Darling, I think
you are working much too hard.
Yes, I am killing myself,
but it is all for the profit,
and after the explosion,
I will be in a better place.
That corner office
with the downtown view.
(doorbell rings)
Oh, it’s you.
What do you want?
I want to apologize for
being such a jerk at dinner,
and I thought the best
way to do that would be
to come to your house
and poke around.
Mr. Simpson,
I accept your apology.
Good-bye.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait.
I read somewhere your people
are hospitable to guests.
Is that true?
(sighing):
Yes.
Praise be Oliver.
That’s Allah.
Yeah... we’ll look
it up in the Corona.
So... now
that we’re alone,
um... death to America,
right?
Homer, why are
you really here?
Oh, look at that.
We’re out of almond paste.
Don’t get up.
I’ll grind
the almonds myself.
A computer.
(computer chimes)
I’m in.
Springfield Mall?
They’re going to blow it up.
Homer, I don’t hear
almond grinding.
(singsongy):
Just listen.
I’m grinding them now.
(imitates grinder)
Ow, my finger!
Ooh, here comes the ambulance.
(imitates European
ambulance siren)
My, you’re a handsome fellow.
(in accent):
Just get in the ambulance,
Mr. Simpson.
We’ll see to your finger.
(in normal voice):
Why, thank you.
(imitates European
ambulance siren)
-(thuds)
-Ow, my finger!
Everyone, get out!
Run for your lives!
Run for your--
uh, stay where you are.
Bart!
(gasping):
Boy, don’t blow up this mall.
It has the cookie store
that gives free samples.
I can’t believe
your dad gets paid
to blow stuff up.
Actually, Bart, my job is
about math and engineering.
Every calculation is to make
sure the explosion is safe.
Did you factor in
one bald idiot?
No, I...
USA, USA!
USA!
(grunting)
(explosion)
Dad, it was an empty building.
It was supposed to come down.
What about the bridge?
That was supposed
to open tomorrow.
Did we really need
a bridge there?
The Duff Brewery
is on that island.
I’ll save you!
(spy theme music playing)
(Homer chuckles)
That banner has really paid
for itself over the years.
We accept
your apology.
Lisa, add another name
to our Christmas card list.
(whispering):
Next to our Jewish friends.
Where is Lisa?
She said something about
"the bottom of the ocean"
and "be back in a month."
FEMALE VOICE:
Welcome to Mapple Headquarters.
The cost of this journey
will be added to your bill.
Come on... come on.
Yes!
16 million results.
Mr. Mobbs, there’s a surface
dweller here to see you--
MyTunes user
JazzGal62.
Hmm... oh, Lisa Simpson.
Send her in.
Mm-hmm.
Lisa, it’s insanely
great to see you.
Um, Mr. Mobbs,
I sort of downloaded
too many songs onto my MyPod,
and I don’t have the money
to pay for them.
And do you think
you could consider
a reduced payment plan?
I’m sorry.
I know our posters say
"Think differently,"
but our real slogan
is "No refunds."
(sniffling):
Oh...
can’t you open your Mapple menu
and click on the compassion bar?
Oh, please.
Lisa, how would you
like to work for Mapple?
(gasping):
Would I ever.
Think differently.
Think
differently.
Think differently.
(sighs)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh.
Enhanced by Fotokem