CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(all scream)
Woo-hoo!
St. Patrick’s Day.
I love how they made
the river green.
Actually, my nuclear
plant did that.
And now that you know,
your life is in danger.
(hums tune)
Greetings, fellow Irishmen
and lady Irishmen.
I, Joseph Fitzgerald
O’Malley Fitzpatrick O’Donnell
the Edge Quimby,
welcome you to Springfield’s
first booze-free
St. Patrick’s Day!
(booing)
Oh, come on, people.
Your drunken shenanigans
destroy this town every year.
And Ireland is so much more
than the imbibing of spirits.
The Irish gave the world
the paddy wagon,
the Shamrock Shake
and folk dancing
where you don’t move your arms.
(Irish folk music playing)
(groans):
Oh.
Where’s the IRA
when you need ’em?
We renounced the ways
of the gun and the bomb.
(passengers cheering)
(sighs)
In the old days, we would
have been all over that.
(bagpipes playing)
(crowd chattering)
(children clamoring)
(lively march playing)
Oh, no.
The Northern Irish
are also having a parade.
Two kinds of
Irish people?
What are they
fighting over,
who gets to sleep
in the bathtub?
Actually, those Prots
and Cathies
have hated each other
for centuries.
(sighs)
It always comes down to
transubstantiation
versus consubstantiation.
(growling, muttering)
Stop it! Both of you!
You have a common land,
a literature
and the sweetest songs on Earth.
♪ Toora loora loora ♪
♪ Toora loora lie ♪
♪ Hush, my little baby ♪
♪ Hush, now don’t you cry ♪
♪ Toora loora loora ♪
♪ Toora loora lie ♪
ALL:
♪ Toora loora loora ♪
♪ It’s an Irish ♪
♪ Lullaby ♪
(all chattering)
(grunts)
(clamoring)
Oh, no! Without the booze,
these guys all remember
how much they hate each other!
(growling)
Oh!
This was such a pleasant
St. Patrick’s Day
till the Irish people showed up.
(children chattering)
Urchins!
They took my cupcakes!
All right,
you unwanted miracles,
give back
the lady’s cupcakes.
You don’t have
the teeth for it.
Aye, but we could
gum the frosting.
If it’s good gummin’
you’re after,
wouldn’t you rather have
this lovely cabbage?
(children oohing)
(children chattering excitedly)
Cabbage!
Here you go, ma’am.
Not a sprinkle
nor Jimmy askew.
Thank you
so much, Mister...
Patrick Farrelly
at your service.
Marge Simpson.
Well, Mr. Farrelly,
the least I could do
is offer you a cupcake.
Hmm.
Mmm.
Light, moist, and such
a marvelous shape retention.
Marge, I own
a small bakery.
Will you bake for me?
Me? A professional
baker’s employee?
Imagine how different
my life would be.
Here we are
at school, kids.
Hey, what are those boxes
in the back?
Cakes!
-See ya.
I’ll do it!
Bless your heart.
You won’t regret it.
I already don’t.
Homer, I’ve got great news!
I’ll use my one phone call
to find out all about it!
Mulk request change of venue.
Green monster cannot
get fair trial
in Downtown Springfield.
Granted.
Homer Simpson?
You are a repeat offender.
Three-peat.
Bail is set at $25,000.
(scoffs)
I make that in a year.
I suggest you see
a bail bondsman.
Okay, Simpson,
all your information
checks out.
I called your boss to
verify your employment,
and he says you’re fired
for getting arrested.
(laughs)
You’d be amazed how
often that happens.
(groans):
Oh!
We’ll put up
your bail money.
Just pay us ten percent and
show up for your court date.
And if I don’t show up?
Then you got
to deal with me.
The name’s Wolf,
and I’m a bounty hunter.
If someone skips bail,
I track ’em down
and bring ’em back.
I also take a tooth,
make a plaster cast,
put it on this necklace, then
replace the tooth at my expense.
Well, time to go back
to my world of sleazy bars,
tattoo parlors
and greasy spoons.
What a great job.
And I could use
a job right now.
Whoa, not just anyone
can be a bounty hunter.
You have to pass
an online exam.
No, wait, they got
rid of that.
There is a $10 filing fee,
but you can get around it.
Congratulations!
You’re now a bounty hunter!
Mmm!
Okay, I’ve set my trap.
Now to scatter my cheese cubes
and the rats will come.
Condos!
Affordable condos!
Bail-jumpers welcome!
"Bail-jumpers welcome."
That’s refreshing, after
the cold shoulder we got
at the Townhomes
at Sterling Pointe.
(tires screeching)
Let’s not get too excited
till we find out if it’s
in a good school district.
Oh, so wait. Are we
telling people now?
Stop in the name
of a private citizen
with no connection to the law!
Now, are you gonna come quietly,
or do I have to...
(screams)
Now, let’s think about this.
If you shoot me,
I won’t be able to stop you,
and you’ll be free to go.
-(cocks gun)
-But...
someone may come after you.
Probably not,
given your reputation
for shooting people
who come after you.
What I’m trying to say is
not shooting me now
would be the biggest mistake
of your life.
(screams)
(screaming)
Oh!
Huh?
-Bullet-proof glass.
-Flanders?!
Yup, I’m just replacing
the front window of my store,
which was broken
in the riot.
(moans)
Young man, what would
your mother say
if she knew you were shooting
nice people in the brain?
She’d say that year off
from Princeton
was the worst decision
I ever made.
Well, son, if you take
responsibility for your actions,
this could be the start
of a better life for you.
Maybe you’re right.
Maybe I should just...
(muffled groaning)
This case is in the bag.
Homer, you could
have killed him!
I sure could have,
thanks to you.
(squeaking)
Now I can clearly see
potential customers
walk right past my store.
Enjoy your shopping
elsewhere!
Hey, Ned,
I brought you something.
(Homer chuckles)
Aw.
What the...?
It’s your share
of the money
for bringing
in that bail-jumper.
Ned, I never thought
I’d say this,
but we make a great team.
Us, a team?
As the salad said to the soup,
"I’m all mixed up."
We should be
bounty hunters together.
You’re kind and smart.
I’m cruel and strong.
Together, we’re nothing.
But together, we’re
the perfect bounty hunter.
Well, I could
use money,
but you have to promise
me something, Homer.
Sure. What is it?
We have to do everything
by the book.
And you have to promise
no diddilies or doodilies.
My friend, you have
a deal-arooney!
D’oh!
Mmm.
Mmm! Mm-hmm!
Mmm, mm-hmm!
Oh, Marge,
your talent with cakes
is a rare and precious thing.
Well, um, thanks, but
I’ve been wondering.
Why do you only have me
make spheres, rods,
and half-moon shapes?
Uh, well, Marge,
I’ll tell you, um...
(door bells tinkle)
...right after I talk
to these customers.
We’re going to
a bachelorette party
for a really
naughty girl.
-(chuckles)
-Yeah.
We need something
tasty and tasteless.
I’ve got just the thing,
courtesy of my newest baker:
freshly-frosted ass cake.
-Oh!
-Boy!
Oh, my God!
This is an erotic bakery!
-Mmm!
Delicious!
Now, what do you have in the
way of a suggestive cannoli?
Oh, we have quite
a selection. Hmm.
-Oh, yes!
-(chuckling): Oh!
Oh. Oh, boy!
I’ll leave you
with the book.
How could you not tell me
this is an erotic bakery?!
Marge, calm down.
For as long as
there’s been baking,
there’s been
erotic baking.
It fills a need
and harms no one.
Harms no one?
(scoffs)
Explain that to...
Well, what about...
I think you forgot about...
Hmm.
My #1 customers
are married couples,
your friends and neighbors.
I just made a custom order
for the Hibberts.
It’s an exact replica
of the good doctor’s...
I don’t want to know!
It’s not what
you think it is.
Good.
It’s his penis.
That’s exactly
what I was thinking!
Marge, this is a
valuable public service.
Without your baking,
people like me will be
forced into back alleys,
repurposing Ho Hos
and Ding Dongs.
You have a great gift.
Don’t let it
go to waste!
Well, okay.
(crackling)
This Taser is awesome.
Finally, a practical use
for electricity.
Dear Lord, thank you for
creating so many evil criminals
for us to bring in.
And also, thank you
for my partner Homer, who...
-(crackling)
-Did you just
Taser my coffee?
Just warming it up.
Now to melt the cheese
in this croissant.
(crackling)
And get rid
of a little excess earwax.
-(crackling)
-(groaning)
And smoke a relaxing cigar.
(crackling)
Homer, can we take it easy
on the Taser?
No problem.
(whirring)
(gasps)
Our first bail-jumper!
Let’s roll.
-(crackling)
-(groaning)
Homer, take the Taser
out of your pants.
No. It looks cool! D’oh!
♪ Boy ♪
(gun chambers clicking)
♪ Now in the street
there is violence ♪
♪ And, and a lots of work
to be done ♪
-MAN: Who’s there?
-Bible salesman!
(yelling)
♪ And, and I can’t blame
all on the sun ♪
♪ Oh, no,
we gonna rock down to ♪
♪ Electric Avenue ♪
♪ And then
we’ll take it higher ♪
♪ Oh, we gonna rock down to ♪
♪ Electric Avenue ♪
♪ And then
we’ll take it higher ♪
♪ Workin’ so hard
like a soldier... ♪
(tires squealing)
Daddy’s home!
I brought you kids some stuff
from work!
Here you go, son.
Shell casings!
Whoa! There’s still bullets
in some of these!
Point them away from your
sisters when you hammer them.
Yes, sir!
What’d you
get for me?
Something for the sweetest
little scientist in the world.
A new chemistry set!
Dad, is this from a meth lab?
The biggest one in town.
This is evidence.
Evidence that I love
my little girl.
Marge, I brought you
some flowers!
A full dozen this time.
No tricks.
Oh, Homie.
I got you something, too.
A sterling silver
picture frame
with pictures of our kids in it.
Yes, for now.
I guess things are
working out pretty good
at your bakery job.
Maybe we could order
one of your cakes
for Lisa’s birthday.
How dare you?!
What’d you
do that for?
Sorry, sorry.
Muscle spasm.
(laughs)
I’m not convinced.
Still on the fence.
Now I believe you.
He’ll be here
sooner or later.
(crickets chirping)
(Homer humming)
So, how about a little
stakeout music?
Homer, I don’t think
we have the same musical tastes.
Well, I like AC/DC.
I like their Christian
cover band: AD/BC.
♪ Kindly deeds done for free ♪
♪ Kindly deeds ♪
♪ Done for free ♪
♪ Kindly deeds done for free ♪
♪ Kindly deeds,
and they’re done for free ♪
♪ Kindly deeds, and they’re done
for free ♪
(crickets chirping)
(bird singing)
Hmm, I’ve never seen anyone
eat pizza like that.
Oh, you’ve gotta try it.
This way,
the pepperonis stay intact
till they reach
your stomach.
Then, bam!
(yelps)
Man, that’s harder to swallow
than evolution.
You’ve got to roll it
from the point.
Here, let me show you.
Not bad.
Now let it unfurl
in your stomach.
-Oh!
-There he is.
(gasps)
(tires squealing)
Oh, kitten whiskers.
There’s one thing
he didn’t count on:
my reckless indifference
to human life.
(tires squealing)
Lord, in your mercy, could you
give my friend a stroke?
Seymour, those string beans
were cooked to perfection.
After 20 years,
I am finally starting
to like you.
Just wait for dessert, sir.
I made it with you in mind.
Outstanding.
I’ll just shut my eyes
and let you place it
before me.
(screaming)
MRS. SKINNER:
Seymour, what’s going on?
I’m coming down there!
Quick, we’ll have
to eat from each end.
We’ll know we’re safe
when our lips meet
in the middle.
(screaming)
Homer, you can’t drive a car
onto a subway.
You need a special sticker
just to bring a bike.
Have you no respect for the law?
Hey, it worked,
didn’t it?
Okay, smart guy,
you’re going in the bag.
(gasping)
Wait, I left a
sandwich in there.
(gasps)
(gagging)
Homer, no, you promised.
Everything was supposed
to be by the book.
You know what
your problem is?
You haven’t become as bad
as the people we chase.
This partnership is over.
I’ll tell you
what’s over.
This partnership!
You know, if you
take your foot
off the accelerator
going downhill,
you wouldn’t use so much gas.
(sighs)
I can’t take another word
out of you.
(gasping)
I can’t believe
Flanders dumped me.
Marge, do we have
any more
of your
extra-long Twinkies?
Oh, no!
Those were for Mr. Smithers’
commitment ceremony.
Marge, what’s going on?
(sighs)
Homie, I’ve got a
confession to make.
I’m an erotic baker.
-(gasps)
-I hid it all
in the one place
you’d never look.
Marge, I can see you
withholding sex
or withholding cake,
but withholding sexy cake?
I know we have
to move past this,
but I don’t see how.
Homie, what do you say
we go to bed?
You, me and the cake.
First, why don’t you and I
and the cake take a shower?
Ooh.
(moans sadly)
(electrical buzzing)
Lucky Jim, I’m out
of the bounty hunting business.
Not so fast, Ned.
I got one more bail-jumper
for you to pick up.
Forget it.
I am turning in my...
well, I don’t really
have anything to turn in.
So that’s that.
I suggest you call
Homer Simpson.
This is one jumper
that Homer can’t catch.
(gasps)
Homer?
Seems he never
showed up in court
on his Saint Patrick’s Day
arrest.
Not interested.
All right, if you
don’t want the job,
I’ll just give it
to one of these guys.
(chainsaw roaring)
I’m sure they’re all
competent professionals,
but, uh, you’d best
leave it to me.
Hello.
Hello, anybody home?
You jumped bail, Homer.
I got to bring you in.
What have you done to my family?
I figured a good time
to pick you up
was when they were
at Lisa’s recital.
And how did you know
I wouldn’t be there?
Lucky guess.
Well, you’ll never
take me alive.
(grunting)
Forgot my keys.
♪♪
(horns honking)
HOMER:
Woo-hoo!
(whinnying)
(horns honking)
(panting)
Huh?
(moans nervously)
(panting, grunting)
I loved you, man.
For the last few weeks,
but most of the time
I’ve known you,
you’ve treated me like dirt.
You hang onto resentment
like a Confederate widow.
I forgave you for accidentally
killing my wife.
Yeah, but you hold on
to the big things.
The point is, the more
I got to know you,
the more I got
to like you.
I like you, too,
but you broke the law.
So, I’ve got
to bring you in.
So, it’s gonna be
like that, eh?
(grunting)
( Batman theme playing)
I’ve got you, my friend.
Thanks, but...
what are you holding on to?
Well, I’m...
(screaming)
(both screaming)
(sighs in relief)
Now all we have to do
is get out
before
the concrete hardens.
(both grunting)
Aw, damn it.
(crickets chirping)
"...lest I come and strike
the Earth with a curse."
Thus ends the book
of Malachi.
I guess I did know
the whole Old Testament
by heart.
Out with the old,
in with the new.
Testament, that is.
Matthew 1.
"The book of the genealogy
of Jesus Christ,
the son of David,
the son of Abraham.
Abraham became
the father of Isaac.
Isaac became
the father of Jacob.
Jacob became the father
of Judah and his brothers.
Judah became the father
of Perez and Zerah by Tamar.
-Perez..."
-Simpson, we’re
gonna put you away
for a long,
long time.
Make it life,
and you’ve got a deal.
MARGE:
Don’t feel too bad, Homie.
You’ll be free tomorrow.
And I used
all my new baking skills
to make a special cake
to remind you of me.
(moaning excitedly)
Oh, baby.
Thanks, Marge.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem