CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(cat meowing)
♪♪
(chickens cluck)
Stupid shopping list,
turning food into work.
Bart!
Look at me!
I’m doin’ something!
D’oh!
You better
settle down, boy,
or I’ll drag you into the blind
spot of that security camera.
and beat you with one of those
big thick women’s magazines
with all the ads in it!
Mr. Homer, why don’t you forget
your worries with this--
the last lottery ticket
on the roll.
They say the last
one is lucky!
Unlike all the others.
Lucky!
Or not.
Hmm, you make
a good case.
I’ll take it!
BART:
Dad, look at me!
Look at me!
Cannonball!
(screaming):
No!
I’ll take that last
lottery ticket, Apu.
D’oh!
(laughs)
Again!
(grunting)
LENNY:
I won!
-I won!
-Huh?
$50,000!
Ponder this, Homer.
This ticket would
have been yours
if your kid hadn’t
been screwin’ around.
That is true.
Another ironic Tale
of the Kwik-E-Mart.
(laughs)
You just
cost me $200,000!
I thought it was 50.
I was gonna bet it
on the dogs!
Hmm,
all the groceries seem
to have been balled up in anger.
That kid has become
a Dennis-level Menace!
Now, Homer,
boys will be boys.
Bart cost us $50,000!
(grunting)
(giggles)
-Hmm?
-(sniffing)
(groans)
I’m going to Moe’s.
MEN (chanting):
Lenny,
Lenny, he’s our guy!
Got the ticket Homer
didn’t buy!
(sighs)
Oh, cheer up, Homer.
The drinks are on Lenny.
I don’t want
your pity booze.
I’ll pay for it myself.
Uh, I gotta check
with Lenny on that.
Uh, is that all right,
Lenny?
Nope, Lucky Lenny’s buying
all the drinks tonight.
Sorry, Homer,
but here’s a compromise:
why don’t you both pay
for the drink?
And tip.
I just want to tell you all that
even before I won this money,
I was the luckiest
guy in the world
’cause I got friends
like you.
ALL:
Aww.
That’s why I’m spending my
remaining Scratcher winnings
on a kick-ass party
for all my friends!
(all cheering)
(screaming)
(sobbing)
(sighs)
Where’s Bart?
We’re gonna be late
for Lenny’s party.
Don’t waste your
shot, Bart.
You’ve got just enough cat pee
to soak two dorks.
(giggling)
Bart Simpson!
Did you just spray
water on me?!
Uh... It was water this morning.
(grunting)
Dang that Bart!
Thanks to him, I have
to wear my backup dress,
which makes my arms look fat.
Oh, you look great.
Ha ha!
You feel
self-conscious.
(grunting)
Why can’t our son just behave?
Well, Marge, you did have
that one sip of alcohol
while you were pregnant.
I now christen
this ship
the USS Float ’N’ Shoot!
SATANIC CHOIR:
♪ Ay, caramba! ♪
Mmm, that was unforgivable.
But I’m beginning to think
that Bart’s bad behavior
-is more than just a phase.
-LISA: Mom!
Bart’s flicking
boogers on me!
They’re not boogers!
They’re clumps
of rubber cement.
That I stored
in my nose.
Oh!
(grunting and groaning)
Ow!
Stop it, both of you!
Don’t make me drive
into that tree!
You know I will!
(tires screeching)
No flicking boogers,
and no driving
into trees!
-Yes, ma’am.
(piano playing)
(sighs)
Wow, Lenny went all out!
ANNOUNCER:
In the beginning,
there was darkness,
so God created man.
But man was alone.
God created the animals
and birds.
(elephant trumpeting)
But man was still lonely.
So God said,
"Let there be friends!"
(singing):
♪ Thank you for being a friend ♪
♪ Traveled down the road
and back again ♪
♪ Your heart is true ♪
♪ You’re a pal and a confidant ♪
♪ Thank you
for being a friend ♪
for being a friend... ♪
Thank you for letting me
take home the centerpiece.
These are going right
on my mom’s grave.
(snaps fingers)
♪ Thank you
for being a friend. ♪
Lenny, it was
pretty cool of you
to spend your lotto winnings
on your pals.
It was worth it so everyone
could have a wonderful evening
and go home
with a gift bag.
Hmm.
Vacuuming robot!
(whirring)
(laughing)
Now, before you all leave,
I know everyone hates vacuuming,
and loves robots...
(all sigh)
(all screaming)
(glass shattering)
(groans)
(screams)
(gasping)
(gasps and sighs)
(screams)
These innocent robots couldn’t
have done this on their own.
Someone would’ve had
to turn them all on at once,
and then imbue them with some
kind of malevolent sentience.
Yep, there it is.
Well, whoever did this must be
long gone by now, Chief.
I don’t know
how we’ll ever catch him.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Hold it right there, Bart!
Can you tell us anything
about who did this?
Bart make Bot bad!
Uh, I can explain.
Kill the child!
(dress rips)
Oh!
Bart, I’ve had it with you!
I’m taking away
all your TV privileges.
You already did that.
Okay, then videogames.
That, too.
No more non-dice board games.
What?
You can’t take my Balderdash!
I just did.
(grunts)
I don’t mean to be bad.
I don’t know why I do
the things I do.
Ah!
(jibbering)
No one understands me.
I wish I had a different family.
I feel exactly
the same way.
Oh, my God.
You look like a dorky
version of me!
And you look like
a dimwitted version of me!
And you two are
ten-year-old versions of me!
The three of us could create
quite a lot of mischief,
but I have to fly back
to New York.
That’s where my wife
and I live.
That’s her.
You want to see pictures
of our kids?
(shuddering)
My name’s Simon
Woosterfield.
"Woosterfield"?
Your family owns
this place!
And Woosterfield Arena!
Bonnie Raitt played there!
You guys must be loaded!
Yes.
No, but the funny thing
about being rich
is sometimes
you wake up feeling...
Terrific? Incredible?
Happy as a clown?
Oh, yeah,
I’m livin’ the dream.
(hacking cough)
(inhaling)
Wouldn’t it be hilarious
if we switched places
and lived each other’s
lives for a while?
Mmm, I don’t know.
I’m pretty attached
to my family, and...
HOMER:
Get out here, boy!
I want to punish you
before I get drunk
-and merciful!
-Deal.
My father’s name
is Homer.
My mother’s name
is Mom.
My sister’s name is Lisa,
but everyone calls her Loser.
(chuckles)
My butler’s name is Chester.
I have a brother named Devon
and a sister named Quenly.
Oh, and my horse is
called Shadowfax.
You can’t miss him.
He’s the only Lipizzaner
in our stable.
Lipizzaner... got it.
There you are,
Master Simon!
Thank you, uh, Lipizzaner.
As you say, sir.
-Watch your head.
-Ow!
Huh?
-Mmm.
-(Homer grunting)
You ruin everything!
Driver, laugh at those people
for me.
My pleasure, sir.
(forced laughing)
(classical music plays)
McMansion.
McDonald’s?
McDreamy.
McSteamy.
McMansion.
Fleetwood Mac,
and Macauley Culkin.
And this is your home, sir.
But of course
you already knew that.
Awesome!
Meh.
This is my bedroom?
A candy corn volcano!
A ceiling from Saddam’s palace!
Ooh, and a racecar bed.
That really races!
(whirring)
Wow, a cool poster
of Joe Montana!
It’s not a poster.
-(screams)
-I’m the real deal.
Every day
I stand here
the family donates a million
dollars to Notre Dame.
Did you know the words
"Notre Dame" are French,
but the team is
the Fighting Irish?
That’s the kind of thing
I think about in here.
Back in the poster, gabby.
Yes, sir.
(fanfare music playing)
Milhouse, it’s me.
Check out the caller ID
on your phone.
"Blocked Number"?
That service is $3.65 a month.
Did you switch places
with a millionaire kid
who looks just like you?
Just sit tight.
I’m sending a car.
(Simpsons chewing loudly)
Why are these noodles orange?
I made it with Cheetos,
just like you like it.
If the sauce is too thick,
I can add more root beer.
Maybe I’m just not hungry.
Human garbage can
to the rescue.
(chewing loudly)
(with mouth full):
Mmm... so at work today,
we got a memo saying
everyone’s getting new chairs.
Father, could you...
Talk louder?
You bet.
Naturally,
I threw my old chair
in the Dumpster
right away,
but then Lenny said,
"No, that was the new chair.
That memo was
two months old."
So now I’m sitting
on an orange crate.
I never felt so...
-Please stop spitting
food on me!
-Huh?
Keep your meal in your mouth,
you semiliterate spew-monkey.
That’s it, boy.
You’re going to bed
without supper.
That was an odd thing
for Bart to say.
Maybe he’s going
through... certain changes.
If that boy thinks
I’m paying
to put him through four years
of puberty, forget it.
(muttering):
Stupid kids think
I’m made of hormones.
Mm...
Mr. La-Di-Da ...
This is the greatest great hall
I’ve ever
eaten in, Bart.
-Huh?
-I mean Simon.
Oh.
This must be my half-brother
and half-sister.
They’re beautiful.
I mean, just the girl.
I didn’t notice
the beautiful boy.
So I said, "Dad, I wanted a
Range Rover, not a Land Rover.
This is the worst
Martin Luther King Day ever."
Well, well,
if it isn’t
our half-wit half-brother.
Ow!
The old hot spoon.
But why?
Because you’re
our half-brother,
you’re blocking our full
inheritance and we hate you.
Oh, now I get it.
Hmm.
Bart, I have a crush
on your new sister.
You had a crush
on my old sister.
Yeah, but that was never going
to happen.
-(growls)
-Give me back my newspaper.
MARGE:
Homer, it’s not
a real paper.
It’s a rubber chew toy.
For your information,
The Daily Growl
is the only newspaper
that’s not afraid
to say how great
this country is.
-(grunts and chuckles)
-(toy squeaks)
How’s the war going?
-(squeaks)
-We’re winning?
That’s great.
And our standing abroad?
-(squeaks)
-Fantastic.
(line ringing)
This place is insane.
Tonight, I got sent to bed
without dinner.
Oh, yeah.
Well, what’s up
with your brother and sister?
They’re jealous because
my father left their mother
to be with my mother, to...
Eh, you lost me.
Well, got to go.
Enjoy the upper-lower
middle class.
(groans)
Bart, honey, I saw
you didn’t like your dinner,
so I thought
you might like
pepperoni pizza
with the crust cut off.
Now, let me tuck you in,
fluff your pillow,
and sprinkle
a little fairy dust
to keep
the monsters away.
(whispering):
It’s cinnamon.
Mm...
Nighty-night, sweetheart.
I could get used to this.
Fancy party.
This is like a rap video
before the rappers show up.
Mmm... mmm.
Simon, have you ever seen
the family mausoleum?
All the Woosterfields
will be buried here.
Do you know
that after a hundred years
dead bodies turn
to red licorice?
Whoa-ho, let me at it.
Help! Let me out.
I have my doubts
about this licorice!
(groans weakly)
Oh, Mr. Burns,
I’m really sorry.
(chuckling):
Nonsense, young Woosterfield.
Your fortune
is greater than mine.
It is, it is I
who am at your service.
Smithers, fetch us
some lemonade.
(grunting)
(panting)
All they had was
Sunnytime Pink.
Premix? I beg your
forgiveness, lad.
Smithers, pour it
down your pants.
Now, squish about
in those pants,
rewetting every hour.
Come with me.
You know, Master Simon,
I too was once the youngest
in a wealthy family.
You were once the youngest
of something?
But fortune ended up
smiling on me
while snuffing the life
from my siblings.
My older brother was trampled
by a horse.
My sister died
of a poisoned potato.
My twin was shot.
That girl was stabbed.
He ate
another poisoned potato.
Spontaneous combustion.
Fell down a well.
Potato. Potato,
and impaled
on the Chrysler Building.
Wow, only you survived.
(gasps)
Which means
the entire fortune went to you.
Yes, funny that.
A word of caution,
young Woosterfield:
watch out
for those closest to you.
Devon and Quenly?
You don’t know
when they’ll strike--
a boating accident,
a mishap during a ski trip--
but rest assured,
one way or another,
they will do you in.
Oh, my God.
Simon set me up.
And all this time
I thought he wanted the life
of a stranger
he met in the bathroom.
Now, would you care
to continue this conversation
on the teeter-totter?
(grunting)
Why won’t you come down?
I told you I only weigh as
much as my clothes and keys.
Hmm...
So I looked down the barrel
of my Winchester rifle,
I pulled the trigger,
and I shot that buffalo.
You shot a buffalo?
(sputtering):
You were listening?
(groans)
That means I’ve got to come up
with an ending
for this
nonsense.
(whispering):
Bart, what are you doing?
Politely listening
to our grandfather.
Huh.
It was the war to end all wars,
but Pepsi would not give up.
They continued
to challenge Coke.
(yelps)
Okay, listen, you.
I don’t know
who you are
or what you’ve done
with the real Bart, but...
God help me,
I want him back.
I don’t know
what you’re talking about.
Oh. The real Bart would have
thrown me out the window.
He would have
defenestrated you?
You’re just digging yourself
even deeper.
(grunting)
Come on, Bart.
You’ve got to get out of here.
Pack like you’ve never
packed before.
You know,
I have never packed before.
(grunting)
This is hard.
So, you’re packing.
You must have already heard.
Heard what?
We’re going to Aspen.
On a little ski trip.
Ski trip?
You won’t know how they’ll
strike-- a boating accident...
(sighing in relief)
...a ski trip.
(screams)
MARGE (to tune of "Loving You"):
♪ Scrubbing you ♪
♪ Is easy
’cause you’ve been pre-rinsed ♪
♪ And when you’re covered
with goo ♪
♪ That’s when
I’m scrubbing you ♪
♪ Scrub-bub-bub-bub-bub ♪
♪ Scrub-bub-bub-bub-bub... ♪
Mom, "Bart" has something
to tell you.
(groans)
I don’t like the look
of those air quotes.
So now Bart is on
his way to Aspen,
where they’re going
to try to kill him.
Thank you, future Bart,
for traveling back
through time to warn us.
Boy, Aspen
sure is ritzy.
Even the winos look better.
Uh, we’re champagnos.
Who wants a mimosa?
Uh...
this trail is for
experienced skiers.
Which is what you’ll be
if you make it to the bottom.
Which you won’t.
-(grunts)
-(screams)
Soon he’ll be dead.
And we’ll split
the inheritance.
Yes, split.
Potato?
(gasps)
There’s Bart!
This looks like a job
for Captain Crazy.
Up, up, and away!
Oh, come on, gravity.
You used to be cool.
D’oh!
(yelling)
(both yelling)
Occupied.
(screaming)
(yelling)
(both yelling)
(sighs)
Two hot chocolates, please.
Are you guests at the lodge?
No.
(both yelling)
You know, I feel
sorry for you, kid.
Going back to that cold,
loveless family.
I’ll survive.
Your favorite, sir.
Hot fudge sundae with
gold leaf and diamond flakes.
Take me with you.
I’ll be anything
and everything you want.
Don’t leave me here with them!
I never thought I’d say this,
but I missed you guys.
Even what’s-her-name--
Lisa.
(growls)
Now we tuck in the tummy,
the tushy, and the tootsies.
(speaking gibberish)
(laughs)
(kisses)
This is the life.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh.
Enhanced by Fotokem