CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Aye, caramba!
(car sputters)
(sputtering)
Out of gas?!
But how?
I put a dollar in this morning
and we’ve only driven 90 cents.
You had to drive
with the windows down,
didn’t ya, Rockefeller?
Now get some gas while I read
my bingo strategy guide.
Let’s see, B-12...
(truck horn blows)
(horns honking)
Uh! Oh-oh!
I did it!
Bonehead.
(horns honk)
(horn blows)
Huh?
This counts
as a parent-teacher conference!
Whoa! Am I seeing this right?
I am.
Time to spread the word.
(dialing)
-(rings)
-Hey, Milhouse.
Talk to me.
Skinner’s doing what?
(cell phones ring)
-I’m on my way.
(horns honking)
(kids laughing)
(groans)
(panting)
I’ll clean you up good,
giant beer can.
(screams)
-(screaming)
-Whoa!
(laughing)
Where’s Simpson?
I couldn’t get
a hold of him.
No cell phone.
But if I know Bart,
he’s busy doing
something awesome.
I don’t know why
I agreed to this.
Because you love the taste
of my imaginary tea.
(slurps)
Oh, you’re right.
(gulping)
Hey, Spaz!
While you were
here spazzing yourself,
you totally missed out.
Missed out?
I didn’t miss out.
What’d I miss out on?
(gasps)
(grunts):
Huh?
(groans):
Ugh...
Oh.
I wish I had a cell phone.
Here’s an imaginary
cell phone.
What, do you think
I’m crazy?
Mom, even Milhouse
has a cell phone.
Your son is lamer
than Milhouse.
What does that say about you?
Sweetie, we can’t afford
to get you a cell phone.
As it is, I’m buying frozen peas
on installments.
(groans)
Oh...
Oh, I’m never gonna get
a cell phone.
And I’m never gonna go
to Machu Picchu.
In this family, you get
used to disappointments.
How am I ever gonna get
a cell phone?
Ow!
(groans)
(growls)
Is this your ball?
Why, yes, it is.
(chuckles)
Here you go.
Don’t tell me
where I go.
A dollar?
What for?
It’s the least I can do.
These balls cost
five dollars new.
So I can get a dollar
for every ball I find?
Then if a cell phone costs $100,
how many balls do I need?
This is why my kids go
to private school.
(up-tempo country tune plays)
♪ I keep my nose
on the grindstone ♪
♪ Work hard every day ♪
♪ I might get a little tired
on the weekend ♪
♪ After I draw my pay,
I go back working ♪
♪ Come Monday morning,
I’m right back with the crew ♪
Yee-haw!
♪ I drink a little beer
that evening ♪
♪ Sing a little bit
of these working man blues ♪
I’ll fix you, you varmint!
Wow, I’m just 20 balls away
from a cell phone.
So it’s you!
You’re the one who’s been
poaching on me territory.
Groundskeeper Willie?
Weekends and summers,
I’m Greenskeeper Willie.
Your ball-scavenging
days are over.
And those orphan
golf balls belong to me.
Ah! Dimpled gold.
I’m rich.
Now I won’t have to pleasure
a country-club wife
to get me steak dinner.
(sighs heavily)
I’m never gonna get
a cell phone.
Oh, great!
We’ve got to wait
for Denis Leary.
Hey, Leary, if you want
to have a tea party,
go back to Boston.
(laughing)
Boston.
Come on, Ice Age.
Take the shot.
Ice Age was the name
of the film.
I played Diego,
the vicious saber-toothed tiger,
who, guess what, has a heart.
Now shut up
or I’ll have you all kicked out
of show business.
ALL:
Ooh.
(cell phone ringing)
Damn it!
Huh? A cell phone!
It’s mine!
Aw, cool.
You can even
watch commercials on it.
(dialing)
Hey, Milhouse,
guess where I’m calling from?
Well, I know you don’t
have a cell phone,
so you must be in your kitchen.
Or one of your bedrooms.
Unless you have a wall jack
in your basement.
That would be huge!
Look outside your window.
I’m not supposed
to look out the window
when I’m alone.
Just do it!
Cell phone!
Let’s assign each
other ringtones.
(beeping)
That felt good.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
You want Denis Leary?
Wrong number, dumb-ass.
Come on, Denis. It’s me,
producer Brian Grazer.
I just paid $5 million
for the screen rights
to the book Everybody Poops.
I’m a big fan.
Only one face
came to mind
for the constipated
gorilla: yours.
Sure-- on one condition.
I want to do my own poops.
I wouldn’t have it
any other way.
Of course I’ll do it
for minimum.
Great.
I’ll see you next Monday
in Tunisia.
This phone belongs
to Denis Leary!
Denis Leary?
Boston comedian-turned-movie-
star-turned-basic-cable-notable?
That’s right.
Let’s call his business manager
and tell him to spend
all his money on Yankees hats
and Derek Jeter jerseys.
I don’t know, Bart.
What if Denis Leary gets mad?
Naw, he’s cool.
He’s gonna think
this is hilarious.
No longer must
we live in shame!
Let the decree go forth:
everybody poops!
And... cut!
Great, great, man.
You really nailed it!
I don’t even remember
agreeing to be in this movie.
Well, you did.
Bring in the poop.
Milhouse, I hold in this hand
Denis Leary’s cell phone,
and in this hand,
the phone numbers
of bars around the world.
Let’s start with Hawaii.
-(phone ringing)
-Aloha.
Aloha to you.
I’m looking for Maya.
Last name Normousbutt.
Hang on. I’ll check.
Has anyone here seen
Maya Normousbutt?
(laughing)
(phone ringing)
I got a "Drew P. Wiener" here.
Anyone expecting
a Drew P. Wiener?
I hold in my hand
a Drew P. Wiener.
Better put it
down then, mate.
(laughing)
(phone ringing)
Ja?
I shall inquire.
Is there a Mr. Myfriendsaregay?
First name Olaf?
Attention, everyone.
Olaf Myfriendsaregay.
(laughing grimly)
Wait a minute.
If I ever get
a hold of you...
I will thank you for showing me
the futility of human endeavor.
(both laughing)
Oh, the sun never sets
on the Bartish Empire.
(phone ringing)
Yo. Who’s this?
Denis Leary, you little puke!
I’m gonna rip out your heart
with two fingers!
They taught me how
to do it for my show!
Which one,
the one that got canceled
or the one that’s gonna
get canceled?
You are so dead!
(laughing)
That laughter sounds like
the result of misbehavior.
Bart, how did you
get a cell phone?
Same way you got me:
by accident, on a golf course.
Whose phone is this?
You’ll never get it out of me.
Okay. Milhouse?
It’s Denis Leary’s!
I’m sorry, Bart.
I’m desperate for any
signs of adult approval.
You did the right thing.
(sighs)
(phone ringing)
Uh... Bart Simpson’s
stolen cell phone.
Can I help you?
Damn straight you can!
I’m Denis Leary,
and your kid is out of control!
I’m sorry, Mr. Leary.
Sometimes it’s hard
to be a parent.
No it’s not. It’s easy!
I’ll tell you what’s hard:
having to watch my stunt double
run into a burning building,
worrying that people might
realize it’s not me; it’s him.
Try doing that!
I don’t think I could.
Mr. Leary, I’m so sorry.
I’ll send you your phone
back right away.
Keep the phone. In fact,
can I give you some advice?
Of course. You’re Denis Leary!
Give your kid back the phone...
but first, activate
its built-in GPS system.
That way you can log on
to your carrier’s Web site
and track your son’s movements,
the way I track every actor who
gets a movie that I was up for.
Shouldn’t you just be happy
for their success?
I should be a lot
of things, lady.
My Tarts!
(sighs)
Okay, here goes.
Bart, I have
something for you!
Huh?
Wait a minute.
I thought you said
I couldn’t have this.
Well, sweetie...
I know I said you
couldn’t have a cell phone,
but, in these days
of stranger dangers
and sinister ministers,
I think it’s important
that we’re in touch.
Lady, you are the best mom ever!
(groans)
Did he take the bait?
Like a big-mouthed bass.
(laughing mirthlessly)
Okay, Bart went
to the comic book store.
Time to head home.
(gasps)
Bullies!
Hey, he went into
a construction site.
That’s a hard hat zone!
(laughing):
You sure this is safe?
Sure, I got my seat belt on.
MARGE:
Bartholomew J. Simpson!
(gasps)
What are you doing
at this construction site?!
Uh, trying to do something
constructive?
(groans)
I’ll just take
Milhouse home.
♪ You better watch your step ♪
♪ My, I send you
all my regards ♪
♪ You’re so tough,
you’re so hard ♪
♪ Listen to the hammers falling
in the breakers’ yard ♪
♪ You better watch your step ♪
♪ Ooh, watch your step... ♪
(screaming)
Hey, Bart just keeps spinning
around and around and around.
What’s his angle?
What are you two doing
in the laundry room?
Uh...
we’re doing laundry.
Dad, do laundry.
(chuckles nervously)
No problem.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm...
Hmm... Hmm!
(humming tune)
Tracking software?
(gasps)
You’re spying on Bart!
Honey, keeping track
of someone
because you love them
is not wrong.
It shows you care.
(static)
That’s right,
my beautiful, beautiful Midge.
(laughing evilly)
Soon you’ll be mine.
Keep talking, creep-o.
Every word buys you
another year in the slammer.
Bart, there’s something
I need to tell you.
Mom and Dad...
Shh!
I’m listening to financing terms
for double-glazed windows.
-(phone rings)
-Awesome. Another call.
You got Bart.
It’s me, you idiot.
Mom and Dad are
spying on you.
There’s a tracking chip
in your cell phone.
(gasps)
They’re spying on me?
That’s horrible!
I know! It’s a complete
violation of your rights.
Not to mention...
Hold that thought.
I’m getting a text.
Viagra at five dollars a pill?
Whatever it is,
it’s goin’ in Skinner’s coffee.
What is in this coffee?!
(twittering)
Mm-hmm.
Track this,
Mom and Dad.
(chuckling)
MARGE:
Look at Bart go!
(gasps)
He must be running away!
Eh, he won’t get far.
Not on the crappy breakfast
I made for him.
Oh, my God,
he’s out of frame!
Zoom out! Zoom out!
What...?
Hmm. He’s circling the
Shelbyville Bird Sanctuary.
(laughs)
Our little boy
has lost his mind.
Let’s get him.
(chuckles)
Looks like I’ve got the house
to myself for a while.
I can do anything I want!
First, I’m gonna take a bath.
Then I’m gonna eat
some vegetables
and then I’m gonna get
to bed nice and early,
with no TV.
(laughing)
So your family’s been gone
for three days?
Yeah. And I think they
may be gone a while longer.
Ooh, it looks like the
grilled Twizzlers are ready.
Mmm. Oh, yeah.
This baby is done.
(grunting)
Mmm. Awesome.
But I better get goin’.
It’s gettin’ dark.
My mom’s gonna wake up soon.
She gets upset
if someone’s not there
to tell her where she is.
(laughs)
Typical mom.
You sure you don’t wanna stay
and have a sleepover?
I made sleepover shirts.
Huh? Huh?
Listen Bart,
if I don’t get home soon,
there won’t be time for my mom
to give me a hug,
my dad to read me a story,
and both of them
to sing me a song
until I gently fall asleep.
Anyway, you have fun
by yourself.
Huh, there’s
no moon tonight.
Real boogeyman
weather.
(wind blows)
(shuddering)
Bart’s been moving nonstop
all afternoon.
Maybe there’s too much sugar
in his Sugar-Frosted Candy O’s.
Something about this
just doesn’t seem right.
Pull over.
Bart’s in this field.
Bart!
Where are you, boy?!
Don’t worry.
I won’t strangle you.
(twittering)
(Lisa gasps)
I think we’re
following you.
What’s your species,
little guy?
Oh, you’re a
scarlet tanager.
You’ve been flying south
because you’re migrating to...
Machu Picchu, Peru!
Well, I could tell Mom and Dad
the chip is in the bird
and hope they take me to
Machu Picchu another time, or...
Shoo. Shoo.
Mom! Dad!
Bart’s on the move!
(owl hooting)
Oh, man.
When you’re alone,
night is scary.
Day is awesome!
(television static)
Night is scary.
Day is awesome!
Night is scary...
Are we ever going to find him?
Absolutely.
That unpleasantness
in Ecuador is behind us.
My coca leaf addiction
is under control,
and Bart is finally trapped in
that paradise above the clouds.
Bart!
Where are you, Bart?
Is that him?
No, it’s just a bush.
Clearly the work of Wirakocha,
the trickster god.
You guys look
exhausted.
Maybe you ought to rest
for a while.
No! All I care about
is finding my boy,
and then I’m never letting him
out of my sight again.
(snoring)
Greetings,
sky-haired sun mother.
Um... I don’t need
any new friends.
I’m just looking
for my little boy.
I need to protect him
from himself.
Like the mothers
of ancient Machu Picchu
protected their children?
(thunder rumbling)
(Marge yells)
Hmm. Hmm.
STATUE:
Our mothers were
the most overprotective
in the greater Machu Picchu
metropolitan area.
They forced their children
to live in this
walled mountain city.
Those walls do look safe.
Walls that keep out danger
keep out knowledge.
Our young people never learned
to survive on their own,
so when they grew up,
they were no match
for the conquistadors.
(Three Stooges-like yelling)
Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoop-whoop.
Whoop, whoop, whoop,
whoop, whoop, whoop...
(Three Stooges-like yelling)
Oh, my God.
You’ve taught me
a valuable lesson.
I didn’t mean to.
I’m just chatty.
I sold my business
a few years ago
and I miss talking
to people.
So I can’t always
be there for Bart.
He’s got to learn
to take care of himself.
The computer says Bart’s
standing on the computer,
but all I see is a stupid bird
with a tracking chip
on its leg.
It doesn’t add up.
(chirps)
I think it’s time
for us to go home.
(slurping)
Hey.
Thank God you’re okay!
Were you guys gone?
We were gone for two weeks.
I didn’t even notice.
(sighs)
I just made
a 3,700-mile car trip.
I need to wash up.
Oh!
Never leave again.
Aww...
(grunting with effort)
Where’s Maggie?
Oh, uh, she’s, uh...
(drums pounding)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh.
Enhanced by Fotokem