(eerie music plays)
(wind howling)
(humming)
Mm-hmm.
Hello, I’d like to vote
for president, governor,
and anything that will take
money away
from our parks and libraries.
Eh, use machine
number three.
(humming)
(grunts)
Oh!
I can’t fit in the booth!
Use the double-wide.
Ooh!
One of those electronic
voting dealies.
COMPUTER VOICE:
One vote for McCain. Thank you.
(chuckles)
No, I want to vote for Obama.
Two votes for McCain.
Huh?!
Come on. It’s time for a change.
Three votes for McCain.
No! No! No!
Six votes for President McCain.
Hey, I only meant one
of those votes for McCain.
(gasps)
This machine is rigged.
(whirring)
Must... tell.. President McCain.
(shrieks)
This doesn’t happen in America.
Maybe Ohio, but not in America!
(screaming)
("Hail to the Chief" plays)
(dramatic music plays)
Okay...
all I need is a Christmas gift
for Lisa.
I don’t have time
to read all that.
(humming)
Hmm?
Montreal Expos jersey.
Somber String.
Jacks, no ball.
And a Slunky.
Oh, I wouldn’t give these
to my worst enemy,
which happens to be Lisa.
(whirrs, clicks)
Girls don’t like trucks.
Come back when you’re
something else.
(whirring)
-(honks)
-(gasps)
Perfect!
Merry Christmas, Dad.
We bought you three
more minutes of oxygen.
Oh, thank you, son!
Can I play with it outside?
Can I?! Can I?!
(chuckles)
Sure.
(laughs)
(breathing rapidly)
(laughing)
Hmm?
Hey, Lis, I think I see one
with your name on it.
I don’t know how you could top
last year’s gift--
a box of your burps.
Yeah. Here’s your
stocking stuffer.
(belches loudly)
Wow! A Malibu Stacey
convertible!
Oh, Bart, an actual present.
(whirrs)
(zapping)
(crackling)
(pops)
(whirs)
That’s right, Maggie.
It’s a car.
(whirrs)
(whirs)
MALIBU STACEY:
Let’s go to the... (grunting)
(zapping)
(deep, heroic voice):
Pos-i-bots, transform!
Snooze!
Threeway!
(clicks three times)
(deep male voice):
Melody!
(moans)
(whirring)
What?
(groans)
(clicks and whirs)
Wait a minute.
We’re missing Sex-Toy.
(soft, jazzy music plays)
Where have you been?
(chuckles)
Where haven’t I been?
(whirring, clicking)
Hmm. Is there
something different
about the kitchen?
ALL: No.
(whirs, clicks)
Well, the toaster’s never lied
to me before.
Hep, two, three, four...
Nice planet.
(humming)
-(clanking)
-HOMER: Whoa!
(screams)
(whirs)
(grunts)
(mechanical, droning voice)
Pos-i-bot, engage.
Battle commencing
in ten, nine, eight...
Hey!
(clanking, whirring)
Hey, Homer.
How was your Christmas?
It was okay.
I got Seinfeld, Season 7.
Finally a boxing day
that lives up to its name.
Lisa! What’s happening?!
Well, if I had
to guess,
I’d say that two
alien robot races,
who’ve been battling
for centuries, have chosen
our planet as a site for their
ultimate confrontation.
It is a good planet
to settle things on.
(tires screech)
(clanking)
-(whirring)
-(gasps)
Stop it! Stop it!
Look, you have made
the nacho machine cry.
(whirring)
Cool!
Carnage Destructicus,
the moment has arrived:
our final battle.
(clanking, whirring)
Your final battle,
Bestimus Mucho!
Stop it!
Just because you’re mad
at each other,
doesn’t mean you have
to destroy our town.
That does not compute.
Really?!
It computes a little.
What’s this whole intergalactic
tiff about anyway?
You know I, I...
I don’t remember.
Neither do I.
Hmm. Maybe the non-transforma
thing is right.
Thank you,
human grandmother,
for pointing out
that it is futile to fight
if we do not know why.
And now that we are
not fighting each other,
we can team up
to enslave your planet.
That’s great!
Because working together,
you can...
Oh...
(yelling)
Okay, who’s the idiot who
taught them what foosball was?
I thought
they might enjoy it.
(yelling)
( Mad Men theme paying)
♪ ♪
(children giggling)
Okay, Maggie, we’ll be back
in three hours.
Or longer if something
happens to us.
Maybe we shouldn’t
do this.
She doesn’t know
anyone here.
Look, sweetie,
there’s a familiar face--
Krusty!
(Maggie giggling)
Hey, hey, kids!
Your old pal Krusty’s gonna
teach you five new words:
unlicensed use of my image.
All right, boys.
See those Krustys
nobody paid me for?
Sandblast them!
Entertain the troops?
No way!
What have they
ever done for me?!
Krusty, you made
my daughter cry!
Hey, my intellectual property
rights were being infringed.
Do you know
how that feels?
Do ya?! Huh?! Do ya?!
(grunts)
(yelling)
(screaming)
One, two, three.
Oh! It’s no use.
(doorbell rings)
Mr. Simpson, you have
quite a talent
for killing celebrities.
(chuckling modestly):
Well...
I’m no drunk driving.
I’d like to introduce you
to some stereotypical ad men.
Simpson, we got a swell
little notion for you.
Did you know you can put
a dead celebrity in a commercial
and you don’t have
to pay them a thing?
♪ ♪
Oh, my God, you finally did it.
You mixed Buzz Cola
with the smooth, rich taste
of lemon.
Unfortunately, there are certain
stars who won’t do what we want.
What’s their problem?
They’re still alive.
And then we thought,
"Who’s good at killing
celebrities?"
Me!
That’s right.
Homer, would you be willing
to acquire some more, um...
uh, accounts for us?
Well, you know,
it is awfully hot today.
(chuckles)
Now I’m too cold.
Mmm.
♪ Psycho killer ♪
♪ Qu’est-ce que c’est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa
far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run, run, run,
run away ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Psycho Killer ♪
♪ Qu’est-ce que c’est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa
far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run, run, run,
run away ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh... ♪
♪ Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Psycho Killer ♪
♪ Qu’est-ce que c’est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa-fa
far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run, run, run,
run away. ♪
We can’t just sit here
while they exploit our images!
ANNOUNCER (on TV):
Hey, John Wayne,
have you heard
about stockswapper.org’s
low, low transaction fees?
Sounds... like... quite...
a... deal... pilgrim!
I hate...
trans... action... fees!
(laughs)
Hey, George Washington,
see if you think
this is funny.
♪ ♪
ANNOUNCER:
It’s the Springfield
Wedding Chapel’s annual
President’s Day
marriage-a-thon!!
(moaning)
That ad implies
that Mr. Lincoln
and I are...
betraying
familiarities!
It’s an outrage.
(chuckles)
Yes, uh, an outrage.
(clamoring)
(horse whinnying)
So, are we gonna sit here
flapping our jaws,
or are we gonna do something
about it?
-(clamoring)
-Now wait
just a gosh-darn minute here.
We can’t go taking the law
into our own hands.
These are people with hopes
and dreams and-and, uh...
Put a sock in it,
mushmouth!
(cheering)
All we are saying is
"Let’s eat some brains"!
(indistinct chattering)
Great party, Homer!
Murdering Kate Winslet paid
for that chocolate fountain.
(horse whinnying)
-(gasps)
-Huh?
(rumbling)
(gunfire)
(people screaming)
G-g-g-golda Meir!
("Hava Nagila" playing)
(sighs)
Ah, you ripped me off. See?
No, I didn’t. See!
You’re gonna pay
for what you done. See!
(groans)
I always thought I’d die
of hepatitis... C.
(groans)
Rip Taylor?
You’re not even dead!
Someone needs to check
my apartment.
(laughs)
(humming)
(gasps)
Let’s get him!
Little Sister, is that
moustache comin’ or goin’?
Well, your wife likes it.
(laughing)
You’re all right,
Goofy Grape.
People, please.
(cocks gun)
We’re here to kill this jerk.
Before you kill me,
I gotta know...
what is the one true religion?
It’s a mix of voodoo
and Methodist.
(Homer grunts)
(laughs)
Shouldn’t have left the key
under the mat, suckers!
So what do you do
for fun around here?
Well, tonight we’ve got
a poker tournament
at the rec center.
Ooh!
After you, Mr. Pennyface.
Is your wife up here?
(chuckles)
Well, uh, we have
an understanding.
Mmm.
( Peanuts theme song playing)
(yawning)
Phew!
Good grief.
I like your witch
costume, Lisa.
I’m not a witch.
I’m a Wiccan.
Why is it when a woman is
confident and powerful,
they call her a witch?
(trombone playing)
What did you say, Mom?
Nothing.
I’m practicing
my trombone.
♪ ♪
So, what are you wearing
to the Halloween party,
Milhouse?
I’m not going
to the party.
I’m going to the
pumpkin patch
to wait for the
Grand Pumpkin!
♪ ♪
That means
"you kids have fun"!
What’s the Grand Pumpkin?
Every Halloween,
the Grand Pumpkin visits
all the pumpkin patches
in the world
and brings candy to kids
who truly believe!
Milhouse, for the
last time,
I made that up
to mess with you.
The Grand Pumpkin
isn’t real!
I appreciate you
testing my faith, Bart,
but it’s not necessary.
I believe in the Grand Pumpkin,
almighty gourd,
who was crustified
over Pontius Pie-plate,
and ascended into oven.
He will come again to judge
the filling and the bread...
Sigh.
(gasps)
You’ve all come
to wait for the
Grand Pumpkin with me!
Who wants to sing
pumpkin carols?
I’ve got a pumpkin
carol for you.
(clears throat)
♪ You are such
a stupid moron ♪
♪ It makes people
want to punch you ♪
♪ The Grand Pumpkin’s
superga-ay ♪
♪ Punch, punch, punch,
punch, wedgie! ♪
(groans)
(laughing)
Your god is wrong!
Let’s get
to the Halloween party.
I want to hit
the apple tank
before all the Granny
Smiths are bobbed out.
Lis, you comin’?
Eh, I think I’ll stay
with Milhouse.
His glasses fog up
when he cries.
DOLPH:
More Granny Smiths
for me.
Lisa, Lisa, wake up!
-He’s here!
-What?
The Grand Pumpkin is here?!
No. I’m rehearsing what I’m
gonna say when he shows up.
He’s here! He’s here!
He is here!
♪ ♪
You owe me restitution!
If he sees us fighting,
he might not come.
(groans)
Grand Pumpkin,
I know you’re real.
Why won’t you show yourself?!
(sobbing):
Why?
(sobbing)
Whoa!
Happy Halloween!
The Grand Pumpkin!
You are real!
That’s right, Milhouse.
Your childlike belief
has brought me to life!
I knew you’d come!
I even baked you a loaf
of homemade pumpkin bread!
Oh, how delightful--
bread made especially
for pumpkins.
(munching)
-Mm-hmm.
-Actually,
it’s made from pumpkins.
Wha...?!
(vomiting)
Uh-oh.
Revenge!
(screams)
(panting)
(chuckles)
I’m gonna give you
crossed eyes
like you might see
on an idiot,
a stupid triangle nose,
and a big mouth
full of the ugliest shaped
teeth there are--
square.
And I’m gonna make
your friends watch.
(screaming):
No!
(whimpering)
Ladies.
Stupid.
(airplane whirring)
♪ ♪
Everybody, listen!
The Grand Pumpkin is real!
Hey!
-No hard-soled shoes!
-(thud)
(kids screaming)
Oh, God!
Everywhere I look--
pumpkin atrocities!
Care for a pumpkin seed?
-(sizzling)
-(gasps)
You roast the unborn?
(screams)
(grunting)
Touch me
and I’ll cut your friend!
What do I care?
That’s a yellow pumpkin.
(gasps)
You’re a racist!
All pumpkins are racist.
The difference is I admit it!
(grunts)
I’d rather die
than hate!
This is all my fault!
The Grand Pumpkin said
my childlike belief
was what made him
come to life!
Belief, eh?
Hmm.
Say, Milhouse, have
you by any chance
ever heard of
"Tom Turkey"?
No. Who is he
and what’s his origin story?
Um...
well, Tom is a magical turkey
who gave the pilgrims
the technology
to put buckles on their hats.
Now he appears
every Thanksgiving
to children
who believe.
Sounds plausible.
Tom Turkey, help me.
I believe in you.
Are you looking for a particular
part of my brain or...
Halt, yon pumperkin
most succulent and plump!
I be Tom Turkey!
A giant talking turkey?
Preposterous!
Prepare for the Almighty’s
judgment,
thou stinking fruit
of rotted vine!
(horn playing)
Pumpkin segregation forever!
(groans)
(all sigh)
I can’t live on the outside.
I can’t!
(whimpering)
Milhouse, your childlike
innocence saved us all!
Tom, how can we repay you?
How about
a Thanksgiving feast?
You can carve
the turkey.
(gasps)
You eat turkeys?!
Oh, yeah.
It’s delicious!
Especially when
we take stuffing
and shove it up
the turkey’s...
Revenge!
(kids screaming)
Looks like those kids found
the true spirit of Halloween.
Or Thanksgiving.
Or whatever.
And for those of you who feel
like we’ve trampled
on a beloved children’s classic,
I encourage you to write
to the following address.
♪ ♪
Happy Holidays, everyone!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem