CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
D’oh!
(screams)
-Huh?
Lemonade!
Sweet sunshine in your mouth!
Buy a cup,
or I punch my sister!
It’s true!
He’s not bluffing!
Hmm.
Ow.
Maybe we should
put a dollar in the jar,
prime the pump.
What are we,
a piano bar?
(tires screeching,
people clamoring)
I’ll take 15 lemonades.
Make that 16.
Huh?!
Lousy dog.
If you had your way,
I’d walk you every day.
(gasps)
Lemonade!
(whimpers)
(panting)
-(people groaning)
-Stop pushing!
Six cups, please.
And put it on my tab.
Keep moving,
deadbeat.
Cash only.
Fine.
Lemonade’s for babies anyways.
I’m going to Moe’s, for beer!
Have fun drinking
your lemonade, babies!
(car engine sputtering)
Lisa, can Daddy
borrow your bike?
I guess.
(grunting)
(screams):
Oh...!
(moaning)
(bell dings)
(grunting)
(straining)
(pop)
(sighs)
Hey, Moe, give me a...
Homer, shush!
We’re watching Krabappel try
to break up with Skinner.
Seymour, I have
something difficult
I want to
say to you.
I understand.
It can be very difficult for
a woman to propose marriage.
But I am willing
to go halvsies on a ring.
Seymour...
(groans)
Excuse me.
Any of you lugs
want to break up
with my boyfriend for me?
I’ll buy
you a beer.
Seymour, Edna asked
me to talk to you.
Splendid!
Shall we discuss music
or the weather?
No, this is
about you.
Edna wants
to break up.
She wants to break up?
-Yeah.
-With me?
Yeah.
Look at it this way:
you’re a free man.
Unlike me.
You have all
your hair.
Unlike me.
No kids tying you down
or a crippling mortgage
that you refinanced at 26%
because a dancing
Internet cowboy told you to.
(sobbing):
Oh, God, I hate my life.
(sobbing)
Gee, compared to you,
my life is one big half-day.
Exactly.
You’re good looking,
you have a decent job.
What lonely widow wouldn’t
consider you an option?
Thanks, Homer.
I don’t think
the school pep squad
could’ve cheered me up more,
and they were
state runners up in 1997.
(whistling happy tune)
Homer, that was amazing.
He actually felt better
coming out of
the breakup
than he did going in.
Say, Homer,
you’re real good at this.
Think you could dump my
girlfriend Doreen for me?
Doreen.
She’s cheated on
you with everyone.
Well, except for me.
And I’ve showered her
with gifts--
fancy soaps and massage oils
and, uh, what have you.
Ooh, here she comes.
Work your magic, Homer.
Is Lenny here?
Oh, I’m afraid
Lenny’s dead.
What?
I just talked to him.
And you will again, because
he isn’t really dead.
And now this next piece
of news won’t seem so bad.
(children clamoring)
Lemonade!
We want lemonade!
Don’t worry, folks.
Our master chef is
stirring up a fresh batch.
Stop that transaction!
I’m a part-time field agent
with the Springfield
Department of Commerce.
Great gig.
It is a great gig.
May I see your
vendor’s license?
Um, I think it’s...
We don’t have one.
(coins clinking)
35 cents?
Where did that come from?
Can’t be mine.
Must be yours.
I don’t care
if it’s 45 cents,
I don’t want it.
Submit this form to
the License Bureau.
Until then, this
stand is closed.
til then, this
stand is closed. Boys.
Geez, I’m thirsty.
You got any lemonade?
Not anymore!
(muttering):
...lemonade.
(grunts)
-(people grumbling)
-Come on already.
Come on, come on.
I was halfway through
an operation
when my license expired.
I’ll get to you,
just as soon as I finish
this crossword puzzle.
-(grumbling, groaning)
-Ah, no, come on.
Let’s go, buddy.
I left bananas in my car.
Let’s see, uh, ten across:
"Franklin Roosevelt’s
middle name."
Excitement.
Oh, wait, that don’t fit.
(grumbling, groaning)
Maybe you could use some help.
"FDR’s middle name": "Delano."
"Oxidized surface":
Well, that’s "rusty."
"Bartenders serve them ’dirty.’"
Ham sandwiches!
No, "martinis."
Oh, right.
(chuckles)
One more word!
"Singer of Yentl," 13 letters.
Um...
I got it!
"Isaac Bashevis!"
Now, give me my license!
Give everyone their license!
(cheering)
Whoo, what is
a four-letter word for "hero"?
"Hero."
Yes,
but I meant "Lisa."
ALL (chanting):
Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
(phone rings)
-Y’ello.
-Homer?
It’s your old roommate, Grady.
The gay guy?
That’s not all I am!
Well, it’s a lot of what I am.
Any-hoo, I heard how good
you are at breaking up couples.
I need your help
to break up with Julio,
’cause I met
someone new,
someone much more
cool and refreshing.
Uh-huh, got it.
(calling out):
Marge,
I’m going to
a hardcore gay club,
and I won’t be home
till 3:00 in the morning!
MARGE:
Have fun!
(giggles)
Ay carumba!
Bart, I’ve fallen in love
with crosswords.
(laughs hysterically)
It finally happened.
You’ve gone completely
fruit loops.
"Fruit Loops."
That’s the answer to 38 down:
"Toucan’s delight."
No, I mean
you’re loco in the coco.
"Cocoa": "Ice rink drink."
-You’re losing it!
- "Losin’ It":
"Risque ’80s teen flick."
Fine, go nuts,
see if I care.
"Eye care":
"Optician’s concern."
Oh, thanks
for your help, Bart.
"Bart":
"San Francisco people mover."
Speaking of San Francisco
people mover...
(loud dance music playing)
(Spanish accent):
Grady is breaking
up with me?!
You’ll always have
a special place in his heart!
In his what?
Aw.
Oh, baby, you are
the breakup king.
You-You have made
the seven minutes
that I’m gonna go without love
so much more bearable.
Anyone else want me to get rid
of that special someone?
Okay, everyone,
rotate one to your right.
Guess what, Mom.
I’m a cruciverbalist.
Another religion?
(sighs)
You know, you’re just
gonna drop the whole thing
when you go to college
and get a Jewish boyfriend.
Probably.
But a cruciverbalist
is a fan of crossword puzzles,
which I am!
Me, too!
I been doing
them since 1958.
Back then, we called them
Alphabet Hotels,
’cause every letter
gets its own little room.
(laughs)
I still do the Springfield
Shopper puzzle every day.
Uh-huh, let’s see there.
Grampa, everyone knows
that the only real test of skill
is the New York Times puzzle,
edited by Will Shortz.
"Will" and "shorts"--
two things I’m no longer
allowed to change by myself.
Okay, back to the real world.
(gasps)
Isn’t it beautiful?!
Sure is.
Who’s driving
the bus?
What bus?
(kids screaming)
-(phone rings)
-HOMER: Sweet Conclusions
Breakup Service.
Oh, yes, we dispose
of your loved one humanely,
thanks to our patented
TenderDump System.
(chuckles)
I’ll be there in 30 minutes,
or your breakup is free...!
("Farewell To You, Baby"
by Carl Martin playing)
♪ I’m leaving you, baby ♪
♪ With my clothes in my hand ♪
♪ Farewell to you, baby ♪
♪ Get yourself a monkey man ♪
♪ I’m leaving ♪
♪ With my clothes in my hand ♪
♪ Farewell to you ♪
♪ Get yourself a
monkey man. ♪
(humming tune)
Simpson!
What in the blue blazes
are you doing
to my hopscotching grids?
I-I made them into a crossword.
Oh.
(chuckles)
Well, I’m a bit
of a puzzle head myself.
They, uh, help me wind down
after a day of dealing with
(shouts):
Skinner!
You called?
Made reference.
My mistake.
Lisa, I think you might
be ready for this.
"Bald Man’s
Basketball League"?
Hmm? Sorry, wrong flier.
I meant this.
"Citywide
Crossword Tournament"?
Oh, thank you!
Ah, you’re welcome.
Now, uh, I have to go home
and make sure my pool boy
is using his
(shouts):
skimmer!
You called?
You misheard.
My mistake.
(Homer humming tune)
Marge, if I had
a hundred dollars
for every customer
I’d broken up,
I’d have exactly
this amount.
’Cause that’s
what I charge.
(laughs)
Homie, I’m not sure about
this new business of yours.
You’re making it too easy
for couples to break up
just because
they hit a rough patch.
I know this is hard on you.
But in time, you’ll come
to see it’s for the best.
That’s one of your
breakup lines!
What would have happened
if there was someone
who could break us up every
time I had my doubts about you?
(snoring)
(gasps)
Who are you?
We are the spirits
of the relationships you killed.
(all moaning eerily)
(screaming)
We’re the babies those
couples would have had.
(gasps, screaming)
And we’re the antiques
those couples would have
bought together.
(gasps)
Get him, chairs and babies!
(gasping)
(screaming)
Homie?
Marge, I’m getting out
of the breakup business.
And I don’t know if I’ll ever
sleep soundly again!
Well, maybe...
(snoring)
Wow, so this is
what this is.
Cruciverbalists from far
and wide have gathered here
for a no-holds-barred
test of skill.
Surely some holds
are barred.
No, none.
Well, it sounds
really exciting,
and you’re a delightful
young lady.
Now if you’ll excuse me.
(humming)
Hey, what’s going on?
It’s kind of a secret, so shut
the door most of the way.
We found a way to make this
tournament interesting.
We bet on the matches.
Really?
Well, I did bring this envelope
full of money.
And these days, betting in a bar
is safer than any stock,
bond or real estate investment.
Agreed.
So, who are you gonna bet on?
I want you to put it all on
my little girl.
And parlay with the Asian kid.
He has a name,
you know.
What is it?
I don’t know.
He’s not my kid.
I win!
She won!
And like any
prudent gambler,
I know when
to walk away: never!
♪ Yo, pretty ladies around
the world ♪
♪ Gotta a weird thing
to show you ♪
♪ So tell all the boys
and girls ♪
♪ Tell your brother, your
sister and your mama, too ♪
♪ ’Cause they’re about
to throw down ♪
♪ And you know
just what to do ♪
♪ Wave your hands in the air
like you don’t care ♪
♪ Glide by the people as they
stop to look and stare ♪
♪ Do your dance, do your dance,
do your dance quick, mama ♪
♪ Come on, baby, tell me
what’s the word ♪
♪ Word up, everybody say ♪
♪ When you hear the call,
you’ve got to get it underway ♪
♪ Word up. ♪
-(whistle blows)
-Okay, everybody,
take a break.
(chuckles):
Dad, I could actually
win this thing!
And when you win, I win.
(laughing)
I’ll explain that to you
on your deathbed.
My only fear is
I always sabotage myself
when I’m on the verge
of happiness.
-You what?
-In my young life,
I’ve seen that every time
I’m about to achieve
true happiness,
some little piece of me says,
"You don’t deserve this."
And another little piece
says, "I agree."
Right, right.
But will it happen
this time?
With my luck,
I bet it will.
It’s practically
a sure thing.
Hmm...
(gasps)
Contestants to your boards.
Wish me luck.
Just be yourself.
I want to change my bet.
I’m going against my daughter.
-(all gasp)
-I’ll take your money,
but I won’t look
you in the eye.
Fine.
I won’t look you in the eye.
(grunting)
Have I made the bet yet?
I got it.
We’re down to our final two
contestants.
But before they compete,
we would like to pay tribute
to all the words that have been
removed from the dictionary
in the past year.
(soft music plays)
(applause)
You know,
my wife Shirley,
she’s the real
crossword ace
in our family.
Fills in those letters
fast as hail on a tin roof:
ping-ping-ping, she’s done.
Ah, Shirley passed away
two years ago,
but I’m still not over it.
Aw, that’s so sad.
Hey, what can you do?
Life keeps changing
the music,
but you gotta keep up
the cha-cha-cha, huh?
(humming)
(buzzer sounds)
Let’s see, I’ll spread
some Qs around.
That’ll get my brain going.
(gasps)
Oh, I dropped my glasses.
Oh, Shirley, baby,
I let you down.
(sobbing)
Hey, there are no lenses
in these glasses.
Let’s see,
that’s "Enrico Fermi",
and there you’ve got
the "Pet Shop Boys,"
and cross the T and zing the Z
and skit-skat skoodily
I’m all the way home.
(buzzer sounds)
(all cheering)
Lisa got hustled.
Oh, I blew it again.
She blew it again.
Whoo-hoo!
Here’s your money...
drenched in your
daughter’s tears.
You know,
for a bartender-bookie,
you’re awfully judgmental.
(whistling happy tune)
Boy, Dad seems
awfully happy.
And there’s something
different about him.
He bought new shoelaces
with fancy metal tips.
Dad, did you come
into some money
we don’t know about?
(gasps)
No.
You got highlights
in your hair!
Uh... the sun did that.
And your car antenna
has been straightened
and re-balled.
What’s going on?
Well, sweetie, Daddy made
a little extra money
betting against you
in the crossword tournament.
You’ll understand
when you’re a parent
placing large wagers
against your own children.
I hope you’re not mad.
No, I’m not mad.
You sure you’re not mad?
No. I’m not mad.
No, I’m not mad.
Mr. Teddy,
can you ask Lisa if she’s mad?
What’s that, Mr. Teddy?
You’re saying
that you know women,
and that when women say
they’re not mad,
they’re madder than ever?
Oh... she’s gone.
Can you drive me home?
I’m a little drunk.
Lisa?
Lisa?!
Lisa, sweetie,
please look at your Daddy.
You stopped
being my Daddy
as soon as you
bet against me!
All I have now is a mom,
which is why I’m taking her
maiden name!
From now on, I’m Lisa Bouvier!
(gasping)
Hey, Mr. S.
Lisa B.
(screams):
No...!
Would you like to buy
some band candy?
Yes...!
Lisa’s mad at me,
and now she’s using Marge’s
maiden name instead of mine.
Homer, whatever you done
to that little girl,
you just gotta do something
even nicer to win her back.
She may never take
back your name,
but there’s
still a chance
she’ll take you
back as a Daddy.
Wow, nobody gives better
parenting advice
than childless drunks.
So the name "Lisa Simpson"
is available, huh?
Lotta goodwill attached
to that name.
I gonna take it.
(phone rings)
Lisa’s Tavern, Lisa speaking.
Lisa, sweetie,
I’m honored
that you chose my name,
but it’s not that great.
Back in high school,
the boys used to call me
Marge "Boobier."
Hey, Bouvier was Jackie
Kennedy’s maiden name.
Really?
I never knew that.
What did you think
her name was
before it was Kennedy?
Jackie "O."
Like SpaghettiOs.
I thought that was where
her money came from.
Look, why don’t
you cheer up
by doing a New York Times
crossword puzzle, huh?
I’m through
with crosswords.
My innocence died
in those 441 little boxes.
It might be a fun way
to kill a couple hours.
A couple hours?
I can do the Sunday puzzle
in less than one hour.
(chuckles)
(scoffs):
A couple of hours.
Last clue: "Loses on purpose."
Huh...
(gasps):
Diets!
(chuckles)
Oh, Will Shortz,
you clever rascal.
And a new record time.
Wait a second.
"Dumb Dad Sorry For His Bet."
Wow, it’s almost as if
Dad planted that message.
No, it must just be
a weird coincidence.
But what if it’s not?
Oh, it must be.
Or mustn’t it not?
Dad, I know
this is crazy,
but did you plant
a message to me
in the New York Times
crossword puzzle?
Well, I had a little help
from this guy.
(gasps):
New York Times Crossword
Editor Will Shortz!
(gasps):
And master puzzle
constructor Merl Reagle!
I actually wrote that crossword.
And I edited it.
Now get back
to crosswording!
Yes, sir.
Well, I must admit,
I’m kind of touched.
"Dumb Dad Sorry
For His Bet."
Nice.
You didn’t get Homer’s
whole message, Lisa.
I didn’t?
Take a look at the first letters
of all the clues.
HOMER:
Dear Lisa,
you make me so happy.
Really, really, really happy.
Sorry, he told me I needed
a 144 letters.
What was my point again?
Oh, right.
Bouvier or Simpson,
I cherish you.
Oh, Dad.
♪ "Cherish" is the word
I use to describe ♪
♪ All the feeling
that I have ♪
♪ hiding here
for you inside ♪
♪ You don’t know
how many times ♪
♪ I’ve wished
that I had told you ♪
♪ You don’t know... ♪
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem