CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(clocks ticking and chiming)
(horns honking)
BILL (on radio):
Bill and Marty
here in the middle
of another Fourth of July
weekend Shock Jock Talk Block.
All weekend long,
we’ll be counting down
the top 500 wacky sound effects
of all time.
MARTY:
And here is #499.
Where were you
when you first heard this?
("boing" sound effect playing)
BILL:
I’ll tell you where I was.
I was out eating...
(Chinese jingle playing)
-I think I had kung pao...
-(cat meowing)
and I ended up on the...
-(toilet flushing)
-(laughing)
I can’t listen to this anymore.
Nobody shuts out
my blather!
Uh-oh.
Homie, let’s pick up
those hitchhikers.
They don’t look like
the stabby kind.
Mom, you said
all hitchhikers
were drug-crazed
thrill-seekers.
I said they were
thrill-crazed drug-seekers.
Don’t put words
in my mouth.
Thanks for stopping.
This is my girlfriend,
Beatrice.
(giggling)
Aw... young love.
(chuckling)
Were we ever
that stupid?
Of course we were.
Marge, I thought
of a new thing.
It’s called
"biking out."
It’s a combination
of biking and making out.
I don’t know.
Come on.
All the teens on bikes
are doing it.
(screaming)
(groaning)
Howdy-do, strangers.
Hop on in before you become
a couple runneth over.
Ned, are you sure?
They’re covered with mud.
And in that mud,
I’m planting the seed
of friendship.
(chuckles)
Name’s Ned Flanders.
As the elephant said
to the peanut vendor,
toss those in my trunk.
(whispering):
Marge, I love this guy.
Put her there,
muddy buddy.
Oh, he rhymes!
Oh, happy day.
So, are you two engaged?
Engaged to be engaged?
Well, we thought
we’d wait a little while.
Really, not married?
And you were bicycling
two abreast?
I wish.
We were bicycling to a lake.
(chuckles)
Wordplay.
Never cared for it.
But it’s never too soon
for you two
to join the
"I do" crew.
Now, I’m not saying
it’s all Jell-O with Cool Whip.
She’ll nag you.
She’ll try to change you.
You’ll be fighting
the same basic fight
for years and years and years...
Ned, don’t you think
you’re exaggerating just a bit?
I think I’d like to
finish my sentence.
And years.
Um, how long
have you two been married?
Since 2:00
this afternoon.
Welcome
to our honeymoon.
-Whoa.
-(groaning)
Marge Bouvier,
will you not marry me?
Homer Simpson,
I would be delighted
not to marry you.
Then, I now
pronounce us just dating.
(moaning)
I love kissing you.
I never want
to knock it off.
Knock it off!
How dare you expose my children
to your tender feelings.
Bart, don’t you dare
take your eyes
-off that GameBoy.
-Yes, sir.
Avast, you!
(guns firing, screaming)
(giggling)
(humming)
(guns firing, screaming)
I’m cuckoo for killing stuff!
Video games:
the reason this generation
of Americans
is the best ever.
I can’t believe Homer
ruined another family picnic.
Hey, everybody pees in the pool.
Not from the diving board.
(grumbling):
Why did we have to have
these two jerks along?
You’re driving too fast.
You’re losing your hair.
You sneeze like a girl.
SELMA:
Your neck looks like
a sideways ass.
HOMER:
That’s it!
(tires screeching)
Eat gravel, hags!
Homer, that was rude
and shortsighted.
Patty and Selma
have the map.
I have the situation
under control.
The compass needle
is pointing east.
That’s the fuel gauge.
HOMER:
Uh-oh.
How many times do I
have to say I’m sorry?
You haven’t said
you’re sorry.
I know, I was hoping
the number might be zero.
(grumbling)
(doorbell ringing)
Can we use your phone?
Of course, it’s just past
the sushi bar,
behind the limbo pit,
right in front
of the blackjack table.
And feel free to stay.
We just put out the cheese.
We have cubes of yellow,
cubes of orange,
and cubes of orange
and yellow.
A really fun party
full of colored cheeses
and awesome stuff
to do?
Doesn’t seem like your
kind of thing, Marge.
(grumbles)
We’ll stay for one hand roll
or two nigiri.
Then, we have
to get back to the kids.
Oh, let my dad enjoy them
a little longer.
(Grampa laughing)
Stop!
(laughing):
Where are the cookies?
I don’t remember.
Wrong answer.
(laughing miserably)
(grunting)
Oh, for me?
No, get two of your own.
(laughs)
You’re a funny one.
That’s strong.
Are you trying
to get me drunk?
No, I’m trying
to get me drunk.
(chuckling)
You know,
my horoscope said
I’d meet the man
of my dreams tonight.
Well, a horoscope
would never lie
to a pretty girl like you.
You are adorable.
Are you alone?
No, I’m talking to you
at this great party.
Well, then, would
you like to limbo?
Limbo?
You mean the dance
or that place where
unbaptized babies go?
Either way, I’m in.
(chuckling)
("Limbo Rock" playing)
♪ Every limbo boy and girl ♪
♪ All around the
something world ♪
♪ Gonna do the limbo rock ♪
♪ Something something
limbo something ♪
♪ Limbo lower now ♪
♪ How low can you go? ♪
That’s how low
you can go!
Why are you dancing
with that strange woman?
She’s not strange.
She’s fun.
And she doesn’t
get jealous
when I talk
to other women.
Well, then, she can have
you all to herself!
(grumbling)
(whispering):
How about a sushi fight?
Sushi fight!!
Huh?
(all laughing)
These fish died
for nothing!
(laughter continues)
Homer Simpson,
I wish I’d never met you.
Thanks for the lift.
What a cute couple.
(whispering):
She’s gonna take him
for a lot of money.
Here we are.
A log cabin?
What am I, Davy Crockett?
Also, who’s Davy Crockett?
Kids, this place
has very special memories
for your mother and me.
Well, leaving
right now
will become a special
memory for me.
(giggling)
They have a pedal car.
(singsong):
Pedal cars suck.
They’re worse
than walking.
(singsong):
I’ll put 100 bucks
in your college fund.
(singsong):
I’ll take
ten bucks now.
(singsong):
I’ll steal it back
when you’re sleeping.
(wheels squeaking)
Well, when the sun
goes down,
it means God’s
gone to China
to watch over
those good folks.
Time for some shut-eye.
(chuckles)
Why, Flanders, you rogue.
All Marge and I need
are a queen-sized bed
and a king-sized
"Do Not Disturb" sign.
(growls seductively)
Sorry, Homer, I’m afraid
it’s separate accommodations
for you notly-weds.
What?
But I have urges.
That’s just your
trouser devil talking.
He’s not talking.
He’s yelling.
(sighs)
Good night, Marge.
(humming)
Sweet dreams,
my new best friend.
(humming)
(creaking)
Oh, what better way
to celebrate our wedding night
than by keeping
an unmarried couple apart.
Oh, Maude.
Your dead grandmother’s pajamas.
You know what that does to me.
(gasps)
(sighs)
I never thought
I’d say this, but...
stupid Flanders.
There’s absolutely nothing
to worry about.
I’m in my own room,
being chaperoned
by an actual Christian.
Well, I just don’t trust
that Homer Simpson.
He’s that
rare combination
of up to something
and good for nothing.
(chuckling)
Good one.
We should put that
in the file.
(laughs)
Nice.
(both laughing)
(laughing)
(humming)
(soft sobbing)
Madame, perhaps I can be
of some assistance.
But I can’t take
a dress from a man
who looks so good
and smells so clean.
Please... when you came
through the door tonight,
I instantly imagined you
in a ruched burgundy
bias-cut evening gown
with a wolverine hem
and a contrasting
cerise tulle décolletage.
Really, me?
You did?
Oh, yes,
with a pair
of saffron brocade
diamond mink pumps.
Oh.
Pumps are shoes.
That explains a lot.
Mm-hmm.
(grunts excitedly)
Marjorie,
you look beautiful.
Let me take you
for a ride.
Or, should I say, "glide"?
I’m just happy
you’re talking again.
You didn’t say a word
for 45 minutes.
Marge?
You don’t need her, baby.
Sylvia’s got everything
you want.
Do you have
a pineapple pizza?
Pineapple and pepperoni.
Oh. This is all
going so fast.
We should be getting
back to the party.
Marjorie, that party
was beneath a woman
of your elegance
and sophistication.
You... Oh, look,
a budget motel!
I see the word vacancy is lit,
and the word no is not.
Let us pray the no
is not broken, huh?
(groans)
(crickets chirping)
Alberto, I’m not sure
if this is such a good idea.
Uh, uh, uh!
First we make love,
then we decide
if it was a good idea.
That’s the European way.
I came here once
with Marge.
Are you Marge, Sylvia?
Homer, I can be whoever
you want me to be.
I want you to be Marge.
(Marge sighing)
Marge?!
Mmm, mmm,
mmm, mmm...
HOMER:
Marge, is that you?
(gasps)
My husband!
Why do married women
always have husbands?
(grunting)
Aw!
Ooh!
Aah!
(grunting)
Marge,
what are you doing here?
Uh the same thing
you’re doing here.
You better not be!
I mean, great!
We both came to rekindle
our precious memories
of when we were young
and in love, right?
We sure did.
Rekindle, rekindle.
Okay, let’s go.
Oh, oh, oh,
I have a better idea.
Let’s spend the night
together right here.
Fine, but I don’t
want to sleep
in the same room
with that chest.
I feel the same way
about that lamp.
Okay, but first the chest.
Okay.
(grunting)
(sighs)
There you are!
Homie, what’s taking so long?
Listen, you’re a classy lady
and a great sushi fighter,
but you’re going
in the box.
(whimpers)
MARGE:
Homie?
Coming, Marge!
(singsong):
Mmm, mmm!
(door squeaks)
(squeaking)
Good evening.
-I am Alberto.
-Sylvia.
Let’s get out of this chest
and go have a drink.
Actually, I am quite
comfortable here.
There is a flask of
cognac in my pocket.
Do you think
you can reach it?
SYLVIA:
Okay.
Uh, is this it?
ALBERTO:
No, but don’t
stop twisting.
(both laughing)
Now let’s spend the rest of
the night making sweet, sweet...
(sighs)
Kids?!
(Homer and Lisa giggling)
I’m through baby-sitting
these monsters!
Good night.
(snoring)
We won!
He’s asleep!
And we’ll stay
up forever!
(both humming)
Oh.
(snores)
(laughing):
Well, that takes care
of those three.
Want to go
for a lakeside snuggle?
Homer Simpson,
you devil!
-Mmm...
(laughing):
Well, that takes care
of those three.
Want to go play
some Lakeside Boggle?
Homer Simpson,
you devil!
(giggles)
But I think we
should unpack first.
Hmm. All right.
The trick is to ease them off.
(whipping)
(screaming)
(grunting)
What is this dump?
Ah, Ruthie, this dump is where
your mother and I met.
It was a tale
of betrayal, redemption,
and a lovely
continental breakfast.
(Homer whimpering)
Homer, those are
our wedding bungees!
(Homer grunts)
(yowling)
Marjorie?!
Homer?
It’s so good to see you.
We owe you two
a debt of thanks.
Homer, if I hadn’t come
to this motel with you,
I never would have
met Alberto.
(gasps)
And Marjorie, if you had
completed your seduction of me,
I never would
have met Sylvia.
(gasps)
I can’t believe one
of the most beautiful moments
in our marriage
is based on lies!
You’re just as bad as me!
And you used to be better,
so that makes you worse!
I don’t think we can ever
trust each other again.
Ruthie, kick me away
from this nightmare.
Okay.
I wish I’d never met you!
-Or you!
-(Bart and Lisa giggling)
Why can’t you just admit
we’re lost?
I’ll tell you what’s lost:
your sense of adventure.
Just ask those guys
for directions.
Hmm. Anti-nuclear activist
Dr. Helen Caldicott?
Director Julie Taymor?
Do you love these women?
They’re okay,
I guess.
Let’s just skip to the
Windsor knot instructions.
LISA:
Excuse me, boys.
My brother is lost,
and kind of a jerk.
If he’d brought a map
of the grounds as I suggested,
-then we would...
-(grunting)
Lisa, do you know
why I spend every day
after school
in detention?
So I don’t have to
come home to you!
Oh, Bart, don’t say things
you can’t take back.
It’s out there.
-Deal with it!
-(sleepy, baby chatter)
Oh, great.
Now you woke the baby.
I told you we should have
left her with your mother!
My God, Bart,
what happened to us?
We grew up.
So, I’m sure
you missed Marge last night.
Yeah. I missed her,
like, five times.
What a charming single entendre.
Now, look,
I know marriage is scary,
but if you really think
she’s the one,
it gives you two a shot
at forever.
Forever?
That would be awesome.
Okay, here she comes.
Why don’t you take Marge
for a walk,
open your heart
and see what pours out?
I suppose you and Maude
will be coming along, as well?
(chuckles)
Don’t you think
I got better things to do
on my honeymoon
than spy on you two?
(static crackles)
Red Dog, this is Mustache One.
We have possible male/female
interaction.
Be prepared to terminate
inappropriate contact.
(clicking)
Ready with the ice water.
NED:
Lock onto his wiener.
We have wiener-lock.
Marge, when I’m with you,
I get that feeling
like when I got that smart kid’s
report card by mistake,
and for a minute,
I thought I had all As,
and that my name
was Howard Simberg.
You make me feel
that way, too.
I know we’ll get married
some day, and to prove it,
I’ll carve our names
on this tree
so all who are hopelessly lost
in the woods can see it.
Oh, I hate other people’s love.
(grunting)
(mumbling)
(grunts)
Oh!
(mumbling)
So that wasn’t Marge’s glider
parked outside the motel
five years ago!
I’m getting out of this marriage
while I’m still young
and handsome.
Hmm?
Oh!
(sniffles)
4EVER.
(sobbing)
I couldn’t even keep a promise
I made to a tree.
Maybe it’s not too late!
Maybe I can still save our love.
If I just show her
that carving.
(whimpering)
(grunting)
Huh? What are
you doing?
Saving our marriage!
(grunts)
Don’t be silly.
Our marriage can weather
any storm, just like this tree.
(rumbling)
-(crackling)
-(whimpering)
Oh! Help!
Fat man hanging from a tree!
Uh-uh.
That’s for fires.
Take my hand!
I don’t want to let go
of our special carving!
Homer, our marriage
isn’t on a piece of bark!
It’s in us!
Now take my hand!
(both grunting)
(gasps)
(Homer screaming)
D’oh!
Oh!
(sobbing)
(screaming)
(grunts)
(gasps)
Marge, I don’t want to die
with us mad at each other.
Me neither, Homie.
I know parts of our marriage
are based on lies,
but so are a lot
of good things:
religion, American history.
I know. We had a fight.
We were both tempted.
We’re human.
The important thing is
we love each other.
Aw.
-Mmm!
-(gasp)
Now we wait for the river
to freeze.
If my theory of global cooling
is correct.
Hey, you guys want a lift
in my pedal boat?
It’s not a pedal boat.
It’s a pedal car
that Bart drove into the river.
Because he knows a shortcut
that’s not on the map.
How’d you like a shortcut
to the bottom of the river?
If it’s your shortcut,
I’ll be high and dry.
(grunts)
(squeaking)
-Mmm...!
Knock it off
back there.
But we’re
married.
Okay, but
keep it PG.
How about R?
-PG-13.
-(whoops)
Adult situations!
(moaning and giggling)
Hey.
(squeaking)
(Homer yawning)
Ow!
(squeaking)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem