MUSASHINO FOREST SPORTS PLAZA MAIN ARENA
It's the first day
of Hey! Say! JUMP's concert tour.
Hours before the doors open,
fans were lining up in anticipation.
But inside the venue, they were still...
Okay, let's start the dress rehearsal.
Let's work hard.
Please turn on the lights.
The dress rehearsal was underway.
Time is limited until the concert begins.
It's the first day,
so the members are feeling nervous.
But these youths
were also fighting nerves
as they faced this day.
They are the staff behind the scenes.
-He's so nervous he's about to throw up.
-Really?
-You're nervous?
-Yes.
Are you okay?
Do your best.
This is a story of youths
who placed their dreams
in the world of entertainment.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Five minutes before the concert.
The members gather below the stage.
They're waiting for us.
Hello.
The first day is so scary.
The young concert staff members
are feeling scared too.
With any concert, the first day is
when I feel the most nervous.
I've never been this nervous before.
SPECIAL EFFECTS
MICHIRU YABE (AGE 21)
They experienced many setbacks
along the road to this day.
Well, I feel like
I'm constantly exhausted.
I feel like I could've done more.
STAGE FACILITATOR
MASAHIRO UEDA (AGE 27)
But it's difficult.
But time won't stop for them.
I'm excited.
We're shaking with excitement.
Let's gather together.
Three more minutes.
Channel your nerves into energy.
Are you crying?
Be careful not to injure yourself.
-Okay.
-Keep control.
Let's go.
All right!
Four youths are supporting
the concert from the sidelines.
Will they be able to survive
the first day?
The first ones to face a challenge
are the special effects team.
The confetti brightens up the arena.
The one diligently cleaning that up
was Michiru Yabe.
SPECIAL EFFECTS
MICHIRU YABE (AGE 21)
She chose this career because
she fell in love with special effects.
But a few days ago,
she experienced a major setback.
Special effects team!
They're taking it all down?
This is a special apparatus called
the scroller, which rains gold confetti.
SCROLLER
It's going up.
But an unexpected mechanical problem
prevented the equipment from going up.
We didn't panic,
we just didn't know what to do.
I was worried
and nervous the whole time.
I'm sure no one expected
that kind of trouble.
I was worried, thinking that
we may not be able to use it.
She once dreamed of a career
in the music industry,
but she gave up.
Her new dream was to excite
the audience with special effects.
Will they be able to rain
gold confetti from the scrollers?
Then it happened...
The confetti and feathers
that rained from the ceiling
created a sensual performance.
I've always wanted to
take part in a concert,
and I'm finally able to join
the arena tour.
I don't want to forget that feeling
I had when I was
in the audience at a concert.
I want to do more so that more people
can enjoy the concerts together
with the special effects.
RYOSUKE YAMADA
The members appreciate
the staff's determination
more than anyone else.
Having the special effects
makes a very big difference.
It gets us excited,
and that relays to the audience.
It makes me realize that this stage
is created with teamwork.
Without the special effects,
I'm just rolling around
on the couch during my solo performance.
Of course, I put my all into it,
but that creates the atmosphere.
On stage, they are about to begin
an important act, the quick change.
Both of you wanted to sing, right?
Yeah.
Standing by under the stage was Ueda,
from the stage facilitator team.
STAGE FACILITATOR
MASAHIRO UEDA (AGE 27)
He joined this tour with only
three months of experience.
Gripped in his hand
was the concert progress chart.
-Hey.
-Yes.
-Come here!
-Yes!
He has been anxious
since the first day of preparation.
It's very fast-paced,
so I have a hard time catching up
and understanding.
I'm so anxious.
But he always showed consideration
towards the members,
and paid attention to the small details.
We were planning to place a basket here
where the performers
can return their glow sticks.
We're deciding on the height
of the basket.
It's time for the quick change.
Ueda prepares the ring for
the members' quick change.
Since each team must work together,
he is feeling nervous.
So, you're going to change?
The ring made it safely to the stage.
Let's change.
Start changing!
This is the quick-changing time!
I'm going to take a little peek.
He was wearing this the whole time?
But this is where
the real challenge begins.
They must gather the props
that are thrown down to them.
Even if the props hit them on the head,
they don't have time to stop.
Because they must start preparing
for Chinen's solo performance.
There's something
he has been taught repeatedly.
Personally, what I try to keep in mind
as a person behind the scenes,
is that we're not supposed to stand out.
We're not supposed to be seen.
If people see us,
or we if show up on the screen,
it lowers the quality of the concert.
So I'm very careful about that.
Ueda has been with us ever since our...
YURI CHINEN
...dance rehearsal.
He does so much for us,
from organizing the props we use
to taking care of all the small details.
It's really dark behind the stage.
It's darker than you expect,
so when we leave
the bright stage
and step into the dark area,
we can't see a thing.
So, when he lights the way for us
and directs us to our next location,
it's a big help.
When the concert begins,
I'm not aware of my surroundings,
so when he's there to help me,
I can rely on him,
and that allows me
to concentrate on what I have to do.
I've been performing
in concerts ever since I entered Johnny's,
so sometimes I take this life for granted.
But if I was starting from scratch,
performing on the streets
instead of a concert,
I'd probably be just another boy.
So, by working with
these professionals, it's actually
shaping me to become professional as well.
The fans probably think
that's who I really am.
I don't think they would like me,
if they saw who I really was.
We're made to look glamorous, thanks to
the lighting, stage production,
and costumes.
I really believe
that we are able to continue
as idols because of
those people behind the scenes.
SOUND
TAKUMA KURAMOCHI (AGE 22)
Like Ueda,
Kuramochi works below stage
with the sound team.
He has overcome
many obstacles to get here today.
Nakajima has a tap dance routine
for his solo performance.
In order for that sound to reach
every corner of the arena,
he attached
a small microphone to his shoes.
But the day before...
I'm not sure, but he may have
stepped on the cable.
There was a problem,
and the cable disconnected.
The cable disconnected
during the rehearsal.
Through trial and error,
he was able to make improvements.
Will the sound of his shoes
be heard throughout the arena?
SPECIAL EFFECTS
MICHIRU YABE (AGE 21)
Yabe from special effects
was also behind the stage.
She is fanning smoke in preparation
for Nakajima's entrance.
It has begun...
The tapping of his shoes
could be heard throughout
the entire arena.
Perfect.
Nakajima says that
without Kuramochi's idea,
his performance
could not have been executed.
When I performed this tap dance
routine in the past,
the cords were attached
to the inside of my pants,
and the mics were attached here.
Here on the arch of the foot.
But this time,
I had to move over here,
right after my solo,
to the center stage
and get on the lifter to perform
a song called "To the Galaxy."
And I had to change in between that.
So, this time he attached
a thin cord on the outside
of my pants using Velcro.
If the cord is too loose,
it can get stuck
or catch on something when I spin around.
So he secured the cord with several
pieces of Velcro down the pant leg,
so that it wouldn't stand out.
That was a great idea.
A performance like this
doesn't simply happen just because
I want to perform a tap dance routine.
There are a lot of things to consider
in order to make it happen.
I have so much respect for the staff
who make everything possible for us.
We work together
to overcome obstacles.
They always have a backup plan for us.
We get to see the excitement
behind creating and building a stage.
So it's very reassuring
to be on the same team as them.
Now the concert is about to
display its main attraction,
the mobile stage.
A young man was working
to create that important moment.
The concert is nearing its end.
All the members dance on the mobile stage.
This is the main attraction.
First, the center stage tilts to
one side as they perform
"To the Galaxy."
Waiting for his cue
in the shadows under the stage,
was the rookie special mechanic,
Shoichiro Fukuda.
He helped construct this stage.
SPECIAL MECHANICS
SHOICHIRO FUKUDA (AGE 24)
Since all the members
will dance on top of it,
they had to make sure it was safe.
What troubled the staff was its weight.
Some parts weighed over one ton.
Insert the bolt with the ratchet.
Okay.
We'll start with Fukuda's side.
Don't smash your finger.
It's your finger, not mine.
During "Dance The Night Away",
the main stage moves around.
Fukuda was placed in charge
of a lifting apparatus called the lifter.
Not only does it carry the members,
it also lifts props onto the stage.
With perfect timing, these stairs
were lifted onto the stage.
When I see the equipment
that we set up actually move,
and I hear the crowd cheering,
it makes everything worthwhile
and it motivates me to continue this work.
I trust the staff members.
During the initial meeting,
we made some impossible requests.
But what's important is...
how close they can
turn that image into a reality.
This time...
That center stage
goes up and tilts to one side.
And it spins while it's tilted.
It's easy to
come up with those ideas,
but it's difficult to carry them out.
But they think about
how they can materialize our ideas.
The fans...
are here to see us,
so they may not give much thought
to those behind the scenes.
But we're creating this together
with the professional staff members.
They bring all of our ideas to fruition.
They're working with us
to turn our dream into a reality.
They continued to tour
around the entire country.
NAGANO BIG HAT
The final day of the tour
was held in Nagano.
As the concert was nearing its end,
Yabe from the special effects team
was in the back making preparations.
SPECIAL EFFECTS
MICHIRU YABE (AGE 21)
Yabe was once in the audience
feeling moved by
the impressive special effects.
Now she's on the side of
providing that experience.
We are...
Come on!
Hey! Say! JUMP.
Thank you.
-Good job, good job.
-Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
-Bye.
-Good job.
-Thank you.
Two months passed since the tour started.
With training under her belt,
Yabe silently completes her task.
During the double encore,
when they were performing
their hit song "Come On A My House,"
the concert staff members
came onto the stage.
They were all standing there
with big smiles on their faces.
They got up on the stage with us.
During the song "Come On A My House,"
all the staff went up
onto the stage
and started dancing with curry.
All of us were like,
"What? You're supposed to be working."
But the Hey! Say! JUMP concerts
allow people to do things like that,
and the fans really appreciate
that warm atmosphere too.
So, we're like family.
I consider them
part of the Hey! Say! JUMP family.
Thank you.
-They left.
-That was awesome.
AFTER THE CONCERT
The concert has ended.
Ueda was just seen on stage,
but now he's back to lighting
the walkway for the members.
It's the end. Good work!
Good work.
See you at the dome concert.
Thank you.
See you again.
At the dome concert.
The dome.
Thank you.
-That was so fun.
-Thank you.
Even after the members are gone,
Ueda was taking care of
other staff members.
After the audience left,
everyone gathered in the arena
to take a group picture.
The four youths have a look of relief
as the arena tour comes to an end.
Ready?
Where's the cue?
Please give the cue.
We are...
Hey! Say! JUMP.
Okay.
See you at the dome.
Thank you.
The youths started moving forward,
towards the dome concert.
To provide a great concert,
no matter what happens.
On the next Ride On Time...
KAZUYA KAMENASHI
Resisting the cruelty of fate,
they have come back.
KAT-TUN.
I knew that we would
get together again someday.
We shared so many heartaches together.
So, I want the three of us
to have a chance at happiness.
Stubbornness or principle...
Or maybe it's my pride.
Their tumultuous 300 days
were filmed on camera.
RESTARTING THE GROUP
THE TUMULTUOUS 300 DAYS
Subtitle translation by Lili Morita