"This is a record of youths
who devoted their adolescence
to entertainment."
Cut it out.
Stop playing around.
Because they take it seriously,
because they trust each other,
sometimes they clash.
When I think about what would've happened
if I didn't join Johnny's
and gave up on
becoming a pro, it scares me.
What is it that awaits them?
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
The debut of King & Prince
was announced in January.
The six of them, who were just
regular youths up to now,
will embark on the craziest
adventure of their lives.
So many died.
I want everyone who is connected
with me to stay alive.
The bitter memories
that became their driving force.
He surpassed me and others.
I was speechless.
Dancing before a crowd
only brought me stress.
We realized that nothing could
bring us down any further.
I think I used up
a lifetime's worth of tears.
Together they've overcome
trials and uncertainty
and made their way
to their big performance.
I feel like it's finally showtime.
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA, AUGUST 9TH, 2018
August 9th.
The day before the opening day
of their concert tour,
they held a rehearsal.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Twenty-one shows in five cities
is out of the ordinary for a new group.
-Is that honey?
-Yes, it is.
My throat isn't that strong.
Actually, it's really weak.
Which one? I accidentally
poured coffee last time.
This is coffee. Thank goodness
I checked. This is the one.
Kaito, Jinguji, Genki.
More than ten thousand fans
will fill this arena.
It's the biggest show
they've done by themselves.
Can you go to the center?
-This is really long.
-It really is.
They've set up trolleys
on the second floor.
We said we wanted to be
as close to the fans,
and see each one of them,
as much as possible.
Spread out more.
Is 2,5 better?
They want their feelings
to reach every corner of the arena.
Another thing they will experience
for the first time
is the sound reverberation
unique to large arenas.
What should I do to stay
on the original beat of the song?
-Do you need a click track?
-Yes.
It's so new to me. The echo is so loud.
GENKI IWAHASHI (AGE 21)
He has experienced various struggles
and continues to battle an illness,
but he has made it all the way here.
He is especially overjoyed.
Did you make amends?
In the pamphlet for this concert,
there is a part that asks us
who we were most influenced by.
In my interview,
I answered Jinguji.
I wrote that he has supported me the most
since we were Johnny's Jr. members
and has always been by my side.
I don't remember saying that.
It's kind of embarrassing.
-See you.
-Okay, thank you.
AUGUST 10TH, 2018
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA
It's opening day.
The arena was buzzing with excitement.
We asked Hirano how he's feeling,
and he gave us a unique answer.
I don't see them as complete strangers.
The fans, I mean.
They're closer...
I know I shouldn't,
but I see them as relatives.
But I want to look good in front of them.
It's like Sports Day!
Like doing your best in the relay race
because your family is there.
No?
Fifteen minutes until showtime.
They can't hide their excitement.
All right!
To the right.
One, two, one, two!
-Let's go!
-No, no!
Right before showtime...
Genki, Ren insists that we form a huddle.
-Here he is.
-Sorry.
Please catch this on camera. This is rare.
At last, it's King & Prince's
first concert.
-Must we do this?
-Yes.
-Let's do it.
-Bear with me.
It's a special beginning for us.
Without making mistakes, let's―
I might mess up.
-Kishi, don't stop him!
-We'll try not to!
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
-Let's go, everyone.
-Let's do this.
I want a rice ball.
You found one? Yeah!
TEN MINUTES UNTIL SHOWTIME
He eats right before showtime.
You're eating a rice ball?
What's inside?
I suddenly became so hungry.
Here I go.
I'll hype up the crowd.
-Break a leg.
-Bye.
AUGUST 10TH, 2018
YOKOHAMA ARENA, SHOWTIME
At last, it's showtime.
CINDERELLA GIRL
GENKI
Yokohama Arena!
This is our first concert!
Make some noise!
Are you ready?
Here we go.
KATSUNDA WIN!
Hey, Yokohama Arena!
Relieve yourself from your stress!
Let's go!
In just three months since their debut,
they've made a big achievement.
But their journey here
was anything but smooth.
SUMMER STATION
Three years ago, they formed a unit
under the name Mr. King vs Mr. Prince.
They hoped to debut once
but were divided into two units
the following year.
Here we go!
The reason why they were able to
debut despite that fact
was because they shared a strong bond.
HELLO!!! HARUIRO
People have called it
a direct negotiation,
but what actually happened was
we went to the president for advice.
He asked, "What do you want to do?"
For us to have a stable job,
we thought that
we would need to debut.
From there,
Mr. Johnny did everything for us.
And next thing we knew,
we were called to the press conference.
Every single member
has a strong sense of self
and his own beliefs.
Each one of us
can help each other grow
and become a unified team.
We're a balanced group like that.
That's how I feel.
All six of us are very unique
and have our own strengths.
The six of us would talk about it often.
Debuting is one of the goals
of any Johnny's Jr. member,
so I was really happy.
And now that we have,
I have a sense of awareness
that this is going to be
my life from now on.
The members are so important to me.
Out of the six of us,
it's as if the five of them
are in front of me
and pulling me forward.
As long as I'm with them,
I have nothing to fear.
We started working
together with Mr. King,
and it was...
our first time working together,
but it didn't feel like it at all.
I took away a lot from that experience.
I could feel a different kind of power
awakening in me,
and I was ready to use it.
You never know if you will
pass the auditions,
and you aren't even told if you do.
And we don't know who or when
someone will debut.
We were struggling in a situation...
where we had no answers.
AUGUST 12TH, 2018
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA
Their last day at Yokohama Arena.
Good morning.
Each member
is experiencing fatigue like never before.
They've already sung
more than 100 songs within two days.
For the members,
this room has become an oasis.
-My back doesn't hurt that much.
-Not your back?
As I expected,
I completely lost my voice.
They treat them using acupuncture.
He is having trouble using his voice
because of fatigue.
Do you have back pain often?
Not really.
Jinguji, on the other hand...
What is up with my calf?
It's so swollen.
AUGUST 17TH, 2018
OSAKA
On this day, they needed to change
a part of the performance.
The song where each member is introduced
has a part that needs fixing.
It is the call and response part where
Kishi introduces Nagase.
Say Nagase...
The fans can't get the timing right.
After the show, they held a meeting.
I think this part...
...is difficult.
You're saying, "He's so sexy, say!" right?
I think that part confuses the fans.
They don't know where to say Ren's name.
Everybody say Ren.
Ren, Ren, Ren.
Something something, Nagase Ren.
-Everybody, everybody, Ren.
-You don't get it!
Everybody say Ren.
You have to say Ren first, so they know.
Ren.
Try it once.
Here we go.
-Everybody, ready...
-No.
No, no, no. You have to say Ren.
-Everybody say Ren.
-Everybody say Ren-kun.
-Ren-kun.
-Why do you add a "kun" at the end?
Just say Ren.
Everybody say Ren.
Everybody say...
Ren.
-Ren.
Looking good, Nagase Ren.
-I've got it.
-Why do I...
have to be after him?
Everyone's favorite, Kishi Yuta
The following day...
Everybody say Ren!
Ren!
Nagase Ren!
If I do it so that
I don't have any regrets,
and I'm satisfied with how much I did,
then even if my hard work doesn't pay off,
I can still accept that.
I have a feeling I can still
reach my goal eventually.
-We'll do our best.
-Break a leg.
Fist bump.
SEPTEMBER 22ND, 2018
SENDAI
And at last, it's the final day
of their tour.
It may be because it's the final day,
but the youngest member,
Takahashi, looks thoughtful.
When I saw it for the first time,
I was so surprised.
I couldn't believe they would
make something like this for us.
It's so elaborate.
Performing on this set
is so much fun for us too.
But the one who has been dealing
with uncertainty more than anyone
is Takahashi.
I can't believe it's our last day.
I just don't have a lot of
self-confidence.
That's how I am. Every day,
I would go home and cry.
And after the concerts,
I would cry.
NAKANO, TOKYO
After Takahashi joined Johnny's,
he led a busy life
as a Johnny's Jr. member
during high school.
Back then, there was someone
who helped him.
Long time no see.
Wow.
Please have a seat.
When he was feeling unsure
while juggling work and school,
the one to always offer a listening ear
was his teacher, Tadashi Nakao.
I remember Mr. Nakao was
one of the only people
who always looked out for me.
He always knew when I was tired.
He could tell if I was up late at night.
Every day, I would talk to him
about my work,
as if I was reporting to him.
That's right. You did that a lot.
-You would tell me your plans for the day.
-And what I did that day.
I haven't looked at it since I graduated.
You haven't?
A yearbook full of memories.
There I am.
The very last row?
The very back. The very back
of the entertainment course.
Many days he would be tardy
or have to leave early,
but he had one rule.
This brings back memories.
But you rarely missed school.
I didn't miss school.
I felt like I had to do well
at school too.
If I didn't get good marks on tests
or get good grades,
I would feel really frustrated.
One time on a test, I came in
first place in my entire grade,
and I bragged about it to everyone.
I told everyone I'm a Johnny's member.
Really? You didn't seem like the type.
Mr. Nakao
had something he wanted to give him,
now that he has debuted.
-This.
-Wow.
I'm so happy.
LAUGHTER, APPRECIATION
Oh, wow.
These are things
that I like to keep in mind
as an idol.
LAUGHTER, APPRECIATION,
AND HARD WORK PAY OFF
One second. When I went
to your place,
you gave me one.
I brought it.
Now I have a complete set.
They have a magical power.
It makes me realize that
it's important for me
to always be smiling.
-That's right.
-Yes.
That's what an idol is to me.
All right, say cheese!
It was almost time for their final show.
SEPTEMBER 22ND, 2018
SENDAI
September 22nd.
Before their final performance,
they have a special ritual.
A photo with the people who've
supported their long journey.
I've always wanted to do this.
Thank you so much
for all your hard work.
Thanks to the support of
each and every one of you,
we are able to stand here.
I hope we can work together
from now on too.
-Go ahead, Kishi.
-Okay.
All right, say cheese!
FIVE MINUTES BEFORE SHOWTIME
Here we go.
See you later.
What is it that awaits them?
When the time comes that any of us
could be the face of the group,
we'll be invincible.
I want to find
our strength quickly and fortify it,
to make it so no one can beat us.
That's my goal.
I hope we can all stay friends.
That will always show in our performances.
I want to become an adult
who can proudly say
I am in King & Prince,
even when I'm an old man.
I hope I can stay
charming enough to say that.
I want to stay like this forever.
The six of us. A little shy
and close-knit.
I want to be able to support each other
while also being able to
stand on our own two feet.
That would be ideal.
Instead of walking down
someone else's road,
I want to create our very own road
and become a group like no other.
We are...
King & Prince!
Thank you.
RIGHT AFTER THE SHOW
Encore!
What if we left?
If we just left...
Well, of course we have to go out.
Let's go.
King & Prince, the six of them
have just begun their journey.
On the next Ride On Time,
we follow four young staff members
who work at the concert events.
I thought I could do better,
but it's not that easy.
When I heard the crowd screaming,
it made it all worth it.
They share the same desire
to entertain the fans
just like the artists.
I don't know how it will work
on the day of, so I'm worried.
I don't think I've ever been
this nervous before.
We see their pride in their work
and dedication to the concert.
Behind the scenes of the concert.
The challenges of new recruits.
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita