MUSASHINO FOREST SPORTS PLAZA MAIN ARENA
That day, four youths stand in the arena,
ready to face the trials that await them.
Good morning, Hey! Say! JUMP.
Good morning.
It's the Musashino Arena rehearsal.
Let's work hard.
Thank you.
Standing on stage,
are the members of Hey! Say! JUMP.
The five-month tour will start
the following day.
In order to provide a quality performance
for the waiting fans,
the rehearsals are taken seriously.
This is Fuji TV?
They're staff.
But they're not filming us.
Yes, the camera is filming
the young concert staff who support
the tour behind the scenes.
They're working hard
in a field where perfection is expected.
-Hey.
-Yes.
-Come here!
I feel like I could've done more.
But it's difficult.
I'm constantly exhausted.
When it's time for the special effects,
I get really nervous.
I'm anxious.
There's been some trouble.
I've never been this nervous before.
I'm really glad that this provides
an opportunity
for the viewers to see
all the people working hard
behind the scenes.
This is a story of youths
who placed their dreams
in the world of entertainment.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
The road to setting up a concert venue.
There are many roadblocks
that challenged these youths.
STAGE FACILITATOR
MASAHIRO UEDA (AGE 27)
Masahiro Ueda from
the stage facilitator team.
His work consists of
paying attention to small details.
We were planning to place a basket here.
We're deciding on
the height of the basket.
SPECIAL EFFECTS
MICHIRU YABE (AGE 21)
Michiru Yabe from
the special effects team.
On the first day of the stage set-up,
she faced unexpected trouble.
They could not raise
the equipment that rains
confetti onto the stage.
SCROLLER
We didn't panic,
we just didn't know what to do.
We didn't know if we'd be
able to raise it up.
The last day of the rehearsal.
The person placed in control of
the intricate stage was facing
a challenging situation.
Fukuda from the special mechanics team.
SPECIAL MECHANICS
SHOICHIRO FUKUDA (AGE 24)
-We'll start with Fukuda's side.
-Okay.
Don't smash your fingers.
-Ready?
-Yes.
And there's Kuramochi from the sound team.
He also had to perform last-minute tasks.
There was a problem,
and the cable disconnected.
They're calling you.
The challenging final rehearsal.
Will they be able to overcome it?
1:30 P.M.
The members start to confirm
their positions on stage.
Let's start from the top.
Do you want to try it once?
Be careful up ahead.
The members and staff
have a certain piece of equipment
that requires a safety check.
It is one of the concert's
main attractions.
The mobile stage
in the middle of the arena.
MOBILE CENTER STAGE
Controlling it
is the special mechanics team.
The lifters are attached
to the main platform,
and some lifters are raised
above the surface of the stage,
while some go below the stage
to spin around,
with various height settings.
So those are the various types of lifters.
I'll be near the lifters,
to operate the machine.
This mobile stage helps
to deliver a dynamic stage.
But because of that, it comes with risks.
The rehearsal for
this stage alone takes three hours.
There are things we use
for the actual performance
like the equipment, machines, and props.
When we use them during
the rehearsal, we find that it doesn't go
the way we had planned on paper.
That's why spending three hours
with the staff to discuss
all the issues that need attention
is a very important process.
And once we all agree
that it's completely safe,
we can have the JUMP members use it.
As the members confirm
their position on stage,
every team is busy preparing
for the dress rehearsal.
SPECIAL MECHANICS TEAM
The one facing the real test,
is the special mechanics team.
SPECIAL MECHANICS
SHOICHIRO FUKUDA (AGE 24)
Fukuda will operate one of the lifters
attached to the main stage.
It's going up. It's moving.
In order to synchronize
the lifter with the music,
he must remain fully focused.
SOUND
TAKUMA KURAMOCHI (AGE 22)
Meanwhile, Kuramochi from
the sound team is in charge of
passing the microphones.
If he is not aware of every move
the members make,
it can disrupt the flow of the concert.
-Yamada's.
-Yamada.
Inoo.
I try to be prepared for
any unexpected events,
but I still end up panicking.
I can't calm down.
STAGE FACILITATOR
MASAHIRO UEDA (AGE 27)
SOUND
TAKUMA KURAMOCHI (AGE 22)
Kuramochi receives
a new request from
the stage facilitator team.
During the quick costume change,
they want him to retrieve the microphones
without being seen by the audience.
On stage left is Inoo.
So we need to retrieve it there.
No one told me that.
So, in order to retrieve it...
I should go up too?
The lifter will go down to level zero.
So we'll have him climb on,
to give Kuramochi the microphone.
Okay, no problem.
We have an added step now.
I'm going to get on the lifter, which is
a platform that goes up and down,
and retrieve the microphones
from the members.
It's a new task.
Kuramochi is staring intently
at one member on stage.
It's Yuto Nakajima, who has
a challenging tap dance routine.
I'm going to attach a microphone
to Nakajima's tap shoes.
So the sound of the shoes
reach every corner of the arena,
he is attaching a small
microphone to the shoes.
SMALL MICROPHONE
It's my first time.
All right.
This part is iron,
so if the cable gets stuck here,
it will disconnect.
YUTO NAKAJIMA
Nakajima looks worried as well.
But when this...
But if it sags,
it might disconnect, and that's scary.
-Yeah, I understand.
-Thank you.
Will the tap shoes be ready in time?
Five more hours until the dress rehearsal.
But there's still
a lot of work left to do.
FIVE HOURS LEFT UNTIL DRESS REHEARSAL
I'll do that. You should go eat.
You'll die.
-You won't die?
-If I eat,
I'll get sleepy.
You get sleepy?
Kuramochi,
make sure to take your lunch break.
See, I told you.
We're all thinking the same thing.
I'll get lunch.
Okay.
In the meantime, Ueda,
from the stage facilitator team
was fighting against anxiety.
STAGE FACILITATOR
MASAHIRO UEDA (AGE 27)
He's worried about the movement
during the quick change.
Take this onto the stage
so that Takaki and Inoo
can get inside and change.
Just be careful when we take it down.
It'll either fall or stay up there.
Whatever is there after the ring drops,
I can pick up. So make sure
to have the ring set up.
Okay.
It's only been three months
since Ueda started this job.
But he can't slow everybody down.
I want to take the responsibility
I've been given
and complete it with a high level
of quality, without making any mistakes.
Eventually, I want to reach the top
and become a stage director.
The one that sends out
cues and things like that.
I hope I can gain more skills
to reach that level.
It's almost time for the dress rehearsal.
The members changed
into their costumes and started to check
the special effects equipment
called sparklers.
Please turn on the sparklers.
Get ready.
SPARKLER: SPECIAL EFFECT FIREWORKS
THAT ARE SAFE TO TOUCH
Wow it's not hot at all.
This will be shooting out the whole time.
Watching over the rehearsal
is Michiru Yabe from
the special effects team.
She has a strong determination
towards this job.
MICHIRU YABE
During junior high school and high school,
she dreamed of working
in the music industry,
but she realized her limitation,
and gave up that dream.
But...
HEY! SAY! JUMP JUMP NATIONWIDE TOUR 2013
She found her new dream
when her friend invited her
to a Hey! Say! JUMP concert.
She was instantly mesmerized
by the special effects.
But even after she started this job,
she experienced many setbacks.
In the beginning,
I didn't know anything.
I was constantly getting yelled at
and being scolded.
I was the type that gets depressed
when someone gets mad at me.
So I would hide in the bathroom
and cry by myself.
I felt like quitting.
Even now, I sometimes get the feeling
that this isn't the right job for me.
I can't help but feel like that sometimes.
The reason why she didn't give up
is that she wants to create
the same kind of stage
that gave her a new dream.
It's the reaction of the audience
when the special effects take place.
Special effects tend to get
all the attention.
When I help set it up
and see it take effect during
the actual performance,
I'm still really moved by
how amazing it is.
Individuals like her
help to create the concert.
Let's get ready to start.
The dress rehearsal.
Will these youths
be able to get through it?
It's 8 p.m.
Okay.
Center stage and below. Everyone except
the members must be on standby.
Thank you!
It's finally the dress rehearsal,
where they will conduct the final check.
Everyone on standby.
Underneath the stage, the members
and staff get into position.
Let's be safe and work hard.
Let's work hard.
Sound on.
DRESS REHEARSAL STARTS
Standby!
Go!
It's going to spin.
It's off to a good start.
The four youths are of one mind.
They want to provide a great concert
for the audience.
Whether things go well or not,
will all depend on the cooperation
between the teams.
The first challenge is the quick change.
Ueda from the facilitator team
gets ready with the props.
Kuramochi from the sound team
gets ready to receive
the members' microphones.
Kuramochi received the microphones
from the members.
Now, it's Ueda's turn.
Let's start changing!
The members' costumes and props
are thrown down one by one
into this small area.
As a safety precaution,
they must be retrieved right away.
Don't reach for it.
That's good.
Take it.
We're off the lifter.
Let's transfer this.
However...
Okay.
Time's up, so this is where we'll end.
Let's discuss the rest later on.
9 P.M. DRESS REHEARSAL ENDS
They run out of time,
so the dress rehearsal ends
without getting halfway through the show.
They suddenly decide to finish the rest
on the day of the concert.
SOUND
Kuramochi from the sound team
faces another challenge.
SOUND
TAKUMA KURAMOCHI (AGE 22)
I'm not sure, but he may have
stepped on the cable.
There was a problem,
and the cable disconnected.
I'll think of something else.
The cables on the tap shoes
were disconnected.
It's what he was afraid might happen.
He must think of a countermeasure
by tomorrow morning.
Let's start.
The managers of each team gather
in the meeting room
to discuss all the details.
For "Bubble Gum"?
I felt like the first part
was a little too cute.
This sound, right?
Yes, that sound.
And after that?
That won't change.
Just the first part.
This won't change.
If you can just use the part that goes,
"dan dara dara ra ran."
That's the part I want.
This part can stay the same.
-And the next part?
-Yes.
These small adjustments
have a big effect on the final outcome.
Tomorrow is the big day.
I feel like I could've done more.
But it's difficult.
MUSASHINO FOREST SPORTS PLAZA MAIN ARENA
The next day.
It's finally the day of the concert.
But they still have to finish
the dress rehearsal from the day before.
There are seven hours left
before the concert begins.
SOUND
Feeling more anxious than anybody else
was Kuramochi from the sound team.
The cable had disconnected...
SOUND
TAKUMA KURAMOCHI (AGE 22)
So I changed the way it attaches
onto the shoe.
Trouble occurred
when the small microphone
attached to the tap shoes
became disconnected.
He hopes to resolve the issue
by improving the way
it's taped to the sole.
As the camera was following Kuramochi,
Nakajima took notice.
We're used to having
cameras follow us around.
But I'm so glad to see this.
Because we're usually in the limelight.
I'm really glad that this provides
an opportunity for the viewers to see
all the people working hard
behind the scenes.
Thank you.
We have a great team here.
LATTER HALF OF THE DRESS REHEARSAL BEGINS
The latter half
of the dress rehearsal begins.
But below the stage...
There was an unexpected accident.
They can't find Chinen's microphone.
No microphone?
It was not where it should've been.
Inexperienced Ueda failed
to catch that mistake.
Bring it for him.
It's usually over there.
Sometimes the PA can't be here
to help with all that.
Okay.
I understand.
Be ready for the unexpected.
Not everything goes as planned.
What's important is having the strength
to cope with any situation.
Their last challenge is the mobile stage.
They make sure to synchronize the stage
with the members' movements.
Okay, now we're ready
for the actual performance.
END OF DRESS REHEARSAL
But there's much to do
before the concert begins.
The dress rehearsal brought out
some points for improvement,
so we will work on that.
SPECIAL EFFECTS
MICHIRU YABE (AGE 21)
I hope to do my very best
during the performance tonight.
After the doors open, we'll do
another wireless mic check,
and check with the musicians.
SOUND
TAKUMA KURAMOCHI (AGE 22)
We have a lot to do.
How much rice?
Not too much.
Less? Okay.
The staff members are enjoying
a meal before the concert begins,
and a nervous-looking Ueda
is one of them.
STAGE FACILITATOR
MASAHIRO UEDA (AGE 27)
-He's so nervous he's about to throw up.
-Really?
You're nervous?
Yes.
You're that nervous?
Are you okay?
-I'm okay. I'll do my best.
-Do your best.
Sometimes I forget how to do something,
even though I know how to do it.
Yes...
The venue is already surrounded by fans.
There's only one hour left
until the concert begins.
Thank you.
-Let's work hard.
-Hello.
The curtain is about to rise
for the first day of the concert.
Will these four youths be able to
make it through the entire concert?
Subtitle translation by Lili Morita