JULY 27TH ONE WEEK UNTIL
NATIONAL TOUR STARTS
Today, the three KAT-TUN members,
who have reunited after two years,
find themselves in an awkward position.
It's hard. Yeah, it's...
I don't know what we should do.
The throes of creation.
In order to create something new,
this time is necessary.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
2016 10TH ANNIVERSARY LIVE
TOKYO DOME
KAT-TUN debuted in 2006.
But members left one after another.
Two years ago,
after promising they would return,
they entered a recharging period.
We will prove to you that having this time
is needed to protect KAT-TUN.
We're counting on you until then.
Thank you very much.
The moment to fulfill
that promise they made
to fans all over the country
was approaching.
Even before we did the recharging,
I thought we could become
something fresh after a restart.
I had confidence.
Of course, I had worries,
but I also had confidence.
If we didn't do at least that,
I thought we wouldn't be able to
move this ship called KAT-TUN.
I want KAT-TUN
to be a ship that can fight.
And then the national tour started.
We documented the journey
of their return to the stage.
MAY 29TH
One month after their
return in Tokyo Dome...
Good work on your Tokyo Dome concerts.
The meetings for the new album, CAST,
and their first album tour
in four years started.
First, they need to decide
what the stage will look like.
I like the LEDs we've been using,
but they have been so widely used.
If we keep it like that,
it will become predictable.
I think it would be more interesting
if we added something more than LED.
Like, playing a clip of water falling down
on the LED screen,
and having real water running
from where the screen ends.
If we don't go that far,
and just use the latest technology,
I'll feel a little sad.
I'm really thankful.
And it's because of that...
But to be honest,
anybody could do it, if they had money.
So, I want to go with that idea.
So, for now the platforms...
Instead of platforms,
we'll use a moving stage and...
What they suggested was using rails
that move the members while they dance,
instead of platforms for the stage.
What are the benefits of the rails?
It's easier to use the platforms.
With the rails, we can be
moved while we dance.
We don't have to walk.
And then, Ueda...
There are times when we want to
walk on our own feet,
and move on our own...
without having to ride on something.
Because they are arenas,
I want to feel a sense of closeness
and make use of the space.
If they are on this or that side...
In their first meeting,
it was agreed that they will
be as close to the fans as possible.
Next, what should they sing?
It's been four years since KAT-TUN
has done a national tour.
Should they sing familiar songs
for the fans who've been waiting,
or perform new songs?
What do the members think
regarding that balance?
JUNE 13TH
I think we don't need to sing
every song from the album.
We always have to sing
all the songs on the album, right?
I think it's better to use more of
our singles and hit songs.
So, if you had ten
songs you would leave three out?
Well...
I'd leave half of them out.
Half?
But it is a tour for the album, after all.
That's right.
We need to do this properly
and show our fans new performances.
If we don't use at least half
of the new album,
those who bought it would be confused.
Half sounds good.
JULY 2ND 33 DAYS UNTIL NATIONAL TOUR
There's one month until the national tour.
This time, Kamenashi was thinking of doing
an experimental performance.
3RD BLOCK
That was his solo song, "One way love."
RECORDING OF KAMENASHI'S
SOLO SONG, "ONE WAY LOVE"
It's his first time singing
a song entirely in English.
It's about the delusional love
a man feels toward a woman.
One month before the recording,
he told the director what he
wanted to include in the song.
Sort of erotic?
Like when you're...
thinking of someone.
-They aren't dating?
-They aren't.
It's all in his imagination.
Like, "I want to do
this or that with you."
How is he going to express
those feelings on stage?
JULY 13TH
On this day, a dancer
was called to the studio.
Which way is it?
He is known worldwide
for his creative dancing,
Tomohiko Tsujimoto.
Kamenashi performed a unique
dance in a commercial.
Po!
The one who choreographed it
was Tsujimoto.
He also helped with
the production of his solo song.
Basically, it'll just be me.
I want to be alone
with just my imagination.
Without using props.
I think it would be good
to use the floor a lot.
Do something like that.
I think it would be good
to use your body to that extent.
It'll be a bit tough.
It'll be tough.
I will add some tough movements.
JULY 18TH
It's been five days, and
choreography rehearsal is starting.
You're so pale.
It shows how I can't fully enjoy summer.
-So pale.
-I can't enjoy the summer.
Express those feelings
that no one else understands.
Like, "What is he doing?"
Be vague, be vague.
Be more spontaneous.
He is going to perform this dance alone
on top of the wide stages of the arenas.
It hurts.
Meanwhile, Ueda's solo song...
He holds a sword
for this fighting performance.
And the back-up dancers...
We will go with this style.
They're dressed like revolutionaries.
The theme is about fighting hard.
There are many unreasonable things,
all kinds of things,
that we are always fighting against.
Right?
It doesn't only happen to entertainers,
but to others as well.
Aren't we always
fighting against something big?
I want to make that reach
the fans and the people listening.
And then, Nakamaru...
-Good morning.
NAKAMARU SOLO
How will he perform
the solo song he wrote himself?
The ideas he came up with each day
jumped out in rapid succession.
The camerawork on music shows
is complicated, right?
How about doing that at the concert?
I want to split the screen
and show it in an interesting way.
And the back-up dancers?
They will wear masks
and dance with them on.
Did we use a stroboscope somewhere before?
A see-through screen...
-Yes.
-Have we used that before?
How can he use something
new and interesting?
JULY 21ST 14 DAYS UNTIL THE NATIONAL TOUR
It's two weeks before the tour starts.
Almost all the elements
of the concerts are ready.
All that's left is to fine-tune
the details for the actual concerts.
Nakamaru makes a new
suggestion to the members.
Piano?
I'd like to talk about the piano.
The piano...
It is Ueda's strength,
and he has played it
at many concerts in the past.
Nakamaru wants him to play the piano
along with his beatboxing.
I'll do it if I have to,
but there's not much time left.
Really, I could only play the chorus.
Honestly, doing it perfectly
in only two weeks would be really hard.
That's why you don't need
to do the full song,
but you could mix in
some parts you are good at.
At this point Kamenashi says...
It's the same as before.
What if it wasn't...
We're always doing the same thing.
We have no new tricks.
How can they do something new?
it would be easy to do...
I have to think quickly
about what I can do.
JULY 28TH, 7 DAYS LEFT
One week later.
They decide that the song for the session
would be a ballad called "vivid LOVE".
Ueda starts practicing the piano.
Can he learn it in time?
And then Nakamaru
brought in a certain machine.
A loop machine.
With it, a recorded sound
can be played over and over again.
How will they use this
for their piano session?
We can play with the sound
and make it vanish...
and then go on.
We can play with it in a fluid way.
We will go, "pin pin"
and the piano will go, "jan jan."
But to Ueda, this idea...
Really?
We could go to "vivid LOVE" without
playing the piano part first.
The essence of the piano is lost.
If I play the piano
for five or ten seconds...
Ueda thinks that
the piano and loop machine
will drown each other out
if played at the same time.
But the piano part
doesn't need to be live.
The rehearsal has stopped.
It's hard. Yeah, it's...
I don't know
how we should use the piano.
Getting the piano out
just to play an easy phrase...
Showing the piano will
get the audience hyped for nothing.
Since I've played
difficult things in the past.
Ueda feels that at this time,
he can't do it and doesn't want to.
But I think it's
not about doing this or that.
So in that sense, this time...
First, we show that Ueda can play
the piano, so people think it's amazing,
then I sing, Nakamaru beatboxes,
and then the three of us do it together.
That image, if we can show it,
and make it the main subject,
I think we should do it as
many times as we need.
Shall we try it?
Will the composition change?
Definitely.
The contents...
Will it turn out okay?
The three started to move
to make the session happen.
-Did you get it?
-Yes.
They are testing what
the piano and loop machine
can do together.
Try adding beatboxing, for example.
How will it be if they add
someone's voice?
Meow.
They're exploring different methods.
Once we're done with this,
we can move here.
It's not necessary
to get the piano out for "vivid LOVE."
And then...
It flows better like that.
AUGUST 4TH MARINE MESSE FUKUOKA
Finally, it was the first day of the tour.
Fans arrive early
since it's the first show in four years.
Twenty minutes before showtime.
Backstage, we find Ueda
playing the piano until the last moment.
The concert will start soon.
It's the first day, so let's have fun.
It's KAT-TUN's first tour in four years.
We'll be at 23 more venues.
Let's do our best.
Let's go!
-Yes!
-Let's do it!
A new journey is starting for KAT-TUN.
The members
come down from the ceiling.
The solo songs.
And finally, the session
with the three together.
We've got a piano and some instruments
to use with the loop machine.
For a few months since their restart,
we have been following the three members.
They haven't spoken much.
Instead, they have expressed
themselves in front of the cameras.
Through filming, we learned that
being an entertainer
may seem glamorous at first,
but it is a harsh world
where professionals
must trust their feelings
and work hard.
AUGUST 29TH, NAGOYA
KAT-TUN's national tour
has arrived in the third city, Nagoya.
Kamenashi's routine is
to make a smoothie before a concert.
With a good tempo...
Would you like some?
Is that okay?
Thank you very much.
Did you experiment with this?
Not exactly.
It's very simple.
"Would you like some?"
Since this documentary started filming,
this was the first time
Kamenashi spoke to the director.
Let me film you drinking it.
Suddenly, a relaxed smile.
How has he been feeling
all this time during filming?
The national tour ended in November.
In the last interview, we asked about it.
Well, first of all,
because I am in the position
of being an idol,
I'm very much against
any project that shows everything.
Before going on the stage
or before going to work,
we need to prepare.
Those are not moments for people to see.
But we decided to do this project, so...
It would've been
different if I was smarter
and better at this kind of thing.
But for me, just because
there are cameras,
I don't think about being more fashionable
or making sure I'm shaved or anything.
It's not about that.
That wouldn't be a documentary.
I don't think...
it's good to expose everything,
but certainly
if my way of life was going
to be shown somehow,
well...
Situations that need to be exposed,
situations that should be exposed,
need to be shown openly.
-Thank you for this year.
-My pleasure.
Be kind when you edit this.
I haven't behaved TV-like at all.
Was it okay?
Yes.
It's because he can be very honest.
Yuichi Nakamaru.
Tatsuya Ueda.
Kazuya Kamenashi.
We are...
KAT-TUN!
Their journey continues.
On the next Ride On Time is NEWS.
Like this...
The members have expanded their
playing field to other genres.
Okay.
In the 15 years since their debut,
they've faced many trials.
SELF RESTRAINT
"Is it all right to be an idol?"
I was really worried then.
I thought I had to quit.
It's for the fans who've been waiting.
Each one of us is needed.
Unless the four of us are together,
we can't get over this wall.
NEWS, 15th Anniversary Since Formation:
Let's Live.
Subtitle translation by Jordan Woodard