April 20th. Tokyo Dome.
Let's set sail!
After two years, they've come back.
Today, we are completely finished
with the recharging period!
The return of KAT-TUN.
Originally,
they started as a group of six,
but went through difficult times,
and are now three.
They stand onstage carrying
many feelings in their hearts.
YUICHI NAKAMARU (AGE 35)
All three members are necessary,
and I think the moment that changes,
we won't be KAT-TUN.
After all the difficult things
we went through,
I want the three of us to
find happiness together.
It's a way to show my resolve
to the members who left.
And I guess we also have our pride.
And the fans.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
The concerts for KAT-TUN's return
lasted for three days at Tokyo Dome.
The title represents
the unity of the three of them.
It's called UNION.
-Good morning.
APRIL 22ND BEFORE THE CONCERT
A meeting is held backstage.
While discussing what concept
they should use for the new album,
the topic changes to
the new direction KAT-TUN should take.
I feel like we can finally put an end
to the kinds of messages
we used for these concerts.
Like the logo we are using.
In the past years,
we have been losing members,
so a lot of the themes have been linked
to how we felt at the time.
I want to leap ahead
and have a more creative start
to go to the next level.
Rather, if we don't
go to the next level,
it'll be a problem.
Especially after this concert.
Aren't these concerts like that?
We are always saying,
"Let's laugh and move on."
Since it's like that,
I think it'd be cool to
take a step forward.
So we will be properly
connected to the audience.
We follow their daily lives.
APRIL 5TH CHOFU, TOKYO
Good morning.
On the same day as the rehearsal
for the concerts,
Kamenashi goes to film a commercial.
FILMING OF COMMERCIAL
"HOKEN MINAOSHI HONPO"
He will take on something
he has little experience with,
contemporary dance.
Good morning.
Thirty seconds...
The one in charge of the choreography
is world-famous dancer,
Tomohiko Tsujimoto.
He is the first Japanese male dancer
to have worked in Cirque du Soleil.
After I learn this today,
I'm going to forget all the concert
choreography from up until yesterday.
Let's do our best.
They only have an hour
and a half to practice.
One, two, three,
four, foot.
Elbow.
Front. One, two,
three, po.
One, two, three, po.
This requires different muscles.
These movements are completely different
from how he normally dances.
Turn and left foot.
The left one.
-I can't.
-Your left leg.
How can you all stand still?
We'll get on our shoulder.
-On the shoulder?
-Yes.
Yes, like that.
Like that, turn your right leg
and put your left hand
on the floor and use it
to lift your body up.
Like this...
-Each step is becoming harder and harder.
-And po.
I'm lost.
It's important for Kamenashi
to express himself using only his body.
Now salsa. One, two,
Salsa. One, two, three.
The real take. Will he be able
to meet their expectations?
Ready... start.
Po!
Okay, cut!
When I saw my hand, it was too late.
Okay, let me try again.
If I could do it again...
Ready...
Start!
Po!
It's like my leg wouldn't lift up.
And then...
-Like this, right?
-Yes.
I can't lift it from here.
1 HOUR AND 30 MINUTES
SINCE START OF THE TAKE
I can't stand firm.
-Your legs are tired?
-My legs are tired.
I can't hold it.
Now, I want to work harder
to increase the quality.
I want to stay perfectly still.
Po!
Wait! My leg...
It's not responding.
It's swollen.
He joined the agency at the age of 12.
It's been 20 years.
He is going to meet
everyone's expectations.
That is the path he has chosen.
Contemporary dance is amazing.
Let's go.
I'm a contemporary dancer.
Po!
Cut!
He's danced for three hours.
He's met their expectations.
KAT-TUN members are troublemakers.
No way.
Troublemakers.
Is that why we lost three members?
But I think it's good.
-That's true.
-It was your destiny.
I really think so.
Once you turn 30,
you realize everybody is different.
That's how it is.
It's amazing that you're doing
the Dome with three people.
It must be tough.
I'm thankful.
It's amazing.
The three of us can perform at the Dome
thanks to the fans.
Of course.
That's why they have to do
something only the three of them can do.
TATSUYA UEDA (AGE 35)
APRIL 17TH FILMING OF VS ARASHI
On the other hand, Ueda
appeared on a popular program
that makes you use your body.
Start!
Ueda is known for being an idol
with a lot of athletic ability.
Ten seconds have passed!
He is also able to run
400 meters in 50 seconds.
Even athlete Sou Takei,
was also surprised.
Your physical ability is pretty good.
There aren't many ordinary people
who can do that.
It's because he hates losing,
that he developed these abilities.
I don't know, but with Johnny's idols,
they are very popular from
the beginning, right?
While their own abilities
are still insufficient,
they have a huge fan base.
During the process of growing up,
they try to live up to
the expectations of those fans.
They acquire different abilities
and expand into different fields.
For Ueda, it's his physique.
He moves more than anybody else.
To find his very own weapon
he is working hard, training every day.
He also texts me sometimes
asking me to go running with him.
-Really?
-Yeah.
He is a very greedy man.
There is something that Ueda
has been devoting himself to
ever since his debut.
That thing is boxing.
He once aimed to be a professional.
He didn't, due to everyone's objection,
but that's how obsessed he was.
The sound of the sandbag
when you punch it, is something
that I really love.
It's like the accomplished feeling you get
after you give your all for something.
I think I like that.
It's similar to concerts.
I'm very sensitive to the voices
of the fans in the audience.
I can sense their mood for that day,
like if they're a calm crowd.
So, when we raise the curtain
and I hear them scream,
I'm happy and think, "Today feels good."
He started boxing right after his debut.
With all the disputes they had,
Ueda was always fighting.
The outlet for his irritation was boxing.
Okay.
This is very hard.
Today's sparring partner is a boy
who is aiming to be a professional.
He devotes himself to it
to feel a sense of accomplishment.
That has become his support
to stand onstage
as an idol.
That's enough!
Good job!
Yes, when I feel like that...
In the past,
when I was a member of Johnny's Jr.,
I was short-tempered,
and I was always fighting.
If I didn't have this, the stress
of work and everything else...
It's because I have boxing
that I can find that compromise.
I've been boxing for more than ten years.
Without this, I probably
would've become a bad adult.
Fifty is enough. Fifty times.
...eight, nine, ten...
One, two, three, four, five...
Thirty. One, two, three...
On this day, Nakamaru goes to
a company in the metropolitan area.
How long has it been?
About half a year.
YUICHI NAKAMURA (AGE 35)
Someone he wants to see is here.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-It's been a while.
-Nice to see you.
He is game designer Hideo Kojima.
HIDEO KOJIMA GAME DESIGNER
He's created games like
the Metal Gear series.
Now, he is a man who is respected
by creators from all over the world.
THE AMERICAN ASSOCIATION
OF PRODUCERS CHOSE HIM
AS ONE OF THE MOST INNOVATIVE CREATORS
AND PRODUCERS IN THE WORLD (2006)
This is the trailer of his latest
project that hasn't been released yet.
They met eight years ago
and connected immediately.
Nakamaru is inspired by
Kojima's attitude towards creating things.
-On the PlayStation engine...
-Wow.
On that day, they were checking
the CGI effects used on humans.
This is the motion capture.
We draw dots and...
While using the latest technology
there are some things
they can only get
from real human beings
to get a sense of reality.
CG CHARACTER MODELED AFTER AN ACTOR
And that way of thinking
has had a big influence on Nakamaru.
While he's here...
How interesting...
Amazing.
It's amazing. I can feel the combination
of technology and human beings.
Thank you for this experience.
You can be a cameo.
Feel free to use it.
I can be an extra.
We don't have data
of your facial expressions...
They decided to have dinner together.
Places like these are the best
to study Kojima's way of thinking.
Kojima's attitude
towards creating things
and his way of thinking is something...
I'm always trying to imitate...
Always.
-I thought I'd put it out there.
-Thank you.
When was it?
I think it was because I saw
the making of a video game.
That really influenced me a lot.
They finished it,
or so I thought.
But after that, you continued
to work on it for several weeks.
You said it was very
important for the quality.
-That's amazing.
-How much time was left?
Yes.
How that time could determine if it is
a bad or good game.
I don't mean to compare it literally,
but for concerts,
until the end of the production,
depending on how much
energy you put into it,
it could be a good or bad concert.
Kojima's words always
come to mind, and I think,
"Ah, I have to work hard."
To create something good,
don't you use your instinct?
Even if it worked before,
if you feel hesitant,
you should trust that feeling
even if it's just you.
Of course, you might be wrong,
but whether you think that or not,
will change everything.
Entertainment isn't a necessity, you know?
If you don't have great dedication,
it's impossible.
"Why is he so passionate?"
"Why is he saying that?"
Even if they don't understand
at that time, when you work together,
they will know it eventually.
That's how one creates things.
What's important is to keep thinking
until the very end.
Ready... start.
June.
TOKYO, JUNE
FILMING OF THE MUSIC VIDEO FOR "KUN"
While making KAT-TUN's new album,
the three of them were in a hurry
to film the music video.
On top of that,
Nakamaru had a deadline coming soon.
Okay. Cut.
-Okay.
-Cut.
Have you finished your lyrics?
No. As expected, I haven't.
As expected...
I have them with me.
They're due today.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
-Really?
I've only completed like 6,5%.
Oh, man.
He still hasn't written the lyrics
for his solo song.
Where do you work?
In the car.
Can we film it for a bit?
Yes, but it's not finished at all.
LYRICS
What is the theme?
About love.
A boy and a girl love each other
but for some reason,
they can't get together.
I'm not progressing at all.
It's like, I wonder
if something is good...
I go forward two lines and then back two,
so I make no progress.
I thought it would be
better to write it myself.
I think the fans will
pay more attention to it
if I do it.
That's why I'm writing it.
-Good work.
-Thanks.
What's important is to think
about it until the very end.
At the same time...
Kamenashi was playing
the lead role in a drama
while he was still working on the album.
TEGAMI BY KEIGO HIGASHINO
The original work is a masterpiece
adapted for movies and stage plays.
He plays an earnest young man named Naoki,
who faces discrimination and prejudice
after being identified
as a murderer's brother.
I'd like to light some incense.
It's one heavy scene after another.
MAY 25TH
He is in the midst of filming.
Is my schedule out?
Tomorrow's?
For the album,
there's one song that he hasn't received.
With the Hanshin players...
Hanshin will be in Koshien tomorrow.
What song is included?
"Unstoppable"
is an option.
-The PV filming is on the second, right?
-Yes.
If we have to film it,
learn the dance, and record it,
why don't I have the song yet?
He is doing various jobs at the same time
and he is in a position where
he has to meet expectations.
We tried to ask him about that.
Kamenashi, a lot of genres―
Not right now.
Ah, sorry.
I need to focus on the lines.
He is focused
on the work before him.
MAY 31ST
It's the final day
of filming for Kamenashi.
It's the scene where he faces
his older brother, who is a murderer.
He's very focused.
-Okay, we are starting.
-Okay.
Ready... action.
You can go.
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry.
Don't just say sorry!
Answer me!
Why did you do something so stupid?
Stop!
The filming has finished.
The last lines were difficult.
He is still immersed in his character.
Tomorrow, he will start recording.
On the next Ride On Time,
KAT-TUN will prepare for
their first national tour in four years.
We need to properly tackle something new.
How will the three of them
face the new stage?
We'll also see the difficulty
they faced before the first concert.
It's hard. I don't know what we should do.
What happened?
We'll finish watching
their 300 hectic days.
Subtitle translation by Jordan Woodard