"This is a record of youths
who devoted their adolescence
to entertainment."
This place is amazing.
SHO HIRANO (AGE 21)
Nagoya!
Sho Hirano of King & Prince.
What are his undisclosed thoughts?
I wanted to quit.
I wanted to just quit and go away.
But thankfully,
the agency convinced me to stay.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
With much anticipation,
King & Prince sailed out into the world.
It's a new experience,
so it's nerve-wracking.
We've never done anything like this.
The six of them were faced
with large obstacles.
YUTA KISHI (AGE 23)
The leader,
Yuta Kishi's bitter experience.
I don't think I've ever been that shocked.
I was speechless.
KAITO TAKAHASHI (AGE 19)
The fear that Takahashi felt.
Every day, I would go home and cry.
And after the concerts, I would cry.
GENKI IWAHASHI (AGE 21)
The reality Iwahashi had to face.
The life that we led as Johnny's Jr.
is completely different
from the world we're in now.
YUTA JINGUJI (AGE 20)
The days of despair Jinguji had to endure.
It was really disheartening.
I went from being the center of attention,
to suddenly hitting rock bottom.
REN NAGASE (AGE 19)
The unforgettable past that haunts Nagase.
I was really thinking of quitting
at 20 or 21.
I didn't like dancing in front of people.
With each of them
carrying their own convictions,
they take a step forward.
-Good morning.
King & Prince's leader, Yuta Kishi.
NISEKOI PHOTO SHOOT
SEIJO, TOKYO
This day, he had a poster photo shoot
for a film set to release in December.
I'd like one shot with you full of energy.
Ready...
The film he is in is set in a school.
He's playing a comic relief role.
Can you do a funny face?
Go all out.
Yes, that kind of face. Perfect.
His facial expressions change rapidly
according to the staff's requests.
He's excellent.
It hasn't been long since his debut,
and he's willing to do everything he can.
You were number one on the Oricon Charts.
-That's right. Thank you.
-Congratulations.
-That's an amazing feat.
-We are number one on the charts.
Congratulations on debuting.
It's precisely why they will expect
all the more from him during this film.
If it's for this role, I will do anything.
That's how determined I am.
Doing a funny face means nothing to me.
When distorting your face,
you go from one to one hundred.
Once you go to a hundred,
you can always subtract from there.
I feel like you don't know very much
until you go all the way to one hundred.
NISEKOI MOVIE FILMING
MISHIMA, SHIZUOKA
He stays true to his words
even on the set.
Just think of anything.
In this scene before the festival...
Give me ideas.
I'm dying to do Romeo and Juliet!
What about everybody?
Kishi did not experience
this kind of youth himself.
I didn't go to a regular school.
It was a correspondence school.
So I didn't really have
a typical experience as a youth.
I guess I'm experiencing it now.
Although, I'm already 22.
What is adolescence, anyway?
The reason Kishi entered this business
was because his aunt
sent in his application.
Studying was always
my worst enemy.
I thought I'd take a chance
instead of getting a regular job.
I took a gamble.
That was when he was thirteen,
in his second year of junior high.
This is where I had my first audition.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
It still makes me nervous
when I come here.
Right here in this room,
there were so many people.
Where was I, again?
I think I was somewhere around here.
McDonald's... We were served McDonald's.
I think Mr. Johnny orders it each time,
but to me, McDonald's
never tasted so special.
From there, Kishi continued
to take lessons as a Johnny's Jr. member
in hopes of debuting.
But the existence of one man
led him to suffer a major setback.
That man is Shori Sato, from Sexy Zone.
Sato joined one year later than Kishi,
but he quickly made his debut at age 15.
Being a backup dancer
for someone one year his junior
was a bitter experience
he cannot forget even now.
I was a complete mess.
I really was.
I lost my motivation to work.
I couldn't understand why
I had to do certain things.
Personally, I thought that
I slowly made my way up to the point
where I was worthy of holding a mic.
But the moment he joined,
he rose up so quickly
and surpassed me and others.
I was speechless.
Debuting seemed
unrealistic to me at times.
I used to think that way back then.
That bitter experience
is what fuels him now.
On this day, another member was shooting
for a film set to be released next year.
MOVIE FILMING
NERIMA, TOKYO
In a way, Ren Nagase has also used
his trials as stepping stones.
You came all the way here,
but it's raining.
-Either way, we'll be indoors.
-That's true.
That's embarrassing.
Jinguji also has a role in the film,
as Nagase's best friend.
They are members of the same group,
but they barely speak to each other
in between each scene.
Is there an unspoken rule
that you can't chat?
I don't want others to feel excluded,
so I was planning to keep
my distance from him.
I guess people in Johnny's
have always done it this way.
When different Johnny's
would be on the same set,
they would be careful
not to come across as a clique.
That's what I've heard.
That's not a problem.
What is Nagase's trial?
He mentioned it
while talking with the director.
You said you don't cry, right?
I never really cry.
It takes a lot to make me cry.
I only cry when I yawn.
I was watching a movie with my friends
and I asked them if they cried afterward.
They said yes and asked me if I did,
and I said no.
They told me, "you're not human."
I'm told that pretty often.
His inability to cry
may have something to do with
the environment in which he grew up.
Nagase's family was constantly
moving because of work.
Every time he made new friends,
he would have to say goodbye.
After a while,
he began to build up emotional walls.
I'm naturally very shy.
Because of my family's work situation,
I've moved to so many places.
About five or six cities.
Because I transferred schools
so many times
and had to make new friends each time,
I became very shy.
As a kid, I didn't talk at all.
I was naturally a gloomy kid.
But Johnny's helped in changing
my personality.
He joined Johnny & Associates, Inc. when
he was in his first year of junior high.
There, he found peers
who had the same goals as him.
Along with his peers,
he immersed himself in the lessons
and in time,
his trials turned into his strengths.
Saying that I was reborn
may be an exaggeration,
but that's how much I've changed.
I enjoy hanging out with people,
eating out with people,
and talking to people.
That is how
I improved my communication skills.
I changed a lot.
More than anything else,
he is grateful that he has friends
he can walk shoulder to shoulder with.
One of those friends is Jinguji.
He was on his way
to shoot a difficult scene.
He says it's a critical scene
at the climax of the film.
Cut.
Okay. Let's take that again.
It's a long take that lasts
for ten minutes.
He continues to consult with the director
on how to portray the emotions.
DIRECTOR, SHINJI KUMA
However...
Cut. Let's retake that.
Cut. We'll retake that, sorry.
Cut.
Okay.
Was it good?
The first half was good.
They have taken approximately
ten retakes of this scene.
By the time the director
gave his approval,
two hours had already passed.
Cut. That's good.
Okay.
He is exhausted.
That was the longest line
I've said in my life.
I'm exhausted right now,
but it was fun at the same time.
It's fun. I'll go enjoy myself.
The reason why Jinguji can persevere
is because his bitter experiences
make him stronger.
Jinguji has always admired idols
since he was a young boy,
and in his first year of junior high,
he submitted his application himself.
MYOJO LIVE! 2015 SUMMER CONCERT ISSUE
And in 2015,
the current members were elected
from among the Johnny's Jr.
to create a unit and perform
under the name Mr. King vs. Mr. Prince.
MYOJO LIVE! 2017 SPRING CONCERT ISSUE
The following year,
the six of them were divided
into separate units.
However, the spotlight
always seemed to shine
on Mr. King only.
Prince would go through a time
where they wouldn't get any job offers,
leaving them feeling
frustrated and jealous.
That was really shocking for me.
I was 18 at the time.
That was the toughest time of my life.
When we didn't get offers.
I was in my third year of high school,
and I had to think about college.
If I'm not going to get any work...
If there's no work coming in
even though I'm willing,
I thought for a second,
that maybe I should quit.
I feel like I became...
one step closer to being an adult
from going through all those emotions
during that time.
But because we went through all of that,
because we hit rock bottom,
we realized that nothing could
bring us down any further.
There's nothing to fear,
so we decided to do all that we can
from now on.
There is a place where Jinguji
goes for emotional support.
I've been here so many times.
TOYOKAWA INARI TOKYO BETSUIN
MOTOAKASAKA, TOKYO
Toyokawa Inari is well known
in the entertainment world.
JOHNNY & ASSOCIATES, INC.
I like the atmosphere here.
You don't feel like you're in Akasaka,
even though you are.
It's Inarin.
-Someone wrote King & Prince.
-Really?
"May their debut single,
'Cinderella Girl,' sell a million copies.
I pray for their five-dome tour
to be a success. Congratulations."
The date is the day you debuted.
What? You're right!
Wow.
That makes me happy.
I'm honored.
ACCORDING TO OUR BUTLER FILMING
NERIMA, TOKYO
Meanwhile, Nagase,
the one who cannot cry...
The film is almost about to wrap up.
Cut.
-Are we good?
-Yes.
That means...
That's a wrap.
Yes!
In his eyes...
I am sure my lack of experience
has caused all of you a lot of trouble.
Thank you so much for the past month.
And that wasn't all.
-Thank you.
-Good job.
What? Why?
I came from Chiba.
Just for this?
-Thank you.
-Good work.
It's hot in here. I'm so hot.
That's it for today.
Thank you for your work.
The man who could not cry
is covered in tears.
Hello?
Words from his co-stars.
What are you doing?
This emotion I'm feeling
is completely new to me.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
A brand-new Ren Nagase?
-Good luck on your shoot too.
-Thanks.
It's raining.
Come on, days like this call for sunshine!
Come out, sun!
After the commercial,
we'll learn of another member's struggles.
You're lying!
WEEKLY GIANTS MAGAZINE INTERVIEW
KANDA, TOKYO
This day, we found one member
at a certain sporting goods store.
-Is this chair for sale too?
-No, it's not.
Genki Iwahashi.
As a Johnny's Jr. member,
he came in first place on the
"list of men you want as a boyfriend"
for five years straight.
Despite his androgynous looks,
he is actually a huge baseball fan.
I played every day.
I was either on the field or at the salon.
That was my life.
Iwahashi has his own series
published in a baseball magazine
and was here for an interview.
The things he asks about are so technical.
Regular people don't really
think about that.
He will try out a new item
before it hits the market.
This ball has a built-in sensor.
I see.
As soon as it is thrown,
it sends the ball's speed
and spin rate to your smartphone.
-According to these numbers...
-By the way,
how fast was your self-proclaimed
ball speed?
Self-proclaimed?
One hundred kilometers per hour.
I want to pass the 120 kph mark.
Here I go.
This challenge would show us
how Iwahashi has surprisingly
strong determination.
That was 97 kph and 1,350 rpm.
That was 115 and 1,562.
It was 115?
I'm only 5 kilometers from 120.
Good catch.
That's 117.
One hundred and seventeen?
Just three more kilometers.
Okay.
Wow!
That was 117.
That's 119.
You should take a photo.
Record the data.
One hundred and nineteen!
-I'll take it when I hit 120.
-Wait, wait.
Should I?
Should I throw the ball lower or higher
to get a faster speed?
-Lower is better.
-Can you sit for me?
Of course.
That was 119.
Does it even go up to 120?
-How long can I stay here?
-How long?
Ask them.
-No time limit?
-No.
He never gives up.
One less!
That was 119.
You're lying!
I bet it only goes up to 119!
And on his 58th pitch.
You did it! It was 120!
Look at that!
Thank you.
He did indeed pass the 120 kph mark.
Were you really going
to keep throwing until you hit 120
as long as you had time?
Of course.
This is going to air on TV, right?
I'd be portrayed as the guy
who gave up at 119.
That's unacceptable.
I don't want to settle.
Once you settle, that's the end.
That goes for King & Prince too.
His motivation to work hard
also comes from an inner struggle.
Suddenly, he begins to talk about
his complicated feelings
toward the other members.
Because there are
six of us in King & Prince,
I feel like it's important
to keep a good balance.
So many of the members are working hard
in different fields.
Right now, it's not my time to shine,
but I think that supporting those members
and helping them shine even brighter
is my duty as a fellow member
and my personal role.
No matter what people might say,
even if they call me a loser,
I want to follow the path
that I believe in.
And as I'm saying this,
we're still inside the shop.
"Right now, it's not my time to shine.
It's time to make
the other members shine."
As someone who gained tremendous
popularity as a Johnny's Jr. member,
Iwahashi seems to be suppressing something
deep inside of him.
Next time,
that something begins to surface.
Listen to what I'm saying.
What happened to Iwahashi?
Can't you see?
On the next Ride On Time...
Cut it out.
We see the members clash
for the first time.
If you can't take it seriously, just quit.
It may be destiny.
A brief moment of relaxation.
Their big performance
is now just around the corner.
Can the six of them restore their bond?
There are so many noises reverberating.
I'm completely fine.
I suddenly became so hungry.
Bye.
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita