Aspiring idols dream of performing
at a dome concert.
Believe it or not,
a newly formed idol unit
are about to be performing at one.
It's a good kind of nervous.
SHUNSUKE MICHIEDA (AGE 16)
It's unpredictable.
What will be the outcome?
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Hello, we're Kansai Johnny's Jr.
Let's have some fun!
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR.
They are all the rage in Osaka right now,
Kansai Johnny's Jr.
They have the power to sell out theaters
that seat thousands for consecutive days.
From Osaka, they're working
to become known nationwide.
Are you having fun?
Make some noise!
KANSAI WALKER PHOTO SHOOT
Last year,
for the first time in four years,
a new unit was formed within
Kansai Johnny's Jr.,
called Naniwa Danshi.
NANIWA DANSHI
Quietly reaffirming his determination
to become known nationwide...
is the frontman, Daigo Nishihata.
DAIGO NISHIHATA (AGE 22)
Compared to Johnny's Jr. members in Tokyo,
we may not get as many jobs...
or have as many facilities available,
but I never want to say that we didn't get
a chance just because we're in Kansai.
Those sentiments are shared by all
of the Kansai Johnny's Jr. members.
From elementary school kids
to youths in their 20s,
there are more than 50 members.
Singing and dancing
are not all they have going for them.
Some dedicate themselves
to playing instruments...
and others to comedy.
Hello! I am Mr. Windshield Wipers.
I will wipe your heart.
They also have reliable helpers.
Kanjani∞ members Tadayoshi Ohkura...
and You Yokoyama
have volunteered to support them.
YOU YOKOYAMA
I am really impressed by their enthusiasm.
Seeing them giving it their all
and working so hard at it
touches my heart.
It motivates us too.
Thank you.
Their seniors have given them
the ultimate gift.
That gift is the chance to stand
on the dome stage of their dreams.
NOVEMBER 2018
KYOCERA DOME OSAKA
Last November,
Kanjani∞ performed at this dome
for two consecutive days.
There, Naniwa Danshi performed one song.
A few other
Kansai Johnny's Jr. members also got
the opportunity to stand on stage
as backup dancers.
The Kansai Johnny's Jr. members
have arrived.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
It's almost rehearsal time.
The members have changed clothes.
Even the somewhat experienced
frontman of Naniwa Danshi, Nishihata,
and the eldest member, Joichiro Fujiwara,
can't hold in their excitement.
The screens are the members' colors.
Take a look at that.
The band introduction
was replaced by "Naniwa Lucky Boy!!"
You're right.
A pre-existing time-slot
was cut out of the program
to fit in the Naniwa Danshi song,
"Naniwa Lucky Boy!!"
It was replaced with "Naniwa Lucky Boy!!"
They have a huge responsibility...
I see...
Let's do our best.
I am so excited,
that it's made a full circle.
I don't even know what's going on.
Wake up.
KAZUYA OHASHI (AGE 21)
Ohashi, who leads Naniwa Danshi
with his countertenor voice,
is the carefree type.
I will explain the general flow of things.
Okay.
This is how it looks?
It's time to go on stage.
Good morning.
It's huge!
-Wow!
-Good morning.
As the Naniwa Danshi members
stand on stage,
they are about to receive
an even bigger surprise.
Wow.
After that...
The large screen behind them
shows each member's face
along with their individual names.
Okay, that's set.
Now, onto the next position.
This has also been arranged
by their seniors.
Yes, look at the numbers.
Their original song,
"Naniwa Lucky Boy!!"
They've performed in theaters
that seat thousands of people many times,
but they still don't have the skills
to sell themselves to 45,000 people.
Okay, try it.
Yes.
Based off of his own experiences,
Ohkura gives them tips
on where they should stand
and where to look.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Having gone down the same road,
he shares the way he feels.
Because they already have
so much potential at this point,
I am very excited to see what kind of
people they will become.
That's why I want people to witness this.
That's how I feel.
It's so spacious, I was overwhelmed.
It's made me want to work harder.
Since we've been given this opportunity,
we must seize it.
This is a chance for us to mature,
so I'll do my best.
Every single thing they experience
fuels their ambition to get to the top.
I want to eat everything.
Even the catering menu
is more elaborate than usual.
I always take too much
in these situations.
RYUSEI ONISHI (AGE 17)
-I want to try it all.
-Yeah.
The more they experience,
the stronger their desire becomes to be
known in Tokyo and around the nation.
One member looks up
something on his phone...
Oh, no! What happened to you?
"The pros and cons of living in Tokyo."
-Hey!
-Seriously?
What in the world!
You're going to Tokyo?
They've also been told that
they'll be interviewed on a talk show.
Okay.
Thank you.
Things are moving so fast.
DAIGO NISHIHATA (AGE 22)
I am constantly surprised.
We've never been on a talk show before.
Ohkura taught us three lessons of sorts.
First, have fun.
This is a chance for Naniwa Danshi
to perform a song,
so we have to have fun.
Second,
don't forget the view.
We must not forget how the audience
reacts to us when we perform
in this Kyocera Dome.
And lastly,
come back here with our own strength.
We can't always be relying on others.
I want to show everyone
that there are still
fresh faces in Kansai.
That's my goal.
A member with similar sentiments
as Nishihata
is watching the rehearsal by himself.
JOICHIRO FUJIWARA (AGE 23)
Naniwa Danshi's gray eminence,
Joichiro Fujiwara.
Unless you sit here, you don't know
what the audience is seeing.
If you just look forward while dancing,
the people on the third floor
can only see your head.
Just by lifting your head,
they can see your face.
Things like this, I learned from Kanjani∞.
When we're in these domes,
instead of just waving at the top floors,
we should look at each of their faces,
or else our feelings won't reach them.
They taught me that.
Fujiwara joined the agency
when he was eight years old.
Even after entering college,
he couldn't find his breakthrough,
and thought about
quitting his idol career.
The first, second,
and third years of college, I thought
about getting a job.
I even attended the job fairs,
but then the people
from the companies asked me
what I wanted to do.
I said I wanted to talk.
They said, "How about sales?"
but that wasn't really
what I wanted to do.
You know,
I feel the most alive when
I'm talking in front of a large audience.
So...
in the end, this is the job for me.
It is my vocation,
but it's scary.
It's so scary.
Because, my whole life is at stake.
It's the gamble of all gambles.
When the members who were in college
would go out to eat,
that's all we would talk about.
From now on,
every day will be a challenge.
The concert is about to begin.
Good morning.
Here's a gift.
The other Kansai Johnny's Jr. members
and little children
have come for moral support.
-Oh, wow.
-Amazing.
Wow.
It's pink.
It's finally showtime.
We're ready.
Without hesitation...
Just being themselves...
We'll be in your care.
Here we go.
They are urged by their seniors
to move backstage.
-Please have fun.
-Yes!
Treasure each moment.
Thank you!
Here we go!
Their seniors have taken the stage.
Amazing.
The voices are so loud.
How cool.
I'm nervous. I can't stay still.
It's our seniors' stage,
so we can't mess up.
I'm scared right now.
It's almost their turn.
It's Kanjani∞ after all,
so the crowd is revved up.
And we're going to jump in there.
Let's not stop this wave,
let's ride this wave.
Let's promote Naniwa!
Let's become popular!
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
And now, for the first time in four years,
a new unit has been born in Kansai.
Please give them a warm welcome.
Let's go, Naniwa Danshi.
The seven of us are Naniwa Danshi.
To all of you Eighters...
thank you for your precious time!
We did it!
We were fresh.
It was so fun.
There was so much more to see than usual.
The cheering too...
The moment they said Naniwa Danshi,
the crowd cheered for us,
so it was easy to do and fun.
I was so nervous.
What was the stage of their dreams like?
DAIGO NISHIHATA (AGE 22)
We only sang and danced to one song,
but I was so nervous,
my heart was beating so fast that
I think it'll be sore tomorrow.
I never imagined the crowd would
cheer for us like that.
I couldn't hide my surprise.
Before I knew it, I was laughing out loud.
I purposely had my in-ear monitors off.
I had it off my ear.
When they said, "Naniwa Danshi"
and the crowd screamed,
I felt reassured and put it on
and sang, "Hey guys!"
I got a little teary-eyed at that moment,
and I felt more determined to work harder.
Next time, they will come back here
with their own strength.
That is what they promised their seniors,
who gave them the best gift.
Late-November.
Since witnessing the excitement
of a dome concert,
the Kansai Johnny's Jr. members have been
exerting themselves even more
in their rehearsals for
the end-of-year performances.
Among them, a group of five junior high
boys aiming to be the next unit
have especially become self-aware.
For now, their goal is to become
like Naniwa Danshi.
Those members are such
a big influence. They're our rivals.
I want to catch up.
They're much older than us,
but they're shining.
They're the classic idol types.
Today, they're participating in this.
It's their first time filming
a TV show together.
It's a special end-of-year show
where comedians and athletes
run in a long-distance ekiden relay race.
They are from Kansai Johnny's Jr.
It's a pleasure to be here.
What's your goal for
your first Kansai Ekiden?
Since we're representing Johnny's,
we're here to win.
We'll try to leave claw marks.
Claw marks, you say?
Whether it's breaking a record
or making a funny comment,
they want to produce some kind of result,
so that they are invited back again.
If we use our youth
to beat those old guys,
it will make for
an interesting show, right?
-We'll overthrow them.
-That's right.
We'll start in one minute!
The first runner is Takuya Nishimura.
Will these five
be able to produce results?
-Ready...
-All right!
-Let's go.
-Set...
All right.
He is off to a good start.
However, his opponents are adults,
and some are even athletes.
He is trailing behind.
-Seriously?
-This is bad.
So, um...
Nishimura is the seventh
out of eight teams to pass the cord.
1ST LEG, TAKUYA NISHIMURA
2ND LEG, KOTARO OKAZAKI
Kotaro!
You can do it!
Do your best, Kotaro!
Although they're being cheered on,
the other members can't
close the distance.
3RD LEG, FUGA ONISHI
I'm exhausted.
4TH LEG, TOA SHIMASAKI
LAST LEG, RUKU TOMA
By the time the last runner starts,
they are one lap behind.
7TH of 8 TO THE GOAL
They were utterly defeated.
It was harder than I thought.
How frustrating.
So frustrating.
Happy New Year, everyone!
In the end, they couldn't even
make a memorable comment.
Did you leave claw marks?
-Not at all.
-I have regrets.
-Not even a scratch.
-We didn't.
They left a scar on us.
The person from Shochiku Geino
was so amazing.
The way he helped facilitate
the conversation was amazing.
Everyone got a chance in the spotlight.
I learned a lot from him.
You all did well!
You Johnny's members did well.
Thank you.
Everyone started like this.
-See you next year.
-Next year.
These five junior high boys
are always giving it their all.
After this,
they were given
an official unit name, "Lil Kansai".
JOICHIRO FUJIWARA (AGE 23)
The younger ones, like Toa and Ruku
and Nishimura... The five of them
are really charging forward with force,
so we have to work hard
to not fall behind.
And on November 30th...
The special end-of-year performance
that will serve as a new stepping stone
for the Kansai Johnny's Jr. members
is about to begin.
On the next Ride On Time...
The Kansai Johnny's Jr. members
are finally getting ready
for their Christmas concert.
Rock, paper, scissors!
They've always stuck together
like brothers
and aimed for the top together,
but an issue arises.
That's not acceptable for Naniwa.
I don't think we can make it as a group.
What will happen to them?
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita