In August of 2018,
in the record-breaking heat,
over 50,000 fans came
to Ajinomoto Stadium in Tokyo.
The fans that filled the stadium
knew the special meaning
behind the concert being held this day.
It was a concert celebrating
NEWS's 15th anniversary.
Walking towards the stage
as the show is about to start
is Shigeaki Kato.
SHIGEAKI KATO (AGE 31)
Takahisa Masuda.
TAKAHISA MASUDA (AGE 32)
Yuya Tegoshi.
YUYA TEGOSHI (AGE 31)
And the member for which this concert
holds a particularly deep meaning,
Keiichiro Koyama.
KEIICHIRO KOYAMA (AGE 34)
This would be his first appearance
since resuming activity with the band.
Ride on time, a documentary series.
When they debuted, NEWS had nine members.
But one by one, the members left.
FIVE MEMBERS DEPART
After Tomohisa Yamashita
and Ryo Nishikido left,
they were called a strawberry shortcake
without the strawberry.
Everyone doubted the group could survive.
-Let's have fun and make everyone happy!
-Right!
Let's do this!
But the four members somehow
made it to their 15th anniversary concert.
Playing off the combined meaning of
"one" and "five", its name is Strawberry.
They've overcome many rumors
about their disbandment.
This is for their fans who've supported
and waited for them.
All right!
They poured 15 years
of gratitude into their songs.
Even if we have to do it
thousands of times,
we'll rise, fight
and show you all our appreciation.
And so, this last song is for all of you.
They finish the concert with their song
"Ikiro".
This single was released after
Koyama's activities were suspended.
You're the best!
Thank you!
-Thanks so much!
-Thanks!
We're so happy!
Let's meet again!
The curtain closed
on their 15th anniversary concert.
The ending credits rolled on the monitor
to the music of "Ikiro".
At that moment, Koyama heard something.
The fans started singing their song,
"Ikiro".
Nice to meet you.
OCTOBER 2018
They'll be doing a dome tour
that starts at the end of 2018
and extends into 2019.
Their first concert is on New Year's Eve.
This dome tour is an encore concert
to the Epcotia tour that started in March
and was held in eight cities.
Epcotia is NEWS's ninth album and features
the concept of journeying through space.
The concerts transported the audience
into space.
Are you all ready?
The Epcotia tour ended with a big bang.
Let's go! And we are...?
All together!
NEWS!
This time, they need to recreate
the arena tour into a dome tour, but...
I think we have to change some things
and give the fans
something to be surprised about.
We can float up...
They don't want to repeat
the same concert.
How can they entertain the fans
inside the large dome venue?
Tegoshi, what's that thing you have?
-The Segway?
-Is that fun?
It's fun to ride on.
It's super-fast, right?
-The speed?
-Yeah, it's fast.
I don't know, I think it would be cool
to go around the venue
riding on something futuristic looking.
We can come out on that
to our original music.
The one offering detailed suggestions
concerning the stage production
is Masuda.
After finishing one meeting,
Masuda goes into another meeting
by himself.
But this part here is...
-How is it?
-Turn around.
The one who oversees most of
NEWS's costumes is actually Masuda.
Yoneyama has been working
with him for eight years.
COSTUME MANAGER
YUYA YONEYAMA
He has the knowledge.
He checks out lots of different
brand names as well as vintage shops.
He has so many styles of clothing.
Whatever ideas he has,
I never have to second guess his choices.
We have a mutual understanding
in that sense.
He's a big fashion lover.
He even has a regular spot in a fashion
magazine featuring his everyday wear.
NEWS's costumes have also
been featured in Soen,
a fashion magazine
with over 80 years of history.
Masuda's fashion is very highly regarded.
MASUDA'S SERIAL CORNER "MFFB"
For example,
the costumes they wore for
the opening act during their last concert
were made to look like
they were pilots or conductors
guiding people on
a journey through space.
For the "Chankapana" costumes,
he gathered pictures of places
that were memorable for each member
and printed them onto the fabric.
We want to know the thought process
behind his work.
That's what the documentary staff
were thinking,
but they were having difficulty
getting close to him.
The other members of the group...
-Good morning.
-Hi.
Hello.
...had quickly accepted
the cameras for this documentary show.
But as for Masuda...
Good morning.
We can't seem to get close with him.
We had to do something.
We tried to talk with him
during a private interview.
For some reason,
we feel that you have your guard up
and that you're keeping us at a distance.
Of course, our being here...
might be inconveniencing
the members and the other staff.
Not at all.
But the only thing we can do is to
make a great documentary.
But if things continue like this,
we won't be able to relate anything.
Well... we sensed that you probably
don't like documentaries.
Yes.
Why's that?
Documentaries...
Well, I'm glad you guys can film a part
of our lives and air it on TV.
But... well... as a professional,
if I have something I'm working on,
something which will take shape
and be sent out to the public,
I put my whole life into it.
Even if I experience
hardships or difficulties,
the only thing I want people to see
is the finished product at the end.
I don't feel the need
to tell them everything.
There's a side of me
that thinks I shouldn't tell them.
Personally, I like it when concert DVDs
have behind-the-scene footage.
It's like...
you get a glimpse into
how that person is living.
I like watching those.
So I am looking forward to when this airs.
How should I say this...
I don't want anything to be made up.
-Was that okay?
-Yes.
He wants us to show his real self.
That is Masuda's wish.
For us to better understand Masuda,
we ask his fellow band mates
who have been with him for 15 years.
Yeah... he's very creative.
His creativity is something
I really respect.
The pride he has in being a pop idol
is just impressive.
I've never seen anyone like him.
Even among non-idols.
I still remember...
during high school,
I was busy with schoolwork.
But he'd be so particular
about every little thing.
I told him, "Who cares?"
and he got so angry.
I was offhandedly saying
"Who cares?" or "It doesn't matter."
After I said it several times,
he looked at me
with an angry expression and said,
"What did you say?"
Until then, I didn't think he could get
so emotional.
I realized that small details were
important to him.
Back then, I couldn't understand that.
So I saw a new side of him.
There's a saying that goes
"God is in the details."
There are moments when the small details
end up making a big difference.
DOME TOUR
BAND REHEARSAL
Masuda doesn't compromise
when it comes to work.
During the dome tour,
there is a number which
they synchronize with the band.
This time, there are
four new costumes being made.
They've begun discussing the costume
for the number with the band.
For the sweatshirt,
the main color will be yellow.
More like mustard actually.
First, he relays his vision
to the costume designer, Yoneyama,
regarding the color and shape.
Then Yoneyama shapes that vision
into a design.
They're going to use the sweatshirt
being sold at the concert
and recreate it with patchwork.
It's changed drastically.
Yes, it has.
The hood and the cloth material
are the only features left
from the original piece.
They start the meeting
based on the drawing of the design.
I want a white T-shirt with red writing
and red sweat pants.
How about if it's inside out?
And you can see the stitching.
Or you can see the pattern inside.
From among the various fabric samples,
they select which ones
to patch on to the sweatshirt.
Is this a little weird? Wait, hold on.
Maybe green?
If it's green...
-Is it too much?
-The color's too similar.
How about navy blue or stripes?
I know. How about this shade of purple
and adding this blue? Is that cute?
Let's do that.
He spends time behind the scenes
to design and create costumes.
That is usually done after he leaves
the limelight of being an idol.
His time is limited.
What time is it?
I thought it was afternoon,
but it's night.
He has a strong attention to detail.
What he's after is a look that will make
the four members of NEWS stand out.
I never think about
how I'll look in the costumes.
It's about how NEWS will look.
When the members wear the costumes
and think they look great
and like the way they look in them,
they become items
that give them confidence.
My goal is to have each member
love what he wears.
It's for the members. It's for NEWS.
How will Masuda's work turn out?
Preparations for the concert continues.
Today, they're taking pictures
for the concert merchandise
such as uchiwa fans.
In between the shoot, each member
checks the design of their uchiwa.
This one is... interesting.
What about this one?
Aside from the uchiwa,
they look through every piece
of merchandise that will be sold.
I think this will come apart easily.
This is a new tote bag.
At the members' request,
two samples have been prepared.
One has a pocket, and one does not.
Can you try placing the logo
on the corner to the right?
First, they try placing the concert logo
on the one without a pocket.
How about in the middle?
Not bad?
What's the back like?
There's nothing on the back.
Just two lines.
So both sides can be used.
-Then, let's do that.
-There are no pockets.
Should we go with this?
Then, we'll put the logo
on the back pocket.
Whoever wants to remove it
can turn it around.
I like the pocket one.
That's already set.
-Yeah.
-We're going with the pockets.
If you say something now,
it'll sound like you had the final say
on the pockets.
We've already decided.
We're talking about logo placement.
The pockets have been confirmed.
It's nothing new.
You didn't make the final decision.
Girls like to carry around small items,
like tablets.
We three already decided to go
with the pockets.
Me too.
So you agree.
And the inner pocket is deeper now.
-For the phone.
-The phone fits?
-Perfectly.
-Nice.
A mirror can fit in too.
It would be cool
if a glasses case was attached to it.
Glasses?
Once you take them off,
-there's no place to put them.
-True.
This one.
They were very particular
about the fabrics
for the towels and sweatshirts.
We choose what we personally like
and what we want them to have.
We also try to think
from a girl's point of view
and of what they would want.
We get together and consider everyone's...
ideas.
After having all these meetings,
we get attached to it.
-That's important.
-That's the main thing.
Tegoshi wears it every day.
-Yeah. He wears it the most.
-All the time.
I always take my NEWS towel
when I play soccer or futsal.
-It's the right size?
-Yup.
How does it feel?
It feels soft.
It feels good.
DECEMBER 2018
11:00 P.M.
Late at night one day,
we saw Kato working on
something on his laptop.
As an author,
he is writing the script
for a certain segment in the concert.
The theme of the last arena concert
was journeying through space
in a space shuttle name
the Epcotia Liner.
During their journey, they met...
Oh no, they found us.
...three aliens.
What?
Bonsen.
You don't know?
Kota.
Kai.
Let's try holding hands again.
Kato did more than create the story.
Everyone hold hands!
Hold hands!
The voice behind the characters...
is Kato himself.
If everyone will raise their voices,
I think I can get up.
Maybe a little more...
If everyone will raise their voices,
I think I can get up.
Is that funnier?
I think its fine.
I'll try that.
It takes a while before he's satisfied.
If everyone will raise their voices,
I think I can get up.
Why does Kato do this alone
without asking the other members?
It's partly because it's faster this way.
There's no time to really explain
what tone I want them to use.
The members have no idea
how much work this is.
They'd be surprised to see me doing this.
They aren't aware of all I do.
I'd say 70% of the work I do
goes unnoticed.
This is a good chance then.
Please air this part.
But I do it because I enjoy it. Thank you.
Next time,
we follow each member
in his various activities.
Pardon me.
Someone once said,
"The Kindaichi you portray is too pretty."
I was frustrated by that comment.
No! Mother!
He aims to show an expressive and personal
portrayal of Kosuke Kindaichi.
Call the doctor!
Hello.
Koyama meets someone
whom he greatly admires.
Whenever I'm struggling with something,
you're who I imagine talking with.
Really? Glad to hear that.
V6
YOSHIHIKO INOHARA
What is the answer he finds
as he faces his inner struggles?
Subtitle translation by Sara Morita