Shigeaki Kato has something
that he will never forget.
During elementary school...
there was a story about a goose named Gan,
who gets shot by a hunter.
It was in the textbook.
What was it called...
Anyway, it's a story.
Our teacher read that to us
in elementary school,
and we had to share our thoughts
about it by drawing a picture.
And so, even though
it's not in the story at all,
I drew a picture of a present.
I drew a present
with a bow on it and everything.
I turned that in,
and when all the drawings were posted up,
almost everyone had drawn a bird.
They drew a scene from the book.
I remember thinking,
"Those aren't thoughts."
And that stuck in my mind.
You drew a boxed present?
-Yes.
-What was the meaning behind that?
To me, it felt like
I had received a present.
-I see what you mean.
-Yeah.
I felt that I received a present,
so that's what I drew.
But when I saw that everyone
had drawn a bird,
it made me feel sad,
but at the same time I was...
determined to never to draw a bird.
I never want to be
the type of person that draws a bird.
I still remember that
from elementary school.
That always comes to mind
when I write a novel.
Really?
His debut novel was released
when he was 25.
About 450,000 copies
were printed.
But what made him think of
writing a novel to begin with?
I had this vague idea
to write a novel by the time I was 25.
That's one reason.
But I think
the real reason is
that I did it for NEWS.
You know, back then...
Back then we had more members
than we do now.
We didn't know what would happen next.
I felt like I wasn't contributing
anything to the group,
even though I was part of it.
So I went to the office
to ask for more work.
Then,
they asked me what it was that I could do.
I was part of the group,
but I had to do something to be there.
I thought that writing a novel
would be something...
that I could take responsibility for.
I knew some people may criticize it,
but then some might enjoy it too.
I figured some people would admire me
for trying something new.
I thought that it would be
wrong to give up
before trying it out first.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
It's been 15 years since NEWS debuted.
NOVEMBER 2018
DOME CONCERT VIDEO SHOOT
Their dome concert is approaching.
It will start on New Year's Eve 2018
and continue into New Year's Day 2019.
YUYA TEGOSHI (AGE 31)
Today, they're filming footage
that will be shown at the concert.
Okay... Start!
TAKAHISA MASUDA (AGE 32)
The name of concert, Epcotia,
is from their ninth album which tells
the story of a journey through space.
The video footage is also
made to look like they're in space.
In between shoots,
we see Kato in front of his laptop.
He's writing a novel that is regularly
featured in the magazine, anan.
SERIAL NOVEL "MERE KISS SYMPHONY"
ANAN MAGAZINE
APRIL 4TH, 2018 ISSUE
-Is the deadline soon?
-By the end of the year.
I'm nowhere near the end,
so I'm writing whenever I can.
I'm busy this month and next month.
Even though it's the beginning
of December,
Kato is not finished with
his serial novel.
Before he starts writing,
he maps out a character chart.
In this novel,
multiple characters
interact with one another.
He was having a hard time deciding
how to develop the story.
To be honest,
I'm just playing it by ear.
I never know...
where this road is going to take me.
Ultimately, I do have to get somewhere.
Right now, I'm just running around
and hoping I'll get somewhere.
But I do have to decide
on a destination soon.
Creative work
is like trying to find a road in the dark.
He puts together a plan
and finally faces the laptop.
However,
he stumbles at an unexpected place.
He is writing a scene
where someone delivers an item
that was left behind in a karaoke room.
Twenty minutes after starting to write...
his hands stop moving.
Suddenly, he turns to our staff.
Do you ever lose things?
-Lose things?
-Do you leave things behind?
-Yeah, I do.
-Like what?
-My phone.
-That is the most common thing.
Or cigarettes.
Cigarettes!
Would cigarettes be better?
What should I do...
When he first started writing,
the lost item he was imagining
was a phone.
The phone was a good idea.
But this person is using it
in the beginning of the story.
I messed up.
She could've gotten it back,
but she's already using it...
It will be inconsistent
if he chooses the phone.
But, since Kato doesn't smoke,
he can't find a reason
for it to be cigarettes.
Do people turn to e-cigarettes
after they quit smoking?
It's possible.
He starts asking many questions.
A lot of single mothers smoke, right?
Oh yeah, lots.
I bet you'll see a lot of people using
e-cigarettes at a school reunion.
Yeah.
If it's a regular cigarette,
even if someone left it behind,
you wouldn't return it
to the owner, right?
-The person would just buy another one.
-They would.
But if it's an e-cigarette...
Someone may return it.
After that discussion,
he changes the lost item
to an e-cigarette.
It's another long day for Kato
as he searches for ways
to express his thoughts.
It must be hard to write about something
you haven't personally
experienced yourself.
I'm thankful I can work
while asking these questions.
It's like an informal interview.
There are always people around,
so I'm always asking questions.
But in the end,
I'm the one who has to write it.
But really, what should I do?
I wonder...
Which is better...
That's my homework.
Now, I'll go sing and dance.
Kato heads out
to the concert rehearsal.
Time is ticking down for NEWS
until their dome tour scheduled to start
right after the New Year's Eve Countdown.
If the encore starts right away...
The lights could be flashing...
The topic of discussion
is how to decorate the cranes.
The cranes are important
pieces of equipment
that the entire audience can see.
They're particular
about how they will appear.
On the crane,
the Epcotia logo
is in the middle,
but it's so close to the bottom.
Wouldn't it be cooler to have the logo
near the platform where we're standing?
-The middle's fine, I think.
-Then how about...
Should we put something here?
Nobody can see it there. It's too small.
Is the platform fine the way it is?
When we're on the platform and the camera
closes in on us it will show the railing.
The other parts are flashy,
but this part is kind of plain.
How about a strawberry?
While the other members give their ideas,
Koyama mostly sits back and observes.
Are you all having fun?
But during the concert,
he's the lead MC.
We'd like all of you
to clap with us to the beat.
Everyone, please get ready.
Let's put everything down.
-I'm putting down my mic.
-No, keep that.
-Oh, okay.
-Please.
Everyone, both hands up.
And now,
Tego-chan will tell you what to do.
Thank you for the introduction.
I am Tego-nyan. Thank you.
Why do I feel like
this will take a while?
You can just do it right away.
-And I will put my mic―
-Never mind that.
But in the past...
I had this great fear towards being...
the MC.
Every time,
I'd be shaking from nervousness.
Koyama is still searching for a solution,
so he meets up with someone.
-I'm Koyama.
-Long time no see.
-Sorry.
-I'll be in your care.
That someone
is Yoshihiko Inohara from V6.
Whenever I'm struggling with something,
you're who I imagine talking with.
Really? Glad to hear that.
I debuted 15 years ago.
We had nine members,
and there was a talking segment
during the concert.
Yes.
But...
we didn't know who would do the talking
or who would take the lead.
It was a big disaster
during that first concert.
Just as I was thinking about what to do,
I was looking at a magazine
and read your interview.
You had said
that you take notes
of things your group members do.
You said that you try to observe them.
I read that excerpt
from the magazine.
I knew I had found my answer.
By observing his group members
and making them part of his skit,
the talking segment greatly improved.
He's trying so hard.
I wanted to bring something up.
Tegoshi, the shower
isn't just yours to use.
-I usually go after you.
-Yeah.
I'm always cleaning up after you.
-No way.
-You trash it.
Is it dirty?
There's body wash all over the walls.
-But I rinse the walls off―
-Sorry, hold on.
Are you listening, Shige?
I am, I am.
I was quiet because I might be
the one who's guilty of that.
It's you?
We all learned to banter with each other.
Yeah, yeah.
Before, I was just glad
if they'd even respond to my questions.
I told them to keep their mic up.
-I get that.
-Do you?
If not,
they can't maintain the tempo,
or keep up with the conversation.
If their mic is down
when you ask them a question...
-"Why yes..." It stops the flow.
-Yes.
-Isn't that right?
-Yeah.
But actually, I came to realize
that the pause is part of the fun.
Because this rhythm
is just my own personal rhythm.
Right.
Everyone is different.
When it all comes together,
it will break the rhythm,
but that's what makes it funny,
and you have to enjoy that.
-That's what I try to keep in mind.
-I see.
For Koyama,
Inohara is eight years his senior.
Everyone has this image of you
as someone outgoing and nice.
I'm sure you get that often.
-Yeah.
-And we all think that too.
But I'm sure you also
worry about things or feel down.
-Right.
-Do you get like that too?
-I used to. But not anymore.
-Oh, is that right?
Well, not completely.
I learned to have fun and to be happy.
I hate to say this,
but I realized that I'm really a good guy.
Just yesterday.
That's recent.
-No, you see―
-You're lucky.
I was responding to a text.
There are people who text
with a serious face.
Yeah.
They're typing "hello" using cute emojis.
But they still have a serious face.
But...
I was smiling
while typing a smiling emoji.
I was expressing my honest feelings
in that text.
Did someone tell you
that you were smiling?
No, I realized it myself.
That felt great.
I hope when I get to your age,
I'll be smiling while texting too.
Please do.
Please continue to support us.
-Thank you.
-No, no, thank you for your time.
-Work hard.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
NOV. 21, 2018 EARLY MORNING
THE INUGAMI FAMILY FILMING
-Good morning.
Shigeaki Kato has been chosen to play
the Heisei Era's last Kosuke Kindaichi.
-It's Shigeaki.
-Thank you!
He begins filming as the lead role.
-And here we go.
-Let's go... Action!
The filming starts with the last scene.
After solving a case,
Kindaichi leaves town.
It suddenly starts from the last scene.
I'm glad I can build this character
by filming a walking scene first
instead of a scene with lines.
This is a gravel road.
-It's so hard to walk on it.
-With the geta?
You don't usually...
But not being used to walking like this
might be true to his character.
He's not the type who can
smoothly walk on gravel.
I see.
-He's a bit clumsy.
-Oh, I see.
No matter what it is he's doing,
he can't do it very gracefully.
-That's what I'm trying to portray.
-Ah, I see.
How to act out his interpretation
of Kosuke Kindaichi...
That's what he's been thinking of
since long before filming began.
Is the room upstairs?
Yes.
Someone once said,
"The Kindaichi you portray is too pretty."
I was frustrated by that comment.
It was never my intention
to create a pretty character.
Acting while trying
to make myself look cool
is just lame.
I've always thought that.
This Kindaichi is endearing
because he doesn't try to act cool.
I think that's the appeal.
And start!
He wants to portray this character
as someone people can relate to.
It shows his passion for his work.
Every job that I do,
I do it thinking it's my last.
You never know what will happen.
Every day.
I don't want to have any regrets,
even if this is my last piece of work.
So I give it my all.
Film rehearsals start
for the scene
where he identifies the suspect.
PRODUCER, KENSAKU SAWADA
If you do nothing,
the person you tried to protect
will be made the culprit.
Aren't you...
the real culprit?
Instead of bluntly pointing out
the culprit,
he's more kind.
He asks, "Aren't you the culprit?"
He's kind-mannered.
He doesn't talk in a demanding way.
He...
sits down each time.
He sits down near them.
Being at eye level is important.
The Kindaichi that Kato
is trying to portray
shines through in this next scene.
Let's start.
Ready... action.
If you do nothing,
the person you were trying to protect
will be made the culprit.
Aren't you...
the real culprit?
No! Mother!
What happened?
There was poison in this cigarette.
It's the same one Mr. Wakabayashi smokes.
Call the doctor!
Meanwhile, Tegoshi pays a visit to
what could be called his starting point.
Hold on.
This isn't the Mei-naka that I know.
This is your alma mater, right?
Yes, it is.
See, it's written here.
Meiji University Nakano Junior High
and High School.
I attended from first year junior high
to my first year of high school.
His alma mater has transformed,
after it was renovated six years ago.
Wow, seriously?
It looks like a university.
It's so different.
The soccer field he used to play on
has changed too.
Wait, hold on.
It's turf?
No way.
Hold on, it's turf now?
It has transformed into a splendid field
with artificial turf grass.
Back then,
Tegoshi was devoted to soccer.
The work and the result are all on me.
You don't do it for anyone else.
I wanted to be on the team, have fun,
and win as a team.
I was playing soccer
to share in that joy.
The time I spent here
and the memories I made
with everyone
like my team and the teachers,
had a great influence on me.
At that moment...
-Hey, can you aim better?
-Sorry.
-I'll come closer.
-What?
Want to join?
Who? Who are they?
-Kadoya?
-That's me.
What are you doing?
And that's Michiki!
-Good to see you.
-Why're you here?
-Practicing.
-What are you doing?
-I'm here filming something.
-Oh.
Congrats on your wedding.
I heard about that.
They are former teammates
that he played with in junior high,
Michiki and Kadoya.
I'd go to your house a lot.
-And I would spend the night.
-We would both go there.
-That's right.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Since they owned a bathhouse.
-Yeah, we'd both use it.
I thought you'd come by to use it again.
That's right, I did say that.
We were on the regular team...
for a long time.
Tegoshi would pass
the ball to Kadoya, and I'd block it,
so that you could score a goal.
That's right.
Only the good players made the team,
no matter what grade you were in.
When Chami was the coach,
-he'd choose those who practiced hard.
-Yeah, he did.
We were lucky in that sense.
-Should we go for a run?
-Seriously? There's no way I'm running.
-Let's run.
-That scared me!
It's been forever!
-Good to see you.
-It's good to see you again.
This is Coach Usami.
Wow, I was not expecting him to come out.
-Seriously?
-Do you remember him too?
-About Tegoshi?
-Of course.
-Really?
-What kind of student was he?
He hated to lose.
I'd tell him to juggle,
and he would go on forever.
-Maybe about 500 times.
-I did.
It has been 16 years
since they kicked a ball around
in this nostalgic place.
Whoa, it's hard!
He learned something by spending time
with his team here.
It was like living under the same roof.
The time we spent outside of soccer,
like at lunch time or on the way home,
all contributed to teamwork
and led the team to victory.
Now ten years later,
I get to see my former coach
and my teammates,
whom I played with on this field.
It's brought me back to my roots.
This was a nice experience.
-All right!
-Okay!
On the next Ride On Time...
It's the concert they've been
preparing for.
On the night of New Year's Eve,
over 50,000 people come
to attend the concert.
Hear the emotion NEWS
puts into their song, "Ikiro".
Subtitle translation by Sara Morita