-We only have four minutes.
-Okay.
Within that time, we must
-promote Naniwa Danshi.
-Claws.
All right.
Let's go!
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2018-2019
TOKYO DOME
This New Year's holiday,
they will be facing a moment of truth.
We are Naniwa Danshi.
Last year, a new unit was formed
out of Kansai Johnny's Jr. members
called Naniwa Danshi.
Tonight, for the first time,
they fulfilled their dreams
of performing with their seniors.
Meanwhile,
the members who stayed behind in Kansai
were making new resolutions.
KOJI MUKAI
When I see Naniwa on TV,
I do feel envious...
and motivated to work hard from tomorrow.
You have to work hard,
or you get left behind in this business.
Ride on Time, a documentary series.
Kansai Johnny's Jr.
began their journey with their
end-of-year shows
at Osaka Shochikuza Theater.
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR.
They have more than 50 members,
including elementary school kids.
Song, dance...
What?
...and comedy.
Anything to entertain their audience.
They are still young,
so sometimes they don't see eye to eye.
Do you want to continue
as a member of Naniwa?
What are you thinking?
I don't even know
if there's a point to this.
Their seniors watched over them
and continued to encourage them.
This is a team sport.
Everything about it is.
We want to become known nationwide.
And now, it's time for their
big New Year's performances
at Osaka-Jo Hall.
What will be the outcome?
December...
DECEMBER 2018
OSAKA
Their journey to Osaka-Jo Hall
has already begun,
and every experience
is something special to them.
Wow. We've never experienced this before.
Believe it or not,
this is their very first time filming
an opening video
for a concert.
The one who is most grateful
for this experience
is Koji Mukai, who has been working hard
as a Johnny's Jr. member ever since
he joined 12 years ago.
KOJI MUKAI
It's really a luxury to be able to film
an opening video.
That's a huge step
for a Johnny's Jr. member.
A huge step for Johnny's Jr.
Okay.
This time,
the costumes that were prepared
for Naniwa Danshi's new song
are the most elaborate they've ever seen.
Thinking about where Kansai Johnny's Jr.
was just the other day,
it's an enormous improvement.
It feels good.
When Johnny's WEST broke off from us,
the fans called us "burned ruins."
DAIGO NISHIHATA (AGE 22)
Then Hirano and Nagase went to Tokyo.
Yeah.
We were called "burned ruins" back then.
It was a rough time.
Honestly, I don't want to lose to them.
On New Year's Day...
JANUARY 1ST, 2019
TWO DAYS BEFORE THE CONCERT
These are the final stages of practice.
Naniwa Danshi,
who just performed
in Tokyo the night before
at the New Year countdown concert,
came straight back.
-The one you did last year?
-Including that one.
TADAYOSHI OHKURA
Ohkura and Yokoyama from Kanjani∞
also came for moral support.
-...it could be random.
-Okay.
-I'll add to it later.
-Got it.
YOU YOKOYAMA
There was something that
Ohkura was concerned about.
That something was
the group of children referred to
as trainees within Johnny's Jr.
They lacked professionalism
and didn't have the choreography
memorized.
-We'll stop here for a moment.
-Trainees.
-Yes.
Come here.
Ohkura has gathered the trainees.
You don't have to perform
if you're unmotivated.
If we're having an important conversation,
you have to listen.
Yes.
You're not here to make friends.
It's a good thing that you get along,
but I need you to take this seriously,
or you'll never get to hold a mic.
Yes.
Age doesn't matter here.
How serious are they
about working toward their goal?
He wanted them to think about it.
JANUARY 2ND, 2019
DAY BEFORE THE CONCERT
That's why the next day...
I was so worked up about them,
I broke my foot.
-Yeah, right.
-Don't say that!
It apparently happened the night before,
but he still came all the way
to the practice.
How will they respond
to the consideration he shows them?
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR.
There's only one more day
until showtime.
Rehearsals at the actual arena have begun.
They are used to performing
in venues that seat about 1,000 people,
so an arena
that fits 15,000 people feels huge.
Everyone please move to your positions
on the center stage.
So they can entertain their fans
sitting in every corner,
they thoroughly check where and how
they should move.
We're going to dance here?
TAKUYA NISHIMURA
I might fall.
-You're stupid.
-Okay, everyone.
The little kids are done for now.
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR.
They're trying out new methods.
A trolly, to get closer to the fans.
-Naniwa, are you okay?
-Yes.
And even their entrance...
The stairs team
will go straight to the staircase.
They all look nervous.
Go.
KAZUYA OHASHI (AGE 21)
It's hard to get the timing
while keeping your balance.
It's not funny,
-you can get hurt.
-I'm sorry.
KENTO NAGAO (AGE 16)
The youngest member, Nagao,
is looking like this.
Go.
That was close.
-That was too early.
-Okay.
When coming up, you should push down.
As it rises, go like this.
Then you'll come up.
At the right timing,
jump like this.
Use the momentum.
Next is the variety corner.
Sorry, can you clearly state
that it's a tournament,
so people understand?
The speaking part and explanation is...
Their seniors give them
tips on even the smallest details.
When you finish that part
and move on to the next...
However,
they can't rely on them for everything.
Yes, let's do that.
It happened when
they were checking the song which
the trainees will also participate in.
Trainees, come on out.
Answer if you can hear.
Their dancing is still unpolished.
-Are you ready, trainees?
-Yes.
The one who took action was Nishihata.
You guys...
Some of the trainees
haven't memorized the dance, am I right?
Some of them don't have it down.
-You should get on it.
-Yes.
You'll only embarrass yourselves.
Yes.
This was the first time
we've seen Nishihata speak sternly
toward the children
since we started filming them.
The atmosphere between
the Kansai Johnny's Jr. members
is changing.
Watching this situation
from a different perspective was Mukai.
KOJI MUKAI
He spoke about it himself, suddenly during
his New Year's visit to a shrine.
I'll be working in Tokyo for the most part
from next year, so it'll be a bit sad.
How far I can make it on my own...
This day, Mukai had already
decided to move to Tokyo to join a unit.
But I'm sure that my fans will support me
no matter where I am.
So I'll rely on that fact. Well, I want to
live up to their expectations.
I want to work out there too,
and hopefully have a good effect
on Kansai Johnny's Jr.
Takizawa Kabuki ZERO
is where I will start again.
I should tell them.
However, Mukai still had not
told the other members about his decision.
Happy New Year.
And the eldest member, Muro,
also had something
he hadn't told the others.
Muro had decided
to focus on acting from now on.
We'll go with that.
I will go down my own path.
As a Kansai Johnny's Jr. member,
it's likely my last time performing
at Osaka-Jo Hall.
I am a bit sad, but...
I decided that I won't cry.
I really want to make
this concert successful.
Not...
Not just for myself,
but for Kansai Johnny's Jr. as a whole.
Kojima's line during "Biribiri DANCE"...
This is the last time
they will all perform together.
JANUARY 3RD, 2019
OSAKA-JO HALL
The day has finally come.
An overwhelming number of fans
encircle the arena.
Joichiro and I will...
They do their final checks.
I'll get off.
Stage left, stage right, center.
From stage left,
you'll go to the outer aisle.
You, from stage right.
Listen to the music
and dance like you mean it.
You better practice.
-There are mirrors here for that.
-Yes.
The looks on the trainees' faces
have changed.
On the other hand, one member,
Nagao, had injured his foot
during the latest rehearsal.
KENTO NAGAO (AGE 16)
-Can you manage to smile as you dance?
-Yes.
Actually, I'll be laughing more.
At how clumsy I am.
Their journey, which started last autumn,
has made them tough.
It is almost showtime.
All right. Are you ready?
Daigo?
-No, Ryuta.
-Ryuta.
-Ryuta!
-Me?
Please.
-Please.
-Okay.
It is 2019.
Let's show them
what Kansai Johnny's Jr.'s got!
Okay, let's get this started!
Yes!
Let's go!
All right!
Finally,
the two fateful days
and four concerts will begin.
Happy New Year!
And their trademark variety corner.
It lit up and broke in two.
What came out
from inside was... Ken!
Nailed it!
Kansai Johnny's Jr. aimed for
a performance that all the fans can enjoy,
in which all the members
can share the spotlight.
They believe that it would open up
a new path for them.
It's Naniwa Danshi's new song.
We present to you,
"Diamond Smile."
And now,
all that is left is the final show.
JANUARY 4TH, FINAL SHOW
That day...
The members were told
that Mukai will be moving to Tokyo.
This is
the last performance they will do
together as Kansai Johnny's Jr.
The stage is yours.
Okay. It's our last time, after all.
That's right.
Two departing members take stage.
RYUTA MURO
Thank you for coming today, everyone.
In life, there are fun times
and tough times.
Many things happen.
During the tough times,
the concert we did here...
Did you have fun today?
Do you love Kansai Johnny's Jr.?
Listening to their voices,
Nishihata was crying.
Friends whom he has worked with
to build up Kansai Johnny's Jr. together,
are starting new journeys.
Well then, it's time for the last song.
Here is, "My Dreams."
"My Dreams"...
A song that represents
all of the members' feelings.
Okay.
Thank you.
Don't forget your mics, everyone.
Doing their best to hold in
their emotions,
each member heads to the stage
for the encore.
It's time to say goodbye.
Thank you so much.
Muro, who'll move on
to the world of acting.
How will I take this home?
And Mukai,
who will start working in Tokyo.
Really...
Do your best. I will do my best too.
I really love all of you. Do your best.
Cheers.
Because there are goodbyes,
it paves way for the new era.
Thank you very much.
Next time
will be when we debut.
Until then. When we debut,
let's do a documentary.
Thank you.
And now they can enjoy
some well-earned time off.
No... I can...
Fujiwara had something he wanted to do
no matter what.
It's baseball.
A curveball?
That's crazy!
Seriously? Wow...
One more ball.
No matter what happens,
if you keep on running,
then one day...
We are...
Kansai Johnny's Jr.
Next time on Ride on Time...
Takizawa Kabuki
ZERO.
Hideaki Takizawa's
ultimate Japanese entertainment.
This year, it will star Snow Man.
JOHNNY'S JR. UNIT
SNOW MAN
They're burdened
with responsibility and pressure.
It's not enough.
I can't show this to people.
This is definitely crazy.
You'll be coughing up blood.
Their resolve to stand on stage
will be tested.
I plan to create a world
that even Takizawa didn't imagine.
In the world of entertainment,
will they be able
to dance and spread their wings?
PREPARE FOR A NEW BEGINNING
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita