DECEMBER 31, 2018
OSAKA KYOCERA DOME
On New Year's Eve in 2018,
over 50,000 NEWS fans
came from all over Japan.
They filled the Kyocera Dome.
Hello!
For NEWS, which is celebrating
its 15th anniversary,
this is their first...
TAKAHISA MASUDA (AGE 32)
...solo countdown concert.
KEIICHIRO KOYAMA (AGE 34)
Let's get this started!
All right!
We're so glad to be spending
the end of 2018 and the beginning of 2019
with all you lovely people,
who have always been there for us.
-All right! Here we go!
-Yeah!
Let's work hard.
They've reached the end of the year.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
The countdown concert
approaches with every second.
NEWS will be singing over 40 songs
during this concert.
On this day, Tegoshi was rehearsing
the entire song list by himself
without the other members.
Pretending it's a real concert,
he sings and dances
without taking any breaks.
It's what we do at the actual concert.
So I have to do a real
run through beforehand,
to see what it's like.
Because if we're up on the stage,
and we're wheezing,
it'll look so lame.
Since it's our job to be pop idols.
If the song list that we have now
is too hard to complete,
I'll go out and run. Outside, at night.
That day,
he rehearsed and checked everything
until he was satisfied.
His solo rehearsal
lasted for four hours.
Meanwhile, there were still
things to discuss about the concert.
At this meeting, the topic of discussion
was the video footage
which would appear during the song.
It's the font, right? As usual?
It does make a difference.
Depending on the color
and the design.
There are various types of fonts.
Why is this important to Kato?
Words are one way
to express an atmosphere.
The cool visuals help to create
that world and deliver the lyrics.
That way, the fans can enjoy
both the sound and visual.
He checks some text samples
of the lyrics that the staff made.
This is a gothic style font.
The next one is Mincho style.
Mincho style is cooler,
for this song at least.
It's an important way
to convey what the song means.
He can't cut corners.
Three more days until New Year's Eve.
The costumes are coming along.
Four new costumes
were made for this concert.
The costume fitting begins.
This purple coat is for the opening song.
The important thing
is how it looks when all four members
go up on stage.
Maybe I'll add some stripes to the collar.
The neckline is looking a little...
This here?
To make changes to their costumes,
decorations are added
to Kato and Tegoshi's sleeves.
And...
Masuda feels Koyama's neckline
is also looking bare.
Will you have a necklace on?
Well... not really.
Then...
I was thinking about this chain.
-Can you try this on as a necklace?
-Sure.
How is it?
It does look better.
If you don't like that,
we can add something else to your costume.
Yeah. I probably won't wear this.
How do the members feel about
the costumes that Masuda makes?
He's always thinking about
how the costumes
can make each member look his best.
If a highly experienced stylist
or designer were to make them,
they might be
of higher quality and look nice,
but the costumes
wouldn't be made with love.
That's something only he can do.
December 30th, 2018 at Kyocera Dome.
Good morning.
It's the day before the countdown concert.
The members arrive at Kyocera Dome.
Good morning.
This is the first rehearsal
using the actual stage
that they will be performing on.
Each member corrects
whatever he feels needs to be fixed.
Can the Johnny's Jr. members
come in from a different place?
Meanwhile,
in the dressing room backstage...
Three sewing machines
were brought in to modify the costumes.
It's 11:00 p.m. at night.
After eight hours of rehearsing,
Masuda comes in.
Then...
What type of buttons do you have for this?
-A button?
-Yeah.
He suggests adding gold buttons
to the purple coat.
Doesn't that look nice?
It looks weird if there aren't any here.
-So should we put it on both sides?
-That would be good.
So...
They decided to put gold buttons
on both sides of the zipper.
This is the costume
for their new song, Spirit.
If we write something on this,
it'll look better.
How about "Spirit?"
After saying that,
he heads out of the room.
-Can I borrow this?
-Sure.
He borrowed a permanent marker.
See you tomorrow.
-I found it.
-Wow.
He starts to write something,
on the leather patch.
On Kato's costume,
he even wrote Kato's birth date.
He works diligently on small details
that the audience may not notice.
He believes
that there is a meaning behind all of it.
It's so cute.
It's finally
the day of the countdown concert.
DECEMBER 31, 2018
DAY OF THE COUNTDOWN CONCERT
It's 12 hours until the concert starts,
but the costumes
were still being modified.
TEN A.M.
There are 15 costume staff,
including those
who help with the fitting.
Will they be finished on time?
We're cutting it close.
YUYA YONEYAMA
-Will Masuda be coming by to check again?
-I think so.
-He's coming in now.
-Good morning.
Oh, thank you.
I got some extras too.
There are 15 in total here.
There are 15 people here, right?
-Thank you.
-Please share cups if there aren't enough.
Thank you so much.
He's always so considerate.
He doesn't need to do this.
We're just doing our jobs.
The modifications on the coats
for their opening song
were finishing up quickly.
This is the completed costume.
There are gold buttons from the waist up,
and decorations were added to the collar.
The collar has two different designs,
used to create contrast
when all four members stand
next to each other.
KOYAMA & MASUDA VERSION
KATO & TEGOSHI VERSION
EIGHT P.M. DOORS OPEN
The concert will begin any minute.
For NEWS,
it's their first countdown concert
on their own.
The venue is filled
with over 50,000 fans.
Let's get this started!
All right!
We're so glad to be spending
the end of 2018 and the beginning of 2019
with all you lovely people,
who have always been there for us.
-All right! Here we go!
-Yeah!
Let's work hard.
The moment has finally arrived.
We want to hear all of your voices!
Let's be one!
It's the third song into the concert.
At that moment Masuda...
These costumes
are the concert sweatshirts
that they had redesigned.
This is the costume
that Masuda put his whole soul into.
And as for Kato, who searched for
the perfect font
and design for the lyrics...
It's finally the countdown.
Three! Two! One!
Happy New Year!
But you know, isn't it amazing that NEWS
got to perform a countdown concert?
It's amazing. We're so blessed.
Thank you so much everyone.
We're so blessed.
I get why Masuda got overwhelmed
with emotions.
That was fast.
What are you talking about?
Don't tell me you forgot.
They've spent 15 years together.
Each member carries
his own memories in his heart.
Then, they sing this song.
"Ikiro".
Happy New Year!
-Thank you, everyone.
-Good work!
Let's do a review.
Thanks so much.
-Did your tears say it all?
-I didn't cry.
Was it emotional?
Yeah, it made me happy.
Takahisa Masuda is a crybaby.
He said he wasn't crying.
No, no. He cries like this...
That's how it looks to us.
We gave the best performance
that we could give at this moment.
Our songs weren't perfect,
and our performance
or our dancing wasn't perfect either.
Nothing was perfect.
But in terms of what NEWS
and the NEWS fans can do,
to put on a great concert,
I feel like we gave the best one so far.
After seeing you guys
under the spotlight, I realized that
you guys really are pop idols.
-Did you?
-I'm glad.
Glad to hear that.
I hate to say it
but being a pop idol is amazing.
That's why we have to work harder.
Is it fun being a pop idol?
-Well yeah, we love it.
-Yeah.
Or you won't last.
I think people who choose
to be idols are crazy.
I am, and you are, too.
You can blow a kiss on a whim, right?
That's not a normal thing to do
for a guy over 30.
But you'll continue doing it?
-Of course.
It was a good way to end the year,
and it gave us a new resolve
to start fresh,
as pop idols once again.
Keiichiro Koyama.
Shigeaki Kato.
Takahisa Masuda.
Yuya Tegoshi.
They will continue together as NEWS...
On the next Ride On Time,
it's a special edition.
King and Prince appears again.
Their crazy New Year's schedule
as the pop idol group
representing this century.
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2018-2019
...a year where everything changed.
Their thoughts and emotions
of what happened in that one year.
JANUARY 17, 2017
Since I debuted,
I have wanted to give it my all.
Because we hit rock bottom,
there's nothing to fear.
I think I used up
a lifetime's worth of tears.
I want to follow the path
that I believe in.
That's how determined I am.
It's the day of their
performance on Kohaku.
We're excited, but nervous
at the same time.
I'll do my best in the Kid's Corner.
And we will feature
the Kansai Johnny's Jr. member
Nice to meet you!
We are Kansai Johnny's Jr.!
Subtitle translation by Sara Morita