Thank you.
On this day, a group of idols
based in Osaka
faces a new beginning.
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR.
It is Kansai Johnny's Jr.
and the unit that was born from them,
Naniwa Danshi.
At the Christmas performance
that is coming up,
they will have to show their worth.
We are motivated to work harder
to become known to more people,
and to make them say
the next unit to debut
will come from Kansai.
You'll be even more nervous.
-Hey!
-Wait a second.
Don't say that.
Ready... Viva!
What in the world?
How many times must we do this?
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
They are all the rage
in the Kansai region,
Kansai Johnny's Jr.
Last autumn, Naniwa Danshi
had the privilege of performing
on their dream stage
at the Kanjani∞ dome concert.
It was so fun.
And they made a promise.
We can't always be relying on others.
We'll come back here
with our own strength.
Their first step is to
successfully complete 35 performances
during their month-long residency
at Osaka Shochikuza Theatre.
OSAKA SHOCHIKUZA THEATRE
NOVEMBER 29TH, 2018
It's the day before the opening day.
After the second song,
when "Awatenbou" begins,
we circle around.
Will we make it in time?
All the Kansai Johnny's Jr. members
will work together to tackle this event.
-Everyone, gather at the center.
-Yes.
Each of the members have
their own unique talents.
Those with high-level guitar technique
and those with a good sense of humor.
If you do it ten times, you get 100 yen.
One hundred?
Their ages range from
elementary school kids
to youths in their 20's.
That is the charm of Kansai Johnny's Jr.
I think what makes
Kansai Johnny's Jr. special
is the fact that each member
has a unique personality.
What kind of performance will they put on?
How long have you been there?
From when you were butchering the piano.
NOV. 29, 2018
OSAKA SHOCHIKUZA THEATRE
The day before opening day,
Naniwa Danshi's leader, Kazuya Ohashi,
was more nervous than anyone else.
KAZUYA OHASHI (AGE 21)
This concert will start off
with his solo performance
of Mariah Carey's iconic song,
"All I Want for Christmas is You."
During practice, it was decided
that he will sing
this vocally demanding song.
It happened five days ago.
Ohkura from Kanjani∞,
who is in charge of the composition
and stage direction of the show,
focused on Ohashi's
trademark countertenor voice.
What they're worried about
is the last high note.
It's fine. It'll be okay.
Okay, I'll sing it.
To help them mature,
Ohkura wants them to try out something
a little more challenging.
I'm sure everything
they do will be
a learning experience for them.
I am very excited to see what kind of
people they will become.
Yes.
It's the opening day.
They practice until the very end.
Okay.
-That's how we'll do it.
-Thank you.
Ohkura and Ohashi
were checking the high notes
that come out in the chorus,
over and over again.
The show's variety corner was composed
and directed by KANJANI∞'s Yokoyama.
YOU YOKOYAMA
SHOTA YASUDA
KANJANI∞'s Yasuda provided the music.
-You're so cute. Do your best.
-Yes!
SHINGO MURAKAMI
And KANJANI∞'s Murakami
also came to visit.
Yokoyama and Ohkura's
presence really increased
their chances a lot, I think.
In that sense,
how they will seize this opportunity
depends on their judgment.
In a way, I do feel envious.
The show will soon begin.
I'm nervous.
What outfit is this?
-You have eight minutes.
-Okay.
What are you holding?
It's finally showtime.
Worried, Ohkura is also by the stage wing.
Will Ohashi pull off Mariah Carey's
"All I Want for Christmas is You"?
Everyone held their breath
as they listened.
In the end,
he wasn't able to keep the high notes
during the most important chorus.
But there are no second chances.
That's show business.
And the variety corner...
Santa Danshi!
Nailed it.
We're Kyara Jutai Santa!
Is that supposed to be cool?
Thank you so much for today!
See you again.
On the opening day,
no one looked satisfied with the outcome.
Good work.
Of course, that includes Ohashi.
-Hey.
-Good work.
It's my fault.
-It's my fault. Because I messed up.
-About what?
-I started off on the wrong foot.
-I didn't notice.
-No, I messed up.
-But that was...
Ohkura had put all that together for me,
but I wasn't able to make
the most out of it.
That is frustrating.
I'm sure a lot of things will happen
from now on,
but I'll take this as a personal trial.
I have to become stronger mentally.
The one before this.
An evaluation meeting
in the hallway backstage.
It's such a waste when you look down, Toa.
They're really working hard,
so I feel like for their sake,
I need to think of something
to get the audience laughing.
In order to live up to those expectations,
each one of them must improve themselves
during the span of this month.
Meanwhile, they have other jobs lined up.
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Kansai Johnny's Jr. no Bari Bari Sound.
On this day, they had their radio show.
The members are Naniwa Danshi's Fujiwara,
Ohashi, Takahashi,
and the one who supports the show
with his guitar skills,
Yoshinori Masakado.
This is a request from a listener.
He's a sincere man.
"I Gotta Feeling" by The Black Eyed Peas.
After he dyed his hair black
for a certain job,
we met up with Masakado to film him
practicing his guitar.
Good morning.
When were we supposed to meet?
Half past one.
You can tell how nervous I am
by how early I got here.
At first, he started learning
the guitar on his own.
But he took up lessons,
so he could use it
in his activities as a Jr. member.
I'm sure people would say,
he's good for being an idol.
They'll always have preconceptions.
And so,
if I can excel at something
and reach the same level
as a so-called professional,
people will be surprised to see
a Johnny's member like that, I'm sure.
I want to overwhelmingly
exceed their expectations.
Not just a little bit.
This day, Ohkura came to check on
Masakado and the band.
The outro...
How will their senior
evaluate their skills?
-Amazing.
-Isn't it?
-Right?
The amount of time
he's dedicated to it has paid off.
Meanwhile, tonight is...
the day of Ohashi's weekly vocal lesson.
KAZUYA OHASHI (AGE 21)
He feels a strong sense
of responsibility as someone
who leads Naniwa Danshi with his vocals.
I don't know what it sounds like outside.
Outside?
-I mean, to the audience.
-On our end?
Is it good or bad?
When I hear myself in the recording,
it sounds really bad.
Ohashi joined the agency nine years ago.
His goal has always been to debut.
Naniwa Danshi
is the agency's first unit in four years.
He doesn't want it to end as a failure.
I only have one chance,
considering my age.
So I want to seize this opportunity.
I believe each of us
has to work hard individually in order
to succeed in that.
I've always been conscious of
working hard as individuals.
All we can do is work hard.
Really.
On this day,
RYUTA MURO
The oldest member of Kansai Johnny's Jr.,
Ryuta Muro, was also trying
to pave a new road for himself.
Today, I am solo.
Thinking I can't afford
to make any mistakes
makes me nervous, and I end up messing up.
Look at the center, please.
Muro will be playing the role
of a rakugoka in a stage play
starting in February.
He is especially nervous.
Do you and your character
share any similarities?
We're taking on challenges.
His desire to make it big
is similar to how I feel,
in my opinion.
-At first...
-Yes?
At this point,
nobody knew that Kansai Johnny's Jr.
was about to change.
It's easier to remember that way.
DECEMBER 2018
OSAKA SHOCHIKUZA THEATRE
Mid-December,
their month-long residency
has reached its midpoint.
They were already preparing
for their next big performance.
Two consecutive days
at Osaka-Jo Hall in the New Year.
Good work. We don't have much time left,
so we have to get on it
or we won't make it in time.
It's not just one thing.
We're doing multiple things at once,
and that makes me so happy.
-Now...
-It feels like we're working.
-It's like we're superstars.
-I know!
The sense of fulfillment
wins over fatigue.
...we're multitasking, and I'm so happy.
But on the other hand,
as they perform one day after the next,
some members may have become stagnant.
Fujiwara was concerned about that.
Is Naniwa Danshi
really moving forward every day?
That was when...
Can I ask you a question?
Sure, no problem.
A member came up
to Fujiwara to pitch an idea
for the variety corner.
...a lot of questions like this.
Sota Okumura.
By the pillar...
He joined six years ago.
Diagonally, like this.
He's been diligently working hard.
Such a nice voice.
He has a silky voice
and a good sense of humor.
What's your favorite food?
Shirataki.
-How cool!
-Very nice.
I thought of questions and answers
that might be funny.
WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE ANIMAL? GIRAFFE
Okumura
has come up with multiple ideas.
I like the one about the animal.
We can use that giraffe thing.
Last night,
I asked Okumura
if he could think of something,
and he said yes.
And the next day,
he already has six ideas.
I can see that everyone wants
the variety corner to succeed,
and that makes me want to work harder.
Without delay, they used it that day.
What's your favorite animal?
The giraffe.
With his hard work,
he got the crowd laughing.
He wanted to let the members
of Naniwa Danshi know.
After the show,
Fujiwara called all the members
into one room.
The voices we overheard
were filled with anger.
What are you thinking?
Do you want to continue
as a member of Naniwa? If you're thinking,
"I don't care," you should just quit.
People like Okumura and Sano
put so much thought
into the variety corner.
I asked them yesterday,
for one idea
and they gave me three or four.
I ask for one
and they give back three or four.
I ask you guys for one,
and what have you given me?
Nothing.
I don't even know
if there's a point to this.
There's no reason in doing this.
Actually...
Excuse me.
DAIGO NISHIHATA (AGE 22)
I do feel like this group is in
a grave situation right now.
Did you say things you didn't want to say?
Yes.
But, we're a team.
It hurts me to say these things...
but I do hope they get the message.
Yes.
It'll depend on how those kids change,
and us as well.
We'll see.
The next day...
-Are you free?
-Yeah.
Are you free?
Try it with music.
Yes, thank you.
What they said was true.
We won't become any better
if we're just sleeping
in our dressing rooms.
It'd be better if I practiced here.
That's why I'm here.
I was grateful.
That they would scold us like that
for our sake.
What's important is to always remember
what your goal is.
After that talk we had,
we've become more motivated,
and we're moving toward a good direction.
In team sports, whether or not you have
good teamwork changes
your odds of winning.
To us, this is a team sport.
Everything about it is.
Whether it's a small game or big game,
we will win
and defeat Tokyo, and together,
we want to become known nationwide.
Yes.
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR.
X'MAS PARTY!! 2018
The shows are coming close to their end,
and it is Christmas Eve.
Every day, at the beginning of each show,
Ohashi has been singing
"All I Want for Christmas is You"
without a break.
And today...
Ohashi succeeded in singing
that chorus while retaining the high note.
On the next Ride On Time...
Kansai Johnny's Jr. members move on
to the next stage.
They will face a concert at an arena
that seats around 60,000.
It's like we have 400 meters to go.
It's the hardest leg.
However,
the members run into many problems.
They must also say goodbye
to a precious friend.
It's likely my last time performing
at Osaka-Jo Hall.
A tearful performance.
What's at the end of the road
which they are speeding down?
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita