December 31st, New Year's Eve.
Tonight was the night of King & Prince's
performance on a special stage.
I'm tired.
We saw you.
This year was really...
SHO HIRANO (AGE 22)
...a year where everything changed.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Wow!
JANUARY 17TH, 2018 CD DEBUT ANNOUNCEMENT
King & Prince's debut was announced
in January of 2018.
"You guys are debuting."
I thought it was a myth,
but it actually happened.
That marked the beginning
of a year of activity.
We'll take Sho and Genki.
Go!
They keep aiming for the top,
while searching for their originality.
I can't do such a typical idol pose.
I'm really not cut out to be an idol.
You have to say things
that'll make their hearts throb.
I really can't do that.
But they were determined...
YUTA KISHI (AGE 23)
...to do anything.
If it's for this role, I will do anything.
That's how determined I am.
Doing a funny face means nothing to me.
Cut. One more time.
YUTA JINGUJI (AGE 21)
They struggle to deliver
the high-quality work expected of them.
GENKI IWAHASHI (AGE 22)
Each of them searched for what
they could bring to the table.
KAITO TAKAHASHI (AGE 19)
My brain isn't functioning.
However, they were encouraged by
the people who support them.
REN NAGASE (AGE 20)
That's hot!
Delicious.
In what ways did they mature
during this year?
At the end and beginning of a year,
we follow them one more time
on their road to Tokyo Dome and Kohaku.
THE IMPERIAL THEATRE
December 30th.
The year is coming to an end.
Outside of the theater,
fans were creating a long line.
The show called Johnnys' Island,
which has been held every year,
will be crowned with King & Prince
for the first time.
2020 IS IN OUR HANDS
A total of more than
70 Johnny's Jr. members perform
in this approximately
two-month-long show.
There is singing.
There is dancing.
The youths mature into entertainers.
This is a stepping stone
that their countless
predecessors have treasured.
This time, the group to take
center stage is King & Prince.
We filmed them just two months ago.
The members have become so dependable.
One of them in particular has gained
a lot of experience,
through starring in several
drama series and movies. Sho Hirano.
Throughout this year,
Hirano has been moving at top speed.
It's no surprise he looks tired.
I am pretty busy. It's hectic.
This year was really
a productive year. That's the only word
that can describe it.
Ready...
JULY 2018 COMMERCIAL FILMING
Even when his schedule is packed,
Hirano's genuine personality shows
through his innocent smile.
He would also say things
you wouldn't expect from an idol.
Look at how I walk.
I look like an old man.
An idol shouldn't be
walking like this, actually.
I should be walking like this.
Hirano decided to become an idol
in elementary school.
He was able to work hard
because he wanted to help his mother.
I was raised by a single mother.
My mother almost died once.
I didn't want to make my mother sad,
so I felt like I had to
work hard at my job.
There's nothing here.
What left an impression was
what he said in his hometown of Nagoya.
SEPTEMBER 2018 NAGOYA
Was there anything you wanted to be
other than an idol?
So many things.
I like protecting people.
I wanted to go to
disaster areas and help out,
but I was told that...
even if I can't physically help them
by removing debris and whatnot,
people who see us on TV,
or in magazines, or at concerts
can be emotionally uplifted
and motivated to live another day.
That's why, at the end of concerts,
I often say, "Don't die."
Even if we couldn't make eye contact
at the concert,
I want everyone who is watching me
and who is connected with me
to stay alive. I really do.
The reason I'm continuing this job,
is because I want to
lift everyone's spirits.
All right.
How did Hirano deal with
the massive pressure that weighed down
on him this past year?
One, two, one, two.
His answer was unique.
Let's go!
Pressure... I didn't really feel it.
I guess I should have felt the pressure.
The agency would want me to.
Before a big performance,
they would tell me,
"We're counting on you!" pretty often.
Even during the shows,
they're constantly telling me,
"Please make it work"
and "We're counting on you to do this."
I get that a lot.
But I don't want to let those words
get me nervous.
I brush it off. I dodge their words.
I make sure that I'm putting in
one hundred percent, though.
In the show,
the one who played a fighting soldier
was Yuta Jinguji.
For him, this year was
a crucial turning point in his life.
TOYOKAWA INARI TOKYO BETSUIN
MOTOAKASAKA, TOKYO
Jinguji opened up about
his deepest thoughts
when we visited a certain temple.
That was really shocking for me.
I was 18 at the time.
That was the toughest time of my life.
When we didn't get offers.
If there's no work coming in
even though I'm willing,
I thought for a second,
that maybe I should quit.
MYOJO LIVE! 2015 SUMMER CONCERT ISSUE
The six of them formed a unit together
for the first time in 2015,
but from the following year,
they broke up into two units of three.
One unit caught people's
attention immediately.
However, the unit Jinguji was in
was left in the shadows.
Without work,
they were left feeling frustrated.
MYOJO LIVE! 2017 SUMMER CONCERT ISSUE
JUNE 2018 MOVIE FILMING
That is why, when it was decided that
the six of them were going to debut,
he swore to do anything it took.
Cut.
When he was filming a movie,
he was repeatedly told to retake
one scene for over two hours.
What has supported Jinguji
during this past year?
Since we were the ones who told
Mr. Johnny that we wanted to debut,
of course I felt
the responsibility and pressure.
What if...
What if our CDs don't sell?
What if we don't live up
to their expectations?
I did worry about that.
Mr. Johnny created us,
so I felt the pressure
of not wanting to put him to shame.
But now, those thoughts don't even
cross my mind anymore, because our fans
are so supportive of us.
Now, all I can think about
is how I can give back.
I want to give back to them.
Supporting the group
with similar feelings to Jinguji
were the two youngest members,
Ren Nagase
and Kaito Takahashi.
These two met up with their mentors
who gave them courage.
SEPTEMBER 2018 OSAKA
During his brief time off,
Nagase headed toward Osaka,
where he spent
his middle and high school years.
This is also where I joined Johnny's,
so I see this city as my birthplace
as a Johnny's member.
My personality
was shaped here in Osaka as well.
There he is.
Long time no see.
He met up with his homeroom teacher
from middle school, Mr. Ukon.
When Nagase was unsure about his future,
he was there to give encouragement.
He was worrying about it
more than anyone else.
You wanted to either study
or work in the entertainment industry.
Because my grades were pretty good.
That's right. You weren't sure.
I thought it would be a waste.
I thought that if I chose
while I was young,
I'd still have time to start over again.
You've grown up so much.
It's the fans.
Seriously, it's all thanks to them.
I mean...
When the fans cheer for us
during our concerts,
-it honestly feels really great.
-I see.
It feels better than you'd imagine.
You came so close, remember?
And during your performance,
you waved at me.
When I called out your name,
Then the fans around me
started screaming,
but inside, I was thinking,
"No, he's waving at me!"
There are people who are
watching over him from afar.
Meanwhile, in a previous interview,
Takahashi had said this...
I just don't have a lot of
self-confidence.
That's how I am.
It was decided in January.
I was worried if I could
handle all the pressure.
Tears just began to stream down.
Long time no see.
One person who gave Takahashi courage
was his high school teacher, Mr. Nakao.
TEACHER TADASHI NAKAO
He always knew when I was tired.
He could tell if I was up late at night.
Every day, I would talk to him
about my work,
as if I was reporting to him.
That's right. You did that a lot.
You would tell me your plans for the day.
And what I did that day.
What made Takahashi the happiest
was a gift from his teacher.
Wow!
LAUGHTER, APPRECIATION
I'm so happy.
Oh, wow!
One second.
When I went to your place,
you gave me one.
I brought it. Now I have a complete set.
HARD WORK PAYS OFF
KAITO TAKAHASHI
They have a magical power.
It makes me realize that
it's important for me
to always be smiling.
That's what an idol is to me.
With those words ingrained in his heart,
how did he survive this past year?
Days off? Ever since I started
performing at the theater
I haven't had a single day off.
Yeah, not a single day.
But I feel like I can be myself
when I'm working
more than when I'm not.
I want to spend more time
with the other members.
I want to talk more with the staff too.
Time has turned the young boy
who was constantly crying
into someone so dependable.
Nagase, on the other hand...
It went by so fast.
It felt like seconds.
I made so many memories, of course.
I made so many memories,
I can't choose the best one.
So, it was productive.
But time flies when
you're having fun, you know?
That's why this year felt so short.
I wanted the year
to pass by quickly, though.
-Really?
-Yes.
Why?
Because I'm 19.
I'll be able to do a lot more
when I turn 20.
That's my only reason.
It's super personal.
DECEMBER 31ST, 2018 TOKYO DOME
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN REHEARSAL
December 31st is finally here.
We'll be in your care.
This day's schedule
begins with the rehearsal
for the countdown concert
which they'll perform with their seniors.
After that, they will perform
at NHK's Kohaku Uta Gassen.
They will then return to Tokyo Dome
for the New Year's live broadcast.
On this celebratory day,
there was a man with a serious face.
Yuta Kishi.
As they keep rising in popularity,
he was calmly reflecting on the past year
and their future with him as the leader.
We experienced so many things
for the first time.
We had new experiences
and worked with people
who we never worked with before.
Everything was new to us.
Of course, trying new things
sometimes led to discouragement.
And... I would learn new things
and become downhearted.
Everyone feels...
downhearted at times, you know?
Like when I'm invited on a show,
but I fail to make everyone laugh.
That happens very often.
I feel under pressure
for any job, honestly.
But I feel like this is
to be expected now that
we've debuted.
Having a busy schedule
is something we are grateful for.
It's an honor
to be able to work as a group.
But you know...
we can't expect it
to be like this forever.
What we need to do at the moment
is to give everything our best.
We just have to try our best
to deliver what is expected of us.
Yeah...
As a group, I hope we can become
the type of people
who can go above and beyond
people's expectations.
DECEMBER 31ST, 2018
BEFORE THE PERFORMANCE
It was finally time to perform
on the stage of their dreams, Kohaku.
We're excited, but nervous
at the same time.
-Let's go.
-Here we go.
I'll do my best in the Kid's Corner.
Focus on "Cinderella Girl."
DECEMBER 31ST, 2018 TOKYO DOME
December 31st.
They've completed their mission on Kohaku
and it is now 11 p.m.
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2018-2019
1:30 TO LIVE BROADCAST
Another stage King & Prince has dreamed
of performing on,
the Countdown Concert was about to begin.
We have five seconds.
Here they are!
-Hello.
-They're here.
Are you King or Prince?
Here are some behind-the-scenes footage
from before the live broadcast.
You're not Tetsu and Tomo?
No, we're not.
You got the "and" part.
Oh, really?
Do your best!
-Yes!
-Remember, you're the opening act.
Yes!
Form a huddle.
-Yes!
-You should.
King & Prince!
When's our cue?
-Sorry.
-Give us a cue.
King & Prince!
LIVE BROADCAST BEGINS
The live New Year's broadcast
has finally begun.
Until last year,
performing here was just a dream.
This year, they're singing
as the opening act.
At this moment, the five of them
were determined to perform for their fans
on behalf of one member
who couldn't be there.
That determination was apparent
when we asked Takahashi
about the group's future.
We are who we are,
when the six of us are together.
Six people make up King & Prince.
The member who was the most committed
to being an idol.
At the moment,
he is getting treatment for his illness.
There's no more beef tongue chili paste.
Despite his illness, he has been
supporting the group
with a smile on his face
from before their debut
to their first concert tour.
You can have the oil.
I'll do it.
Not the chili.
-Why not?
-Not the chili.
All right.
Iwahashi had one wish...
I hope we can all stay friends.
That will always show in our performances.
I hope we always stay aware of the fact
that we represent King & Prince,
and never forget to show
appreciation and respect.
I hope that we can
keep on living like that from now on too.
If we do that,
we will always know what we need.
NHK KOHAKU UTA GASSEN
AFTER THE PERFORMANCE
Thinking of Iwahashi,
on the stage of Kohaku,
they had a spotlight shine
where he would've stood
and sang as the sixth man.
I got a message from him.
-Really?
-Yeah.
He said, "Thank you for including me."
About the spotlight.
He sent a photo and said
he was on stage with us.
-So he was watching it live?
-Yes.
-He was watching.
-That made me happy.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
-Here we go.
King & Prince's journey has just begun.
What kind of dreams
will they chase after this year?
Nice to meet you!
We are Kansai Johnny's Jr.!
On the next Ride On Time...
We're Kansai Johnny's Jr.
Osaka's hugely popular
Kansai Johnny's Jr. will be on.
You own a pet, right?
It died.
They range from kids
in elementary school to men in their 20s
and total over 50 people.
They all support each other
and diligently aim for the top.
Last year, a unit called Naniwa Danshi
was formed from there.
It's a turning point for them.
I think it's an opportunity.
A month-long residency
at a traditional theater
and a two-day arena concert.
The rising anticipation.
A large knife!
The encouragement from their seniors.
KANJANI∞, TADAYOSHI OHKURA
What lies beyond their hard work?
Yeah!
-Here we go!
-Yeah!
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita