MUSASHINO FOREST SPORTS PLAZA MAIN ARENA
August 31st.
The first day of Hey! Say! JUMP's
concert tour is about to begin.
-Did everyone stretch?
-First day!
Yes, we did.
Channel your nerves into energy.
Be careful not to injure yourself.
That's right.
-Okay.
-Keep control.
Right!
Let's go.
All right!
Four youths are nervously
watching over the members.
They've faced many challenges
while working toward this day.
-Hey.
-Yes.
-Come here.
-Yes, sir.
I feel like I could've done more.
But it's difficult.
I'm constantly exhausted.
I'm anxious and not sure what to do.
I'm very worried.
It's spilling.
There's been some trouble,
which has set us back.
I've never been this nervous before.
This is a story of youths
working on the sidelines
to support the center stage.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
It happened one evening,
as they were preparing for
the tour's opening day.
The staff members were faced with trouble.
A piece of equipment that's used for
attaching lights and special effects,
called a rounded truss,
could not be raised up.
ROUNDED TRUSS
It might be the weight.
STAGE FACILITATOR
MASAHIRO UEDA (AGE 27)
The calculation should be correct, but...
it's overweight and won't go up.
Ueda, the rookie stage facilitator,
stands still in shock.
SPECIAL EFFECTS
MICHIRU YABE (AGE 21)
But feeling even more overwhelmed,
was Yabe from the special effects team.
-Take down two units.
-Two units?
Yes.
The piece of equipment that had to be
taken down is called the scroller.
SCROLLER
It's a device that hangs up above
and scatters gold and silver confetti.
This scroller is what helped Yabe
to overcome setbacks
and choose this line of work.
Will they be able to use the scroller?
What is causing this trouble?
The stage manager takes command,
and they decide to take down
two of the four scrollers.
But...
It's not working.
It stopped.
We took down 100 kilos.
Yabe's boss, Nikami, looks worried.
SPECIAL EFFECTS CHIEF OPERATOR
ASAKI NIKAMI
Remove them all.
And then...
-Special effects!
-We're taking them all down?
We'll try taking them down once.
They will take all the scrollers down.
Without the scrollers,
they can't rain confetti onto the stage.
For Yabe, there is nothing
more disappointing than that.
MICHIRU YABE
Yabe learned to play the piano
at a young age,
and from junior high she played
the saxophone in the school band club.
She dreamed of a career in music.
But it was a competitive world...
I aspired to be a musician,
but everyone around me was so much better
that I felt overwhelmed.
Becoming a professional
requires a lot of determination,
and even as a professional,
you're on your own as a solo artist.
My will alone
was not enough.
I was faced with the harsh reality
of the music business.
That's when she came across a new dream.
Everybody jump.
NATIONWIDE TOUR 2013
It was at the Hey! Say! JUMP dome concert.
The extensive stage production
captured her heart.
It was my first year of high school,
and I tagged along with my friend
who had front row seats.
That was my very first concert.
It was unreal. I saw fire and other
special effects right in front of me.
I have to say...
the most memorable part
was when the silver streamers
came down, and everyone...
reached out to grab them.
That left a big impression on me,
and it made me want to take part in
creating something like that.
It was all I could think about
at that moment.
Yabe went to vocational school,
studied stage production,
and began working at
a special effects company.
Will she be able to fulfill her dream
and rain confetti onto the stage?
Day two of setting up.
SPECIAL EFFECTS
When Yabe and her special effects team
arrived at the venue...
The structure had been raised up
with four scrollers attached to it.
Apparently, the motor that lifts the truss
was set at the incorrect voltage.
This morning they re-wired everything,
and it went up.
I've done it three or four times now.
SPECIAL EFFECTS CHIEF OPERATOR
ASAKI NIKAMI
They feel relieved,
but there's no time to rest.
Where's the Viper?
To gain more responsibility,
she must learn to master many more
techniques and types of equipment.
This is a piece of equipment
called the Viper.
VIPER
A Viper...
creates smoke.
What kind of smoke does it produce?
It's a water-based smoke.
Usually, when the artists are dancing,
this smoke covers
the surface of the stage
to create a nice atmosphere.
You can also emit a large amount of smoke
all at once to momentarily hide someone.
There are many ways to use it.
VIPER
Various special effects
can either surprise an audience
or engulf them in a mystical atmosphere.
To create this special effect,
Yabe tirelessly connects
the cables together.
There are pieces of equipment
that I'm using
for the very first time.
Learning about new equipment while
on the road for a long period of time,
can be emotionally
and physically draining.
But when I complete this tour,
I hope I'll have become more experienced.
Regarding the rookie,
her senior Nikami says...
Although she's a new recruit,
she takes initiative,
and she's very proactive.
So as a second-year recruit,
she's doing very well.
Sometimes she's absent-minded,
but that can be resolved with
time and experience.
She once dreamed of being center stage.
But now she faces the future
with a helmet on.
The bright world of entertainment
is supported by people like her.
There's 24 hours until rehearsal begins.
Masahiro Ueda, the stage facilitator.
During the tour, he's in charge of
looking after the members
and managing their safety,
but he's still a rookie
with only three months of experience.
He studied computers in vocational school
but started working here as a part-timer.
Eleven in the morning.
Ueda is below the stage,
setting up a quick-change room
for the Hey! Say! JUMP members.
Okay.
If some areas are difficult to maneuver,
you can fold it over.
This is where the members come
for a quick costume change.
We're laying down the cover.
Can you spread it out a little more?
Helping the artists, so they can perform
on stage without anxiety,
directly affects the quality
of the concert.
STAGE FACILITATOR
KEIKO OKABAYASHI
What they need is the power
to discern what is required of them
in the moment.
There are eight members,
but each one
is different in height
and body shape.
Since I'm not tall myself,
I never gave it much thought,
but there may be obstacles overhead
that could harm certain members.
So I put myself in every member's shoes
as I walk below the stage,
searching for any possible hazards.
I feel like I gave it a lot of thought
and did my best
in that area.
Ueda and his co-worker
are having difficulty making a decision.
How high should it be? Two hakoba?
HAKOBA: WOODEN BOXES USED TO
ALTER STAGE HEIGHT
They will have to bend down
like this, right?
It's so low.
That's too obvious.
They constantly think of the members.
We were planning to place a basket here
where the performers can return
their glow sticks.
We're deciding on the height
of the basket.
Why do they put so much thought
into the smallest details?
They're thinking of the members
and the compatibility
with the stage production.
For example, here,
they're singing with glow sticks,
but during the interlude,
they place them back in the basket.
Please turn off your glow sticks.
Then, when I give the signal,
turn them on starting from the front row.
If the basket is too low,
the members must bend down.
But if it's too high,
it becomes visible to the audience,
and will pull them back to reality.
Having it higher makes it
easier to access,
yet it can't be too visible.
But it also can't burden the members.
They continue experimenting.
Should we get the wooden planks
and use that to adjust the height?
Okay.
Let's try adjusting the height.
There's a saying that goes,
"God is in the details."
The experienced members know that
attention to detail makes miracles happen.
We need to be flexible,
since we have to make decisions
in varying circumstances.
That's something I need to work on,
as well as quick thinking skills,
since I can't understand things sometimes.
We need to secure the runway tracks.
Can you do that when you're
marking the stage?
-With the arrows?
-Yes, that's right.
Okay. I understand.
Perfect.
Let's go.
There are many staff members
inside the arena who channel their passion
into this detailed work.
It's hard work, but they take pride in it.
As the time for rehearsal with
Hey! Say! JUMP nears,
SPECIAL MECHANICS
SHOICHIRO FUKUDA (AGE 24)
Shoichiro Fukuda from
the special mechanics team
is finalizing his work.
They must construct a complex stage
that moves up, down, and rotates around.
All the team members
begin to construct the center stage
in the middle of the arena.
Right now, we're setting up
the base of the stage
called the turntable.
This causes the whole stage
to spin around.
This stage is essential for this concert.
It spins 360 degrees,
allowing the audience to view
the members from all angles.
We're checking to see if it spins.
Heavy equipment will be placed on top,
so we need to make sure the turntable
works beforehand.
Stop.
Can you spin it the other way now?
Does it look okay?
Yes.
To complete the turntable,
we first cover it with veneer,
and then we will start
attaching more parts to it.
Eleven lifting apparatus called lifters
will be installed on the center stage.
LIFTER
Combining the movements of
all eleven lifters
creates a dynamic stage production,
which is a highlight
of the concert this time.
It's over a ton.
Is there any way we can connect
these boards together?
Each lifter weighs over a ton.
Fukuda was placed in charge
of the lifters.
Ready, set, go.
Is it okay?
Okay, stop.
Moving heavy equipment by hand
is potentially dangerous,
so tension is running high.
Insert the bolt with the ratchet.
Okay.
We'll start with Fukuda's side.
Don't smash your finger.
It's your finger, not mine.
-Ready?
-Yes.
A little more.
Okay.
In college, Fukuda was studying economics.
But he wanted a job
where he could create something
to gain a sense of accomplishment.
So, he chose this career.
I was interested in work
that's done behind the scenes.
I used to play music...
So I started searching for something
that was related to concerts
or live music performances.
That's how I started this job.
In high school I played wind instruments,
and during college I was into jazz.
Right now, I'm so busy that I have
no time to play music.
What does Fukuda's superior
think about his job performance?
SUB CHIEF OPERATOR
MASAKI YAMANAKA
As his senior?
He's a hard worker. But inexperienced.
I want him to gain experience.
Difficulties?
What's exhausting?
Well, I feel like
everything is exhausting.
I'm constantly exhausted.
But I've never wanted to quit.
Maybe that's why I'm still here.
SOUND
The sound team is finalizing
their work as well.
One of the young workers is Kuramochi.
Sequence is okay.
This is the first time
he has been appointed as the stage chief.
He sets up the instruments
the members will be using
and passes the microphones during
the concert.
This job doesn't allow room for error.
I used to play instruments
and was also in a band club
a long time ago.
I liked playing instruments,
but I was more fascinated with
the sound itself.
It amazed me
how sound has the ability
to stir up emotions.
I was wondering if there
was a job that would
allow me to do what I like,
and work with sound.
That's when I came across this job
as a sound technician for concerts.
That's why I chose this job.
Under the stage, Kuramochi started
a meeting with the stage facilitator team.
This is the quick changing area?
Yes.
The areas with fluorescent lights.
Is that okay?
Absolutely.
Over here...
He's searching for a place to hold
the sound equipment
that'll be used during the concert.
With quick-change rooms set up,
space under the stage is limited,
so he must plan out his course
with the stage facilitation team.
She's from the stage facilitation team,
so she knows the entire set up,
and makes sure everything runs smoothly.
We would ask her
where things can be set up,
or when we need an extra hand,
we'd ask her to send us a helper.
That's the process.
We can't do anything without that team.
Teamwork is what makes a concert happen.
TEAMWORK
That's why each team strives
for perfection.
That is how the venue is constructed.
They conduct final adjustments
right up until the very last minute.
Even though these four youths
are inexperienced,
they're still expected
to work like professionals.
I'm nervous. I have to do what I can.
Starting tomorrow,
the members of Hey! Say! JUMP
will arrive to start the rehearsal.
SETTING UP
DAY 3
August 30th.
The members of Hey! Say! JUMP
are going to arrive for rehearsal.
During this one practice,
they must verify the entire flow
of the concert.
Once the members arrive,
and they grasp
the general flow of the concert,
we will do a dress rehearsal
and run through the entire program
like it's the actual show.
So today is the day when
a lot of things will be set in stone,
and a lot of things that were
already set will change too.
So it will actually be a lot busier
than the day of the actual concert.
That's how it is.
I don't have a clear picture
of the end result,
so we'll make adjustments
once it's all set in place.
Yesterday,
the lifter had some technical issues,
but we were able to fix that today
and now it's working well,
so everything is okay.
Everything is last minute.
We don't have a lot of time left.
We're in a rush.
Although these four youths have
different job descriptions and positions,
they have the same goal.
They want to provide a great concert
for the audience.
That's their one wish.
It's 1:30 p.m.
The members of
Hey! Say! JUMP have arrived.
Good morning, Hey! Say! JUMP.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
This is the rehearsal for
the first day of the 2018 tour
in Musashino Arena.
Let's all work hard.
The countdown to
the main event won't stop.
There's one more day
until the first day of the concert.
I create situations that I know
people will want to take pictures of.
It's kindness.
It's rather difficult.
Today?
I'm just simply tired.
On the next Ride On Time,
the rehearsal officially begins.
The four young concert staff members
face an emergency situation.
Will they be able to welcome
the opening day with a smile?
Subtitle translation by Lili Morita