"This is a record of youths
who devoted their adolescence
to entertainment."
Since their debut in May, King & Prince
have been basking in the spotlight.
However, each of them has experienced
various trials on their road to success.
The days when they were
desperate for work.
That was really shocking for me.
I was 18 at the time.
We hit rock bottom.
The disappointment of
being overtaken by a younger generation.
He surpassed me and others.
I was speechless.
I was a complete mess.
And even now, after their debut,
there are members
who are facing inner struggles.
When I think about what would've happened
if I didn't join Johnny's
and gave up on
becoming a pro, it scares me.
Only people who've gone through it
would understand.
Iwahashi was doing his best
to suppress his deepest emotions.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
The six of them have begun preparing
for their first concert tour.
-I can do that.
-We can try keeping a distance.
Want to try it once?
They rehearse
during the little time that they have.
But as they do, disagreements
begin to rise among the members.
Listen.
You've got to listen.
It was Iwahashi who lost his temper.
Take it seriously.
If you can't take it seriously, just quit.
What happened to Iwahashi and Jinguji?
With their first concert tour coming up,
can the six of them restore their bond?
SHINKIBA, TOKYO
Ready.
In late June, they were doing
a photoshoot for the merchandise
for their first concert tour.
Okay.
-Now, let's do a serious look.
-Okay.
It's hot today. I'm sweating.
He had just finished
filming a drama series.
Are you getting rest?
Somewhat, I guess.
I don't have any free time, though.
I haven't been able to
go out to eat or anything like that.
I guess the schedule was...
pushed back. Everyone was pretty busy.
Next, we'll take photos
for the tour pamphlet.
His busy schedule as an idol
has made him resilient.
Here is Genki Iwahashi, a man who is
strongly committed to being an idol.
He has a remarkably strong
sense of responsibility
as a member of King & Prince.
During the photoshoot, Iwahashi opened up
about his feelings toward the group.
If the six of us...
appear on music shows
or perform at concerts,
and all of us are shining,
the audience will begin to lose interest.
When the six of us
are together, I think about
how everyone else will shine
and how I can help them shine.
Iwahashi's resolve is so strong
at just 21 years of age.
Iwahashi joined the agency
in his 2nd year of junior high.
His sweet, androgynous appearance
instantly caught people's attention.
By the time he was in the unit Prince
with Kishi and Jinguji,
his popularity had brought him to
first place on the list of
"Johnny's Jr. members you'd want
as a boyfriend" for five years straight.
As a Johnny's Jr. member,
that was my biggest claim to fame,
but it's nothing more than
a past achievement.
But at the same time,
I am very honored that I was ranked
first place in those boyfriend rankings.
I couldn't be more honored.
And so, now that we're a group,
I want to make the five of them shine
and make our group even bigger,
so that we can provide all sorts of
entertainment to the people
who have been supporting us.
That is how I want to repay them.
You'll get a tan.
-I don't mind.
-You don't?
It's okay.
Iwahashi's feelings toward the group
will end up manifesting
in an unexpected way.
TOKYO
July.
-Good morning.
It is finally time
for the concert tour rehearsal.
Good morning.
On this day, something that the members
were waiting for was revealed.
-Oh, wow!
-Amazing.
-It's so cool.
-The inside will have a damaged look.
The stage costumes were
designed according to each member.
These pants are really cute.
Even the stage design is massive,
something unheard of for a new group.
You're here. Can you see your color?
More than ten thousand fans
will fill this arena.
For "Ho! Summer"...
All six of them must memorize
their own movements.
During the chorus, you will move here.
They only explain it once.
No one asks for him to repeat it.
Hirano, you'll come down here briefly...
-and then return.
-Understood.
It's like this each time. Even if you
don't know, you say "Understood"
and memorize it as you go.
At Johnny's, things move along
at a very fast pace.
We've gotten used to that.
This is the result of that.
Speed is everything.
That goes for dancing as well.
Their brand-new song
that they just received
still had no dance routine.
However, in just a few days
they've come this far.
Stay in the line!
The centrifugal force
is really strong for me.
From the last chorus.
In the worst-case scenario,
we memorize it the day of.
We get the routine that day
and go up on stage.
They teach you the routine once,
and you have to be able to dance it
by the next time they play the song.
We've been trained like that
since we were in Johnny's Jr.
We memorize like our lives depend on it,
and that's why it's possible.
If you can't memorize the routine quickly,
you can't survive here.
You have to respond instantly.
Good morning.
However, a few days later,
a problem will arise during the rehearsal.
It doesn't hurt!
On this day, they had finished
rehearsing most of their songs,
and the atmosphere was relaxed.
During the first chorus...
Even when deciding
who will be singing what line...
Exit the stage during the chorus.
Hey, let's focus, guys.
Okay, I'll assign the parts.
Someone was concerned
about this atmosphere.
That someone was Iwahashi,
who was here despite having a sore throat
and feeling under the weather.
Just then, the three members of Prince,
Kishi, Jinguji, and Iwahashi,
were told to correct their routine.
During the verse of "Summer Station"
when Prince turns around,
Kishi and Jinguji have the numbers wrong.
In "Summer Station"?
Prince's three members were called.
This is number one.
They must correct it quickly.
You were off to the side.
I made it!
There's a somewhat laid-back atmosphere.
Wait, what part are we doing?
The part where you wait
with your backs turned.
No, I'm zero.
Really? Oh, it goes like that?
As Iwahashi shows him the moves,
he seems a bit irritated.
Listen.
You've got to listen.
Cut it out.
During the introduction dance...
And in time...
What's your problem?
Something about Jinguji
was irritating Iwahashi.
The other members can only watch.
What was he angry about?
You're off doing your own thing.
I'm telling you,
but you won't even listen.
That's why you still don't get it,
and you're laughing it off.
It's been happening a lot lately,
and I've been holding it in.
I lost my temper, and that wasn't right.
But if you're a member of this group,
you have to get it together.
Jinguji was doing his best
to take in Iwahashi's words.
They joined the agency
on exactly the same day
and are called Jiguiwa by their fans.
They are like brothers.
In Johnny's Jr.,
they were both part of Prince.
As Mr. King kept rising in popularity,
both of them shared the same
frustration and trials
as they pursued the same goal.
Iwahashi may have
chosen to speak up about
the laid-back atmosphere to Jinguji,
because he trusts him.
And the one who knows that the most
is Jinguji himself.
Genki's the only person
who can say that kind of thing to me.
Oh, really?
Have you seen him talk
that way to anyone else?
-I guess not.
-Right?
He can only speak up about it to me.
Genki is the type of person
who overthinks things.
Unlike me.
He has a lot of pent-up stress
from all those thoughts in his mind,
I think.
Jinguji knows
about Iwahashi's suffering.
Iwahashi opened up about it
while strolling around Tokyo Dome,
a place where he has
always longed to perform.
It's so hot.
It started with the bitter experience
he went through in third grade.
They'd ask,
"Why doesn't he come to school?"
or "Why does he get special treatment?"
and I would get bullied.
That kept me
from going to school even more,
so I stopped going altogether.
Iwahashi was actually diagnosed
with a sickness
when he was a child.
As a result, he would miss school
and was even bullied.
Iwahashi finally felt like he belonged
when standing on the stage as an idol.
It was because he was able to
become a different version of himself.
To tell you the truth,
I have always suffered from
something called panic disorder.
When I'm put in a situation
where I can't escape
or I don't know what to do,
I lose control of my emotions.
The only one
who knows about it is Jinguji.
I've been saved by him before.
I don't know when this will go away,
so I think of it as something
I will carry with me forever.
Finding how I can express myself
while living with this disorder
is a personal struggle of mine right now.
That's why,
I could never go up on stage
as the Genki Iwahashi that I am right now,
the way I am on my days off.
I can only show
the idol version of myself.
Or else, I'll have a panic attack.
But in a way, instead of hiding it,
talking about it like this
makes me feel better.
I want to perform here one day.
Another member talks about his struggles
at a place memorable to him.
As the concert date approaches,
they continue to rehearse.
Dance in front of me.
Even after they run through it as a group,
one member stays to rehearse by himself.
Spin.
It's Ren Nagase.
I'll be wearing a lot of fur.
It's really bulky.
Then just graze the fur.
On top of it, like this.
Nagase is determined
to fulfill his duty as an idol,
since it is the job that he chose himself.
During the concert merchandise photoshoot,
he would check each photo.
Thank you.
It affects the sales.
Are you making sure, as an idol,
that you look good in the photo?
Wouldn't you want to look good?
I get a sense
of what angle looks best
when I look at it.
That's what I check for.
I'm a professional.
Let's leave it at that.
Nagase also had to overcome
his own struggles
in order to stand here today.
He grew up in a family
that had to move constantly.
Since childhood,
he would transfer schools often.
The pain that came from
parting with his friends
led him to put up emotional walls.
Johnny's was where Nagase
was able to build precious friendships.
However, during junior high,
he was contemplating
whether to stay an idol
or return to being a normal student.
OSAKA
At the time, he was living in Osaka.
This is also where I joined Johnny's,
so I see this city as my birthplace
as a Johnny's member.
My personality
was shaped here in Osaka as well.
Of course, being able to
spend all three years
of junior high
in the same school until graduation
had a big effect on me.
He wanted to meet the people
who supported him during those times.
-Yes?
-There he is.
-Long time no see.
-How have you been?
-I'm great.
-So I hear.
-Thank you.
-Come in.
What a nice house.
For all three years of junior high,
his teacher was Mr. Ukon.
When Nagase was contemplating
about his future,
he was always by his side.
He was worrying about it
more than anyone else.
He wanted to choose the right high school.
He didn't want any regrets.
He thought about that
more than anyone else.
I looked up schools
that were understanding of his work,
but I remember him saying no.
You wanted to either study
or work in the entertainment industry.
Because my grades were pretty good.
That's right.
-You weren't sure.
-I thought it would be a waste.
Well, I ended up going
to a school that was
understanding of my work.
You did.
I thought that if I chose
while I was young,
I'd still have time to start over again.
I had that mentality already.
At the time,
I probably wanted to choose, early on,
whether to lead a normal life
or continue working
in the entertainment industry.
-Out of everyone, he had the hardest time.
-Oh, yeah?
-He would do his own research and such.
-I did!
He searched for places where
he could balance both work and school.
You also felt like you were
causing your parents trouble.
So, you wanted to carefully decide
between working in entertainment
and focusing on studying.
That's right.
You've grown up so much.
But it's just begun.
I have to work hard from here.
And there's one more thing
that supported Nagase.
WE'RE OPEN, WELCOME!
His best friends from Osaka.
"Handsome men eat for free,"
so I always ate for free.
Long time no see!
-Welcome back.
-Long time no see.
Good to see you. Welcome back.
This is Nishiyama, his classmate,
and his family-owned
okonomiyaki restaurant.
When he was in junior high school,
he ate here almost every day.
I want oden too, later.
Have you found someone?
-No.
-Come on!
-Find someone!
-I'm glad I didn't.
I would've had to say their name.
I would've asked for a photo.
Or else I wouldn't go home.
College is like that, isn't it?
I know, it's like that for me too.
Spending time with friends
just like those days.
What a luxurious time.
Delicious.
They would come after school
and eat here
before going home all the time.
Tell me if you want anything.
I remember your birthday.
-What?
-It's early in the year, right?
-You're February, right?
-Yeah.
-That's all I know.
-The 15th.
Right, it's near Valentine's.
What about me?
-January 23rd.
-Wow.
You remembered it was near Valentine's.
What a random conversation.
It's a rare sight.
-Hey!
-Where's Kazuya?
More friends have come over.
-You're late! Where's Kazuya?
-Sorry. Kazuya's over there.
Kazuya, run! Hurry up.
Long time no see.
How nostalgic.
ODEN
50 YEN
-You should come to Tokyo.
-He does go.
I went the day before yesterday.
-Yeah, he did go.
-Seriously?
-By train, it's 15 hours one way.
-What do you mean?
-It's torture.
-You took the regular train?
-Not the bullet train?
-I'm poor.
That's why?
But still...
He buys the Seishun 18 ticket.
-You're not 18.
-Yeah, but you can still buy it.
You can?
-Our youth is over.
-It never came.
They're still 19.
He engraved into his heart
the emotions that are
easily forgotten in the limelight.
All three of you should come to Tokyo.
-I want to go.
-You don't have school right now, right?
-Just for a day.
-It's torture.
-Let's go!
-Eight hours one way.
I'll be all alone!
On the next Ride On Time...
Their concert tour has finally begun.
-What is this?
-This will hurt.
They are completely worn out,
but they keep performing.
When my eyes turn like this,
it's very bad.
Excuse me.
A brief moment with his mentor.
That's what an idol is to me.
Thank you for your work.
Here we go!
It's time for their last stop on the tour.
Bye.
What is it that awaits them?
-Thank you!
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita