"This is a record of youths
who devoted their adolescence
to entertainment."
Say cheese!
-You guys are the best.
-My hands are wet.
Hey, Takahashi!
Sorry, sorry. I'm really sorry.
You're late again.
-What are you carrying chocolates for?
-I'm sorry.
Never mind, they're filming.
-Forget that they're filming.
-Why?
Because these candid scenes
make this documentary.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
From this day forward,
their lives changed drastically.
We'll be in your care.
I give you the members of Mr. King.
Johnny & Associates, Inc's
first group to debut in four years.
I give you the members of Mr. Prince.
Their name is King & Prince.
"You guys are debuting."
I thought it was a myth,
but it actually happened.
This is a documentary
covering a span of eight months.
Their real selves...
You scared me.
I'm not a classic idol,
so I was unsure and hesitant.
I can't do such a typical idol pose.
The pressure...
I was worried if I could
handle all the pressure.
Tears just began to stream down.
THE PASSION
Cut it out.
Strong emotions clash.
We may be idols, but we're still human.
At times we get annoyed,
and at times we get mad.
Whether it's my fault or not,
he needs to get over it.
THE CHALLENGE
Constantly taking up challenges.
If I keep at it,
I feel like I can reach my goal.
I'm trying to absorb every single thing.
Everything is an opportunity to learn.
AUG. 10TH, 2018
YOKOHAMA ARENA
Like that,
they reached their big performance.
What were their battles
and what are they trying to overcome?
For the next four weeks,
we'll show you the footsteps
of King & Prince.
We are...
King & Prince!
MARCH 15, 2018
ROPPONGI, TOKYO
March 15th.
On this day, these six
reached a special milestone.
Can I say it?
Let's do it.
The title of our debut song
is "Cinderella Girl"!
"CINDERELLA GIRL" WILL BE RELEASED!!
Scheduled to be released in May,
this would mark their official debut.
With nervousness showing on their faces,
they spoke about their feelings.
In a sense, we're vowing to
dedicate our entire lives.
It's kind of like getting married.
-Don't you think?
-True.
We're getting married?
It's basically the same thing.
I mean, we'll always be together.
RAY MAGAZINE PHOTO SHOOT
SHINJUKU, TOKYO
Hello.
Let's briefly introduce
each of their characters.
Good morning.
We'll start with the one who likened
the forming of their group to marriage.
I like to use two razors.
YUTA KISHI (AGE 23)
Yuta Kishi.
In this group of six with an average
age of 20, he is the leader.
GENKI IWAHASHI (AGE 21)
Genki Iwahashi.
He is strongly committed to being an idol
and is popular for his androgynous charm.
It's amazing. I can do this.
KAITO TAKAHASHI (AGE 19)
Kaito Takahashi.
He's the youngest of the group,
and everyone's innocent younger brother.
Only when I don't have work.
On your days off?
Yuta Jinguji,
the always calm, grey eminence
of the group.
Was it Iceland?
That game...
Ren Nagase,
the one who takes on the emcee role
with his light Kansai accent.
No, no, no.
And the one who takes
center stage in the group,
Nagoya native, Sho Hirano.
Despite his attractive looks,
he has a rather ditzy personality.
That contrast has been
attracting many fans.
But today, he seems exhausted.
That may happen.
What does he want the most right now?
About 50% of me just wants to sleep.
For the other 50%,
I don't know what I want.
Maybe I want to go to the countryside
or go to Nagoya.
Sleeping in Nagoya is different
from sleeping in Tokyo.
I feel like I get
a really good night's sleep.
Wake up, Sho.
None of us are really like that.
He was exhausted because...
Maybe Genki.
HANA NOCHI HARE DRAMA FILMING
EBISU, TOKYO
...he was starring in a drama series
which had begun filming in April.
It is the last day
of his four-month shoot.
-Good morning.
-Oh, good morning. Thanks for coming.
Thank you.
He was playing the role of a boy
who is a charismatic leader at school,
but is actually a coward on the inside.
I hear you were filming until midnight.
Yesterday, we were scheduled
until two o'clock,
but we wrapped up early
and finished at around twelve o'clock.
But that's still very late.
Sometimes we would film
until five o'clock.
And that was normal.
But despite that fact,
I'm sad that it'll be over.
Even though it was tiring.
It's not done yet, though.
Ready, action.
At last, it's his final scene.
That day...
When I met him...
Cut.
Look.
Sho, it's too soon for that.
I'm not!
It's Sugi's fault.
That was the final scene.
We survived this heavy schedule
thanks to you.
Thank you!
He went from coward to king.
It's a wrap for Haruto Kaguragi,
played by Sho Hirano.
It's a wrap!
Thank you.
I'm really sad,
and I don't know what
I'm supposed to do from tomorrow.
That's how much
it has become a part of my life.
At first, I was really nervous about
working among actors and actresses,
and I wasn't sure
if I was the best choice,
but here I am today.
Thank you all for the past four months.
Thank you!
Where do I keep it?
Are flowers refrigerated?
Um, flowers are...
I don't know where to put them!
Your fridge must be huge.
MYOJO MAGAZINE PHOTO SHOOT
KANDA, TOKYO
There is another side to Hirano.
We'll take Sho and Genki together.
Then, we'll take all six of you.
During a photo shoot
for an idol magazine...
I'm still doing this at 21?
How long will I keep doing this?
How tiring!
It looks good on you.
You were saying,
"How long will I keep doing this?"
You think about that often?
I do.
I'm really not cut out to be an idol.
I like singing and dancing,
because it's fun.
But it takes more than that to be an idol.
You have to say things
that'll make their hearts throb.
I really can't do that.
I tend to
look up to men who are very manly.
People tell me that I'm manly too.
I doubt a manly person
would wear rabbit ears.
But they say you guys are
this generation's most classic idol group.
People do say that about us.
But we really aren't.
I'm serious.
Hirano as a young boy.
In second grade, he took up dancing,
which paved the way for his career.
I've been shy ever since I was young.
I would cry every time
we had singing recitals at school.
Going out in front of everyone
wasn't my thing.
I'm still like that now.
How did such a boy find his way here?
I wonder.
I think the main reason why
I was working hard
was for my mother.
I was raised by a single mother.
My mother almost died once.
Frankly speaking,
being an idol is a job.
I would see my friends getting married,
working at their jobs,
supporting their families,
and being very "human" in a way.
I felt like that was what you had to do
as a human being.
I didn't want to make my mother sad,
so I felt like I had to
work hard at my job.
Ready...
COMMERCIAL FILMING
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA
The job he started for his mother.
Tsum Tsum Land...
He hasn't forgotten his roots even now.
He doesn't put up a facade
and is always true to himself.
Look at how I walk.
I look like an old man.
An idol shouldn't be
walking like this, actually.
I should be walking like this.
But this is how I walk.
When I was filming the drama,
a staff member told me that
because I didn't act like a typical idol,
they felt an affinity with me.
I was told often
that they felt closer to me
because I would show them my real self.
If I were to put up a facade,
the fans I would gain
would only like me through a filter.
So...
I don't want to lie to them.
I want people to like me
for who I am naturally,
which is why I act this way.
Excuse me.
We would end up hearing
Hirano say something unexpected...
Don't film my old man walk.
...later on in the documentary.
JUNE 20TH, 2018
TOYOSU,TOKYO
June.
Ever since their debut,
their popularity has been
skyrocketing by the day.
Thank you!
Compared to other groups,
they may not have debuted very quickly,
but they've been through it all together
and have a strong bond.
The members wish to see the group grow
and share a common idea.
Each of them wants to find something
that only they can do.
It's too much.
Now that we're a group,
I think about what I can do
and what kind of effect
it will have on the group.
I want to be able to contribute
positive things to the group.
In doing so,
I want to become one of the many
who support this group.
BETSUCOMI MAGAZINE INTERVIEW
SHINJUKU, TOKYO
To do so,
Takahashi has taken up a project.
How professional.
He will try publishing a series
in a monthly shojo manga magazine.
MANGA ARTIST KYOSUKE MOTOMI
With the help of a real manga artist,
he chooses his tools.
I like this feeling of starting
from scratch. This is fun.
Takahashi has liked to draw
since childhood
and was influenced by his older sister
to read shojo manga.
BETSUCOMI
HITOTSUBASHI, TOKYO
But if he is going to publish
a manga series,
they will expect
a professional job from him.
A lot of it is unfinished.
This day, he was working to complete
what they call a "name,"
which is somewhat like a script for manga.
He's writing a romantic comedy
set in a school.
I don't know if I'll make it.
He uses the time in between
his work for the group,
so inevitably time is limited.
And of course, he must get it
checked by the editor.
At first, you can't tell if this person is
in junior high or high school.
I see.
I don't think you know
how to go about drawing this.
-Yes.
-So, we'll talk about how to do that.
My brain isn't functioning.
Seriously,
my brain is using up all my sugar.
This one.
Another issue is how he will draw
the most important "kabe-don" scene.
There was a reference book
with a collection of kabe-don poses.
Instead of drawing it
without any reference,
if you are unsure about the poses,
it may be better to use these as a guide.
Even for just one kabe-don scene,
there are endless possibilities.
By this point, he is already worn out.
-Did you have the day off yesterday?
-Yesterday? Yes.
What did you do?
I literally slept until the evening.
But you know how we have
a set schedule like this every day?
So, even when I get a day off,
I don't know if I should rest all day
or make the most of it.
I want my manager to tell me
what to do on my days off too.
As a child,
Takahashi lacked self-confidence
and always cared about others' opinions.
He was not good at sports either.
The one thing he was confident in
was dancing.
He joined the agency
under the encouragement of his mother.
But even during his time as a Johnny's Jr.
he was unsure of what he could contribute
and was filled with anxiety.
Even when they debuted...
Generally, I just don't have
a lot of self-confidence.
It was decided in January,
and we actually debuted in May.
I went back home and thought about it
but thinking about my future
made me so scared.
I had my head on my pillow the whole time,
and I was thinking.
I don't know what triggered it,
but tears just began to stream down.
And in the end,
I fell asleep not knowing
what exactly was making me anxious.
That continued every day
for about three or four months.
I think I used up
a lifetime's worth of tears.
Maybe I felt pressured
from having to go out into the world.
The fact that I debuted
was a cause for joy,
but I was worried about
whether I could handle all the pressure
that would come as a result.
I was worried the whole time.
Those days would not go to waste.
There's nothing here.
After this, a member
will return to his hometown.
Nagoya!
He unveils all of his hidden thoughts.
I wanted to quit.
I wanted to just quit and go away.
This day, Hirano,
the face of King & Prince,
was in Nagoya.
NAGOYA, AICHI
There's really nothing.
It's very calming, though.
I love Nagoya, after all.
I used to like to lay out tarp
around these type of places
and eat rice balls.
In elementary school?
No, I was totally a third-year
junior high student.
There was nothing around my hometown.
Nowhere to play.
I spent my youth doing random―
That's a huge grasshopper!
-That scared me.
-You don't like bugs?
Now, I don't like bugs.
I used to live in this kind of place,
so bugs used to be so normal to me.
But after I moved to Tokyo,
I lost touch with bugs.
Now there's a wall between bugs and me.
His peaceful hometown.
There's nothing here.
He moved to Tokyo
when he was 18 years old.
I was so desperate at the time.
I was like, "Tokyo?!"
I wasn't sure, but I decided to go.
Honestly, I only knew of it
as a world on TV.
I never thought I'd go
from this riverside to Tokyo.
A boy who was picking
four-leaf clovers over there
is on stage in Tokyo now.
Even now, when I'm on stage
it feels strange.
And he opens up to us.
By the way,
was there anything else you wanted to be
other than an idol?
So many things.
First, a dance instructor,
then a preschool teacher,
and an animal keeper.
-You like animals?
-I love animals too.
There are lots of jobs I'd like to try.
Last year I wanted to quit.
I wanted to just quit and go away.
I told people in the agency
that I was thinking of quitting that year.
I was in a commercial,
so I was thinking of quitting
when the contract
for the commercial ended.
But the people at the agency said
something really nice that stopped me.
They told me that people
who see us on TV, or in magazines,
or at concerts
can be emotionally uplifted
and motivated to live another day.
And there really have been fans like that.
A lot of people have told me
that I lifted their spirits
or moved them to do their best in school.
But recently,
I've lost a lot of people I know,
like among my relatives
and a friend of mine last year.
So many have died.
That's why, at the end of concerts,
I often say, "Don't die."
Even if we couldn't make eye contact
at the concert,
I want everyone who is watching me
and who is connected with me
to stay alive.
I really do.
The reason I'm continuing this job
is because I want to
lift everyone's spirits.
And that's why King & Prince exists now.
On the next Ride On Time...
The bitter experience
all six members went through.
What is adolescence, anyway?
This feels really strange.
Unforgettable pasts.
That really shocked me.
A reunion with friends.
Okay, I'll be waiting.
Working toward their big performance.
The third day at Yokohama Arena
was amazing.
All I'm thinking about these days
is how to surpass that
as a group.
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita