STAND UP ON YOUR OWN TWO FEET
Going down.
How brutal will the show be?
This device provides the answer.
While letting themselves be rotated
at high speed, they keep drumming.
Three more spins and I'll probably puke.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
A six-man unit whose athleticism is superb
even by Johnny's Jr. standards,
Snow Man.
A grand show to further their careers has
been made for them to perform in spring.
I hope to take the audience into the world
of ultimate Japanese entertainment.
MINAMIZA THEATRE
The first stage on which they'll perform
in this endeavor
will be in the birthplace
of Kabuki, Kyoto.
The name of the show is
Takizawa Kabuki ZERO.
In the short time they've had to prepare,
they've had to overcome many high hurdles.
Nice smiles, please!
More than anything, this has called for
an even deeper sense of unity.
POTATO MAGAZINE SHOOT
To give Snow Man a power-up,
an additional three members
have been added,
making them a unit of nine.
3 NEW MEMBERS TURN 6 TO 9
I think what we have to do now is
actually try out all kinds of things.
Surely we need to explore, right?
Now that there's nine of us.
However, unused to this style of training,
one member went through a hard time.
They're so fast!
It's Koji Mukai, who was with
Kansai Johnny's Jr. before now.
KOJI MUKAI (AGE 24)
It's not so much strenuous
as it is unfamiliar.
I guess I'm used to having it easier.
A new wind is blowing
in Snow Man's direction.
I've always wanted to protect this group.
We wanted to be that one step
ahead of other groups.
And now we've grown by three members,
and we're a new Snow Man.
However, as the inheritors
of the Takizawa Kabuki name,
the level demanded of them is sky-high.
As the first show draws near,
it's been a relentless process
of trial and error.
After the "soiya",
the drummers here go "hah".
Over there, too.
There isn't a single scene
that we've perfected yet.
It's getting really scary.
It's bad.
However, as they head for
the opening night,
they've had to overcome
an even tougher obstacle.
JANUARY 2019 TOKYO
Good morning.
The boys will be undergoing
a new experience today
and seem a little nervous about it.
Doesn't that look good on you?
-Seriously?
-It does.
They're checking the wigs
and practicing the makeup
for the Kabuki part of the show.
Iwamoto will be playing
the famous Ishikawa Goemon.
The kumadori, please.
Kumadori is a unique style of makeup
used in Kabuki.
Even the rough outline of the process
lists 15 stages of application.
Start at the top and really daub it on.
-I can just go for it?
-Yes, absolutely.
Yes, that bit, too.
Actors' white face paint
is also new to him, naturally.
That's it, that's it. Go down now.
Now pat it down. Pat, pat, pat.
Let's do it.
Finally, it's on to the real deal.
This is the only time he'll have it
done for him.
When it's the show, he'll have to draw
every single stroke himself.
You have a slender face, don't you?
You have to look at the whole face.
The angles aren't what you think they are!
That's it! Very good.
What's more, if he doesn't complete
every step within eight minutes,
he won't make it to the stage in time.
Go right up. Just like that. Go up.
The show will end
while I'm still doing my makeup.
You'll get faster than you are now.
Once the wig is on, the work is complete.
-How cool do you look?
-Wow!
You look great.
This is in fact
an extremely difficult challenge
in comparison with
past Takizawa Kabuki shows.
-Didn't Tackey wear a mask?
-He did.
Yes, even he didn't do the makeup.
-Huh?
-That's right!
-I think this is a first.
-Nobody else has done it.
Nobody has done their own makeup.
Give it your all!
-Yeah.
-Yeah? I'll give it my all!
-That's the spirit.
-You can do it!
Learning it's a new challenge,
the other members are spurred on. But...
I'm really crap at this.
If you mess up once...
-It's ruined.
-You'll run out of time.
You will.
I got it in my eye and now it's watering.
Taking on a similarly difficult task
are Mukai, Sakuma and Meguro, who've been
trusted to be the central drummers.
REN MEGURO (AGE 22)
The bits where you shout are confusing me.
When you shout,
you lose track of where you are.
After this, their eyes are met
with an unbelievable sight.
JANUARY 2019
It's waiting for them in a warehouse.
Placed in the center of the ring
of taiko drummers,
this device has been dubbed
the Mecha Taiko.
The trio will ride it as they drum.
This makes for a shocking image.
It's like we're being crucified!
They climb up,
and try using it while shut inside.
I'm scared!
In the real thing, they'll have to keep
drumming even as they're being lowered.
Are we supposed to hold ourselves up
with our feet?
-That's right.
-Oh, man.
I'm going to lower you now.
The Mecha Taiko takes them
from a 90-degree angle
and moves them even lower.
Great abdominal strength is required.
Furthermore, their entire body weight
must be held by
their feet alone using hooks.
This is crazy!
-Does the blood run to your head?
-Yeah, really badly.
-Mind your head.
-Oh, yeah.
Spin it a little harder.
Getting faster.
This is still doable.
Whoa, this is fast!
-We'll lower you now.
-Okay.
Take it away.
Takizawa-kun!
How was it, Sakuma?
Is that the speed we'll do it at?
More or less.
-Maybe a little faster if it looks better.
-Really?
Their physical and mental strength
will be tested
in what could be considered
the zenith of the show.
They're already exhausted.
Is it tough?
Is it tough on the body?
On the body?
The blood rushes to your head
and your brain stops working.
If I didn't constantly tense my stomach,
I'd probably slip down in some bits. So if
I tense, I should be able to drum fine.
-All three of you?
-Yes.
I think I'll puke after three more spins.
It's that bit where you have
to sit up and drum.
Could we maybe come back to here?
Got it, let's do that.
Can you move like this after that?
I think we should be able to do it
moving back.
On that same day, Miyadate takes on
another part of the show
without any of his band mates.
Are you okay?
RYOTA MIYADATE (AGE 25)
It's the flying scene,
something previously done by Takizawa.
That might be the safest way.
-Right.
-Okay.
That's good.
You're going to spin. Ready?
One, two.
Snow Man are taking over
the lead roles from Takizawa.
It seems that this responsibility
is beginning to dawn on them.
I've always been someone who
manages something and leaves it at that.
But I've been made to think again
about adding my own flavor
or style to something
after I've learned just how to do it.
I want to take things five steps forward.
Not just one step,
but five steps ahead of where I am.
What I want to surpass is
my previous self, I suppose.
As the opening performance nears,
the tension in the training room
has started to bubble over.
This scene features a sword fight.
A platform is supported by just
two boards on each side.
No nails are used.
The bottom, Masakado! It's out of place.
Make it as level as you can.
If everyone isn't completely focused,
there's a risk of someone being injured.
Right. I see.
You float up. You have to resist it.
So, you have to make sure
your weight's on it properly.
Until now, it was Snow Man
who lifted Takizawa up.
It was their utmost concern
to support him so he wouldn't get hurt.
Which is exactly why this happens.
Say if it slips.
-Higher.
-Line the corners up.
That looks a little off.
You fix it. Quickly!
If you mess up, it will be
the person on top who gets hurt.
-Yes, sir.
Think about what's at stake, everyone.
It's really irresponsible.
-You raised your voice there.
-Really?
It's only because I understand the danger.
You have to do things properly.
One slip in concentration
means a real injury.
I believe you should
let people know if something
is good or bad
whether they're your junior or senior.
You have to
if you want to make things better.
You don't know these things
unless you're told.
"Oh, so that's how you do it."
I want people to think that.
Shut your damn mouths!
I've got nothing to say to...
And then something happens
that same day as they rehearse a scene.
One of the performers
is called out for not focusing.
It's the perfect time
to see Kanda River. This way!
SEIJI TANAKA
It's Seiji Tanaka from Johnny's Jr..
He was chosen to be part of the main cast.
You're a little switched off
all the time, Seiji.
Always be aware of the fact you're acting.
Even when you don't have lines, listen
to those who do and come up with your own.
Break time. The first person to go
and talk to Tanaka is Sakuma.
Evil must not be allowed
to go on spreading unchecked.
Your voice is still far too weak.
There are members
of the audience all the way back.
They need to hear you clearly.
They paid for their tickets, too.
I want to make this world a just one.
Louder.
Say it so I can hear you.
I want to make this world a just one.
No, I can't hear you.
Evil must not...
Evil must not be allowed
to go on spreading unchecked.
From here more.
They can only hear you over here.
They can't hear you back there.
Always be conscious
of the people at the back.
You're on the main cast.
The Kansai Johnny's Jr.
are outperforming you right now.
I'm sure Seiji has an ideal
that he aspires to,
but there was something
he just couldn't express at all,
and he still didn't get it
when it was said to him gently.
So, I had to take
a slightly stronger tone with him.
"If you keep trying harder, you can do it.
I did it, so you can too."
You should always think like that
when dealing with your juniors.
Be more aware of the danger yourself.
Because it's not
good enough at all right now.
You can't give an audience that.
It's your own responsibility to come up
with something you can give the audience.
Bang, in one.
They've been down this path themselves.
Louder.
That's why these sentiments
are passed down to the next generation.
MAY 3, 2012
SNOW MAN FORM
Snow Man officially became a unit
seven years ago.
Since then, they've performed
in every Takizawa Kabuki.
It's also been
a learning opportunity for them.
The biggest lesson Sakuma received
from Takizawa
was about letting the audience
feel your passion.
There's lots of new ones out!
The value of an artist's passion
is something Sakuma notices
especially in manga and anime.
This is good. It's cute.
Here it is!
It's a manga called
Koi Wo Shiranai Bokutachi Wa.
I really like this.
I read shoujo manga.
I don't think I have part four!
I'll get it.
I could talk about this forever.
Anime and manga make a complete
and thorough effort to entertain the fans.
Sakuma feels a link between this
and his own work.
The artists don't cut any corners, and put
their hearts and souls into their work.
That quality
really makes you feel something.
They're pieces of art that are made
by lots of people working together.
That really resonates with me
as I think about the Johnny's shows.
If someone isn't picking up the slack,
it really doesn't sit well with me.
If you're not constantly giving more
than 100 percent onstage,
I don't think you can stir
people's emotions.
So, in the end,
will they be able to create a show
that will stir emotions?
Their three weeks of training in Tokyo
are now drawing to a close.
January 31st.
They arrive at a rainy Kyoto.
KYOTO SHIJO MINAMIZA THEATRE
-Good morning.
Good morning!
Here we go.
The drums are all set up.
There are three days until the show.
They need to hurry to finish
the final touches.
Good work! See you, then!
I've left the box here, Sakuma.
The first thing Snow Man do after arriving
in Kyoto is set up their dressing rooms.
For the next month, this is home.
Time to start making my dressing room.
The most fastidious band member
when it comes to dressing rooms
is Watanabe.
This is... What do you call this again?
Do you know?
I hate it being here or facing this way.
I want the logo to be facing out
nice and neatly.
It seems he's the very organized type.
This is the new member of the crew.
Dermatologists use it.
I sometimes bring things
they use in hospitals, too.
It's to make sure his skin
isn't dried out by the makeup.
I can't help but enjoy finding a place
for everything to go.
He has so many cosmetics because of
something he feels strongly as an idol.
Everyone has beautiful faces,
beautiful skin.
Beautiful hair.
A cool haircut and stylish clothes.
That's what people dream of.
They expect that when they come to see us.
So, before worrying about my personality,
my top priority is to look immaculate.
As if I'm glittering.
I like to take that seriously.
Looking to the future,
I'd like people to see me
as the strong vocalist of Snow Man.
That's an accolade I aspire to.
I'm aiming to be in that spot.
So that each of the boys' unique
characteristics can shine in the show,
the different parts have been
carefully mapped out.
TAIKO
A display of remarkable strength,
the taiko.
TAKIZAWA KABUKI SAKURA NO MAI DANCE
A bewitching dance, portraying women.
Thank you ever so much!
There are comedic parts, too.
Watanabe, who hopes to be
the unit's main vocalist,
has one solo performance.
BALLAD "MY FRIEND"
SWORD FIGHT (MONOCHROME)
And doing battle in this fight scene
is Miyadate.
His search to find something
only he can do brought him here.
SHOCHIKU FILM SET, KYOTO
They have a moment's rest in Kyoto.
Time to soak in the atmosphere
on the set of a period piece.
If they don't fall completely
in love with this world,
the passion they need to move people
just won't be there.
QUESTION: HOW DO YOU PREPARE
TO ENTERTAIN PEOPLE?
I think it comes down to the question
of if you can influence people or not.
They might like your face,
the way you dance or your voice.
That's all well and good.
But can you, this person they like,
influence people or can't you?
Will they work hard so they can see you?
Will they spend their hard-earned cash
to come to your concert?
To see your show?
I want to be an idol
who gets people to do that.
I chose to follow this path in life,
so I absolutely don't want
to cut any corners.
I want to see it all the way through.
Being a part of Johnny's,
and the idol Ryota Miyadate.
And I want people to see Ryota Miyadate
growing as an actor in a historical drama.
FEBRUARY 3
THE DAY OF THE OPENING PERFORMANCE
At long last,
the time has come for Snow Man.
On the Ride On Time finale...
Why am I doing a fake smile?
With the show imminent,
the process of trial and error
goes right up the last minute.
The collar won't stay up on this side.
It's a race against time to rehearse.
Offstage, it is like a war zone.
My wig!
We're wasting time.
And an accident befalls Iwamoto.
Now I've gone and done it.
The first performance is finally here.
What will they obtain from this
incredible opportunity of a show?
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams