AFTER TWO YEARS, THEY'VE COME BACK
MARCH 22ND, 2018
On this day,
after a two-year long voyage,
they have returned to where they belong.
Their name is
KAT-TUN.
There haven't been any issues
with the audience, so we are on time.
Kazuya Kamenashi, 32 years old.
Yuichi Nakamaru, 35 years old.
Tatsuya Ueda, 35 years old.
Ten minutes left.
After a long time,
they are dancing side by side again.
Originally they started as a group of six,
but they are now three.
In a way, they are the opposite
of the flashy image
that may be associated with idols.
They are men who have
confronted their cruel fate.
It's been a while.
Should we huddle up?
-It's time.
-Let's do it!
Hey!
Why did the three of them
decide to continue as KAT-TUN?
We followed them
for 300 turbulent days
after their comeback.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
2006 KAT-TUN DEBUT LIVE
TOKYO DOME
Their big debut came in 2006
when they performed to a full audience
at Tokyo Dome.
They broke one record after another,
gaining their place in music history.
Their rise shocked the world.
A word to describe their charm
would be "wild."
They were far from
the typical idol image.
Hey, Dome!
Scream until you can't anymore!
Make some noise, you bastards!
However, they had
very different personalities,
so the group faced many challenges.
For various reasons,
one member left after another.
At times, they'd keep performing together
even after members had decided to quit.
That created a difficult atmosphere.
We had to spend several months together
after they decided to quit.
I can't describe the feelings I had.
Each of them...
TATSUYA UEDA (AGE 35)
They each have their own life,
and decide what kind of life
they want to live.
That's something that I
just have to accept.
Nevertheless,
they decided to stay together
and took time to recharge.
They promised the fans they would return.
We will prove to you that having this time
is needed to protect KAT-TUN.
We're counting on you until then!
Thank you very much.
How should KAT-TUN continue?
How should we make KAT-TUN grow?
It's a way to show my resolve
to the members who left.
And I guess we also have our pride.
And the fans.
That's why I don't want to be the one
to break up the group.
Maybe it's the beauty of it...
to be able to make KAT-TUN continue.
Or maybe because we feel
we have a responsibility.
Now it is time to fulfill
that responsibility.
The place they have chosen
for their return
is a sacred place for KAT-TUN,
Tokyo Dome.
They will perform there
for three consecutive days.
Preparations began
at the beginning of the year.
On this day at a Tokyo studio,
they're doing a photo shoot for the uchiwa
that will be sold at the concerts.
We want cool instead of playful.
Okay!
We are going all out already.
Let's do our best!
KAZUYA KAMENASHI (AGE 32)
Kamenashi
joined the show business at age 12.
It's already been 20 years.
He is a disciplined professional
with a caring attitude.
Two years' worth of emotions.
He can also make this face, if asked.
On the other hand, Ueda...
I took it.
Wasn't it too fast?
-I took it because he looked cool.
-Okay.
He doesn't react even once
to the compliment.
He is a man
with an unwavering heart.
And Nakamaru is a man of ideas,
who likes funny things.
YUICHI NAKAMARU (AGE 35)
Every year, he makes
the same face for his uchiwa.
He has little interest
in showing his cool side.
-Let's go with this angle for both sides.
-Okay.
Soon people won't have any reason
to buy it anymore.
Their appearances and personalities
are so different.
When these three people reunite,
they become KAT-TUN.
On this day, while discussing
the components of the concerts,
something else happens.
KAZUYA KAMENASHI'S 32ND BIRTHDAY
Congratulations!
Tell us your aspirations as a 32-year-old.
As a 32-year-old,
I want to move forward
with the group again.
I want to work well together.
-I hope you have a good year.
-Yes.
These concerts are
centered around the group's hit songs.
The most important issue
is how they will present
the renewed KAT-TUN.
I remember the swing...
Yes, remember that first.
Just the parts you need.
This video is from
ten years ago,
when there were six members.
So young...
This time, they want to be even better.
Kamenashi has insisted on redoing
all of the songs from scratch,
including each of their singing parts.
In the end, it's the best to
change everything, right?
-Yeah.
-Must we go out of our way to do so?
If we don't have to...
I want to check the balance
and do a brush-up.
Now that it's the three of us.
If it's fine...
Up until now,
one of them would just fill in
for the members who left.
However, Kamenashi thinks that
the reborn KAT-TUN
needs to make a strong impression.
Of course, some parts need to change,
and some parts don't.
What doesn't change...
Right now, all we're doing
is filling in the empty parts.
I want to brush-up on the balance
of those parts again.
I think that it's better to not
change them if it's unnecessary.
I'm sure some fans
have become familiar with them.
We want to consider our fans' feelings.
Of course, I understand that some parts
match the image of certain members.
That's true for all the songs
we are singing this time.
We want people to want to listen.
No matter what, it's a fact that
there are only three of us.
It's not about someone wanting
to sing a certain part.
It's been two years since the 10Ks!
If they see that we
haven't changed anything,
it'll seem like we lack variety.
I think it would be better
to properly show
that we're now a group of three people.
That's why I want to change them.
He wants people to think
that the current KAT-TUN is better.
Okay, please start from the beginning.
Kamenashi has been acting
since before he debuted.
He also has a job as a newscaster
for a sports program.
But even so,
he still cherishes the experience
of standing on the stage.
It's horrifying to think of
not being able to do it.
Being in an environment
where I can't sing, dance,
or hold concerts...
The other day, on the radio,
and I was able to call my fans.
They told me, "I can't wait!"
and I was like, "Oh yeah, that's it!"
"That's what this is all about."
It should've been obvious,
but it was like...
I really got it.
We'll have concerts
and people will come...
People want to come and there's a raffle.
That's why we have to face the concerts
with all our might.
It's important for me to remind myself
of this foundation.
Our foundation is singing, dancing,
and getting cheers in response.
Kamenashi was born in 1986
in downtown Tokyo,
as the third son of four children.
The name "Kazuya"
came from a character in Touch,
which was a popular
baseball manga at the time.
He aimed to be a professional
baseball player.
He joined the agency
when he was 12.
An older relative of his
sent in an application on her own
and he was selected by chance.
But, worried he would never
make his debut,
he decided to quit the agency
when he took his
high school entrance exams.
How many months were there
when I didn't have work or lessons?
I studied for the entrance test
and managed to pass the exam
for a public school.
Then I told Johnny that I was quitting,
and he said things like,
"What are you thinking?"
"You know, I'm thinking of
making a group."
"Ah, is that so?"
Like, "Eh? Seriously?"
And the group was formed was...
KAT-TUN.
However, they had strong personalities
and different goals.
They were always butting heads.
Before their debut,
they acted out this scene on the stage.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
-What's your problem?
-Hey!
-What are you doing?
-Come here.
In this scene,
they are actually reenacting a big fight
they had backstage.
At that time,
Kamenashi was also
just a selfish young boy.
Then, in 2005,
Kamenashi starred in
the hit-drama, Gokusen,
and he immediately became a star.
What's more, the song he recorded
with Tomohisa Yamashita
sold over a million copies.
1,628,000 COPIES SOLD
Eventually,
despite being the youngest in the group,
Kamenashi started
to be treated as the leader.
That was also something that troubled him.
During performances,
KAT-TUN had a dressing room,
and another dressing room
was arranged just for me.
Since I was pretty much the leader.
Honestly, it was uncomfortable.
But I had to do it.
I slowed down the pace of my solo work.
I thought it might be better
for us all to stay on the same level
and focus on the group.
That's what I told the agency.
But at that time, Johnny told me,
"If you don't sell,
KAT-TUN will fail."
I thought, "So, that's how it is."
I felt a lot of pressure.
And thought that I needed to work hard.
And then, on the same day
as their debut,
they had a big concert in Tokyo Dome.
When he saw the fans in front of him,
he felt a sense of responsibility
that still remains within him today.
Even now as a group of three,
there are fans who continue
to support them.
Quitting KAT-TUN wasn't an option.
Anyway, what I felt was
that there were fans who
supported KAT-TUN as a group.
There were people cheering us on,
so I wanted to have confidence in myself.
I also had this feeling...
of not wanting to hurt KAT-TUN
any more than it already had been.
I didn't want that.
We probably could have just gone on
and gotten past this,
But...
I don't want us to exist as
that kind of a group.
That's why...
I'm really thankful to all the fans
who have been genuinely supporting us
since the beginning.
Tomorrow,
they will perform at Tokyo Dome
for the first time in two years.
APRIL 19TH DAY BEFORE CONCERT
TOKYO DOME
In one day, the three members
must make their feelings
reach the 55,000 people
who will fill this huge venue.
-Good morning.
Kamenashi has arrived at the venue
four hours before the final rehearsal.
He reviews
the dance and lyrics of each song.
He's giving his all.
That's his responsibility
towards the fans.
It's good like this.
He's checked all 36 songs
that they will sing in the concert.
Every one of them.
Good morning.
When all the members arrive,
the final rehearsal starts.
Testing...
How long...
Especially now with only three,
they're feeling the stage's massiveness
all over again.
How can they make their performance
reach every corner?
Hurry here.
Walking speed...
How they will be seen by the audience...
They check every detail.
Here...
Is it weird if I prolong
the spin at the end?
It's not extended.
If it were extended,
I wouldn't have to rush, right?
If I don't pay attention,
and do whatever I feel like,
I won't be facing the audience.
It's not impossible.
First and foremost,
the three of them rehearse this song.
Their opening song,
"Real Face", 2018 version.
THE RAP HAS ALSO BEEN RE-WRITTEN
How will fans react
to the new "Real Face"?
And now, the rehearsal
of Kamenashi's cherished solo part begins.
It can be lifted now.
-I wait until the very end?
-Yes, wait until the end and then spin.
It's a performance in the air.
Furthermore, this time...
-Is this done without a lifeline?
-Yes, that's right.
There's no lifeline.
He's not using a lifeline.
I hold my tension like this?
Yes, yes, yes.
The highlight is this.
He holds his fallen body
with just one arm.
Holding all of his weight with his hand
is quite burdensome.
Damn, it's scary.
It's scary.
I won't let my right hand go
no matter what.
Instead of relying on
the latest technology,
he wants to show his passion.
If you rely on equipment or videos,
it ends up being about money.
It's like...
what it means to be an idol...
I want to value myself as an artist
and the things that I experience.
If I had to choose,
I'm the type of person
who prefers talking face-to-face
rather than discussing
things over e-mail.
Like when we meet up or have concerts.
That's something I really want to value.
The day has finally come.
APRIL 20TH
FIRST CONCERT SINCE THEIR RETURN
However,
something has happened to Kamenashi.
My right arm is not good.
Flying is really tiring.
It takes a lot of energy.
It's a passionate performance.
The price of that is not small.
Will the concerts be a success?
Next time,
their first Dome concerts
in two years will begin.
We'll hear the thoughts
of Ueda and Nakamaru,
who support the band alongside Kamenashi.
It's the same love as family.
No matter what happens,
in the end you love them.
All three members are necessary.
I think the moment that changes,
we won't be KAT-TUN.
-You're a mess.
-Yes, indeed.
What will they show
when they take the stage once again?
-We are...
-KAT-TUN!
Subtitle translation by Jordan Woodard