After two years, they've come back.
The return of KAT-TUN.
They carry one feeling in their hearts.
It's a way to show my resolve
to the members who left.
And I guess we also have our pride.
And the fans.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
2006 KAT-TUN DEBUT LIVE
TOKYO DOME
Their big debut came in 2006
when they performed
to a full audience at Tokyo Dome.
DEBUT SINGLE SOLD 1,046,000 COPIES
Their steady rise shocked the world.
Their charm was in their wildness
which was far from the typical idol image.
Hey, Dome!
Scream until you can't anymore!
Make some noise, you bastards!
However, they had very
different personalities,
so the group faced many challenges.
For various reasons,
one member left after another.
They had doubts about
continuing with the group.
But as a result...
2016 10TH ANNIVERSARY LIVE
TOKYO DOME
...their bond became stronger.
All three members are necessary,
and I think the moment that changes,
we won't be KAT-TUN.
After all the difficult things
we went through,
I want the three of us
to find happiness together.
And they confronted Tokyo Dome
for the first time in two years.
Each of them
has their own feelings within them.
February.
FEBRUARY 23RD, 2018
Thank you.
On this day, the meetings about
the Tokyo Dome concerts have started.
We catch a glimpse of what they each
wish to value the most moving forward.
I'd like to push this sort of 1-1-1 image
for this year's concerts.
I think we should look back at the work
each of us did during
the recharging period.
-I remember talking about that.
-Yes.
Wouldn't it be nice to show
each of our personalities?
Even as a group,
they still care about their individuality.
They even keep to themselves
during the breaks.
Nakamaru is writing something.
Ueda is checking the stage.
Kamenashi is reading about pro baseball.
They also learn
the choreography separately.
They don't exchange words.
We ask the staff around them
and they tell us how KAT-TUN
is different from other groups.
In the past, KAT-TUN used to
practice dancing in sync.
But they were told, "Don't dance in sync!"
"Don't destroy what makes you good."
The messy look is their charm.
They are cool because each of them
is completely different.
It's 100 times harder
to make a cool dance like that.
They feel the responsibility of
having to look cool
even though they're not in sync.
So, their individuality grew.
And that is their distinct color.
Every group has individuality. Probably.
But, well, we were taught that way,
and were told we had something good.
That "something" is big.
On this day,
Nakamaru shot a video
by himself for the concerts.
Good morning.
-You're a mess.
-Yes, indeed.
Looking like this,
he is going to shoot a video
to showcase the concert's merchandise.
Can I check it out?
He is not only going to introduce it,
he also wants the fans to have
fun with the video.
Okay.
The top items this time
are bath salts that Nakamaru
produced himself.
They come in each of the member's colors.
He also drew the illustrations himself.
I want to review it.
Knock, knock, knock.
Let me out! Let me out!
I'm trapped.
I've been trapped for two years!
Damn it!
Inspired by home shopping
channel infomercials,
he wrote the script from scratch himself.
Who's in there?
Start the camera.
The filming starts.
It's ready, go.
Hey! Let me out!
I'm serious, let me out!
It's been too long!
I've been trapped.
I've been trapped here for two years!
That three-person pirate group,
KAT-TUN, is terrible!
Especially Kamenashi and Ueda!
Because... they grabbed me by the arms.
And now it's torn.
How will this showcase the bath salts?
Let's take a look at the finished result.
I'm tired! I want to take a bath.
Ah!
This is what you need!
KAT-TUN's hot bath for a rapid recharging!
These bath salts are amazing!
Even those with fatigue
can be quickly recharged.
Ah, my fatigue has melted away!
For this special occasion,
it comes in the three colors of
the members and the price is only
600 yen.
Please consider it!
You want to kill me?
For an intense KAT-TUN concert,
this can be a good highlight.
I'm tired! I want to take a bath!
You're having fun?
Having fun is the most important thing.
I thought that it would be better
to have this kind of angle.
Yeah.
Because I think it's good
to have diversity in concerts.
So, I think it's good to
have a funny part like this.
Nakamaru was born in 1983
as the eldest of three
to a father who was
a strict civil servant.
When he was little, he was naughty.
He was often scolded
because he couldn't keep quiet.
He joined the agency when he was 14.
Since he was one of hundreds
of aspiring idols,
he thought of a plan to get his big break.
Since there were 100 or 200
members in Johnny's Jr.,
I thought of how to stand out.
I looked at the others who were chosen
to be part of Johnny's & Associates, Inc.
I looked...
I looked into the periods
when they debuted.
I looked into why
they were chosen and so on.
"The next member will be chosen soon."
"We will be called
for this or that reason."
Those are things that I kept in mind
as I tried to follow the trends,
so I would also be chosen.
Also, my parents told me
that if I wanted to be an entertainer,
I'd have to have at least one skill.
So, I had thought for a long time
that I needed to learn something.
Because being a member of Johnny's Jr.
has its risks.
It's a world where you don't know
whether they'll choose you or not.
I was stressed about it every day.
I was that competitive.
And this is what he found.
BEATBOXING:
REPRODUCING THE SOUND OF
PERCUSSION INSTRUMENTS
WITH ONLY THE MOUTH AND TONGUE
He practiced with the metronome
every day until his tongue hurt.
And there's one more thing.
To survive in show business,
he has one rule for himself
on the film sets.
And that rule is this.
That's okay.
I don't need it.
It's not necessary.
-You don't sit down?
-I don't.
Only if it's an emergency.
I have to be careful.
They offer chairs out of kindness,
but if people see me sitting without any
context, they'll think I'm arrogant.
I can't carelessly sit.
It's a trap.
But the person who gave you
the chair will feel bad...
I'm thankful for it,
but there are people who don't know.
"He feels important sitting there..."
But they know that staff and artists are
different, so they wouldn't think that.
-I would think that.
-How petty.
Isn't sitting back while being fanned
and having your sweat wiped off terrible?
-That would be bad.
-Right?
Ready... start!
On the other hand,
Ueda has his own way of living.
His role in today's filming
is a cook at a ramen shop.
You are doing great. Let me see.
This is perfect.
Even when praised,
he doesn't stop until he is satisfied.
Ready...
He is the type who dives into things.
-I did it.
-Well done.
Ueda was born in 1983 in Yokohama.
Due to his father's work,
he moved a lot when he was little.
He joined the agency on his own at 14.
But he had a hard time fitting in,
and dreamed of making it as a soloist,
instead of being part of a group.
I hate being around people.
It's not that I hate it...
How should I say it?
I hate noisy crowds.
Like when there are lots of people.
I also don't like it when we have
to go everywhere together.
But the agency made him join KAT-TUN.
Since Ueda liked to be alone, the friction
with his surroundings didn't go away.
TATSUYA UEDA
But as one member left after another,
he unexpectedly started to deepen
his bond with the others.
During their recharging period,
he used his sports program
to help support boys
who have yet to debut.
On this day, Ueda's
Johnny's Track and Field Club
have a relay race against
the para-athlete team.
Do your best.
Since the athletes this time
are amazing...
I want you to enjoy it.
-Don't be nervous.
-Okay!
Come on!
I've made a 180-degree change
from when I was put in KAT-TUN
before we got our big break
to my current self.
We have reduced the number
of members by half now.
After overcoming those things with
the members at those times,
it's like our unity is stronger now.
I really do think that
sharing difficult experiences...
makes our bond stronger.
It's the same love as family.
We've spent more time with each other
than our families.
It's not only love,
we also irritate each other.
But...
How do I say it?
After all we've overcome together,
I think it's good being just us three.
That kind of love.
Like, no matter what happens,
in the end you love them.
No matter what happens...
After all the difficult things
we went through,
I want the three of us to find
happiness together.
They're headed to Tokyo Dome
for the first time in two years.
APRIL 19TH, DAY BEFORE CONCERT
TOKYO DOME
In this huge venue,
how will these three members
be able to entertain the fans?
The highlight of Kamenashi's part
is this aerial performance.
Be careful.
He holds his entire weight
with his right arm,
so it's a big burden.
Ueda will take a drive on a motorcycle
between the audience seats.
He wants to be as close
as possible to the fans.
As expected, Nakamaru has a unique idea.
He has a miniature set of the stage
and shows it on the screen.
He is acting out what will happen
in the second half of the concert.
...the amount of feathers. Also,
it would probably be better
if the front of the uchiwa is visible.
Like that.
Without relying on the latest technology,
he is thinking about how to make it
have a realistic feeling for the audience.
Kamenashi quietly watches the screen
where that rehearsal is being shown.
They want to make their
passion reach the audience.
That is the determination
of all the members.
It's like...
what it means to be an idol...
I want to value myself as an artist
and the things that I experience.
I'm the type of person
who prefers talking face-to-face
rather than discussing
things over e-mail.
Like when we meet up or have concerts.
That's something I really want to value.
April 20th.
APRIL 20TH
FIRST CONCERT SINCE THEIR RETURN
Since morning, the outside
has been packed with fans
who have been waiting for their return.
There are even fans from overseas.
HONG KONG
My right arm is not good.
It takes a lot of energy.
It's a passionate performance.
The price of that is not small.
Finally, the three days of concerts
is about to start.
Will they be able
to deliver a satisfying performance
to the fans who've been waiting so long?
Can I get some eye drops?
The moment has finally come.
2 MINUTES TO SHOWTIME
They have been on
the Tokyo-Dome stage many times.
Even so, they are nervous.
It's been two years, and these are
going to be three important days.
Let's give it our all today.
I'm counting on you.
Let's go!
SHOWTIME
It begins.
Tokyo Dome is filled with 55,000 fans
who have been waiting for
the three of them to appear
since the last song they sang
two years ago.
The members' solo parts.
The concerts lasted for three hours
with a total of 36 songs.
For three days,
they will continue with all their might.
Their fans wave their hands
at the three of them until the end.
Because they exist,
we can continue moving.
I can't just move forward
based on what I want,
like "I want to sell"
or "I want to do this more."
It's because people
are expecting it from us,
that we are able to move forward.
I'm thankful for that.
-We are...
-KAT-TUN!
They've returned.
Good job.
I'm at my limit.
KAT-TUN's new story has just begun.
They have now started moving ahead
to the next tour.
On the next Ride On Time,
we'll look at how they continue
to face their daily lives
for the sake of the new KAT-TUN.
Fifty times.
If I hadn't started boxing, I probably
would have become a bad adult.
And they start production on
their first album in four years.
Properly making songs
for a group of three.
I think it would be good to
have something surprising.
The feeling of needing to go
to the next level.
Action!
-What are you doing here?
-Ueda?
Huh?
What do they want their future to hold?
Subtitle translation by Jordan Woodard