STAND UP ON YOUR OWN TWO FEET
Here they are again,
working as hard as they can
to achieve their dreams.
The new stars of the idol world, Snow Man.
JOHNNY'S JR. UNIT
SNOW MAN
And the dream show they're taking on
is called Takizawa Kabuki ZERO.
Their first performance is
within touching distance.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Snow Man, a unit whose athleticism
stands out even among Johnny's Jr. groups.
They've been together seven years.
At long last an enormous chance
is within their grasp
in the form of taking the lead roles
in Takizawa Kabuki ZERO.
I hope to take the audience into the world
of ultimate Japanese entertainment.
As part of a plan to give the unit
a power-up,
Snow Man's members grew in number
from six to nine.
THREE NEW MEMBERS JOIN
Takizawa-kun!
However, Takizawa Kabuki has been
a high mountain to scale.
There are countless things
they must learn.
The lower your shoulders,
the prettier you look.
It involves some danger, too.
If you mess up, it will be
the person on top who gets hurt.
Louder.
I want to make this world a just one.
No, I can't hear you.
There are members
of the audience all the way back.
They want it to be a success
no matter what.
Snow Man has just one wish.
I want to overcome being unknown.
I want people to know who we are.
The curtain on the first show will open
in the birthplace of Kabuki, Kyoto,
at the legendary Minamiza Theatre.
Finally, the time for battle is upon them.
The collar won't stay up on this side.
I want to get rid of the one-piece look.
First, it's costume fitting. Miyadate
is now in charge of all the costumes.
RYOTA MIYADATE (AGE 26)
Reduce the fringe for now.
In order to become more independent,
Snow Man have taken over for Takizawa,
and have to make their own decisions.
The dances are very intricate,
so how should they look?
I want it to be fresh,
with a bit of a poppy feeling to it.
I can't wait.
Next, it's a hurdle they'll have to
manage to overcome somehow.
The Kabuki makeup.
It's done in between
two parts of the show,
meaning they only have
eight minutes to apply it.
The kumadori makeup that takes
the longest to apply
requires some highly complicated work.
I have numbers to tell me the order
to draw the lines in.
There are 16 strokes just for red.
And there are five for black.
It's a little under 30 steps in total.
Will everyone be able to finish
within the eight minutes on the night?
No way can I do this.
My eye's stinging!
I got it in my eye!
Mistakes can't be redone.
It must be right first time.
Okay, all done.
How have they done?
Let's call that 12 minutes.
12 minutes just isn't quick enough.
They remove their makeup
and try to beat the clock again.
Your current time isn't practical.
-More urgency, please.
-Yes, sir.
Three times quicker than last time, maybe?
-Got it.
You can definitely do it.
The band members
have all tensed up at once.
Okay, start.
You've had five minutes now.
-Done, Iwamoto?
-Yes.
It's a big reduction in time.
Fukazawa done.
Do you want to hear your times?
Iwamoto, for example, has gone from
six minutes to a time of 2:37.
-You've cut it down.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
You, too, Fukka.
You've gone from 6:52 to 2:37.
-I hope that's good enough.
-You can do it. That's how it is.
Try and you will succeed.
If you don't practice this,
it's all pointless.
-Yes, sir.
They'll have to do it with even more
pressure on them when it's the show.
This is really difficult.
Trouble strikes when they begin
onstage rehearsals.
In the second scene of the show,
Iwamoto plays an Edo-period detective.
When I do the pose
after I go up, I face this way.
The highlight of the scene comes
when he poses at the top of a ladder.
-Dropping you down now.
-Okay.
-That was close!
-Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Everyone thought it was just a slip.
But he's hurt his shin badly.
You've scraped the skin off.
We'll disinfect it.
I don't want to be injured!
You've taken quite a chunk out.
-Here it comes.
-Right.
With the opening night imminent,
he seems to be angry at himself
for getting hurt.
Now I've gone and done it.
Come on, man.
I've been getting injured too much lately.
The pain doesn't bother me.
I just wonder what the hell I'm doing.
It's at this moment
that one of the new members,
Meguro, turns up.
Don't you think that guys like us
-look cuter if we have a wound?
-Well...
isn't this more of a hindrance?
-Will you be all right?
-Of course.
I'm just letting it dry.
Sure.
This is Snow Man's
long-awaited big chance.
No matter what happens, if they don't
stand on the stage with their own strength
they'll have lost their tomorrow.
It looks like Iwamoto's determination
is as steely as ever.
FEBRUARY 2, 2019
It's the day before the show.
A press conference is being held
on the stage.
This is what they had to say
to the crowd of reporters.
I hope to seize all opportunities
and show lots of people and all the fans
how Snow Man is charging
full steam ahead into our new era.
I believe there's a reason why
we were trusted to be at the forefront
of Takizawa Kabuki ZERO,
and we'll prove it.
Oh, man.
It's our first full dress rehearsal.
I'm getting nervous now.
They'll be going through the whole show
in one go, wearing their costumes.
Curtain up.
They've been through each part thoroughly,
and now the challenge is
to fit them together without a hitch.
THE DRESS REHEARSAL BEGINS
The franticness backstage
makes it seem like a war's going on.
They're constantly changing costume
and moving around,
fighting for every second.
They're sweating this much
a little under 30 minutes in.
You still have two minutes.
The crew's help is essential
for the costume changes. However...
Where's my wig?
Iwamoto's wig is nowhere to be seen.
My wig!
We're wasting time.
Can they iron out all these kinks
before the real thing tomorrow?
They also need to give attention
to their junior performers.
Don't look down like this.
Be bold and open.
I know you're uneasy because
you don't know what will happen.
But the audience doesn't know that,
so make it big.
Just don't cause an accident.
Will they meet the hopes of Takizawa,
the man who entrusted them with this?
I think your job in entertainment
is to work as one unified body
to convey a message
through your performance.
I really want Takizawa Kabuki
to be something for the performers
to really put their hearts and souls into
and show their passion.
What we're doing is real Kabuki,
real taiko drumming.
We're not professionals at those things,
but it's our task
to show the audience
our passion for taking those things on.
At long last, the day is here.
FEBRUARY 3, 2019
-Good morning.
Good morning! It's the day of the show!
Yeah!
This is awesome!
Used during a production's run,
this is a chakutoban, used by the cast
to sign in as they arrive.
This gets them fired up.
This band member
hasn't had a single day off
for the three weeks
leading up to the opening night.
We still haven't really started.
Tonight's the first show.
But I'm exhausted.
I had a quick bite to eat yesterday
then came back and watched
the recording of the dress rehearsal.
I made notes of all the things
we need to improve on.
I want to do my best.
-I look forward to it.
-Thanks.
Meanwhile, how's Iwamoto doing
after there was concern about his injury?
Did you manage to sleep at all?
Like a log.
A wall down the corridor
has been decorated.
Cool, right?
To think they'd give us
this much coverage.
Scenes from yesterday's dress rehearsal
are being used in big newspaper spreads
to coincide with the opening night.
There you go. The opening night
of Takizawa Kabuki ZERO.
Time to go bean-throwing.
It's February 3rd, the Setsubun festival.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
In the bean-throwing ceremony,
they'll pray for a safe three weeks
as they perform at Minamiza,
and for no bad luck.
-Demons!
-There are demons!
They're working.
They were about to throw the beans, but...
You stay down low for this bit.
Then lift it up.
It's Setsubun!
-Not yet, Koji.
-Oh, sorry!
Which bit is it?
The bit at the start the goes...
-This bit?
-Yeah.
One, two, three, four.
Before they knew it, they're absorbed
in checking their choreography.
It's all about the first beat in this one.
Just remember that.
Will the show be a success?
They're definitely dedicating a lot
of energy to this question.
I don't want people just to be going on
about the technology.
I want this show to be the first step
towards people recognizing
that we really know what we're doing.
It's about meeting the demands
of all the parts of the show,
which come thick and fast.
It's like I have an iron rod down my back
the whole time. I have to get it perfect.
There's a sense of not wanting to waste
everything we've done so far.
You need to think about
what you're here for.
30 MINUTES TO THE SHOW
It's 30 minutes until the curtains go up.
A line snakes outside the theater.
The band members head for Takizawa's room.
It's a tradition observed each year.
Hurry up.
-Five minutes.
-Hello!
-We've come to see you.
-Huh?
-We came to pay you a visit.
-You didn't have to.
-Whoa!
-Don't say sad things like that.
We do this every year.
You're in charge now.
Right, I'll see you
in my dressing room, then.
Let's head back!
We're not going.
The torch has already been passed.
Nobody is in charge but themselves.
15 MINUTES TO THE SHOW
Are you nervous?
Yeah, but it's different
from normal nerves.
It's more excitement.
-This is going to be a blast.
-Yeah!
But even so...
I think I'll go down.
It's no use, I can't calm down.
SHOTA WATANABE (AGE 26)
I'm feel restless too, so I'll join him.
Okay.
Everyone will be fine.
The cast. The crew.
And if the audience are ready for it,
I'll take them into that world.
Iwamoto has led Snow Man
since they were first formed.
Perhaps to reassure himself, he says
how ready he is over and over again.
I'm planning on going to a world
not even Takizawa has imagined.
In the snap of a finger.
The show will begin any minute now.
The theater is filled with spectators
waiting for that very moment.
ONE MINUTE TO THE SHOW
Snow Man's future hangs on this endeavor.
They welcome this moment
with the greatest smiles.
FEBRUARY 3
THE OPENING NIGHT OF TAKIZAWA KABUKI ZERO
The curtain lifts
on a new Takizawa Kabuki.
MUSICAL SUITE
Japanese music with Western dance.
SWORD FIGHT (MONOCHROME)
BALLAD "MY FRIEND"
TAIKO DRUMS
What the band members spent more time
than anything else on in training...
The taiko.
TAKIZAWA KABUKI GOEMON ZERO
And now even deeper into old Japan.
TAKIZAWA KABUKI SAKURA NO MAI DANCE
The climax of the play is the ladder,
for which Iwamoto has overcome his injury.
Watching the show, it's clear to see
that this form of entertainment that fuses
all these Japanese elements has blossomed.
Takizawa Kabuki ZERO.
Tonight, they've used up
every last one of their abilities.
Thank you.
-Great show.
-Thanks, everyone.
I love ZERO!
The dressing rooms, after the show.
Everyone's beaming from ear to ear.
That was seriously the best.
Great, wasn't it?
I feel our energy and enthusiasm
came across to the audience.
Still excited, Iwamoto and Fukazawa
are heading somewhere.
It's a show debriefing
with the main crew members.
What they want to hear above all
is the appraisal of Takizawa himself.
On the whole,
there were no problems at all.
As the initial excitement goes down a bit,
you might find it feels routine.
So ideally, I'd like you to retain
this level of enthusiasm throughout,
if I had to say anything.
The important thing
is that they don't lose their passion.
I feel grateful and happy
that we've done the first show,
but this isn't the finish line.
There is no finish line
with Takizawa Kabuki.
That's it.
Thank you for being with us for so long.
From the first day of training
to the final night at Minamiza,
Snow Man have charged ahead
without stopping.
This is crazy.
Takizawa-kun!
-Here it comes.
-Right.
It's all about the first beat.
APRIL-MAY 2019
Takizawa Kabuki has no finish line.
Wouldn't it actually be better
to come forward here?
Just like how they're back in action
as they're joined by Raul.
for the next leg of the show.
Their new journey that began with ZERO
moves to the next step.
Snow Man, a unit with an overwhelming
amount of passion.
And they're going to keep on dancing.
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams