Finished, sir?
Yeah. Hey, do you have a light?
Old Gold man, huh?
Lucky Strike here.
Can I ask you a question?
Why do you smoke Old Gold?
I'm sorry, sir.
Is Sam here bothering you?
He can be a little chatty.
No, we're actually just
having a conversation.
Is that okay?
Can I get you another drink?
Yeah. Do this again.
Old-fashioned, please.
So you obviously need to relax
after working here all night.
I guess. I don't know.
But what is it? I mean, low-tar?
Those new filters?
Why... I mean... Why Old Gold?
They gave 'em to us in the service...
a carton a week for free.
So you're used to 'em,
is that it?
Yeah. They're a habit.
I could never get you
to try another brand...
say, my Luckies?
I love my Old Golds.
All right, well, let's just say tomorrow
a tobacco weevil comes
and eats every last
Old Gold on the planet.
That's a sad story.
It's a tragedy.
Would you just stop smoking?
I think I could find something.
I love smoking.
"I love smoking. " That's very good.
My wife hates it.
Reader's Digest says it will kill you.
Yeah, I heard about that.
Ladies love their magazines.
Yes, they do.
You weren't worried
about waking me, were you?
Am I interrupting anything?
Mmm, no.
You're lucky I'm still up working
and I'm alone.
How's it going?
They invented something called
Grandmother's Day.
That ought to keep me busy
drawing puppies for a few months.
Can I run a few ideas past you?
Does that mean
what I think it means?
Because I'm familiar
with most of your ideas.
I'm having a situation
with my cigarette account.
Wow, you really are here to talk.
The Trade Commission is cracking down
on all of our health claims.
I get Reader's Digest.
This is the same scare
you had five years ago.
You dealt with it.
I know I slept a lot better
knowing doctors smoke.
Well, that's just it.
The whole "safer cigarette"
thing is over.
No more doctors,
no more testimonials,
no more cough-free,
soothes your T-zone,
low-tar, low-nicotine, filter tip.
Nothing.
All I have is a crush-proof box
and "four out of five
dead people smoke your brand. "
Is this the part where I say,
"Don Draper is the greatest ad man ever,
"and his big, strong brain will find a way
to lead the sheep
to the slaughterhouse"?
I don't want to go to school tomorrow.
You gonna pitch to me or not?
Midge, I'm serious. I have nothing.
I am over, and they're
finally gonna know it.
Next time you see me,
there will be a bunch
of young executives
picking meat off my ribs.
That's a pretty picture.
What's your secret?
Nine different ways to say...
"I love you, Grandma. "
We should get married.
You think I'd make a good ex-wife?
I'm serious.
You have your own business.
You don't mind when I come over.
What size Cadillac do you take?
You know the rules.
I don't make plans,
and I don't make breakfast.
Sterling's having the tobacco people in
in nine hours, and I have nothing.
People love smoking.
There's nothing that you,
the Trade Commission,
or Reader's Digest
can do to change that.
There's this kid who comes
by my office every day,
looks where he's gonna put his plants.
Is he handsome?
23.
Uh, not right away.
Pal, could you take the long way up?
I am really enjoying the view here.
You going to Campbell's
bachelor party?
Yeah, I want to be there
before they tie an anchor around his neck
and drag him out to sea.
I hear she's a nice girl.
Eh, who wants that?
What did you do that for?
She'll probably be
assigned to one of us.
Then she'll know what she's in for.
You got to let them know
what kind of guy you are.
Then they'll know what kind of girl to be.
I have a feeling we won't be going
to your bachelor party soon.
Yeah, well, compared to Campbell,
I'm a Boy Scout.
Excuse me. Is he expecting you?
He's not expecting anything.
Oh, honey, don't worry.
I'll get home safely.
I have an important
appointment right now,
so why don't you go
shopping or something?
Take your mother to lunch.
Tell her it was my idea.
Wow. He's good.
It's just a bachelor party, dear.
No, I really don't know
what they have planned,
but judging from the creative brain power
around here,
we'll probably end up
seeing My Fair Lady.
I'll tell you what.
I'll drop by your place on my way home.
Your mother can check
under my fingernails.
Of course I love you.
I'm giving up my life to be with you, aren't I?
What a great gal.
Tell ya, boys,
she stole my heart.
And her old man's loaded.
Now, this is the executive floor.
It should be organized, but it's not,
so you'll find account executives
and creative executives all mixed in together.
Please don't ask me the difference.
Great.
Hopefully, if you follow my lead,
you can avoid some of the mistakes
I've made here.
- Hello, Joan.
- Like that one.
So how many trains did it take you?
Only one, but I got up very early.
In a couple of years,
with the right moves,
you'll be in the city with the rest of us.
Of course, if you really make
the right moves,
you'll be out in the country,
and you won't be going to work at all.
You'll be here just
across the aisle from me.
We'll both take care of Mr. Draper
for the time being.
I don't know what your goals are,
but don't overdo it with the perfume.
Keep a fifth of something
in your desk.
Mr. Draper drinks rye.
Also, invest in some
aspirin, Band-Aids,
and a needle and thread.
Rye is Canadian, right?
You better find out.
He may act like he wants a secretary,
but most of the time,
they're looking for something
between a mother and a waitress.
And the rest of the time, well...
Go home, take a paper bag,
and cut some eyeholes out of it.
Put it over your head, get undressed,
and look at yourself in the mirror.
Really evaluate where your strengths
and weaknesses are,
and be honest.
I always try to be honest.
Good for you.
Now, try not to be overwhelmed
by all this technology.
It looks complicated,
but the men who designed it made it
simple enough for a woman to use.
I sure hope so.
At lunch, pick up a box of chocolates,
a dozen carnations,
and some bath salts.
I'll explain later.
Thank you, Miss Holloway.
You're really wonderful
for looking out for me this way.
It's Joan.
And listen,
don't take this the wrong way,
but a girl like you,
with those darling little ankles,
I'd find a way to make 'em sing.
Also, men love scarves.
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
Oh! And Mr. Sterling. How are you?
Morning, girls.
You look like a hundred bucks.
Long night?
It's not this tobacco thing, is it?
It's been on my mind.
Yeah, well, I should hope so.
Lee Garner, his father,
the whole Lucky Strike family
will be here at 4.
You worried?
No.
If I was worried,
I'd ask you what you've got,
but I'm not, so I'm just going to assume
you've got something,
which means you should be worried.
So you came here because you wanted
to watch me get dressed?
No, I wanted to make sure
you were here.
In body. Give me about a half hour
for the rest of it.
How do I put this?
Have we ever hired any Jews?
Not on my watch.
That's very funny. It's not what I meant.
We've got an Italian.
Salvatore, my art director.
- That won't work.
- Sorry.
Most of the Jewish guys
work for the Jewish firms.
Yeah, I know.
Selling Jewish products to Jewish people.
That's very good.
It's just that our 11:00
is with Menken's Department Store
and I wish we had someone
to make them feel... comfortable.
You want me to run
down to the deli and grab somebody?
You missed a button.
Ah. Look at you, Gidget.
Still trying to fill out that bikini?
Summer's coming.
Without the medical claims,
all we have is a white box
with a red spot on it.
My neighbor posed for that.
Believe me, he always
looks very relaxed.
Of course, he doesn't smoke.
Had him hold a pencil.
If I know these guys,
you're better off with a little sex appeal.
Can you give me a woman
in a bathing suit,
put her next to your guy?
A sexy girl? I can do that.
Give you a chance
to get a real model.
Oh, I love my work.
Speaking of sexy girls,
are you going to Pete's bachelor party?
I'm not really big on those things.
Tell me about it. It's so embarrassing.
If a girl's gonna shake it in my face,
I want to be alone so I can do something.
Should we drink before
the meeting or after?
Or both?
So... that's it, huh? Relax?
Don't be short with me.
You're the writer.
I thought it was worth a try.
Greta Guttman is here to see you.
Send her in.
Oh, great.
Now we get to hear from our man in research.
Mr. Draper, Mr. Romano,
you both seemed more relaxed
than I expected.
Do you have some kind of surprise
for the tobacco people?
I'm doing my own research.
If you're planning to continue
with medical testimony,
you'll only be inviting
further government interference.
We must police ourselves.
- There's your slogan.
- The medical thing is dead.
We understand that.
Yes, dead. An apt choice of words,
considering the public is convinced
that cigarettes are poisonous.
If we can't insist that they're not,
I believe my most recent surveys
have provided a solution.
We can still suggest
that cigarettes are part of American life,
or too good to give up,
or, most appealing,
an assertion of independence.
So, basically, if you love danger,
you'll love smoking.
We can put a skull
and crossbones on the label.
I love it.
Before the war,
when I studied with Adler in Vienna,
we postulated that what Freud called
the death wish
is as powerful a drive
as those for sexual reproduction
and physical sustenance.
Freud, you say?
What agency is he with?
So we're supposed to believe
that people are all living one way
and secretly thinking
the exact opposite?
That's ridiculous.
Let me tell you something,
Miss Guttman...
Doctor.
Dr. Guttman.
Psychology might be great
at cocktail parties,
but it so happens that people were
buying cigarettes before Freud was born.
The issue here isn't
why should people smoke.
It's why should people
smoke Lucky Strike.
Suggesting that our customers have a...
What did you call it? A death wish?
I just don't see that on a billboard.
So what if Reader's Digest
says they're dangerous?
They also said Bambi
was the book of the century.
There's no proof.
There's conclusive proof
that none of these low-tar,
low-nicotine, or filtration systems
have any effect on the incidences
of lung cancer.
Just give me the damn report.
I think you'll find it very convincing.
I'm sure I will.
You're the one who found
all of our medical testimonials
in the first place.
That's true, Mr. Draper, but I...
Has anyone else seen this?
Of course not. It's your account.
Good.
I don't want to hear about it anymore.
I'm sorry. I just find your whole
approach perverse.
Good luck at the meeting.
I'm sure it will be a quick one.
Sal, I'll take that drink now.
Mr. Draper.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to wake you,
but Mr. Campbell is outside.
He doesn't know I'm sleeping in here, does he?
No, sir.
That's good.
Who are you?
I'm Peggy Olsen, the new girl.
Can you go out there
and entertain him?
I know it's my first day,
and I don't want to seem uncooperative,
but do I have to?
I see your point.
I brought you some aspirin.
Send him in.
You look like a hundred bucks.
Ready to go sweet-talk
some retail Jews?
You are tough to take
first thing in the morning, Pete.
I've never had any complaints.
Speaking of which,
who's your little friend here?
She's the new girl.
You always get the new girl.
Management gets all the perks.
Where are you from, honey?
Miss Deaver's Secretarial School.
Top notch.
But I meant where are you from?
Are you Amish or something?
No. I'm from Brooklyn.
Well, you're in the city now.
It wouldn't be a sin
for us to see your legs.
If you pull your waist in,
you might look like a woman.
Is that all, Mr. Draper?
Hey, I'm not done here.
I'm working my way up.
That will be all.
Peggy, right?
Yes.
Oh, and it's time for
your 11:00 meeting.
Oh, and sorry about Mr. Campbell here.
He left his manners
back at the fraternity house.
She's a little young for you, Draper.
The future Mrs. Pete Campbell
is a very lucky woman.
When's the wedding again?
Sunday. Did Ken tell you
about the bachelor party tonight?
He sure did.
So do I get first crack at her?
Word is she took down more sailors
than The Arizona.
How old are you, Pete?
I just turned 26.
I bet the whole world looks like
one great big brassiere strap
just waiting to be snapped, huh?
You are good with words, Draper.
Campbell, we're both men here,
so I'm gonna be direct.
Christ, are you already
sleeping with her?
Advertising is a very small world,
and when you do something
like malign the reputation
of a girl from the steno pool
on her first day,
you make it even smaller.
Keep it up, and even if you do get my job,
you'll never run this place.
You'll die in that corner office,
a mid-level executive
with a little bit of hair
who women go home with out of pity.
Want to know why?
Because no one will like you.
Oh! Here are our miracle-workers now.
You know Pete Campbell, of course,
your account executive
if you choose to do business with us.
And this handsome fellow is Don Draper,
the best creative director in New York.
Well, at least the building.
Pleasure to meet you.
Oop. Sorry about that.
I'm Rachel Menken.
Oh. Uh, sorry. I was expecting...
You were expecting me to be a man.
My father was, too.
And you are?
Why, Don, you remember David Cohen
from the art department.
Of course! David.
One of the rising stars
here at Sterling Cooper.
Well, why don't we make
ourselves comfortable?
And, Miss Menken, you can tell us
what you have in mind.
Wonderful.
That's very subtle.
Isn't that your shirt?
Had to go all the way to the mailroom,
but I found one.
So you must be Peggy Olsen.
Joan Holloway sent you over.
She's a great girl. How is Joan?
She sends her regards.
She's a lot of fun.
Must be a scream to work with her.
Yes, it's pretty terrific.
Try to make yourself comfortable.
Relax.
I see from your chart, and your finger,
that you're not married.
That's right.
And yet you're interested
in the contraceptive pills.
Well, I was...
No reason to be nervous.
Joan sent you to me
because I'm not here to judge you.
There's nothing wrong
with a woman being practical
about the possibility of sexual activity.
Spread your knees.
That's good to hear.
Although, as a doctor,
I'd like to think that putting a woman
in this situation
is not gonna turn her
into some kind of strumpet.
Slide your fanny toward me.
I'm not gonna bite.
I'll warn you now,
I will take you off this medicine if you abuse it.
It's for your own good, really.
But the fact is,
even in our modern times,
easy women don't find husbands.
I understand, Dr. Emerson.
I really am a very responsible person.
Well, I'm sure you're not
that kind of girl.
Now, Joan...
I'm just kidding along here.
You can get dressed.
I'm gonna write you
a prescription for Enovid.
They're $11 a month,
but don't think you have to go out
and become the town pump
just to get your money's worth.
Excuse my French.
So what Don is saying
is that through a variety of media,
including a spot during
The Danny Thomas Show,
if you can afford it,
we could really boost awareness.
Then, a 10% off coupon
in select ladies' magazines
will increase your first-time visitors.
Once we get them into the store,
the rest... is kind of up to you.
Mr. Draper, our store is 60 years old.
We share a wall with Tiffany's.
Honestly, a coupon?
Miss Menken, coupons work.
I think your father would
agree with the strategy.
He might, but he's not here
because we just
had our lowest sales year ever.
So I suppose what I think
matters most right now.
Miss Menken, why did you come here?
There are a dozen other agencies
better suited to your... needs.
If I wanted some man who happened
to be from the same... village as my father
to manage my account,
I could have stayed where I was.
Their research favors coupons, too.
It's not just research, Miss Menken.
Housewives love coupons.
I'm not interested in housewives.
What kind of people do you want?
I want your kind of people, Mr. Draper:
People who don't care about coupons,
whether or not they can afford it.
People who are coming to the store
because it is expensive.
We obviously have very different ideas.
Yes, like the customer is always right?
Gentlemen, I really thought
you could do better than this.
Sterling Cooper has a reputation
for being innovative.
Miss, you are way out of line.
Don, please.
Let's not get emotional here.
There's no reason
we can't talk this out.
Talk out what? This silly idea
that people are gonna come
to some store they've never been to
because it's more expensive?
It works for Chanel.
Menken's is not Chanel.
That's a vote of confidence.
What Don's saying is,
Chanel is a very different kind of place.
It's French, it's continental, it's...
Not just another
Jewish department store?
Exactly.
You were right, Roger.
This place really runs on charm.
- This is ridiculous.
- Don.
I'm not gonna let a woman
talk to me like this.
This meeting is over.
Good luck, Miss Menken.
Hey, Don, I don't blame you.
She was way out of line.
Adding money and education
doesn't take the rude edge out of people.
Roger's not gonna be happy,
so I guess that's good for you.
I'm not gonna pretend I don't want your job,
but you were right.
I'm not great with people, and you are.
I mean, not counting
that meeting we were just in.
So I'm kind of counting
on you to help me out.
There's plenty of room at the top.
Look, I'm sorry I was
so hard on you before.
It's just this damn tobacco thing.
You'll think of something.
A man like you
I'd follow into combat blindfolded,
and I wouldn't be the first.
Am I right, buddy?
Let's take it a little slower.
I don't want to wake up pregnant.
Fuck you.
Dr. Emerson's a dream, isn't he?
He seemed nice.
He has a place in South Hampton.
I'm not saying that I've seen it,
but it's beautiful.
Now, don't be nervous,
but this is the nerve center of the office.
You and your boss rely on the willing
and cheerful cooperation
of a few skilled employees.
Never snap, yell,
or be sarcastic with them.
And above all, always be a supplicant.
I know you girls are busy,
but we've got a new one.
Peggy, this is Marge, Nanette, and Ivy.
I brought you some things.
I guess a sort of
"getting to know you" gift.
Well, aren't you a sweetheart?
If I know Joan, the candy's for me.
Joan, you're not fair.
You know she has to lose 8 pounds
by the Christmas party.
I think you look great.
Yeah, it's because I'm sitting down.
You can come back and visit
any time you want, honey.
Who does she work for?
Don Draper.
They got rid of Eleanor?
She moved on.
Draper wasn't interested.
Well, she couldn't get a call through.
Rude little thing.
We see that you've got your hands full.
Don't want to be a bother.
Nice meeting you.
Hey, you have great legs.
I bet you Mr. Draper would like them
if he could see them.
Sterling Cooper.
How may I direct your call?
I just don't know what we have to do
to make these government interlopers happy.
They tell us to make a safer cigarette,
we do it,
and then suddenly that's not good enough.
Might as well be living in Russia.
Damn straight.
You know, this morning I got a call
from my competitors
at Brown & Williamson,
and they're getting sued
by the federal government
because of the health claims they made.
Yeah, we're aware of that, Mr. Garner,
but you have to realize
that through the manipulation
of the mass media,
the public is under the impression
that your cigarettes are linked to...
certain fatal diseases.
Manipulation of the media?
Hell, that's what I pay you for.
Our product is fine.
I smoke 'em myself.
My granddad smoked 'em.
He died at 95 years old.
He was hit by a truck.
I understand. But our hands are tied.
We're no longer allowed to advertise
that Lucky Strikes are safe.
So what the hell are we gonna do?
We've already funded
our own tobacco research center
to put this whole rumor to rest.
And that's a very good start.
But it may not affect sales.
Don, I think maybe that's your cue.
Well, uh...
I have been, uh...
thinking quite a bit about this,
and, uh...
I mean, you know I'm a Lucky Strike man
from way back, so...
I might have a solution.
At Sterling Cooper, we've been pioneering
the burgeoning field of research,
and our analysis shows that the health risks
associated with your product
is not the end of the world.
People get in their cars
every day to go to work,
and some of them die.
Cars are dangerous.
There's nothing you can do about it.
You still have to get where you're going.
Cigarettes are exactly the same,
so why don't we simply say,
"So what if cigarettes are dangerous?
"You're a man.
"The world is dangerous.
"Smoke your cigarette.
You still have to get where you're going. "
That's very interesting.
I mean, if cigarettes were dangerous,
it would be interesting.
Except they aren't.
That's your slogan?
"You're going to die anyway. Die with us"?
Actually, it's a fairly well-established
psychological principle
that society has a death wish,
and if we could just tap into that,
the market potential is...
What the hell are you talking about?
Are you insane?
I'm not selling rifles here.
I'm in the tobacco business.
We're selling America.
The Indians gave it to us, for shit's sake.
Come on, Dad.
Let's get out of here.
The bright spot is at least we know
if we have this problem,
everybody has this problem.
Gentlemen, before you leave,
can I just say something?
I don't know, Don. Can you?
The Federal Trade Commission
and Reader's Digest
have done you a favor.
They've let you know that
any ad that brings up
the concept of cigarettes
and health together...
Well, it's just gonna
make people think of cancer.
Yes, and we're grateful to them.
But what Lee, Jr., said is right.
If you can't make those health claims,
neither can your competitors.
So we've got a lot of people
not saying anything that sells cigarettes.
Not exactly.
This is the greatest advertising opportunity
since the invention of cereal.
We have six identical companies
making six identical products.
We can say anything we want.
How do you make your cigarettes?
I don't know.
Shame on you.
We breed insect-repellent tobacco seeds,
plant them in the North Carolina sunshine,
grow it, cut it, cure it, toast it...
There you go.
But everybody else's tobacco is toasted.
No. Everybody else's
tobacco is poisonous.
Lucky Strikes...
is toasted.
Well, gentlemen, I don't think I have to tell you
what you just witnessed here.
I think you do.
Advertising is based on one thing:
Happiness.
And you know what happiness is?
Happiness is the smell of a new car.
It's freedom from fear.
It's a billboard on the side of the road
that screams with reassurance
that whatever you're doing... it's okay.
You are okay.
It's toasted.
I get it.
You had me worried.
I don't know if you were drunk or not drunk,
but that was inspired.
For the record, I pulled it out of thin air,
so thank you, up there.
You're looking in the wrong direction.
So now that I've got you
in the afterglow here,
what do you say you reconsider this
presidential campaign?
I don't know. Bunting and babies?
That's hard work.
I'd only make hash of it.
Modesty. That's adorable.
Consider the product:
He's young, handsome, Navy hero.
Honestly, it shouldn't be too difficult
to convince America Dick Nixon is a winner.
Mr. Draper, you've got visitors.
Could you be a little
more specific, honey?
We heard you saved the day.
Oh, thank you, boys. I appreciate it.
I told them how amazing you were.
I'm still tingling.
Well, looks like you're all going to engage
in a little mid-level camaraderie,
so I'll be on my way.
Don, thanks again for the home run.
- I love to come through.
- Speaking of which,
any chance you could
patch things up with Rachel Menken?
Any way you can be
as charming as I said you were?
Haven't you had enough
of my magic for one day?
She's worth $3 million.
You're a whore.
Peggy...
Could she get us a little more ice?
- Yes, Mr. Draper?
- Just a minute.
Fellas, I think this party's gonna
have to move elsewhere.
We'll move wherever you want, but it's 5:15.
The bachelor party's underway.
I don't know.
Oh, come on, Don. All hands on deck.
Aren't you gonna help
give Pete his big sendoff?
Maybe next time.
Come on, guys.
Don will join us later, right, Don?
If Greta's research was any good,
I would have used it.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying I had a report just like that.
And it's not like there's
some magic machine
that makes identical copies of things.
I still think she was right.
Have a great night, Pete.
Congratulations.
I heard you were
amazing in the meeting.
Fear stimulates my imagination.
I just wanted to thank you
for a great first day,
and for, you know...
standing up for me with Mr. Campbell.
First of all, Peggy,
I'm your boss, not your boyfriend.
Second of all, you ever let Pete Campbell
go through my trash again,
and you won't be able to find a job
selling sandwiches in Penn Station.
He said he left his fountain pen in here.
I didn't know.
I hope you don't think
I'm that kind of girl.
Of course not.
Go home. Put your curlers in.
We'll get a fresh start tomorrow.
Oh. And, Peggy,
I need you to place a call.
I want to see you here every 15 minutes,
whether you have drinks or not.
Uh, every five minutes.
Let's live here.
Better do more than look tonight.
Do you have a girlfriend, Salvatore?
Come on. I'm Italian.
Is there some kind of party here?
How did you swing it?
They work at the Automat.
He pressed a button, and they came out.
I hope we're not interrupting anything.
Definitely not.
Well, I have the best seat.
What are we drinking?
More of whatever's
making you the way you are.
I love this place.
It's hot, loud, and filled with men.
I know what you mean.
Oh, my God. I can already feel it.
I have a feeling you're like this all the time.
I like to laugh.
Is that right?
Now, you stop that.
You said you like to laugh.
I mean it.
It's... It's too...
Too delicious.
Hey, I said stop it.
What do you think you're doing?
You know exactly.
Um, you know what, girls?
I think we should go.
Oh, come on.
You're hurting me.
I'll be good.
Buy the girls whatever they want.
So, uh, what do you fellas do?
You're looking at the finest
ad men in New York.
Hell, the world.
For the lady, a special Mai Tai,
and one whiskey neat.
So...
you're going to ply me with drinks
and convince me what a terrible
mistake I'm making.
That is quite a drink.
You got in trouble, didn't you?
I shouldn't have lost my temper,
and I certainly
shouldn't have treated you
like anything less than a client.
Apology accepted.
So you understand.
Now I do.
It was, uh, refreshing, really.
I mean, actually hearing all the things
I always assumed people were thinking.
Well, I'm not really as bad as all that.
I was under a lot of pressure.
Another account.
Doesn't really matter.
No, it doesn't.
So, without making things worse,
can I ask you a personal question?
Don't you want to get
a second drink in me first?
Why aren't you married?
Are you asking
what's wrong with me?
It's just that you're
a beautiful, educated woman.
Don't you think that getting married
and having a family
would make you happier
than all the headaches
that go along with...
fighting people like me?
If I weren't a woman,
I would be allowed
to ask you the same question.
And if I weren't a woman,
I wouldn't have to choose
between putting on an apron
and the thrill of making my father's store
what I always thought it should be.
So that's it. You won't get married
because you find business to be a thrill.
That and...
I've never been in love.
She won't get married
because she's never been in love.
I think I wrote that once to sell nylons.
For a lot of people,
love isn't just a slogan.
Oh, you mean love.
You mean the big
lightning bolt to the heart
where you can't eat and you can't work
and you just run off
and get married and make babies.
The reason you haven't felt it
is because it doesn't exist.
What you call love
was invented by guys
like me to sell nylons.
Is that right?
I'm pretty sure about it.
You're born alone,
and you die alone,
and this world just drops
a bunch of rules on you
to make you forget those facts,
but I never forget.
I'm living like there's no tomorrow...
because there isn't one.
I don't think I realized it until this moment,
but it must be hard being a man, too.
Excuse me?
Mr. Draper...
- Don.
- Mr. Draper,
I don't know what it is
you really believe in,
but I do know what it feels like
to be out of place, to be disconnected,
to see the whole world
laid out in front of you
the way other people live it.
There is something about you
that tells me you know it, too.
I don't know if that's true.
You want another drink?
No.
But you can tell your boss
that you charmed me.
So I guess we'll be
seeing each other again.
I'll be back in the office Monday morning,
for a real meeting.
I'd like that.
We're not buying anything.
Actually, for the first time today,
I'm not selling anything.
Does Peggy live here?
Hold on.
Do you know him?
It's okay, Marjorie.
We work together.
He's really drunk.
It's okay, Marjorie.
So... what are you doing?
Nothing.
Just, uh, sitting in my room
listening to records.
I'm getting married on Sunday.
I heard that.
You must think I'm a creep.
Why are you here?
I wanted to see you tonight.
Me?
I had to see you.
Marjorie?
Yeah, Peg?
I'm going to bed now.
I called the office. They said you'd left.
I didn't want to bother you.
It's no bother.
I just assumed you were staying
in the city again.
There's a plate in the oven.
Unless you're not hungry.
I'm not.
I'll be right back.
Don't move.