Mommy, look at that!
Hello.
Don Draper. How are you?
Probably about like you:
Enduring the splendor of Fiorellol
You know we got
that Israeli tourism thing, right?
Mazel tov.
I ran into Jim Jordan from BBDO
at the Athletic Club
with, uh, Frank from Y&R.
Your name came up.
Three millionaires
in towels in a steam room.
I don't know how to take that.
Take it as a compliment,
a sign that you're
destined for greater things.
I think "Jesus Over Rio"
was the best tourist campaign
I've seen in over 20 years.
Wasn't good enough
to land the Israelis.
Ah, that's not you.
That's the tiny store you work in.
Now, if you were with me at McCann,
you'd have over 500 people
at your disposal...
and that's just in New York.
We can get a lot of things done.
Can you get me out
of the second half of this show?
All I'm saying is you've done your time
in the farm leagues.
Yankee Stadium is on the line.
I changed my mind.
I decided you deserve a visit to the bar.
Adele, this is Donald Draper.
If we're being introduced,
I assume that you're in advertising.
Would you both like
to talk about that some more?
Betty.
My wife.
Jim and Adele Hobart.
Hello. Betty Draper.
A pleasure.
Your husband here was about to prove
that he can speak about things
other than advertising.
Oh, he's very interesting.
Well, then, come with me.
Let's get those drinks.
We'll be back.
Champagne?
Besides getting the handsome prince,
are you an actress or something?
No, I'm a housewife.
I did do some modeling...
a lifetime ago.
I'm not surprised.
That is some face you've got there.
Anybody ever tell you
you're a dead ringer for Grace Kelly?
They used to.
You know what?
Coca-Cola's deep into this, uh,
international campaign right now.
A European face like yours,
like Grace Kelly's,
might be a road we could go down.
Uh, we could put a call out
for a Grace Kelly type,
but, uh, I don't think we'd come this close.
You say you've modeled?
I'm retired.
This is silly.
Think about it.
Your coloring with a green bottle
and an Irish setter...
Oh, drink up.
It's back to Tammany Hall.
I like the show.
Very gay songs.
Well, we'd better get back in there or leave.
Come on.
Uh, it was very nice
meeting both of you.
Why didn't you want
to go to dinner with Jim and Adele?
People like Jim Hobart
always talk business
because they have
nothing else to say.
I can see that.
You know, he gave me his card.
Really?
Did he tell you to put it
under my pillow of something?
No. Actually, he was talking to me
about modeling.
Was he?
I don't think it was like that.
He said something about Grace Kelly
and Coca-Cola.
Well, then, there's no need
to doubt his interest, then.
I did model, Don.
Am I that wrong for Coca-Cola?
You're not wrong for anything.
So are you going to go there?
How was Fiorello exclamation point?
Lt'll be six months before I can get Don
back into a Broadway theater.
Oh, we ran into this agency head.
Apparently he's courting Don.
He gave me his card.
Asked me if I wanted to do any modeling.
That's a heck of a line.
What did Don say?
He basically said the man was trying
to sleep with one of us
and that he didn't like the idea of either.
I did do some modeling, you know.
I did not know, but I'm not surprised.
Carlton calls you Grace Kelly.
I was a model when I met Don.
A model in Manhattan?
Yes.
It was exciting.
But when I got started...
the summer after college, in Italy.
Italy?
There was this Italian designer: Giovanni.
He wanted to be called Johnny.
That's how much he loved Americans.
Well, he loved American girls.
It was more of an artist/muse relationship.
Okay.
So... he made you all this,
and it was platonic?
No petting, nothing?
Mamma mia.
And put my hair up like this.
And Salvatore said he has
the Menken's artwork,
and to meet him in the art department
because you're going
to need a red pencil.
Any other good news?
I think the mail boy
dropped that off for you last night.
Peggy, can you get me
an outside line?
Right away.
Don Draper.
Now, why would you
call me out of the blue?
I appreciate the gesture.
It's not a gesture, Don,
it's an overture.
Let me tell you, you're
a hard man to run into.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
The next step is a quiet rendezvous.
The Algonquin?
There's a small hotel.
Isn't that the song?
I don't know. I'm...
I'm not ready to wave the flag just yet.
What about the details?
I'd rather do this face-to-face.
But you already know
what you're going to say.
I don't have to tell you
the obvious limitations of Sterling Cooper.
But you're going to.
Do I need to be careful here?
It's a mom-and-pop.
McCann Erickson
is an international company.
We have a network that extends
far beyond Madison Avenue:
Europe, South America.
We're publicly traded.
We issue dividends.
Small is bad.
Don,
do you know the kind
of clients we attract?
Pan Am, Coca-Cola,
Esso.
Can you imagine the lifestyle
that goes with handling Pan Am?
It's a panty-dropper.
Television?
You could be in that in a bigger way.
You know that.
What, you want to sell corn?
We do a show about Indians.
Imagine yourself
in a three-year contract.
35 per annum, security set in stone.
Sterling probably hasn't
let you break 30 yet.
No comment.
I really don't like
doing this over the phone.
All I can say is
eventually you come up here,
or you die wondering.
He gave me his card right in front of Don.
Well, not right in front of him, I guess.
Well, I told Don about it.
I was a model, you know?
In fact, I met Don on a photo shoot.
I was wearing this Russian blue fox coat.
He was just a copywriter at the fur company.
I remember
he saw that I didn't like
giving the coat back.
It's always the hardest part.
He asked me out.
He wasn't shy. I liked that.
I said no.
Then three weeks later,
the coat arrived at my apartment.
Who knows what kind
of Indian trading
he had to do to get it?
I think I only had
two more jobs, maybe three,
before we got engaged.
And then I got pregnant.
It's always a nightmare
raising children in Manhattan,
so we moved to Ossining.
Suddenly I...
really felt so old.
Tell me more about that.
My mother was very concerned
about looks and weight.
And I've always eaten a lot.
And I like hot dogs.
Mother used to say,
"You're going to get stout. "
And then I became a model,
and she hated it,
even though Suzy Parker
made $100,000 that year.
My mother hated it.
Manhattan.
She called me a prostitute.
You're angry at your mother.
What?
Are you going to talk now?
You are angry at your mother.
Of all the things I've said in here.
You're sitting up.
You don't listen to me.
You don't listen to what I say,
and then out of nowhere you provoke me.
Tell me more about that.
I miss her.
I understand that.
It's good and bad.
She wanted me to be beautiful
so I could find a man.
There's nothing wrong with that.
But then what?
Just sit and... smoke and...
let it go till you're in a box?
I don't care why he gave me his card.
Where'd you get this?
Kurt Teasdale over at Gil Bascom.
It's already on the air.
They wanted to do it
before she had the baby.
Am I alone? I don't understand it.
Because it's in Spanish.
I recognize that finishing school voice.
You can't govern and listen to that all day.
I'm happy to give up
any Spanish speakers
and hope this goes away.
Cooper thinks if Kennedy creeps up
any more in the polls,
Nixon will panic,
and they'll get desperate for our efforts.
He wants everything in place.
More risk.
Why are we doing this again?
And out of pocket?
I for one don't question
the wishes of our clients.
Clients come and go, Campbell.
Sometimes it's best to rid them
of unrealistic expectations.
Are you trying to say that we can't win?
Nixon's got an 8-point lead in the polls.
Not much.
And we still haven't figured out a way
to make an impact about
the Nixon campaign's involvement.
My marching orders
were undecided states.
I think a plan of attack
would make Coop happy.
The 50/50s: Texas, New Jersey, and Illinois.
Now, it's easy to just say that, isn't it?
I think women will hate her.
It's like their better-looking sister
marries a handsome senator,
and she's going to live in the White House.
I'm practically jealous.
Hi.
I called.
I assumed you were staying in the city.
The girl.
We gave her a little extra work,
and now she's distracted.
Look at that.
It's raw, Don.
Don, I realized something today.
I miss modeling.
You were always
telling me you hated it.
Maybe the passing of time
has made me... feel differently.
Maybe it's Jim Hobart.
So what?
It's still an opportunity.
You want to go back to work?
A few days. I mean, is that so bad?
I get paid.
I can get Ethel to watch the kids.
She watches them half the time now.
That's three-, four-hour stretches.
I think it would be fun
to go in and be that girl again.
You're serious?
There will still be ham.
I promise.
Are you resolved?
Or is this even worth arguing?
No, it's not like that.
It's just... something I'd like to do.
Well, I can't stop you
from doing what you want to do.
You have no idea
how boring it is around here.
Really? I would think one hour
on the Sterling Cooper switchboard
would be a Russian novel.
They told me it would happen,
but the truth is
you really just stop listening.
And put ice on your wrists.
Peggy, do you need to go home?
What?
The sweater.
Are you having one of those days?
It's not that.
I'd like to go home,
but I just don't think I can.
Then what is it?
You're not helping your silhouette.
I ripped my skirt.
You don't have a needle and thread?
It's a big rip.
Oh, honey, I've got
a spare outfit squirreled away.
You can borrow it.
We're not exactly dressed
for that, are we?
I've lost men like you before.
It usually had to do with
my unexpressed confidence.
I think you're one in a million, Draper.
Those are nice clubs.
That bonus from Cooper
must have made you happy.
It was designed as a kind of an armor
against men like Jim Hobart.
How'd you hear about it?
I saw those clubs
going down the hallway.
I thought they were for me.
They're from Jim Hobart.
What did he offer?
Bigger.
The world, basically.
Well, it can't just be
a number on a salary,
because you know we're open to that.
Pan Am.
Pan Am... is not McCann Erickson.
Big talent attracts big clients.
We can try and make
that happen here.
- That's true.
- But don't be fooled.
You hear Pan Am,
you imagine London,
holed up at the Dorchester
with three stewardesses.
The truth is it's more like
a 20-hour boomerang flight
so you can make
a coupon sing in Spanish.
And when you have stockholders
like McCann does,
you can't fire clients.
I know you'll hate that.
I thought about leaving once.
But you know?
It's daunting.
Why entertain the prospect of failure?
That's a sad thought.
No. It made me look at this place.
I don't want to sound sentimental,
but it's not just accounts.
Look around here at what you have.
You want to start over?
I haven't made up my mind.
I'm taking this very personally.
Why? It's business.
Is it?
McCann Erickson is the major leagues.
Good. Let him go.
You're right. Maybe he'll take me with him.
Can you imagine the money?
I heard he's making 30 already.
He's not ten times better than me.
You love him.
Everybody loves him.
Sure. His moods and the way he talks.
I don't even know what he's
saying half the time.
Clients do.
I'll admit she crossed my mind once.
She's having a very bad
freshman year.
They went nuts for her writing.
Belle Jolie, she did that.
Belle Jolie was okay.
She obviously let it go to her head...
and other parts of her.
No, I don't think it's the job.
I think we're seeing the real her:
One of those girls
who slimmed down before she got here.
Now she's here, and there she is.
Who thinks about her?
Maybe she'll go with Draper, too.
It's a tragedy.
Piece of fruit that went real bad real fast.
And no one ever got to eat it.
Well, I got some work to do.
Suddenly upon news of others' success,
a young man is filled with ambition.
Drop dead.
Harry, you busy?
Well, hello. I can't believe this.
I'm sorry. I, uh, overdid it.
You're out of the business
a few years, and things change.
Please, I'm overwhelmed
with the style of you.
Betty Draper, meet Ronnie Gittridge.
He handles the art for Coca-Cola.
He's also my brother-in-law.
It is a pleasure.
Look at her. What did I say?
You ready to work?
I'm excited.
It's not that complicated.
He's either going to tell you
to think about something else
or just stand there.
Jim thinks everyone else's job is easy.
Shall we?
Mrs. Draper,
it's just a tryout.
No guarantees.
I told you I've done this before.
Now, where did you get that dress?
So basically,
whereas Secor previously
spent their money
on local print and radio,
we increase the network buy to 30%.
More points for each dollar.
Secor laxatives.
You know, I have to talk
to those people.
They're not what you would expect.
They have absolutely
no sense of humor about their product.
Who knew that college
was going to get me out of the army
and into laxatives?
College was the moment, wasn't it?
Fun and games... and girls.
Were you in a frat?
Alpha Delta Phi.
Also known as cutups.
We were the cutups.
We had this stray Dalmatian.
Our mascot Mamie.
So it died,
and in classic fraternity manner,
we decided to throw a party.
Mamie's funeral.
One of the pledges pipes in
that our rivals, Psi U...
They are so gung-ho.
Psi U is throwing a beauty pageant parade
on Main Street
with the girls' school down the road.
Now, my friend Chip...
he's a lawyer now...
says "Why don't we go down there
and get a permit,
throw a grand funeral for Mamie,
and let the girls run away crying?"
That's great. Did you do it?
We had police barricades
and 30 brothers following that pledge,
who had the honor of pulling
Mamie in a Radio Flyer.
That's beautiful.
Idiots.
Wait a minute.
Nixon and Kennedy
are both buying up air time
in these undecided states.
It's an arms race.
Nixon buys, Kennedy matches.
So if we can't increase
Nixon's presence,
we can decrease Kennedy's.
How do we do that?
We make big buys in New Jersey,
Illinois, and wherever
for Secor laxatives.
Well, hold on.
So Nixon's selling laxatives?
No. We're selling laxatives.
Nixon's selling Nixon.
And Kennedy's
watching Mamie's funeral.
This is scary.
It is.
Isn't it?
Even careful mothers can't completely
protect their families
from household germs
just by cleaning alone.
That's why you need Lysol.
Lysol, added to your
regular cleaning water,
eliminates germs that cause odors
that may cause illness.
Lysol: Fastest, easiest,
most effective way
to kill household germs...
It was for me.
...and lingering odors.
Who was it?
I'm the girl. The girl with the cola.
It's only a couple days' work.
You know, just a couple of photo shoots
and then some kind of testing.
But I guess you know how it works.
I do.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to ruin this.
I'm very happy for you.
I know you don't like it.
But I know you're
a little bit proud of me.
Come upstairs.
No.
Right here.
Okay.
How are these open already?
Well, Betty, we don't want life
to look difficult, now do we?
You're too much.
No! No!
Polly, no!
Let it go.
If I see that dog in my yard again,
I'm going to shoot it.
I see you got there and back in one piece.
Yes.
And even though I got lost,
I sent Ethel home at 4.
They went to the park,
then to visit Ernie at Francine's.
All in all, everyone had a nice day.
So how was it?
There was this man Ronnie.
I don't even know what his job is.
Ronnie Gittridge.
He's the art director. I've met him.
He is such a character.
He tells funny stories.
I brought the form home.
I thought you could
help me fill it out
so I can get paid.
I'd love to.
Sweetie pie.
What happened?
I had a bad dream.
Get in bed with Daddy.
What was your dream?
I don't want anyone to shoot Polly.
No one is going to do that, honey.
Yes. Mr. Brestwood said he would
because Polly ate one of his doves.
They're pigeons.
And he said this to you in your dream?
No, he said it today
when Polly ate the birdie.
She wasn't hurt that bad.
She could fly.
No one is going to hurt Polly.
Good night, honey.
Now they can't play in the yard?
I'm going to get my robe on
and go over there
and find out what happened.
2 in the morning.
He's our neighbor. You'll make it worse.
I'll talk to him.
You should have Ethel talk to him.
Don, they play in the yard
when I'm here, too.
And she didn't tell you?
I'm sure they didn't tell her.
They probably wouldn't
have told me, either.
There'll be over at Francine's
for the next shoot anyway.
It's one day.
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
Maybe not.
She'd never slept well.
That's not true.
Did you see those big tears?
I really want to get a picture
of her crying one day.
I have to say, Don,
Lucky Strike, even in this lawsuit,
is stronger than ever.
It was a brilliant campaign,
like some supersonic jet
flying right over the market.
I was there.
Great work.
Thank you.
Sorry to interrupt.
Who is responsible?
We've made a significant commitment
for as-yet unproduced
Secor laxative commercials.
This didn't go by me.
No, it went by Bob Wilkins
in Media, right to me.
Who is responsible?
Mr. Cooper, sir, it was me.
You thought of this?
Well, uh...
I bear some of the responsibility as well.
What did they do?
Every commercial block on air
in the Land of Lincoln
is clogged up with laxative buys.
And a little bit of Nixon time.
The Kennedy people won't know
what to do with themselves.
They're going to have
to put his pretty face on the radio.
And with that accent.
Nicely done.
I didn't think you had it in you,
and I mean that.
- Thank you.
Inspired.
Congratulations, boys.
Peggy, you want to write that down?
Don said congratulations.
Are we done here?
No.
I really thought
it was going to go bad for a minute.
I was sure it would.
No kidding.
You almost let me detonate
a thousand feet from the ground.
So much for camaraderie.
Mr. Rumsen sent this over.
Unopened. Very nice.
Hildy, stay. Have a drink. It's an order.
No, thank you.
I'm going to my parents' after work.
You know, when something
good happens to me,
it also happens to you.
I know that.
I said congratulations.
You should do something
with that sour puss.
You're very beautiful.
Just being honest.
I love watching you walk.
I should go.
You should.
Is he in?
Always nice to see you.
I'd give you my assurance
that nothing good will happen to that boy,
but I can't seem
to keep my word on that,
hard as I try.
I might ask you to take me with you.
I see no reason to leave.
Or maybe I see a million.
A million? Is that
what it's going to cost me?
I was thinking more like 40.
45 is good.
I'm not going to be a little girl
and ask you why you stayed.
I know it's not money,
and I hope it's not to keep
your foot on Pete Campbell.
I like the way you do business.
Well, I try to be
as civilized as you can be.
No contract.
45 and no security.
What's in it for me?
If I leave this place one day,
it will not be for more advertising.
What else is there?
I don't know. Life being lived.
I'd like to stop talking about it
and get back to it.
I've worked with a lot of men like you,
and if you had to choose a place to die,
it would be in the middle of a pitch.
I've done that.
I want to do something else.
Jim Hobart, McCann Erickson.
Of course.
Line 1.
Don,
incredible pictures, am I wrong?
No, you're not.
So, your wife's already here with us.
I know she's happy.
Why don't you join her?
I don't know about that, Jim.
You can do better than that.
You know what I'm offering here?
It's Yankee Stadium. I know.
What, did Sterling come to the rescue?
If this is about money,
I have to say I might
have judged you wrong.
It's not.
I'm surprised.
I thought your wife coming here
meant you were interested.
No, that was her idea.
Can't blame me for trying.
Maybe not, but, uh...
I can't exactly say
that was a big league move.
All's fair. No stone unturned, right?
It's a pity to lose both of you.
You're a very lucky man,
landing that woman.
What's going on with Mr. Draper?
Even if I knew, I wouldn't tell you.
Very good.
I've been meaning
to give this back to you.
I had it completely dry cleaned.
Why don't you keep it?
Have it taken in here and let out there.
It's your dress.
Hot tea. That's a good idea.
What are you talking about?
Peggy, you are falling prey
to a very common situation for new girls.
I'm not new anymore.
Well, that's just it.
Don't you want to do well here?
I'm the first girl to do any writing
in this office since the war.
Marge told me.
Writing?
Is that what this is about?
I thought you were doing that
to get close to Paul.
Thank you. Again.
I heard you were being
considered for an account
because a client's wife saw you
and thought it would be okay
if he worked with you.
You know, you're not a stick.
And yet I never wonder
what men think of me.
You're hiding a very attractive young girl
with too much lunch.
I know what men think of you:
That you're looking for a husband,
and you're fun,
and not in that order.
Peggy, this isn't China.
There's no money in virginity.
I'm not a virgin.
No. Of course not.
I just realized something.
You think you're being helpful.
Well, I am trying, dear.
I'm going home.
Did you have a good day?
I did. It was splendid.
Well, Betty, I have some good news
and some bad news.
There's bad news?
The client's moving
the international work to London.
Oh.
More Audrey Hepburn, less Grace Kelly.
I see.
As for us,
we're all going back to the malt shop.
The good news is you have two
wonderful sets of pictures
to start your book again.
That's true.
I really am sorry.
This was fun.
You can keep the dress
and the hairstyle.
I don't do that for everyone.
Oh, honey,
it has nothing to do with you.
Thank you.
What do you think, Paul?
Should we move this whole thing
down to MacDougal Street?
We're doing great here.
It's good she left.
It probably wasn't
going to happen for her tonight.
It depends how much we drink.
How drunk do you have to be?
My brother works at the Exchange.
They call a girl like her a lobster.
All the meat's in the tail.
Are they giving you guys a bonus?
Would you calm down?
Come on!
Drop you at the station?
Sure.
Campbell, you sucker-punched me.
What is wrong with you?
Come on.
You just had a fight,
and I was not part of it.
Either you two make up,
or I do not stand a chance tonight.
Perfect timing.
The children are down,
but only because they were
running around all day.
They fell asleep in front of the TV.
How did it go today?
Good. Fun.
They were talking about a whole string
of other possibilities for me.
But honestly,
I don't think I want to work anymore.
I don't like you coming home to some...
whipped-together mess
of whatever's left in the fridge.
And frankly, I don't like
Manhattan on my own.
It's harsh.
It can be.
And what am I going to do?
Run around the city with my book,
like some teenager,
making a fool of myself?
If that's what you want,
and it's my job
to give you what you want.
You do.
Look at all this.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Birdie, you know I don't care
about making my dinner
or... taking in my shirts.
You have a job.
You're mother to those two little people,
and you are better at it
than anyone else in the world.
At least in the top 500.
I would have given anything
to have had a mother like you.
Beautiful and kind...
filled with love like an angel.
You're sweet.
And this does not taste whipped-up.
No. It's good, isn't it?
Have a good day, Daddy.
You, too.
Have a good day.
We're going to the community center
to watch them fill the pool.
That sounds fun.
Have a good day.
I already am.
Mommy, I'm eating.
Be careful.
Don't jump off the bed.
Okay!
Mrs. Draper,
what the hell are you doing?
Mrs. Draper!