# You woke up
this morning #
# Got yourself a gun #
# Your momma always said
you'd be the Chosen One #
# She said you're...
you're one in a million #
# You've got
to burn to shine #
# But you were
born under a bad sign #
# With a blue moon
in your eyes #
# When you
woke up this morning #
# And all that love
had gone #
# Your papa never
told you about #
# Right and wrong #
# But you're...
you're lookin' good, baby #
# I believe that
you're feelin' fine #
# Shame about it,
born under a bad sign #
# With a blue moon
in your eyes #
- # So sing it now #
- # Woke up this morning #
# Got a blue moon...
got a blue moon in your eyes, yeah #
# Woke up this morning #
# You say you woke up
this morning #
# The world
turned upside down #
# Lordy, well,
things ain't been the same #
# Since the blues
walked in our town #
# But you're... but you're
one in a million #
# 'Cause you got that
shotgun shine #
# Shame about it,
born under a bad sign #
# With a blue moon
in your eyes, yeah #
# Woke up
this morning #
- # Uh-huh #
- # And got yourself a gun #
- # Woke up this morning #
- # Got yourself a gun #
- # Uh-huh #
- # Got yourself a gun. #
# Every night
it's the same #
# I hear your heart
turn cold as rain #
# And although
you'll be gone again #
# I hear
the front door close #
# You say you
got to go downtown #
# I guess there's
someone else you found #
# So why you're
still comin' round #
# Heaven only knows #
# Heaven only
knows just why #
# Lovin' you
should make me cry #
# Make me feel
like I could die #
# That's the way it goes #
# Heaven only ever sees #
# How love's made
a fool of me #
# I guess that's how
it's meant to be #
# But heaven only knows. #
AJ!
Jesus, Meadow,
chill out!
Inevitably, Sukanya,
what goes in must comes out.
And these people now being released
from prison were jailed
during the big mafia
crackdowns of the 1980s?
Seems like yesterday,
doesn't it?
For years we heard how law enforcement
broke the back of the mob.
Well, they've
served their time.
"It's the old never-ending
battle against crime and corruption,"
- to quote Superman.
- What do you think is gonna happen
with this infusion
of new blood?
We could be looking at a period
of potentially violent struggle.
- They gonna paint everythin' the worst.
- How long till dinner?
- Any familiar names?
- In New York, the only old-style boss
still in place
is Carmine Lupertazzi.
He'll soon be rejoined by Angelo Garepe,
his former consigliere.
Also Philip Leotardo,
long-time Lupertazzi captain.
Can you help me here?
Crush some ice?
- I'll be right there.
- New Jersey's a better case in point.
You've got
Michele "Feech" La Manna,
released just this week,
a man greatly feared
- and respected in the '70s.
- Amen to that.
Similar situation with Anthony Blundetto
in that same
- Jersey crime family, the Sopranos.
- Oh!
- Let me see how he looks.
... still is as far as I know.
28 years old when he went away.
A rising star.
Thought to be the central suspect
in the car-bomb killing
of Thomas Gilardi and his driver.
That's the best picture they could find?
He was a fox.
Will you pipe down?
We're tryin' to watch.
It's my house, Tony.
- What are you watching?
- Go call your brother for dinner.
- Bobby!
- Be nice to have him back, huh?
- Your cousin?
- Missed the shit out of him.
The older you are, the more
you're entitled to eat.
Hi, sorry.
- Where the hell you been?
- Your mother didn't send anything?
She wasn't even home. Her and Aunt Ro
went out to dinner, I think.
Everybody sit!
Now please.
This is great of you,
Aunt Jan,
keeping the Sunday dinner
tradition going.
Can you get the roast
out of the oven?
- Canned clam chowder?
- Go sit, God damn it.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
My wedding ring.
- Goin' to strap on the bag, Ton'?
- Yeah.
Would you say this is an interesting
point in the history of the mafia?
I'd say we're looking at a great year
for crime reporters, Sukanya.
- Anthony!
- What?
I wanna say hello.
Wh... can you stop
a minute?
- How was dinner?
- Fine.
- What'd you have?
- Roast beef.
Did your father pick up his mail
when he dropped you off?
No, he didn't come in.
He was tired.
He said he just wanted to go to bed.
I'm trying to practice.
I see you didn't bring
the power vac in
from the pool house
like I asked.
Why does that even
have to be done?
Grandpa's still gonna
have to lift it into his truck.
I don't want him to have to drag
it from all the way out back.
# It's so nice to have
a man around the house. #
You should've thought
about that before.
What did you say?
Go out and get
that vacuum, now!
What did I
just say?! Go!
Mommy!
Oh my God.
Mommy, help!
Mommy! Mom.
Mommy.
AJ, be quiet,
don't move.
Mommy?
Mommy!
Go get Dad's gun!
It's all the way
in the dining room!
Hey, go away! Go!
Hey! Get outta here!
Go!
How's the olive loaf?
You know what I like?
- I like the Gulden's Brown Mustard.
- Are you leaving?
Yeah, I got a overseas
call comin' at home.
Finish your sandwich,
at least, first.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, no.
- Sheesh.
Could be the same one
from Willow Drive.
God. The most densely
populated state in the country,
- and still this.
- Gone.
He went through your neighbor's
garbage, though, the Kalcheims?
It's been goin' on all over.
If my son had been alone...
You're not gonna
put your trash cans out
until as close
to pick-up time as possible.
- You hear that?
- Put ammonia or bleach
in the container and on the lid.
I posted a notice for your neighbors.
If this had been
a category two,
injury or serious
property damage,
- we could set traps, but not for this.
- God.
You should've busted a cap
in his ass with Dad's rifle.
It's illegal to discharge firearms
within the borough limits.
- You're gonna call Dad, aren't you?
- No.
The great percentage
of them don't come back.
If he does...
call us.
Oh, do you have
bird feed back there?
Ah, duck food,
yes, my husband's.
It's probably what
attracted the animal.
See, the corn's gotten
damp and aromatic.
You might wanna tell
your husband to put it inside.
Right.
Setting up the equipment
is a complicated affair.
Video cameras
with built-in recorders...
- Then the car that he qualifi...
- Hello.
Mmm.
I'm Dr. Lowenstein.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Go back.
- What?
- Come on.
- You're kidding.
No, go back, please!
- Why don't you come in?
- I like Nolte.
- Why didn't you tell me last night?
- I'm sorry.
That's a long story,
let's just skip it.
I'll try to think
of a better one.
- What's bothering you?
- Global warming, acid rain,
the national debt?
Never even know what's goin' on.
Look at her nails,
totally real.
- You weren't paying attention.
- Let's face it,
women are more
devious than men.
One of my therapists
was a woman.
Too bad you didn't get
all your talkin' done with her.
You expect a man to be
a tower of strength.
Then when it turns out he's got a few
weaknesses and some insecurities,
what do you do?
You turn around and you betray him!
So you feel that
your mother betrayed you?
Doggone, I hate
this Freudian crap.
It's not your job to listen
to my problems anyway!
If you don't mind,
I'd like to go.
- You're free to leave anytime you want.
- Good!
Goddamn shrink.
- Who was I kiddin'?
- What are you smiling at?
- I was a champion...
- Nothin', I don't know.
- You have this goofy look on your face.
- Come on.
...until Susan Lowenstein
came along.
Her questions makin' me
as dizzy as her perfume.
- Jennifer Melfi?
- Yes?
So we open
the fuckin' trunk,
this suffocatin'
Russian cocksucker pops up!
He's still alive!
We lead him through the snow.
This asshole's shiverin'...
he's wearin' fuckin' pajamas
and slippers in like 8° weather.
- Hey!
- Ho!
- Here he is.
- How you doin'?
- Fellas?
- The B?
- Hey, Ton'.
- Radio on the way in.
- Another incident at the airport.
- Fuckin' assholes.
I gotta make
a couple calls.
Anyway, he starts
runnin', the Russian.
Boom! I'm tellin' you the top of his
head came off like a fuckin' bad rug.
What a beating we had to give
this prick, ooh Madonn'.
- Where is he now?
- Who the fuck cares, right, Chrissie?
- Who the fuck knows?
- Poor bastard.
Never would've happened if Paulie
hadn't initially overreacted,
but it's one
for the books.
What do you mean
overreacted?
You choked him with the lamp,
Paulie, or we could've got
Silvio shcarole without havin'
to spend the night in the open.
You let him jab you with that shovel
was the problem. Lets his guard down.
We would've caught up
to the prick
- if you didn't lose your fuckin' shoe!
- Wait, you lost your shoe?
You didn't tell us about that.
"Chrissie, please, don't leave
me out here. "
You little cocksucker!
I covered your ass with Tony
about that whole thing,
and never a word
of fuckin' thanks, ever!
Always playin' that
blood-relation card.
- Tony's little favorite.
- Fuck you!
- What?
- Come on! Come on.
What the fuck?
That was a good story,
damn it.
Tellin' you right now...
it's finished with us.
- Goodbye, Dr. Melfi.
- See you next week.
- Hello?
- Like the flowers?
And yeah, before you ask,
I am takin' the medication.
How are you, Anthony?
It's been a long time.
I'm great,
actually. You?
Thank you for that
beautiful arrangement.
I see you haven't lost
your sense of humor.
You gotta have a sense of humor
in life, right?
- You taught me that.
- And how is life?
Good, good.
Well, I'm separated,
me and Carmela.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Don't be,
Well, I always thought
I saw some good things there.
Two healthy kids,
other than that...
look, the reason
I called...
I'd like you to have
dinner with me.
Since we're not in therapy no more
and I'm a bachelor again...
That's very
thoughtful of you.
Unfortunately, because of our prior
clinical relationship,
- I just can't do it.
- What, eat?
- You must be a toothpick.
- You know what I mean.
See, I knew you were gonna say
somethin' like that.
I can't, Anthony,
I'm sorry.
You know, I waited
a respectable period or whatever
- before makin' this call.
- Then you realize yourself
there's something not
quite right about us dating.
No, I'm not
undeterred by this.
- We will talk again.
- Thank you for the flowers.
- And the detergent.
Of course,
what's wrong with me?
I don't know,
but we'll find out.
Leave it to Dr. Tony.
- What's the matter?
- The bear. Stay there!
Oh, right,
lock the door.
What, do you think
he's gonna wipe his feet, too?
He'll smash
through the glass.
Now where is
that guy's card?
I don't know.
You've reached Fish and Game.
- If you know the extension...
- Unbelievable.
If not, press zero
for directory.
Hello?!
For hunting and fishing
licenses, press two.
You get a letter from
my cousin in the can?
Yes, Officer Zmuida, hi.
Yes, Mrs. Soprano from North Caldwell?
- We had the bear in our yard.
- What the fuck?
- You're the guys with the pool?
- Yes, it came back.
- Was anybody hurt?
- No, thank God.
- Property damage?
- No property damage either I could see,
but I didn't really
wanna go out there.
Oh, one of those
Eastern black bears?
- We'll be up in about an hour.
- Yes, that'd be great,
- Okay, we'll be here.
- All right, see you then.
Jesus Christ,
when did this happen?
The first time Sunday night,
and I saw it again just now.
AJ didn't even
mention it to you
- when you two went to the game?
- No!
I have to warn
the Cusamanos.
They keep Esterhaz chained up
along the side there.
That bear will
rip him to pieces.
Cusamanos weren't home.
Got the machine.
Well, I don't
see Esterhaz.
Why didn't you call me
when this first happened?
I called the cops.
They called Fish and Game.
Are you tryin'
to prove you're independent?
This isn't "Little House on the
Prairie. " Those things are dangerous.
The ranger, whatever, said it was your
duck food out there that attracted it.
I never heard of that
happening before.
Trapper Joe over here.
Hmm.
We didn't find a spoor.
I was just tellin' the gentleman
the animal still doesn't meet
- the parameters for removal.
- Oh, Jeez.
So, when somebody's
leg is gone...
Problem is it hasn't
really threatened anybody.
Sorry.
Whoa, whoa,
hold on a minute.
You and your pal
buy some new...
lanyards for
your whistles.
Oh, we can't
accept that.
And we don't
have whistles.
Thanks, though.
Ranger Rick's a little light
in the timberlands, huh?
Everybody's always
gay with you.
He's a good-looking guy,
that's all.
I already put
the ammonia on the cans,
I told you.
Look, I came here
to give you your money, but...
this bear thing,
though, I'm... I'm...
I'm worried.
You and AJ here
by yourselves.
What can we do?
You want coffee?
Last time it had
a weird taste.
The coffeemaker
is shot.
The heating element
is corroded, I told you.
That's not the problem.
You don't need another one.
Last month, it was
the upstairs toilet. Basta.
He goes down the street
to Willow Drive, too,
maybe he'll
stay down there.
All right, look,
you and AJ, you check
yourself into a hotel
until this thing blows over. Here's
1,200 extra on top of our agreement.
- I'm not going to a hotel.
- Why not?
I don't wanna break
Anthony's routines.
He'll get a kick out of it.
It's an adventure.
God knows he loves
room service.
Yeah, I'll give him room service...
the end of my foot.
What's with the attitude?
Well, he's an asshole,
that's what.
- So what? It's his age.
- Yeah, thank you, I know.
But you buy him
too much stuff,
I think because you feel
guilty about the separation.
Excuse me.
It wasn't my idea.
There is more than one way
to ask for something.
- Could we please not?
- Spend $5,000 on a set of drums...
SAT tutor, coffeemaker,
I gotta fight you tooth and nail.
All I said was
I wanna see statements
from the tutor
or he doesn't get paid!
He's a college kid, Tony,
he's not set up for that.
You worried he's gonna
soak you for an extra pencil?
Oh, rimshot!
What I think, Tony, is you're
trying to make my life now
as hard on me
financially as possible.
- Oh, it should be easy.
- Unbelievable.
What do you think,
you're the only Catholic here?
I'm old school. I don't believe in this
separation shit and divorce,
even if my wife was going
after some fucking immigrant!
Yet you are modern enough to use
a cell phone to call Italy
and every other fucking place
to threaten the guy's life.
Oh, that's right.
Certain people see him,
- he's a dead man.
- He had coffee here, Tony, that's all.
And now
the coffeemaker sucks.
How do you like
them apples?
You don't wanna stay at a hotel,
you suit yourself.
This is Anthony.
Could you call me
at 973-555-1299?
I'm thinking maybe
I gotta come back,
you know,
for therapy.
- Smells good, Feech.
- Yeah?
- You want a taste?
- Nah, I'll wait.
No offense, kid, but don't look to me
like you do a lot of waiting.
Just like
his old man, huh?
Lotta changes since
you went away, huh?
20 years, Madonn'.
Know what the biggest change for me is?
Broads shaving their bushes.
I went over to Silvio's, it's like
the Girl Scouts over there.
I think I'll let
this simmer a bit.
Must be different in the can now,
not like the old days.
Fuckin' animals.
It's all about
setting a precedent.
First day there,
I walk in a mess,
I'm wearin' a puss,
a fuckin' scowl.
I look around...
My nephew.
Right in the middle
of my story!
There he is,
the man, the legend,
Feech La Manna.
Hey, my God
look at you!
You big galoot!
What'd you go straight
from the joint to Earl Scheib?
Look at this fucking tan.
You close the cellar door
when you came up?
It's like the Bowery Boys in here
with this house arrest here.
Code words
and secret passages.
- He's in the middle of a story.
- When isn't he?
Hey.
It's day one,
I'm in the mess,
I look around
and I spot
the biggest, blackest motherfucker
that I can find.
Everybody's looking at me
and I walk right up to him and I say,
"What the fuck are you looking at?"
He says, "What?"
I said, "You heard me,
motherfucker.
What the fuck
are you looking at?!"
With that, I hit him! Bam!
Right across the fucking coconut!
He goes down,
I'm on top of him.
Everybody around!
He gets some shots in.
Everybody's going
fucking crazy!
The screws,
this guy, everybody!
"Motherfucker!"
From that time on,
nobody so much as
looks at me cross-eyed!
- Well, welcome home, huh?
- Cent'anni.
- Welcome home.
The reason I wanted to see you,
Junior, Tony too,
now that I'm out,
I'd like to get back in the game.
What'd you
have in mind?
You know me,
I'm an entrepreneur.
Get my shy going,
sports book, whatever you say.
As long as you don't
step on anybody's toes.
Me?
I'm Fred Astaire.
What's this
Feech tells me,
you got a bear
up there at the house?
What, it's on fucking CNN?
No, it's just that your wife's up there,
and the kids...
your ex-wife, whatever.
It's just that wild animals,
they're dangerous.
People talk.
What people? Who?
I don't know.
What am I supposed to do, go up there
personally and set fucking bear traps?
We're separated,
for Christ's sake.
So, where's the dinner at?
Oh, I forget the name.
It's in the car.
Who's gonna be there?
What are you,
on the school paper? Guys.
It's business.
- You got any cash?
- Some.
Hand me my bag.
- That's all you got?
- It's like $400.
I'm low man tonight,
I gotta pay for everybody.
You know, this is fucking
ridiculous, Christopher.
Why should you get stuck all the time?
You should make Paulie pay.
What, I make the rules now?
Guy's a captain.
I know, but when
he was in jail...
All's I'm saying is if you get
the extra responsibilities,
you should get
the benefits, too.
You're right.
I'll say hello
to the guys from you.
Benny, hi!
Come on in.
Tony sent me. He says he wants somebody
stationed in the yard.
- He's worried the bear might come back.
- What?
- No, I don't want this.
- We'll switch off,
- me and Paulie Germani.
- This is silly, I'm gonna call him.
Actually, it's not
that silly, Mrs. S.
If it was my family, I'd wanna know
there was a male at the house, too.
What can you do about it
if it does come back?
Tony said you should
unlock the closet,
- give me the "shkupit" he called it.
- Oh, for God's sake.
We'll call
the Fish and Game, too.
It's just... I'll have
the weapon in case.
He's just worried
about you, that's all.
And Anthony.
Okay, I don't know.
You're very nice
to do this.
Nice got nothing
to do with it.
Stay inside. You don't have to sit
out there like a fistful of dollars.
Tony said not in the house.
I got my little Sony in the car.
You want something to eat?
We were just about to sit down.
Nah, I'm good.
I just stopped at Tio Pepe's.
This freaking olive oil.
The food's drenched.
That's the reason
it happened.
As far as fucking bears
are concerned?
I say get rid
of them all.
They had their turn,
and now we got ours.
That's why dinosaurs
don't exist no more.
- Wasn't it a meteor?
- They're all meat eaters.
- Meteor, meteor.
- Take it easy.
Gentlemen,
whenever you're ready.
- All right, are we set?
- Yeah, sure.
What are you doing,
you ready?
I gotta make
a pit stop.
Eh, you forgetting
something?
You get it.
I got the last one.
Here, baby, have some
more cheesecake.
The other thing with bears is: if you're
ever chased by one, run downhill.
- For some reason, they can't do that.
- It's the moss.
They attack when you're
having your period, too.
No, no,
that's jungle cats.
- So can we go?
- Hold your horses.
- What's goin' on, we ready or what?
- Yeah.
- Fine, I'll get it.
- Gimme the fucking thing.
- I said I'll get it.
- Enough. It's done.
- $860.00.
- What?
You heard me.
That's what you owe from last night.
You said, you got it.
I only got like
$100 on me, anyways.
Then get the rest by tonight
or you start paying points.
I'm thinking of going
for the acupuncture.
- What, your shoulder again?
- Those long drives.
- It's already tender.
- Next time, we get you out there.
After 18 years in the can,
I'm just happy to be outside.
What, they don't have
a golf course at Leavenworth?
Still a smart ass,
this one.
Carmine,
you all right?
You barely touched
your egg salad.
Too much gherkins.
You smell that?
- What?
- Burning hair.
I smell cut grass.
- Any word on your cousin getting out?
- Who's your cousin again?
- Tony Blundetto.
- Oh, yeah, good guy.
Right, right.
He was my best buddy inside.
- So you gonna give him a party?
- When he get home, get him laid.
What's the matter,
Carmine?
- Carmine?
- Jesus Christ!
- Call an ambulance.
- Yes, sir.
Is he breathing?
- Get that egg salad out of his mouth.
- Hurry up!
- Lupertazzi residence.
- Carmine, it's John.
Hey, John boy,
how's the weather?
Look, I got some bad news.
Your dad's had a stroke.
- Oh my God, how bad?
- There's some paralysis.
It's too early to tell yet.
They're doing everything they can.
- Is my mom there?
- I just called her, she's on her way.
We're over
at St. Vincent's.
Anything, John,
anything he needs.
I'm on the next plane.
Sad, this shit, huh?
I wonder if I can
smoke in here.
You know, I haven't forgotten
our arrangement last year,
you leaving me
in the lurch like that.
It was the right thing to do, John.
Taking out a boss? Come on.
- Even still.
- What do you want, an apology?
Fucking Whitman Sampler,
what?
Boy, imagine if his
fucking speech is affected.
Poor bastard.
When you're up at the house,
who comes to visit? Anybody?
Mostly Rosalie Aprile,
Sil's wife.
Who calls on the phone?
Most of the calls seem
to be for Anthony.
So...?
Look, the real
reason I'm here
is to confront you
in a positive way about
taking our relationship
in that other direction.
Why did you have
to be underhanded?
I don't find that
appealing, frankly.
I was gonna ask you out
for coffee or something,
but I didn't think you'd go.
I'll pay for the hour,
that goes without saying.
Forget that.
I was listening
to that guy on TV, Dr. Phil?
And he was talking about
a similar situation
and he said that you could,
if you wanted to.
There's no set rules.
It's basically about malpractice,
- and you probably couldn't get sued.
- That's not the point.
Look, I was thinking about
all kinds of moves...
"Buy her a piece
of jewelry.
Pay the guy to close down
the restaurant
where she eats lunch
and hire a mandolin player. "
This is the place
where we've been
most honest
with each other.
And that's the way
I always liked it.
So that being said,
if you don't like me
personally,
or the cut of my jib,
or my face, or whatever,
then the matter will end here
and I will never ask you again.
You can be honest.
I like you, Anthony.
And, no, you have
a very nice face.
- Working on the weight, too.
- Good.
Explain to me, okay,
why this is a matter
of such importance to you.
There must be plenty
of women out there.
You're different
from what's out there,
not to mention being
drop-dead beautiful.
My training teaches me
to go fairly quickly
to the idea that what you really
want is to come back to therapy.
Jesus Christ Almighty,
come on, will you?!
Your marriage of 20-something
years has collapsed,
no doubt there are issues
with your children.
Why can't I do something that's just
for me for a change?
It would be for you.
All right,
well, I want you.
And not just for the smart things
you say. I-I-I want...
I want your skin.
I want your mouth.
I want your eyes.
You project all these
qualities onto me.
You don't know me.
This is what happens
between doctor and patient.
Don't do that.
Outta respect
for this office.
You know,
forget about the way
that Tony Soprano
makes his way in the world,
that's just
to feed his children.
There's two Tony Sopranos.
You've never seen
the other one.
That's the one
I wanna show to you.
- Hi.
- I... I wonder if I could use the WC?
- Of course, come on in.
- Yeah, okay.
- Is it cold out?
Yeah, a little,
but I got a fleece.
I know him, he'll just keep coming
back and coming back.
How to let him
down easy, I...
- Think it's worth telling the police?
- What?
Jesus, Elliot.
I don't want to paint
in somber tones here,
but the man is a sociopath,
unpracticed in not
getting what he wants.
And now, since
the therapy is kaput,
what use are you to him
except for sex?
Thank you, Elliot.
Your depth of feeling is
really quite extraordinary here.
All you could come up with
was this weak borscht
about professional ethics,
because you are worried
about how this thug
will handle rejection.
You know, at first
I did find him a little sexy...
dangerous, alpha male...
but as year followed year,
the ugliness I saw, I heard...
You kept him
a long time, though.
There's a mutual sympathy
there of some kind, I guess.
Maybe it's just
the Italian thing.
- Sil said you were looking for me?
- Sit down.
This about
the Easter baskets?
I don't even
know what that is,
and, to tell you the truth,
I don't wanna know.
Now what's this shit
between you and Paulie?
- You chiseled him out of a dinner?
- I chiseled him?
- He said that?
- I asked you a question.
Can I say something
in my own defense?
It's not right that
I have to pay all the time.
I've been paying
for fucking years.
You done? Good.
You pay till I tell you
you don't have to pay no more.
And don't give me
that face.
You know how many tabs, how many
dinners I picked up over the years?
I got Richie Aprile,
fat fucking Jerry Anastasia.
Those guys killed me
at Benihana's.
And forget it, if they want a steak.
I put a new wing on Peter Luger's.
Brandy, cigars, champagne.
Could've bought
a fucking plane.
I hear you, Ton',
but that was before inflation...
Whatever.
It's tradition.
It's like in ancient times,
the samurais,
they had these pages...
young boys that
did their errands,
washed their clothes,
shit like that.
It's a sign of respect.
Why don't you cheer up?
One day, some kid'll be
paying for your dinners.
Atlantic City loves
its oldies on Oldies 98.3.
# Now that you're gone... #
So the Pope says,
"Just-a one-a more thing:
She gotta have-a
big-a tits. "
Oh, man!
That was good!
You okay, Ton'?
You're being like a little quiet.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just... I'm full, that's all.
Calm before the storm. Get him near
those crap tables and look out.
Jesus, I'm stuffed. I can't remember
the last time I ate this much.
Sure youse don't
want no dessert?
- Not for me.
- I'm good.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Enjoy it, girls.
I been enjoying looking
at youse the whole night.
- Get some fucking glasses.
- We gotta go.
All right, I'll see you over
at the $100 table.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Ton', you sure you're all right?
You got a big moose on.
It's a fucking broad,
believe that?
Really?
You mean...?
- It's the real deal, I think.
- No shit, huh?
See? The thing is,
we got this
platonic thing going.
We have had
for many years.
She thinks that's what it is,
but it's not,
and no amount of convincing
will change her mind.
- So she was a... friend.
- Yeah.
They're wrapping up a lobster roll
for me to take to Ginny.
- We'll see you's over there.
- Yeah.
- Anything else, gentlemen?
- We're good.
My friend here'll
take the check, though.
Have a wonderful evening.
# Let's get it on #
1184.
Oh... babe.
I gotta play that number.
Hmm, I'm gonna go wash up.
# We're all
sensitive people #
# With so much
love to give. #
I'll tell you,
after a meal like that,
what I could use is
a nice piece of ass.
Who knows,
maybe I'll call down,
have them send
one up to the room.
Why don't you just fuck yourself?
Save a little money.
- What's your problem?!
- Stop trying to bait me.
- You know what my fucking problem is!
- No, why don't you tell me?
You want me to tell you? Fine!
Steaks, 3 Ib. -lobsters,
the shrimp fucking cocktails
you made everybody get.
Then on top of everything else, you send
those skanks a bottle of Cristal?
I was being a gentleman.
You oughtta try it some time.
Not to mention the Lyonnaise fucking
potatoes you didn't even touch.
- What?! I lost my appetite.
- Fuck you!
- Excuse me?
- You fucking heard me!
I'm telling you, I don't give a fuck
anymore who you're related to.
Go ahead, Paulie.
Go for it.
Your big fucking moment.
- You little fuck...
- Excuse me, gentlemen.
Was there a problem
with the service?
- What are you talking about?
- You left me $16, sir.
- Perhaps you miscounted.
- There's 1200 bucks in there.
That's correct,
and the bill was $1184.
Assuming you don't tip
on tax or alcohol, 15%...
I'm tapped out.
You think this job is easy?
I have kids.
Then go back inside
before you get hurt.
- I have a goddamn family to support.
- Fuck off.
Yeah, right.
Go piss it away at blackjack,
- fucking assholes!
- Oh!
What do you
gotta say now?
Chrissie, he's fucked up.
Don't they have medicine they're
supposed to take, these assholes?
I don't know.
He'll say we hit him
with a brick.
He's still going,
this asshole.
That's my money,
Paulie!
How's he doing?
I love him so much
and I can't do shit.
We're all praying
for him.
You know, you were
another son to him.
- Yeah?
- You get some sleep?
Yeah, a little,
you know.
- Fucked up, huh?
- What are you gonna do?
I'm not too worried
about the cops.
Nobody knows us down there.
The reason I called.
Let's bury the hatchet,
you and me.
All this bullshit
with us.
I know, I know,
it's stupid.
Life's too short,
Chrissie.
You can't waste it
fighting with your friends.
Look what could've
happened last night.
One of us could've got hurt
or even killed for Christ's sake.
- I know.
- You're special to me, you know.
- Always have been.
- You, too, Paulie... to me.
We'll split the tab.
I'm sorry, Paulie.
I apologize too, kid.
I'll talk to you later.
When you say that,
you make me feel...
less than.
Next week, everyone.
Good luck.
- I'm going outta town next week.
- Okay.
Good night.
Anthony.
- Hello.
- Hey.
A friend of mine
had these.
I'll see you
next week.
Like I was saying, a friend of mine
had these and couldn't use them.
I figured, well...
maybe we could.
Tickets, Bermuda, lodging
at the Elbow Beach Hotel.
I turned down a wonderful
dinner invitation,
and you think
I'll go away with you?
Well, the guy couldn't
use them and...
you know, he gave them to me. What do
you want me to do, throw them away?
Come on, I'm breaking
out the big guns here.
You're turning me
into half a stalker.
Listen, Anthony, I'm...
I'm not going to
go out with you, okay?
And it's not because
you're unattractive
or I don't think I
would have a good time,
it's just something
I'm not going to do.
And I would like you
to respect my decision,
and just try to feel that
I know what's right for me.
Okay?
But it's not
just the...
psychiatric ethics
stuff, is it?
I wanna preserve
the option for you
that you could always
come back to our work,
if you wish.
And that we could pick up
where we've left off.
I don't think you
get this, I want you!
And that's very
flattering to me.
I'm not interested
in flattering you.
- I know you're not.
- All right, then what is it?
Okay, what is it?
Just...
help me
understand it, okay?
You know, Anthony,
during therapy I...
I never judged you
or your behavior.
It's not the place
of a therapist to do so.
All right,
I get all this. Go, go.
In a personal relationship,
I don't think
I could sit silent.
About what?
Our values are...
- just very different.
- You don't like my values?
- Honestly?
- Yeah.
No.
Okay. Like what?
- It's getting late, I...
- No, no, no. Come on.
It's okay, it's okay.
Well...
you're not
a truthful person.
You're not
respectful of women.
You're not really
respectful of people.
- I don't love people?
- Maybe you love them, I don't know.
You take what you want
from them by force
or the threat of force.
I couldn't live like that.
- I couldn't bear witness to violence...
- Fuck you!
You're a fucking cunt!
Oh.
How come Benny's
not outside?
He just got here,
he's going out.
Where is he?
He's in your office on the phone
with his girlfriend.
Hey, Ton',
how's it going?
You can take the night off.
I'll spell you.
No, no, no, Ton',
that's all right, it's okay, really.
I'll take over,
okay, for tonight.
Okay, well...
night, Mrs. S.
Good night, Benny,
thank you.
- You want coffee?
- No.
# I'm gonna turn
and walk away #
# There's nothing left
for me to say #
# It wouldn't
change things anyway #
# Oh, I suppose #
# The love I gave
was always true #
# Well, I don't know
what else to do #
# And how I'll
ever get over you #
# Heaven only knows #
# Heaven only
knows just why #
# Loving you
should make me cry #
# Make me feel
like I could die #
# That's the way it goes #
# Heaven only ever sees #
# How love's
made a fool of me #
# I guess that's how
it's meant to be #
# But heaven only knows #
# Heaven only knows
just why #
# Loving you
should make me cry #
# Make me feel
like I could die #
# But that's
the way it goes #
# Heaven only ever sees #
# How love's
made a fool of me #
# I guess that's how
it's meant to be #
# But heaven only knows. #