Fuck this! I'm calling Carlo.
Yeah, they didn't show.
The Vespa scooters.
We gotta wait.
Carlo was furious. His guys waited by
the Hackensack River all night.
fuckin' Vespas never got in my hands.
This is Port Newark.
Where were your longshoremen?
Heightened security at ports, al-Quaeda.
- Done, Johnny.
- I gotta go.
Nice job, Billy boy.
Carlo was told it was a go. If it didn't
happen, why did nobody call?
A lotta things didn't happen
that seem like they happen...
Your cousin didn't whack Joey,
the Vespas never got into my hands.
Come on, go, Soph!
- Hey, Soph is open! Come on!
- Over here!
She's gotta be at least 11.
Don't put up with that, Lissie!
Careful with those elbows, number seven!
Hey, out of bounds! Out of bounds!
Oh, Lissie, go!
They're just a bunch of losers!
- No negatives, you!
- Come on, putz, charge the ball!
Charge it!
Foul! That kid tripped my kid!
Legal, she was going for the ball.
- She was not.
- Score!
- Score, come on!
- Your kid is outta control.
She's been tripping all summer.
- Shut up and get outta here.
- Don't tell me to shut up!
What, are you crazy?
Please. Come on! Somebody!
How do you like it now, bitch?
Her kid kicked my kid. Get off!
- Cost ya 100.
- Call.
Sit down. Sit, sit.
I talked to John.
The Vespa scooters came in, but there was
no opportunity to grab them
because of increased security at the ports.
Jesus Christ! The young crowd is crazy
for these scooters.
- He owes me half that load.
- You're not buying it?
I don't know what to think.
He's getting cute with his remarks.
All I know is his behaviour
at that kid's funeral was a disgrace.
It's a big part of my livelihood, that port.
I will say, very interesting timing, T.
You and John had that chat at the funeral...
whatever that was...
suddenly, no Vespas.
All right, I gotta take this.
Take one of Carlo's guys,
start hanging around Port Newark.
Find out what the fuck is going on.
- The property taxes, I know.
- Hello to you too.
Your sister Janice got arrested.
- What?
- In Essex County this afternoon,
an incident of sports rage
among soccer moms
led to the arrest of a Verona woman
with ties to the Mafia.
Our Gillian Glessner was on the scene.
Think that other mother better go
into the soccer-mom protection programme?
Maybe she should, Carl.
It started here at Summit Avenue Park
during a nine-and ten-year-olds'
soccer match.
An altercation between soccer moms sent
one mother to the hospital and one to jail.
Denise McCarthy, a parent,
witnessed the violence.
I just feel so bad for the kids.
Parents taping the match
captured the mêlée.
Somebodyl
How do you like it now, bitch?
Her kid kicked my kidl
Charges are pending, but we know...
that the woman shown here being taken
into custody is Janice Baccalieri,
sister of reputed New Jersey mob boss
Anthony Soprano.
Guess you could call it a Mafia-related hit.
We spoke with psychologist Bela Kakuk.
It's a growing problem in our society.
Psychologists are finding
that certain individuals
are particularly prone to rage.
Almost any frustration, inconvenience
or perceived inconsideration
will set them off.
Motherfucker!
Janice, open the door!
- Where is she?
- It wasn't my fault!
My name was all over the fuckin' TV
because of your bullshit!
It's not that simple.
The woman's kid was picking on Sophia.
- Why didn't they collar her?
- I am suing the township
- for wrongful arrest and the YSO.
- No. No, you're not!
What you're gonna do is call Neil Mink,
play it down, pay the fine
and not turn this into
one of your causes célèbres.
Anybody's side but mine.
That bitch is lucky I didn't kill her.
- Well, we know that.
- What?
- You and your fuckin' temper.
- Get out!
This is the end of it.
Get out!
I know this looks bad.
On the other hand,
she called Sophia her daughter.
I don't give a fuck.
All right, I do give a fuck.
But how many times I gotta tell you?
Get control of your wife!
I'm so embarrassed.
I don't wanna see any of my friends again.
Well, when you're a parent, you'll see.
You'll defend your children
like a lion with her cubs.
- You're not my parent.
- What did you say?
I'm here...
and I try to care very much.
- Now get to sleep.
- You gonna punch me?
Jan, can I talk to you?
Go to sleep.
We'll talk tomorrow. I'm exhausted.
No. Now.
What, I don't have a say in things?
Janice, I think you need professional help.
I'll be having an extra session
with Sandy, believe me.
What does she do? Tells you
you were picked on by your father
and asks you to read her screenplays.
I think there's anger specialists.
You should see a weight-loss specialist.
You don't see it in yourself.
I heard you with Sophia.
You were getting along so much better,
she says one little thing and you get nasty.
- I'm so sore.
- This is not an isolated incident.
They won't let you shop
up at the corner anymore.
Those coffee beans were burnt.
You tasted them.
Janice, I like a spitfire type,
I told you,
but we can't live like this, me and the kids.
Like what?
This was a nice house.
Peaceful... I don't know.
There wasn't all this yelling and tension.
How could you understand?
Your dad was a sweetheart,
even when he had emphysema.
My house... it was dog eat dog.
Well, be that as it may, the past and all,
if you don't go to these anger classes
they have or whatever,
this with us ain't gonna work out.
Gentlemen, it's rollin'. It's nine. Place nine.
What do you think he clears here?
Two craps tables, blackjack, roulette.
You gotta figure he's
grabbing anywhere from 2,500
to five Gs a night for himself.
It used to be you, didn't it?
Teacher's pet?
- Stop making meatballs, Paulie.
- I'm just saying.
Now you know what I went through.
It's the same Gina had at her wedding.
We should see how it looks on your face.
What the fuck?
- What's up?
- Hey there, cuz.
- Guess who called me.
- How'd you find me?
- You're not gonna guess?
- OK, who?
- Our friend with the orchard.
- No shit. He OK?
Yeah, sold the place, moving to Florida.
He should, he's getting on in years.
Oh, shit.
You still got your canned peaches there.
I just had the car serviced.
Watch what ya say.
I gotta move that shit? Again?
That developer's going up there.
Obviously, it wouldn't be good
for you or our friend
if somebody opened the canned fruit.
So you and your cousin here
will take care of it.
- I'll do it.
- I'm worried about the old guy.
- I told ya, I'll do it.
- My old man's got a few jars up there also.
Could make problems for my uncle.
It's gonna be a lotta work,
which with Louise around
can only be done at night.
- That's true.
- Thing's gotta be done in two weeks.
Bulldozers are coming.
- Are you picking out wedding cakes?
- Yeah.
- Hope you have better luck than I did.
- You didn't like your cake?
I think your luck's been fuckin' great,
and listen to you cursing it out.
What, you got something you wanna say?
- All right.
- So call me.
Who is this Uncle Pat anyway?
He was a knock-around guy like Tony's dad,
but they let him retire to this farm
upstate New York.
It sounds funny, but it wasn't.
He had the hiccups for like a year.
Jeez.
Great guy. He had a daughter,
but she lived with her mom.
Us boys each got sent up there summers
when we hit up 12 or 13.
He'd school us.
- Did he have the hiccups?
- I told ya that went away.
You think it's fuckin' funny?
He almost committed suicide because of it.
How would you like it?
Where's my Barney's underpants
with ventilated cotton?
Still in the dryer.
Tell ya one thing,
I need fuckin' Tony B
up there like I need a third nut.
All this resentment.
- He is your cousin.
- Yeah?
Should've seen him when I was little...
him and Tony both.
How they broke my balls, teased me.
One time, I was spending the summer
up at Uncle Pat's farm
just like they used to - I was 11.
They came up -
they were like 19- to shoot guns.
They didn't take me with 'em,
and when I found 'em,
they said I had to be initiated
into a special club
by being tied to a tree
alone in the orchard for an hour.
I was on that tree
till three in the fuckin' morning.
I worshipped these two guys...
Tony Soprano especially.
When he was by himself,
he used to push me on my Big Wheels,
he'd teach me curse words.
When he was by himself.
Where's the Tinactin?
Right on the night table.
And here we are again. Tony B goes wrong,
and Tony lays a 200K-a-year
cash cow on him.
Christopher, don't get mad, OK?
I know we kinda touched on it
a couple times,
but you're so unhappy.
What if we left here,
went far away,
and you went into something else?
- Like what?
- I don't know, like...
Pick up your writing maybe?
Male modelling...
I'll get back to the writing some day,
but from a position of great wealth.
As far as male modelling,
I'd probably be a success,
but I wouldn't want to be
around those people.
I'm a soldier, Adriana.
When are you gonna understand that?
What the fuck?
- Carmela.
- What?
There's no water in the pool.
Yeah, I had it drained.
The electricity costs a fortune.
You're the only one who uses it.
We were getting along better.
So, you polluted all the decent lawyers in
New Jersey so they can't represent me?
- You couldn't play fair.
- I didn't want it!
Let's just pretend that
you weren't begging for it
in a million different ways, OK,
because I am worn out here.
He's a nice kid, Finn, right?
Right.
We gonna throw 'em
an engagement party or what?
If we can be civil.
She's so young.
Same age we were.
It wasn't all bad.
Last time, I asked you to jot down
one or two situations
or people that trigger your anger,
so when you think about it,
you get angry all over again - anybody?
Let's give Bradley a chance this time.
My partner parked me in again.
I couldn't find the keys.
I had to wake him up
and he starts yelling at me.
Describe the feelings.
My stepkids do that all the time.
They leave their bikes in the garage
and if I wanna pull in, I gotta get out
and move the bikes
with a car full of groceries.
Doris, can't you keep Billy's bike
out of the driveway?!
It's a famous commercial from the '60s.
Bufferin.
Guy has a headache
and he takes it out on his wife.
Back to Bradley,
I'm trying to get
into his physical sensations of anger.
He saw red. Who wouldn't?
She's right. Why is he in here?
Why isn't his roommate in therapy
for selfishness issues?
There are always things
that are irritating and out of our control.
What we can control
is our response to those triggers.
So people get a free pass...
the whole world?
I told you about my supervisor...
checking my work and nobody else's?
- I wonder why.
- Cos you're a minority.
Exactly. That's why I'm in here.
- You seem angry about Evelyn's problem.
- It makes me mad.
It doesn't make you mad.
You make you mad.
I come from a biased family,
but I was different.
I put all my faith and my hopes
into the civil rights movement.
I left home and I marched.
And for what?
So they could ride around in their SUVs,
blasting that rap shit and you can't say
anything because they might have guns?
Wait a fuckin' minute. Who's they?
- If the shoe fits.
- This is fuckin' priceless.
OK, let's not time-travel here,
let's try to stay in the present.
Janice, you're angry. Let's stay with that.
What are your physical feelings right now?
I'd like to punch you in the face.
Your hands are clenched.
Did you realise that?
You're provoking me to make a point.
- Maybe that's your job but I don't like it.
- Look at you.
- You're not even listening.
- He's talking to me.
No. You and me, we do most
of the talking in here.
The man is trying to say
that those people outside...
they do the thing,
but we're the ones that get
all upset and start carrying on.
That's all he's saying.
The Hudson Valley.
That Legend of Sleepy Hollow cartoon
scared the piss outta me when I was a kid.
Would you mind watching your shoe?
Oh, sure.
It's a $50,000 vehicle.
I don't want it scuffed up.
Uncle Pat's farm?
When you're 12, 13, man,
it's like fuckin' heaven, right?
Running around in the woods,
driving that tractor.
He made me clear the brush by the fence
with a fuckin' scythe, though.
I had to do that. Tony too.
And water his fuckin'
tomatoes and his basinigol'.
Changed, though, you know, Pat's,
after Louise came back there to live.
It wasn't just you and Pat
and his great stories.
They used to call me Ichabod Crane.
- Who?
- Some very sorry people, that's who.
The Carmela front? Did you two ever
discuss that evening you made love?
It was a one-time deal. I've moved on.
What about the depression?
Your revelation
about your cousin, his prison sentence?
You were very upset.
Tell you the truth, I haven't had
a lot of time to think about that.
My sister...
She attacked some woman
at her stepkid's soccer game.
You've mentioned her temper before.
She got charged with aggravated assault
and resisting arrest.
Excellent.
Let's talk about that.
- What?
- Rage.
- Why?
- Depression is rage turned inward.
Tell me about the Soprano temper.
The thing is, it's bad for business.
Clouds your judgment.
John, he always had a terrible temper.
- John?
- Gotti.
And in the end, I think it hurt him.
See, we forget that in the old days, the ones
that came over, that started this thing,
they didn't get mad.
They just smiled and nodded
and made sure you got it later.
That's the whole beautiful point.
You know what they say.
Revenge is like serving cold cuts.
I think it's, "Revenge is a dish
best served cold. "
- So, what'd I say?
- But why revenge all the time?
Where does it come from, this insatiable
anger you and your sister share?
I was wondering when she'd come up?
Your mother? What about your father?
You never saw her
chop off someone's finger.
- Told you about that, didn't I?
- Yes.
- Jesus, I wish I hadn't.
- Why?
I dress up nice when I come here...
OK, let's stick to the subject.
- Which is what?
- Your own intolerance for frustration.
"Thank you for holding.
Your call is important to us. "
If it's so important to you, answer the phone!
- Stay with that.
- It's just a level of bullshit!
Every fuckin' new idea they come up with
to make things better makes things worse.
OK, right, I agree.
"The centre cannot hold.
"The falcon cannot hear the falconer. "
What the fuck are you talking about?
We live in a time
of technological and spiritual crisis,
but you feel you're above all of it,
certainly above any
inconvenience or annoyance.
And if things don't go your way,
instead of being merely disappointed
or inconvenienced, you blow.
My sister's...
She's taking anger-management classes.
Maybe she's on the right track.
- Is this something you'd consider?
- No.
But I'll admit it's not good for me,
all this fuckin' agitation.
Wears me out.
I'm fuckin' exhausted all the time.
- Where did we start off?
- I don't know.
Depression is rage turned inward.
This is nice.
For inner-city kids like me,
this was important.
You lived next
to the largest mall in New Jersey.
It's over now. She's sticking me
in that home in Florida.
- That's the last I'll ever see of her.
- I'll be right down the road.
I got a beautiful condo.
Thinks she's gonna meet
some old, lonely widower.
Louise, it's time for dessert.
I'm getting it.
And do me a favour, be as polite as
you are when it's just the two of us?
We know where Chrissy buried the guy.
But with Uncle Johnny's,
you gotta help us out.
I'm not exactly sure,
but there was two of them.
- The Johnson brothers.
- You don't remember where?
It was a long time ago.
We can't excavate the whole fuckin' place.
Cos you know
what Tony's gonna say?
Let him come up here and dig then.
Please. He's a heart attack waiting
to happen.
That's no joke. Our bodies are 86% water.
His last blood test, he was 65% zeppole.
When he first heard the term "pie in the
sky," he volunteered for the 82nd Airborne.
That's pretty good.
I learned in recovery that he's just tamping
down his feelings by eating.
I should talk to him. It's a shame, you know.
- He was the funnest guy in the world.
- When was that?
He's got the world by the balls and he acts
like everything's an imposition.
Being at the top, he's isolated himself.
Yeah, it's just him and his money.
Hello.
- Who is this guy, anyway?
- My first. Czechoslovakian guy.
This is the second time I'm moving him.
- Come here, you little fuck.
- Guys, wait.
- It wasn't me...
- Help! Please, don't kill me.
- What the fuck you running for?
The night of the 12th, there was a ship from
Italy with these containers of Vespas.
I don't know anything about any Vespas!
We know they got here.
What happened to them?
I don't know. I wasn't here!
Well, apparently he says he wasn't here.
Who picked up
our motherfuckin', cocksucking Vespas?
In two seconds, this is going up your ass.
It was the guys from New York.
Phil Leotardo and them.
Listen.
Thanks for doing this. You didn't have to.
Fuck that. You're my little cousin.
I think I can imagine what you may
be hearing about me
and what happened in New York.
All I can say is, there's no truth to it.
I didn't think nothing.
And Tony putting me in at the casino,
I knew people would resent that.
But I went away for a long time,
stood up for this family,
and you, or anybody,
can think what they like,
but I feel I had a little coming to me.
Absolutely. I was telling Benny that
the other day. He was complaining.
And what I said about Tony before?
- You know I love him like a brother.
- I love him, too.
We saw the guy down the pier.
John has the Vespas.
To think of how supportive you were of him.
That whole Little Carmine fiasco.
It's fuckin' payback.
Johnny's got it in his head my cousin
had something to do with Joey.
Johnny should be looking for the real killers
instead of spending
all his time on that golf course.
Whole fuckin' shipment
of cheese coming in next month.
The imported provolone.
I guess we can kiss that goodbye too now,
right?
Motherfucker!
- What are you doing here?
- My son is a senior here now.
We were electing party
chairs for a senior night.
Right.
- So, how are you?
- Fine.
Cos you were pretty
upset when you left and I wanted to call.
I began to really rue what happened...
- I'm going back with my husband.
- Oh, that's good.
All the best.
You don't drink no more?
Clean and sober, 14 months.
Yeah, your mother has that problem.
Good for you.
- That's right.
- What?
The Johnson brothers' bodies.
I know where they are.
Over by the fence in the northwest corner,
because that night
I noticed one of my pickers
had stuck a Swiss Colony bottle
upside-down on one of the fenceposts.
And I was plenty goddamn mad they were
drinking on the job, I'll tell you.
It's still there, the glass bottle.
- Are you fuckin' sure?
- Lunch!
- I got for you, Chrissy.
- Thank you.
Sandwich?
Beautiful.
This is mail from three fuckin' weeks ago.
- The girl didn't even show up today.
- Why don't you get somebody new?
Two classes, she's telling
people how to run their life.
Don't let me stop you
from taking your kids to the rink.
You have every right
to be mad at me, and I apologise.
I know it's bad for the family...
for business... but I'm working on it.
Yeah, I know. Bobby told me.
- So how's that going?
- Anger management?
It's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
It's such a relief to let go
of all that shit and...
I never realised what
an angry person I was
and how it fed itself.
- So they got you on tranquillisers?
- No.
Basically, it's taking responsibility
for your anger,
and learning to recognise
your feelings of anger
and that they're just feelings,
you don't have to act on them.
People want that
so they can walk all over you.
A lot of anger is self-importance.
- Self-importance?
- Problems with authority.
Dr Seepman locks the door
promptly at seven.
People wig out if they don't get in, start
banging on the door. It's a big lesson.
I was making everybody
in my life miserable,
yelling and screaming,
or pouting and feeling victimised,
but I feel so much better
now about everything.
It's like this great sadness
is beginning to lift.
- Sadness?
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm happy for you.
- Thank you.
I am.
Your bid, Chrissy.
You expecting someone?
There he is!
My God, I don't believe it.
Who's that... Anthony?
What's the matter? You all right?
God, you're big.
Look at those shoulders.
- Jan sends her love and Barb, too.
- Did you eat?
Louise, don't ask him. He's a guest.
Just go get him a plate!
Sit down.
- You look good.
- Feel good.
So how we doing?
Took care of mine last night.
The Johnson brothers we'll get tonight.
Uncle Pat was like Johnny Mnemonic.
Right, Uncle Pat?
We're playing pinochle.
Take a hand.
- This is the life, huh?
- I'm with you.
Yeah, we were just saying that.
To a job well done.
This place hasn't changed much.
Met some pretty nice college girls
the other night.
She liked you, Miss Raven-Hair?
Pat seems good, huh?
Louise seems fat.
The human body is 86% water,
but Louise's last blood test,
she was 65% zeppole.
That's a good one.
I knew a guy, when he was gonna eat
Philly cheese steak,
the mayor of Philly would have
to call out the National Guard.
What the fuck's so funny about that?
Doesn't even make sense.
- Well, he's drunk.
- Him?
No way. He's in recovery.
If you recover
your fuckin' balls, give us a call.
We might like to hang out.
No, seriously, it's not funny.
He's a 12-stepper, right?
Well, yeah. You know that. That's right.
Maybe he can take another couple of steps
out the door so we could have some fun?
Come on, don't get pissy now.
He's just having a joke, that's all.
Sobriety's hard enough
without having to get mocked for it.
Jesus Christ,
why don't you have a fuckin' drink?
You're driving
everybody crazy with this shit.
The fuckin' Higher Power
yammering and the sweets
and the Key lime pie and the... Jesus.
Order a fuckin' bullshot,
will you? Do me a favour.
I'm sorry, I didn't realise
I was being a jerkoff.
Look, it's just... you know, come on.
You're doing the right thing.
So, how do you like his car?
Schwarzenegger's. Pretty great, huh?
The humvee. Yeah, it's nice.
- Kinda steep.
- You told me you didn't pay for it.
- You gave the guy a hum-job.
- For the hum-vee.
Maybe he'd like to hum me.
- A friend of Bill over here?
- Fuckin' wits over here.
Bill? I'll say.
That? That's not a bill, that's a beak.
You know...
that was you he made
that joke about, the zeppole content.
On the way home,
we can drop him off at Beakskill.
Well, if beaks could kill,
that one certainly would.
I could've called you
Ichabod Crane, but I didn't.
What the fuck's he talking about...
Ichabod Crane?
Nothin'.
Here's to the Johnson brothers,
whoever the fuck they were.
...Port Newark...
...but one example.
Six million containers
enter U.S. ports every year,
yet fewer than two per cent of them
are opened and inspected by U.S. Customs.
It is impossible to check every container
without essentially stopping
global commerce.
But what keeps officials
from sleeping at night
is that terrorists could use
shipping containers
to smuggle in a weapon
of mass destruction.
It is within the capabilities
of Islamic fundamentalists
to track a container
with a Global Positioning System
and detonate a nuclear
or biological weapon hidden inside.
Son of a bitch.
A terrorist could use a shipping container
to smuggle himself into the country.
There he is.
What I saw on TV last night.
The ports are wide open.
Government's not doing shit.
- Where's my butter substitute?
- In front of you.
Didn't you hear what I said?
I knew it was bad.
Seven million containers. The news team
put radioactive shit in one of 'em.
- It wasn't even detected.
- Please, my ears.
Sit down. Sit.
Come on. I made eggs.
Could've been a goddamn A-bomb.
- You want coffee?
- Yeah.
Fuckin' terrible nightmares.
Yeah, it knocked the edge
right the hell off your appetite.
- What's the matter with you?
- No, it is some scary shit.
Not my problem much longer.
Speaking of scary shit,
was that you in the bathroom?
Oh, yeah. I thought they already dropped
the biological weapon.
All right, I gotta go.
I thought we were gonna go hunting.
- You hear the turkeys this morning?
- No, I gotta take off.
Uncle Pat. Take care of yourself.
- Be careful of the alligators down there.
- All right, tough guy.
Hey, Tone! What'd you do,
knock over a roadside stand?
My uncle's farm.
Less than 100 miles from here.
It's like a whole different world.
The bullshit really falls away up there.
Hear about that shit with the ports?
Customs agents are bad for us, but
antiterrorism-wise, they're doing nothing.
What's it gonna take,
a fuckin' nuclear bomb?
They caught one al-Quaeda cocksucker
in one container.
- They caught him.
- There's enough they don't catch.
The administration's busy too,
giving noncompetitive
building contracts to friends.
Hell, we can all understand that.
We're sitting ducks here.
Only thing between our homes
and Port Newark is a chain-link fence.
They get a nuclear bomb in a container
and we're fuckin' dead.
That's why you gotta live for today.
- What'd you say?
- That's why you gotta live for today.
Talking about annihilation,
you stupid fuck!
Your kids, my kids, burning into cinders!
I can't even think about it.
You stupid...
Can't even fuckin' think about it?
Motherfucker, huh?
Think about it now?
- How about now?
- Hey, Tony!
Tony, take it easy.
- Take a walk.
- Get some air.
Take a walk.
Take a walk outside.
Sorry, everybody.
Come on, take it easy.
- I wake you up?
- Yeah.
I just come from the hospital.
They said you wanted to know.
Oh, how's he doing?
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
Doctor has a peel at one.
- Hi.
- How you doing, hon?
- Call me?
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- See you later.
- That the dermatology nurse?
- Yeah.
- Nice-looking.
- They get all the skin treatments half-price.
So, what'd they say?
He's gonna be OK, the kid?
He's big, strapping, he'll be all right,
but some hearing loss, one ear.
Looks like it could be permanent.
Skip, the poor fuck knows
he should keep his mouth shut.
Go over there.
You make sure he gets the best.
Thing is, Tone, he's quitting the Bing.
And he told Sil, he goes,
"I'd appreciate if Tony don't come visit me. "
He don't wanna see you.
I told him watch his mouth.
These things happen, T.
That's why I don't like to talk politics.
- You did?
- Please, I couldn't believe it myself.
- Well, are you going back with Tony?
- No.
- Then why'd you say it?
- I don't know. It just came out.
Asshole. He was gonna call me.
- Did he?
- Jerk.
Come in!
Uncle Pat.
- Where's AJ?
- He's not coming.
You lose 'em for a little bit,
but he'll be back.
Hi, Uncle Tone!
- Before dinner?
- Half?
Thank you.
Mahatma Gandhi over here. Nice.
I thought I heard your voice.
- Hello?
- Good game on later.
I think we're on the do-not-call list.
Oh, no, we're happy with our service.
Those telemarketers...
just hang up, hang up!
We're just sitting down to dinner.
OK, please don't call again.
Thank you.
Come on!
It's a G5. It's got a 64-bit architecture.
A different language
now with these computers.
I saw a show on computers,
how the prices have dropped so low
that you can buy one
for $500 at Costco
more powerful than the one that put
the astronauts on the moon.
Good eggplant, Jan.
Yeah, delicious.
I wonder where Harpo's
eating his Sunday dinner.
What?
Just wondering what Harpo's up to.
- Who's Harpo?
- That's Hal, Janice's son.
- You have a son?
- You didn't tell us that.
You know that song,
Harpo's Song by Phoebe Snow?
That's the song
you named Harpo after, right?
He's half
French-Canadian, Harpo.
All right, Tony.
Make fun of a boy because of his name.
I wonder what's French-Canadian
for "I grew up without a mother. "
Where is my mama?
You son of a fuckin' bitch!
Daddy!
- Easy, easy, easy!
- You miserable fuck!
I don't got a right to ask?
I'm the boy's uncle.
Easy, easy.
- Easy.
- I hate him, I hate him.
English