[indistinct party chatter]
[Future's "Real Sisters" playing]
♪ ♪
Yo, I think Chris knows
we're here or something.
Yeah, go see him.
Get us paid, and ask him
what the fuck is up with this.
Champagne. We get three bottles.
Of this shit?
Naw, man, I need brown, bro, not no...
rosé... whatever this
bubbly SpongeBob piss is.
No, no, it's whatever, man.
You know, I get 20% of
my drinks for free, so.
How so?
I'm that guy; people see me
and they just want to
give me free drinks.
What can I say? I'm the guy.
Hey.
Shit. Yeah.
[chuckling]
Hey.
Yo, it's just a club appearance, man...
Man, why I feel like
nobody care I'm here?
It... see, see, man,
that section, over there?
That section? That should
be my section, man.
Man, who over there more
important than me, anyway?
Shit. [chuckles]
If you want to stunt,
we can do that next year,
but right now, let's
focus on getting paid.
[scoffs] Now, hold up, man.
Make sure you keep an
eye on that promoter?
I don't trust his kind, man.
He gonna try and play us.
- His kind?
- Yeah.
What is this, "The Hobbit?"
"We're from two different worlds."
Man, he... he Nigerian, man.
I don't trust Nigerians.
Darius is Nigerian.
He is?
Yeah.
This nigga... man.
[groaning]
Relax, man.
No, man, I don't trust
niggas in the club.
Yo.
Are you Paper Boi?
Yes.
- Naw.
- Yeah you are.
Then nigga, why'd you ask if
you already know the answer then?
- Man, I love your shit, bro.
- Okay?
"Trust I'ma get these
bricks off the shelf.
"Trust Paper Boi, trust no
man, I don't even trust myself."
Yeah, I know it. Thanks, man, cool.
"This is what it be like
"when you wake up
with that paper on you.
"Cold world, N-word snitching,
caught that lead pneumonia.
"Cold world, but a N-word,
not from North Carolina.
"I put the bricks on a boat,
make it hard to find 'em.
"I just might sling it to your
daughter for that new designer.
"This is the realest shit I
wrote, I never touch a liar.
"I got the clips in the
drawer dresser behind the CK.
"Got this long thing in
your face like Dekimbe.
"Got a bitch calling out
my name, oh, you thirst-ay?
"I've been..."
♪ Running the streets ♪
♪ Looking out for a real one ♪
♪ I'ma move like a crook
move, but I'm God's son ♪
Thank you. All right, man.
♪ I been running the streets ♪
♪ Looking out for a real one ♪
♪ I'ma move like a crook
move, but I'm God's son ♪
Thanks, man.
♪ Around with me, you
tryna dodge bullets ♪
♪ Serving packs of
chickens in a Dodge Hemi ♪
[music muffled]
[indistinct talking]
Yo, how we feeling, Primal?
[cheers]
No, no, no, no. How we feeling, Primal?
[cheering and whooping]
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
We got a surprise tonight.
Marcus Miles is in the house.
Atlanta Hawks' point guard, what's good?
[cheering and whooping]
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
And... we got my nigga...
Paper Boi!
Paper Boi is in the house!
- Make some noise!
- [air horn blaring]
[smattering of applause]
[Young Dro's "We In Da City" plays]
[beat drops]
♪ Car ain't got no roof ♪
♪ I can't hear it, bro ♪
♪ We be in da city ♪
♪ All my bitches with it ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Uh-oh, where your ho at? ♪
_
- ♪ We be in da city ♪
- _
♪ All my bitches with it ♪
♪ Where you be at bruh? ♪
♪ My crips in the city ♪
♪ My bloods in the da bitty ♪
♪ Guns up in Rambo house ♪
♪ Blocks in dat bando house ♪
♪ Choppas come from Yucatan ♪
♪ You da man, you da man ♪
- ♪ I'm sittin up in this dually man ♪
- _
- ♪ Don't make me spray this Uzi man ♪
- ♪ Pop shit you get popped quick ♪
- _
- ♪ No roof this drop sick ♪
- ♪ My crew we rock shit ♪
- _
- ♪ Uh-oh where your ho at? ♪
- ♪ You heard me? ♪
- _
♪ Uh-oh she where dro at! ♪
- What?
- _
♪ Car ain't got no roof ♪
- ♪ Car ain't got no roof ♪
- _
All right, cool.
♪ We be in da city ♪
♪ All my bitches with it ♪
[music mixes]
[cheers and whistles]
[trap music]
♪ Got smart big head ♪
♪ Double cut sprang ♪
♪ Good grams kush with it ♪
♪ Had wood sprang ♪
♪ Your shit have respect ♪
♪ Where you know me? Sprang ♪
♪ Pull up jumpshot ♪
♪ Fade away sprang ♪
♪ Sprang, sprang, sprang,
sprang, sprang, sprang sprang ♪
♪ Sprang, sprang,
sprang, sprang, sprang ♪
[groans] This shit is wack as fuck!
Ah, come on, man. It ain't all that bad.
Why, man? 'Cause we still getting paid?
Man, fuck the club!
Could have stayed at home and finished
"Amadeus" and had a better time, man.
- [muttering] Well, that's true.
- Look, man.
Marcus Miles over there getting all
the cream, man, hogging all the hos.
Fuck him too!
Marcus Miles is pretty cool, man.
You know he got that invisible car?
What?
[scoffs] Nigga, no he don't.
He do. It's like a prototype,
something like... look.
Man, that...
That shit ain't real, man.
Come on, man. Chill out, man, look.
We can turn this thing around.
Like, uh... look.
That girl right there.
She been looking this way all night.
All right, and I know
she ain't looking at me.
Well, how you figure she want me though?
'Cause she would have been notice
this creepy look I've been giving her.
Psychology.
Well, we bout to find out.
Hey!
Hey, who want to party
with Team Paper Boi?
[cheers]
- Bottles on me!
- [cheers]
- Yeah! Here!
- That's what I'm saying!
Whoo-hoo!
Come on to the other side.
Hello, hello, hello.
This VIP, welcome, welcome, welcome.
[indistinct talking]
Hey.
Chris.
Hey, there you go, what happened?
I turned around, you were gone.
Yeah, I lost you in the crowd, man.
That's all good, man. You want a shot?
No, I... I hate shots.
Okay, can we just finish
the financial aspect of this?
I got you.
Just let me take these
drinks to my ladies
and we'll finish up, all right?
Follow me.
Ladies, this is Earn.
Hey, what's up?
Um. No thanks.
No, it's cool, I'm...
I'm friends with Chris.
We don't know him either.
I hate shots, man.
[Crime Mob's "Knuck
If You Buck" playing]
♪ ♪
Oh, I... I'll be back.
Excuse me.
Coming through, coming through.
Hey, man, uh, can you help me out?
No problem, player.
Thank you, player.
Question. Have you ever had
to throw out another bouncer?
- Yeah.
- How was it?
Hard.
- He knew all the moves.
- Hmm.
- There's the guy.
- Here I am.
Whoo.
I'm gonna go watch people smoke.
See ya.
[mumbles indistinctly] Excuse me.
[muffled club music]
[toilet flushes]
Sup, Chris.
Earnest. What happened, man?
What happened was you
slippery as fuck, Chris.
And I want my money, now.
All right, man.
Just relax.
Let me finish up.
Gonna wash your hands?
No.
Yo, what up? I'm back.
VIP only.
Come on, man.
You got a wristband?
Yeah. Right here.
- It's purple.
- So?
So to get in this section,
you need a yellow one.
Oh, well... uh...
I don't have a yellow one,
but I do have this purple one
and this red one.
I don't know what a red one's for.
Me neither.
I can't help you, man.
Come on, man, you literally
just let me out of here.
Remember, we did the...
fist bump and everything
and none of that don't mean shit to you?
This is meaningless.
[Dreezy's "Body"
featuring Jeremih playing]
Let me get a Hennessy.
Want something?
Laphroaig.
Damn.
You really going for my pockets, huh?
I earned it.
Thanks, honey.
Cheers.
♪ Yo body on my body, baby ♪
♪ I'm about to catch
a body in here baby ♪
The fuck?
[laughing]
I'm sorry,
but that was awesome.
You saw... you saw that, right?
- Yes.
- Fuck, he...
Hilarious.
You should see your face right now.
[laughs]
Thank you.
Thanks... You're awesome.
Thank you for...
for being awesome.
Love it.
Relax.
You ain't got to get so sensitive.
I hate shots.
I hate the club; I hate...
people at the club, I hate...
This shit is pointless,
it's like a money suck.
Can I give you some advice?
Sure.
Leave.
No one is keeping you here.
But if you're at the club, that means
you deep down want to be at the club.
You're not special.
To be fair, you don't
look the usual type.
What's the usual type?
That guy.
Excuse me, sir. Sir.
You need to move up out of
here. We don't do that in here.
[scoffs]
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait...
- so you hit his car?
- Uh, yeah.
- No...
- I had to.
So then I go back and sit in my car...
- Mm-hmm.
- and I'm crying.
- Well, fake crying.
- [cracks up]
[both laugh]
And the guy comes up
to me and he's like,
[as man] "Damn, I was gonna let you go,
baby girl, but my car's fucked up!"
Oh, no. No... no, you know what?
- Whatever to that nigga, man.
- Whatever.
- Hey you want to get a photo?
- Mm-hmm.
Let's get a phot... Hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Nigga, hey, hey, hey,
where you going, Ansel Adams?
Man, you don't want to get a
exclusive photo of Team Paper Boi?
No, I'm good, man.
Wait. Man, look.
You sure?
Marcus Miles got his
pet peacock here tonight.
And it's got a leather jacket on.
That's front-page news.
Nice shoes, bro.
[camera snaps]
[laughs]
Yeah, man. To that
nigga, man? Whatever man.
Hell, let's... let's toast it up, man.
- Yeah.
- Toast it up.
See, he's tell them some bullshit about
how VIP is at capacity
but he can hook them up.
See, there are four of them, but
he says he only has two wristbands.
See, if only two go, they feel special.
They have a better time. [chuckles]
Everyone needs to
feel special sometimes.
Even if it's some janky nigga
telling your two friends
they can't come in.
Why do you think porn exists?
Wow.
You were Marxist until
you got kind of sexist.
[scoffs]
Then why am...
why am I here? Tell me that.
The same reason everyone else is here.
To feel good about yourself and stunt.
[imitates buzzer] Wrong.
I'm here for work.
Exactly.
You want to make more money
to feel good about yourself
like everyone else.
And you're stunting by playing like,
"Oh, I came here to handle
business like a boss."
No... no.
No...
Don't be an asshole...
okay? You asked.
[scoffs]
All right, then, I guess I'll
just take the check, Tiresias.
You better tip.
Hey, Ken. What's up, hon?
You want the regular?
_
Fire alarm.
[muffled club music]
- That nigga called the cops on me.
- What?
And that wasn't even the crazy part.
- Oh, come on.
- Then he goes,
"Oh, shit, my gun",
runs back to his car an
stashes it in the bushes.
Damn, girl, you wasn't scared?
Scared for what?
The cops was on their way.
I straight told on his ass.
[laughs]
Oh, I was just gonna
top you off, big dog.
No, no, no, I... I can
top myself off, dude.
- I got you.
- I can top myself off, man!
Who the hell are you?
I'm a promoter, man.
Well, actually... actually,
I'm a rapper from Harlem,
you know. You know A$AP Rocky?
Well, I don't know any of them, but...
I went to school with
Janice. Isn't that?
Yo, I got... I got a CD
that's about to drop too, man.
I got like four followers on MySpace...
[voices blur indistinctly]
[club sounds blur indistinctly]
[glass knocks over]
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
He cool, man, he with me.
Nigga, who are you?
Hey. Hey!
All you niggas, get the
fuck out of my section!
Get up, let's go!
Hey... hey... hey,
wait... you... you, hey, come on.
Come on, not y'all, y'all cool.
Come on back here. [chuckles]
Okay, girl, let's go.
'Cause Marcus Miles' section
is over there with the bottles.
No. No-no-no-no-no,
I'm bout to get bottles right now.
Hey, hey! Sweetheart!
Yeah, over here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ladies and gentlemen,
Marcus Miles has just bought
the entire bar tonight!
[cheers and applause]
So we will no longer be serving drinks.
All: What?
He owns all the liquor in the club,
and, uh, I think he's leaving.
[crowd murmuring]
- Hey, fuck you!
- So...
[indistinct talking]
[laughs]
You broke!
[lighter clicks] No, I could hook it up.
[R&B music over radio]
Bro, what are you doing in here?
I want m...
[barfs]
I want my money.
I want my $5,000.
Oh, you mean your $750?
W... what?
Let me explain something to you.
You know what it takes to run a club?
The expenses?
Well, let's do some math.
We paid for the flyers.
And then your boy exceeded
his alcohol order limit.
[gags]
And then we had to
pay for extra security
because Paper Boi's a thug.
And that's not cheap.
And then, he was supposed to perform.
- What? No.
- Yeah.
He was supposed to perform.
So all in all, you guys get $750.
And that's me being nice.
Nigga, that wasn't the deal, man...
Hey, don't start that
with me, motherfucker,
'cause I don't play that shit.
That's what I'm paying you.
Now, you better check your tone
and get the fuck up out of my office
before I go get the heater.
♪ I don't care. No one to love me ♪
♪ I don't care. No one to think of me ♪
♪ I don't care. No one ♪
Damn, this shit lame. [scoffs]
It ain't even 2:00 a.m. yet.
- Yeah, this is so wack.
- [chuckles]
[sighs]
But at least it wasn't a complete loss.
I met a cool-ass nigga.
Me?
Well, hold up, okay? Hold up, baby.
[phone rings]
[video game playing over TV]
Yo.
Hey. Hey, man, were you go?
We leaving.
Yo, I'm already at the crib, bro.
What?
Mm-hmm.
I guess I had on the wrong
color wristband or something.
Now I'm on this Zoo Tycoon.
Nigerians, man.
Hey, hey, Janice... hey.
Hey, man, let me call
you back, all right?
Yep.
[slurps]
Hey. Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey-hey, baby.
Hey, wait, wait-wait-wait-wait-wait.
Let's exchange information or something.
Yeah. You can follow me on Instagram.
Come on.
- Well, I have a boyfriend.
- [laughs]
Wait, what?
Oh. That's so sweet.
I'm for real gonna check
out your music on SoundCloud.
Come on. Are you serious?
[sighs] A boyfriend?
So you been wasting my
time this entire night then?
Wasting your time? Wait...
We had a good time, right?
That's why you came here.
To party with cute girls
like me and have a good time.
We did that.
Yo, what the fuck!
[groans]
Hey... hey, man. Hey, where you been?
Look, we need to get out of this club
before I punch somebody in the face.
Man, you get our money?
Earn.
Man, he fucked us, man, like he...
He only gave us $750,
man. I'm sorry, man...
I just don't scare people like you, man.
Like, niggas know I
drink juice and shit.
Fuck that!
We getting our fucking money, man.
What's up, Earn?
Nigga, what's up, Swiff,
what are you doing here?
You know sweaty-ass Tony,
it's that nigga birthday man.
Ah, no, nigga ah... Let's go!
[Baby Huey's "Hard Times" plays]
Okay, this nigga in my ear.
- Just follow, just follow.
- Oh shit.
♪ Cold, cold eyes upon me they stare ♪
♪ People all around me
and they're all in fear ♪
♪ They don't seem to want
me but they won't admit ♪
♪ I must be some kind of... ♪
[screams]
Oh, shit.
Where my money, nigga?
Man, I gave Earn your money.
- [blow lands]
- Damn!
Where's my fucking money, man?
- Please! I can write you a check.
- Nigga, do I look like a bank?
I don't take fucking checks!
- Oh!
- [indistinct shouts]
- Where's my money at?
- I got it all right here, man.
- Just take it, just take it.
- Shit.
This is gangsta.
Yeah, nigga.
- [slap lands]
- Oh!
Shit! Damn!
- Hey, yo.
- Come on, man.
We got to dip now.
Hey, man, you should really
practice better business habits.
- Shit out the door.
- Really man?
Oh, my God.
You all right?
[pants]
That boy's gonna be a star.
Man... call the police!
He talked to you like, don't...
"I don't take checks."
- No, wilin-ass looking nigga.
- I don't take checks.
[both laugh]
Yo, dude, I thought he was gonna die.
I told you I don't like the club, bro.
- Yo, we just like...
- I mean.
- Shit was fire, man.
- [chuckles]
We should get some food, though,
man, let's get out of here.
- No, man, I'm so hungry.
- I know.
I want like, a, a waffle and
like a chicken sausage so bad.
What you gonna do with
that chicken sausage?
- Tear it up, man.
- Tear it up.
- That's some gay-ass shit.
- Man, I'll...
- I'll gobble it.
- [laughs]
Gobble it, swallow the whole thing, man.
- Shit, man.
- [indistinct shouts]
Man... oh, this nigga's getting in here?
The fuck is happening?
- Hey!
- Oh, damn.
[gunfire]
- Oh, shit!
- [people screaming]
Go, Earn, man! Go, go, go, go!
[tires screech]
[engine revving]
- [laughs]
- Oh, my God.
- Yo, that shit was so crazy.
- Yo, man.
I heard them gunshots and I just
went into survival mode, boy.
- I was like...
- Yeah, I bet you did.
You see that man? He just
blew that dude's brains out.
Wait, wait, so that was Marcus Miles?
Both: No, no.
- Man...
- Well, who was it?
Wait, I missed something.
Who was it, was it Marcus...
Oh! Oh, ow, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
- Nigga, you drunk.
- [laughs]
[over TV] Tonight on Channel 5 News,
a man was shot in an altercation
at local area nightclub, Primal.
And popular Atlanta rapper Paper
Boi is wanted for questioning
about an armed robbery
at the same establishment.
[news theme music]
Fuck the club.
[Little Beaver's "I Can
Dig It, Baby" plays]
♪ ♪
♪ Whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Hey babe ♪
♪ You say you want to go out ♪
♪ And haveyourself a little fun ♪
♪ Well, I can dig it baby ♪