-[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
-I'm Charles. Your brother.
Hey. Your days of exploiting kids
to do your dirty work ends tonight.
Didn't you say we'd turn this place
into a community center?
-Jughead?
-Are you my roommate?
-So much for a new start.
-[doorbell rings]
[whirring]
What--?
What is this?
Fast-forward.
It's literally six hours of our house.
Why would somebody do that?
Film it and then leave the evidence
on the front doorstep?
To unsettle you,
let you know you're being watched.
Yeah, but why a videotape?
Why something so anachronistic?
Maybe it's just a prank.
[Jughead] If it was,
it was an elaborate one.
Over the next few days, then weeks,
more and more citizens of Riverdale
received copies of similar tapes.
Footage of their houses...
being watched from across the street.
For hours...
upon hours.
No messages were included
with the videos...
which somehow made the whole thing
even more disturbing.
So that by Halloween,
the entire town was on edge.
Who would get the next tape?
What do they mean?
Were they a warning?
A test?
[FP] Another one?
Keep me updated.
-The Muggses also got a tape.
-Ooh.
I'll get over there and get an interview
with them for tonight's broadcast.
That's the fringe benefit of living
with the sheriff.
I get the inside scoop
before any other reporter.
-[FP] Mm-hm.
-[Alice] Mm-hm. [giggles]
Hey, Betty, is Jug still coming home
for Halloween?
Yeah, that's the plan.
We're gonna hand out candy
and watch scary movies.
Oh.
-Why don't you invite your brother?
-Half brother.
Charles doesn't know anybody in town.
Okay, well, why is he still in town?
He's helping me with the tapes
and a couple other cases.
It's the one good thing that came out
of this nightmare.
It brought the entire family together.
Except for Jughead,
who's at Stonewall Prep.
And Polly,
who's in a facility being deprogrammed.
I think it's time, Cheryl.
-Time? Time for what?
-To say goodbye to Jason.
You've been promising me for weeks.
I know. And I'm going to.
But I can't do it before Halloween.
It's our favorite holiday.
Babe, then you're gonna say the same thing
about Thanksgiving, and then Christmas.
You're not gonna let this go, are you?
Okay, fine.
We'll rebury him on the Blossom
family plot on the grounds of Thornhill.
But I'm warning you,
he's not going to like this.
I'll get the shovels.
Moose, why do you have this?
Oh. Just thinking maybe I'm done
with high school.
I mean, I'm 18. And the Army doesn't care
who you are or where you're from.
Dude, what Bret did,
spreading that article about you,
was a real scumbag move.
But you can't let him win.
He wants you to leave.
Hell, he wants both of us to leave.
Let's not give him that satisfaction,
okay?
It's easy for you to say, Jug.
They're not calling you Gargoyle Boy.
[students chattering]
Hey. You and you.
I made it very clear that there will be
no costumes on school property.
Now, take off the masks. Come on.
Hand it over.
Get to class.
[Veronica] B, you okay?
Um, I'm not gonna lie.
I'm a little on edge this Halloween.
I mean, people are dressed up
like the Black Hood and the Gargoyle King.
And there are those damn videotapes.
I'm with you, girl.
Ever since my dad broke
into the Pembrooke,
I've been looking over my shoulder.
-And if the town's got a voyeur now--
-[Reggie] What's up, guys?
Who wants to TP Mr. Honey's office with me
tomorrow night?
Reggie, it's senior year. We're seniors.
Exactly. It's senior year. This is
our last Halloween at Riverdale High.
-I'm in, Reggie.
-Huh?
What? Kev. Why?
Honey gave me a week's detention for going
to the bathroom without a hall pass.
-That's what I'm talking about.
-Mm-hm.
[Munroe] Yo, Red.
I just got some distressing news.
You remember that crew that was working
out of the arcade? Dodger and his boys?
He's still pissed that he got beat up
and jumped by--
That, uh, vigilante.
They're planning
on wilding Halloween night.
Looking to bust some heads.
Damn it. The kids in the neighborhood
will be sitting ducks.
-We gotta do something.
-Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
Maybe keeping the center open
later than usual.
Why don't you guys host a Halloween party
at the community center?
That'll keep the kids off the streets, out
of harm's way. Don't worry about costumes.
One of my gal pals in New York,
Katy Keene,
she goes to the High School
of the Performing Arts
and is an amazing designer.
-Let me see what she can whip up for you.
-Yeah. Sounds great.
[Chipping] What about you, Jughead?
Which of your favorite horror writers
did you bring in to share?
I brought the collected works
of H.P. Lovecraft.
[chuckles] There's nothing scary
about Lovecraft.
Says the guy that brought in "The Raven"?
My favorite Poe story
is "The Cask of Amontillado."
That's the one where the guy is sealed
behind a wall, behind bricks,
and then is never seen
or heard from again.
Now, that'd be a horrible way to go.
Don't you think, Forsythe? To just vanish?
Like the Stonewall Four, you mean?
I'm betting Forsythe could make it
the Stonewall Five.
We're overdue for a vanishing.
[Jughead] Who or what are
the Stonewall Four?
Four students,
all of whom went to this school,
all of whom...
disappeared without a trace.
-All at the same time?
-No.
Uh, over 30 years or so.
And they didn't really go missing.
They dropped out.
What are you saying?
The Stonewall Four is an urban legend.
Jughead, it's campus lore. That's all.
[Toni] I am so proud of you, babe.
You are the strongest person that I know.
Well, it's not the first time
I've had to bury my brother,
but hopefully it's the last.
Well, it was the right thing to do.
Cheryl, what's that?
Oh, no.
-I was afraid of this.
-Of what?
Jason's ghost. I think he's mad at us
for what you made me do.
I know exactly where this is going.
The trash.
What are you reading, Jones?
[sighs] The Stonewall Sentinel.
Coffee? It's fresh brewed.
Yeah. Thanks.
Searching for something in particular?
Like... articles about
the Stonewall Four, perhaps?
How'd you guess?
You love a good mystery, don't you?
I've searched through years of articles,
and so far, there is nothing
about disappearing students.
My next stop is the town newspaper office
and the police station.
Jones, you okay?
Yeah. Uh...
I think I...
I think I need some air.
No.
You need to lie down.
[heart beating]
Say hello to the Stonewall Four for us.
Okay, opening my eyes now.
We look ridiculous.
You look adorable, both of you.
What are our names again?
According to Katy, you, Archie,
are Pureheart the Powerful,
and you, Munroe, are the Shield.
Right on.
Veronica, you need a ride to the center?
No, I'll take an Uber.
I still have to do some cleanup over here.
But save a dance for me, Pureheart,
won't you?
Why aren't you in a costume?
I am. I'm dressed as Laurie Strode.
Who?
From the original Halloween... movie?
[doorbell rings]
I got it.
[both] Trick or treat.
You guys look great.
-Have fun.
-[kid 1] Thank you.
-[kid 2] Thank you.
-Yep.
What time is Jughead getting here?
Uh, I don't know. I keep texting him.
Whatever. I'm going upstairs
to play Minecraft.
Okay.
Happy Halloween to me.
[woman screaming on TV]
-[thud]
-[Jughead groans]
-[Jughead] Ow.
-[thud]
-[Jughead] Ouch.
What?
All right.
That's really funny. Let me out now.
Hey!
All right, Bret.
I know you love Edgar Allan Poe,
but trying to prove
that the premature burial is scary,
the joke is on you
because I've already survived way worse.
Hey!
All right, you sick, preppy bastard.
Let me out.
Let me out!
Ow!
Hey!
[phone ringing]
[music playing on TV]
Hello?
[panting on phone]
[line clicks, then dial tone]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Jug, is that you?
[distorted voice] No, Betty. It's me.
Who is this?
You know who this is.
I don't know what kind of sick joke
you think you're playing,
but the Black Hood is dead,
and I'm calling the police.
Have you checked on the children lately?
[bell jingles]
Oh. I'm sorry, but we're closed.
You know, I've been driving straight
the last 18 hours. I--
I could really use a cup of coffee
and a home-cooked meal.
I'll be quick, I'm trying to get home
to my family by daybreak.
Take a seat. I'll get you a menu.
[man] Thank you.
["Shook" playing over speakers]
♪ I wake up in a cold sweat ♪
♪ Shoot, I feel like trash magic ♪
♪ Knew it was a dangerous idea ♪
[Archie] Eddie. What the hell?
What are you doing with that?
You know the rules. You can't have
a knife in here. Hand it over.
-Can I get it back before I go?
-Maybe.
Red, we got trouble at 2 o'clock.
Dodger and his crew just came in.
[Archie] Crap.
Hey. This is a private event.
Really?
'Cause the sign outside says
-it's open to the public.
-Not for you and your crew, Dodger.
Do I know you?
[Dodger chuckles]
Well, I know that one.
[whistles]
Eddie!
Didn't tell me
you were taking the night off.
Who's handling business out there
while you're in here having a good time?
-Time is money. Come on, let's go.
-He's not going anywhere with you.
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do about it,
Captain Spandex?
I heard you got your ass kicked
not too long ago.
If you'd like a repeat,
I'll happily oblige.
Now leave.
This is private property.
Be seeing you boys.
You, too, Eddie!
[Archie] Keep moving.
So, what do you think, Miss Isley?
Are we ready for any trick-or-treaters
who might come our way?
Oh, we're ready for a lot of things
about now, Miss Quinn.
[giggling]
[baby crying on monitor]
And cue the Toxic Twins.
They're being fussier than usual.
It must be the blood moon tonight.
Aren't they with Nana?
They're asleep.
Nana, where's the other baby monitor?
I heard him crying.
Your brother.
In the chapel.
[Toni] Okay, that's not possible.
I threw that doll away.
I told you.
It's Jay-Jay.
He's angry and now he's haunting us.
Are you messing with me?
On the ashes of Thornhill,
I swear I'm not.
But... I do think we should have a
Halloween séance to try to talk to Jason.
[Kevin] Cool.
Can we get out of here now, Reggie?
Relax, dude.
We're good.
We're golden. You saw the parking lot.
You, stay here.
Kevin, come with me.
[thud]
Jellybean?
Are you okay?
[thudding]
Got ya! [chuckles]
You should see your face.
[phone ringing]
Do not answer that.
Stay in here. Lock this door.
Listen to me, you sick son of a bitch.
I don't know who you are--
Yes, you do. I'm your father.
That's impossible.
I saw you-- Him.
I saw him die.
-You saw what I wanted you to see.
-Stop lying!
Tell me, Betty. Do you know
where this call is coming from?
Leave me alone!
It's coming from inside the house.
[pounding on door]
[line clicks, then dial tone]
Charles. What the hell are you doing here?
I was just headed home.
I thought you guys might want some pizza.
What--? Is everything okay?
[panting]
[Veronica] Here you go.
-Right off the grill.
-I really appreciate it.
Hey, can I show you something?
It's my family.
My wife and my two little girls.
Aww.
-Aren't they angels?
-They are. They're beautiful.
And very lucky to have a father
who's willing to drive through the night
for them.
-I'm gonna get you a refill.
-Thank you.
[Charles] So, someone pretending to be
the Black Hood keeps prank-calling you?
Mm-hm. On and off all night.
You know, um...
I could help you trace the call.
Really? You can do that?
Yeah. Yeah. I've got a unit
in the back of my trunk
and it would only take a few minutes
to set up.
What do you think?
Let's do it.
Yeah, I've been reviewing your records,
Kevin. You've had a rough year.
Well, a rough couple of years.
Hmm.
After everything you've been through,
I can only imagine how...
alone you must feel.
Friendless.
Sometimes, yeah.
And it's that vulnerability
that Mr. Mantle exploited, isn't it?
Miss Burble tells me your first choice...
for college is NYU.
Theater program. It's a great school.
Could be a fresh start for you.
-Sadly, I doubt you'll get in.
-Excuse me?
Hm. No.
Not after Carrie.
Not after Heathers.
And not after tonight.
It-- It-- It was Reggie's idea
to trash your office. I'm--
I don't know, I'm so sorry, okay,
-Mr. Honey?
-No, it's very good, Kevin.
It's very good.
That's all I needed to hear.
You can go now.
Talk to me, Eddie.
What's Dodger got you doing for him?
Running? Collecting? Stealing hubcaps?
What do you care?
I care because I don't want you
getting in trouble. Or worse.
Yo, Red.
You're gonna wanna check this out.
-What?
-Some of the kids wanted to go home.
Went to see if everything was cool and--
-And?
-There's trouble out front.
Hey, wait. Can I bounce?
Hell, no. You're staying here until the
party's over, then I'm walking you home.
[door opens]
[Archie] Hey!
I told you to get out of here.
Nah, it doesn't work that way.
That crap gym of yours might be
private property, but this lot isn't.
That's it. I'm done playing.
Yeah, you do that, son.
Come here and get your ass shot.
That'll make our Halloween, right, boys?
[line ringing]
Come on, come on.
[line beeps]
Mr. Jones, it's Archie. Can you do me
a favor and swing by the gym?
We got a bunch of kids here
and some punks with guns out front.
Let me know.
What do we do in the meantime?
We keep the party going
as late as we have to.
[Cheryl] I call upon the invisible forces
all around us
to aid and guide us through
this communication with the spirit world.
Is the entity inside this doll present?
Okay, come on, Cheryl. Stop moving it.
I would, Tee-Tee, except I'm not.
I swear.
Spirit... what is thy name?
I know you're upset that I made you bury
your dead brother's corpse,
but this is so messed up.
I already told you, it's not me.
It's Jay-Jay's ghost self
trying to engage with us.
This is not Jason, Cheryl.
He's not moving this board.
Antoinette's right.
It's not Jason.
It's Julian.
What do you mean, Nana?
Who's Julian?
Your mother held three babies in her womb.
Julian was to be your triplet.
But in the end,
only you and Jason were born
because, as the midwife explained it,
you, Cheryl...
had absorbed the third one.
Eaten it.
That-- That can't possibly be true.
Oh, Penelope was devastated.
So she procured this doll
and reared it alongside the two of you...
until you were no longer infants.
At which point,
Julian was retired...
to the attic.
So, now that the doll's back,
the spirit of Julian
is haunting Thistlehouse?
What other explanation
could there possibly be?
That you and Nana Rose
are working together.
And to what end
would Nana and I be colluding?
I don't know, babe.
To make me realize that things were better
when Jason was here?
So we dig him back up
and park him at the kitchen table.
Back here in the chapel
would be acceptable.
And if we did bring Jason back home...
would this haunting stop?
Could we get rid of this creepy-ass doll
once and for all
and bury him in Jason's grave?
Yes, Tee-Tee. I agree to your terms.
You know, this persona
that you've cultivated, Mr. Mantle,
this prankster, this class clown,
has made it impossible for your peers
and your teachers to take you seriously.
Do you think this has anything to do
with your father abusing you?
What?
People won't notices the bruises
or the pain
if they're laughing at one of your jokes.
Is that the thinking?
Because the thing is...
they're not laughing with you, Mr. Mantle.
They're laughing at you.
Now, you consider that
as you clean up my office
and you leave it exactly as you found it.
We haven't talked much
since everything went down with the Farm.
Haven't we?
You have every right to be wary of me.
Starting with the fact that you let Mom
walk right into the lion's den with Edgar.
Let the record show,
when I reconnected with Alice,
she found out I worked with the FBI.
She wanted to go undercover.
To help Polly. To get a story.
What about you?
What do you want?
I guess I've, um...
I've always wanted to be a part
of a real family.
But I know that that takes time.
[phone ringing]
[clears throat] Um...
Just, uh, keep him talking, okay?
Hello?
Hello again, Betty.
Who is this?
Don't play dumb.
Sorry.
I just have been getting
a lot of prank calls tonight,
pretending to be... you.
I mean, it is Halloween
and I do live in the Murder House, right?
You're testing my patience.
You remember Halloween, don't you?
We used to go trick-or-treating...
as a family?
You, me, Mom, Polly.
We'd walk up and down Elm Street.
I remember.
Then when we got home,
we would go through our bags of treats.
You didn't want us to eat the apples,
you thought there might be razor blades.
Which is pretty funny
all things considered, huh?
-Elizabeth.
-Bye, you sicko.
Did you trace it? The number?
Charles?
What is it?
Where is the call coming from?
Um...
It's coming
from Shady Grove Treatment Center,
where your sister's been staying.
Polly has been prank-calling me?
Yeah.
I'll call the main line at Shady Grove
and see how she got access to a phone.
No, no, no. Wait.
I have a better idea.
[woman on phone] Shady Grove.
How may I assist you?
Hi, I was wondering if I could speak
to one of your patients, please.
-Name of patient?
-Polly Cooper.
Who, may I ask, is calling?
Edgar.
One moment please.
[Polly] Edgar? Is it really you?
No, bitch. It's your sister.
-What?
-Edgar is worm food.
And you're as good as dead to me now, too.
What? Betty? How could you pretend
to be Edgar?
How could you pretend to be Dad?
-I-- Uh--
-You are sick, Polly. Really, truly.
[line clicks, then dial tone]
So ends
the Case of the Mystery Prank-Caller.
You know, I wish that I could say
tonight's been particularly insane
because it's Halloween, but no.
This is actually fairly typical.
[music playing on TV]
I'm not usually on kitchen duty
so I hope the burger was all right.
Delicious.
Nothing like a home-cooked meal.
[chuckles] Well, we here at Pop's try.
Any room for dessert?
We have pumpkin pie. Homemade.
Oh, well. I will take a slice of that.
-All right.
-Thank you.
[TV beeps]
[Alice on TV]
We have just received breaking news.
An extremely dangerous patient
escaped Shady Grove Treatment Center
earlier today.
A serial killer nicknamed the Family Man,
Michael Matthews,
forced his many victims to cook him meals
before brutally murdering them.
He is of average height and medium build.
After escaping from Shady Grove,
he killed a trucker,
and stole his clothes and vehicle.
[pounding on door]
[glass shattering]
[door splintering]
[footsteps]
[chuckling]
-Locker rooms are secure.
-Check the bay doors next.
[cell phone rings]
-Mr. Jones.
-[FP] Hey, sorry it's taken me a minute.
It's been a crazy night,
but I'm pulling up right now.
Okay, great.
Where's Eddie?
I'll check around back.
-[gunshots]
-[crowd screaming]
Hey!
[whimpering]
Eddie! Eddie!
I need an ambulance now.
El Royale Boxing Club. Right now!
[indistinct radio chatter]
You're okay.
[Charles] Hey, I've been thinking. Um...
Given how well you handled yourself
with the Farm at the motel,
I think you'd make an excellent candidate
for the Junior FBI training program.
An FBI program for high schoolers?
-Is that actually a thing? Hm.
-It is.
We could work together trying to
figure out who's sending these videotapes.
You know this town a whole lot better
than I do.
That's true.
Will you consider it at least?
Looks good, Mr. Mantle.
So, can I go home?
I mean, it's already morning.
As long as we understand each other,
we can walk out of here together.
What the hell? Bella?
Bella!
[gasps] What happened to my car?!
It's such a shame when someone
disrespects your property, isn't it?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
I wonder who did this.
Probably hooligans having
some Halloween fun.
Would you like a ride, Mr. Mantle?
No. No, thank you.
Well...
get home safe.
You're home now, Jay-Jay.
For good.
All is right in the world.
Isn't it, my love?
Yep.
Everything's back to normal.
[creaking]
[door creaking]
[door shuts]
Hey! Hey.
Help! Help!
I'm trapped!
Help me! Help!
[creaking]
Mr. Jones.
Good morning. I, uh...
I see you've been had.
Mis-- Mr. Chipping.
What--? Where--?
I'm always amazed at my students' antics.
How they get extra creative at Halloween.
Creative?
Don't take it personally, Jughead.
It's a Stonewall Prep tradition.
It means you belong now.
Belong to what?
To us, of course.
Here is your phone.
You have a lot of missed texts and calls.
Did you know about this?
Absolutely not.
-What was even the point of this?
-It's a bit of Halloween fun. That's all.
What, we go too far?
Well, in that case,
you could always just leave.
No.
I'm good.
Happy Halloween, kids.
-[Archie] How you feeling, Eddie?
-Like I got shot in the leg.
The doctor said it was just a flesh wound.
You got really lucky, Eddie.
It could have been a lot worse.
If Dodger and his crew did this,
we can help you.
-Me, Munroe, Sheriff Jones.
-Help how?
The last thing I need is for these guys
to think that I snitched.
Especially since you took away
my switchblade.
That's not gonna protect you
from guys like Dodger.
But Munroe and I will.
Come hang with us at the center.
They won't step foot in there ever again.
Okay, then what happens
when the center closes at 10?
Where do I go then?
I'm back out on the street
'cause I have to be.
A lot of us are.
I have two options:
Either I roll with Dodger...
or hide from Dodger.
That's it.
I can't believe you held that guy off
on your own.
I mean, I can.
You know you're a total badass, right?
I like to think so.
And how did Pureheart hold up?
[groans]
Honestly?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I vowed to create a safe space
for the kids in this town,
something my dad could be proud of.
It's never gonna happen as long as guys
like Dodger are on the streets.
Okay, so then we clean up the streets.
Archie.
As well as you fill them out,
you're not actually considering
fighting crime in those tights, are you?
Of course not.
I'm gonna need a mask.
-[Toni] Cheryl?
-How was your shower, my love?
Why was this sitting on the bed?
I thought we agreed to put an end to this.
Jason's back. You got what you wanted.
Although it pains me to admit it...
yes, I was gaslighting you before.
And for that, I apologize.
But I swear on Jason's life, I have
no idea how that got back into this house.
Truly.
Well, then how is this happening?
I mean... we for sure buried this doll,
right?
[Rose] I told you.
It's Julian.
Tee-Tee.
I'm afraid the true haunting
of Thistlehouse has only just begun.
Moose, you are not going to believe
what Bret--
[Jughead] I mean,
it's like Moose completely vanished.
There's not a trace of him anywhere,
Betty.
Well, is it possible
he actually joined the Army?
I don't know.
I placed a couple calls, but I know
it was them that chased him out of here.
I mean, did they lock me in that coffin
because they wanted me out of the way
while they terrorized Moose into leaving?
I don't know.
I just hate that they kept me
from helping you.
I'm sorry that you had
to go through that alone.
Technically, I wasn't alone.
I was with Charles.
Oh.
So, are you warming up
to our half brother now?
I guess so.
[on headphones] Yeah. Kind of.
He wants me to join the Junior FBI, which,
I don't know, I might actually be good at.
[Jughead] Yeah.
I think you would be great at it.
I'm just glad
that Charles was there for you.
[Betty] Yeah.
He might be the real deal.
Meanwhile, I feel guilty
that I wasn't there for you, Jug.
No. Well, actually, you were there for me.
Thinking about you was the only thing
that kept me from losing hope.
And my sanity.
I think I know that if I ever went missing
that you would be the one to find me.
I would, Jug.
I promise.