[Jughead] Forget art imitating life.
Here we had a case of art imitating death.
A snuff film that showed Jason Blossom
being murdered by dear old Dad,
-[gunshot]
-and a bizarre recreation of it.
Months of static shots of houses,
now this. Why change the pattern?
Our voyeur is trying to recreate himself
into an auteur.
No longer satisfied with merely
documenting our daily lives, it seems.
Between this tape
and the one of Betty killing me,
it seems like he's trying
to painstakingly recreate our deaths.
Or near-deaths.
He's trying to blur the line
between fact and fiction.
Is it a warning?
-Could be a rehearsal.
-For what?
An actual murder.
So, our auteur got a copy
of the Jason Blossom murder video,
and then pulls a Gus Van Sant
and tries to remake it?
Where did he get the original video?
Blue Velvet Video.
Is there anything else we can do
at this point?
Wait for another tape.
Keep going through the videos
that we confiscated
from the Scarlet Suite.
I'm gonna have
to let you two fellas handle that
because I have to finish proofing
the yearbook tonight.
That's the most high school thing
you've ever said.
[Betty sighs]
Here it is, Mr. Honey.
Riverdale High's yearbook, as requested.
There will be no yearbook this year,
Miss Cooper.
Sorry, what? Why?
The deadline for the printers
was two days ago.
Yes, but I called the printers,
and they said
if we get it to them this afternoon,
the yearbooks will be ready by graduation.
Yes, but I told you
that I would need to approve every page.
And I will not be able to do that
by this afternoon.
I pulled all-nighters to get this done.
And because I'm two days late,
you're punishing all of my classmates?
-How is that fair?
-I'm sorry, Miss Cooper...
but my decision is final.
[cell phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[woman] Is this Forsythe Pendleton Jones?
-Depends who's asking.
-My name is Deena Lunham.
I'm the admissions coordinator
at the University of Iowa.
Do you have a moment
to talk about your application?
Breaking news, everybody.
So, the University of Iowa has one of
the best writing programs in the country.
I applied for spring,
but then they told me
they could take me as early as fall.
You're a good writer, bro.
Wait.
So, this acceptance is conditional?
Yeah. They require additional materials,
which means I need another story.
But this could be my redemption
after that Stonewall hell.
The only problem is, the well
of my creative unconscious is tapped out.
Well, you could write a monster story
about Mr. Honey.
-I am proud of you though, Jug.
-What did he do?
Honey is refusing to publish the yearbook.
Our legacy,
the written record of our last four years,
our friendships, our loves, clubs, dances.
Bee, if it's about money,
I'm happy to help pay for the printing.
Thank you, Vee.
But it's the principle of it.
Mr. Honey has been on our case
since day one.
Do you remember when he threatened us
on our first day back?
And how many of us are already banned
from going to prom?
Fangs, Reggie, Toni and I are all banned
because of Ticklegate.
And I'm out because
of that bogus quiz show cheating scandal.
Lest we not forget
my transcendent rendition of "Cherry Bomb"
which got Veronica, the Vixens and myself
barred from the promenade.
So, literally the only people going
to prom are...
-You wanna go to prom with me, Jug?
-I'd be honored. But I'm not putting out.
Let the fan fiction begin.
Cousin Betty, I share your outrage.
Something must be done
to stop this heinous villain.
Like what? Every time we make
a move against him, he hits us back.
He's not letting Archie walk
with the rest of us at graduation.
He's a fiend.
Although one thing
that would stop Mr. Honey...
is if we killed him.
Or scared him enough to leave town.
I mean, it would be so easy.
Mr. Honey works late on Tuesdays.
He usually leaves around 9.
-[record scratches]
-Wouldn't he recognize us?
Good point, Arch. Okay, let's say,
we wear bunny masks
and Stonewall Prep jackets.
[Archie] I could sneak up
and knock him out, take him down.
[Betty] Then we'd tie him up
and stuff him into the trunk of a car.
What do you say, Reggie?
Can we borrow Bella for this?
After the way Honey trashed her
on Halloween night?
[Reggie] Bella! [gasps]
What happened to my car?
Such a shame when someone disrespects
your property, isn't it?
Hell, yeah.
[Archie] Now where do we take him?
My family still owns that cabin
in Fox Forest.
[Betty] Then we take him there.
And make him think he's gonna die.
[Cheryl] And I know just the way
we can do that.
Veronica?
Do you remember when we maple-boarded
my monster of a Mumzie?
[coughing]
We're letting you go.
But you're leaving town tonight.
And if you don't, we'll keep doing this.
And we won't stop until you're dead.
You're insane.
Fine. More syrup please.
Someone start digging his grave.
No, no, no. I'll leave. I'll leave!
At least that's one way
we could get our revenge.
Well, we could do that. For sure.
Or we could pull off
a classic senior prank,
the likes of which
will never be forgotten.
And I've got just the one for Mr. Honey.
It's an oldie... but a goodie.
[squelching sound]
[ringing]
["Chase The Feeling" playing]
Miss Bell, could you come in here?
-Miss Bell!
-♪ There's no room in this city ♪
♪ Smokestacks burned my house
Ain't pretty ♪
♪ Show me you're down to watch ♪
♪ And I will tell you
'Bout what you've begun ♪
♪ Most days my nose is bloody
Most days I just think it's funny ♪
♪ I sail across the oceans
And I fly into the night ♪
♪ I'm coming out ♪
Looks like we won this round.
Maybe.
Though I still think
we should've killed him.
Jug. What are you doing?
I'm writing a new story for Iowa.
You gave me the idea actually.
It's called "Killing Mr. Honey."
Great title.
It's perfect. I get to write something
for my Iowa submission
while simultaneously working on
our collective revenge fantasy
against Mr. Honey.
I printed some pages on your night table
if you wanna read.
[Jughead] Kidnapping Mr. Honey
was supposed to be a joke, a prank...
payback for how he terrorized them
all year long.
[Jughead] Where are his glasses?
[Archie] Crap. They must have fallen out
on the way.
[Jughead] No one was supposed to die.
I can barely see without my glasses,
so you might as well take
those ridiculous masks off.
[Archie] Shut the hell up.
I know exactly who you are. Mr. Mantle.
Mr. Andrews.
And Mr. Jones.
And clearly you've partnered
with Miss Lodge, Miss Blossom
and of course...
Miss Cooper.
-[Archie] What the hell are you doing?
-He said he knew who we were.
Actually, I didn't know, Mr. Mantle,
I suspected.
But thanks to your stupidity...
my suspicions have been confirmed.
He played you like a cheap violin.
-You just blew our cover, you idiot.
-[laughing]
You think that's funny?
You think you're better than me?
-Reggie!
-Hey, Reg, come on. Come on, stop it.
-Stop. You're gonna kill him. Stop.
-Stop, Reggie!
Tell me, Mr. Mantle...
is that what your father does to you?
-Shut up!
-Hey, Reggie!
We're leaving now, Mr. Honey.
But we'll be back soon.
You shut your damn mouth
or we're gonna let him back in.
Wow, that's dark.
Is it too dark?
No. I love it.
[cell phone dings]
Well, duty calls.
Charles wants us to meet him
at his office.
Is there any way you could take point
on that? I wanna continue working on this.
Sure.
[Jughead] Once Mr. Honey was secure
at the cabin, we took turns watching him.
Cheryl was first.
Have one of you found them?
My glasses?
TBH, I don't know.
It's not too late, Miss Blossom, you...
You can make this right.
We are making it right.
By kidnapping me?
How do you think this ends?
Betty and Jughead have a plan.
Huh.
Well, I've never taken you
to be a follower.
Yes, well, you've given us something
we've never had before:
a common enemy.
You were cruel to me, Mr. Honey.
You barred me and all of my Vixens
from prom.
You locked Miss Appleyard in her office.
She had a panic attack and quit.
What was I supposed to do?
What am I supposed to do now?!
Hmm.
Agree to make a video.
Giving us permission to go to prom
and promising
that you won't punish us for this,
or anything, ever again.
Might I suggest an alternative,
Miss Blossom?
Release me. Call the police.
Tell them it was a...
It was a school prank
that went horribly awry.
You will be punished, of course.
But at least your lives won't be ruined.
So, you won't make that video, then?
Absolutely not.
Fine.
Then it's your funeral, Mr. Honey.
Mrs. Klump received this new videotape
this morning.
-[Alice screams over video]
-[Betty] Oh, my God. Another recreation?
But where did you get the actual footage?
Finished going through the videos
we confiscated from Blue Velvet.
Turns out Jason Blossom's snuff film
wasn't the only contraband that David had.
Where the hell is he getting these from?
[Jughead] Next, it was Archie
and Veronica's turn
to check on their captive,
to see if he'd had a change of heart.
[door creaking]
Mr. Honey.
Does he have a pulse? Here. Let me check.
Is he okay?
Is he alive?
[Honey] You're late.
And you are?
I'm Principal Weatherbee's replacement.
Mr. Honey.
Things are gonna be different this year.
We'll have order, discipline.
[Archie] Is he okay? Is he alive?
No...
he's not.
He's dead.
RIP, Mr. Honey.
[rock music playing lightly over speakers]
Brace yourselves, bitches.
I just saw our most hated foe,
the malefactor Honey, entering his office.
Was his ass still glued to his chair?
I heard they had to use turpentine
to unstick him.
He was smelling particularly odious.
[mic feedback whines over PA]
Students of Riverdale High,
unless the person or persons
responsible for yesterday's
so-called prank step forward,
prom is officially canceled.
I knew it. I knew your juvenile antics
were going to end in tragedy.
Turn thyself in, Reginald, immediately.
No way.
I pranked Mr. Honey
on behalf of all of us.
And for the record...
I did not prank alone.
Oh, God. And who would be stupid enough
to help you?
-Kevin.
-Archie?
What's the big deal?
It's not like any of us
were allowed to go.
We were going to crash it, you doddypoll.
Now there's nothing left to crash.
I refuse to be the only sitting president
in the history of Riverdale High
who didn't sponsor a prom!
Okay, everyone, chill.
Reggie's not the enemy here. Mr. Honey is.
If we all turn against each other now,
we all lose.
If we want the prom back,
we need to think strategically.
Betty, what should we do?
We research our enemy,
determine if there are any skeletons
in his closet we can exploit.
I'll take point on that.
In the meantime...
Nobody panic.
[Reggie] I don't understand.
-I didn't even hit him that hard.
-Why'd you even have to hit him, Reggie?
-You were the last one to see him alive.
-I didn't do anything.
He was fine when I left him. He must've
toppled over in his chair or something.
We wanted to scare Mr. Honey,
not kill him.
Well, he's dead.
There's no walking back from it.
Jughead's right. What's done is done.
The only question is,
are we going to let
this terrible accident,
and yes, I am calling it an accident,
which it was,
ruin our lives, our future?
I hope not.
I'm going to Highsmith College.
I'm going to Barnard.
-I'm going to Yale.
-I'm going to the Naval Academy.
I'm trying to go
to the University of Iowa.
And I'm going
to Riverdale Community College.
Maybe.
All right, then, who here has experience
in getting rid of a dead body?
Am I the only one that hasn't gotten rid
of a dead body before?
No time like the present, bro.
You're not gonna believe this.
I did some sleuthing
on our least favorite tyrant
and it turns out there's a pattern
to his reign of terror.
Honey has canceled prom
at every high school he's worked at.
For different reasons,
but the end result is always the same.
Jeez. He's like the Grinch
that stole prom.
What are we gonna do with this?
We share this key information
with our troops
and dispatch them
to the appropriate parties.
-Hi, honey. How was school?
-Well, Mom, now that you mention it...
Mr. Honey canceled prom.
That's not even the worst of it.
He's doing it out of spite.
And, look, I'm not one for school dances,
but this one means a lot.
Nana, it's our senior year, and I
for one did not suffer for four years
to have this one magical night taken away
by some hateful he-shrew.
This is like a personal vendetta with him.
We can't let
Mr. Honey take this away from us,
not after everything we've been through.
Mr. Jones, Mom...
we need this.
["Ready Let's Go" playing]
♪ Knocked down, but I won't take no
Show up that I'm in the zone ♪
♪ Can't get hot 'till you bend down low ♪
♪ Are you ready, are you ready
Are you ready ♪
♪ Dumb it up, I will not go slow ♪
♪ Are you ready, are you ready
Are you ready, let's go ♪
Mr. Honey,
as concerned parents, we're here
to demand that you reinstate prom
and you re-invite those students
you so rudely barred from attending.
That won't be possible.
You see, it's my job
to prepare these students
to be upstanding citizens of the world,
and their behavior needs to reflect that.
So far, it has not.
Oh, I'll show you some behavior.
Mr. Honey, Mary Andrews here,
attorney-at-law.
May I bring to your attention the case of
Murray et al
v. The Greendale School District?
A small-town principal canceled prom,
and the parents of said small town
sued him for psychological damage
and won.
I'm a very good lawyer, Mr. Honey.
And might I add,
as the mayor of Riverdale,
I have a direct line to Governor Dooley
and the Board of Education.
And I'd hate for them to look into,
and possibly revoke, your credentials.
And RIVW has been hungry
for a gripping public-interest story
that would make nationwide headlines.
"Principal Cancels Prom Out of Spite,"
I think would surely fit the bill.
[sighs]
-And what will you two do to me?
-Oh, we're just the muscle.
[Honey chuckles]
Well, I am sorry,
but my decision is final.
Actually, it's not.
As president of the PTA,
I have a right to demand a vote
on this matter.
Perhaps if all of us,
say, over the age of 20,
would like to adjourn to my office,
we might discuss this as adults.
Yes, let's do that.
And as student body president,
I'll be joining.
[Honey] Fine.
♪ Are you ready, are you ready
Are you ready ♪
[Jughead] And so the dragon that had been
terrorizing the halls of Riverdale High
was beaten, vanquished.
All that remained was giving it
a proper burial.
Hurry up. It's almost dawn.
How deep does this grave have to be?
Deep. It's Riverdale.
What's shocking is, how many times have
we said these very words in real life?
I know, isn't it chilling?
Hobo. Bride of Hobo.
As student body president,
I have an announcement to make.
Although, I believe this proclamation
calls for a more festive setting.
[indistinct chatter]
[clears throat]
Classmates,
mothers, fathers,
Nana...
prom is officially back on!
[all cheering]
So, I'd like to propose a toast.
To generations united.
Together, we have proven victorious.
To all of us...
and to a senior prom we will never forget.
-Cheers.
-And if I may speak for the grown-ups...
-[FP] Yep.
We're just so very, very proud of you
and the thoughtful, intelligent
young adults you've become.
You kids have been through a lot,
much more than we did
when we were at Riverdale High.
[Alice and Mary laugh]
And we may not say it enough,
but you mean the world to us.
And although it may not always
seem like it,
we have your best interests at heart.
You worked hard. You deserve to celebrate.
My boy is gonna be the first Jones man
to go to college!
-[whoops]
-[all cheering]
[Jughead] They were supposed
to feel relief.
Honey was dead and buried.
And they'd gotten away with it.
They were free.
Free to go back to talking about college
and homework and prom.
So, in terms of a theme for prom,
I was thinking old Hollywood.
I was going
to suggest F. Scott Fitzgerald,
The Beautiful and the Damned.
-But old Hollywood glamor works as well.
-[Betty] Mm.
-How many limos should we get?
-How can you talk about prom and limos
after what we did last night?
Hey, Reggie. Shut the hell up right now.
All I'm saying is,
last night was majorly messed up.
Reg.
Guys, I was just in the front office
and I saw Miss Bell talking to the police.
What? What were they talking about?
You know
how Principal Honey's gone missing?
Well, some Adventure Scouts
were camping in the woods,
found a pair of glasses
that might belong to Mr. Honey.
So, now the police
are suspecting foul play.
They're canceling class,
sending out a search party.
Should we go sign up?
This is a great complication, Jug.
-You think so?
-Mm-hm.
You don't think the Adventure Scout
finding the glasses is too contrived?
Guys, I was in the office just now.
Mr. Honey asked me to find you.
Said he wanted to see you ASAP.
That's weird.
Charles.
Mr. Honey.
What's up, Chuck?
Well, a videotape was delivered
to the school this morning.
And I called Agent Smith,
and he told me that the two of you
have been helping him with his case.
I thought you might wanna see this.
Be warned, it's extremely unsettling.
Now, it's just the school's facade
at first.
But then...
How long does this go on for?
[Honey] Hours.
Whoever shot this video covered
every inch of the school,
every hallway, every classroom.
The gym, the auditorium, the locker rooms.
But what could it possibly mean?
Because it feels like a...
I don't know, a warning or a threat.
Wouldn't you agree, Agent Smith?
That's one way to interpret it. Yes.
Well, in that case...
it seems I have no other option
but to put the school on high alert.
And despite the PTA's wishes, cancel prom.
If this tape even suggests the possibility
of violence against any of my students,
every precaution must be taken,
including curbing
extracurricular activities.
Will you let your friends know
while I alert your parents?
Mm-hm.
-This feels very wrong.
-Completely agree.
We know that our guy has moved on from
simple recordings and on to recreations.
This tape feels like he's backtracking.
-I mean, unless he's revisiting themes.
-[Jughead] Or it could be a hoax.
Think about it.
The general public does not know
our voyeur-slash-auteur has moved on
to recreations, right?
-Correct.
-I'm following you, Jughead.
So, if someone wanted to pretend
to be our auteur
and they didn't have
the privileged information that we do,
they would have shot a video
exactly like the one Mr. Honey was sent.
It's not a coincidence.
Honey wants to cancel prom,
he's conveniently sent a video
that gives him the perfect excuse?
Guys, unless we have conclusive proof
that this videotape was made
by someone other than our original guy,
Honey's well within his rights
to cancel prom.
-Can we borrow a copy of Honey's tape?
-Sure. Why?
-So, we can review every second of it.
-[Betty] No.
You have a story to write.
I will watch the damn tape. Let's go.
[Jughead] And then, without warning,
their carefully constructed plan began
to unravel,
thanks to a guilt-ridden Reggie.
Hey. You know what I heard about Honey?
I heard he was hooking up with a student
and got run out of town.
Who cares? The guy was a total perv.
Gave me the creeps.
[Reggie] What are you saying?
What are you saying?
That you're glad that he's dead?
Reggie, shut the hell up.
No. That's not what we're saying.
Look, all I'm saying is,
the guy was a total weirdo.
If he ran off, who cares? Good riddance.
He didn't run off.
They found his glasses.
-[Jimmy] What's your point?
-Dude. Reggie, I'm serious.
Just that...
they found his glasses,
but Honey will never be found 'cause he--
Shut up. Shut up.
You don't know what you're talking about.
I'm ordering Chinese. You want lo mein?
Yep. And some fried wontons, please.
Chicken or veggie?
Oh, hell, no.
Charles.
I think we got him.
[door opens]
Agent Smith.
Miss Cooper, Mr. Jones.
May I help you?
Yes, you can tell us
whether or not this is you
in the screen grab
from the video you received.
[Jughead] Is it you holding the camera
in that photo?
I mean, it's only two frames,
but it's enough to nail your ass.
If you're suggesting
that I'm sending videotapes around town--
No, not all the tapes. Just this one.
You're a copycat, Mr. Honey,
and not a very good one.
Using the voyeur's MO
to ramp up your personal feud
against me and my friends?
Feud?
I've been trying to protect you.
The only person we need protection from
is you, Mr. Honey. You're deranged.
I was trying to help you.
To prepare you for a life
outside of Riverdale.
You can justify your actions all you want,
but we already sent copies of the videos
to the school board, aka our parents,
so between them and the FBI,
I hope you have a good lawyer.
Guess that's checkmate, Mr. Honey.
Don't mess with us in our own town.
What causes a principal
to hate his students so much?
Was he bullied in high school?
Is his entire career based on revenge?
Well, maybe he should have had sessions
with Mrs. Burble
along with the rest of us.
At least now you can finish your story
without any real-life interruptions.
How close are you to being done?
Oh, I'm close. Reggie just died.
Reggie? Why did Reggie have to die?
[Cheryl sobbing]
It's not right.
Reggie didn't deserve that.
Of course he didn't deserve it, Cheryl.
You need to get ahold of yourself.
Do you understand me?
It's very sad, tragic even,
what happened to Reggie,
but he was out of control.
He couldn't handle himself
when Mr. Honey died.
Died? Are you serious?
Jughead's right, Cheryl.
Reggie was spiraling. He was drinking.
Tell her, Arch.
Yeah. If I hadn't been
in the locker room that time,
I don't know what he would have said.
Fine, but did we have to cut his brakes?
I mean, we murdered our friend.
What are you talking about, Vee?
We didn't cut Reggie's brakes.
His death was an accident.
The truth is,
he was never taking care of that car
the way he should have.
Eventually, it just caught up with him.
We can't change what happened.
The only thing we can do is live
our lives.
Wow, are you hearing yourselves?
It's like you actually believe this crap.
Ronnie, two people are dead right now.
Dead.
And right now, the world thinks
that Reggie died from a car accident.
A horrible car accident.
So, this ends.
Right now.
If we all just stick together...
-Will you do that for me?
-My God.
I knew Betty and Jughead had
a dark streak,
but when did you become
such a monster, Archiekins?
[snickers] Come on.
Don't kid yourself, Veronica.
In this town, we're all monsters.
We've always been monsters,
and that includes you, too.
The question is,
are we going to be monsters in college?
Or in jail?
Wow.
So, we're the monsters.
I kind of just go wherever
the story leads me.
But don't worry, I'm gonna change
all of our names before I submit it.
So, no one is going to know
the perverted truth about us...
but us.
So, what happens next?
Do Veronica and Cheryl go to the police?
Or does your teen-angst body count
increase by two?
I honestly don't know yet.
I'm still trying to decide
between some cautionary morality tale
and a nihilistic dark comedy.
Guys. Dead man walking. Hallway.
Right now.
-That was fast.
-["Trigger Bang Bang" playing]
♪ It sounds like
Trigger bang bang, trigger ♪
♪ Trigger bang bang ♪
♪ Trigger bang bang, trigger ♪
♪ Bang bang, bang, trigger ♪
♪ Trigger bang bang ♪
Well, Mr. Honey.
Looks like the good guys won.
What?
Is that what you think happened here?
Well, you're leaving and we're staying,
so yeah, I'd mark that as a win.
Hmm.
I stand by everything that I've done...
including the videotape.
Everything that I have done
is to make this school better, safer,
for you and your classmates.
Because what goes on around here,
murder, mayhem, depravity...
it is not normal.
Well, it's normal to us,
which is why we had to stop you.
[scoffs] Stop me?
Miss Cooper...
I saw the writing on the wall days ago
and I lined up my next job.
I am Stonewall Prep's new headmaster.
It seems they cleaned house
and were in need of a strong leader
to help them rebuild their reputation.
And my salary,
it's triple what I've been making here.
All right, you know what? Screw Mr. Honey.
-He sucks.
-[Veronica] That's right, Archiekins.
I mean, who doctors up fake evidence
just to cancel prom?
-And takes away a school's yearbook?
-And censors a variety show?
A psycho, that's who.
That man is anything but.
I have been working in that front office
for 50 years.
And in all that time,
I have outlasted eight principals.
And beyond a doubt, the best by far
was Mr. Honey.
Poor Miss Bell.
You've fallen under the monster's spell.
Do any of you have any idea
what that man has done for this school?
This year alone,
he personally arranged
for six low-income students
to go to colleges on full scholarships.
Wait. Really?
Also, this year's average GPA is higher
than it's been in decades.
And more seniors will be going to college
than have since 1956.
Oh, and of course,
no students have died under his watch.
He asked me to mail this for you...
but I don't think I will.
You may wanna read it though,
to fully comprehend your actions.
What is it, Jug?
It's a letter written by Mr. Honey
to the University of Iowa.
Are you gonna open it?
Look, it can't be worse
than whatever you're imagining.
What did Mr. Honey say?
Was he trying to screw you over?
Oh, my God.
I have to change it.
-Change what?
-My story. I have to fix it.
[Jughead] The problem with believing
you have all the answers
is that it blinds you to the truth
that's right before your eyes.
[door creaking]
Mr. Honey.
Ronnie, what do we do?
Call 911.
-No, if we do that, then--
-If we don't, he'll die.
Call 911.
I'll give him CPR.
Hi, yeah. We need an ambulance.
-What the hell happened?
-It's okay.
-The doctor said Honey's gonna make it.
-No, I'm more worried about us.
Okay. What do the police know?
What did you tell them?
The truth.
That this all started as some stupid prank
and that things got out of hand.
A prank? Do you realize what you've done?
Yeah. We kept a man from dying.
And ruined our lives.
Reggie's right. You guys just
wrecked everything. Our futures.
-None of us are gonna go to college.
-Who cares about college?
We could spend the next 20 years
of our lives in Shankshaw--
[whispers] In Shankshaw Prison.
Are you listening to yourselves?
Mr. Honey could have died.
We would have been murderers.
Better that than what's coming next
for all of us.
You don't mean that, Betty, do you?
That you would have preferred
Mr. Honey to die?
[Betty] What made you rewrite it?
Guess I finally realized
what I was saying, how I was saying it.
I've been reveling
in this town's sickness,
and I was enjoying the suffering
of another person.
Even if it was Mr. Honey.
This is about Mr. Honey's letter,
isn't it?
-What does he say in it?
-Hey, guys.
Hey, Jellybean, uh,
now's not the best time.
Well, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but this was on our doorstep.
["Everything's a Lie" playing]
♪ Everything's a lie ♪
♪ A lie, a lie, a lie ♪
More house shots?
Maybe it's another copycat?
Maybe it's an invitation.
Yeah, but where? That place doesn't
even look like it's in Riverdale.
No, but I've seen this place before.
That's the cabin where Veronica's mom
killed Sheriff Minetta,
where they had their affair.
I'll go get my keys.
What's that for?
Looks like a makeshift screen.
This projector reminds me of the ones
we used to have at the drive-in.
There's no film in it though.
Jug.
[Honey] Dear Headmaster Koontz,
greetings from Riverdale High.
I wanted to follow up on our conversation
with a short note.
Though Jughead Jones has had
an incredibly difficult year, as you know,
and I've only interacted with him
a scant few times, he is a special kid
and he is a superb writer.
But he needs a break,
he needs good teachers
and a healthy environment,
which I know
the University of Iowa can provide.
Now, I don't say this lightly,
but I do believe Jughead Jones will be
an important voice of his generation.
If you'd like to discuss him further,
please call me at any time.
All my best to you and Edith.
Sincerely, Holden Honey.