[Jughead] It was over.
The evils of Stonewall Prep
had been vanquished.
And life in Riverdale, more or less,
picked up where it had left off.
But at its heart,
Riverdale was and is a wicked little town.
So, no one was surprised
when a third round of sinister videotapes
was delivered to our doorsteps.
♪ You know the sun is in your eyes ♪
♪ And hurricanes and rains
And black and cloudy skies ♪
♪ You're running up and down that hill ♪
♪ You turn it on and off at will ♪
♪ There's nothing here
To thrill or bring you down ♪
♪ And if you've got no other choice ♪
♪ You know you can follow my voice ♪
♪ Through the dark turns and noise
Of this wicked little town ♪
♪ The Fates are vicious
And they're cruel ♪
♪ You learn too late
You've used two wishes like a fool ♪
♪ The pious, hateful and devout ♪
♪ You're turning tricks
Till you're turned out ♪
♪ The wind so cold, it burns
You're burning out, blowing round ♪
♪ And then you're someone you are not ♪
♪ And Riverdale, it ain't the spot ♪
♪ Remember Mrs. Lot and ♪
[all] ♪ When she turned around ♪
♪ And if you've got no other choice ♪
♪ You know you can follow my voice ♪
♪ Through the dark turns and noise
Of this wicked little town ♪
[Jughead] No one slept much that night...
as they waited for a new day to dawn.
Daddy?
You have a doctor's appointment,
don't you?
Which I'll go to as soon
as I finish my coffee.
[Hiram grunting]
Come on.
[grunts] Little help. Little help!
[exhales sharply]
-Holy crap, Mr. Lodge.
-Thanks, Archie.
Maybe you should ease up...
you know, considering your condition.
What the hell are you talking about?
Veronica told me that you're sick.
Well, clearly, my daughter's confused
because I'm perfectly healthy.
But if she is concerned
for some unfounded reason,
then you'll agree that...
she doesn't need to know about this.
-Mr. Lodge, look, if you need help--
-What I need is privacy.
This is not your business,
nor hers frankly.
Do we understand each other, Archie?
Yes, sir. We do.
All right, take a plate off.
So, I talked to all your teachers,
and we figured out a way for you
to catch up on all of your classes.
Phew. That's not daunting at all.
-[scoffs] There's an index?
-Mm-hm.
And it's color-coded.
Red is for American History.
You missed the midterm,
so you can catch up by writing an essay
on either the Trail of Tears
or the Salem witch trials.
-Salem witch trials, definitely.
-Mm-hm. Blue, English.
You can choose
amongst Steinbeck's The Pearl,
Hemingway's The Old Man and the Sea
and London's The Call of the Wild
-for your book report.
-[sighs]
What, you already read all three of them.
No, I know. It's just--
Writing a book report?
Now I know how Sisyphus must've felt.
Given how far behind I am
on literally every topic,
is it even worth trying
to catch up at this point?
Look, I know this is a lot.
It's a lot of work,
but it's only for a couple of months,
just to make sure
that you graduate... with me.
What is more important than that?
Jughead. What a surprise.
What do you need?
Something to stimulate my brain
as I plow through this pile of work
that Betty has lined up for me.
I was thinking, in between writing
these mind-numbing essays,
I can help you review the latest round
of videotapes from our mysterious voyeur.
Absolutely. I could use some help
scrubbing through the footage.
The voyeur's stepping up his or her game,
filming more and more houses.
I don't ever wanna see what would happen
if he found his way inside a house.
Thank you.
Oh, uh...
One more thing.
If you could keep
my moonlighting on the DL?
You mean from Betty?
How about this? I won't bring it up to her
unless she asks me directly.
Thank you.
Here you go, Principal Honey.
Another list of sign-ups
for the variety show.
Hmm. Well, I've reviewed
the acts submitted so far.
They mostly seem fine, with one exception.
Yours.
I'm sorry, but you won't be allowed to do
a number from Hedwig and the Angry Inch.
That show is...
It's not appropriate
for students and families.
It was on Broadway.
-There's a movie version of it.
-An R-rated movie version.
Look, why don't you do a number
from a classic musical,
like Oklahoma! or Carousel?
Instead of some niche,
downtown, cabaret show
that would be more appropriate
for pre-Nazi Berlin?
Hedwig is not a niche show.
It celebrates identities, genders,
expressions of all kinds.
And it speaks to my entire generation.
We are relentlessly slammed
with crisis after crisis.
And we take it, and we're numb, yes,
but also screaming on the inside.
Please, just...
Just listen to us.
We're people, not numbers.
We're Generation Z.
["Random Number Generation" playing]
♪ All our feelings and thoughts ♪
♪ Expressed in ones and in oughts ♪
♪ In endless spiraling chains ♪
♪ You can't decode or explain
'Cause you are so analog ♪
♪ God, dog, I, eye, I, God, dog ♪
♪ We're the random number ♪
♪ Generation, we are ♪
♪ Random number generated ♪
♪ We are random numbers ♪
♪ In the regime of the solid state ♪
♪ Wheels spin as you iterate ♪
♪ K is X squared minus 1 ♪
♪ But 0.54321 ♪
♪ When X is taken times 2
That's when we're coming for you ♪
♪ We're the random number ♪
♪ Generation, we are ♪
♪ Random number generated, we are ♪
♪ Hey, here we are ♪
♪ We're the random number ♪
♪ Generation, we are ♪
♪ Random number generated ♪
♪ We are random numbers ♪
[school bell rings]
You see, the music of Hedwig is
the perfect fit for--
Mr. Keller, you can either pick
a different song,
or recuse yourself from the variety show
and all your attendant duties.
Effective immediately.
Damn it.
[Kevin] Late breaking news.
I am now singing
"Oh, What a Beautiful Mornin'"
from Oklahoma! for the variety show.
What happened to Hedwig?
Honey nixed it.
Said it was too controversial.
Kevin, if you wanna do Hedwig,
you should do Hedwig.
He'd yank me offstage
before the first note.
Hell, I don't even think you should wait
for the variety show.
I think you should go rogue.
Go rogue in what way?
Okay.
You know I support you,
and I think you're an amazing writer, Jug,
but this feels a little... phoned-in.
There's typos and incomplete sentences,
and I'm not even sure what the thesis is.
Yeah, okay.
Maybe I'll go offline,
hole myself up in the bunker
after school and really focus on it.
Play Thomas Pynchon for a while.
[school bell ringing]
[Veronica] Ooh. He comes bearing gifts.
And some news.
I know this seems a little last minute...
but I signed us up for the variety show.
To perform as a band.
Well, obviously, I'm completely in.
You know I support you kids
and your rock 'n' roll,
but I really have to finish these essays,
or else my girlfriend over there
is gonna lock me in the stocks.
It's true, Jug has a lot of work to do,
but I think you can take
a little time out for this.
I mean, look, it's senior year,
and we promised we'll start
taking advantage of that.
Agreed.
-Does this band have a name?
-Mmm.
It's The Archies.
What, was the "Me, Me, Me's" taken?
-Look, we can change the name.
-[Veronica] No.
"The Archies."
-I like it.
-[feedback over PA]
[Kevin over PA] What's up, Riverdale?
Are you trying to tear me down?
That's-- Wait. That's not...?
Well, sorry,
I'm the new Berlin Wall, baby.
Now get your asses to the music room!
["Tear Me Down" playing]
♪ I was born on the other side
Of a town ripped in two ♪
♪ I made it over the great divide ♪
♪ Now I'm coming for you ♪
[cheering]
♪ Enemies and adversaries ♪
♪ They try and tear me down ♪
♪ You want me, baby, I dare you ♪
♪ Try and tear me down ♪
[cheering continues]
♪ There ain't much of a difference ♪
♪ Between a bridge and a wall ♪
♪ Without me right in the middle, babe ♪
♪ Whoa, you would be nothing at all! ♪
♪ Enemies and adversaries ♪
♪ They try and tear me down ♪
♪ You want me, baby, I dare you ♪
♪ Try and tear me down ♪
♪ From East Berlin to Junction City ♪
♪ Hello, Mr. Honey ♪
♪ Hello, Riverdale ♪
♪ You wanna try and tear me down? ♪
You're done, Mr. Keller!
You're off the variety show.
♪ Come on and tear ♪
[crowd cheering]
♪ Come on and tear me down ♪
[feedback squeals]
I said, you're done! You hear me?
You're done!
[Betty] Okay, I'm gonna try it.
[all whooping]
Okay, can we please order pizza
from Little Cicero's?
-Ugh.
-Guys,
it is not a sleepover
without greasy pizza. Right, Kev?
Kev?
Sorry, it's just--
Working on the variety show
made me feel like
I was reconnecting
with the old, pre-Farm Kevin.
Mr. Honey didn't just take that away.
He made me feel like I was nothing.
Like I didn't matter.
[sighs]
You know,
something that makes me feel better...
["Wig in a Box" playing]
♪ On nights ♪
♪ Like this ♪
♪ When the world's a bit amiss ♪
♪ And the lights go down ♪
♪ Across the trailer park ♪
♪ I put on some makeup ♪
♪ Turn on the tape deck ♪
♪ And put the wig back on my head ♪
Ooh.
♪ Suddenly, I'm Miss Midwest
Midnight Checkout Queen ♪
♪ Until I head home
And I put myself to bed ♪
I hear what you're saying, Betty,
but I'm not sure
even a makeover montage will help.
♪ I look back on where I'm from ♪
♪ Look at the woman I've become ♪
♪ And the strangest things
Seem suddenly routine ♪
♪ I look up from my vermouth
On the rocks ♪
♪ A gift-wrapped wig still in the box ♪
♪ Of towering velveteen ♪
♪ I put on some makeup ♪
♪ Some LaVern Baker ♪
♪ And pull the wig down from the shelf ♪
♪ Suddenly, I'm Miss Beehive, 1963 ♪
♪ Until I wake up
And I turn back to myself ♪
♪ Some girls they have natural ease ♪
♪ They wear it any way they please ♪
♪ With their French flip curls
And perfumed magazines ♪
♪ Wear it up ♪
♪ Let it down ♪
♪ This is the best way that I've found ♪
♪ To be the best you've ever seen ♪
♪ I put on some makeup, oh ♪
♪ Turn on the eight-track
Ah, ah, ah, oh ♪
♪ I'm pulling the wig
Down from the shelf ♪
♪ Suddenly
I'm Miss Farrah Fawcett from TV ♪
♪ Until I wake up
And I turn back to myself ♪
♪ Shag, bi-level, bob
Dorothy Hamill do ♪
♪ Sausage curls, chicken wings
It's all because of you ♪
♪ It's all because of you
♪ Ooh ♪
Oh, my... [sighs]
-Hey, Kev.
-Yeah?
What if, for the variety show,
we all performed songs from Hedwig?
[Veronica] Yeah.
As a sign of solidarity.
And as president of the Student Body
and Riverdale High's LGBTQIA Alliance,
I promise you, I will sit down
with Principal Humbug and make this right.
[over jukebox]
♪ Love we, we shared ♪
♪ Our love ♪
On behalf of Kevin Keller
and the entire student body,
we urge you to hear our plea.
Hedwig is not some fringe,
downbeat musical.
It's fun.
It's an old-fashioned, red-blooded,
American musical comedy
with something for everyone.
Including those of us
who are more straight-laced.
Allow us to demonstrate.
["Sugar Daddy" playing]
♪ I've got a sweet tooth
For licorice drops and jelly roll ♪
♪ Hey, Sugar Daddy ♪
♪ Cheryl needs some sugar in her bowl ♪
♪ I'll lay out fine china on the linen
Polish up the chrome ♪
♪ If you've got some sugar for me
Sugar Daddy, bring it home ♪
♪ Black strap molasses
You're my cherry blossom, honey bear ♪
♪ Sugar Daddy, Sugar Daddy ♪
♪ Bring me Versace blue jeans
Black designer underwear ♪
♪ Sugar Daddy, Sugar Daddy ♪
♪ We'll dress up like the disco-dancing
Jet set in Milan and Rome ♪
♪ If you've got some sugar for me
Sugar Daddy, bring it home ♪
That's enough, Miss Blossom.
♪ Oh, the thrill of control ♪
♪ Like a Blitzkrieg on the roll ♪
-♪ It's the sweetest taste I've known ♪
-♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ So, if you've got some sugar
Bring it home ♪
♪ Oh, yeah
Come on, Sugar Daddy, bring it home ♪
What? No applause?
You just proved my point.
Did you even listen
to the lyrics you sang?
Hedwig and the Angry Inch
is highly sexualized.
[scoffs] How queer-phobic of you.
And if every student at Riverdale High
changed their variety show act
to a number from Hedwig,
what would you do then?
Hm. Well, Miss Topaz...
I would make the following announcement.
Any student who performs
a song from Hedwig
will be barred from senior prom.
Now...
as you like to say, Miss Blossom...
toodles.
[cell phone buzzing]
[Archie] So, what happened exactly?
Daddy's downplaying it.
He says he missed a step and stumbled,
but it's still scary and confusing.
He's been going to the doctor.
He just told us he was getting better.
Ronnie, I don't want you to worry...
but your dad's been
working out at the gym.
Okay.
Well, he was bench-pressing,
and the bar slipped.
Luckily, I was there to catch it, but...
I don't think he's been going
to the doctor as regularly as he says.
And you haven't told me this before, why?
He said it was nothing.
And when Hiram Lodge asks you to shut
your mouth and mind your own business,
-you mind your own business.
-No, no!
You drag him to the car,
and you drive him to the doctor yourself.
-That wasn't an option, Ronnie.
-So, you do nothing instead?
This is my life, Archie. My father's life.
How could you be so short-sighted?
[VCR whirring]
[Betty] Jughead!
I came to surprise you with a study break.
-Tell me this is not what it looks like.
-It's not.
Oh, so you're not lying to me
about doing your homework
while you try to crack
some new unsolvable mystery?
I'm doing both.
I went to the mat for you with Mr. Honey
and with all of your teachers.
-I didn't ask you to do that.
-I'm trying to make sure you graduate.
Jug, I'm trying to make sure
we stay together, that we have a future.
I'm sorry, in what future
are we not together?
I'm going to New Haven
in a few months, Jug.
That is happening.
Where are you going to be?
I thought I'd be your dorm-husband,
just eating pizza
while you studied criminal psych.
Yeah, well, I would rather that
than this dead-end Jughead.
Oh, the Jughead that was brained
with a rock?
I'm sorry I'm different now.
I guess death just changes a person.
["Exquisite Corpse" playing]
♪ Inside I'm hollowed out
Outside's a paper shroud ♪
♪ And all the rest's illusion ♪
♪ That there's a will and soul
That we can wrest control ♪
♪ From chaos and confusion ♪
♪ A collage! ♪
♪ I'm all sewn up ♪
♪ A montage! ♪
How do you think I feel?
♪ A random pattern
With a needle and thread ♪
♪ The overlapping way diseases
Are spread ♪
♪ Through a tornado body
With a hand grenade head ♪
♪ And the legs are two lovers entwined ♪
-I was trying to do the right thing.
-You weren't thinking.
Give me a break, Veronica.
It's been a crappy year.
♪ Oh, God, I'm all sewn up
A hardened razor-cut ♪
♪ Scar map across my body ♪
♪ And you can trace the lines
Through misery's design ♪
♪ That map across my body ♪
♪ A collage! ♪
♪ I'm all sewn up ♪
♪ A montage! ♪
♪ The automatist's undoing ♪
♪ The whole world starts unscrewing ♪
♪ As time collapses and space warps, oh ♪
♪ You see decay and ruin ♪
♪ I tell you, "No, no, no ♪
♪ You make such an exquisite corpse" ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ A collage! ♪
♪ I'm all sewn up ♪
♪ A montage! ♪
♪ I'm all sewn up! ♪
-[knock on door]
-Principal Honey,
I need to alert you to a situation
that's taking place in the hallway.
And the games begin.
Consider this a peaceful protest,
Mr. Honey.
Though I will weaponize
these babies if I have to.
Clearly, you are all...
very passionate about what you're feeling.
But hot heads lead to unpredictability.
And anger.
Violence.
So, I'm afraid...
the most prudent action to take
at this moment is to...
cancel the variety show.
[students groaning]
Hi, sorry I'm late.
Betty?
I forgot to text you guys
that rehearsal is canceled.
Oh.
I kind of screwed up with Veronica.
Well, Jughead and I just got
in a fight, too, actually, so...
Yeah, man, I'm sorry.
This is not what I wanted this week to be.
I wanted us to have fun.
When was the last time that happened?
That time we ordered sea monkeys
from the back of a comic book was fun.
[both laugh]
-Yeah, we peaked in the first grade.
-Yeah.
When I saw that sign-up sheet...
I flashed back to sophomore year.
I was on stage,
freezing up from stage fright.
Until I saw my dad.
And suddenly, I could just... play.
He gave me the biggest hug afterwards.
He was so proud of you.
He was always so happy
whenever you played.
Look, just because Veronica
and Jughead aren't here
doesn't mean we can't rehearse.
All right.
["Origin of Love" playing]
♪ When the earth was still flat
And clouds made of fire ♪
♪ And mountains stretched up to the sky
Sometimes higher ♪
♪ Folks roamed the earth
Like big rolling kegs ♪
♪ They had two sets of arms
They had two sets of legs ♪
♪ They had two faces peering
Out of one giant head ♪
♪ So they could watch all around them
As they talked, while they read ♪
♪ And they never knew nothing of love ♪
♪ It was before, mm ♪
♪ The origin of love ♪
-♪The origin of love ♪
-♪ The origin of love ♪
♪ The last time I saw you
We just split in two ♪
♪ You were looking at me
I was looking at you ♪
♪ You had a way so familiar
I could not recognize ♪
♪ 'Cause you had blood on your face
And I had blood in my eyes ♪
♪ And the children of the moon
Look like a fork stuck on a spoon ♪
♪ They were part sun, part earth
Part daughter, part son ♪
♪ Oh, the origin of love ♪
♪ Now the gods grew quite scared
Of our strength and defiance ♪
♪ And Thor said, "I'm gonna kill them all
With my hammer ♪
♪ Like I killed the giants" ♪
♪ And then he grabbed up some bolts
He let out a laugh ♪
♪ Said, "I'll split them
Right down the middle ♪
♪ Gonna cut them right up in half" ♪
♪ And then storm clouds gathered above
Into great balls of fire ♪
♪ And then fire shot down
From the sky in bolts ♪
♪ Like shining blades of a knife ♪
♪ And it ripped right through the flesh ♪
♪ Of the children of the sun
And the moon and the earth ♪
♪ And Osiris and the gods of the Nile ♪
♪ Gathered up a big storm ♪
♪ To blow a hurricane ♪
♪ To scatter us away
In a flood of wind and rain ♪
♪ A sea of tidal waves
To wash us all away ♪
♪ And if we don't behave
They'll cut us down again ♪
Hi.
One fully-researched, thoroughly-proofed,
MLA-formatted essay
on the Salem witch trials.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
I do.
I'm sorry.
Jug...
it's okay.
No, it's not.
I shouldn't have been as ticked off
as I was that you had faith in me.
-You okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
I really need to finish that essay
on Call of the Wild.
But you can distract me anytime you want.
-Bye.
Penny for your thoughts, handsome?
Ronnie...
I wanted to give you this, Archie.
It was too short notice to get cupcakes
from Magnolia, so these are from Pop's...
but you deserve an official
Veronica Lodge "I'm sorry."
You're sorry?
I am.
I was... scared...
and lashing out, but at the wrong person.
The truth is, you didn't need
to come clean to me, but you did.
Thanks to that, I got a doctor who said
it was lucky he saw Daddy when he did.
Because it could've been
much worse than a fall.
-So, thank you... Archiekins.
-Veronica, I--
So, more good news.
Though Honey canceled
the variety show at school,
Kevin called me with an amazing idea.
To host it at La Bonne Nuit.
So, me, you, Betty and Jughead will
all get to perform together, after all.
-Isn't that amazing?
-Yeah, that's awesome.
The show must go on, as they say.
Even in our wicked little town.
["Wicked Little Town (Reprise)" playing]
♪ Forgive me for I did not know ♪
♪ 'Cause I was just a boy ♪
♪ And you were so much more ♪
♪ And when everything
Starts breaking down ♪
♪ You take the pieces off the ground ♪
♪ And show this wicked town
Something beautiful and new ♪
♪ And there's no mystical design ♪
♪ No cosmic lover pre-assigned ♪
♪ There's nothing you can find ♪
♪ That cannot be found ♪
♪ 'Cause with all the changes
We've been through ♪
♪ It seems the stranger's always you ♪
♪ Alone again in some new
Wicked little town ♪
♪ When you've got no other choice ♪
♪ You know you can follow my voice ♪
♪ Through the dark turns and noise
Of this wicked little town ♪
♪ Oh, it's a wicked ♪
♪ Little town ♪
♪ Goodbye, wicked ♪
-♪ Little town ♪
[applause]
[feedback squeals]
Ladies and gentlemen,
for our final performance of the evening,
I am beyond honored to introduce,
for the first time ever,
The Archies!
[cheers and applause]
[FP] Get him, boy!
[whoops]
["Midnight Radio" playing]
♪ Rain falls hard ♪
♪ Burns dry ♪
♪ A dream or a song ♪
♪ That hits you so hard ♪
♪ It's filling you up ♪
♪ And suddenly you're gone ♪
♪ Breathe, feel, love ♪
♪ Give free ♪
♪ Know in your soul ♪
♪ Like your blood knows the way ♪
♪ From your heart to your brain ♪
♪ Know that you're whole ♪
♪ And you're shining
Like the brightest star ♪
♪ A transmission
On the midnight radio ♪
♪ Here's to Ronnie ♪
♪ And Archie ♪
♪ And Betty ♪
♪ And Jughead ♪
-♪ And Choni ♪
[Archie and Jughead] ♪ And Reggie ♪
Yeah!
♪ And me ♪
♪ And all the strange rock 'n' rollers ♪
♪ You know you're doing all right ♪
♪ So, hold on to each other ♪
♪ You gotta hold on tonight ♪
♪ And you're shining
Like the brightest star ♪
♪ A transmission
On the midnight radio ♪
♪ And you're spinning
Your new 45's ♪
♪ With all the misfits and the losers ♪
♪ Well, you know you're rock 'n' rollers ♪
♪ Spinning to ♪
♪ Your rock 'n' roll ♪
[crowd cheering]
♪ Lift up your hands ♪
♪ Lift up your hands... ♪
[Jughead] There's a problem that comes
once you get caught up on your homework.
Your mind wanders and evil creeps back in.
Was the voyeur somewhere
amongst us in the crowd?
Playing his long game?
Turning the temperature up
ever so slowly...
so that by the time we frogs realized
we were being boiled alive,
it was too late.
[panting over TV]
♪ Lift up your hands ♪
[cheering]