[Jughead] Winter had come to Riverdale,
and everyone was suffering
from an acute case of Quiz Show fever.
No one more so than Betty Cooper,
who was pouring her considerable energies
into beating the tar
out of Stonewall Prep's team,
led by-- Wouldn't you know it?
--Bret Weston Wallis.
The only person immune to Quiz Show fever?
My pal Archie Andrews,
who was feeling a lot less lonely
these days.
Hey, Archie.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm great, Uncle Frank.
Not me.
First day as foreman.
Man, I'm more nervous
than when I started basic training.
Nah, you're gonna do awesome.
In fact, I got something for you.
It's Fred's tool belt.
Hey, I can't take another man's gear,
especially not my brother's.
Well, you're not taking it,
you're borrowing it.
He'd want you to.
So do I.
Thanks, Archie.
For everything.
♪ You've got to do it slow
All night ♪
♪ Come try
The night ♪
♪ Baby, don't you know? ♪
Thank God for Bret's morning workouts.
Jug, do not mention him right now, okay?
And ruin this moment.
I just love getting you all wound up.
-Why are you smiling?
-Just everything.
You're here, I've turned in my draft
for Baxter Brothers book.
And Yale said--
Yale said what?
[Jughead sighs]
Did you get accepted into Yale
and not tell me?
Yeah, I think I did.
Wow.
Are you okay?
Yeah, no. I'm just-- I'm just processing.
But I'm happy for you, Jug.
-I'm happy for you. I'm proud of you.
-Really?
Yes.
Let me show you how much.
♪ You've got to do it slow
All night ♪
Oh, you two are finally done.
I thought I'd be late for class.
Oh, I guess I'll see you
at New Haven next year.
Of course, you'll just be a visitor.
You got into Yale?
Yeah, don't look so surprised.
And don't worry, Betty, I will try to keep
the coeds away from Forsythe. No promises.
But I do promise to crush you
in the Quiz Show finals.
If Riverdale makes it that far.
Dr. Beaker, as our chemistry teacher,
we're hoping you have the skill set
to help us with something
of a personal nature.
Are you a rum drinker, Dr. Beaker?
Not during school hours...
and never with students.
Ugh. Calm down, Dr. Egghead.
We're simply asking you to analyze
our maple-based concoction
to ensure that our recipe
is different enough from Lodge Rum.
That way, we can't be sued
or ceased-and-desisted by my father.
So, I ask you again, Dr. Beaker...
are you a rum drinker?
The board that runs
the Baxter Brothers has taken a look
at the first draft of your book,
and they have a few thoughts.
Well, one more global thought.
They would like a new mystery.
New mystery? Like, the whole book?
They think the boy-in-the-river story line
is a bit soft.
They're looking for something darker.
They mentioned something about, say, um,
serial killers being
a potential fertile ground to explore.
Okay, um... I'll just have
to think about it.
Well, think fast
and have some pitches prepared.
The Brotherhood is coming here
to meet with you.
[Jughead] So, I need
some serial-killer advice.
My publishers want a dark and edgy villain
for the book, Charles.
I have to come up with pitches
in the vein of Zodiac or Hannibal Lecter.
-I figured you would have some ideas.
-Yeah, sure. No problem.
But don't you have firsthand experience
with an infamous serial killer?
You mean the Black Hood?
No, I couldn't do that to Betty.
Fair enough.
I've got boxes full of killers,
so I'll pick out
my ten most gruesome ones for you.
Thank you, Chuck. I owe you.
[Frank] I know you all worked hard
for my brother.
Rest assured, as the new foreman,
I plan on busting my ass
the same as you do.
And I specifically want
to thank Tom Keller
for filling in
during these difficult times.
-All right, cool, guys, let's get to work.
-Okay, guys, let's go!
Arch, I would've appreciated a heads-up
that I was being replaced.
I know, Mr. Keller, I'm sorry.
It happened fast.
But Frank has a ton of experience
and I think the crew's gonna love him.
I gotta be honest with you, Arch.
I don't know about your uncle.
He's been trouble
since the day he was born.
I must have arrested him
half a dozen times when I was sheriff.
That was then.
My dad believed in second chances.
So do I.
[game show music playing]
Welcome back
to the regional RIVW Quiz Show semifinals.
Seaside High trails Riverdale 210 to 240.
And now for the final round.
Which Venetian island has been famous
for glassmaking since the 13th century?
Murano.
-Correct.
-Never go in August. So many mosquitos.
What is the length of the diagonal
if the side of the square is ten?
Ten square root of two.
-Correct.
-My brilliant little savant.
Which of the following is the powerhouse
of the cell?
-Mitochondria.
-Correct.
Which American architect's house
in Southwest Pennsylvania--?
-Frank Lloyd Wright.
-Correct!
Who also designed Thornhill. I knew that.
[bell dinging]
Well, time's up. Riverdale has won.
They will go on to face Stonewall Prep
in the finals.
Hey, Betty. You did great out there.
Great might not be enough to beat him.
Ah. That's Bret, huh?
Bret Weston Wallis clearly came here
to throw me off my game.
Is there any way
you could help me with him?
As long as it doesn't
involve shallow graves and lye.
No. I just wanna make him sweat.
He's the son of a diplomat,
brags about being untouchable.
But what skeletons are buried
in his closet?
Any intel you could find
that would help me mess with his mind
would be... much appreciated.
Is it because he got into Yale
and you didn't?
Alice told me.
Charles, I worked my ass off
for four years.
I put in extra time at the Blue and Gold,
I maintained a 4.1 GPA,
and I still didn't get in.
Not knowing why is driving me crazy.
My former mentor at the FBI,
he teaches criminal law at Yale.
I'll see if I can get you some answers...
about Yale...
and Bret.
Thank you.
[Jughead] So, anyway, the Baxter Brothers
are trying to catch this serial killer
named the Fishmonger.
Who gets his name
because he guts his victims--
The idea of a serial killer is intriguing,
but what we've heard so far feels a bit...
forced.
Okay.
What about a serial killer
that uses social media
in order to stalk his prey?
Forsythe's best work stems
from his personal experiences.
Might I suggest you start there.
What about a dark and ominous force
that threatens the town of Seaport?
An obsessed killer who is looking
to expose the hypocrisy
and sins of his neighbors?
The Baxter Brothers discover
that the man unleashing his righteous rage
is the father
of Bobby Baxter's girlfriend, Tracy True.
This sounds promising.
What's the name of the killer?
Uh, the Brown Hood.
If you give me a little more time,
I can come up
-with another--
-No. We like this.
You ask me,
this sounds like a million-dollar idea.
-Hey.
Just drove by the site.
Where are the guys?
Oh, Frank called it a day
and decided to invite everybody
back to your place for beers
and tall tales.
You didn't wanna go?
Somebody's gotta balance the books here.
They're a bit of a mess.
How so?
For starters, nobody received
their Christmas bonuses.
Your dad never missed a year.
We'll bounce back, Mr. Keller,
we just need more time.
You gotta remember, at this point,
Fred is three sheets to the wind, okay?
And he somehow convinced himself
that stealing Seaside's mascot
would give Riverdale the edge
in the playoff game, okay?
So, he climbs over this big fence, right?
And he goes to grab Peter the Pig
out of his pen, and get this:
He can't climb back out.
-[men laughing]
-He is absolutely trapped.
So, the next morning, security shows up,
and there's Fred,
all curled up in the mud,
holding on to the squealing hog.
And without missing a beat,
my brother says:
"I got the bacon, you got the eggs?"
[all laughing]
Your old man sure knew how to pick a crew.
Reminds me of the guys I served with.
Mr. Keller says the guys were upset
they didn't get their bonuses this year.
You are so much like your dad,
always worried about other people.
Relax. We got this.
For you.
Mija, how very generous.
But do I need to remind you that I own
the patent on this rum?
Correction, Daddy. You own the patent
on sad, tired molasses-based rum.
Ours is maple-based.
And in a preemptive move to rum-block you,
we had a scientist analyze it.
According to him, by making
the main ingredient maple syrup,
our rum's DNA has changed by 51 percent.
[Veronica] Which means, legally,
you can't sue or stop us.
And should you be inspired to create
your own version of our invention,
consider yourself forewarned
because we control the patent
on maple rum.
So, toodles.
In other words, Daddy,
our rum war... is back on.
Your instincts were right again, Betty.
As requested, I did some digging on Bret.
[Betty] And what'd you find?
-Betty. What's up?
-I am so on to you, Bret.
God, you just think you're so untouchable
and that everyone is beneath you.
But the truth is,
you are a filthy cheater.
Whoa, Betty. Hang on for a minute.
What's going on?
Your roommate's father paid someone
to take the PSATs for him.
Oh, but don't worry,
his father covered it all up
and then bought his way into Stonewall,
as I'm sure he did with Yale as well.
Because the truth is, you haven't earned
a single thing in your life, Bret.
You're just a pathetic rich kid.
Why are you making me out
to be the villain here?
It's not like I'm
the one writing YA fiction
based off the exploits
of your deranged father.
Is that what your novel is about?
Betty, wait. Betty!
[Veronica] Cheryl, I've been musing.
We now have a truly enviable product.
But we still need to get the word out
to potential customers, so...
what if we make La Bonne Nuit
our base of operations?
Query. Didn't your daddykins revoke
this place's liquor license?
We wouldn't sell rum.
We would hand out free samples.
And instead of being a speakeasy,
we'd reopen La Bonne Nuit as a dance club.
Interesting.
Sweaty people equals thirsty people
equals people desperate
for overpriced mocktails.
Meanwhile, we covertly hand out samples
of our delicious homemade rum.
Our coat-check girl could take down
the names
and orders of potential customers,
and the legitimate money
we bring in at the club
could help fund our shadow operation.
-[door opens]
-[bell jingles]
[oldies music playing over speakers]
[Fangs] Kevin.
Now's not a good time, Fangs.
I'm waiting for my Grind'Em date.
I'm not stalking you,
I'm just picking up a couple burgers.
But I want to apologize...
for what I did to you.
-I was under Edgar's control--
-Thanks, I get it.
I was brainwashed by Edgar, too,
but that doesn't mean
we should get back together.
Can we just go on a date
and see what happens?
[bell jingles]
Sorry. My date just got here.
Hi, are you Terry? I'm Kevin.
Nice to meet you.
Listen, do you wanna get out of here?
I have a room at the Five Seasons.
Unless that's too forward.
No. Not at all.
♪ Why do you hurt ♪
♪ Me so? ♪
[bell jingles]
[Betty] Tell me Bret is lying.
Tell me that you didn't exploit
my family tragedy
for a Baxter Brothers novel.
Betty, it was a Hail Mary.
I had to give
the Baxter Brotherhood something.
I was never gonna go through with it
without asking you first
and I didn't ask you
because I wasn't even going to do it.
If you wanna use my life,
you wanna write about the Black Hood,
have the guts to ask me.
-Don't lie to my face.
-I wasn't lying.
No, you were just omitting the truth,
which is exactly what you did
about the Quill and Skull,
and about getting accepted into Yale.
I told you about Yale. I just had
to figure out the best time to do so.
Oh, and the best time to do so
is right after we had sex?
There isn't a handbook
on how to tell your girlfriend
you got accepted to her dream school.
Yeah, especially not when the only reason
you got accepted to Yale
is because of this stupid school.
[scoffs]
Oh, is that what you think?
That I don't deserve to go to Yale?
[door closes]
-Thank you.
-[Archie] That was good though.
Good news. I just got off the phone
with the mayor's office,
and we've been hired to repair
the drainage system in the prison.
Yep. Government job, real money.
We can't do that, Mr. Keller.
We can't do business with Hiram Lodge.
That prison represents everything wrong
and corrupt about this town.
We'd be taking blood money.
My dad wouldn't do it, I won't either.
Archie, we can't just do business
with the people we like.
-Kid made his decision, Tom.
-I think he's made the wrong decision.
I don't know
if he should be getting advice from you.
Yeah, well, I'm family,
so I got more a say in this than you do.
[Archie] I've made up my mind.
We'll figure out another way
and don't tell the crew about this.
Their morale is low enough as it is.
Let's keep it between us.
Okay.
[door closes]
Hey, Betty. Do you have a minute?
I just heard from my mentor at Yale.
Yeah.
What was it? My grades? My essay? What?
Just... rip the Band-Aid off, Charles.
It wasn't any of that.
It was that they didn't want to accept
the daughter of the Black Hood.
They were afraid
that if your father's identity got out,
it would generate bad press,
problems with other students.
I'm sorry.
What the hell is wrong with you, Bret?
Why would you tell Betty that?
How did you even know?
DuPont mentioned something.
You were supposed to be watching my back,
not stabbing it.
Wait, look.
I didn't do this to hurt you, Jones.
I did it to get under Betty's skin
before the Quiz Show finals.
So, you threw a live grenade
into my relationship
so you could win a trivia contest?
Of course. This is what it means
to be a Quill and Skull.
To win at any cost.
Always.
You'll never be satisfied, will you, Dad?
It wasn't enough that you had to ruin
my past and my present...
but you had to destroy my future, too.
Even rotting in the ground,
you still find ways to torture me.
Not anymore.
I'm done.
I hate you!
[Alice] Betty! Betty! Betty!
Honey. It's okay, honey.
-It's okay. It's okay.
-[sobbing]
I'm so sorry, honey.
It's okay.
Charles told me everything.
I'm sorry.
[indistinct chatter]
There he is! Big Red.
-Come join us.
-One second. I'm just grabbing a soda.
[Frank] Ah, where was I? Oh, right.
[Frank speaking indistinctly]
[country music playing over speakers]
Hey, Carlos, you want a beer?
I'm good.
Um...
Listen, Archie, I heard we turned down
a government contract. Is that true?
-Where'd you hear that?
-From a buddy who's working the gig.
Look, Carlos,
that's not the kind of job we take.
Some of the guys are pretty pissed
about it.
There's a lot of tension on the site.
Something doesn't change soon,
your crew's gonna quit.
And some advice.
You should spend a little more time
with your boots on the ground.
At the site with us.
Okay?
[Kevin giggling]
Okay, okay.
What is with the tickling?
Have you ever videotaped yourself?
-Once. It didn't go well.
-No.
Videotaped yourself getting tickled?
Why does every date I go on have
to get super weird?
It's just tickling. No sex.
You don't even have
to take off your shirt.
I direct you and another hot guy.
It's fun.
-And it pays.
-How much?
-Five grand a video.
-[chuckles]
Um...
So, it's with another guy, not you.
I just work the camera.
But I have someone
who'd be really into you.
A total beefcake.
What do you say?
Sure.
Cool.
I'll text my guy.
He's waiting down at the bar.
[knocking]
You didn't have to come.
Yes, I did.
Especially after what your mom
told me downstairs.
You okay?
I mean, I fully spiraled in a cemetery.
No.
You had a human reaction to a situation
that was totally out of your control.
I'm sorry that I wasn't there for you
when you needed me.
I love you.
I really hate when we fight.
You deserve Yale, Jug.
And I'm...
so happy for you.
It's just hard for me to untangle that
from how sad I am that I won't be going.
It's not fair.
But I've been thinking.
Stonewall got me into Yale,
but what if I could pay it forward?
Helping you in.
-You mean, the Quiz Show?
-No.
You've got that in the bag.
I'm talking about the other bigger game
that we're playing.
♪ Every day we levitate ♪
[dance music playing]
[over speakers] ♪ Always doing better
Even under pressure ♪
♪ Higher than a satellite ♪
♪ Never gonna come down
Never gonna turn 'round ♪
♪ Us against the world for life ♪
♪ We love, we love, we love
Like nobody does ♪
♪ For life ♪
♪ We love, we love ♪
Cheryl, we're a hit.
As is our maple concoction.
But did you expect anything less?
And we already have a long list
of interested buyers.
Let's keep those free shots flowing.
[music stops]
[man] Sheriff's department!
What the hell is this?
Haven't you been through enough
of them to know? It's a raid.
For some trumped-up reason, no doubt.
You may be mayor, but you can't just barge
in here like you own the place.
Well, this warrant says otherwise.
It has been brought to my attention
that there's alcohol being sold
on the premises.
False. We aren't selling anything.
You don't think I know
what game you girls are playing?
Ladies, I'm the grandmaster.
And when you play against me...
you'll lose...
every single time.
[snaps fingers]
[gasping]
[crowd jeering]
♪ I can't wait for the daybreak ♪
Are you sure he understands
what kind of video we're making?
That it's just tickling?
Relax.
Daryl's one of my top earners.
And subscribers love it
when opposites pair up. Trust me.
I've done hundreds of these.
Did you say hundreds?
What kind of operation are you running?
Play your cards right, stud,
and you'll find out.
[knuckles cracking]
[Cheryl] Fear not.
We have a new batch brewing
at Thistlehouse,
even as we lick our wounds.
And to what end?
To become floor polish like that batch?
I know my father, he'll just keep
raiding this place until we cry tío.
Yes.
He will raid this place.
Why are you saying it
like it's a good thing?
Because I've just had one
of my hellaciously simple
yet brilliant ideas.
What if we keep this location open
as a nightclub as a distraction?
Get him to focus on La Bonne Nuit
while we relocate
our rum business elsewhere.
Do you happen to have one
of these magical realms
-tucked away in your back pocket?
-Back pocket?
More like top floor.
You're a natural, Kev.
You have a great laugh.
Terrific timbre.
Great.
You could make a lot more,
if and when you build a following.
Terry, this is a onetime thing.
That's a shame.
You could make some serious bank.
All right, let me ask you:
-Would I always have to work with Daryl?
-Daryl's popular.
But no. Why?
Did you have someone else in mind?
[Veronica] Cheryl, what is this place?
Mumzie's old brothel, the Maple Club.
The most exclusive gentlemen's club
in town just sitting here.
Okay, but is a former cathouse
really on-brand
for our female empowerment start-up?
Mummy Dreadful was certainly no ally
to the cause,
but that doesn't mean we can't use
this place for our own purposes.
Not only is its rent prepaid
for the rest of the year,
but it is and has everything we need.
Private drinking club, check.
Premium security system, check.
List of Riverdale's richest rubes?
Check.
Look at all the names in here.
Cheryl, do you realize what this is?
Clients with the means to pay
at the price point we require?
Exactly.
So, let's tap those scumbags
like maple trees
and start making some real money.
As a valued long-term client,
we wanted you to be the first to know
that the Maple Club is reopening.
No, we are no longer a bordello.
Think of it more as a social club.
Offering exclusivity, discretion...
And high-end maple-centric liquor.
A brand so rare, it can only be purchased
on the premises.
Yes, I had a feeling
that might be of interest to you.
Of course.
[both] You'll be put at the top
of the list.
Between senior year
and operating La Bonne Nuit as a cover,
we're taking on quite the load.
What we need is
a full-time live-in manager.
Someone who will be beholden to us.
Who will live, eat and sleep here
to ensure things run smoothly.
I have the perfect candidate.
[Veronica] You've gotta be kidding me.
Cheryl, she's a killer.
So is Betty's father. So is your father.
[Veronica] True.
Why have you come for me, nightmare child?
To offer you a change of venue, Mumzie.
And a way for you to work off your debt
to society... and to me.
As long as you're willing to play
by our tightly coiled rules.
I knew it was gonna happen, I just didn't
think it was gonna happen this quick.
What's the problem, Mr. Keller?
Two hundred bucks missing from petty cash.
You know anything about that, Frank?
Yeah. I borrowed it against my salary.
You mean you stole it.
Can't steal something
when your family name's on the shingle.
Your brother put up that sign, Frank.
It had nothing to do with you.
Archie, I've done my best to help you,
but if you're gonna stand beside a piece
of garbage like this, we're finished.
Uncle Frank!
Mr. Keller!
That's it! I'm done.
I quit.
Any of you wanna work a job
where you actually get paid,
you know where to find me.
Just gonna keep giving me
the silent treatment?
I stuck my neck out for you, Frank.
How the hell could you steal?
I didn't steal it.
I borrowed it against my future salary.
-Why didn't you just come to me?
-Because you're my nephew!
I'm a 40-year-old man, Archie.
I did eight years in the military,
seven of that in combat.
How the hell do you think it makes me feel
to have to ask a teenager for a loan?
What did you even need it for?
I got a hot tip.
A sure thing at the track.
You're gambling with it?
I was trying to earn enough
to pay the guys their bonuses.
But go ahead and think the worst.
Everybody else does.
[door opens, then closes]
-[woman] We're on in five.
-[man 1] One, two. One, two.
[man 2] Lower that light!
-[man 3] Sound check, please.
-[man 2] Camera one, over here, please.
[speaking indistinctly]
[man 2] Can you stand still for a sec?
-[Jughead] Betty.
-[Betty] Yeah.
This is Mr. Brooks, the Yale recruiter
I was telling you about.
Recruiter. It's a pleasure
to meet you, sir.
The pleasure is mine.
Forsythe was insistent
I see you in action.
He's your biggest cheerleader.
And I'm his, too.
-Okay, break a leg out there.
-Okay, thanks.
[Betty] Nice to meet you.
[man] We'll be ready to start...
-Betty.
-Hey.
Jughead told me about the recruiter.
If you win out there,
you get another shot?
Yep, as if I wasn't already
stressed enough.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
I'm just really excited for you.
I left you a present in the green room.
Oh, my God, Mom. What did you do?
Well, hello, everyone,
and welcome to our RIVW's Quiz Show.
We have our returning champions
Stonewall Prep
facing first-time finalists
Riverdale High.
So, let's get quizzing.
What country has the longest coastline
in continental Europe?
-[buzzing]
-Norway.
-Correct.
-[buzzing]
-The Miracle of Dunkirk.
-Correct.
-[buzzing]
-Aft, bow, port, starboard.
Correct.
[buzzing]
If the limit never approaches anything,
the limit does not exist.
Correct. In his 1899 novella
The Jungle Book, what author--?
-Rudyard Kipling.
-Correct.
-Demand--
-Demand-side economics.
Why are we even here?
It's like she knows the answers
before the questions are even asked.
-[buzzing]
-Burgundy, France.
Ooh! Sorry, that's incorrect.
-[mouthing] I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
[host] To Stonewall.
-Côtes du Rhône.
-Sorry, that's also incorrect.
It's Bordeaux, you jack-hole.
-Actually, Bret, it's Alsace.
-The correct answer is Alsace.
Well, with a thrilling back and forth,
the score is still tied at 520.
[dramatic music plays over speakers]
Well, that sound can only mean one thing,
it is time for our final question.
It's all yours, B.
Destroy that pleated-khaki trash monster.
For the win.
In a manual transmission vehicle,
what mechanical device connects
two or more rotating shafts?
Spark plug.
That is incorrect.
[all sighing]
Riverdale, your chance to steal.
The clutch.
That is correct.
[bell dinging]
Riverdale has won.
-Riverdale are the winners.
-Oh, my God!
[host] There you have it, everyone.
Another fantastic Quiz Show.
Thanks for joining in.
[Alice] Say "Victory."
[all] Victory!
-[camera clicks]
-Okay, it's cute.
I'll take
Genius Girlfriends for 200, Alex.
I don't know what's better,
the win or the look on Bret's face.
We are gonna solve every mystery
in Connecticut,
-and we're gonna eat a lot of pizza.
-[Betty giggles]
[Alice] It looks perfect there.
And I'm so glad to see
that you're not beating yourself up.
You did what you had to do.
Yeah, not in the way that you think, Mom.
I didn't use the answers that you stole.
I tore those up and threw them away.
I wanted to beat Bret fair and square.
I take it the bet came in.
Yeah. Turned 200 into 10 grand.
It's enough to pay the bonuses.
We good now?
This is great, Uncle Frank.
But, no, we're not good.
When you took that money, it felt
like you were stealing from my dad.
I was just trying to help, Archie.
It's not what you did.
It's how you did it.
Andrews Construction isn't just
a business, it's my dad's legacy.
We treat it with honor, with respect.
This can't happen again.
You sound just like him.
And I understand.
[all chanting] Betty, Betty, Betty!
[whooping]
We did it, Mr. Honey. We won.
You did, Miss Cooper.
And, apparently,
how you did it is a grave problem.
I don't understand. What are you...?
This was found in the trash
inside your green room.
My office.
Now!
[door closes]
The school called.
I tried convincing Mr. Honey
that you had nothing to do with it,
that this was my doing to try to give you
an advantage to balance
-the damage your father has done.
-I know, Mom.
Why aren't you at work?
Apparently, somebody told
my station manager.
And I have been put on leave
without pay for who-knows-how-long.
I just don't understand.
How could anyone find out?
I mean, where's the evidence?
I was so careful.
Exhibit A.
Someone must have dug through my trash.
Probably Bret.
-But you didn't even use these answers.
-Doesn't matter. No one believes me.
I saw how hard you studied, Betty.
You earned that trophy.
Well, according to Mr. Honey,
Riverdale's victory has been tainted
by a cloud of scandal.
So, it's been overturned.
And Stonewall Prep wins again.
And I've been suspended
pending further investigation.
[school bell ringing]
Before I say what I'm about to say,
I wanna make one thing clear.
This is not about me wanting
to get back together. Understand?
I've heard better opening lines.
[Kevin] I have a proposal for you.
It's good money. On-camera work.
It's a little weird,
but will be infinitely less weird
if I do it with someone I know.
On camera.
-What are you talking about, Kevin?
-Just promise me you'll keep an open mind.
Okay? Stud.
Thanks for meeting me, Mr. Keller.
I wanted to make sure you got your bonus
and... to apologize.
I'm a grown man, Archie,
I can take care of myself.
Would you consider coming back
to Andrews Construction?
You know that I want to.
But if Frank's sticking around,
I just don't think that's a good idea.
What if I made you foreman?
Archie, you're a good kid.
You always have been.
But you trust too much.
I know who my Uncle Frank is, Mr. Keller.
Sure, he's a mixed bag.
I can't turn my back on family.
I understand that.
Good luck to you.
I just pray that Frank Andrews isn't
the end of your dad's company.
Thank you.
One maple rum punch and one maple-jito
-for Mr. Arklight and his guest.
-[woman] Thanks.
-How's the front of house going?
-Busy.
Word is spreading faster than a fire
at Thornhill.
-Hmm.
-[cell phone buzzing]
It's Pop Tate. Apparently,
La Bonne Nuit just got raided again.
Heavens, whatever will
your father find this time?
Let me think,
a club of sweaty, dancing teenagers
imbibing virgin coladas,
fizzy juice drinks
and coffee-infused colas.
To our two income streams
being up and running.
I'll drink to that.
[Penelope] Is this mask
absolutely necessary?
It's mandatory, Mother.
Unless you want someone
to find out your identity,
you'll keep that false face on and stay
within the walls of the Maple Club.
And if you get the itch to run...
That ankle monitor
and proximity sensor I put on you
will start screeching like a cat in heat,
Mrs. Blossom.
Take this as a win.
You're under house arrest,
minding our shop whilst we're in school.
But at least you're not in that petri dish
of a teen sex bunker.
[Penelope scoffs]
You're a pathological lunatic.
You know that, Bret?
-I know what you did to Betty.
-Easy, Forsythe.
From what I hear, she did it to herself.
You consider yourself
to be this elite man of honor,
but you are nothing more than a joke
and a coward.
When you say things like that, Forsythe,
it really upsets me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Have I besmirched your precious honor?
-You're damn right you have.
-Good.
Because as stated
by the Quill and Skull charter,
any dispute between two members
can be solved
according to the code
of the society of the founding fathers.
A duel.
-You can't be serious.
-Oh, I am as serious
as a shot to the heart.
Um...
Are you scared?
No. Amused... at the thought
of your pony-tailed girlfriend
-weeping over your dead body.
-That's not gonna happen.
So, sudden death? Yes or no?
[bell jingles]
-Hey.
-Hi.
I got here as soon as I could.
What's going on?
I just don't think
I can do this anymore, Arch.
I keep waiting for Jug to come back,
but he doesn't and he won't.
He won't ever come back.
[oldies music playing over speakers]
And I don't know how I'm supposed
to keep going.
Day by day, Betty.
We'll get through this, together.