[Jughead] "Honor,"
a word that gets thrown around a lot
at Stonewall Prep.
Mr. Weston Wallis, you have been
challenged to a duel by Mr. Jones,
who has invoked
arcane Stonewall Prep tradition.
Do you accept?
-That'd be a yes.
-Very good.
-What about fencing?
-Can we just bare-knuckle brawl?
May I suggest that you do both?
And in case of a tiebreaker...
A battle of intellect.
A chess match.
Excellent.
Then it is settled.
You may both now choose a second
for moral and tactical support.
I pick Jonathan.
I'll choose Donna.
And may the best man win.
I'm assuming you've never held
a saber before.
Lucky for you, I'm an excellent coach, and
Bret is decidedly mediocre with a sword.
Hey, by the way, I meant to ask you,
when's your mom get back?
She's wrapping up a case.
A couple more days, she says.
-Gotcha.
-[door closes]
Hey, can we help you?
Holy hell.
Ted Bishop.
How are you, Frank?
Hey.
-What the hell are you doing here?
-It's, uh--
It's bad news.
I'm making the rounds,
I wanted to tell you guys in person.
Greg died.
-Yeah, he had cancer.
-Ah.
Rotted his guts.
After everything else...
I'm sorry. Uh...
Archie, this is Ted Bishop.
We served together.
-Ted, this is my nephew Archie.
-Hey.
-Fred's kid. Nice to meet you.
-Same.
We were just calling it quits for the day,
if you wanna join us for dinner?
Yeah. How about it, Ted?
Yeah, all right.
FYI, Smithers and I are road-tripping
to New York tomorrow.
Oh, what's the occasion?
I have an interview at Barnard College,
if you must know.
And of course, I'll be going
on a shopping spree beforehand
to find the right outfit to impress.
Perfect timing. Your mother and I were
just planning our own trip to New York.
Seriously?
Yeah. I have a few business meetings
I've been putting off.
And I'm having lunch with the girls
at Café des Creatifs.
Don't worry, mija,
as soon as we reach Manhattan,
we'll go our separate ways.
Fine.
But New York... is my town.
Not yours.
[school bell rings]
Fangs, tell me
you're not selling drugs again.
Toni...
so Kevin and I started this little...
side hustle.
And don't worry,
it's nothing illegal per se.
What kind of side hustle?
It looks lucrative as hell.
Is this something I can get in on?
The nerve of that man!
Who does he think he is?
What happened, Mom?
What did Mr. Honey say?
Your principal refuses to believe
that I acted alone.
That's typical.
What's the punishment?
Well, honey, you're suspended for a week
and stripped of your editor-in-chief
duties at The Blue and Gold.
Oh, my God.
And barred from attending senior prom,
for some ungodly reason.
Oh, and that Bret Weston Wallis character?
He's filing a restraining order
against you,
claiming that he "fears for his life."
What, Bret is afraid of me? Why?
Apparently, you cracked open his head
with a golf club?
Oh, right, I did do that.
What's this?
My latest murder board.
[Alice] Who got murdered?
Mr. Chipping. Maybe.
We let the case get cold,
but we know Bret's a total sociopath.
Let's find out if he's a killer, too.
So, there was an ambush
near the city center,
and they sent us in
to extract any wounded.
I end up walking down a blind alley.
I get hit in both legs, and I go down.
But he got me out of there.
It wasn't till we got back
to the aid station, I saw that Frank,
he'd been hit four times himself.
But, hey, you got a Red Badge of Courage
for saving my ass, right?
I got lucky, that's all.
Well, boys, uh,
I appreciate the warm meal
and hospitality, but it's time I ship out.
You can stay here if you want, Mr. Bishop.
My mom's out of town,
there's plenty of room.
-As long as I'm not putting anyone out.
-No, you're not.
[Alice] My, what a tangled web.
And you think
this Bret character is behind it all?
He's definitely the leader of the pack.
Okay. Well, where do we begin?
We have missing students, evil preppies,
dead writers, a teacher's suicide--
Apparent suicide.
Chipping didn't leave a note.
And even though Jughead's classmate Donna
has painted
a very incriminating portrait of him...
I don't think she's telling the truth.
Well, then, that's where we start.
Tell me, Elizabeth,
is there a Mrs. Chipping?
Hey, where's the fire?
Sorry, I'm gonna be late for school.
Ted, don't be a stranger.
Hope to see you again soon.
-Yeah, same here.
-See you.
He's a good kid.
He is. He's just like his father was.
Listen, why don't you finish up and
then I'll drive you to the bus station?
Sounds good.
[cell phone buzzing]
-Hello?
-[on phone] Frank, it's June. Listen.
-June?
-I don't have a lot---
-Whoa, whoa, slow down. Slow down, wait.
-Duckie was murdered.
-He said something about...
-What happened to Duckie?
[June speaking indistinctly on phone]
I don't understand, how can he be dead,
too? That doesn't make any...
What the hell's going on?
I forgot my phone.
I'm sorry, Archie.
I usually have an instinct
about these things.
Uncle Frank, why the hell is one
of your friends trying to kill you?
After the war, I was hard up.
Ted reached out,
and he told me about this security gig.
It paid well, hired vets,
no questions asked.
The thing is,
it was a private paramilitary contractor,
and they sent us all over the world...
as mercenaries.
Okay, so why come after you?
My guess is,
the company's tying up loose ends.
Maybe they're about to be exposed,
Ted's still on the payroll.
So, get ahead of this.
You come forward
and blow the lid off these mercenaries.
It's not that easy, Archie.
I was a part of it.
I did things. I--
I followed orders.
-Then we need to get you out of town.
-No.
It's too dangerous.
Anybody he comes into contact with
in this town is at risk now.
He's not gonna leave till I'm dead.
-Well, in that case, we need backup.
-No way.
No. Uncle Frank, trust me,
this guy can help.
Thank you for coming to see us,
Mrs. Chipping.
We can't even imagine
how hard this has been for you.
And we promise, we're just here to help.
This first question is the hardest.
The answer is no.
I absolutely do not believe my husband
was having an affair with that student.
And Rupert, he had his problems,
but he never cheated on me, not ever.
What kind of problems?
Drinking more than usual,
complaining about
the Baxter Brothers books,
wishing he'd never gotten the contract.
Wasn't he proud to be
a Baxter Brothers writer?
In the beginning.
But then, as the years went on...
he felt like he had an albatross
around his neck.
But hadn't he just finished his last book?
Why... kill himself if he was so close
to being done?
I don't know.
I just-- I-- I don't know.
And I, um...
I brought a box of his personal effects
from when I cleaned out his office.
I can't make sense of any of it...
but maybe you can.
We'll try, Mrs. Chipping.
What does any of this mean?
Why does Mr. Chipping have Army pamphlets?
Unless...
Wait a minute.
A highly trained mercenary tried
to kill you two in the kitchen
and now he's in hiding,
waiting to strike again?
-Is that about right?
-I'm his target, not Archie.
I don't want anyone paying
for my mistakes.
I know what it's like
when the past comes knocking.
As a vet and as a Serpent,
I've been in a couple of bar fights
with these ultra-Marine types.
They're tough bastards,
but I've held my own against them.
Can you lure him out, Uncle Frank?
It would have to be somewhere
under our complete control.
We got that. The gym.
All right.
I'll get him there.
[DuPont] Your weapons, gentlemen.
First to three points wins.
Now...
en garde.
And begin.
Hit on Mr. Jones.
Point to Weston Wallis.
Begin.
[both grunting]
Point to Mr. Jones, one to one.
And begin.
Hit on Mr. Jones.
Point to Weston Wallis, two to one.
Begin.
The match is over.
Weston Wallis is our victor.
[students cheering]
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Katy Keene!
-Hi!
-So good to see you.
It has been way too long, girl.
I know something
that will make you even happier.
The new Proenza Schouler collection
on the fourth floor is to die for.
Can't wait. I need to ooze
collegiate cuteness at this interview.
Well, I've already scoped out
some Barnard-ready options.
Good thing I'm armed
with my mother's Lacy's card.
If that's the case,
I know exactly where to start. Come on!
♪ Got everybody talkin'
Oh, I got them watchin' ♪
♪ All eyes on me
No, I ain't even tryin' ♪
♪ I got the buzz, I got the buzz ♪
♪ Everybody's gonna know
Everybody's gonna see ♪
♪ Everywhere I turn, all eyes on me ♪
♪ Float like a butterfly
Sting like a bee ♪
♪ 'Cause everywhere I go, all eyes on me ♪
♪ I got the buzz, I got the buzz
I got the buzz ♪
♪ Buzz, buzz ♪
Oh, I don't want
this "Rainbow High" montage to end.
Who says it has to?
We can leave our bags with Smithers
and just keep going.
Wait, do you like drag?
My friend Jorge and I always sneak
into this dive bar called Molly's Crisis.
Sounds amazing.
[metal detector beeping]
I'm unarmed.
-I keep my word.
-Good.
We don't want any unnecessary bloodshed.
But just so you know, Ted,
the same way you came after me,
-they'll send someone after you.
-Probably.
But I don't get paid to think like that.
I get paid... to follow orders.
I'm sorry it's gotta end like this,
buddy...
but I'll make it painless.
None of your loved ones will be harmed.
-I swear.
-Ted...
I'm sorry, too, brother.
-[whistles]
-[doors opening]
You broke the code, Frank?
You can't break something
that's been shattered to bits,
-and you're the one coming after me.
-Hands up.
-On the ground. Hands up!
-You broke the code, Frank.
All bets are off now.
You're all fair game.
[handcuffs clicking]
Get some sleep.
At 0800, you got a date with the feds.
Hm.
What about Frank Andrews?
He's a mercenary, too.
Who?
I don't know anyone by that name.
[woman singing in French over speakers]
Hm. Welcome to the Maple Club.
-Now, this is my kind of joint.
-I'm Antoinette.
And what brings you to our establishment
this evening, Mr...?
St. Clair.
I'm looking to throw a small bash
for myself and some pals
to celebrate the fact we all got
into Harvard.
And a chum told me about this place.
From the looks of it,
seems like we'd have a good time here.
That you would.
How about I talk you through some
of Maple Club's offerings and options?
[Betty] Moose, who gave you
the Army pamphlets?
After the article airing
all my dirty laundry was published...
I mean, I was-- I was pretty messed up.
Mr. Chipping suggested I look
into the military.
I'm sorry, what's your connection
to Mr. Chipping?
He recruited me to play football.
Wait, Mr. Chipping's the reason
why you went to Stonewall Prep?
Yeah.
And what's weird is,
after the story about me came out,
he was encouraging me to leave.
Until Halloween night,
when it became more than a suggestion.
He practically shoved me out the door.
Plus, um...
there was a videotape.
What videotape?
Uh, Bret videotaped me having sex
in our dorm room with a classmate.
He was lording it over me,
threatening to release it any minute.
[stammers] I'm sorry...
Bret videotaped you having sex
in your dorm room?
He said it would be a good addition
to his collection.
Breaking and entering?
Is this normal for you, Elizabeth?
Kind of. But it's not really breaking
and entering, Mom.
I mean, this is Jughead's room, too,
and he said I could come
whenever I wanted.
Like when all the preppy scumbags
are in class.
Not quite all.
What the hell are you doing here?
Looking for the dirt that you have
on Moose Mason.
I know you filmed him having sex
to extort him.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
I have no idea what you and, I'm assuming,
your mother are referring to, Ponytail.
Does Moose have this supposed sex tape?
No, he says that you do, in a collection.
Where is it?
Because it's certainly not in this room.
Question: Did Mason ever lay eyes
on this alleged collection?
Question:
Do you have a tape of me and Jughead?
[gasps] Oh, my God!
Mom, calm down.
Moose said that it was filmed
in this room.
Did you tape us, too?
Again, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I don't have any tapes like that.
But if I did,
it sure is a good thing
that I'm such a nice guy.
Because I could really do
a number on you by releasing it.
Leave now, and I won't tell Jones
about this latest escapade of yours.
Or you can come with me to chemistry class
and we could tell him together.
So, assuming that you get in
to Barnard next year,
which you totally will,
is Archie moving here with you next year?
That's still very much up in the air.
Honestly, I don't think
Riverdale could survive without him.
Well, there's always long distance.
Totally. That's what my best friend Betty
and her beau are doing,
and they're making it work, so...
-What about you and your brawny boxer?
-KO?
-Mm-hm.
-Well, we are a real thing now.
I know, he's...
Oh, he's the best.
You know, I remember the first time
you held hands with him
was at my quinceañera at the Plaza.
And you told me his palms were sweaty
because he was so nervous.
Oh, my God, that is so embarrassing.
I can't believe you remember that.
All I remember is that
the Jonas Brothers performed.
-Mm-hm.
-And of course, how stunning you looked.
Yeah, because you
and your mom made the dress,
the dress that launched this beautiful,
unexpected relationship.
How is your mother? How is her shop?
Veronica, my mom's really sick.
And she's getting treatments, and she's--
Oh, she's being so strong.
But, um...
they caught it late, so we're just...
We're not sure what's gonna happen.
[sighs] She's my best friend, Veronica.
Katy...
Ugh. I'm sorry.
I didn't wanna tell you.
I didn't wanna cry today.
Are you kidding me?
What are old friends for,
if not to provide shoulders to cry on?
Come here.
I love you, Katy Keene.
You're gonna be okay, I promise.
-Where are you gonna go?
-Head up to Canada.
Maybe find my way to Alaska,
get some work.
Gotta get as far off the radar as possible
until this whole thing blows over.
If Ted can find me, others can, too.
Uncle Frank, can't you just talk
to the feds, explain what happened?
Maybe if you turn yourself in,
they'll go easy on you.
Or maybe they make me the scapegoat
who goes down for all of this.
Those tend to be the breaks
I get in life, Archie.
If you go on the run now,
you'll never stop running.
Man, you remind me so much
of your old man.
You take care of your mom, okay?
Or I'll come back and kick your ass.
You can try.
[Toni] Babe, what happened to you today?
You ghosted me.
Do you remember that Patrick Bateman-type
from earlier today, at the Maple Club?
Mmm. You mean Nick St. Clair?
Sophomore year...
Nick came to Riverdale one weekend
looking for a party.
He...
spiked my champagne...
and...
coaxed me back to his room
at the Five Seasons...
where...
he attempted to assault me.
What?
Thankfully, Veronica and Josie
and the Pussycats came to my rescue.
I thought I'd worked through it...
emotionally.
-But seeing him today, it...
-Triggered you.
I get it.
A similar experience happened to me
before I moved to Riverdale.
Tee-Tee.
I'm so sorry.
What did you do?
How did you cope?
It took me a while,
but with a lot of help,
I worked through it.
Babe, I wanna help you get there, too.
Gentlemen, we'll go seven rounds.
-We're not gonna need rounds.
-No. All we'll need is a coffin for Jones,
like the one I buried him in
way back when.
Round 1 begins now.
That's not bad, Bret.
Oh.
Well, he's got a glass jaw.
Told you we weren't gonna need rounds.
Mr. Jones is the winner.
The duel is officially tied.
Tomorrow's chess match will decide
the ultimate winner.
Oh, crap.
A dead snake, really?
And body checks in the hall?
Since when does Bret even have
so many friends?
He doesn't.
It's pack behavior.
Bret's homegrown,
a Stoney through and through.
Easy to root for.
And think about it,
if you win and Bret loses,
if he's not a man of honor,
what does that say about them?
So, what, this entire school is
against me now?
Not the entire school, Jones.
You still got me.
[Alice] If that tape exists,
we have to find it.
Agreed.
But we can't search the whole school.
What if Bret stores his collection
in the room where they have
those secret society meetings?
In Stonewall Prep's basement.
Okay, but we didn't fare so well
breaking into their dorms.
No, but Jughead still has
one last challenge.
We can slip into the basement
while he's keeping Bret busy.
[cell phone buzzes]
Hey, Mr. Jones, what's up?
[FP] Red, we got a problem. Ted escaped.
Wherever you are,
you have to get somewhere safe ASAP.
What? How the hell did he escape?
He just about snapped Tubby in two.
Get yourself to safety, okay?
Okay, bye.
Ted?
What the hell is happening?
This school is insane.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. [coughing]
[grumbles]
How...? I thought you were gone.
I had a gut feeling
this wasn't over, Archie.
But it is now.
[lounge music playing over speakers]
Refill?
You read my mind, sweetheart.
Maybe you'd like to enjoy it with me
in a private room.
You little minx.
Relax,
drink up and, uh...
I'm gonna get
a little more comfortable, okay?
[Betty] You're gonna mop the floor
with him, Jug.
Yeah, I hope so.
I just have to stay focused if I'm gonna
wipe that smug smile off Bret's face.
Where is the match?
Same place as all the other ones,
the seminar room.
At what time?
[Bret] I wanna raise the stakes.
When I win, you walk away
from the Baxter Brothers contract.
To what end?
The restoration of the rightful,
natural order of the world.
You lose, you slink away
and are never heard from again.
Just like your grandfather.
And Mr. DuPont gives the contract to me.
You wanna know
what the one problem with that is?
You're a terrible writer, Bret.
So, no,
I'm not going to accept your terms.
This is a duel about honor.
And when you lose,
it's going to be
because I'm a better writer...
I'm a better competitor...
and I'm a better man.
So, can we get this started already?
Indeed.
♪ You've been waitin' ♪
Gentlemen...
♪ Lookin' off into the night ♪
...play wisely.
♪ Search the horizon
Watchin' out for smoke and fire ♪
♪ You ♪
Okay, come on,
Veronica said it was this way.
♪ You aren't the only one ♪
♪ And so it begins ♪
-Betty, find the tapes, I'll stand watch.
-Okay.
♪ Standin' on the edge
Taking one last breath ♪
♪ Feel the pull of gravity
Down in the depths ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Knew this day would come ♪
♪ And you aren't the only one ♪
♪ And so it begins ♪
Oh, my God.
Okay, Moose, Moose, Moose...
Oh, that works, too.
♪ And you ♪
[watch beeping]
Someone's broken
into the Quill and Skull's room.
-What are you talking about?
-Silent alarm.
I have it synched to alert me.
Mr. DuPont, may I call a recess?
Yes, of course. We'll resume the game
after this is cleared up.
Betty, we have to go now!
All right. All right.
All right.
Here, take these.
Take these.
[footsteps approaching]
I almost admire your gumption, Ponytail,
but you're done.
You're trespassing.
And you are illegally recording
people having sex.
-And this is your tape of me and Jughead.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
-What the hell is going on?
-Your perv roommate taped us in your bed.
Are you serious, Bret?
All the tapes
in this room are private property.
Consensual testimonies given by students
being inducted into the Quill and Skull.
The tape you're holding right now
is Jughead's initiation confession.
Confession?
I did make a confession.
Right. So, I'll have
my private property back.
Excellent. Now, can we finish the match?
Wait, no, no.
That allows me to put you in--
Checkmate, yeah.
Why? Why would you do that?
Because I'm done playing this game, Bret.
That's game over, Mr. DuPont.
Bret wins this duel.
You...
are more of a Stonewall man
than I will ever be.
Or I'll ever wanna be.
Let's blow this place.
All right. Thank you, Mr. Jones.
I appreciate it.
Okay, bye.
The feds picked up Ted.
He'll be tried for everything he did
in Riverdale.
He said they're looking for you, too.
Of course they are.
My mom's the lawyer, not me,
but wouldn't it go better
if you turn yourself in?
You could cut a deal maybe, too.
All right.
All right, Archie, I'll do it.
I'll turn myself in tomorrow.
I genuinely think this is
the right thing to do, Uncle Frank.
[Hermione] Veronica, your father doesn't
want me to tell you this,
but I think it's important that you know.
We didn't go to New York on business.
We went to see a doctor.
A specialist.
He ran some tests,
and he confirmed
that your father has a disease.
What? What--?
What kind of disease?
It's a neuromuscular disorder.
It will weaken your father.
His muscles will atrophy.
He'll lose his motor skills.
But... there's good news.
I mean, we caught it early,
so there's drugs... and therapies.
So, he's... going to be fine?
We don't know.
We just know that he's very...
He's very sick.
Mom.
[Hermione sobs]
What...?
Where the hell am I?
-Who the hell are you?
-I bet you say that to all the boys.
[Fangs] It's okay.
Yeah, we understand.
Things got pretty wild last night.
[Toni] You wanna see?
You and the boys here made a little video.
[Nick giggling on video]
[Nick] It's too much!
[Fangs] Is it okay?
[Nick laughing on video]
Had enough?
[Nick] How could you?
You can't--
You'd better not show that to anyone,
you bitch, or I'll--
Or you'll what, exactly?
Now, listen up, worm,
because I'm only gonna say this once.
You don't know me, but I know you.
And I know exactly what you did
to my girlfriend, Cheryl Blossom,
and what you've probably done to a lot
of other innocent young women.
You will never set foot
in Riverdale again,
you will not so much as even think
about Cheryl Blossom,
and you will never assault another woman.
Because if you do,
I will let the whole world see
what was done to you.
I will ruin you.
[Nick laughing on TV]
Why are you tickling me?
So... So, Nick is what we
in the tickle business would call
a first-class squealer.
I propose a toast.
To Toni Topaz,
who slayed yet another dragon
from my past.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
I am, as always, one lucky lady.
[Archie] Frank didn't even leave a note.
Sorry, Red.
I know you two got close.
Yeah, we did.
But can I tell you, Mr. Jones...
I knew he was gonna run.
Even when he told me he wasn't,
I just... I felt it.
So, uh, what's next?
-Frank is probably halfway to Alaska.
-No, no.
I mean for you.
I don't know.
My dad was a decent, good guy.
He worked hard.
He loved me. He loved his life.
I believe he slept peacefully at night,
you know?
Unless I was out doing some dumbass thing.
Some days he won
and some days he lost.
But usually it was a draw,
and that was enough for him.
It was just that...
He was a simple man with honor.
-Maybe that's what's next for me.
-Mmm.
Sounds like a good plan to me.
Well, Mom, Dad,
I know it's still months away,
but clear your schedules and mark
your calendars for August 15th,
a very special day.
Special in what way?
It's when Barnard welcomes
its incoming freshman class,
including a certain Veronica Lodge.
[Hermione] Veronica!
You'll be moving me into my dorm.
I'm sorry, did you say "Lodge"?
Yes.
I did.
Going to New York, seeing Katy,
it reminded me of something I was missing.
But no need to make
a federal case out of it, Daddy.
No.
Absolutely not, mija.
[Betty] Any regrets about throwing
the match?
[Jughead] No.
If I've learned anything
over these last couple days,
it's that I really don't have
to prove anything to these people.
They have no idea what true honor is.
And you are not a damsel in distress.
But I'll murder Bret
if he actually has a tape of us.
Speaking of tapes, I did manage to sneak
something out of the Quill and Skull room,
a videotape labeled "Donna."
We were having an affair.
I knew it was wrong, and I didn't want
anybody to get into trouble,
so I tried to break it off with him.
But then he got...
aggressive.
Wait, what's going on?
This is exactly what Donna told me
about Mr. Chipping except--
Wait for this part.
And I was so scared,
I told him if he didn't stop,
I'd go to the headmaster.
I'd never seen Mr. Kotter so mad.
Who's Mr. Kotter?
Based on my research, no one.
He doesn't exist.
Even more chilling,
Donna is 100 percent using
the same language,
even exactly the same words she used
when she told me about Mr. Chipping.
And I-- I didn't want anybody
to get into trouble
so I tried to break it off with him.
But then he got aggressive.
-Meaning?
-She's lying, Jug.
This is a rehearsed speech
Donna has given at least twice.
All this time, I've been thinking,
we've been thinking,
that Bret's the evil mastermind
behind Stonewall Prep.
But I think we need to be
more worried about Donna.