[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
[Hiram] I am excited to fulfill
a lifelong dream of mine
and announce my candidacy for mayor.
Our father needed help.
"Our father"?
Thanks for meeting with me, Mr. DuPont.
I wanted to talk to you
about the first book
in the Baxter Brothers series.
-You didn't write it.
-You're very lucky...
I don't take you to the headmaster
and get you expelled.
-Are you okay?
-[Chipping] I'm sorry, Jughead...
that I couldn't help you.
I will be taking over
Mr. Chipping's seminar.
[Cheryl] Aunt Cricket? Uncle Bedford?
-Cheryl.
-Uncle Bedford.
You are going away
for a long, long time, Cheryl.
[Toni] Let go of her, you monster! [yells]
-You wanna fight me again?
-Don't you need to put your mask on first?
We gotta get him to a hospital.
[Jughead] Thanksgiving.
The time of year when friends
and family gather to eat turkey,
watch the big game and give thanks
for all that they have.
But for Archie,
this year was all about what he'd lost.
It was the first Thanksgiving
without his father.
And the void that Fred Andrews left
was as cold as the winds blowing
through the town.
And while Archie was thinking of ways
to give back,
Riverdale's new mayor was grabbing
all that he could.
Hiram Lodge had run unopposed,
allowing him to ascend to power
virtually overnight.
Meanwhile, across town,
at Riverdale General Hospital,
a different family gathering
was taking place.
For the Dickenson crime clan,
the only dish on the Thanksgiving menu
was revenge.
Now that our boy Dodger is stable...
we'll find whoever did this to him.
Guy from the community center. Gotta be.
What community center?
Who the hell are you talking about?
[Jughead] Weather forecasters were calling
for an epic ice storm,
and you could literally feel
the temperature dropping.
Mija.
Hey. You were missed this morning.
Oh, wait, was your inauguration today?
Well, you can make it up to me
tomorrow night.
I made reservations
at the Sweetwater Country Club.
I'm helping Archie
at the community center.
Yeah, Archie's community center.
Wasn't a man found bleeding out,
on the verge of death,
right in front of it?
Just terrible what's going on
in that part of town.
It's a real problem.
Well, you make sure you wish Archie
a very happy Thanksgiving for me.
All right, everyone. Bring it in! Come on.
Hustle up, hustle up.
All right, look.
We know some of you guys have nowhere
to go for Thanksgiving,
so Munroe and I are gonna keep
the center open tomorrow.
We're gonna have hot meals
with all the fixings!
[all cheer]
-Seriously? You guys are cooking?
-Hell, yeah.
-And my mom.
-And grandma.
So, tell your friends
there's an open door policy.
-Everyone is invited.
-All right.
And with that, the seminar is adjourned
for the remainder of the week.
I hope you all have a restful
and productive Thanksgiving break.
Mr. DuPont, before you go,
I was wondering...
I was wondering
if you had any more information
about why Mr. Chipping killed himself.
Alcoholism. Drove him to the edge.
Rupert had many demons, I'm afraid.
Well, he didn't leave a note.
-Hasn't been much of an investigation.
-At the family's request.
And it was clearly a suicide.
You saw it with your own eyes.
Mr. Chipping didn't come to you
to talk about me, did he?
No, why would he have?
-Well, because I shared with him--
-That ridiculous notion...
of your grandfather writing
the original Baxter Brothers novel?
He never brought it up.
And might I make a suggestion, Mr. Jones?
That you forget about this delusion
over the Thanksgiving break.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
[Jughead] You still gonna make it?
Even with this biblical ice storm
that they're predicting?
Jug, I don't care what my mom
or the weatherman are saying.
There's zero chance
that I'm not seeing you this weekend.
[on speaker] Then, hurry up
and get here already.
-I need your help with something.
-Oh...
You mean writing
your Baxter Brothers sample?
Well, I am on a deadline,
and that's the reason I'm hunkering down,
but also considering you and I are going
to be the only ones on campus,
I figured it would be the perfect time
to do a little sleuthing
into Chipping's death.
Because, believe me,
no one else is doing it.
Hmm. Conspiracy theories
and a murder mystery to solve?
Sounds like a romantic getaway to me.
All right. I love you. See you later.
[Cheryl] Did you hear the good news,
Tee-Tee?
There's a Category 4 ice storm headed
towards Riverdale like the wrath of God.
How is that good news, Cheryl?
Well, whilst the rest of Riverdale
sits down to give thanks,
we'll be dumping Bedford's body
in Sweetwater River,
just before it freezes over.
By the time spring thaw comes around,
the salmon will have gobbled up his eyes.
Toni...
What is it, my sweet?
I feel like somebody's watching me
all the time.
Whatever guilt you're experiencing,
free yourself of it.
You didn't set out to do anyone any harm.
Remember?
You were defending me,
and I love you for it.
Feast your eyes on this, boys,
a true Thanksgiving cornucopia.
Wha--? Ronnie, how...?
Where did you get all of this?
I put in a to-go order
at the country club.
Daddy gave me the idea.
I figured this could supplement whatever
you and yours are cooking for the kids.
Red, tell me this doesn't mean
you are deep-frying a Thanksgiving turkey.
Yes, I am.
It's tradition.
My dad would do one every year.
Best damn turkey I ever tasted.
You should come by tomorrow, Mr. Jones.
Actually, Archie,
that's what we need to talk about.
I hate to do this, but I'm under orders.
To shut you down.
What? Orders from who?
Let me guess, the mayor?
You've got to be kidding me.
He can't do this.
Yeah, he can.
He's mayor now, he can do anything.
And technically, the attack on Dodger's
an open investigation,
so this is still an active crime scene.
Plus, Hiram said
with the ice storm coming--
He's doing this to punish me,
to get me to spend the holiday with him.
-Can't we push back?
-I did.
For a couple of hours.
Look...
I'm not supposed to say this, but I know
what I would do if I was in your place.
Screw him.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but Hiram Lodge is
not canceling Thanksgiving.
Good man.
You're doing your dad proud.
Hey, stranger.
Hey. Wow, that was fast.
I took an earlier train to beat the storm.
Jug, hit save.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm almost done with my first chapter.
Yeah, and I can't wait to read it
and to help you sleuth.
But right now,
we have some catching up to do.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
♪ Feel the heat under the tide ♪
[Alice] FP, what's wrong?
Hiram.
I can't believe I'm working for him again.
Still doing his damn dirty work.
Well, you can do like we talked about.
You could quit.
That's what he expects me to do.
But you know what I'm not gonna do?
I'm not gonna wear that crap uniform
to tell a bunch of teenagers
that they can't feed homeless kids.
It's...
Well, whatever you decide,
I back you 100 percent.
I appreciate that, Alice.
-But I do have one request.
-Hm.
Mm-hm.
I'm not really in the mood to cook.
So, can we have turkey dinner
at Pop's tomorrow night?
Fine by me.
Since we have the house to ourselves...
Oh.
What happened to dinner at the club?
Well, the club was closed
because of the storm,
so we decided to order in.
[Hermosa] Plus, I have to take
an earlier flight back to Miami.
But I couldn't bear to miss
my first Thanksgiving all together.
Hermanita.
Please. Join us.
[Veronica] Never.
Only your blackened heart
would take away Thanksgiving
from a bunch of underprivileged kids
just to get what you want.
Are you referring to my decision
to close Archie's shelter?
It was a matter of public safety, mija.
It's nothing personal.
Neither was that, Papi.
[Archie] Are you sure
you still wanna come, Mom?
[Mary] Yeah. It's Thanksgiving.
I know the difference between the letter
of the law and doing what's right,
and feeding those kids is what's right.
Anyway, Hiram's not gonna have
guards stationed outside the door.
Honestly, I'm more worried
about the storm.
Well, I'll put chains on the truck tires
and salt the sidewalk around the center.
Mom.
-[sobs]
-Hey, what's wrong?
It's your father.
I just miss him.
-It's not right.
-No.
But, hey, we'll get through this.
And we're doing exactly
what he'd be doing.
[Toni] We're in trouble, Cheryl.
-Pray tell.
-I just ran into your Aunt Cricket.
She's parked down the road, spying on us.
That's the reason
why I've been feeling watched.
Did you interact
with that nosy, old turkey waddle?
Babe, how are we gonna get rid
of your Uncle Bedford's body,
now that she's staking us out?
We need to scare dear Cricket off,
once and for all,
and disabuse her of the idea
that she will ever get
even a sliver of our maple empire...
by...
inviting her to celebrate a traditional
Blossom Thanksgiving with us.
One honoring my gothic, ghoulish roots.
I'm afraid to ask.
Toni...
there's a family legend
Nana Rose shared with me
on one of her more lucid days
that will be the centerpiece of
a carefully planned performance art piece.
A tale so gruesome,
it will turn Aunt Cricket's hair white
and send her fleeing into the night,
never to be heard from again.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
I was thinking
about Mr. Chipping again earlier.
How he died just after he went to talk
to DuPont about my grandpa.
I think Mr. DuPont threatened
or blackmailed him into killing himself.
Wow, that's an extreme theory, Jug.
What's the motive?
Well, the Baxter Brothers franchise
is worth something like $200 million.
That's a compelling motive for Mr. DuPont
not to want his fraud exposed.
Yeah, but what leverage
did DuPont have over Chipping
to make him kill himself?
This is where it gets interesting.
How do you get someone to do
something they don't wanna do?
Blackmail, right?
Look... at these yearbook photos
I printed out of Mr. DuPont and Chipping.
These are decades apart.
You notice anything?
-Is that the same tie pin?
-Yes.
Apparently, that is the mark
of Quill and Skull.
It's one of Stonewall's
oldest secret societies.
And like so many secret societies,
what if their initiation has
something to do
with you revealing your deepest
and darkest secrets?
Well, then, DuPont may have used
Chipping's blackmail material
to coerce him into suicide.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
And maybe some of my current classmates
are part of the same society.
I mean, I checked Bret's side of the room,
but so far there's no sign
of a telltale tie pin.
Is it getting colder in here?
Yeah.
The radiator's on.
Just barely.
Is this the part where we freeze
and starve to death?
No, this is the part
where we get back in bed
and order Chinese food.
[Betty chuckles]
-[bell jingles]
-[Hiram] Oof!
["Auld Lang Syne" playing over speakers]
Of all the burger joints,
they have to walk into ours?
Mr. Lodge. Wasn't expecting
to see you here tonight.
Well, truthfully, our dinner plans
fell through, so we braved the storm.
-Take a seat. I'll be right out.
-Thank you, Pop.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
♪ And never brought to mind? ♪
FP. Alice.
♪ Should auld acquaintance be forgot ♪
-Okay.
-Hermione, Hiram.
Would you like to join us?
♪ For auld lang syne ♪
-We would love to.
-Yeah, okay.
[groans]
That's strike three.
Nowhere's gonna be delivering
because of this ice storm.
How about...
I just raid the vending machine?
Yes.
I can finally live out
my Charlie Brown fantasy
of having junk food
for Thanksgiving dinner.
Yes! Okay.
I will have Stonewall's
finest chocolate-chip cookies,
chips, soda, and candy, please.
Get yourself something, too.
[coins rattling]
[machine beeping]
Who the hell are you?
-What do you want?
-[Betty grunts]
Betty.
I saw him sneak past the door.
[Donna] What the hell, you guys?
What did you do to him?
Donna. What did we do?
What are you guys doing here?
And why are you wearing bunny masks?
And carrying an ax?
We were just trying to scare you, Jones,
have a little fun.
All right, well,
now your friend is bleeding,
and I'm sure this place's infirmary
is locked up really tight.
So, yeah, that's fun. Let's get him up.
[Munroe] There he is. What's going on,
Eddie? You want some cider or some cocoa?
[Veronica] Even if the storm's keeping
most people away,
thank goodness you're doing this, Archie.
-Where else would they have gone?
-I don't know.
But I'm thinking maybe we should keep
the center open overnight.
No one should be out in this ice.
You're too good for this world,
Archiekins.
Hey.
How you holding up?
I'm good. Why?
Just wanna make sure you're okay.
I am, Ronnie.
It hasn't totally hit me yet,
I don't think.
Well...
when it does...
I'm here for you.
Okay?
[Munroe] Hi. Okay.
Yo, just make your guys' selves at home
and grab some cider.
Hey, guys, come on in.
Welcome to the center.
And who are you?
I'm Archie. I run the center with Munroe,
my friend. We're glad to have you.
But you're just a kid yourself.
Hey, Archie, uh,
there's a spill over here.
I don't know where the bucket and mop is.
Uh, I got it, Mom.
Excuse me, guys. Help yourself
to some hot chocolate or cider.
Dinner will be ready in a bit.
Well, that's...
That should do it.
Three stitches, not too bad.
Yeah. It's easy for you to say.
Well, maybe next time,
don't threaten my boyfriend with an ax.
"It saddens me greatly to realize
these will be the last words
I ever write"?
Hey. Hands off, Forsythe.
What was that? Was that a suicide note?
Mr. Chipping's?
It was an exercise we did.
We each wrote a note to see
who could best capture
the inner workings
of Chipping's troubled mind.
If it was an official exercise,
then why wasn't I included?
It was outside the curriculum. Relax.
Come on, Bret. Let's get you cleaned up.
-Jug, what are they doing here? Really?
-I don't know.
But I certainly don't believe
any of that BS about a writing exercise.
Well, maybe it's incriminating evidence
that they wanna get rid of
or fake evidence
that they're trying to plant?
Okay, how we gonna play this game?
You said it.
Your chums like playing games.
Let's give them a taste
of their own medicine.
Aunt Cricket. We're so thrilled
you were able to join us
and that you brought Cousin Fester.
Well, I wanted witnesses
so we don't go missing
the way Bedford did.
Don't be silly.
Dinner will be ready soon.
Can I offer you
some mulled berry wine to start?
[oil bubbling]
-Hey, Archie.
-What's up, Eddie?
You see those people over there?
I've seen them before at the arcade.
They're Dodger's family.
What the hell?
You sure?
All right. Thanks for the heads-up.
Go grab a seat, I'll take care of it.
And, hey, be cool.
I'm not sure what you're here for,
but you and your boys need to leave.
We've got kids here.
We don't want any trouble.
We don't want any trouble either.
But we've come for the man
who tried to kill our Dodger.
Got a feeling he's you.
Or one of your friends.
I swear to you,
no one here tried to hurt Dodger.
Well, someone did.
And whoever it is,
he's got a real soft spot for this place.
We think we hang out here long enough,
he'll show.
[Darla] In the meantime...
how about some of that delicious food
I'm smelling?
You guys remember back in high school
when we all used to hang out together?
Us griping about how horrible
our parents were?
And now we're the horrible parents.
Fred never complained about his folks,
not once.
And look what an amazing father
he turned out to be.
I think we could all take a lesson
from that, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, what say we continue
this downstairs over drinks?
-Yes, yes.
-Huh? To toast Fred.
What do you say, FP, huh?
You're not on duty, are you?
Why the hell not, Mr. Mayor?
[Hermione and Hiram chuckle]
Well, considering we are trapped here
until the morning at least,
let's say we pass the time with a game
of Never Have I Ever.
I do love a good salacious drinking game.
I'll start.
Never have I ever kissed a girl.
Betty.
Never have I ever...
done drugs.
Jones, I'm surprised. Isn't Riverdale
like the drug capital of the world?
Never have I ever...
been in a gang.
[Donna] Really?
But you look so sweet.
Oh, well, I'm not as sweet
as you might think.
Never have I ever been
in a secret society.
Oops, looks like you lose that round,
Forsythe.
Now you gotta finish the whole flask.
[Betty] Time for a refill.
I'll go get the bottle
from your room, Jug.
Jug, I found this tie pin in Donna's room,
and it has an engraving on the back.
The initials RC.
-What was Mr. Chipping's first name?
-Rupert.
These are his initials.
How does Donna have this?
Killers often take something
from their victim
as a souvenir or trophy.
How long can this go on for?
We have to fight back.
No offense to your guns, Munroe,
but they have real ones.
If I can get into the office, in my desk,
I have a drawer full of weapons
that I confiscated off the kids,
knives, switchblades--
Now hold on.
I'm not sure I endorse this plan.
Adding more weapons to the stew?
One of those kids could get hurt.
-[Fagan] Ooh.
-[Bill] Whoo!
[Darla] Mmm.
-[Munroe] Malcolm!
-What you doing?
-Want this?
-Relax! He didn't know what he was doing.
Don't do it! He's just a kid.
Everyone, stay back.
[Mary] Archie!
That's for my brother.
You know what I think, Carrot Top?
I think you've got a hero complex.
You know what else I think?
I think you beat my boy Dodger
into a coma,
and then you called an ambulance
so no one would suspect you.
But a mother, she knows.
And you...
you are gonna pay for what you've done!
Now get your ass down!
[oil bubbling]
Say it.
Say it's you.
You're the one who almost killed my son.
Ms. Dickenson, please...
whatever it is that you think
you have to do, you don't.
Say it!
Confess, boy,
before things start getting
real ugly in here.
If I say it...
you'll let everyone else here go?
Then you can do whatever you want to me.
I'll take that deal.
But I need to hear you say it.
Fine.
[Eddie] Please, stop, stop. It's me!
I wear the mask! I'm the dark dude!
-Leave Archie alone!
-Eddie, shut up.
It's not him.
It's me! The mask is mine.
Toby, sit down and shut up.
I'm the guy you want.
[Darla] That's enough!
Now, that was a touching display.
Hell, another day, I might've even cried.
But not today.
I already spilt all my tears over my son.
And, boy,
your mother is gonna find out exactly
what that feels like.
[all gasp]
Go! Get in the office! Go, go, go!
-[screams]
-Don't even try it.
Stop! Step away from my son!
I have the right to protect myself
against intruders with deadly force.
So, unless you want me to use it,
you have exactly five seconds
to get the hell out of here.
One...
two...
-three...
-[groans]
four...
Lock the door behind them.
Let's call the police.
Mrs. Andrews.
I'm obsessed.
Yeah, Mom, since when are you Dirty Harry?
What was that explosion?
Who in their right mind tries
to deep-fry a turkey inside?
[jazz music playing over speakers]
You're nursing it, FP. What's the matter?
You don't like my rum?
[FP scoffs]
Well, someone's gotta be clear-headed
enough to drive the rest of you home.
FP...
you know, I sensed
that you were upset with me
when I asked you to shut down
Archie's community center earlier.
Anyway, I appreciate your cooperation.
-I'm gonna make this clear, Hiram.
-FP.
I am not your puppet.
When I took this job,
I pledged to serve and protect Riverdale,
not to do your bidding.
-Why don't you settle down?
-Mm-hm.
What's the matter?
You put a hit out on my son, you bastard.
You think I forgot about that?
Yeah. Is that why you tried to murder me
at the behest of my own wife?
[Hermione] Hiram.
[Alice] FP!
FP.
Finish it.
Do it.
-Or get the hell off me.
-FP.
[Hiram] Come on.
I'm not gonna do it,
but you deserve it.
Everyone in this room,
hell, everyone in this town,
knows that you deserve it!
[bottle shatters]
[Cheryl] Whilst we all tuck
into our delicious homemade meat pies,
might I suggest we reminisce
about some Thanksgivings of yore?
Nana, will you regale us?
Well...
there is the story
of the first Blossom Thanksgiving,
but it's a dark chapter.
Deeply dark.
That's fine.
I'd love to hear more about your family,
warts and all.
[Nana] The weather turned,
and the Blossom settlers were surprised by
a sudden brutal onset of ice.
Much like tonight.
The wagons were snowed in, and soon after,
the hunger set in.
Deep.
Aching.
Gnawing.
Stomachs groaning so loud,
they drowned out the wind until...
Until what, Nana?
The Blossoms turned on one another.
They had to eat their own.
Survive...
on Blossom flesh.
[Fester gulps]
Do you mean... cannibalism?
Why, I can only imagine what a scandal
like that would do to our family name,
especially if it were to come out
right as Aunt Cricket were attempting
to negotiate a sale
for our maple business.
Please. No one would believe that snuff.
I wouldn't be so sure of that.
We Blossoms have always been
highly carnivorous.
I mean...
I ate my brother Julian in the womb.
And you're eating those meat pies
we prepared especially for you.
[grunts] My tooth.
What on earth?
[Cricket] What...?
Is this Uncle Bedford's ring?
What does this mean?
It means, Aunt Cricket...
that you're welcome to search the house.
It means that Uncle Bedford...
will never be found.
It means that any evidence
he was ever here...
is in the process of being... digested.
In other words...
I think you know what it means.
You...
You're bluffing.
Not even you are deranged enough to commit
such an unspeakable abomination.
On the contrary.
[gasps] Which reminds me,
it's time for dessert.
Tee-Tee?
[Fester screams]
[Cheryl] Face facts, Aunt Cricket.
You and Cousin Fester have just committed
a vile act of cannibalism,
which is illegal in this state.
So, unless you want the world
to learn as much,
you will leave us the hell alone.
You do not knock on my door.
You do not harass my girlfriend.
You do not ask me to sell off
my Blossom legacy ever again.
Are we clear?
Now, would you like me to pack up
the rest of Bedford for you in Tupperware?
[gagging]
Fester!
-[door opens, then closes]
-[Cheryl giggles]
There you two are.
We thought you'd been murdered.
No dice on the booze, I see.
Not a drop to be found.
But I say we keep playing the game,
and I'll go next.
Never have I ever tried
to cover up a murder.
Oh, you guys are just so cool.
You know that?
You're never breaking a sweat,
never betraying an emotion.
Hell, writing fake suicide notes,
how cool is that?
But you guys aren't as devious
as you think.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have left
incriminating evidence,
like Mr. Chipping's tie pin.
You went into my room?
It was an accident.
I mean, all the doors look the same.
[Jughead] Between the suicide note
and the tie pin,
you two are trying to cover up something
about Mr. Chipping's suicide.
Or was it a murder?
Care to explain?
You were there, Jones.
You saw him jump.
No one pushed him out that window.
Not physically.
But psychologically, Mr. Chipping could've
been pushed to the edge.
Donna.
How? Where... did you get this?
We just wanna know the truth.
Mr. Chipping gave it to me, okay?
We were having an affair.
I knew it was wrong,
and I didn't want anybody
to get into trouble,
so I tried to break it off with him.
But then he got aggressive.
I was so scared.
I told him if he didn't stop,
I'd go to the headmaster, and then...
the next day, he jumped out the window.
I can't live my life
doing Hiram's bidding, Alice.
I'm not cut out for it.
There's too much blood on the tracks.
-I hear you.
-I am a Serpent, Alice. I'm a Serpent.
Every bone in my body is a Serpent.
Okay. So, is there a rule that says
that you can't be both?
That's not bad.
If Hiram can be mayor and a kingpin,
who says that I can't be sheriff...
and a gang leader?
[Alice chuckles]
How are you feeling, my love?
I think, relieved.
Am I crazy, or did we just manage
to pull our plan off?
The latter.
By morning,
Sweetwater River will have frozen over,
and Aunt Cricket
and Cousin Fester will be back
in whatever ring of hell
they typically inhabit,
digesting those yummy Iamb meat pies.
And Uncle Bedford's name
will never be spoken aloud again.
I do feel some kind of peace,
in some weird way.
We defended our home
from hostile invaders.
And for the rest of the weekend,
we have nothing to worry about
but ourselves.
And... something I haven't yet said.
I love you...
and I'm so grateful to you.
Yeah, I love you, too, babe.
And happy Thanksgiving.
I'm just so confused.
This whole time,
Mr. Chipping was the bad guy?
It wasn't Bret or Mr. DuPont?
And poor Donna...
I'm not so sure
that Donna isn't playing us, Jug.
What do you mean?
Are you saying she made all of that up?
Well, I don't wanna say that
because there's a possibility
that they had a harrowing affair.
But there's a possibility
in which the story that she told me
was just to stall us from uncovering
the real truth.
You should just talk
to your headmaster, Jug.
I mean, get it on his radar that something
weird is happening at this school.
Yeah. That's a good idea.
I will.
Hey, I was thinking maybe, if the storm
clears up by tomorrow morning,
that we can go home for the weekend.
Sure. In the meantime, how...?
How will we stay warm tonight?
[Betty giggling]
Before we start...
we were never
a particularly religious house,
but the one thing we always did,
the one thing
my husband always liked to do
when we sat down together
to eat as a family,
was to say grace.
He believed in that.
Archie, would you do the honors?
Yeah.
Bless us, O Lord, for these, the gifts,
which we are about to receive.
For this day, for this food,
for our family, for our friends,
we thank you. Amen.
-[Veronica] Amen.
-Amen.
And then he would say...
Dig in, everyone.
I'm grateful to be alive
and to be here with you.
What's this about, sheriff?
Dodger Dickenson's family is at-large
and dangerous.
And we have reason to believe they might
try to get to him before they skip town.
Well, we monitor our patients
fairly closely.
Well, not closely enough, huh, doc?
Ah. Excuse me, headmaster?
[inaudible dialogue]
[Jughead] What's that all about?
Donna came clean to the headmaster
about her affair with Chipping.
How he basically abused and harassed her.
She was trying to protect his family,
prevent any further pain,
but after Betty broke into her room,
Donna felt like she had no choice
but to talk to the authorities
about all the awful things
Chipping did to her.
Well, I guess there's no doubt
about it anymore.
Chipping's death was a suicide,
driven by a guilty man's fear of exposure.
Case closed, Detective Jones.
[playing ballad]
Archie?
Yesterday was, without a doubt,
the strangest Thanksgiving I've ever had.
I mean, I pointed a gun at a woman.
Welcome to Riverdale, Mom.
Yeah, it's a far cry from me, you and Dad
eating fried turkey and watching football.
He never made it past the third quarter.
He fell asleep on the couch.
You know, I've been thinking about
that deep fryer exploding when it did.
I mean, what are the odds of that?
-That saved us, Archie.
-Yeah, we got lucky, Mom.
No, that wasn't luck.
That was your dad watching out for us.
I think you're right.
And that gives me an idea.
[applause]
What do you think, Mom?
Your father never would've believed this.
Everything you've been building here.
All of you.
He'd be honored...
and so proud.