Previously, on
"Riverdale"...
I'm excited to fulfill
a lifelong dream of mine
and announce my candidacy
for mayor.
Our father needed help.
"Our father"?
Thank you for meeting
with me, Mr. DuPont.
I wanted to talk to you about
the first book
in the Baxter Brothers series.
You didn't write it.
You're very lucky
I don't take you
to the Headmaster
and get you expelled.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Jughead,
that I couldn't help you.
I will be taking over
Mr. Chipping's seminar.
Aunt Cricket?
Uncle Bedford?
- Cheryl.
- Uncle Bedford?
You are going away
for a long, long time, Cheryl.
Let go of her,
you monster.
You want to fight me again?
Don't you need to put
your mask on first?
We got to get him
to a hospital.
Thanksgiving.
The time of year
when friends and family
gather to eat turkey,
watch the big game,
and give thanks
for all that they have.
But for Archie, this year was
all about what he'd lost.
It was the first Thanksgiving
without his father.
The void that
Fred Andrews left
was as cold as the winds
blowing through the town.
And while Archie was thinking
of ways to give back,
Riverdale's new mayor was
grabbing all that he could.
Hiram Lodge had
run unopposed,
allowing him to ascend
to power virtually overnight.
Meanwhile, across town,
at Riverdale General Hospital,
a different family gathering
was taking place.
For the Dickenson crime clan,
the only
dish on the Thanksgiving menu
was revenge.
Now that our boy Dodger
is stable,
we'll find whoever did
this to him.
Guy from the community center.
Got to be.
What community center?
Who the hell are you
talking about?
Weather forecasters were
calling for an epic ice storm,
and you could literally feel
the temperature dropping.
Mija.
Hey, you were missed
this morning.
Oh, wait,
was your inauguration today?
Well, you can make it up to me
tomorrow night.
I made reservations at
the Sweetwater Country Club.
I'm helping Archie at
the community center.
Yeah,
Archie's community center...
Wasn't a man found
bleeding out,
on theverge of death,
right in front of it?
Just terrible what's going on
in that part of town.
It's a real problem.
Well...
You make sure you wish
Archie a very
happy Thanksgiving for me.
All right, everyone,
bring it in. Come on!
Hustle up, hustle up.
All right, look.
We know some of you guys
have nowhere to go
for Thanksgiving.
So, Munroe and I,
we're gonna keep the
center open tomorrow.
We're gonna have hot meals
with all the fixings.
- Seriously? You guys are cooking?
- Hell, yeah.
- And my mom.
- And grandma.
So tell your friends there's an
open-door policy.
Everyone is invited.
All right.
And with that,
the seminar is adjourned
for the
remainder of the week.
I hope you all have
a restful and productive
Thanksgiving break.
Mr. DuPont, before you go,
I was wondering...
I was wondering
if you had any more information
about why Mr. Chipping
killed himself.
Alcoholism.
Drove him to the edge.
Rupert had many demons,
I'm afraid.
Well, he didn't leave a note.
There hasn't been much of
an investigation.
The family's request.
And it was clearly a suicide.
You saw it
with your own eyes.
Mr. Chipping didn't come to you
to talk about me, did he?
No. Why would he have?
- Well, because I shared with...
- That ridiculous notion...
Of your grandfather
writing the original
Baxter Brothers novel?
He never bought it up.
And might I make a suggestion,
Mr. Jones?
That you forget about this delusion
over the Thanksgiving break.
Now if you will excuse me.
Are you still gonna make it?
Even with this biblical ice
storm that they're predicting?
Jug, I don't care what my mom
or the weatherman are saying.
There's zero chance that I'm
not seeing you this weekend.
Well, then hurry up
and get here already.
I need your help
with something.
Oh! You mean writing your
Baxter Brothers sample?
Well, I am on a deadline and that's
the reason I'm hunkering down,
but... also, considering you and I are
going to be the only ones on campus,
I figured it would be
the perfect time
to do a little sleuthing into
Chipping's death.
Because believe me,
no one else is doing it.
Hmm.
Conspiracy theories and
a murder mystery to solve.
Sounds like a
romantic getaway to me.
All right. I love you,
see you later.
Did you hear
the good news, T.T.?
There's a category-four ice storm heading
towards Riverdale like the wrath of God.
How is that good news, Cheryl?
Well, whilst the rest of Riverdale
sits down to give thanks,
we'll be dumping Bedford's body
in Sweetwater River.
Just before it freezes over.
By the time spring
thaw comes around,
the salmon will have
gobbled up his eyes.
Toni.
What is it, my sweet?
I feel like somebody is
watching me all the time.
Whatever guilt
you're experiencing,
free yourself of it.
You didn't set out
to do anyone any harm.
Remember?
You were defending me
and I love you for it.
Feast your eyes on this, boys.
A true Thanksgiving cornucopia.
Wow!
Ronnie, how...
Where did you get all of this?
I put in a to-go order
at the country club.
Daddy gave me the idea.
I figured this could
supplement whatever
you and yours are
cooking for the kids.
Red,
tell me
this doesn't mean
you're deep-frying
a Thanksgiving turkey?
Yes. I am. It's tradition.
My dad would do one every year.
Best damn turkey
I ever tasted.
You should come by tomorrow,
Mr. Jones.
Actually, Archie,
that's what we need to talk about.
I hate to do this,
but I'm under orders...
to shut you down.
What?
Orders from who?
Let me guess,
the Mayor?
Well, you have got
to be kidding me.
- He can't do this.
- Yeah, he can,
he's mayor now.
He can do anything.
And technically, the attack on
Dodger is an open investigation.
So this is still an active
crime scene, plus,
Hiram said,
with the ice storm coming...
He's doing this
to punish me.
To get me
to spend the holiday with him.
- Can't we push back?
- I did.
For a couple of hours.
Look.
I'm not supposed to say this,
but I know what I would do,
if I was in your place.
Screw him!
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but Hiram Lodge
is not canceling Thanksgiving.
Good man.
You're doin' your dad
proud.
*RIVERDALE (US)*
Season 04  Episode 07
Episode Title :
Chapter Sixty-Four: The Ice Storm
Hey, stranger.
Hey!
Wow, that was fast.
I took an earlier train
to beat the storm.
Jug.
Hit "save."
I know. I'm sorry.
I am almost done
with my first chapter.
Yeah,
and I can't wait to read it,
and to help you sleuth.
But right now,
we have some catching up to do.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
FP? What's wrong?
Hiram.
Can't believe
I'm working for him again,
still doing
his damn dirty work.
Well...
You could do like
we talked about. You could quit.
That's what he
expects me to do.
But you know
what I am not gonna do?
I am not gonna wear
that crap uniform
to tell
a bunch of teenagers,
that they can't feed homeless kids.
It's...
Well, whatever you decide,
I back you 100%.
I appreciate that, Alice.
But, I do have one request.
Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm.
Not really in the mood to cook.
So, can we have turkey dinner
at Pop's tomorrow night?
Fine by me.
Since we have the house
to ourselves...
What happened to
dinner at the club?
Oh, well, the club was closed
because of the storm,
so, we decided to order in.
Plus, I have to take
an earlier flight back to Miami.
But,
I couldn't bear to miss
my first Thanksgiving
all together, hermanita.
Please, join us.
Never.
Only your blackened heart
would take away
Thanksgiving
from a bunch
of underprivileged kids,
just to get
what you want.
Are you referring to my decision
to close Archie's shelter?
It was a matter
of public safety, mija.
It's nothing personal.
Neither was that...
Papi.
You sure
you still wanna come, Mom?
Yeah, it's Thanksgiving.
And I know the difference
between the letter of the law
and doing what's right.
And feeding those kids is what's right.
Anyway, Hiram is not gonna
have guards stationed outside the door.
Honestly, I'm more worried
about the storm.
Well, I'll put chains
on the truck's tires
and salt the sidewalk,
around the center.
Mom?
Hey, what's wrong?
Your father.
I just miss him.
- It's not right.
- No.
But, hey,
we'll get through this.
And we're doing
exactly what he'd be doing.
We're in trouble,
Cheryl.
- Pray tell?
- I just ran into your Aunt Cricket.
She's parked down the road,
spying on us.
That's the reason
why I've been feeling watched.
Did you interact with
that nosy old turkey wattle?
Babe, how are we gonna get rid
of your Uncle Bedford's body
now that she's staking us out?
We need to scare dear Cricket off,
once and for all,
and disabuse her of the idea
that she will ever get
even a sliver
of our maple empire.
By...
inviting her
to celebrate a traditional
Blossom Thanksgiving with us,
one honoring my Gothic,
ghoulish roots.
I am afraid to ask.
Toni,
there is a family legend
Nana Rose shared with me
on one of her
more lucid days...
that will be the centerpiece
of a carefully-planned
performance art piece.
A tale so gruesome,
it will turn
Aunt Cricket's hair white
and send her fleeing
into the night,
never to be heard from again.
I missed you.
Hmm, I missed you too.
I was thinking about
Mr. Chipping again earlier.
How he died just after he went to
talk to DuPont, about my grandpa.
I think Mr. DuPont
threatened or blackmailed him
into killing himself.
Wow, that's an...
extreme theory, Jug.
What's the motive?
Well, the Baxter Brothers franchise
is worth something like $200 million.
That's a compelling motive
for Mr. DuPont
not to want his fraud exposed.
Yeah, but what leverage
did DuPont have over Chipping
to make him kill himself?
This is where
it gets interesting.
How do you get someone to do
something they don't want to do?
Blackmail, right?
Look...
at these yearbook photos
I printed out
of Mr. DuPont and Chipping.
These are decades apart.
You notice anything?
Is that the same tiepin?
Yes.
Apparently,
that is the mark
of Quill and Skull.
It's one of Stonewall's
oldest secret societies.
And like
so many secret societies,
what if their initiation
has something to do
with you revealing your deepest
and darkest secrets?
Well, then DuPont may have used
Chipping's blackmail material
to coerce him into suicide.
That's exactly
what I was thinking.
Then, maybe some of my current
classmates are part of the same society.
I mean, I checked Bret's side
of the room,
but so far, there is no sign
of a telltale tiepin.
Is it getting colder in here?
Yeah.
The radiator is on.
Just barely.
This is the part where
we freeze and starve to death?
No, this is the part where we get
back in bed and order Chinese food.
Of all the burger joints,
they have to walk into ours.
Mr. Lodge!
Wasn't expecting
to see you here tonight.
Well, truthfully,
our dinner plans fell through,
so, we braved the storm.
Take a seat.
I'll be right out.
- Thanks.
- Thank you, Pop.
Oh, thank you.
FP. Alice.
♪ Should old acquaintance
be forgot... ♪
Hermione,
Hiram...
Would you like to join us?
We would love to.
Yeah, okay.
That's strike three.
Nowhere is going to be delivering,
because of this ice storm.
How about...
I just raid
the vending machine?
Yes.
I can finally live out
my Charlie Brown fantasy
of having junk food
for Thanksgiving dinner.
Yes! Okay, I will have
Stonewall's finest
chocolate chip cookies,
chips, soda
and candy, please.
Get yourself something too.
Who the hell are you?
What do you want?
Betty...
I saw him sneak
past the door.
What the hell, you guys?
What did you do to him?
Donna, what did we do?
What're you guys
doing here?
And why're you wearing...
bunny masks?
And carrying an ax?
We were just trying to scare you, Jones,
have a little fun.
All right, well,
now your friend is bleeding
and I'm sure this place's infirmary
is locked up really tight,
so yeah, that's fun.
Let's get him up.
Oh, there he is.
What's going on, Eddie?
You want some cider,
some coco?
Even if this storm's
keeping most people away,
thank goodness
you're doing this, Archie.
Where else
would they have gone?
I don't know.
But I'm thinking, maybe we should
keep the center open overnight.
No one should be out
in this ice.
You're too good
for this world, Archiekins.
Hey...
How are you holding up?
I'm good, why?
I just...
wanna make sure you're okay.
And I am, Ronnie.
It hasn't totally hit me yet,
I don't think.
Well,
when it does...
I'm here for you.
Okay?
Hi. Okay.
Just make yourselves at home
and have some cider.
Hey, guys, come on in.
Welcome to the center.
And who are you?
I'm Archie.
I run the center with Munroe,
my friend.
We're glad to have you.
But, you're just
a kid yourself.
Hey, Archie, uh,
there's a spill over here.
I don't know where
the bucket and mop is.
Uh, I got it, Mom.
Excuse me, guys, uh,
help yourself to some
hot chocolate or cider.
Dinner will be ready in a bit.
That should do it.
Three stitches, not too bad.
Yeah.
It's easy for you to say.
Well, maybe next time,
don't threaten my boyfriend
with an ax.
"It saddens me greatly
to realize
that these will be
the last words I ever write."
Hands off, Forsythe.
What was that?
Was that a suicide note?
Mr. Chipping's?
It was an exercise we did.
We each wrote
a note to see
who could best capture
the inner workings
of Chipping's troubled mind.
If it was
an official exercise,
then why wasn't I included?
It was outside
the curriculum, relax.
Come on, Bret,
let's get you cleaned up.
Jug, what are they
doing here, really?
I don't know.
But I certainly don't believe
any of that BS
about a writing exercise.
Well, maybe it's incriminating
evidence that
they wanna get rid of,
or fake evidence
that they're trying to plant.
Okay. How are we
gonna play this game?
You said it.
Your chums like playing games.
Let's give them
a taste of their own medicine.
Aunt Cricket, we're so thrilled
you were able to join us...
and that you brought
Cousin Fester.
Well, I wanted witnesses,
so I don't go missing
the way Bedford did.
Don't be silly.
Dinner will be ready soon.
Can I offer you some
mulled berry wine to start?
Hey, Archie.
What's up, Eddie?
You see those people
over there?
I've seen them before
at the arcade.
They're Dodger's family.
What the hell? You sure?
All right.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Go grab a seat.
I'll take care of it.
And hey, be cool.
I'm not sure
what you're here for,
but you and your boys
need to leave.
We've got kids here.
We don't want any trouble.
We don't want
any trouble either.
But we've come for the man
who tried to kill
our Dodger.
Got a feeling he's you,
or one of your friends.
I swear to you,
no one here tried
to hurt Dodger.
Well, someone did.
And whoever it is,
he's got a real soft spot
for this place.
We think, if we hang out here
long enough,
he'll show.
In the meantime,
how about some of that
delicious food I'm smelling?
You guys remember,
back in high school,
when we all used to
hang out together?
Us griping about
how horrible our parents were.
And now we're
the horrible parents.
Fred never complained
about his folks, not once.
Look what an amazing father
he turned out to be.
Think we could all take
a lesson from that, huh?
Hey, what say we continue this
downstairs, over drinks?
- Huh? To toast Fred!
- Yes.
What do you say, FP, huh?
You're not on duty, are you?
Why the hell not, Mr. Mayor?
Well, considering we're trapped
here until the morning, at least,
what say we pass the time with
a game of "Never Have I Ever"?
I do love a good salacious
drinking game.
I'll start.
Never have I ever...
kissed a girl.
Betty.
Never have I ever...
done drugs.
Jones, I'm surprised.
Isn't Riverdale, like,
the drug capital of the world?
Never have I ever...
been in a gang.
Really?
But you look so sweet.
Oh.
Well, I'm not as sweet as you might think.
Never have I ever been
in a secret society.
Oops. Looks like you lose
that round, Forsythe.
Now you gotta finish
the whole flask.
Time for a refill. I'll go get
the bottle from your room, Jug.
Jug, I found this tiepin
in Donna's room,
and it has an engraving
on the back.
The initials "RC."
What was Mr. Chipping's
first name?
Rooper!
- These are his initials.
- Mmm-hmm.
How does Donna have this?
Killers often take something
from their victim
as a souvenir or trophy.
How long can this go on for?
We have to fight back.
No offense to your "guns,"
Munroe, but they have real ones.
If I can get into the office,
in my desk,
I have a drawer full of weapons
that I confiscated off of the kids.
- Knives, switchblades...
- No. Hold on.
I'm not sure
I endorse this plan.
Adding more weapons to the stew?
One of those kids could get hurt.
- Matthew!
- Hey, you little runt.
- You want this?
- Relax. Relax.
- Don't do... Don't do anything!
- He didn't know what he was doing.
Look, he's just a kid.
Everyone, stay back.
Archie!
That's for my brother.
You know what I think,
carrot top?
I think you've got
a hero complex.
You know what else I think?
I think you beat
my boy Dodger into a coma,
and then, you called an ambulance
so no one would suspect you.
But a mother, she knows.
And you...
You are gonna pay
for what you've done!
Now, get your ass down.
Say it.
Say it's you.
You're the one
who almost killed my son.
Ms. Dickinson, please.
Whatever it is that you think
you have to do here, you don't.
Say it!
Confess, boy,
before things start
getting real ugly in here.
If I say it,
you'll let everyone
else here go...
and you can do whatever
you want to me.
I'll take that deal.
But I need to hear you say it.
Fine.
Stop, stop. It's me.
I wear the mask. I'm the Dark Duke.
Leave Archie alone.
Shut the hell up.
It's not him.
- It's me. The mask is mine.
- Toby, sit down and shut up.
I'm the guy you want.
That's enough!
Now, that was
a touching display.
Hell...
another day,
I might have even cried.
But not today.
I already spilled
all my tears over my son.
And boy...
your mother is gonna find out
exactly what that feels like.
Go, get in the office.
Go, go, go, go!
Don't even try it.
Stop! Step away from my son.
I have the right to protect
myself against intruders,
with deadly force.
So, unless you want me
to use it,
you have exactly five seconds
to get the hell out of here.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Lock the door behind them
and let's call the police.
Mrs. Andrews...
I'm obsessed.
Yeah. Mom, since when are
you Dirty Harry?
What was that explosion?
Who in their right mind tries
to deep-fry a turkey inside?
You're nursing it, FP.
What's the matter,
you don't like my rum?
Well, someone's got
to be clear-headed
enough to drive the
rest of you home.
FP...
you know, I sense
that you were upset with me
when I asked you to shut down
Archie's community center earlier.
Anyway, I appreciate
your cooperation.
I'm gonna make this clear,
Hiram.
FP.
I'm not your puppet.
When I took this job,
I pledged to serve and protect Riverdale,
not to do your bidding.
Why don't you settle down?
Mmm-hmm.
What's the matter?
You put a hit out on my son,
you bastard.
You think I forgot about that?
Yeah.
Is that why you tried to murder me,
at the behest of my own wife?
Hiram.
FP.
Finish it.
Do it.
- Or get the hell off me.
- FP.
- Come on.
- I'm not gonna do it.
But you deserve it.
Everyone in this room...
Hell, everyone in this town
knows that you deserve it!
Whilst we all tuck into our
delicious homemade meat pies,
might I suggest we reminisce
about some Thanksgivings of yore?
Nana?
Will you regale us?
Well...
There is the story of the first
Blossom Thanksgiving, but...
it's a dark chapter.
Deeply dark.
That's fine.
I'd love to hear more
about your family,
warts and all.
The weather had turned...
and the Blossom settlers were
surprised by...
a sudden, brutal
onset of ice.
Much like tonight.
The wagons were snowed
in, and soon after,
the hunger set in.
Deep.
Aching.
Gnawing.
Stomachs, groaning so loud,
they drowned
out the wind, until...
Until what, Nana?
The Blossoms turned
on one another.
They had to eat their own.
Survive...
on Blossom flesh.
Do you mean... cannibalism?
I can only imagine what a scandal
like that would do to our family name.
Especially, if it were to come
out right as Aunt Cricket were
attempting to negotiate a sale
for our maple business.
Please, no one would
believe that snuff.
I wouldn't be so sure of that.
We Blossoms have always
been highly carnivorous.
I mean...
I ate my brother Julian
in the womb.
And you're eating those meat pies
we prepared especially for you.
My tooth.
What on earth?
What?
Is this Uncle Bedford's ring?
What does this mean?
It means, Aunt Cricket...
that you're welcome
to search the house.
It means that Uncle Bedford...
will never be found.
It means that any evidence
he was ever here...
is in the process of being...
digested.
In other words,
I think you know what it means.
You... You're bluffing.
Not even you are
deranged enough
to commit such an
unspeakable abomination.
On the contrary.
Which reminds me...
it's time for dessert.
T.T.
Face facts, Aunt Cricket.
You and Cousin Fester have just
committed a vile
act of cannibalism,
which is illegal
in this state.
So, unless you want the world
to learn as much,
you will leave us
the hell alone.
You do not knock on my door,
you do not harass my girlfriend.
You do not ask me to sell off
my Blossom legacy ever again.
Are we clear?
Now,
would you like me to pack up the rest
of Bedford for you in Tupperware?
Fester...
There you two are.
We thought you'd been murdered.
No dice on the booze,
I see.
Not a drop to be found.
But I say we keep playing
the game...
and I'll go next.
Never have I ever tried
to cover up a murder.
Oh, you guys are just so cool.
You know that?
You never break into sweat,
never betraying an emotion.
Hell, writing fake suicide
notes, how cool is that?
Well, you guys aren't
as devious as you think.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
left incriminating evidence,
like Mr. Chipping's tiepin.
You went into my room?
It was an accident.
I mean, all the doors look the same.
Between the suicide note
and the tiepin,
you two are trying to cover up
something about Mr. Chipping's suicide.
Or was it a murder?
Care to explain?
You were there, Jones.
You saw him jump.
No one pushed him
out that window.
Not physically.
But psychologically, Mr. Chipping
could have been pushed to the edge.
Donna.
How... Where...
did you get this?
We just wanna know the truth.
Mr. Chipping
gave it to me, okay?
We were having an affair.
I knew
it was wrong.
And I... I didn't want
anybody to get into trouble.
So, I tried to
break it off with him.
But then he got... aggressive.
I was so scared.
I told him, if he didn't stop,
I would go to the headmaster.
And then...
And the next day,
he jumped out of a window.
I can't live my life doing
Hiram's bidding, Alice.
I'm not cut out for it.
There's too much blood on the tracks.
- I hear you.
- I am a Serpent, Alice. I am a Serpent!
Every bone in my body
is a Serpent.
Okay, so is there a rule that
says that you can't be both?
That's not bad.
If Hiram can be mayor
and a kingpin,
who says, that I can't be
sheriff and a gang leader?
How're you feeling, my love?
I think, relieved?
Am I crazy, or did we just
manage to pull our plan off?
The latter.
By morning, Sweetwater
River will have frozen over,
and Aunt Cricket
and Cousin Fester will be back
in whatever ring of hell
they typically inhabit,
digesting those
yummy lamb meat pies.
And Uncle Bedford's name will
never be spoken aloud again.
I do feel some kind of peace,
in some weird way.
We defended our home
from hostile invaders.
And, for the rest
of the weekend,
we have nothing to worry about
but ourselves.
And...
Something I haven't yet said.
I love you.
And I'm so grateful to you.
Yeah, love you too, babe.
And, happy Thanksgiving.
I'm just so confused.
This whole time, Mr. Chipping
was the bad guy? It wasn't Bret,
or Mr. DuPont?
And poor Donna.
I'm not so sure that Donna
isn't playing us, Jug.
What do you mean?
Are you saying
she made all of that up?
Well, I don't wanna say that,
because there's a possibility
that they had
a harrowing affair.
But there's a possibility...
in which the story
that she told me
was just to stall us
from uncovering the real truth.
You should just talk
to your headmaster, Jug.
I mean, get it on his radar
that something
weird is happening
at this school.
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
I will.
Hey, I was thinking, maybe, if the
storm clears up by tomorrow morning,
that we can go home
for the weekend.
Sure, but in the meantime,
how...
How will we stay warm tonight?
Before we start...
We were never
a particularly religious house.
But the one thing
we always did,
the one thing
my husband always liked to do,
when we sat down together
to eat as a family,
was to say grace.
He believed in that.
Archie, would you do
the honors?
Yeah.
Bless us, O Lord, for these,
the gifts which we're about to receive.
For this day, for this food,
for our family, for our friends,
we thank you, Amen.
Amen.
And then he would say...
Dig in, everyone.
We're grateful to be alive,
and to be here with you.
What's this about, Sheriff?
Dodger Dickenson's family
is at large and dangerous,
and we have reason to believe they might
try to get to him, before they skip town.
Well, we monitor our patients
fairly closely.
Well, not closely enough,
huh, Doc?
Ah, excuse me, Headmaster?
What's that all about?
Donna came clean
to the Headmaster
about her affair with Chipping.
How he basically
abused and harassed her.
She was trying to
protect this family,
prevent any further pain,
but after...
Betty broke into her room,
Donna felt like
she had no choice
but to talk
to the authorities about...
all the awful things
Chipping did to her.
Now I guess there's no
doubt about it anymore.
Chipping's death was a suicide,
driven by a guilty man's
fear of exposure.
Case closed, Detective Jones.
Archie...
yesterday was without a doubt
the strangest Thanksgiving
I've ever had.
I mean,
I pointed a gun at a woman.
Welcome to Riverdale, Mom.
But yeah, it's a far cry
from me, you and Dad
just eating fried turkey
and watching football.
He never made it past
the third quarter.
He fell asleep on the couch.
You know,
I've been thinking about...
that deep fryer exploding
when it did.
I mean,
what are the odds of that?
That saved us, Archie.
Yeah, we got lucky, Mom.
No.
That wasn't luck.
That was your dad
watching out for us.
I think you're right.
And that gives me an idea.
What you think, Mom?
Your father never would
have believed this.
Everything you've been building here...
All of you...
He'd be honored
and so proud.
Synchronized by srjanapala
*RIVERDALE (US)*
Season 04  Episode 07