Previosly, on
"Riverdale"...
I'm Charles, your brother.
Hey, your days
of exploiting kids
to do your dirty work
ends tonight.
Didn't we say we were gonna turn this
place into a community center, Red?
Jughead?
Are you my roommate?
So much for a new start.
What... what is this?
Fast-forward.
It's literally six hours...
of our house.
Why would somebody do that?
Film it, and then leave the
evidence on the front doorstep?
To unsettle you.
Let you know
you're being watched.
Yeah,
but why a videotape?
Why something so anachronistic?
Maybe it's just a prank.
If it was...
it was an elaborate one.
Over the next few days,
then weeks,
more and more
citizens of Riverdale
received copies
of similar tapes,
footage of their houses
being watched
from across the street,
for hours
upon hours.
No messages were included
with the videos,
which somehow
made the whole thing
even more disturbing,
so that by Halloween,
the entire town was on edge.
Who would get the next tape?
What did they mean?
Were they a warning?
A test?
Another one?
Keep me updated.
The Muggses also got a tape.
Ooh! I'll get over there
and get an interview with him
for tonight's broadcast.
That's the fringe benefit
of living with the Sheriff.
I get the inside scoop
before any other reporter.
- Mmm-hmm?
- Mmm-hmm.
Hey, Betty, is Jug still
coming home for Halloween?
Yeah, that's the plan,
Mr. Jones.
We're going to
hand out candy and watch scary movies.
Oh!
Why don't you invite
your brother?
Half-brother.
Charles doesn't know
anybody in town.
Okay, well, why is he
still in town?
He's helping me with the tapes
and a couple of other cases.
It's the one good thing that
came out of this nightmare.
Brought the entire
family together.
Except for Jughead,
who's at Stonewall Prep.
And Polly, who's in a
facility being de-programmed.
I think...
it's time, Cheryl.
Time? Time for what?
To say goodbye to Jason.
You've been promising me
for weeks.
I know,
and I'm going to.
But I can't do it
before Halloween.
It's our favorite holiday.
Babe, then you're going to say
the same thing about Thanksgiving.
And then Christmas.
You're not going to
let this go, are you?
Okay, fine.
We'll rebury him on the Blossom family
plot on the grounds of Thornhill.
But I'm warning you...
he's not going to like this.
I'll get the shovels.
Moose, why do you have this?
Oh, just thinking maybe
I'm done with high school.
I mean, I'm 18.
The army doesn't care who
you are or where you're from.
Dude, what Bret did,
spreading that article
about you,
was a real scumbag move.
But you can't let him win.
He wants you to leave.
Hell, he wants
both of us to leave.
Let's not give him
that satisfaction, okay?
It's easy for you to say, Jug.
They're not calling you
"Gargoyle Boy."
Hey! You and you,
I made it very clear
that there will be no costumes
on school property.
Now take off the masks.
Come on.
Hand it over.
Class.
Bee...
you okay?
Um, I'm not going to lie,
I'm a little on edge
this Halloween.
I mean, people are dressed up
like the Black Hood
and the Gargoyle King...
And there are
those damn videotapes.
I'm with you, girl.
Ever since my dad
broke into the Pembrooke,
I've been looking
over my shoulder.
And if the town's got
a voyeur now...
What's up, guys?
Who wants to TP Mr. Honey's
office with me tomorrow night?
Reggie, It's senior year.
We're seniors.
Exactly.
It's senior year.
This is our last Halloween
at Riverdale High.
- I'm in, Reggie.
- Huh? - What? Kev.
Why?
Honey gave me
a week's detention
for going to the bathroom
without a hall pass.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Mmm-hmm.
Yo, Red.
I just got
some distressing news.
You remember that crew that
was working out of the arcade?
Dodger and his boys?
He's still pissed that
he got beat up and jumped by...
that, uh, vigilante.
They're planning on wilding
Halloween night,
looking to bust some heads.
Damn it. The kids in the
neighborhood will be sitting ducks.
We got to do something.
Yeah, I was thinking
the same thing.
Maybe keeping the center
open later than usual.
Why don't you guys host a Halloween
party at the community center?
That'll keep the kids off the
streets and out of harm's way.
And don't worry about costumes.
One of my gal pals
in New York, Katy Keen,
she goes to the High School
of the Performing Arts
and is an amazing designer.
Let me see what she can
whip up for you two.
Yeah, sounds great.
What about you, Jughead?
Which of your
favorite horror writers
did you bring in to share?
I brought the collected works
of HP Lovecraft.
There is nothing scary
about Lovecraft.
Says the guy
that brought in "The Raven"?
My favorite Poe story
is "The Cask of Amontillado."
That's the one where the guy is
sealed behind a wall,
behind bricks,
and then is never seen
or heard from again.
And that would be a horrible way to
go, don't you think, Forsythe?
Just vanish.
Like the Stonewall Four,
you mean?
I'm betting Forsythe could
make it the Stonewall Five.
We're overdue for a vanishing.
Who or what
are the Stonewall Four?
Four students,
all of whom went to this school,
all of whom
Disappeared without a trace.
All at the same time?
No.
Uh, over 30 years or so.
And they didn't
really go "missing."
They dropped out.
So what're you saying?
Stonewall Four
is an urban legend, Jughead.
It's campus lore, that's all.
I'm so proud of you, babe.
You're the strongest person
that I know.
Well, it's not the first time
I've had to bury my brother,
but hopefully it's the last.
Well, it was
the right thing to do.
Cheryl, what's that?
Oh, no.
I was afraid of this.
Of what?
Jason's ghost.
I think he's mad at us
for what you made me do.
I know exactly
where this is going...
the trash.
What are you reading, Jones?
The Stonewall Sentinel.
Coffee?
It's fresh brewed.
Yeah, thanks.
Searching for something
in particular?
Like...
articles about
the Stonewall Four, perhaps?
How'd you guess?
You love a good mystery,
don't you?
I've already searched
through years of articles,
and so far there's nothing
about disappearing students.
My next stop is
the town newspaper office
and the police station.
Jones, are you okay?
Yeah, uh...
I think I...
I think I need some air.
No.
You need to lie down.
Say hello to
the Stonewall Four for us.
*RIVERDALE (US)*
Season 04  Episode 14
Title :"Chapter Sixty-One: Halloween"
Okay, opening my eyes now.
We look ridiculous.
You look adorable,
both of you.
What are our names again?
According to Katy,
you, Archie, are
Pureheart The Powerful,
and you, Munroe,
are The Shield.
Right on.
Uh, Veronica, you need a ride
to the center?
No, I'll take an Uber.
I still have to do
some cleanup over here.
But save a dance for me,
Pureheart, won't ya?
Why aren't you in a costume?
I am. I'm dressed
as Laurie Strode.
Who?
Halloween...
movie...
I got it.
Trick or treat!
You guys look great.
Have fun.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
What time is Jughead
getting here?
Uh, I don't know.
I keep texting him.
Whatever. I'm going upstairs
Minecraft.
Okay.
Happy Halloween to me.
Ow!
Ow.
Ouch.
What?
All right.
All right!
It's really funny.
Let me out now.
Hey!
All right, Bret.
I know you love Edgar Allen Poe.
But trying to prove
that the premature
burial is scary,
the joke is on you because I've
already survived way worse.
Hey!
All right, you sick preppy
bastard, let me out.
Let me out!
Ow!
Hey!
Hello?
Jug? Is that you?
No, Betty, it's me.
Who is this?
You know who this is.
I don't know
what kind of sick joke
you think you're playing,
but the Black Hood is dead.
And I'm calling the police.
Have you checked on
the children lately?
Oh...
I'm sorry, but we're closed.
You know, I've been driving
straight the last 18 hours.
I could really use
a cup of coffee
and a home-cooked meal.
I'll be quick.
I-I'm trying to get home
to my family by daybreak.
Take a seat.
I'll get you a menu.
Thank you.
Eddie...
What the hell?
What are you doing with that?
You know the rules,
you can't have a knife in here.
Hand it over.
- Can I get it back before I go?
- Maybe.
Red, we got trouble
at two o'clock.
Dodger and his crew
just came in.
Crap.
Hey, this is a private event.
Really?
'Cause the sign outside says
it's open to the public.
Not for you and
your crew, Dodger.
Do I know you?
Well, I know that one.
Eddie?
You didn't tell me you
were taking the night off.
Who's handling
business out there
while you're in here,
having a good time?
Time is money.
Come on, let's go.
He's not going
anywhere with you.
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do about
it, Captain Spandex?
I heard you got your ass
kicked not too long ago.
If you'd like a repeat,
I'll happily oblige.
Now, leave.
This is private property.
Be seeing you boys.
You too, Eddie!
Keep moving.
So, what do you think,
Ms. Isley?
Are we ready
for any trick-or-treaters
that might come our way?
Oh, we're ready
for a lot of things
about now...
Ms. Quinn.
And cue the toxic twins.
They're being
fussier than usual.
It must be
the blood moon tonight.
Aren't they with Nana?
They're asleep.
Nana, where's the other
baby monitor?
I heard him crying.
Your brother.
In the chapel.
Okay,
that's not possible.
I threw that doll away!
I told you.
It's Jay-Jay.
He's angry.
And now he's haunting us.
Cheryl, are you messing with me?
On the ashes of Thornhill,
I swear I'm not.
But...
I do think we should have
a Halloween seance
to try to talk to Jason.
Cool. Can we
get outta here, now, Reggie?
Relax, dude.
We're good.
We're golden.
You saw the parking lot.
You, stay here.
Kevin, come with me.
Jellybean?
Are you okay?
Got ya.
You should see your face.
Do not answer that.
Stay in here.
Lock this door.
Listen to me,
you sick son of a bitch.
- I don't know who you are...
- Yes, you do.
Yes, you do.
That's impossible.
I saw you, him...
I saw him die.
You saw what
I wanted you to see.
- Stop lying.
- Tell me, Betty, do you know
where this call is
coming from?
Leave me alone!
It's coming
from inside the house.
Charles.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I was just headed home,
I thought you guys
might want some pizza...
Wha... Is everything okay?
Here you go.
Right off the grill.
I really
appreciate it.
Hey, can I show you something?
It's my family.
My wife and my two little girls.
Aww...
Aren't they angels?
They are,
they're beautiful.
And very lucky to have a father
who's willing to drive
through the night for them.
- I'm gonna get you a refill.
- Thank you.
So, someone pretending
to be the Black Hood
keeps prank-calling you?
Mmm-hmm.
On and off, all night.
You know, um...
I could help you trace the call.
Really? You can do that?
Yeah. Yeah. I've got a unit
in the back of my trunk,
and it would only take
a few minutes to set up.
What do you think?
Let's do it.
I've been reviewing
your records, Kevin.
You've had a rough year. Well...
rough couple of years.
Mmm.
You know, after everything
you've been through,
I can only imagine how
alone you must feel.
Friendless.
Sometimes, yeah.
And it's that vulnerability
that Mr. Mantle exploited,
isn't it?
Ms. Burble tells me
your first choice
for college is NYU.
The theatre program.
It's a great school.
It could be
a fresh start for you.
Sadly, I doubt you'll get in.
Excuse me?
Hmm, well...
Not after
Carrie.
Heathers.
And not after tonight.
It was... It was Reggie's idea.
To... to trash your office.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Okay, Mr. Honey?
No. It's very good, Kevin.
Very good.
That's all I needed to hear.
You can go now.
Talk to me, Eddie.
What's Dodger
got you doing for him?
Running? Collecting?
Stealing hubcaps?
What do you care?
I care because I don't want
you getting in trouble.
Or worse.
Yo, Red, you're gonna
wanna check this out.
- What?
- Some of the kids wanted to go home.
I went outside to make sure
everything was cool and...
And?
There's trouble out front.
Hey, wait, can...
can I bounce?
Hell, no, you're staying here
until the party's over,
and then I'm walking you home.
Hey!
I told you to get outta here.
Nah, it doesn't work
that way.
That crap gym of yours
might be private property,
but this lot isn't.
That's it, I'm done playing.
Yeah, you do that, son!
Come here and get your ass shot.
That would make
our Halloween. Right, boys?
Come on. Come on.
Mr. Jones, it's Archie.
Can you do me a favor
and swing by the gym?
We got a bunch of kids here
and some punks
with guns out front.
Let me know.
What do we do
in the meantime?
We keep the party going,
as late as we have to.
I call upon
the invisible forces
all around us to aide
and guide us through
this communication
with the spirit world.
Is the entity
inside this doll present?
Okay, come on, Cheryl.
Stop moving it.
I would, T.T.,
except, I'm not.
I swear.
Spirit, what is thy name?
I know you're upset
that I made you bury
your dead brother's corpse,
but this is so messed up.
I already told you, it's not me.
It's Jay-Jay's ghost self
trying to engage with us.
This is not Jason, Cheryl.
He's not moving this board.
Antoinette's right.
It's not Jason...
it's Julian.
What do you mean, Nana?
Who is Julian?
Your mother
held three babies in her womb.
Julian was to be your triplet.
But, in the end,
only you and Jason were born.
Because,
as the midwife explained it,
you, Cheryl,
had absorbed the third one.
Eaten it.
That... that can't
possibly be true.
Penelope was devastated.
So she procured this doll
and reared it alongside
the two of you
until you were
no longer infants,
at which point Julian...
was retired...
to the attic.
So...
now that the doll's back,
the spirit of Julian
is haunting Thistlehouse?
What other explanation
could there possibly be?
That you and Nana Rose
are working together.
And to what end would
Nana and I be colluding?
I don't know, babe,
to make me realize that things
were better when Jason was here?
So we dig him back up and
park him at the kitchen table.
Back here in the chapel
would be acceptable.
And if we...
did
bring Jason back home,
would this haunting stop?
Could we get rid of this
creepy-ass doll once and for all
and bury him in Jason's grave?
Yes, T.T.,
I agree to your terms.
You know,
this persona that you've...
cultivated, Mr. Mantle,
this... prankster,
this class clown,
has made it impossible
for your peers and your teachers
to take you seriously.
Do you think
this has anything to do
with your father abusing you?
What?
People won't notice
the bruises or the pain
if they're laughing
at one of your jokes.
Is that the thinking?
Because the thing is...
they're not laughing
with you, Mr. Mantle,
they're laughing at you.
Now, you consider that
as you clean up my office,
and you leave it exactly
as you found it.
We haven't talked much since
everything went down
with the Farm.
Haven't we?
You have every right
to be wary of me.
Starting with the fact
that you let Mom walk
right into the
lion's den with Edgar.
Let the record show
that when I reconnected
with Alice,
and she found out
I worked with the FBI,
she wanted to go undercover.
To help Polly,
to get a story.
What about you?
What do you want?
I guess I've, uh...
I've always wanted
to be part of a real family.
But I know that that takes time.
Um...
Just, um, keep him talking.
Okay.
Hello?
Hello again, Betty.
Who is this?
Don't play dumb.
Sorry.
I just have been getting
a lot of prank calls
tonight pretending to be...
you.
I mean, it is Halloween,
and I do live in the murder house. Right?
You're testing my patience.
You remember Halloween,
don't you?
We used to go
trick-or-treating...
as a family.
You, me, Mom, Polly.
We'd walk up and down
Elm Street.
I remember.
And when we got home,
we would go through our bags of treats.
You didn't want us to eat apples
because you thought there
might be razor blades in them.
Which is...
pretty funny,
all things considered, huh?
- Elizabeth.
- Bye, you sicko.
Did you trace it? The number?
Charles?
What is it?
Where is the call coming from?
Um...
It's...
coming from Shady Grove
Treatment Center,
where your sister's
been staying.
Polly has been prank-calling me?
Well,
I'll call the main line
at Shady Grove and see
- how she got access to a phone.
- No, no, no. Wait.
I have a better idea.
Shady
Grove, how may I assist you?
Hi, I was wondering
if I could speak
to one of your patients, please.
Name of patient?
Polly Cooper.
Who may I ask is calling?
Edgar.
One moment, please.
Edgar? Is it really you?
No, bitch, it's your sister.
What?
Edgar is worm food,
and you're as good as
dead to me now, too.
What? Betty, how could you
pretend to be Edgar?
How could you pretend
to be Dad?
- I... I...
- You are sick, Polly.
Really truly.
So ends the Case
of the Mystery Prank Caller.
You know, I wish
that I could say
tonight's been particularly
insane because it's Halloween,
but no, this is actually
fairly typical.
I'm not usually on kitchen duty,
so I hope
the burger was all right.
Oh, delicious.
Nothing like
a home-cooked meal.
We here at Pop's try.
Any room for dessert?
We have pumpkin pie, homemade.
Oh, well, well,
I will take a slice of that.
- All right.
- Thank you.
We have just
received breaking news.
An extremely dangerous patient
escaped Shady Grove Treatment
Center earlier today.
A serial killer nicknamed
"The Family Man,"
Michael Matthews,
forced his many victims
to cook him meals
before brutally murdering them.
He is of average height
and medium build.
After escaping from Shady Grove,
he killed a trucker
and stole his clothes
and vehicle.
Locker rooms are secure.
Check the bay doors next.
Mr. Jones?
Hey, Red, sorry
it's taken me a minute.
It's been a crazy night,
but I'm pulling up right now.
Okay, great.
Where's Eddie?
I'll check around back.
Hey!
Eddie?
- Eddie?
- I need an ambulance now,
El Royale Boxing Club.
Right now!
You're okay, you're okay.
Hey,
I've been thinking, um,
given how well
you handled yourself
with the Farm, at the motel,
I think you'd make
an excellent candidate
for the Junior
FBI Training Program.
An FBI program
for high schoolers?
Is that actually a thing?
- It is.
- Hmm.
We could work together
trying to figure out
who's sending these videotapes.
You know this town
a whole lot better than I do.
That's true.
Will you consider it, at least?
Looks good, Mr. Mantle.
So, can I go home?
I mean, it's already morning.
As long as we
understand each other,
we can walk
out of here together.
What the hell?
Bella! Bella!
What happened to my car?
It's such a shame when someone
disrespects your property, isn't it?
Wonder who did this.
Probably hooligans
having some...
Halloween fun.
Would you like a ride,
Mr. Mantle?
No.
No, thank you.
Well...
get home safe.
You're home now, Jay-Jay.
For good.
All is right in the world.
Isn't it, my love?
Yep.
Everything's back to normal.
Hey! Hey!
Help! Help!
I'm trapped!
Help me. Help!
Mr. Jones...
Good morning. I, uh...
I see you've been had.
Mr. Chipping...
Where... Where...
I'm always amazed
at my students' antics.
How they get extra...
creative at Halloween.
Creative?
Don't take it
personally, Jughead.
It's a...
Stonewall Prep tradition.
It means you belong now.
Belong to what?
To us, of course.
Here is your phone.
You've got a lot of
missed texts and calls.
Did you know about this?
Absolutely not.
What was even the point of this?
It was just a bit of
Halloween fun, that's all.
What? Did we go too far?
In that case,
you could always...
just leave.
No.
I'm good.
Happy Halloween, kids.
How you feelin', Eddie?
Like I got shot in the leg.
Doctor said it was just
a flesh wound.
You got really lucky.
Eddie, it could've been
a lot worse.
If Dodger and his crew did this,
we can help you.
Me, Munroe, Sheriff Jones.
Help how?
The last thing I need
is for these guys
to think that I snitched,
especially since you
took away my switchblade.
That's not gonna protect
you from guys like Dodger,
but Munroe and I will.
Come hang with us at the center.
They won't step foot
in there ever again.
And then what happens when
the center closes at 10:00?
Where do I go then?
I'm back out on the street
'cause I have to be.
A lot of us are.
I have two options...
either I roll with Dodger
or hide
from Dodger.
That's it.
I can't believe you held
that guy off on your own.
I mean, I can.
You know you're
a total badass, right?
I like to think so.
And how did Pureheart hold up?
Honestly...
I don't know what I'm doing.
I vowed to create a safe space
for the kids in this town,
something my dad
could be proud of.
It's never going to happen
as long as guys like Dodger
are out on the streets.
Okay, so then
we clean up the streets.
Archie...
As well as you fill them out,
you're not actually considering
fighting crime
in those tights, are you?
Of course not.
I'm going to need a mask.
Cheryl?
How was your shower, my love?
Why was this sitting on the bed?
I thought we agreed
to put an end to this.
Jason's back.
You got what you wanted.
Although it pains me
to admit it...
Yes, I was
gaslighting you before.
And for that,
I apologize, but,
I swear,
on Jason's life,
I have no idea
how that got back into this house.
Truly.
Well, then,
how is this happening?
I mean...
We for sure
buried this doll. Right?
I told you...
It's Julian.
T.T.
I'm afraid the true haunting of
Thistlehouse has only just begun.
Moose, you're not
going to believe what Bret...
I mean, it's like
Moose completely vanished.
There's not a trace of him
anywhere, Betty.
Well, is it possible
he actually joined the Army?
I don't know.
I placed a couple calls,
but...
I know it was them
that chased him out of here.
I mean, did they
lock me in that coffin
because they wanted me
out of the way
while they terrorized Moose
into leaving?
I don't know.
I just hate that they
kept me from helping you.
I'm sorry that you had to
go through that alone.
Well, technically,
I wasn't alone.
I was with Charles.
Oh.
So are we warming up
to our half-brother now?
I guess so.
Yeah. Kind of.
He wants me to join
the Junior FBI,
which, I don't know.
I might actually be good at.
Yeah. I think
you would be great at it.
I'm just glad that
Charles was there for you.
Yeah.
He might be the real deal.
Meanwhile, I feel guilty
that I wasn't
there for you, Jug.
No.
Well, actually,
you were there for me.
Thinking about you
was the only thing
that kept me
from losing hope.
And my sanity.
I think deep down,
I know that if I ever
really went missing,
that you would be the one
to find me.
I would, Jug.
I promise.
Synchronized  by  srjanapala