[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
Do you see those people over there?
They're Dodger's family.
I'm not sure what you're here for,
but you and your boys need to leave.
We've got kids here.
We don't want any trouble.
Mr. DuPont, the first book
in the Baxter Brothers series
was written by my grandfather.
I killed Caramel.
[Kevin] No.
Betty, that wasn't you,
that was your deeply screwed-up dad.
Someone is trying to drive me mad,
but once I find out
who this depraved monster is,
I will unleash
a wrath upon them so wicked,
they will wish they had been consumed
in their mother's womb.
You've reached the Riverdale Hotline.
If you wish to report a problem
in your neighborhood, leave a message.
Anonymity is your choice.
We're here to help.
[Jughead] "And as Buddy and Bobby Baxter
sat down at the dining room table,
exhausted and bruised,
they felt satisfaction.
The Case of the Boy in the River
had been solved.
Tomorrow, there would be another mystery,
but tonight,
their only concern was dinner."
Outstanding, Mr. Jones.
I believe the Baxter Brothers has found
their newest ghostwriter.
Wait, I won the contract?
-Like, right this second?
-That is correct.
Professor DuPont,
you can't actually believe that garbage
was better than my submission.
Oh, I can and I do.
Your contract, Mr. Jones.
Your first step into a larger,
better life.
Provided you play by the rules.
I don't understand.
Dartmouth was my safety school.
I guess you should've accepted
Harvard's invitation.
Nice try, Daddy, but I still have
my interview with Columbia.
Interview, huh?
Good luck with that.
Columbia's extremely competitive.
But I believe Riverdale Community College
has a rolling admission policy.
So, if you study there,
you could launch your rum empire,
if that's still happening.
Oh, it's happening, Daddy.
-[door closes]
-[FP] Hey. Wake up, Red.
Mr. Jones? What are you doing here?
Investigating a vigilante.
Now, be honest with me.
-Is that you?
-Yeah, it is.
-You're not gonna arrest me, are you?
-I should.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Helping. People are too scared to call you
or the cops, so I set up a hotline.
What happens if you get hurt or worse?
People die changing tires
on the side of the road, Mr. Jones.
-At least I'd die with a shred of honor.
-[scoffs] What a load of smug BS.
You think that's gonna comfort your mom?
Why aren't you focused on the center,
protecting these kids?
I am, but trouble shows up here
about every other day.
Starting with the Dickensons,
who are still out there, by the way.
You're doing good work here, Red.
Here. Honorable work.
Maybe I can help you.
[Jughead] What do you say, Chuck?
Can you help me?
So, you want me to use FBI resources
to track down your...
Sorry, our grandfather.
Why the sudden urgency?
Well, look, it's probably something
I should've done months ago,
but I have an important decision to make,
and I can't until I know the truth,
his truth.
Can you help me?
[Veronica] What's wrong, Pop?
Our liquor licensed has been revoked.
As of Sunday, the speakeasy won't
be allowed to serve alcohol.
What? According to whom?
-The mayor's office.
-Figures.
This is payback for me vowing
to challenge Daddy's precious rum empire.
Long-term, we're fighting this injunction.
Short-term...
we're hosting a no-holds-barred blowout
at La Bonne Nuit before the boom falls.
No offense, Veronica,
but your father, he wasn't raised right.
Actually, he was.
And you've just given me a great idea.
[creaking]
[Alice] Betty. Betty, wake up.
What? What's happening?
Honey, it's your sister.
She mutilated a nurse at Shady Grove.
She almost clawed her face off.
[Betty] Maybe this is a mistake.
Polly's messed up,
but she's not a literal monster.
This is security footage from Shady Grove.
Okay. Polly's sitting there, looking like
a zombie, but she's not hurt--
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What the hell happened?
She attacked that nurse for no reason.
She'll only talk to you, she says.
And alone.
Okay. Well, then I'll go talk to her.
First, there's one more thing
you should know.
The nurse that Polly disfigured...
her name is Betty.
[Betty] I heard you wanted to speak to me.
Betty. Oh, thank God.
You're the only one I can trust.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Polly, can you tell me what's going on?
You attacked a nurse named Betty.
That's impossible!
I can't remember
any of what they're saying.
I was in the rec room,
and the next thing I remember,
I'm in here and I'm chained to this bed.
Please, Betty.
You have to believe me. Betty, please.
I didn't do this. Please believe me.
I didn't do it, Betty. I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
Please. I didn't do it.
I didn't do this, Betty. I didn't do it!
Damn, Mr. Jones.
Where'd you get a metal detector?
It's from Southside High
when it shut down.
Between that and the security cameras
we're hooking up,
I think you're in pretty good shape, Red.
Yeah, well, I'll be in even better shape
once Dodger and his family are in jail
or out of town.
But all this is awesome. Thank you, sir.
Hey, I can help you find Dodger.
I know the alleys
and a bunch of us used to work for him.
We're good, Eddie.
The last thing I need is you out there
kicking up dust, okay?
[Veronica] I've missed you, Abuelita.
You've been so busy these days,
mi ahijada.
-Godmother...
-Mm-hm.
I've been thinking about expanding
my business,
getting into rum production.
But there's a real craft to it,
and my father refuses to teach me.
How did he learn?
From me. It is my recipe that he's using.
Could you tell me the recipe?
Of course.
But what about college?
Have you heard back from Harvard?
[speaks in Spanish]
You wouldn't even believe the things
that your son has been doing.
What kind of things?
[cell phone buzzes]
Hey, Charles, any luck?
Yeah. I found him.
More specifically,
the U.S. Postal Service did.
Wait, seriously? How?
Evidently, Forsythe has a PO Box
in Seaside.
He checks it once a month
when he comes in from the forest.
Wait, did you say "forest"?
The crazy thing is,
I actually believe her.
Honey, we saw it with our own eyes.
Well, no. Obviously she did it...
but not consciously.
It's like she was fuguing or something.
Wait a minute.
The doctors at Shady Grove
said Polly received a phone call
about an hour or so before the incident.
[phone ringing]
Charles is trying to figure out
the caller's identity.
[Alice] Cooper-Jones residence.
What? Was it about Polly?
What are you doing?
Mom, what are you doing?
Mom!
Listen to-- Mom!
You're acting just like Polly.
You're acting... hypnotized.
[snaps fingers]
What's going on? Why am I holding a knife?
-You don't remember.
-Did somebody...?
-Did the phone ring or did I imagine it?
-No. It rang, you answered. Who--
Whoever called
must have said something that...
I don't know, triggered you
into attacking me. That even possible?
We need Charles to trace that phone call.
[speaks in Spanish]
What a surprise. When did you get here?
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Picking fights with your daughter.
Your father is turning over in his grave.
Really? Turning my own mother against me?
Oh!
And guess what she shared with me.
Our family's secret rum recipe.
So, brace yourself, Daddy, it's on.
[Mary] Archie, I need for you
to sit down for this.
Vic, your dad's foreman,
came by earlier today.
And he wants to buy us out
of Andrews Construction.
Well, tough, Mom,
'cause we're not selling.
And I'll tell Vic that myself
right after I fire his ass.
-Toby, now's not a good time.
-It's about Eddie.
He and Malcolm went looking for Dodger
and his brothers.
-And they found them.
-What? Where are they?
They're beat up, Archie, bad.
Eddie's in the hospital... again.
-[Betty] What'd you find out, Charles?
-Our hunch was right.
The calls received by Polly and Alice came
from the same place:
Shankshaw Prison.
Charles, something must have been said
on those calls
that made Mom and Polly enter
a trancelike state
that turned them into deranged killers...
-as if they were hypnotized.
-I thought the same thing.
And who do we know
that uses auditory cues and hypnotism
to control its members? The Farm.
Edgar may be dead,
but his lovesick lackey Evelyn sure isn't.
She's in prison.
Any chance that prison is Shankshaw?
You hold it right there, boy.
Now, you are trespassing
on private property.
You're Forsythe Jones I,
and I'm your grandson.
I-- I-- I guess you better come in, then.
Jason.
Julian.
Thank you for joining me, brothers.
The day has finally come.
I'm ending our collective misery today.
The Chernobyl-grade roach bombs
I've set up throughout Thistlehouse
are discharging a toxin
strong enough to kill anything
that crawls within these walls.
I was born in poison...
and I shall die in poison.
[coughing]
Mumzie.
What a surprise.
Whatever your dad said about me...
is probably true.
I'm actually not here
to talk about that... yet.
I'm here to talk about
one of your old classmates.
Francis DuPont.
Oh, I remember Francis, all right.
Look, I think you wrote
the original Baxter Brothers book,
not DuPont.
I think he stole your idea
and then he published it under his name.
Well, you got it all figured out,
haven't you, boy?
Except your facts are a little mixed up.
Why don't you help me sort them out?
Eddie and Malcolm are in the hospital.
Munroe is with them.
They went after the Dickenson brothers.
Bill and Fagan beat the living hell
out of those kids.
I'm not gonna let that go.
All right.
All right, then.
Your dad would pound the tar out of me
if I let you do this on your own,
but this is it.
We handle these Dickenson boys
and then you're putting
this vigilante business to bed. All of it.
If I agree...
will you help me?
Yeah.
Just let me get changed first.
[man] That'll do.
All right, I'll take it.
Well, lookie here.
Bill and Fagan Dickenson.
You guys are the scum of the earth.
Going after kids.
[FP] Big men, huh? Beating up teenagers.
Let's see how you do
against someone your own size.
-I'll break your bones, old man.
-Not before we break yours.
[Cheryl] Time to rise and shine,
Mother dear.
[coughs]
Cheryl?
What--?
Did you really think
I was gassing myself to an early grave?
No. That was a ruse.
But riddle me this, Mumzie.
Do you remember when I was a little girl
and you used to read me
Alice's Adventures in Wonderland?
Cheryl, you release me this minute!
You would ask me if I thought I was Alice.
And I would say,
"No, Mother. I'm the Red Queen."
So, as the Red Queen did to Alice,
I am putting you on trial.
[snickers]
Lunatic child.
What are the charges?
They are as follows:
Prolonged gaslighting in hopes
of driving me cuckoo bananas,
attempted murder of Archie, Betty,
Veronica and Jughead,
and actual murder of my father,
Clifford Blossom,
Claudius Blossom and Hal Cooper,
among others.
How do you plead, Mother most foul?
I gotta say...
that felt good.
Yeah? We kicked ass, Mr. Jones.
Mm-hm.
It's been a while since these fists
delivered some proper street justice.
And the old jacket still fits
like a glove.
And your old man, he's looking down on us
probably shaking his head but...
still...
He'd be glad
your crime-fighting days are over.
And I always loved detective stories,
so, uh...
I come up with this notion to write a book
about teenage detectives.
Right, the Baxter Brothers.
So, how did DuPont steal it from you?
No, no. You're getting ahead
of the story here.
You see, I was burning out at Stonewall,
so, uh, I quit.
And the only thing I had to show for it
all was this one Baxter Brothers story.
I didn't know what to do with it.
Francis said he did.
He offered to buy it from me.
How much?
-Five thousand dollars.
-Five thousand dollars?
That franchise is worth millions now.
Over the years, when I saw how popular
the Baxter Brothers became, I grew bitter.
Started drinking,
took my anger out on the world and...
on my son.
Eventually, I figured it'd be best
for all concerned if I just--
Went out for cigarettes
and didn't come back?
Yeah.
Mr. DuPont asked me
to be the next ghostwriter.
Is that a fact?
All this time, I...
I had thought
that Mr. DuPont was killing people
in order to keep the secret
that he stole the book from you.
[chuckles] That's quite
the theory there, boy.
If that was the case,
he would've killed me, too, wouldn't he?
Yeah. Yes.
Word of advice for you:
I messed up my life.
I messed up your father's life.
You seize the opportunities
you're being given.
Took you long enough.
You weaponized my family against me
by calling them and triggering
some post-hypnotic suggestion.
What's the directive?
How exactly are you getting
your sleeper cells to turn?
When I deliver the activation,
the receiver turns into you.
What the hell does that mean?
They become Betty.
As in Betty Cooper. As in... you.
Why did Polly attack a nurse named Betty?
Why did my mom come after me?
When triggered, they become Betty.
They try to kill Dark Betty, Evil Betty,
Other Betty.
You mean, they try to murder me.
Elegant, isn't it?
It was Edgar's idea.
When they hear the trigger word,
they become you,
and therefore try to kill you.
You're a psycho.
[Evelyn] Mm-hm.
So, what exactly is the trigger word,
Evelyn?
Tangerine.
Repeated three times in a row.
Tan--
What do you say we call it a night, Red?
You need a ride back to the center?
Mr. Jones.
[gun cocks]
[people screaming]
[FP groaning]
I can't believe it, Mr. Jones.
I'm so sorry.
For what?
Hey.
It'll take a whole lot more
than a flesh wound
for me to regret what we did tonight.
-It was Dodger Dickenson.
-No, we don't know that.
Yeah, we do.
Word on the street, it was Dodger
and his crazy-ass mom, Darla.
That it was a parting shot
before the Dickensons get out of town.
-So, they're still in Riverdale?
-Yep, loading out the arcade.
How about you keep
your damn mouth shut, Fangs?
You're already on thin ice with me.
And don't even think about it, Red.
We talked about this.
You agreed to hang it up for good.
Hey!
They're leaving town. Archie!
I left before she could say it
a third time,
but what the hell would happen
if I heard the trigger word three times?
Would I be activated
and wanna kill myself?
One way to find out.
We try it here.
Tangerine.
I don't understand.
Nothing happened.
Maybe because you're already Betty?
Well, the good news is,
you're officially not a ticking time bomb.
[Penelope] Why must we endure this farce?
It's clear no matter what I say,
you're just looking
for a reason to kill me, Cheryl.
On the contrary, Mumzie...
despite your wicked machinations,
I'm looking for a reason
to spare your life.
You're my mother.
And yet,
you've always been so cruel to me.
For why?
You brutalized me my entire life,
you tried to kill my friends,
and then you hid in Thistlehouse
to keep torturing me.
You saw me happy with Toni
and you couldn't let that be, could you?
It wasn't your happiness
with the she-goblin
that I wanted to destroy.
It was your happiness with Jason.
How can I live knowing
that you are happy with my dead son?
You don't get what I can't have!
In that case, Mumzie...
you're guilty of the worst crime of all:
being hateful to your rotten core.
Hm. So, there, you've condemned me.
Execute me, then.
Or cart me off to prison.
Oh, no.
Not jail.
At least not in the traditional sense.
You're going to a place so vile,
so revolting,
you'll wish you were bricked up
in Thistlehouse's walls.
Tee-Tee,
prepare the chloroform.
There you go.
Thanks.
You're dressed to kill, mija.
Am I in any danger?
Not tonight.
Just cutting loose
before the clock strikes 12.
-Mmm.
-[Reggie] Hey, Ronnie.
You got someone asking for you,
says it's official.
[jazz music playing over speakers]
Are you a bourbon gal?
I can whip you up a killer old-fashioned.
Veronica Luna?
I'm Shoshana Rutherford.
The recruiter from Columbia?
What are you doing here?
My interview's on Monday.
Your assistant called my assistant
and requested that I come down
and see your thriving business
in action tonight.
I am so sorry, Ms. Rutherford,
for the miscommunication.
But can we talk in a bit? I'm...
-I promised the crowd a floor show.
-Mm.
No!
You don't get to hurt my kids,
shoot someone in front of me
and leave without any payback.
Dodgie.
Care to pump this bozo full of lead
so we can take his truck with us?
No, Mama, it's all right.
Look at him.
Bill and Fagan got their licks in,
didn't they?
But if it's a fight you're after,
let's have ourselves
a good old-fashioned brawl.
[band playing "Saturday Night's Alright
(For Fighting)"]
[singing] ♪ It's getting late
Have you seen my mates? ♪
♪ Ma, tell me when the boys get here ♪
♪ It's 7:00 and I wanna rock ♪
♪ Wanna get a belly full of beer ♪
♪ My old man's drunker
Than a barrel full of monkeys ♪
♪ And my old lady, she don't care ♪
♪ My sister looks cute
In her braces and boots ♪
♪ A handful of grease in her hair ♪
♪ Oh, don't give us none
of your aggravation ♪
♪ We had it with your discipline ♪
♪ Oh, Saturday night's
All right for fighting ♪
♪ Get a little action in ♪
♪ Get about as oiled as a diesel train ♪
♪ Gonna set this dance alight ♪
♪ Well, we're packed pretty tight
In here tonight ♪
♪ I'm looking for a dolly
Who will see me right ♪
♪ I may use a little muscle
To get what I need ♪
♪ I may sink a little drink
And shout out, "She's with me!" ♪
♪ A couple of the sounds
That I really like ♪
♪ Are the sounds of a switchblade
And a motorbike ♪
♪ I'm a juvenile product
Of the working class ♪
♪ Whose best friend floats
In the bottom of a glass ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
♪ Don't give us none of your aggravation ♪
♪ We had it with your discipline ♪
♪ Saturday night's all right
For fighting ♪
♪ Get a little action in ♪
♪ Get about as oiled as a diesel train ♪
♪ Gonna set this dance alight... ♪
Stop!
You'll kill him!
I told Dodger if we ever fought again,
he wouldn't be able to walk.
So, you drag his ass out of here, Darla,
and if you or any of your sons set foot
in this town ever again,
I'll kill all of you.
[Toby] Archie!
♪ Saturday, Saturday ♪
♪ Saturday, Saturday night's all right ♪
[all cheering]
Well, I hope the song and dance was fun
'cause at midnight,
you turn back into a pumpkin, Cenicienta,
and all this, it goes away.
I may not be able to serve rum...
but that won't stop me from making it
and burying you.
Mm.
About that...
Do you know what this is? It's a patent.
That rum recipe that my mother
so graciously gave you?
I own it.
So, if you use it to make rum,
I will sue you for everything you have.
Oh, and good luck with your interview.
I can't wait to hear what Columbia thinks
about underage party-girl Veronica Luna.
Mm.
Hello.
Are you here to kill me?
Like I killed Caramel?
[gasps]
I leave you alone for one day
and you get shot?
Well, I've had worse
and I'll be home tomorrow morning.
Where you been, anyway?
I should probably sit down for this.
I, uh...
I found Grandpa.
He's living in Seaside.
He's in a converted bus.
Sounds about right.
What'd you do that for?
Mr. DuPont offered me
the Baxter Brothers contract.
I wanted to talk to Grandpa
before I signed or not.
-And now that you have?
-It turns out I was wrong.
DuPont did steal the idea from Grandpa,
but he did it legally.
And for what it's worth...
he feels bad about the way he treated you.
He knows what he did to you and Grandma.
-And he knows that he was a bad father.
-Yeah, that he was.
But maybe this wild goose chase
I went on can be worth something.
Like what?
Would you be willing to talk to him
if I brought him here?
Well, doc has me here overnight.
I guess if he wanted to stop by,
I couldn't exactly say no...
could I?
[sighing] Oh.
Hello, Mumzie.
Cheryl?
What is this?
I trust you approve of this bunker.
After all, it's larger than the cell
you would've gotten at Shankshaw.
With food, electricity, plumbing.
You wretched child. You can't keep me...
On the contrary, Mother.
You need time and solitude to seek
penance for your crimes and cruelty.
-Toodles.
-Cheryl. Cheryl?
Cheryl!
[Betty] It was terrifying, Charles.
When I saw the red door, I... fugued.
I slipped into a trance. Why?
It may be a combination
of hearing the trigger earlier
and then returning to a familiar setting.
What I saw...
me about to kill Caramel...
I think that's when
the dark part of me was born.
If that's true,
if you can go back to the moment
of Dark Betty's birth
and stop it from happening...
you'll essentially be--
Killing my shadow self
before she was even born.
Will you try it?
Yeah.
Tangerine. Tangerine.
Tangerine.
[Betty] Wait.
Let me take that from you.
But what am I gonna do now?
You can go play.
Really? I can go and play?
Yeah, go ahead.
Thank you.
Betty.
I'm-- I'm not sure, but I think I did it.
Well, that's great news.
You're all right.
You're okay now.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting,
Ms. Rutherford.
I'm guessing my shot at Columbia
is pretty much blown.
Not necessarily.
At Columbia, we're always looking
for people with good stories.
I don't know what happened here tonight,
but I'll bet it's a good story.
It is, indeed.
Well, how about you tell it to me?
[Toni] Babe, are you okay?
Are you having second thoughts
about your mom?
No, but...
I was ruminating that perhaps...
it's time to bury Jason.
Cheryl, are you sure?
Yes.
There's been so much pain and poison
in this house.
And Jason, more than any of us...
deserves the peace
my mother spent years denying me.
[Mary] Archie?
What's going on, honey?
Why are you sitting in the dark?
What happened?
Who did this to you?
I did.
I did it to me, Mom.
The Dickensons were leaving town.
They were done with Riverdale.
But I wanted to hurt them, to hurt Dodger.
-Maybe even kill him.
-Archie.
It doesn't make any sense to me, Mom.
How predators like Dodger get to live...
but Dad, he...
The worst part about it is some
of the kids from the center were there
and they saw me standing over him, angry.
Bloody.
-Like a monster.
-No.
You're not a monster.
You're just...
still hurting.
When will this end, Mom?
How does this end?
I've never felt further from Dad
than I do now.
Let me guess,
my old man didn't wanna come?
No.
He ran away.
I'm so sorry.
I feel like a fool.
No, you're not.
You would be
if you turned down that contract, though.
No, I'm signing it.
I think it's time to let go of the past.
Evening, Forsythe.
Uh...
This is the part where you kill me?
No, you ass.
It's an initiation.
Welcome to the Quill and Skull Society,
Jones.
[cell phone buzzing]
Cheryl, what's up?
[Cheryl] Thank you all for coming.
You all were here
last time I was at this river.
When I tried to take my own life.
It's only fitting that you're here now...
with my beloved Toni...
as I give Jason...
at long last...
the funeral he deserves.
[sobs]
He was a good brother, Toni.
I wish you could've met him for real.
I know.
[microwave beeps]
[door opens]
Yeah? Can I help you?
Archie? Archie Andrews?
I am.
It's good to see you, son.
My name's Frank.
I'm, uh...
I'm your dad's brother.
Tangerine.
[glass shatters]
Betty?
Honey?
What happened?
I wanted to make sure that it was gone.
The dark part of myself.
And it was.
He's dead.
What did you do, Betty?