[Jughead] "Lynchian."
Adjective to describe something inspired
by the noted American filmmaker,
David Lynch.
And/or to describe something that is both
incredibly macabre and incredibly mundane.
Also, Riverdale's status quo,
reaching new depths of perversion
with the discovery of a videotape
in which someone wearing a mask of me
is bludgeoned to death by someone
wearing a mask of my girlfriend.
Hey. What are you guys watching?
Jellybean, you gotta get out of here.
Sorry, this is NC-17 stuff.
Fine. Whatever.
[Betty] Okay.
So, that was dropped off
at the sheriff's station
in a bin with all
of the other voyeur tapes?
Yeah, but the other tapes were just static
shots of people's houses at a distance.
This is clearly an escalation.
A recreation of whatever someone
thinks happened to me in the woods.
The big questions are, who is doing this
and what are we gonna do about it?
Me? Nothing.
No, I'm not getting pulled
into some creepy new mystery.
But you can feel free
to get sucked into this one, okay?
Could always use an extra set
of eyes and ears, little brother.
[Hiram whistling]
You're unusually chipper today, Daddy.
Mija, I just closed
a major distribution deal.
As of this morning,
I'll be supplying all the rum
for the Grande family's chain of casinos,
up and down the Eastern seaboard.
You're doing business
with Elio's shady ass again?
All I'm doing is selling rum, mija.
And beating you to a market
you hadn't even considered.
I did consider it, weeks ago.
Instead, Red Raven is expanding
into a heretofore untapped market,
the college crowd.
With an affordable version
of our product, Maple Claw.
Good luck with that.
-What's up?
-[Fangs] What's up, Reggie?
What's up is I hear
you two have some scam going
where you're bringing in
some serious bank.
-Are you dealing again, Fangs?
-No. Are you?
No. That's why I'm broke.
And I want in. On whatever you're doing.
So... what's the scam?
We make tickle videos
for a guy named Terry.
Hmm?
And before you assume the worst,
it's not sexual.
No clothes come off at any time.
It's like an endurance sport.
-And this Terry guy pays you?
-[Fangs] Yeah.
And a lot more than dealing.
That's weird as hell, boys.
But... do you think
Terry could use a guy like me?
[playing ballad]
[Betty] Dear diary, today I fell in love
with the boy next door.
He has red hair and freckles
and a scar on his eyebrow
that he got when he fell off his bicycle.
His name is Archie Andrews.
And he has a dog named Vegas,
who is super cute,
but not as cute as Archie.
[knock on door]
-Hey.
-Hi.
-What are you reading?
-Just looking at one of my old diaries.
Ooh, fifth grade. That's juicy.
-Mom, seriously?
-I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, honey, you're so grown up.
I can't believe you're gonna be
leaving for Yale in a few months.
My precious little girl.
Mom, please do not cry.
If you cry, I'm going to cry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What could you possibly cry about, honey?
You have your whole life ahead of you.
Three cases, as ordered.
-Your party will be the hit of frat row.
-Be a bigger hit if you two came.
You ladies supply anything
other than booze?
Ew. Get out of my sight!
Bye!
Honestly, Veronica,
what happened to "quality always"?
Oh, great,
the cast of Swamp Thing just got here.
[Veronica] Welcome.
I don't have any more orders
scheduled for pickup,
but can I help you?
Actually, little lady, we're just, uh,
checking out the competition.
Jinx Malloy of the Malloy family.
Maybe you gals have heard of us?
I'm afraid I canceled my subscription
to Trucker's Weekly.
That's funny.
You know what's not funny?
You bitches are cutting into our profits.
We Malloys have been running
a maple moonshine business
for generations.
And one of our most lucrative markets
is the college scene.
But, recently, we've been getting wind
of a new product that's eating
into our customer base.
"Maple Claw."
Let's say that's true...
what exactly would you like us
to do about that?
-Just pull your product.
-[snickers]
I don't think so.
See, I can guess who you boys work for.
And you can tell him that Veronica Lodge
and Cheryl Blossom
do not back down from a fight.
Now, if you'll excuse us,
we have bottles to fill.
Don't say we didn't warn you.
-What the hell was that?
-That was a bluff.
Trust me, Cheryl,
this is typical of my father.
Last year, he sent thugs in gargoyle masks
to beat up on Reggie.
This year, it's hillbillies who claim
to produce maple moonshine.
The good news is, both drop-off boxes,
the one at the sheriff's station
and the one upstairs,
are under surveillance, 24/7.
So, maybe we can identify the person
who dropped off this faux snuff film.
Well, there's hours of footage.
Does this place have any popcorn?
[kernels popping]
[keypad clicks]
-Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
-What? Do you recognize someone?
Uh, maybe. But I think I'm gonna check
this lead out alone. Is that cool?
Jughead's working late with Charles.
The videotapes.
Veronica's with Cheryl.
Doing her maple rum thing.
Archie...
why are we here?
I don't know.
But it's nice...
right?
It is, but it's not like
we can do anything...
more than this.
What do you mean?
We're just hanging out.
I love Jughead.
And I love Veronica.
But this is nice, right?
What would you say if you were here, Dad?
Probably something corny, like:
"Follow your heart."
The problem is,
I have no idea where it's pointed.
And I don't wanna hurt anyone.
I'm just--
I'm just missing you a lot.
[school bell rings]
[Jughead] Ethel.
Do you have a moment to talk in private?
Jughead. Sure.
This is so unexpected.
Yeah, what can I say?
It's been a pretty weird year.
Hey, I actually wanted to talk to you
about some of those creepy videotapes.
You dropped off a couple
at the station, right?
I did, yeah.
It was just hours and hours
of our house. Nothing new.
There actually was something new
on one of them.
It was footage
of someone dressed up as Betty
murdering someone dressed up
as me with a rock.
-Oh, my God.
-You don't know anything about that?
What? No, of course not.
It's just you're the only person
with a direct connection to Betty and me
who dropped off a tape.
I didn't.
I swear.
I'm just trying to keep my head down
and make it out of Riverdale in one piece.
I didn't make any tape.
[Betty] Dear diary,
today was the happiest day of my life.
After walking home from school,
little Archie proposed to me.
Of course, I want to marry Archie,
but I know we're too young.
So, I told him that he should ask me again
when we're both 18 and in high school.
Everything all right, Betty?
Yeah. Sorry,
I was just... thinking about...
Simpler times?
Simpler times.
[Honey over PA] Betty Cooper
to the principal's office.
Betty Cooper to the principal's office.
-I really hate Mr. Honey.
-Likewise.
Wonder what I did this time.
I'm confused. What is this for?
For the yearbook.
You are editor-in-chief, aren't you?
Appointed last year?
Um, yes.
In between being attacked
by the Black Hood at junior prom
and being hunted by the Gargoyle King
before the Farm was raptured,
I volunteered to be in charge
of the yearbook.
Wonderful.
So...
ticktock.
-So, did you solve the case?
-Unfortunately not.
I had a hunch, but it didn't pan out.
But I did have another thought,
that maybe our suspect is not a voyeur.
Maybe they're a filmmaker.
Whoever made that video had to know
what they were doing,
and they even hired actors.
Plus, the fact that it's all on videotape,
that's the hallmark of a cinephile.
-Let's start at the Bijou theater.
-Yeah.
There's also Paramecium Records
and Blue Velvet Video.
Okay, that was seriously one
of the best videos we've made yet.
Good work.
Especially you, Reggie.
You have a great laugh.
Nice and deep.
Keep this up...
and we're all gonna make a lot of money.
[Reggie] We should go into business
on our own
and ditch this Terry dude.
We don't need him.
This is Terry's operation, Reggie.
If we act as our own distributor,
we don't have to cut anyone in
on our hard-earned bank.
We make our own website,
put it behind a pay wall.
You know, it's not a bad idea, Kevin.
Look, all you have to do
is let Terry down easy.
I'll take care of the rest.
Getting the equipment,
recruiting us some new talent.
This is gonna pay for our community
college education, boys.
[bell jingles]
I can't believe places
like this still exist.
Yeah. Open 24 hours, too.
[man] Can I help you, gentlemen?
[Jughead] Yes, actually.
This is quite the retro vibe
you got going on.
-FBI. Can we ask you a couple questions?
-Sure can.
We assume you know about the videotapes
being delivered around town?
Sure do.
Have you heard anything about them?
Any of your customers acting suspicious?
They all act suspicious.
Can we check your records?
Who's rented what?
Happy to oblige.
[clears throat]
Old-school. I like it.
Each customer gets a page.
The first column is the date
of when they checked out a tape.
Second column is the date
they returned it.
[Charles] Who's E. Muggs?
Looks like they rented
Friday the 13th 16 times.
Oh, that's Ethel Muggs.
She's one of my regulars.
Well, heck, you may know her.
Goes to Riverdale High.
She's a senior, I believe.
Things aren't looking good
for your pal Ethel Muggs.
I admit that renting Friday the 13th
over ten times is excessive,
but it's not a sign of guilt.
I mean, I've seen Eraserhead
more times than I can count.
-Doesn't mean I'm the Man in the Planet.
-She has a predilection for horror films.
She dropped off a videotape
at the station.
You said yourself that she was
obsessed with you, Jughead.
In my book,
that makes her a prime suspect.
Charles, I'm telling you,
it finally seems
like Ethel is in a good place.
And there's more than a hundred tapes.
I don't think she has the bandwidth
or even the equipment
for that kind of operation.
Just move on.
[cell phone buzzing]
[beeps]
Cheryl?
[Cheryl] You need to get to the Maple Club
right the hell now!
Oh, my God.
What the hell happened in here?
We were invaded by those mountain men
you insisted on provoking.
-Who, the Malloys?
-[Penelope] Yes.
I was sleeping in my secret room
behind the office
and heard the door being kicked in.
It's only by the grace of God
they didn't find and molest my Mumzie.
Ms. Blossom, I am so sorry
this happened to you.
I swear, I'm going to murder my father.
You were out early, mija.
No.
I was out late. All night.
Cleaning up the Maple Club after you sent
those hillbilly Malloys to trash it.
What?
I did no such thing.
I would never do business
with the Malloys.
They're ruthless competitors.
They're dangerous.
Did Jinx's boys threaten you?
If he threatened you--
No, no. If you didn't start this,
then it's none of your concern, okay?
Do not underestimate the Malloys.
I've tangled with them.
Let me help you deal with this, okay?
I'll settle whatever dispute
you have with them.
Absolutely not, Daddy.
This is my business, my war,
and I'm gonna win it on my terms.
Besides, if the Malloys are as dangerous
as you're insinuating,
you may not be strong enough
to go up against them.
[playing ballad]
[mouthing words]
[humming]
[Betty] Dear diary,
today was the best day ever.
Archie asked if I wanted to come over
and listen to records.
I said, yes, of course.
♪ We used to laugh with joy ♪
Turns out the records were his dad's,
but they were still pretty cool.
[knock on door]
Archie, what are you doing here?
Kev told me that Honey's making you do
the yearbook. I wanna help you.
No.
Arch, you're not helping me
with the yearbook,
and that's... not why you're here.
Okay, you're right.
Honestly, I can't stop thinking
about you, Betty.
I've tried, but it's impossible.
Archie, we can't do this.
Not here.
Wait, "not here"? So, that means you--?
I can't stop thinking about you either.
So, maybe...
-We meet tonight. At the bunker, maybe?
-No, not, not--
Not tonight. Tomorrow night.
So, we have time to think about this...
and make sure it's what we really want.
Tomorrow night.
That actually, uh, gives me a little time
to do something, finish something.
Okay.
[school bell rings]
Hi, Miss Bell.
As a senior I should probably know this,
but does this school have an AV Club?
We do, Mr. Jones.
And can anyone get access
to the equipment?
I mean, I assume they have,
like, video cameras and VCRs.
Oh, yes.
But only AV Club members
are allowed to use it.
-Is Ethel Muggs a member of the AV Club?
-She's the president.
How funny.
You're the second person
to ask me that today.
The first was a handsome FBI agent.
Where is he now?
I believe I saw him leaving with Ethel.
Thanks for meeting with me, Terry. Look...
I appreciate all the opportunities
you've given me,
but I think it's time
that I stop making videos with you.
Why?
You're in your prime.
I just--
I'm stressed that somehow
my dad is gonna find out.
And with graduation and college coming up,
I just-- I wanna be done.
That's all.
Okay, Kev.
Okay. I understand.
But if you change your mind...
you know where to find me.
-So, like, we'd be tickling each other?
-Exactly.
I don't know, dude.
It sounds kind of weird.
It's not, believe me.
And, fellas, we are talking
some serious money here.
Maybe if it was like coed,
we could be down.
I think that could be arranged.
[Toni] No freaking way.
I'm not letting your mangy Bulldogs
paw my girlfriend's Vixens
while she's dealing with a maple crisis.
-She would kill me.
-Fine.
If you wanna laugh in the face
of cold hard cash, be my guest.
Hold on a second, Reggie.
I have a counterproposal.
How about the Vixens tickle
the Bulldogs exclusively?
And that way the girls will be in charge,
like it should be.
All right, all right!
It is time to choose our first contestant.
[all cheering]
Our first lucky Bulldog on defense is...
Jimmy!
Okay. And the first Vixen
doing the tickling is...
Audrey!
Okay!
Let the tickle games begin.
[all cheering]
Audrey, Jimmy, follow me
to the Tickle Suite please.
[rock music playing inside pub]
[Hiram] Hunter Malloy.
You threaten my daughter?
You hillbilly scum.
Who?
You mean that sweet rum-runner girl?
We tried talking to her.
What can I say? Some tramps need
more of a hands-on approach.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Okay, I'm sorry! I was kidding.
-Face the wall.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't do it. Please don't do it.
You're Hiram Lodge, right?
I know all about you.
Please, we won't mess with you again.
We'll leave your daughter alone.
We won't disrespect you again,
man, please.
Please.
Thank you. Thank you.
You and your entire clan, you stay away
from my daughter and her friends.
-Are we clear?
-Yes, sir.
[Hunter] You like that, huh?
Where the hell have you been?
Where's Ethel?
At home, with her parents.
I told you that she's not our voyeur.
[scoffs]
What is this?
We searched Ethel's house,
and we found it.
Watch it. Then we can talk about whether
you still believe Ethel's innocent.
Mom? Dad?
Daddy?
Oh, my God.
Ow.
What happened, Daddy?
What did you do?
I was weak, mija.
I had one of the Malloy boys in my sights.
I could have taken him out,
but I showed mercy.
A weakness of will
that I quickly came to regret.
Daddy, it's okay.
I'm always here for you.
[Betty] Dear diary,
I hate, hate, hate Cheryl Blossom.
She made Archie kiss her at school today.
She said it's because
they both have red hair,
which makes absolutely no sense.
[Cheryl] Lost in reverie, cousin?
Hey, Cheryl. Did you come
to drop off your yearbook photos?
Yes. And about that,
I'll be needing two pages.
Uh, it's one page per senior.
Yes, and for average humans,
that would suffice.
But I'd like to pay tribute to Jay-Jay.
Okay, fine. Whatever.
What's wrong, cousin?
Trip down memory lane gotten you blue?
Cheryl, give it back.
My goodness!
I had no idea how much you hated me
back in the day.
And all because I snuck a kiss with--
Wait.
I was right, wasn't I?
When I said you and Archie were doing
more than just pretending to date
-when Jughead was dead?
-No.
That was obviously pretend.
-But have you...?
-No!
No, we haven't.
But I think a part of me has been in love
with Archie for ten years, Cheryl.
False.
You've been in love
with the idea of Archie.
The idea of the perfect romance.
But... that wasn't real.
That was fantasy.
But in this town of nightmares,
you and Jughead found each other.
That's real.
That's maybe even...
dare I say, endgame?
Who knows?
People stray, it happens.
The trick is...
stop straying before anyone gets hurt.
Or even better,
stop before you even start.
[oldies playing over speakers]
[bell jingles]
What the hell?
-You've been a naughty boy, Kevin.
-Terry?
You lied to me.
You weren't getting out
of the tickle business.
You were setting up your own shop.
We don't wanna make trouble.
You already did.
So...
[Kevin groans]
...here's how you're going to fix this.
You and your buddies will give us
40 percent of your profits.
I'll have to talk to my partners.
[whimpers]
Forty percent.
Or you'll never tickle anyone ever again.
Okay, okay. Terry, I get it. Jeez.
[students chattering]
Hey, Ethel.
Got a minute?
This is a sex tape
of me and my girlfriend,
filmed without our consent
at Stonewall Prep.
And Charles found it
while searching your house.
I stood up for you, Ethel.
I believed you.
And you had this tape the whole time?
-Where did you even get this? From Bret?
-No.
There's a place in the back
of the Blue Velvet Video store.
A secret place.
-It's called the Scarlet Suite.
-Uh-huh.
And what's in this Scarlet Suite?
Tapes.
Rougher ones, weirder ones, homemade.
Like the voyeur tapes?
And darker stuff.
Like... sex tapes.
Maybe even snuff films, I heard.
That's where this was?
The video was called Ponytail Playmate.
I thought it sounded fun,
but the second I saw what it was,
I swear I turned it off.
And I kept it because I didn't want
anyone else to get their hands on it.
Please, you have to believe me.
Go to the Scarlet Suite, Jughead.
You'll find what you're looking for.
[Kevin] Shut everything down, ASAP.
We can't.
Our videos are already uploaded.
And we're a hit, bro.
A big, fat, stinking hit.
Then we need to give Terry a cut.
-No.
-Just a taste.
No way. This is our thing, not his.
And I know how to handle Terry.
All I need you to do
is set up a meeting with him
at the Five Seasons.
I got your back, bro, trust me.
[bell jingles]
How can I help you fellas?
You can keep out of our way.
We have a warrant to search your store.
[Jughead] What?
What is it, Jughead?
Hey, only 18 and over allowed back here.
Where'd you get this?
People come in selling and trading
all kinds of tapes.
This is a video of Clifford Blossom
shooting his son Jason Blossom.
It's an actual snuff film.
Hmph.
This is making a lot more sense now.
You boys better have my 40 percent.
[whistles]
You know, if you'd asked
for 10 percent... maybe.
But you got greedy.
So, here are our terms.
You get zilch.
And if any of your goons so much as touch
a hair on my boy Kevin's head,
me and the Dogs will break
a lot more than your fingers.
You boys just made a big mistake.
[Cheryl] I'm so sorry about your dad,
but I got into this business for fun.
To do something fun with you.
And it was, for a while.
But some families have rum in their veins
and other families have maple syrup.
And some blood types
simply aren't compatible.
In other words, partner, I want out.
Effective immediately.
Okay.
[school bell rings]
You asked to see us, Mr. Honey?
I did.
Earlier, I received a troubling phone call
alerting me of a...
clandestine, online tickling ring,
apparently being operated by students
from Riverdale High.
You care to comment on this?
Was it some Terry guy who called you?
It doesn't matter who it was, Mr. Mantle.
Is it true?
You know what, Mr. Honey?
Yeah... we did produce the videos.
And there's nothing wrong with it
because it's just tickling.
-And what we did doesn't break any laws.
-[Reggie] Yeah.
And we were all wearing clothes.
Yes, you were, Mr. Mantle.
In fact, some of you were
wearing Bulldog jerseys
and Vixen practice uniforms,
putting you in violation of at least
a dozen legal and copyright laws.
Not to mention...
under my direct jurisdiction.
Which means, I want your degenerate
website taken down immediately
before it tarnishes
the reputation of this school.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Now get out of my sight.
[Archie] I wanted
to share something with you.
What is it?
It's a song I wrote. For you.
[playing ballad]
[singing] ♪ There's no warning
When everything changes ♪
♪ You let down your guard
And I saw something strange ♪
♪ I thought
"She's not made for this world ♪
♪ And neither am I" ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me-- ♪
Stop.
What? What is it?
-You don't like it?
-No.
This-- It's us.
It's us.
I love Jughead.
And you love Veronica, don't you?
But then, what has this all been about?
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe it's
because everything's changing
in the next few weeks.
And you and I feel safe with each other.
We always have.
I don't know.
But I do not wanna hurt or lose Jughead.
I don't wanna lose
or hurt Veronica either. I--
So, whatever this is...
or it was...
it's just over.
[playing ballad]
[Mary] I love that song, Archie.
Sounds like you wrote it
for someone special.
Has Veronica heard it yet?
Uh, no, not yet. It's a surprise.
Well, she's gonna love it.
Hey, Mom.
If it's not too late...
I'm ready to get serious
about the Naval Academy.
That's wonderful news, Archie.
And, uh, I know I've been
kind of flaky lately...
but I'm all in now, I promise.
It's time for a completely fresh start.
Well, I will call Brooke
and tell her the good news.
[door opens]
[Alice] Elizabeth.
What are you doing, honey?
Exorcising my demons.
Oh, but these are your diaries.
These are your childhood memories, honey.
They're precious.
Well, that's all they are, Mom.
Memories.
Why don't we save this one?
It's okay to keep one, if you want.
Yeah.
Right. One is fine.
Thank you.
[Fangs] So, what's next?
Graduation.
Carnegie Mellon.
So, I got
into the University of Pittsburgh.
You did?
You wanna go there? Why?
Because they gave me a scholarship.
And...
because it's close to Carnegie Mellon.
I wonder what it'd be like for us
to date somewhere that's not in Riverdale.
Yeah, I've been...
I've been wondering that, too.
And...
maybe we find out.
Yeah, maybe we do.
Mmm.
So...
do you think Reggie was right
that it was Terry that called Mr. Honey?
Probably.
I mean, how else would Mr. Honey find out
about a clandestine tickling ring?
[man] Sorry, Holden.
The Scarlet Suite's closed
until further notice.
-What happened?
-The FBI raided me.
All my contraband's been confiscated.
I was just released myself.
I'm sorry to hear that, David.
Well...
it's probably for the best.
I must admit, I'm surprised.
I know it's been a while since
I last came to you asking for money,
but this will allow me to buy Cheryl
out of the maple rum business.
You refused my help numerous times,
as I recall.
Yes. But the reasons I didn't
wanna get into business with you
were your... immoral ways.
What happened when you spared
that Malloy troll...
you said it revealed that you were weak.
But I think it did the exact opposite.
It took strength for you
to not go back to your old habits,
and I'm proud of you for it.
I shouldn't have gone
after one of your sons, Jinx.
It was out of line.
Hiram Lodge, you ought to know by now.
You never turn your back on a Malloy.
Lesson learned.
It showed me that you have
finally, truly turned over a new leaf.
I have, mija.
And might I add, it's a pleasure
doing business with you again.
-It was actually called Ponytail Playmate?
-Yeah.
Just when we thought Bret Weston Wallis
couldn't be any more of a creep, huh?
[cell phone buzzing]
Cheryl's calling me.
[beeps]
Hello?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Cheryl just got sent another tape.
She wants me to come over.
Oh, wow.
Well, I know
you swore off mysteries, but--
No.
I'm in.
Well, well.
Dream team back together again.
It was sitting on my doormat
when we got home.
We thought it was gonna be like
the other tapes at first.
Why me?
Why are they coming after me?
It's not just you, Cheryl.
I got one, too.
I have a feeling we're only the first.