[Jughead] It's been a quiet few months
in Riverdale.
Spring slid into summer,
and some semblance of normal life resumed.
The terrors of the Farm weren't forgotten,
but they had started to fade.
Gryphons and Gargoyles was already
becoming the stuff of suburban legend.
Indeed, the big topic of conversation
around town was July 4th.
After some debate, it was decided
that there would be an Independence Day
parade down Main Street,
Riverdale's first in three years.
But there would be no fireworks display
over Sweetwater River.
The Blossoms used to sponsor them,
but without their support,
the town couldn't afford them.
Like I said...
things had been pretty quiet lately.
Enough that I'd actually gotten
some real writing done.
It's beautiful.
-It's a beautiful story, Jug.
-Really?
You think it's worth submitting
to the contest?
No, I think it's gonna win the contest.
I love you.
I love you, too.
[Veronica] Can we just stay
in bed forever?
[Archie chuckles]
And if not forever, at least for the day?
I would.
But don't we have to finish building a
float for your big Fourth of July parade?
It's not my parade, it's the town's.
Pop's is only sponsoring it.
Well, if not the day...
how about another hour?
Hell, yeah.
Okay, then.
Good morning, Jay-Jay.
Let's see what the hot gossip in town
is today.
And then we'll do the cross... word.
What the hell?
Over my dead body!
♪ All my friends are watching,
I can hear them talking ♪
♪ Tell me what's going on ♪
[tires screech]
Well, well, well...
Stop the presses.
The Riverdale rag finally reported
a story accurately.
Not only is there going to be
some hideous,
janky parade snaking its way through town,
you four are the architects
of this outrage.
-What's your problem, Cheryl?
-My problem, Veronica,
is that the Fourth of July
is a day of tragedy for Riverdale,
not celebration.
Or have you forgotten what happened
to my poor brother Jason.
Cheryl, Riverdale hasn't held a parade
out of respect
for what happened to your brother
in... like, years.
I think it's time.
I mean... you don't have to come.
Oh, I'll be there, insufferable Smurf.
Front and center.
With a sign of protest in one hand
and a horn of compressed air
to silence any revelry in the other.
[car engine starts]
Great.
[tires screech]
Anyone hungry for breakfast?
So, camping this weekend, are we still on?
I'm open, but what are we
talking about here? Like...
[chuckles] The woods.
But remember, this could... possibly be
our last summer to do this
because next year
we'll be getting ready to go to college.
And if anyone is scared of bears, well,
don't be, because Archie's been attacked,
like, what, multiple times
and still survived?
Hey, I wear my scars proudly.
[cell phone buzzing]
Hey, Dad.
Archie.
[whines]
I-- I talked to the sheriff
up in Cherry Creek.
Sounds like... what happened was
Fred was... driving home to Riverdale
when he...
He pulled over to help someone whose car
had stalled on the side of the road and...
another vehicle... came up on them
way too fast and-- And--
And he was struck by it.
No.
I'm sorry, Mary.
I'm sorry, Archie.
Did the other car stop?
The one that...?
So, it was a hit-and-run.
We have to find out who did it.
We have to catch them.
[FP] No, Red.
You don't even think about that right now.
I'll work with the sheriff's office
up in Cherry Creek
and make sure all this is taken care of.
You understand?
So, what happens now?
[woman] Have you decided on a burial
or a cremation?
Burial.
There's a plot next to his father,
Artie Andrews. Arthur Andrews.
Since we're transporting the body
from upstate,
there will be an additional cost
of $9,000.
Whatever needs to be done.
However much it costs.
The driver that makes these trips for us
isn't available until July 5th
because of the holiday.
Then we'll have the internment on the 6th,
if that's all right.
Hey. You remember that tree house
your dad helped us build?
-You mean the one he built for us?
-I remember you fell out of it, Reg.
And broke my arm.
Your dad drove me to the hospital.
[Reggie chuckles]
I remember this one time...
This time, we were having a picnic
when we were still in grade school
in Pickens Park,
and there was a father-daughter
potato-sack race.
My dad...
I don't know where he was, but Mr. Andrews
said that he would do it with me.
So, he was-- He was my dad for the day.
When things started getting bad
with my dad and drinking,
my mom would call up Fred... for help.
And he would drive to the bar,
and he would pick up my dad
and he'd lay him on the couch.
But he'd always stay a little while.
Just to talk to me.
To see how I was doing in school
and... if I had eaten dinner.
He just wanted to know if I was hungry.
I always was.
Your dad was such a gentleman, Archie.
He was the best.
He built and donated all the sets
for the musicals.
You don't have to, but...
do you have any memories you wanna share?
I remember going to...
Going to Sears with him.
Just so I could ride the tractors.
He taught me everything.
Taught me how to play football
and baseball.
Pretty much every other sport.
We fixed up the-- The jalopy together.
He bought me my first guitar.
He even soundproofed the garage just so...
[Veronica] Hey. Archie.
I'm good. I just...
I'm wiped out, you guys.
Can we call it a day?
Yeah.
[indistinct chattering]
Grandpa Artie?
Archie.
Everyone's waiting.
Where's your dad?
I thought...
-I thought he was already with you.
-No. No.
Come see for yourself.
Where's Dad?
Archie... you were supposed to get him.
[panting]
Archie?
I have to go get my dad.
What? What do you mean?
I have to bring him home.
She's all yours, bro.
How do you even have a hearse, Reggie?
It's been sitting on the lot for years.
No one wants to buy it.
Well, I owe you, Reg. Thank you.
And, you guys,
I'm sorry for calling so late.
It's really not a problem, man.
I just-- I don't want my dad stuck
in some weird town.
And I can't wait for after July 4th
for them to bring him back.
He'd wanna be home, I know that.
Hi. I'm Archie Andrews.
My dad, Fred Andrews, was in an accident
on the freeway yesterday.
Oh, yeah. I heard about that.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you, ma'am.
I was wondering
if you found the person responsible yet.
We got a description
of the car that hit your dad.
The make and the model,
but no plate number.
Nothing yet, but we're not giving up.
Okay.
[cell phone buzzes]
Hello?
What happened to my dad's truck?
It's still at the accident site,
parked on the side of the road.
Okay.
Would you mind showing me where that is?
It's a few miles south on Route 80.
Right about... here.
The keys are with the rest of your
father's belonging's at the funeral home.
Okay.
That was them, actually.
They're ready for us.
-Thank you, deputy.
-Of course.
You hang in there, okay?
Thank you.
Hi. Good morning.
I'm Veronica Lodge. We just spoke.
-This is Archie Andrews. He's--
-I'm Fred Andrews' son.
Yes. Of course. My condolences.
How can I help you, Mr. Andrews?
I wanna bring my dad home.
It was my understanding
the deceased would be transported
to Riverdale on the 5th.
I know. It's-- It's not right. I--
I want him home.
And I wanna be the one
who brings him home, today.
I understand.
But I'm afraid that's not possible.
[telephone rings]
-Hello?
-[Archie] Hey, Mom.
Archie?
Aren't you upstairs in your bedroom?
No, I'm in Cherry Creek.
I came up to pick up Dad.
What?
I'm sorry, I didn't think.
The funeral home up here
won't release Dad to me.
Something about me being underage.
Please.
I really don't wanna leave Dad here.
Put me on the phone
with whoever's in charge.
I see.
No, that won't be necessary, Mrs. Andrews.
Of course. I'll just need you
to sign an authorization form and--
Nope. I'll do it right now.
Thank you.
I'll just go
get your father's personal effects, then.
-There was a set of truck keys.
-They're in there.
I'm going to need two to three hours
to get him ready for transport.
You can wait here
or you can come back at noon.
Can I see him?
Archie, you don't have to.
What if they made a mistake, you guys?
-I'd like to see my father.
-Of course.
He's just in the next room,
if you'd like to follow me.
Archie.
I thought--
Archie changed his mind.
But he asked us to make sure it's him.
-Jug, one thing you can help me with:
-Anything.
My dad's obituary.
Could you write it? For the Register?
Of course.
Is it him?
Yes. It is.
I have his belongings.
Are you sure?
Yeah, Arch.
It's your dad.
Mrs. Andrews, we heard the news,
and we're so, so sorry about Mr. Andrews.
Thank you.
Mrs. Andrews.
When my brother Jason died,
I felt supremely alone.
My world was only darkness and despair.
I don't want you or Archie to ever feel
anything even remotely like that.
So... with your blessing,
there's something I'd like to do
for your family.
For when Archie returns.
[car approaches]
Can we help you?
No, I'm just paying my respects.
How do you know what happened here?
Wait, are--?
Are you Archie?
How do you know my name?
Your father told me.
One of my tires blew,
and... I was stranded out here.
You're the one he was helping.
[sobs] I mean, cars just--
You know, they kept...
They kept whizzing by.
Nobody would stop, but your dad did.
He talked about you the entire time.
His-- His son.
How...
he couldn't believe a man like him was
blessed with such a thoughtful, kind boy.
You were with him when he...?
We were working on the tire.
And a car just...
It came out of nowhere.
It-- Speeding, and...
I'm sorry, I just...
I froze in its path,
and your dad, he just--
He pushed me out of the way.
He saved my life.
And...
if he hadn't done what he did,
there's no way that I would be here
right now. I know that.
I am so sorry.
There's nothing I can do
to ever repay him, but--
But I would like to say a prayer for him.
Maybe you'd like to join me?
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread...
and forgive us for our trespasses...
as we forgive those...
who trespass against us.
Lead us not to temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
For thine is the kingdom, the power,
the glory, forever and ever.
Amen.
♪ I don't know what to say ♪
♪ 'Cause you're lookin' away ♪
Guys, my dad saved that woman's life.
A total stranger.
And he sacrificed himself for her.
That's an incredible thing, Archie.
He died a hero.
Why did he have to be one?
Why this time?
Why c-- Why did he have to stop?
Why couldn't he have kept driving
like everyone else?
Because your dad helped people.
-That's just who he was.
-Yeah, and it got him killed.
I mean, he died on the side of the road.
Waiting for an ambulance,
without his family, without his friends.
I'm sorry, but that's not heroic, that's--
That's senseless.
I promise you... that is not true.
-Arch?
-I'm just going outside. Need some air.
[cell phone buzzing]
[FP] Archie?
Yeah. Yes.
-They found him.
-What?
-The guy who killed my dad?
-Yeah, he turned himself in an hour ago.
Who is he, Mr. Jones?
His name's George Augustine.
He lives in Cherry Creek. No priors.
-Is he in jail?
-No, he...
-He made bail. He was released.
-What? He's out?
He should be rotting in a cell, Mr. Jones.
He will be, but this is how it works.
And for what it's worth, the chief told me
the guy's real broken up about it, so...
He killed my father.
Your dad's gonna get justice,
I promise you.
Yeah, you're right, he will get justice.
Archie. Where are you?
Yes, can I help you?
-Are you George Augustine?
-Yes. What can I--?
Fred Andrews.
-Wha--? Wait.
-That's the man you killed.
My father.
Fred Andrews.
You hit him with your car
and you kept driving.
You left him there to die. You coward!
S-- Son, listen.
-I was just--
-No! Shut up!
You took away the only man
who can call me that.
Why did you do it?
Huh?
Were you on your phone? Were you drunk?
What were you doing when you murdered him?
Tell me.
-Tell me or I swear I--
-[boy] Please, stop!
He didn't do it.
-What?
-He didn't do anything wrong.
[George] Jeffrey, get upstairs.
What's he saying? What do you mean?
He told the police he did it.
To protect me, but it wasn't him.
Okay, it wa-- Yeah, it was me.
It was my fault.
I took the car when I wasn't supposed to.
I-- I-- I--
I-- I don't even have my license.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[car doors shut]
-Archie.
-You had us really worried.
You okay?
How'd you know where I was?
My dad called. He had a bad feeling.
What happened?
I...
I came looking for...
He's just this dumb kid.
-Who is?
-The kid driving the car that hit my dad.
He's just stupid.
Terrified.
That's something that I would have done.
Taking the car out without permission.
Hell, I did it a dozen times,
and his dad was...
Was protecting him.
The same way mine would have.
I don't know what the hell I'm doing,
you guys. I can't believe I'm here.
I can't believe I did this.
I'm a terrible son.
You're not a terrible son.
I just went into a stranger's house
and almost hurt an innocent man.
I think... your father would understand...
under these circumstances.
All we ever did was fight, Ronnie.
I lied to him constantly.
He would be ashamed of me.
I'm ashamed of me.
Archie, listen to me.
Your dad loved you... more than anyone
and anything else.
Whenever he looked at you...
there was pride in his eyes.
He was proud of you.
[sighs]
-I don't know what to do.
-I do.
Come here.
You're gonna finish what you started.
You're gonna bring your dad home.
Okay.
The hearse is behind the funeral home,
ready to go. Ronnie and I will take it.
-You guys take my dad's truck back?
-Of course, Arch.
Yeah. We'll just follow you guys.
Thanks.
-Everything all right, Mr. Jones?
-Everything's good, Red. I...
I heard what you and Jug and the girls
were up to
and I wanted to be a part of it.
I'd like to give your dad a police escort
the rest of the way home,
if you're okay with that.
He deserves it.
-Yes, sir.
-All right.
-Follow me then?
-Yeah.
-I couldn't leave him there, Mom.
-I know.
I brought Dad home.
You did.
You sure did.
I'm so proud of you.
I know he would be, too.
[Josie] ♪ Amazing Grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch like me ♪
♪ I once was lost ♪
♪ But now am found ♪
♪ T'was blind but now I see ♪
And now... Fred's son, Archie,
would like to say a few words.
[sniffs]
[sighs]
Earlier, I was thinking...
on the drive over here...
how much of Riverdale my dad built.
Or just fixed up.
Houses, office buildings.
A bit of everything.
He helped build this town.
And one day, if I'm lucky enough
to have a son or a daughter of my own...
I'll be able to point to a building...
or even just a brick in a building
and say:
"Your grandpa made that...
with his hands."
It's the Fourth of July.
I remember this one Fourth...
it was raining.
The fireworks show was canceled.
And I was so bummed,
I remember sitting in the backyard
just balling...
until my dad came home
with all these fireworks.
I mean, enough to burn a house down.
You remember that, Mom?
And...
we lit them in the backyard.
It was just-- It was the best night.
My dad was there
for every high and every low.
He's the greatest man I've ever known.
It hurts me
that I never got to say goodbye...
that I won't get to see him again
or talk to him...
but his spirit and his memory lives on
in this town and in everyone he's met.
Fred Andrews will always be a part
of Riverdale.
I love you so much, Dad.
-Excuse me. Mrs. Fisher?
-Oh.
-Wonderful service, didn't you think?
-Yes. It was.
-I'd like to discuss the payment with you.
-It's already been taken care of.
By Mrs. Andrews?
-I didn't want her paying for any of this.
-No, by your father.
He paid the bill in full.
[Jughead] How do you sum up the life
of a man like Fred Andrews?
You could start with the facts.
That he was born
at Riverdale General Hospital.
That his parents
were Arthur and Virginia Andrews.
That he led
the Riverdale High baseball team
to two consecutive state championships.
Took over the family business at 18,
got married, had a son, settled down.
And while others were rushing
to get out of Riverdale,
Fred was setting down roots.
When our town saw a pariah
and closed its doors,
Fred saw a lost soul and opened his.
There was always room at his table,
in his home, for others.
Whenever our town was under attack,
Fred was on the front line,
fighting for it, defending it.
He was our Good Samaritan,
our George Bailey,
our knight in flannel armor.
And by the way,
he was a hell of a good tipper.
Damn right, he was.
Fred left Riverdale better
than when he found it.
That's his legacy.
Mom.
We're about to start. Are you ready?
[chattering]
[Arlo Guthrie's "I'm Going Home" playing]
♪ Like the tree that grows so tall ♪
♪ Leaves turn gold and then they fall ♪
♪ They've gone down,
But now they've grown ♪
♪ They're going home ♪
♪ Mountain streams may run and flow ♪
Imagine if everyone was even half as good
as my dad was.
You already are, Archie.
No, not yet.
But I'm gonna honor him.
I'm gonna honor his memory every day.
[inaudible dialogue]
[sobbing]