Previously on Riverdale...
What were you doing in there?
I was... praying.
My team's been investigating Edgar
Evernever for quite some time now.
We had someone on the inside,
someone tasked with
getting close to Edgar.
My mother is an FBI informant?
Charles, what if that
means she's been found out?
You should go to Stonewall Prep, Jug.
Look me in the eye and tell me
you don't want to go to a school
that recognizes your talent.
Hey, are you Forsythe?
Yeah.
Bret Weston Wallis.
Mr. Chipping asked me to
roll out the red carpet.
The Lodge name is... tainted.
But my mother's maiden name, Gomez?
I think I could work with that.
But I did see Edgar,
and, Betty, he's armed.
Edgar's digging in.
He's getting ready for war.
Sit your butt down and don't move.
You need to chill out, okay?
Nothing happened!
- Everything all right, Munroe?
- Anything but.
Malcolm's been hanging
out at the Wipeout Arcade.
So?
That place is crawling
with dealers and fiends
and I don't want him
getting mixed up in that.
Didn't we say we were
gonna turn this place
into a community center, Red?
We are. I still plan on it.
But...
life kind of threw me a curveball.
But you're right,
feels like it's time.
Found it.
Well, we are certainly not
in Riverdale High anymore.
Welcome to the Dead Poets Society.
Not a bad coop, boy.
Okay, kitten, let's go
find the vending machine
and I'll buy you some Triple Bubble.
You still okay with this?
Yeah.
I'm just gonna miss you,
that's all.
Well, you better take your breaks
from me while you can, Cooper.
'Cause you and I are in
this for the long haul. Okay?
I don't know what happened.
I thought I wanted to sign the document
and officially change my
name to Veronica Gomez,
but...
in the moment, I just couldn't do it.
Look, if it didn't feel
right, it didn't feel right.
I still want to do it.
I just need to figure
out who I'm going to be.
And you will.
In the meantime, you want
to go with me to the gym?
I'm meeting with Ms. Weiss
about turning the place
into a community center.
Of course.
Do we need to leave now?
I mean, we've got some time.
Jughead?
Moose.
What the hell?
It's good to see you.
Actually, it's, uh...
It's Marmaduke now.
Marmaduke?
Wait, are you my roommate?
What are you doing here, dude?
After my dad was arrested
for impersonating the...
Gargoyle King,
it, uh...
kind of blew up my life...
my family... everything.
I... kind of had a nervous breakdown.
I even ended up in a facility
for a couple of months.
- Aw, man.
- When I got out, we decided
it would be better if
I started someplace new,
someplace fresh.
So took a year off
and I came here to play
football and start over.
Well, are you feeling any better?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. I...
You know, I feel like a person again.
Like this... this darkness is off me.
But, please just keep
this between us, okay?
If some of these guys got a whiff...
- of who I was...
- No.
Your secret is safe with me, Marmaduke.
Thanks, man.
And we'll need to be especially
tight-lipped around Bret.
You rang?
Forsythe, welcome.
- Lovely to see you again.
- Yeah, and you too.
I see you've met our roommate.
Ah, yeah. Marmaduke and I
were actually just getting acquainted.
Well, it's about time for seminar.
Did you do the reading?
Munroe and I will group the kids
for boxing and MMA lessons
according to their age.
We'll keep the gym open until 10:00,
so kids like my brother have
a place to hang after school
and keep them off the
streets before they go home.
Oh, that all sounds wonderful.
I just want you to be aware
of how much work this
will actually entail.
And what about school, Archie?
Mr. Keller will be here during the day.
Archie, when was the last time
the gym had a safety inspection?
If this really is going
to be a community center,
there are updates you'll have to do.
At minimum, adding a second bathroom.
Oh, that sounds expensive.
We'll figure it out, Mom.
You're just in time.
Thanks to your friend Kevin's Intel,
I've had this derelict motel
under 24-hour surveillance.
According to city records,
it's owned by one of Edgar's followers.
And...
look who's answering the front door.
Great.
If we know they are, then
what are we waiting for?
Have you ever heard of Waco, Betty?
Charles?
Check this out.
Farm's been getting
pizza deliveries every day
about the same time.
We've got an agent in disguise
about to make a delivery as we speak.
Yeah? Who are you?
Sorry, I got lost.
Pizza delivery. 10 cheese, 10 pepperoni.
You're not our guy.
Go. Take him!
Get him.
What was that?
Here we go. Come on.
Echo, this is Charlie, do you read me?
Echo, do you read me?
Charles, is that you?
Sending someone in with a wire?
You're usually more clever than that.
I know all your secrets.
Don't send anyone else in
or their blood will
also be on your hands.
Wait to hear from me.
There goes your Nana Rose again.
I swear, it's like every night.
It's like she's scratching
inside the walls.
Nana Rose is a restless spirit.
Babe...
it worries me leaving
the twins alone with her
while we're at school.
Maybe we should hire caretaker for her.
And have a stranger living amongst us,
sticking their noses into our business?
Absolutely not.
We're all doing just fine.
Nana?
Are you okay?
Oh, Penelope.
There you are.
Thank heavens...
I thought I saw the triplets...
burning in the fire.
Nana...
it's me,
Cheryl.
And Juniper and Dagwood,
the twins,
are sleeping soundly in the nursery.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
I'm looking at around 40 grand
to pay for the renovations
that the gym needs.
I hate to say it, again,
but I could just lend you the money.
No, Ronnie, I don't want
to take any more handouts.
I want to work for it.
I just need to figure
out what that work can be.
We could host a charity concert.
Could have a bake sale?
You'd have to sell a lot of cupcakes.
Now, hold on, I think
Bee's onto something.
Not a bake sale, per se,
but, looking at you
four strapping young men,
there is another classic way
to raise money.
♪ At the car wash ♪
♪ Workin' at the car wash Girl... ♪
Thank you.
Great work, Reginald.
every suburban housewife in the county
is spreading the word
about our sudsy fundraiser.
What can I say, I have a deep fanbase.
Yes, you do.
♪ Work and work ♪
♪ Well, those cars never
seem to stop coming ♪
♪ Work and work ♪
♪ Keep those rags and machines humming ♪
♪ Can't wait till it's time to go home ♪
♪ Hey, get your car washed today ♪
♪ Come on and give us a play ♪
♪ Do the wash, right away ♪
What's the haul, Ronnie?
A little over four.
Grand?
That's great!
Hundred, Archie.
I think I overestimated
the financial pull of your pectorals.
Hey,
we're just getting started.
Maybe we do a Magic Mike night
at La Bonne Nuit.
Or...
dare I say...
you boys go the full Monty?
We'll figure something out.
We always do.
Oh, my God, Mom.
I was so worried.
No, Betty,
it's me.
Edgar.
How did you get my mom's phone?
I suspected we had a
pretender in our midst.
When I...
started cutting people's fingers off,
your mother admitted to me it was her.
I have a list of demands.
I'm listening.
I need $250,000,
passports for all each and every one
of my followers,
food, water,
and a bus
for transport.
Why did you call me?
Why didn't you call Charles?
Because I think you'll have
a better chance convincing him
than I will.
You have five hours.
Charles, I just heard from Edgar.
"My mother has asked me to
help her with the turkey,
and I wonder, vaguely,
when she'll die."
Discussion is open.
What is everyone's take on Bret's story?
In a word...
astonishing.
Yeah, agreed.
It's brilliant.
Thank you, Jonathan.
What did you think, roomie?
Yeah, it was good.
It was good?
We've got a real Harold Bloom here.
Don't hold back, Jones.
I'm a... I'm a big boy. I can take it.
To be honest...
it wasn't really my taste.
I thought it was, uh...
Salinger-derivative.
Thank you for that constructive
criticism, Forsythe.
You'd mind if I give you
my thoughts on your story?
What was it? The Gremlin King?
- The Gargoyle King.
- I thought it was a puerile,
tawdry waste of time.
I mean... it's pulp.
Pulp is not an insult to me.
Not to mention, your
prose reads more like
a pre-teen journaling
about his abandonment issues
than as a coherent narrative...
Hey, hey, hey, keep it clean, guys.
Taste aside,
all good writing does have
one thing in common...
Authenticity.
That's my problem, then.
I can't relate to Jughead's work
because I'm not from his world.
I don't have any experience
with lowlives, or criminals,
- or trailer trash.
- Oh, no?
I could give you the crash
course in about five seconds.
Jughead,
there is a zero-tolerance
violence policy
at Stonewall Prep.
Do you hear me?
Nana? Babies? I'm home.
And who, pray tell, are you,
interloper?
Hello, you must be Cheryl.
Hey.
Babe, don't get mad, but this is Darius.
He's a night nurse I found online.
I thought he could help
with Nana and the kids.
Fine.
But you will do as you're told,
nothing less,
nothing more.
You may tend to Nana where she is,
but you are not,
repeat, not...
to go into the Blossom
Chapel in the basement.
It is forbidden.
Sacred.
Don't sweat it, Dee,
not even I'm allowed to go in there.
Do we understand each other, Darius?
Absolutely, Miss Cheryl.
Dude, there's a tie on the door.
I'm... I'm just not
used to this. I'm sorry.
Donna?
I'm sorry. Look, I'm
not one for gossip, so...
I don't care if you are.
I'm not ashamed of anything I do.
But, a word of advice, newbie?
I'd watch your back around Bret.
Why? What is his deal?
He's a diplo-brat.
Son of a diplomat.
Thinks that gives him immunity
to do whatever he wants.
Like, beat me up?
That's not how Bret fights.
Okay. It's psychological with him.
And he's not afraid to play dirty.
Okay. I'll take your advice.
Bye, Marmaduke.
Catch you later.
I'm sorry.
Look, I thought you were...
I like guys and girls.
- Cool?
- Yeah.
Totally. I'll...
keep an eye on the doorknob.
What happened?
What did Governor Dooley say?
The same thing that he's been saying.
That we can't give Edgar what he demands
and he will not negotiate
with a cult leader.
Is he kidding? What about Mom and Polly
and all of the other Farmies?
It's Edgar. What do I say?
You need to buy us time.
Okay? I'll walk you through it.
Hello?
Hello, Betty.
Did you get what I asked for?
We're unable to meet any demands
unless he releases a hostage
as a sign of goodwill.
They want you to release
a hostage first, Edgar,
as a sign of good faith.
Betty, Betty, Betty...
I thought you would
be smarter than this.
Working with people who don't share
your same interests is a bad idea.
At any rate,
anticipating that you and your partners
wouldn't take my demands seriously,
I've already released a hostage.
What?
But...
What the hell is he talking about?
What... What hostage?
Betty?
Polly?
No. Stop!
Oh, my God!
Polly, stay calm. We're
going to figure it out, okay?
- Tell him to stay back.
- Charles, please. Stay back.
Please. Please.
She's holding a dead man's switch.
If she lets go, the bomb explodes.
Okay...
Uh, all right, Polly,
I know Edgar must have
said something to you, okay?
But it doesn't... It doesn't matter.
I know you don't want to do this.
I know you don't want
Juniper and Dagwood
to grow up without a mom,
or me without a sister, okay?
So, we're gonna figure it out, okay?
Okay. What are we gonna...
Betty, look at the timer.
There's wires connected to the C4.
Three of those are decoys.
They'll trigger the detonator.
You need to find the one that's linked
- to the firing circuit and the battery.
- And the battery.
Can I come up and check, Polly?
- Yeah.
- Okay, okay.
Um...
The firing circuit and the battery.
Firing circuit, battery.
Uh... it's the yellow...
It's the yellow one.
- It's the yellow.
- Here, take these.
- So I have to... Okay.
- Yeah.
Careful.
It's going to be okay. It's
going to be okay. It's fine.
It's going to be okay. Okay?
- It's counting down even faster.
- It's a tripwire.
There may be a system override
on the dead man's switch.
A pin connected to a chain,
that slides beneath a hole.
It goes underneath the trigger.
- Polly, where's the pin?
- Edgar took it.
- Took the pin.
- Everybody, get down. Betty!
What am I doing? The detonator needs
a pin. Needs a pin. Needs a pin.
- No! No!
- Betty! Come on.
Oh...
It worked.
It's okay.
Scholars, I'm cancelling
this afternoon's seminar.
Instead, we will be
having an evening session.
You've each been given a copy
of the same mystery story,
with the final chapter omitted,
in which the murderer's identity
would be revealed.
You're each to write your
own version of the ending,
in whatever style you choose.
We'll then read all the endings,
and decide the winner
by a vote.
Best story wins?
Challenge accepted.
What exactly will this
so-called exercise prove, Mr. Chipping?
That there is no single way
to tell a story, Donna.
So...
see you back here by 9:00 p.m.
Don't be late.
Red! We gotta go.
We gotta get these guys, now!
What are you talking about?
Malcolm... got jumped by some thugs
for not making deliveries.
He wasn't even hanging at the arcade.
He listened to me, and
he still got hurt, Red.
Is he going to be okay?
He's a tough kid.
He's seen worse.
Malcolm said that the thugs work
for some guy named Dodger.
He recruits kids from the arcade,
gets them to break into
houses, make deliveries,
jack cars... All kinds of crap.
Riverdale's no place for
people that prey on kids,
so let's teach them a lesson.
Me and you.
Let's go down there, like old times.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
If you get caught, you
might end up behind bars.
And you got your
brother and your grandma
depending on you now.
I'll talk to FP,
put this Dodger guy on his radar,
and we'll let the cops take care of it.
But this place,
this is how we're
going to help Riverdale.
Polly, you have to help us stop Edgar.
There is no stopping Edgar.
You just...
have to do what he says.
Governor Dooley isn't letting Charles
or the FBI negotiate with him.
Then just do it yourself.
Just get him what he's asking for.
Or what?
Or he'll start sacrificing
his followers one by one.
What about Mom?
Where is she? Is she okay?
If she's still alive,
it won't be for long.
Unless you do what Edgar says.
I don't think I can get that much, Bee.
$250,000 is a lot to come up with.
I'm sorry, Vee.
I know that this is an insane ask,
but I can't say anything more
except that there are lives at stake.
It doesn't need to be cash, does it?
Those Glamourge eggs,
they're worth $50,000 each.
That should do it.
Oh, my God, Vee. Really?
Aren't those your dad's?
My mom's, actually.
Take 'em.
But...
How are you going to
get the other stuff?
I know people.
What do you think?
You need fake passports
for all these people?
They don't need to be fake.
Blank passports are fine.
They'll do everything else.
I really can't get into it,
but it's a matter of life or death.
Okay.
I know a guy.
Thank you, Toni.
Ms. Cooper.
What is the emergency?
I'm sorry to bother you, Ms. Bell,
but I left my calculus book
on the bus this morning.
I'm sorry, dear,
but you'll have to pick it up tomorrow.
Mr. Fritz has already left for the day.
Oh, geez.
Well, if he's already gone...
Yes, Betty?
I got everything you asked for.
Let me in.
Well done.
I'll see you outside.
At last, we meet again.
I got everything that you asked for.
Money, passports, food,
water, it's all in the bus.
Now where's my mom?
Mmm...
I knew you wouldn't fail me.
Oh...
Betty. It is such a shame
that you didn't accept the simple truths
I tried to instill in you...
Edgar. Where is my mom?
... because without those truths...
Betty,
all you're left with...
is pain.
Nighty-night.
Could you knock it off?
Sorry, am I distracting
you from your genius?
Hey, Forsythe,
I was wondering, is it common
for gangs...
to have a writer among its ranks?
I mean, I suppose
a kid like you needed something
to call a family.
After all, weren't you
just a little urchin
wandering the streets
after your mom ditched you
and your good-for-nothing
drunk of a father?
And, come to think of it,
isn't your little sister
a budding hooligan herself?
Only 13 years old,
and already roped into
your mom's drug business.
You're right.
I wasn't born in rarified air.
I didn't grow up with any silver spoons.
But my dad
had the strength to turn his life around
and become a sheriff.
And I have friends,
and family that actually care for me.
Can you even say the same?
So why don't you try
writing a compelling drama,
instead of starting it?
Smithers?
Daddy?
You're supposed to be in jail.
Mija, I own that jail.
I come and go as I please.
I heard a nasty little rumor
that you were dropping the Lodge name.
I've never taken the trash out, Daddy,
but I know when something's rotten.
That name is mud,
and I'm done with it.
Do you know who Jaime Luna was?
Doesn't ring a bell.
Yeah, well, Luna was my father's name,
And Jaime Luna
was the name of his only son.
Me.
I wasn't born Hiram Lodge.
I became him.
You have no idea what it was like
to be a Luna in a town like Riverdale.
Everyone looked down on
us because of that name.
So, I took a name that
people would respect.
Lodge.
And when my father found out,
he was angry,
and he beat me.
And I didn't understand it,
because I didn't want
his life, I wanted mine,
my own name. What was the big deal?
Well, mija,
it is now...
in this very moment
that I understand my father's rage.
Do you think
that changing your name is
going to wash away your sins?
It won't.
I'm not going down the
same path as you did, Daddy.
You keep telling yourself that
because you will always
be part of this family.
It's in your blood.
And that...
doesn't wash out.
Don't bother changing the locks.
You can't keep me out.
Hey, can we talk?
Sure. What's up?
I want you to come
back to Chicago with me.
Mom...
You can finish your senior year there.
You can start again.
I don't want to start again.
And my best bet at going to college
is on a football scholarship.
Otherwise, how would I even
be able to afford college?
Your father and I started a
fund for you when you were born.
What?
A fund? I have money?
I was reluctant to tell you
because I thought that you would want
to use it on the community center.
Of course I would.
Archie, as noble an idea as that may be,
do you really think
that's going to make a
difference here in Riverdale?
I mean, all the crime here,
your friend Munroe's little brother
beaten up by a bunch of thugs?
Is that really the town
that you want to invest in?
No one is safe here.
Look. I'm not going to give up
on Riverdale the same way you did.
I moved to Chicago
because I couldn't find a job here.
And don't blame me if I
am trying to stop my child
from putting his money
into a losing proposition.
Yeah. Well, I guess that's the
difference between you and me, Mom.
I don't think Riverdale
is a losing proposition.
The same as Dad.
I'm not moving.
And I will make a difference here.
All right, if we're gonna do
this, we got to do it right. Okay?
- You guys follow my orders...
- Hey...
You Dodger?
That ain't your business.
Yeah.
Your days of exploiting kids
to do your dirty work ends tonight.
I want you and all your little buddies
out of Riverdale.
You and that Louisville Slugger?
I'd take a closer look, friend.
You're outnumbered 5-to-1.
I'll take those odds.
I'm sorry I came by
so late, Mrs. Andrews.
No, not at all, but Archie's in bed.
I'm actually here to see you.
That's $40,000.
I'm giving it to you,
to give to Archie for
the community center.
He's too proud to take it from me.
Veronica...
thank you.
But we can't accept this.
We can't be in that kind
of debt to your family.
And if you put that
money into the center,
it keeps Archie here in Riverdale,
away from college, away from his future.
At the risk of
overstepping, Mrs. Andrews,
I'm not investing in a building,
I'm investing in your son.
I believe in Archie,
and...
he makes me want to believe in myself.
And I need that right now.
Tear the check up if you want.
But I really hope you don't.
Rise and shine, my dearest.
It's another magnificent day
that's ours for the taking.
Jay-Jay?
Weren't you over there
whilst I read to you at nighttide?
Red?
What the hell happened?
You should see
Dodger and the other guys.
They're not going to be
messing with your brother
anytime soon.
You went after them without me?
And what happens if those scumbags
come looking for payback?
They're not going to.
I was in disguise.
Oh, so you're a superhero now?
Look, the good news is,
we got enough money to
buy a second bathroom.
Oh, hell no!
You know we can't use this, right?
This money is dirty.
Only a fool would spend this cash.
It needs to be cleaned first.
Any chance your girlfriend
could help us with that?
So, we have three votes for Story C.
Which makes makes Story C our winner,
which is penned by...
Donna Sweett.
Stories A and B,
written by Bret and Jughead,
tied for last place.
Well, at least you
didn't kill each other.
Elizabeth...
Elizabeth?
Mom.
Where are we?
In one of the motel rooms.
Edgar's been keeping me here
ever since he figured
out I was the mole.
I'll kill him.
Honey, I'm so sorry,
I was trying to keep you safe.
I didn't want you to know,
and I needed to get Polly out.
Do you know what Edgar's plan is?
What?
Evelyn is going to drive
the bus full of Farmies
off of a cliff as a distraction
while he...
What?
Takes off in his rocket.
- What?
- Yeah.
He bought a rocket?
No, he's been building one.
Yeah, because harvesting
organs isn't... isn't enough.
What is he planning to do with us?
We're going to be tied to the
front of the bus as shields.
Unless we can figure
out a way out of here.
I think I actually have an idea.
We have to get back to back.
Miss Cheryl, Miss Antoinette,
I'll be needing some money
and the skeleton key for the house.
Excuse me?
What possibly for?
Thistlehouse has rats in the walls.
- I went into the basement...
- Halt!
You went down to the basement,
specifically after I ordered you not to?
You didn't go into the chapel, did you?
No, Miss Cheryl...
Thistlehouse has never had rats.
But, Babe, we did hear
something last night.
Remember?
No,
you're right, Tee-Tee.
And suddenly,
I am feeling the presence of a rat,
a six-foot-tall rat with
muscles and bedroom eyes,
Darius,
I knew you were a mistake
from the beginning.
So...
you're fired.
Toodles.
All right, ladies. Times up, let's go.
♪ When the dark is ♪
♪ Closing in ♪
♪ What's your... ♪
Those bitches...
♪ Tell me... ♪
♪ Tell me, would you
burn your kingdom down? ♪
Now we just have to make it to
the courtyard without being shot.
♪ Tell me are you laughing now ♪
♪ When there's nowhere left to go? ♪
♪ Who's gonna save your soul? ♪
♪ Tell me what's your endgame? ♪
Where did you get this from?
I took it off some lowlife drug dealers.
Ronnie, I hate to ask you this,
but is there anything you can do?
Any way you can clean it, so
I can use it for the center?
Archie...
I know you're trying to do good,
but this...
isn't it.
My advice...
Burn it.
All of it.
And let me pay for the renovations.
- Ronnie.
- Archie,
please just forget
your pride for a second
and let me be a part
of what you're doing.
I need to be a part
Keep it moving, keep it moving.
Hey, Edgar has decreed
it's time to go. Okay?
Everybody on the bus. Keep moving.
That's the thing about cults.
Speak with enough authority,
and they'll do anything you say.
Once we drive the Farmies out,
Charles can move in and
take down Edgar. Okay?
Traitor.
There is a trait...
He's... he's fine.
Get him in the bus, okay? Please. Okay?
Keep... keep going.
Keep going. Keep moving, all right?
Oh, no.
Give me the gun.
Get everybody on the bus.
- I'm going to stop Edgar.
- Okay.
Okay. Keep going, keep going.
Mr. Weatherbee?
I told Edgar I wasn't the mole,
but he wouldn't listen.
He cut it off.
Ms. Cooper, I don't
know how I let myself
get embroiled in this madness.
Mr. Weatherbee,
this is your last shot
at redemption. Okay?
Get everybody on this bus.
Go. Please.
Okay?
On the bus, please.
Everyone get on the bus.
Let's go, everybody.
- Hello?
- Charles, it's me.
I'm inside the motel.
Betty, you have got to get out of there.
Governor Dooley is sending in
a team of mercenaries right now.
Tell them to stand down.
There's a busload of unarmed civilians,
including women and
children, headed your way.
Hands up, Edgar.
Sister Alice.
Come with me peacefully, or so help me,
I will shoot you in the kneecaps
and drag your ass out of here myself.
You betrayed us.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Do you remember the story
of the prophet Elijah, Alice?
He was seized by a whirlwind
and lifted up into the
sky in a chariot of fire.
Elijah ascended.
And I will too.
Mom?
Oh, my God, Mom.
What happened? Are you okay?
Edgar ascended.
Jab high. Jab high.
Jab low.
Jab high.
And cross. Good work.
And cross!
And... jab.
And... jab!
And... cross!
Need any help?
Mom, what's going on?
I was leaving,
but what's going on
is I will be focusing
more on pro bono work in
the foreseeable future,
here in Riverdale.
And my first order of business
is to get your community
center declared a 501.
That's a non-profit.
It means that you can ask for donations,
you don't have to pay taxes,
you can apply for grants.
Well, that's amazing.
Except that I don't know
how to do any of that.
Yeah.
You're lot like your dad in that way.
So, you'll just leave it to me,
and you can go help
those kids out there.
Deal.
What happened to Chicago?
Um... I'll call the airline
and cancel the flight.
I don't think I'll be back anytime soon.
Hello, Daddy.
I'm sure you'll be getting
a call from Mr. Sowerberry soon,
but, I just wanted to
let you know face to face
that I'm no longer a Lodge.
Mija...
How many times must we go through this?
I'm officially changing
my name to Veronica Luna.
And I am changing the locks.
And I'm installing an alarm.
And I'm sleeping with
a taser under my pillow.
And you better believe I'll use it.
He didn't see you...
did he, Jason?
Ahhh! Get off! Get off him!
We're gonna fix you right up, Jay-Jay.
Cheryl?
What the hell is going on here?
Toni...
you've never met Jason, have you?
Oh, no.
His dad was the Gargoyle King.
His real name is "Moose".
His girlfriend was
murdered by the Black Hood.
Everybody knows.
So much for a new start.
I'm done here.
_
He was a broken man, Betty.
And it was Bret, of course.
He did it because he blames
me for not winning the contest.
Or maybe he's just a sociopath.
He knew that he couldn't
get to me directly
so he went after Moose.
This is nothing like
fighting the Ghoulies.
This is psychological warfare.
God. Poor Moose.
Just be careful, Jug.
Aw, don't worry about me.
Hey, how's your mom and Polly?
My Mom was already working
on her expose of the Farm.
Polly started this program
at the Shady Grove Treatment Center.
She's getting the help that she needs.
What about Charles?
Is he the real deal? Can we trust him?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm just happy that this nightmare is...
finally over.
Famous last words.