-[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
-What were you doing in there?
I was... praying.
My team's been investigating
Edgar Evernever for quite some time now.
We had someone on the inside.
Someone tasked
with getting close to Edgar.
[Betty] My mother is an FBI informant?
Charles, what if that means
she's been found out?
You should go to Stonewall Prep, Jug.
Look me in the eye and tell me
you don't wanna go to a school
that recognizes your talent.
Hey. Are you Forsythe?
Yeah.
Bret Weston Wallis.
Mr. Chipping asked me to roll out
the red carpet.
The Lodge name is tainted.
But my mother's maiden name, Gomez?
I think I could work with that.
But I did see Edgar.
And, Betty, he's armed.
Edgar's digging in.
He's getting ready for war.
♪ I've been walking through fire ♪
[door opens]
[Munroe] Sit your butt down
and don't move.
You need to chill out, okay?
Nothing happened.
-Everything all right, Munroe?
-Anything but.
Malcolm's been hanging out
at Wipeout Arcade.
So?
That place is crawling
with dealers and fiends,
and I don't want him
getting mixed up in that.
Didn't you say we were gonna turn
this place into a community center, Red?
We are. I still plan on it. But...
life kind of threw me a curveball.
But you're right.
It feels like it's time.
[Jellybean] Found it.
Oh.
Well, we are certainly not
in Riverdale High anymore.
Welcome to the Dead Poets Society.
Not a bad coop, boy.
Okay, kid.
Let's go find the vending machine.
I'll buy you some Triple Bubble.
You still okay with this?
Yeah.
I'm just gonna miss you, that's all.
Well, you better take your breaks
from me while you can, Cooper.
'Cause you and I are in this
for the long haul, okay?
I don't know what happened.
I thought I wanted to sign the document
and officially change my name
to Veronica Gomez, but...
in the moment, I just couldn't do it.
If it didn't feel right,
it didn't feel right.
I still wanna do it.
I just need to figure out
who I'm going to be.
And you will. In the meantime,
you wanna come with me to the gym?
I'm meeting with Ms. Weiss about turning
the place into a community center.
Of course.
Do we need to leave now?
I mean, we got some time.
Jughead?
Moose.
What the hell?
It's good to see you.
Actually, it's, uh... It's Marmaduke now.
Marmaduke.
Wait, are you my roommate?
What are you doing here, dude?
After my dad was arrested
for impersonating the Gargoyle King,
it, uh... kind of blew up my life,
my family.
Everything.
I kind of had a nervous breakdown.
Ended up in a facility
for a couple months.
-Oh, man...
-When I got out,
we decided it'd be better
if I started someplace new,
someplace fresh.
So, I took a year off and came here
to play football and start over.
Well, are you feeling any better?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. I-- I--
You know, I feel like a person again.
Like this-- This darkness is off me.
But please just keep this between us,
okay?
If some of these guys got a whiff
of who I was...
No. Your secret is safe with me,
Marmaduke.
Thanks, man.
And we'll need to be
especially tight-lipped around Bret.
[Bret] You rang?
Forsythe, welcome.
-Lovely to see you again.
-Yeah, you, too.
I see you've met our roommate.
Uh, yeah, Marmaduke and I were
just getting acquainted.
Well, it's about time for seminar.
Did you do the reading?
Munroe and I will group the kids
for boxing and MMA lessons
-according to age.
-Keep the gym open until 10,
so kids like my brother have a place
to hang after school
and keep them off the streets
before they go home.
Well, that all sounds wonderful.
I just want you to be aware of
how much work this will actually entail.
What about school, Archie?
Mr. Keller will be here during the day.
Archie, when was the last time
the gym had a safety inspection?
If this is really gonna be
a community center,
there are updates you'll have to do.
At minimum, adding a second bathroom.
Oh, that sounds expensive.
We'll figure it out, Mom.
[Charles] You're just in time.
Thanks to your friend Kevin's intel,
I've had this derelict motel
under 24-hour surveillance.
According to city records,
it's owned by one of Edgar's followers.
And... look who's answering
the front door.
Great. If we know where they are,
then what are we waiting for?
-Have you ever heard of Waco, Betty?
-[man] Charles.
Check this out.
The Farm's been getting pizza deliveries
every day about the same time.
We've got an agent in disguise
about to make a delivery as we speak.
[knocking on door over radio]
[door opens]
[Evelyn] Yeah? Who are you?
[agent] Sorry, I got lost. Pizza delivery.
Ten cheese, ten pepperoni.
[Evelyn] You're not our guy.
-[man] Go! Take him!
-[grunting]
[Evelyn] Get him.
What was that?
[Evelyn] Hurry up, come on.
[gunshots]
Echo, this is Charlie, do you read me?
Echo, do you read me?
[Edgar] Charles, is that you?
Sending someone in with a wire,
you're usually more clever than that.
I know all your secrets.
Don't send anyone else in,
or their blood will also be on your hands.
Wait to hear from me.
[loud creaking]
There goes your Nana Rose again.
I swear, it's like every night.
It's like she scratching inside the walls.
Nana Rose is a restless spirit.
Babe...
it worries me, leaving the twins alone
with her while we're at school.
Maybe we should hire a caretaker for her.
And have a stranger living amongst us?
Sticking their noses into our business?
Absolutely not.
We're all doing just fine.
[Nana screams]
Nana.
Are you okay?
Penelope, there you are.
Thank heavens.
I thought I saw the triplets burning
in the fire.
Nana, it's me, Cheryl.
And Juniper and Dagwood, the twins,
are sleeping soundly in the nursery.
I'm looking at around 40 grand to pay
for the renovations that the gym needs.
I hate to say it again,
but I could just lend you the money.
No, Ronnie,
I don't wanna take any more handouts.
I wanna work for it. I just need
to figure out what that work can be.
We could host a charity concert.
We could have a bake sale.
You're gonna have to sell
a lot of cupcakes.
Now, hold on. I think B's on to something.
Not a bake sale, per se, but...
looking at you four strapping young men,
there's another classic way
to raise money.
♪ At the car wash ♪
♪ Workin' at the car wash ♪
Thank you.
Great work, Reginald.
Every suburban housewife in the county
is spreading the word
about our sudsy fundraiser.
What can I say? I have a deep fan base.
Yes, you do.
-♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
-♪ Work and work ♪
♪ Well, those cars never seem
To stop comin' ♪
♪ Work and work ♪
♪ Keep those rags and machines humming ♪
-♪ Work ♪
-♪ I can't wait till it's time ♪
♪ To go home ♪
♪ Hey, get your car wash today ♪
♪ Come on and give us a play ♪
-What's the haul, Ronnie?
-A little over 4.
Grand? That's great.
Hundred, Archie.
I think I overestimated the financial pull
of your pectorals.
Hey! We're just getting started.
Maybe we can do a Magic Mike Night
at La Bonne Nuit.
Or, dare I say...
you boys go The Full Monty?
We'll figure something out. We always do.
[cell phone rings]
Oh, my God, Mom. I was so worried.
[on phone] No, Betty. It's me, Edgar.
-How did you get my mom's phone?
-[Edgar laughs]
I suspected we had a pretender
in our midst.
When I started cutting
people's fingers off,
your mother admitted to me it was her.
I have a list of demands.
I'm listening.
I need $250,000...
passports for each and every one
of my followers,
food, water and a bus
for transport.
Why did you call me?
Why didn't you call Charles?
Because I think you'll have a better
chance convincing him than I will.
You have five hours.
Charles, I just heard from Edgar.
"My mother has asked me to help her
with the turkey
and I wonder, vaguely, when she'll die."
Discussion is open.
What is everyone's take on Bret's story?
In a word, "astonishing."
Yeah, agreed. It's brilliant.
Thank you, Jonathan.
-What did you think, roomie?
-Yeah, it was good.
It was good? [snickers]
Got a real Harold Bloom here.
Don't hold back, Jones. I'm a big boy.
I can take it.
To be honest...
it wasn't really my taste.
I thought it was, uh, Salinger-derivative.
Thank you for that constructive criticism,
Forsythe.
Mind if I give you my thoughts on your
story? What was it? "The Gremlin King."
"Gargoyle King."
I thought it was puerile,
a tawdry waste of time.
I mean, it's pulp.
Pulp is not an insult to me.
Not to mention your prose reads
more like a preteen journaling
about his abandonment issues
than a coherent narrative.
Hey, hey, hey. Keep it clean, guys.
Taste aside, all good writing does have
one thing in common:
authenticity.
That's my problem, then.
I can't relate to Jughead's work
because I'm not from his world.
I don't have any experience with lowlives
or criminals or trailer trash.
Oh, no? I could give you the crash course
in about five seconds.
Jughead. There is a zero-tolerance
violence policy at Stonewall Prep.
Do you hear me?
Nana, babies, I'm home!
And who, pray tell, are you, interloper?
Hello, you must be Cheryl.
Hey.
Babe, don't be mad, but this is Darius.
He's a night nurse I found online.
I thought he could help with Nana
and the kids.
Fine. But you will do as you're told,
nothing less, nothing more.
You may tend to Nana, where she is...
but you are not...
repeat, not to go into the Blossom chapel
in the basement.
It is forbidden.
Sacred.
[Toni] Don't sweat it, D.
Not even I'm allowed to go in there.
Do we understand each other, Darius?
Absolutely, Miss Cheryl.
Dude, there's a tie on the door!
I'm-- I'm-- I'm just not used to this.
I'm sorry.
Donna.
Look, I'm not one for gossip, so...
I don't care if you are.
I'm not ashamed of anything I do.
But a word of advice, newbie:
I'd watch your back around Bret.
Why? What is his deal?
He's a diplo-brat.
Son of a diplomat.
Thinks it gives him immunity
to do whatever he wants.
-Like beat me up?
-That's not how Bret fights, okay?
It's psychological with him.
And he's not afraid to play dirty.
Okay. I'll take your advice.
[Donna] Bye, Marmaduke.
Catch you later.
I'm sorry.
-Loo-- I thought you were...
-I like guys and girls. Cool?
Yeah, totally. I'll...
keep an eye on the doorknob.
What happened?
What did Governor Dooley say?
Same thing that he's been saying.
That we can't give Edgar what he demands
and he will not negotiate
with a cult leader.
Is he kidding? What about Mom and--?
And Polly? And all of the other Farmies?
[cell phone ringing]
It's Edgar. What do I say?
You need to buy us time, okay?
I'll walk you through it.
Hello?
[Edgar] Hello, Betty.
Did you get what I asked for?
We're unable to meet any demands
unless he releases a hostage
as a sign of good will.
They want you to release a hostage first,
Edgar, as a sign of good faith.
Betty, Betty, Betty.
I thought you would be smarter than this.
Working with people who don't share
your same interests is a bad idea.
At any rate,
anticipating that you and your partners
wouldn't take my demands seriously,
I've already released a hostage.
What? What--?
[cell phone beeping]
What the hell is he talking about?
What--? What hostage?
[Polly] Betty.
Polly.
No, stop.
Oh, my God.
Polly, stay calm. We'll figure it out.
-Tell him to stay back!
-Charles, stay back.
-Please. Please.
-[Charles] She has a dead man's switch.
If she lets go, the bomb explodes.
Okay. Polly, I know Edgar must have
said something to you, okay?
But it doesn't-- It doesn't matter,
I know you don't wanna do this.
I know you don't want Juniper and Dagwood
to grow up without a mom
or me without a sister, okay?
So, we're gonna figure it out, okay?
-Okay. What do we do?
-Betty, look at the timer.
There's wires connected to the C-4.
Three of those are decoys.
They'll trigger the detonator.
Find the one that's linked
-to the firing circuit and the battery.
-Firing circuit and the battery.
-Can I come up and check, Polly? Okay.
-Yeah.
Um... Firing circuit and the battery.
Firing circuit and the battery.
It's the yellow--
It's the yellow one. It's the yellow--
Here. Here, take these.
-[Betty] Do I have to...?
-[Charles] Yeah.
-Careful.
-It's gonna be okay. It's fine.
[Polly whimpering]
It's gonna be okay. Okay?
[beeps]
It's counting down even faster!
It's a tripwire! There might be
a system override on the switch.
A pin connected to a chain.
It slides beneath the hole,
goes underneath the trigger.
-Polly, where's the pin?
-Edgar took it.
-He took the pin.
-Everybody, get down!
Betty! We gotta go!
-Detonator needs a pin. It needs a pin.
-[Charles] Betty! Betty, come on!
[Polly] Okay.
[gasps]
It wor-- It worked. It's okay.
Scholars, I'm canceling
this afternoon's seminar.
Instead, we will be having
an evening session.
You've each been given a copy
of the same mystery story
with the final chapter omitted, in which
the murderer's identity would be revealed.
You're each to write your own version
of the ending.
In whatever style you choose.
We will then read all the endings
and decide the winner by vote.
Best story wins?
Challenge accepted.
What exactly will this so-called exercise
prove, Mr. Chipping?
That there is no single way
to tell a story, Donna.
So...
see you back here by 9 p.m.
Don't be late.
[Munroe] Red! We gotta go!
-We gotta get these guys now!
-What are you talking about?
Malcolm. Got jumped by some thugs
for not making deliveries.
He wasn't even hanging at the arcade.
He listened to me and he still got hurt.
Is he gonna be okay?
He's a tough kid. He's seen worse.
Malcolm said that the thugs worked
for some guy named Dodger.
He recruits kids from the arcade,
gets them to break into houses,
make deliveries, jack cars.
All kinds of crap.
Riverdale's no place for people
that prey on kids.
So, let's teach them a lesson. Me and you.
Let's go down there like old times.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
If you get caught,
you might end up behind bars.
You got your brother
and your grandma depending on you now.
I'll talk to FP,
put this Dodger guy on his radar.
We'll let the cops take care of it.
But this place?
This is how we're gonna help Riverdale.
Polly, you have to help us stop Edgar.
There is no stopping Edgar.
You just... have to do what he says.
Governor Dooley isn't letting Charles
or the FBI negotiate with him.
Then just do it yourself.
Just get him what he's asking for.
Or what?
Or he'll start sacrificing his followers,
one by one.
What about Mom? Where is she? Is she okay?
If she's still alive,
it won't be for long.
Unless you do what Edgar says.
I don't think I can get that much, B.
Two hundred and fifty thousand dollars
is a lot to come up with.
I'm sorry, V.
I know that this is an insane ask,
but I can't say anything more
except that there are lives at stake.
It doesn't need to be cash, does it?
Those Glamourge Eggs
are worth $50,000 each.
-That should do it.
-Oh, my God, V. Really?
-Aren't those your dad's?
-My mom's, actually.
Take them.
But how are you gonna get the other stuff?
I know people.
What do you think?
You need fake passports
for all these people?
They don't need to be fake.
Blank passports are fine.
They'll do everything else.
I really can't get into it,
but it is a matter of life or death.
Okay.
I know a guy.
Thank you, Toni.
[ringing]
Miss Cooper.
-What is the emergency?
-I'm sorry to bother you, Miss Bell,
but I left my calculus book on the bus
this morning.
I'm sorry, dear,
but you'll have to pick it up tomorrow.
Mr. Fritz has already left for the day.
Oh, jeez.
Well, if he's already gone...
[line ringing]
-[Edgar] Yes, Betty.
-I got everything you asked for.
Let me in.
Well done. I'll see you outside.
[line disconnects]
At last, we meet again!
[laughs]
I got everything that you asked for.
Money, passports, food, water.
It's all on the bus.
Now, where's my mom?
[grunts]
I knew you wouldn't fail me.
Oh, Betty.
It is such a shame
that you didn't accept the simple truths
I tried to instill in you.
Edgar, where is my mom?
Because without those truths...
Betty, all you're left with...
[grunts]
is pain.
Nighty-night.
[chuckles]
-Will you knock it off?
-Am I distracting you from your genius?
Hey, Forsythe. I was wondering.
Is it common for gangs...
to have a writer among its ranks?
I mean, I suppose a kid like you
needed something to call a family.
After all, weren't you
just a little urchin wandering the streets
after your mom ditched you and your
good-for-nothing drunk of a father?
Come to think of it...
isn't your little sister
a budding hooligan herself?
Only 13 years old and already roped
into your mom's drug business.
You're right.
I wasn't born in rarified air.
I didn't grow up with any silver spoons.
But my dad had the strength
to turn his life around
and become a sheriff.
And I have friends and family
that actually care for me.
Can you even say the same?
So, why don't you try writing
a compelling drama...
instead of starting it?
[classical music playing over speakers]
Smithers?
Daddy?
You're supposed to be in jail.
Mija, I own that jail.
I come and go as I please.
I heard a nasty little rumor
that you were dropping the Lodge name.
I've never taken the trash out, Daddy...
but I know when something's rotten.
That name is mud. And I'm done with it.
Do you know who Jaime Luna was?
Doesn't ring a bell.
Yeah, well, Luna was my father's name
and Jaime Luna was the name
of his only son.
Me.
Yeah, I wasn't born Hiram Lodge.
I became him.
You have no idea what it was like
to be a Luna in a town like Riverdale.
Everyone looked down on us
because of that name.
So, I took a name
that people would respect: Lodge.
And when my father found out...
he was angry.
And he beat me.
I didn't understand it because
I didn't want his life, I wanted mine.
My own name. What was the big deal?
Well, mija...
it is now...
in this very moment
that I understand my father's rage.
Do you think that changing your name
is gonna wash away your sins?
It won't.
I'm not going down the same path
as you did, Daddy.
You keep telling yourself that
because you'll always be part
of this family. It's in your blood.
And that... doesn't wash out.
Don't bother changing the locks.
You can't keep me out.
Hey, can we talk?
Sure. What's up?
I want you to come back
to Chicago with me.
-Mom.
-You can finish your senior year there.
-You can start again.
-I don't wanna start again.
My best bet at going to college is on
a football scholarship.
Otherwise, how would I even be able
to afford college?
Your father and I started a fund for you
when you were born.
What? A fund? I have money?
I was reluctant to tell you
because I thought you'd wanna use it
-on the community center.
-Of course I would.
Archie, as noble an idea as that may be,
do you really think that it's gonna make
a difference here in Riverdale?
I mean, all the crime here,
your friend Munroe's little brother
beaten up by a bunch of thugs?
Is that really the town
that you wanna invest in?
No one is safe here.
Look, I'm not gonna give up on Riverdale
the same way you did.
I moved to Chicago
because I couldn't find a job here.
And don't blame me
if I'm trying to stop my child
from putting his money
into a losing proposition.
Well, I guess that's the difference
between you and me, Mom.
I don't think
Riverdale is a losing proposition.
The same as Dad.
I'm not moving.
And I will make a difference here.
[video games beeping]
If we're gonna do this, we're gonna do it
right, okay? You guys follow my orders.
[Archie] Hey.
You Dodger?
That ain't your business.
Yeah.
Your days of exploiting kids
to do your dirty work ends tonight.
I want you and all your little buddies
out of Riverdale.
You and that Louisville Slugger?
[man] Exactly.
I'd take a closer look, friend.
You're outnumbered 5-to-1.
I'll take those odds.
Sorry I came by so late, Mrs. Andrews.
No, not at all. But Archie's in bed.
I'm actually here to see you.
That's $40,000.
I'm giving it to you to give to Archie
for the community center.
He's too proud to take it from me.
Veronica, thank you.
But we can't accept this.
We can't be in that kind of debt
to your family.
And if you put that money into the center,
it keeps Archie here in Riverdale,
away from college, away from his future.
At the risk of overstepping, Mrs. Andrews,
I'm not investing in a building.
I'm investing in your son.
I believe in Archie,
and he makes me wanna believe in myself.
And I need that right now.
Tear the check up if you want,
but I really hope you don't.
[Cheryl] Rise and shine, my dearest.
It's another magnificent day
that's ours for the taking.
Jay-Jay.
Weren't you over there
whilst I read to you at nighttide?
Red?
What the hell happened?
You should see Dodger and the other guys.
They're not gonna be messing
with your brother anytime soon.
You went after them without me.
What happens
if those scumbags look for payback?
They're not going to. I was in disguise.
So, you're a superhero now?
The good news is we got enough money
to buy a second bathroom.
Oh, hell, no.
You know we can't use this, right?
This money is dirty.
Only a fool would spend this cash.
It needs to be cleaned first.
Any chance
your girlfriend could help us with that?
So, we have three votes for Story C,
which makes Story C our winner,
which is penned by...
Donna Sweett.
Stories A and B,
written by Bret and Jughead...
tied for last place.
Well, at least you didn't kill each other.
[Alice] Elizabeth?
Elizabeth?
-Oh...
-Mom.
-Where are we?
-In one of the motel rooms.
Edgar's been keeping me here
ever since he figured out I was the mole.
I'll kill him.
Honey, I am so sorry.
I was trying to keep you safe.
I didn't want you to know.
I needed to get Polly out.
Do you know what Edgar's plan is?
What?
Evelyn is gonna drive the bus full of
Farmies off of a cliff as a distraction,
while he...
-What?
-...takes off in his rocket.
-Yeah.
-He bought a rocket?
-No. He's been building one.
Yeah, because harvesting organs isn't--
Isn't enough.
What is he planning to do with us?
We're gonna be tied
to the front of the bus as shields.
Unless we can figure out
a way out of here.
I think I actually have an idea.
We have to get back-to-back.
Miss Cheryl, Miss Antoinette.
I'll be needing some money
and the skeleton key for the house.
Excuse me? What possibly for?
Thistlehouse has rats in the walls.
-I went into the basement--
-Halt!
You went down to the basement?
Specifically after I ordered you not to?
-You didn't go into the chapel, did you?
-No.
-Miss Cheryl--
-Thistlehouse has never had rats.
But, babe, we did hear something
last night, remember?
No. You're right, Tee-Tee.
And suddenly,
I am feeling the presence of a rat.
A 6-foot-tall rat with muscles
and bedroom eyes.
Darius, I knew you were a mistake
from the beginning.
So, you're fired.
Toodles!
All right, ladies. Time's up. Let's go.
♪ When the dark is closin' in ♪
♪ What's your endgame? ♪
Those bitches.
♪ Tell me, tell me ♪
♪ Would you buy your kingdom now? ♪
Now we just have to make it
to the courtyard without being shot.
♪ Tell me
Are you laughing now? ♪
♪ When there's nowhere left to go ♪
♪ Who's gonna save your soul? ♪
♪ Tell me
What's your endgame? ♪
-Where did you get this from?
-I took it off some lowlife drug dealers.
Ronnie, I hate to ask you this,
but is there anything you can do?
Any way you can clean it
so I can use it for the center?
Archie, I know you're trying to do good,
but this... isn't it.
My advice? Burn it.
All of it.
-And let me pay for the renovation.
-[scoffs] Ronnie.
Archie, please just forget your pride
for a second
and let me be a part of what you're doing.
I need to be a part of what you're doing.
Keep it moving, keep it moving.
Edgar has decreed, it's time to go, okay?
Everybody on the bus. Keep moving.
Speak with enough authority
and they'll do anything you say.
Once we drive the Farmies out,
Charles can come in, take down Edgar.
Traitor.
There is a trai-- Ooh!
He's-- He's fine.
Get him on the bus, okay? Please?
Okay. Keep going. Keep going.
Keep moving. All right?
Oh, no.
Give me the gun.
Get everybody on the bus.
I'm gonna stop Edgar.
Okay.
Okay, keep going, keep going.
Mr. Weatherbee.
I told Edgar I wasn't the mole,
but he wouldn't listen. And he cut it off.
Miss Cooper, I don't know how I let myself
get embroiled in this madness.
Mr. Weatherbee, this is your last shot
at redemption, okay?
Get everybody on this bus.
Go. Please.
-Okay?
-On the bus.
Okay.
[Weatherbee] Everyone, get on the bus.
Let's go, everybody.
[cell phone rings]
-Hello?
-[Betty] Charles.
It's me. I'm inside the motel.
You've gotta get out of there.
Governor Dooley is sending in
a team of mercenaries.
Tell them to stand down.
There is a busload of unarmed civilians,
including women and children,
headed your way.
[Alice] Hands up, Edgar.
Sister Alice.
Come with me peacefully
or I will shoot you in the kneecaps
-and drag your ass out of here myself.
-You betrayed us.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Do you remember the story
of the prophet Elijah, Alice?
He was seized by a whirlwind...
and lifted up into the sky
in a chariot of fire.
Elijah ascended.
And I will, too.
[gunshots]
Mom?!
Oh, my God, Mom.
What happened? Are you okay?
Edgar ascended.
[Munroe] Jab high. Jab high.
Jab low.
Jab high.
And cross. Good work. And cross.
And jab. And jab.
And cross.
And jab.
Up high, jab.
Need any help?
[Munroe] Good job. Cross. Up high.
Mom? What's going on?
I was leaving, but what's going on is,
I will be focusing more on pro-bono work
in the foreseeable future
here in Riverdale.
And my first order of business is to get
your community center
declared a 501(c)(3).
That's a nonprofit.
It means that you can ask for donations,
you don't have to pay taxes,
you can apply for grants.
Well, that's amazing.
Except I don't know how to do any of that.
Yeah. You're a lot like your dad
in that way.
So, you'll just leave it to me,
and you can go help those kids out there.
Deal. What happened to Chicago?
I'll call the airline
and cancel the flight.
I don't think I'll be back anytime soon.
Hello, Daddy.
I'm sure you'll be getting a call
from Mr. Sowerberry soon, but...
I just wanted to let you know face-to-face
that I'm no longer a Lodge.
Mija, how many times
must we go through this?
I'm officially changing my name
to Veronica Luna.
And I'm changing the locks
and I'm installing an alarm,
and I'm sleeping
with a Taser under my pillow.
And you better believe I'll use it.
He didn't see you, did he, Jason?
[screams] Get off! Get off of him!
[thud]
We're gonna fix you right up, Jay-Jay.
Cheryl, what the hell is going on here?
Toni.
You've never met Jason, have you?
-[Jughead] Oh, no.
-[girl] His dad was the Gargoyle King.
[boy] His real name is Moose?
[girl] His girlfriend was murdered
by the Black Hood.
Everybody knows.
So much for a new start.
I'm done here.
[Jughead] He was a broken man, Betty.
And it was Bret, of course.
He did it because he blames me
for not winning the contest.
Or maybe he's just a sociopath.
He knew that he couldn't get to me
directly, so he went after Moose?
This is nothing like fighting
the Ghoulies.
This is psychological warfare.
God, poor Moose.
Just be careful, Jug.
Aww, don't worry about me.
Hey, how's your mom and Polly?
[Betty chuckles]
My mom is already working
on her exposé of the Farm.
Polly started this program
at the Shady Grove treatment center.
She's getting the help that she needs.
What about Charles? Is he the real deal?
Can we trust him?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm just happy
that this nightmare is finally over.
[doorbell rings]
Famous last words.