[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
Jughead?
Moose.
What the hell? Wait, are you my roommate?
Hermione Lodge, you're under arrest
for conspiracy to commit murder.
Your own husband's.
Mija, I'm not paying for your crimes.
I told the world what you are.
Deal with it.
I think you'd make an excellent candidate
for the Junior FBI training program.
So are you warming up
to our half brother now?
[Betty] Yeah. Kind of.
[Jughead] I'm just glad that Charles
was there for you.
[Munroe] Didn't you say we'd turn
this place into a community center?
[Archie] Feels like it's time.
No one is safe here. Is that really
the town that you wanna invest in?
You're not considering
fighting crime in those tights, are you?
Of course not.
I'm gonna need a mask.
[Jughead] They say every town
gets the hero it deserves.
Riverdale's was Archie Andrews.
High school athlete by day,
would-be crime fighter by night,
patrolling the shadows of Sketch Alley
down by the Southside Docks
where Archie's community center is.
You wouldn't wanna be caught there
too long after dark.
That's when the rats came out.
[woman shrieks]
-Here.
-Stay away from me!
[groaning]
All in all,
not an auspicious second outing
for Riverdale's dark-suited vigilante.
[school bell rings]
And speaking of crime-fighting...
Kev, what are your after-school plans?
Cruising the bathrooms at Sheds and Royal.
Perfect. Then you can join me
for my first Junior FBI class.
The one that
your hot half brother's teaching?
Yes. I asked Charles if you could enroll
and he said everyone's welcome.
Remind me,
is your brother gay or straight?
I actually have no idea.
But seniors from a bunch
of different high schools signed up,
so who knows, maybe you'll meet
a cute, gay FBI agent-in-training.
I'm in. When and where?
It seems that the district attorney
is pinning her entire case
on linking you to Hiram's
would-be murderer, Tall Boy Petite.
Which is absurd.
I've never even had
any interaction with the man.
There is still the issue
of the large sum of money the police found
in your monogrammed Tucci bag
in Tall Boy's apartment.
Obviously, Hiram planted it there
to frame me.
FP will testify that he searched
Tall Boy's apartment right after he died.
He'll swear that there was no bag of money
in evidence at that time.
This week is insane.
I've got two papers due,
your trial is starting,
Daddy's trial is around the corner...
I've heard the federal prosecutor's
going after your father pretty hard.
Oh, I know,
I've been meeting with her on the DL.
Goals for this week?
Get Mom out of jail
and make sure Daddy stays rotting in his.
[Donna] What are you working on?
The same thing as when
you drugged me, Donna.
Except this time,
I actually found something.
The Stonewall Four
is supposed to be an urban legend,
but when I checked the town paper,
four people had actually gone missing
over the last 30 years.
It's exactly what happened to Moose.
Marmaduke is fine.
He's just busy in basic training.
Look.
We've been texting.
[Chipping] You guys are in for a treat.
Advanced copies of my latest novel.
Doesn't hit stores till Christmas,
so no spoilers.
Wait, Mr. Chipping,
you wrote a Baxter Brothers mystery?
Are you Franklin P. Paxton?
I am. Well, it's my nom de plume.
But The Secret of the Old Windmill
came out like, what, decades ago?
How is that possible?
I am merely the latest in a long line
of ghostwriters over the decades.
My mind is blown. I used to love
these books when I was a kid.
They were my gateway drug
into serious crime fiction.
[scoffs]
[Chipping] Well, then you're in luck.
To celebrate the publication
of Ten Little Boy Scouts,
Stonewall Prep is throwing me
a little wine and cheese,
to which you are all invited.
As are the previous ghostwriters.
[door bells jingle]
♪ Things I said I'd do ♪
What's wrong, Pop?
It's a subpoena.
From your father's defense team.
Oh, no.
They'll probably ask
if you doctored La Bonne Nuit's books
to make my father look guilty.
Which I did.
And I have no regrets about that,
Veronica, you needed the help.
But I cannot place my hand on a Bible
and say otherwise.
Let me get into it
with the federal prosecutor.
Don't worry, I won't let you
get caught up in this.
Just when I thought
you couldn't possibly go any lower,
you prove me wrong, Daddy.
Pop Tate is a good man. There is no need
to drag him into the mess of your trial.
I'm fighting for my freedom.
And to be clear,
I didn't drag Pop into this, you did.
Because you were extorting me.
You can spare Pop
and end this right now, mija.
Come clean to the feds,
admit you framed me.
-Hard pass.
-Then I'll be seeing Pop Tate in court.
And tell your mom good luck on her case.
I'll be rooting for her.
We have a problem. If Pop takes the stand,
he'll tell the truth.
And before you ask,
no, Ms. Federal Prosecutor,
I won't tell Pop to lie.
Your father's broken many laws.
But those books you provided the FBI
proving Hiram's guilt
-are at the heart of our case.
-Call me as a witness.
I'll testify that I was the one
who tasked Pop with doctoring the books
as a last resort because my father
was extorting me, which is the truth.
Once I do that, I doubt they'll wanna
spend much time talking about any books.
Okay. Meanwhile,
good luck with your mother's case.
For our first session, thought we'd start
in the deep end of the swimming pool.
With serial killers.
Your half brother is so hot.
I've put together a little exercise
to kick us off.
This is a crime scene where six victims
were found buried along a riverbank
in the Pacific Northwest.
Before I start filling in the details,
any guesses on which one of these men
is the murderer?
It's the third man.
That's correct, Betty.
How did you know that?
I don't know, just intuition?
Okay, then.
Let's try another one.
Which one's the serial killer?
The term "serial killer"
is relatively new.
It wasn't until the 1970s
that the phrase "serial murderer"
or "serial homicide"--
It's the one in the middle.
Correct again.
Your intuition is like a sixth sense.
Let's go again.
When defining a serial killer,
it usually refers to someone
who committed three or more murders--
None of them did it.
Excellent work, Betty.
Not many people
have that kind of raw instinct.
You're like Beautiful Mind, but...
for serial killers.
Can any of you guess
what the murderers all have in common?
Nothing. Isn't that kind of the point?
They all have one thing in common.
A specific set of genes.
[Alice] They discovered
that you have the MAOA
-and the CDH13 genes.
-CDH13, also known as--
The serial killer genes.
Hey, Dad, have you seen
my Baxter Brothers books?
I swear I took them out of the trailer
before it burned.
I don't know. Might have thrown them away.
You threw away my books?
Calm down. Before you accuse me
of book-burning,
why don't you check the storage room
in the basement?
I used to worship these guys.
Other kids wanted to be superheroes,
I wanted to be a Baxter Brother.
Oh, my God, they used to do
crossovers with Tracy True.
-Those were my favorite, remember?
-[Jughead] Yeah.
My dad used to get me one of these
each year for my birthday.
Hey, Dad, why'd you stop?
You outgrew them, boy.
I gotta run.
I'm never gonna outgrow these books.
-[Betty chuckles]
-[Jughead] This was my favorite.
[boy snoring]
[Bret] Mm. Jones, lights out.
Some of us are trying to sleep.
[yawns]
Late night, Red?
Algebra 3 is kicking my ass this year.
[man] One of you named Archie?
Yeah, that's me.
This kid says you'll vouch for him.
That's Toby, he hangs out here.
Is there a problem?
Yeah. He was shoplifting
in my convenience store.
I was reading comics.
You were loitering and then you started
to put this comic book in your jacket.
Why don't I pay for whatever
that comic book costs?
Four ninety-nine.
I don't want any of your delinquents
stepping foot in my shop.
It's bad enough
we have to walk by this halfway house.
[Munroe] Keep the change.
Grab a brush.
Here is the hero of the hour.
Class, this is Francis J. DuPont,
the originator
of the Baxter Brothers franchise
and the very first Franklin P. Paxton.
Francis, this is Bret, Joan,
Jonathan, Donna and Jughead.
Jughead?
-Is that a nickname?
-Yes, sir. It is.
And it's an honor to meet you.
I didn't have
the greatest home life growing up,
but your books
really helped me through it.
Jughead is the newest addition
to the most promising
group of students I've ever taught.
Really?
Well, is the successor amongst us, then?
Successor for what?
Chipping has written
the last four Baxter Brothers books.
It's time he pass on the torch.
Therefore, we're on the hunt for the next
ghostwriter to continue the franchise.
-You're going to pick one of us?
-Keep it in your pants, Jones.
Every Baxter Brothers author,
beginning with Mr. DuPont himself,
has gone to Stonewall Prep.
We're always looking
for young and clever minds
to keep our adventures fresh and relevant.
If you're interested in the job, you'll
have to write the first three chapters
of the next Baxter Brothers novel
and an outline for the rest of it.
[Bret] Obviously, I'm winning this.
Is there any particular style
or subject area?
We have not yet decided on a theme,
but we'll let you know.
I pulled your files, Miss Cooper.
I can confirm that you do have
the MAOA and CDH13 genes.
All good. Nothing to worry about.
I don't have the genes.
See, I told you. What a relief.
You gotta be kidding me.
Hey, get the hell away from that car!
Who are you?
You run with Dodger?
Get the hell out of here. Go!
Tell him it's over.
Tell him he's done for!
All right, listen up.
Sheriff Jones gave us a call.
Apparently, some of Dodger's crew
was stealing hubcaps last night.
He suspects it was someone
from this center.
I gave him my word that it wasn't
any of you guys, and I hope that's true.
Anyone running with Dodger's crew
is going to end up in juvie
or in an early grave.
Trust us, you don't wanna go to juvie.
If even one of you guys gets arrested,
this whole place gets shut down.
So, new rule: If you run with Dodger's
crew, then you're not welcome here.
That's it. No exceptions.
Any questions?
Yeah, I got a question.
Aren't you guys seniors?
What happens when you graduate
and go to college?
That's months away.
But what happens? You said it yourself,
they're trying to shut you down.
Why? Because of us. Because no one
wants us. At least Dodger cares.
Dodger only cares
about the money you can bring in.
We want you here, but you can't have it
both ways. You have to choose.
[Charles] One thing we see
in a lot of serial killers
are instances of animal cruelty
in their youth.
Jeffrey Dahmer, the cannibal of Milwaukee,
started killing dogs
when he was in grade school.
Ian Brady, the infamous Moors murderer,
killed his first cat when he was 10.
I'm all the dark deeds you did
in our youth,
like what we did to our old cat, Caramel.
Caramel ran away.
I didn't do anything to her.
Oh, Betty, we both know
that we drowned Caramel.
[Charles] Robert Thompson tied rabbits
to railway tracks.
Betty, are you okay?
I need to get some air. Sorry.
[Charles] Okay.
[FP] I arrived at the cabin alone.
The suspect, Tall Boy, got violent.
Resisted arrest. And unfortunately,
I had to discharge my weapon.
He expired on his way to the hospital.
And later, when you searched
Tall Boy's motel room,
did you find Hermione Lodge's Tucci bag
full of cash?
No.
And yet, the prosecution claims
they found the bag there.
-If it was, it was planted later.
-Thank you, sheriff.
Your witness, counselor.
The cabin where you claim
to have shot Tall Boy,
do you know who owns that cabin?
I assumed it was Hiram's.
This is a copy of the lease.
Kindly read the owner's name.
"Hermione Lodge."
[crowd murmuring]
-[Judge] Order.
-[gavel banging]
Order.
[Jughead] Excuse me, Mr. DuPont.
Did you happen to know my grandfather?
Forsythe Jones the First?
That is why you look familiar.
Your grandfather was an excellent writer.
Tell me, how's he doing?
Does he still write?
I... I actually don't know.
I've never met him.
Up until this exact moment,
I didn't even know he was a writer.
A bit of a brawler, too.
Forsythe got into all kinds of
rabble-rousing before he left Stonewall.
Is that why he left?
He was kicked out for fighting?
Oh, It was so long ago,
I don't remember the exact circumstances.
But I will never forget his talent.
We would read his works in class and
I couldn't believe a teenager wrote them.
-Does your father write?
-No, he's a sheriff.
Would you invite your father
to the reception tomorrow?
I would love to meet Forsythe's son.
Yeah, I'll see if he can come.
Thank you.
Mrs. Andrews is back-channeling
with the DA's office.
They're talking plea deals.
Mom... why didn't you tell us
that the cabin was under your name?
Because it wasn't.
Veronica, your father must have forged
a lease or a contract or something.
So, then why didn't you say
that you'd never even been to this cabin?
Because I have.
[gunshots]
Mom, it's now or never.
I need you to tell me the truth
about everything so I can help you.
[Mary] If everything you've told me
is true, then I have no moves left.
The more the prosecutor digs,
the guiltier you'll be.
And that's for crimes
that aren't even on their radar yet.
There's no magic wand
that makes this just go away.
What if there were one?
And my mother changed her plea to guilty?
-Veronica--
-Look, Mom, we've gotta be realistic here.
Why not admit
to what everyone already knows,
before something else,
something worse comes out?
Veronica, your mother would go to prison
probably for the rest of her life.
Not if we get someone
with a magic wand to pardon her.
[Mary] That can only happen
at the state level.
So unless you're friends
with Governor Dooley...
I wouldn't say friends exactly,
but we do have a history.
All of us.
[cat whining]
Hey, are you okay?
What are you doing?
No!
Caramel.
[knock on door]
[Jughead] Hey.
You free for lunch?
You wanna go to Pop's and get a burger?
I got a lot on my mind. What's up?
I wanted to ask you about Grandpa.
Did you know he was a writer?
Yeah.
Where'd you hear that?
Oh, one of his old classmates
is visiting Stonewall Prep.
They have a reception later,
if you wanna come hang out.
Waste a day with a bunch of blue bloods
who think they're better than me? No.
You're the one that pushed me
to go to Stonewall Prep.
Hell, you'd probably make me put on
a tie and a blazer.
And just so you know, my old man
wasn't a writer, he was a dropout.
All right? He couldn't hold down a job.
He was a mean, mean drunk who took all
of his anger out on me and your grandma.
Was the best day of my life
when he skipped out on us.
So, do I wanna hear about what a great
writer he was back in high school? No.
No, I'm...
I'm good with my memories
but you have fun.
[door closes]
Governor Dooley! You made it.
-Oh, no, not again.
-Yes, again.
I have a small favor to ask you.
I was told this meeting
was requested by the FBI.
No, I'd rather keep the FBI out of this,
if at all possible.
So, in this folder,
you'll find evidence that paints
a rather corrupt portrait of you,
governor.
Ordering a bogus quarantine.
Accepting drug money as a bribe.
Receiving kickbacks from my father's jail.
Young lady, how many times do you think
you can blackmail me?
Help me now and this will be the last.
I'll put that in writing.
As you know, my mother's on trial.
If she pleads guilty, I need you
to grant her a pardon, immediately.
In exchange, I won't release this file
of incriminating evidence.
What do you say, Donald?
Once more for old time's sake?
[DuPont tapping on glass]
May I have your attention?
In Literary Society tradition,
it wouldn't be a proper reunion
without a little game of murder.
[Chipping] For neophytes,
the rules are as follows:
Everyone draws a card.
Whoever picks "murderer"
must walk amongst us,
winking at their prey.
If you are winked at,
you die five seconds later.
The object of the game of course is to
identify the murderer before being killed.
Happy hunting, everybody.
[Donna] Enjoying yourself, Jones?
So, this is what one-percenters do
for fun. They play murder, huh?
Oh, by the way...
Wicked, Jones.
-I should--
-Yeah, go on, then. Let me die in peace.
[groans]
[boy] Nicely done.
[Chipping] Down to the wire, boys.
[coughs and chokes, then body thuds]
-It's Jughead. He's the murderer!
-Because I just killed you.
I knew it was him beforehand. I win.
I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
Because you're dead.
-No, I'm not, I--
-[DuPont] Boys. Let's be men about this.
It's clear that Jughead Jones
won the game, fair and square.
-And what a formidable murderer he was.
-Wha...
[all clapping]
I'm disappointed
I didn't get to meet your father.
Oh, yeah. He's been busy with work.
Oh, I understand.
I hope you'll enter the contest
to be our new ghostwriter.
I mean, the grandson of Forsythe Jones
would be a worthy inheritor of the mantle.
[Charles] Serial killers are compulsive.
They leave clues, take trophies,
keep records.
Journals, diaries, letters.
They see themselves as the hero
in their own stories.
Sometimes it's difficult for them to
distinguish between reality and fantasy,
fact and fabrication.
By studying childhood diaries
of serial killers,
we can gain invaluable insight
into how their minds work.
Your Honor,
in lieu of a closing statement,
my client would like to say something.
Proceed.
Your Honor, after careful consideration,
I've decided to change my plea.
I, Hermione Apollonia Lodge...
plead guilty to the charges against me.
[crowd murmuring]
[Betty] I lied to you, Kevin.
At the hospital, Dr. Patel told me
that I do have the genes.
And there's more.
Something that I think
I may have repressed.
Do you remember my cat, Caramel?
A car hit her.
-And I found her on our front lawn.
-[Caramel whining]
She was in pain.
Dying.
And it sounded like someone screaming.
So I went to get my dad for help.
And he took me back outside.
[Hal] Caramel is your cat, Betty.
You need to take care of this.
And he handed me a rock.
And he made me...
[Caramel squeals]
[Hal] Good girl, Betty.
Very good girl.
I killed Caramel.
No, Betty, that wasn't you.
That was your deeply screwed-up dad.
Oh, and I'm not screwed up?
I'm repressing memories
of killing animals, Kevin.
Betty, I think this FBI training might
be getting a little too intense right now.
I think we should
maybe consider withdrawing.
[Archie] That's it, keep your hands up.
Protect your face.
[Munroe] Jab, jab.
Good job.
[Archie] Keep those hands up.
That's it.
[FP] Hey, Red, you got a minute?
[Archie] Sure. What's up, Mr. Jones?
Some of the local business owners
have lodged a few complaints
against your center.
Littering, vandalism, public urination.
Due respect, Mr. Jones, that's BS.
I'm here every morning and I lock up
every night. These kids aren't doing that.
When I rolled with the Serpents,
we dealt with the same crap.
Wherever we set up, complaints followed.
No one wants a gang around.
The problem isn't the kids, it's the thugs
that show up after we lock up.
They're gnarly. This place is supposed
to make the neighborhood better.
Well, show them that.
Do what the Serpents used to do.
Invite some of the yokels over
for a get-to-know-you clambake.
People are less likely to call the cops
if they've had a conversation with you.
All right?
You think you really pulled something off
at the reception, don't you?
Bret, Bret, Bret. Are you really still mad
about that murder game?
All right.
Well, if it means that much to you...
Poof.
Consider yourself
raised from the dead, preppy.
"Preppy."
You turn your nose up at us,
you scorn us for our privilege.
But the only reason you're here is because
some school benefactors
thought it'd look good
to take on a charity case.
Some dirt-poor scholarship kid.
I'm here because of my writing.
Just get over it.
No, Jughead, you're not here
because of your talent.
The admissions committee?
None of them have read
a single word you've ever written.
You're a statistic, a project.
Every year there's one of you.
Some welfare freeloader
who never amounts to anything.
Just like your grandfather.
He couldn't even make it a semester.
That is your past,
present and future, Jughead.
Shut your mouth!
Looks like you've inherited
his temper, too, huh?
They all know I'm right.
And deep down, you know it, too.
Most of you know me by now,
but my name's Archie Andrews.
I run this place with Munroe Moore.
And we invited you here today to set
the record straight about a few things.
Starting with...
Despite a few bogus complaints
that have been made...
this community center
isn't going anywhere.
In fact, starting today,
we will be expanding our hours to 11 p.m.
and we'll be open on Sundays.
So, to my neighbors, I say:
Instead of working against us,
why don't you come in and help out?
Sponsor a baseball team. Donate your time.
These kids need people
to show them that they care.
Which is why we're starting
a Big Brothers and Big Sisters program.
The Riverdale High Bulldogs and Vixens
have already volunteered,
so why don't you?
And if you still wanna shut us down,
then go ahead and try.
My mom is a very good lawyer.
Or you can try the cops.
I'll call my best friend's dad,
the sheriff of Riverdale.
Otherwise, my friendly advice to you
is get out of my way.
-[Archie] Can I help you?
-Look, I own the hardware store on Drury.
And I admire what you're trying
to accomplish here.
And I'm not the only one.
So, why didn't you say that, then?
The thing is, many of us business owners
are getting... pressured
to speak out against your center.
Not by Hiram Lodge?
No. Um...
His name is Dodger.
And we've been paying him
a protection fee.
Lately, he's added a request.
Protest your center...
or risk losing his protection.
And then maybe our stores get robbed
or burned to the ground.
So Dodger's the one
who wants us out of here.
Every kid who sets foot in your place
is one less running scams
for him on the streets.
Well... look what the cat dragged in.
I'm done with Stonewall Prep.
That place is toxic.
I'm going back to Riverdale High
to be with my friends.
Nope. Mm-mm.
You're not throwing away this opportunity.
You're giving me whiplash, Dad.
What opportunity?
So I can be buried alive in a coffin?
Or be told that I'm only there
because I grew up in a trailer park?
-Someone said that to you?
-Yeah, Bret did.
Well, who cares how you got in? You're in.
And those silver spoons?
They feel threatened.
Look, this Bret kid?
He knows you're better than him,
that you're gonna leave him in the dust.
And you'll do it
without the privilege or the fancy name.
But if you drop out now,
you're no better than my old man.
If you hated him so much,
then why would you name me after him?
It's my name, too, don't forget.
And, yeah, I hate him,
but he's still my old man,
so that's gotta count for something, huh?
Also...
those books weren't from me.
Your grandad sent them from...
wherever the hell he was.
I didn't tell you because...
Because I'm still angry
at how he treated us.
Now, he was a hard man
and there was no love lost between us,
but I gotta give the devil his due.
Those books you love...
were from him.
-And you have no idea where he is now?
-No.
-Do you want me to look for him?
-No, I don't.
But I'll tell you what I do want.
I want you to go back.
I want you to do what my father never did,
what I never did. Graduate high school.
Show those preppies
what it means to be a Jones man.
Bring honor to our name.
I'm quitting the program, Charles.
-But you're a natural.
-That's the problem. It's too easy for me.
I could identify every single killer
in your slideshow.
Because I'm like them.
I have the same genes as them.
All the more reason for you
to stay in the program.
To make sense of that part of yourself.
You couldn't understand, okay?
You just don't get it.
I can.
And I do, Betty.
I have the genes, too.
In fact, it's why I joined the FBI.
To control those impulses.
You have the serial killer genes?
Yeah. You can use this. Harness this.
To keep the darkness in check.
I did.
[Veronica] Oh, that's amazing news.
Thank you so much, governor,
I really appreciate it.
No, that's fine.
I'll pick her up myself. Bye now.
Sounds like you just got some good news.
Yes, I did.
My mother's been away for a while
and she's finally coming home.
Same as your father.
-I'm sorry, do I know you?
-No, you do not.
But I'll tell you the same thing
I told the federal prosecutor.
That I'm a licensed private investigator.
That I was hired by Hiram Lodge
to uncover any malfeasance against him.
And that I can unequivocally prove
that the federal prosecutor
colluded with you to frame
and bring false charges against Hiram.
-That's not true.
-Yes, it is.
I have many recordings
of you two... plotting.
Including a conversation you two had
at that booth over there...
discussing Pop Tate's subpoena.
You had my place bugged?
Yes, I did.
So, here's what happens next.
The federal prosecutor
has already told the judge
that she's dropping the charges
against Hiram,
thanks to information I provided.
Look... whatever Hiram's paying you,
I'll double it.
Nice try.
But that won't work with me.
You see, our father needed help,
someone he could trust,
so he had me come up from Miami.
I fix things.
That's what I do.
Our father?
I don't understand.
I'm Hiram's other daughter.
Hermosa.
♪There's trouble ♪
He needed me, so I came.
♪Trouble ahead ♪
[door closes]
♪ Sun going down ♪
♪ And come back up again ♪
♪ I cry ♪
♪ Mama is cryin' ♪
♪ There's trouble ahead ♪
"Li'l Forsythe III, happy birthday.
Sorry I'm not there to celebrate with you.
Never let anyone tell you
that you don't belong.
Love, Grandpa.
P.S. Trust few.
And never let them
take anything from you."
♪ Oh, Lord, there's trouble ahead ♪
[reporters clamoring]
-[reporter 1] Sir.
-[reporter 2] Over here, over here.
Hiram. Hiram, Alice Smith with RIVW.
Please tell our viewers,
what are you feeling right now?
I couldn't be happier with the outcome.
And now that you've been vindicated
of all your crimes,
will you and your...?
Daughter.
Be leaving Riverdale?
On the contrary, I'm excited to fulfill
a lifelong dream of mine...
and announce my candidacy
for mayor of Riverdale.
[reporter 1] Mr. Lodge, is this
the beginning of your political career?
[reporters clamoring]
-[reporter 2] Do you have any idea...
-[reporter 1] Mr. Lodge!
[reporter 3] How's it feel
to have your case dismissed?
I'm confused. So we're not bailing
on your hot brother's FBI class?
Based on what happened to Caramel--
That was before I got privileged
information that made me realize
that we don't actually know anything
about Charles.
Forget "Is Charles gay or straight?"
I'm interested in,
"Is he a serial killer or not?"
I'm serious, Kevin.
The only places I've ever seen him
are Pop's, my house and the FBI office.
I mean, what does he do all day?
Where does he go? Where does he live?
And again, why is he still in Riverdale?
[Kevin] I thought he was helping out
Jughead's dad with some cases.
[Betty] What cases?
He's keeping secrets from me, Kev.
I know it.
That's why we have to stay close to him.
[Archie] We need to talk.
For too long, you've been preying on
the youth of Riverdale. That ends now.
It's time for you to book
a one-way bus ticket out of town.
I've got manpower.
The support of the people.
You... whoever the hell you are, don't.
Consider this a declaration of war.
Leave town or the next time we meet,
you won't be driving away.
You won't even be walking.
It's a promise.
I'm not going anywhere.
You're a dead man. You hear me?
You're a dead man!
Mr. Chipping and I have conferred
and decided on the theme
for our Baxter Brothers
writing competition.
Who's interested?
Jughead?
Oh, no. I'm in. And I'm winning.
And please, Mr. Chipping, from here on,
you can call me Forsythe III.
It's after my grandfather.
[DuPont] Wonderful.
Then you and your classmates
will be challenged to devise...
the perfect murder.
That's your theme.
Let the bloodbath begin.
Archie Andrews,
Betty Cooper and Veronica Lodge,
you're under arrest for the cold-blooded
murder of my son, Jughead Jones.
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Howl ♪