[Jughead] The weirdest thing
about pretending to be dead is
that after a while, you actually start
feeling like you're dead.
As in "dead as a doornail" dead.
[beeps]
For starters, I was underground,
as if in a tomb.
Granted, I was hiding out
in Dilton's doomsday bunker
and not in a coffin, but still.
Two weeks, no sunlight,
with no sense of time or its passing.
It's gotta be what Limbo
feels like, right?
Other similarities to being dead:
Not one, but two obituaries about me ran.
A rather perfunctory one
in The Riverdale Register.
A second, more irreverent one
in The Blue and Gold.
I liked that one.
And a funeral.
Well, a wake.
I watched it on my laptop.
Live-streamed from a camera
Betty had set up in the living room.
Betty and I suspected
the Stonies would show up.
And sure enough, they did.
We wanted to study them,
to see if anything they did
was suspicious.
Not that there was any doubt
in our mind about their guilt.
The preppies had stone-cold murdered me
and were trying to pin it on Betty.
We just couldn't prove it.
Not yet.
Meanwhile, the hardest part
of playing dead
was letting everyone believe
I was in the semisweet hereafter.
Our family, our friends.
The lies we had to tell,
the things we had to do
to sell that illusion.
Like pretending that my bereft girlfriend
had found comfort
in the strong, steely arms of my best bud.
Which turned out to be
the greatest misdirect of them all.
Of course, we needed
to let some people know the truth.
Except in one case.
My kid sister, Jellybean?
Didn't have to be told.
Oh, you found the fake blood.
Thanks, Jellybean.
Do you need it for Jughead?
What? What do you--? What do you mean?
Do you need it to help my brother?
Jellybean, do you know where Jughead is?
I heard you whispering on the phone
to Charles last night.
The walls are super thin.
You don't have to tell me where he is,
just that he's okay.
Is he... okay?
-Can you keep a secret?
-[knocking on door]
[Jughead] We brought my dad into it
pretty quick, too.
Hey, Betty.
I, uh...
I gave that bloody rock to Charles.
He said the FBI was gonna have it tested.
When they do, they'll tell you
that it's covered in fake blood
that you can buy at a drugstore.
-What the hell are you talking about?
-I don't want you to worry anymore.
I'm really sorry
that you've been worrying.
Jughead's fine.
He's-- Okay, he's not fine, but he's okay.
Hold on.
-You know where Jughead is?
-Yes.
I will tell you everything, okay?
But we really, really need your help,
please?
I'm afraid to ask, but what kind of help?
For starters...
a search party.
[Jughead] Archie went rogue
and told his mom, too.
Mom, I have to confess something to you.
[Jughead] And then there was
Veronica's sister, Hermosa,
who was sniffing around,
looking for bones.
All right. What do you want to know?
Let me ask you straight up, hermanita.
Did you help Betty kill her boyfriend?
What?
No, why would I do that?
Because that's the kind of thing
secret girlfriends do.
They kill each other's boyfriends
so they can be together.
Okay.
I don't know what kind of crypto-lesbian
pulp fiction you're conjuring, Hermosa,
but Betty and I are just friends.
Well, then what did happen
to that dead Torombolo?
Either you can tell me,
or I'll just keep digging.
-Don't forget, I'm a licensed private--
-Private investigator. Right.
I'm not sure why I didn't think
of this before...
but maybe you could help us
with something.
Me, Betty and Archie.
How much do you charge, Hermosa?
And is there a discount
for family members?
[Jughead] In the months that followed,
people will ask us,
did we need to do it?
Go to such extreme lengths?
Maybe. Maybe not.
But this I did know:
If I was going to recover without
the preppies trying to kill me again
and figure out how to solve my own murder,
I needed the illusion to be perfect
to buy myself time.
[woman] Please make sure
you're following along.
[Jughead] And so while above me,
a world without Jughead
continued spinning forward...
I pored over every scrap
of evidence we'd gathered.
Went over every detail of my time
at Stonewall Prep,
looking for hidden patterns,
hints and clues.
But this was a different kind of mystery
than the ones we'd tackled before.
This wasn't a whodunit.
This was a whydunit. More psychological.
I needed to get under my suspects' skin,
inside their heads.
I had to let my intuition take over,
to draw these strands together.
The missing Stonewall Four,
the accidental deaths
of DuPont's classmates,
my attempted murder.
How were they all connected?
A key piece of information
came from Hermosa.
Which was that Donna--
Jug?
Are you okay?
Yeah, sorry. I was just going
over everything one more time.
-What's up? Did they find him?
-Yeah. Yes. We did.
-Well, I mean, Charles and FP did.
-Did he agree?
Completely.
He's showering as we speak.
-So, are we gonna do this or what?
-Oh, yeah.
We are gonna blow Stonewall Prep
out of the water.
Crime and Punishment,
a novel of murder
and its psychological toll.
Floor is open.
Any thoughts regarding
Dostoyevsky's take on morality?
Hey, guys.
What? Did you even miss me?
-You gotta be kidding me.
-Mr. Jones.
I, uh-- I don't understand.
We all thought--
That I was dead? Well...
-actually for a minute there, I did, too.
-Yeah.
Hey, what's that, um,
oft-used Mark Twain quote?
"Rumors of my death
have been greatly exaggerated."
What is happening right now?
It is called getting
your comeuppance, Joan.
You guys are reading
Crime and Punishment, huh?
How... apropos.
You know, the one kind of crime story
that we never touched upon in this seminar
is the time-tested genre
of a locked-room mystery.
Where all the suspects
are sequestered in a room,
one or more of them could be the killer,
but the door is not unlocked
until the identity is revealed.
Betty, could you do the honor?
The next bell doesn't ring
for half an hour,
so for the next 30 minutes,
your asses belong to us.
I knew you weren't really dead.
Good job, Donna.
Yet, since you failed to prove it
or find Jughead,
we had time to figure out all the twists
and turns of this murder mystery
that we've all been living
for the past few months.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh, look, don't worry.
I'll take you through it step by step.
This is ridiculous.
Mr. DuPont, I'm calling security.
Shut the hell up, Bret. Like I said,
for the next 30 minutes, we're in charge,
so give me your phones.
-Why the hell--?
-Joan, just do what she says.
We have nothing to hide.
I'd get comfortable if I were you.
'Cause I'm going to take you through it
from the very beginning.
Starting with that very curious fact
that both Moose Mason and myself
were invited to Stonewall Prep
during our senior year.
Jughead?
Moose.
What the hell? It's good to see you.
Was it like that when you met
my grandfather, Forsythe the First?
He was asked to study at Stonewall, too.
You were roommates with him,
weren't you, Mr. DuPont?
Yes.
And you're very much like him, Mr. Jones.
Your grandfather was
an arrogant fool, too.
Why do you say that?
Huh?
Because he had the gall to consider
himself worthy of your inner circle?
The first iteration
of Stonewall's Literary Society.
What exactly is this proving?
That this is not a story about a murder.
This is a story about grandparents
and their grandchildren.
Of the sins from one generation
being passed down to the next.
Cycles of violence.
Which brings me to my next point:
Halloween, when I was drugged
by you psychos.
I think I...
I think I need some air.
No.
You need to lie down.
[heart beating]
Say hello to the Stonewall Four for us.
[Jughead] Only to wake up in a coffin
and be let out a day later...
to return to my dorm.
Moose, you are not going
to believe what Bret--
And find that Moose had vanished.
So, naturally, I assumed he went out
the same way as the Stonewall Four,
that group of students
that mysteriously vanished
while attending Stonewall Prep
over a few decades.
Oh, here we go again.
Now, Moose's fate was more banal.
He joined the Army.
But there's a twist.
Mr. Chipping was the one
who encouraged Moose to enlist.
But it was more like force him to.
He was encouraging me to leave.
Until Halloween night,
when it became more than a suggestion.
He practically shoved me out the door.
So, what was the connection
between Moose and Chipping
that would make him take his advice?
He recruited me to play football.
Wait, Mr. Chipping's the reason
why you went to Stonewall Prep?
Chipping had recruited Moose
the same way he had Jughead,
and then ran him out of Stonewall Prep.
Meaning what, exactly?
Meaning, Chipping knew
Moose was going to get murdered
and was trying to save his life.
And I would remember that next point.
It's gonna be on the quiz.
-Oh, Mr. Jon--
-Shut up!
Mr. DuPont,
as they say in Lord of the Flies:
"I have the conch."
Now, after Halloween is
when things got really interesting.
See, that's when you announced
the writing competition.
Chipping has written
the last four Baxter Brothers books.
It's time he pass on the torch.
And someone in this very room was going
to be anointed the next ghostwriter.
You had already taken
a shine to me, Mr. DuPont.
You were asking about my father
and my grandfather.
Your grandfather was an excellent writer.
Tell me, how's he doing?
Does he still write?
So, imagine my surprise...
when I found out my good-for-nothing,
dropout grandfather
had actually written
the original Baxter Brothers novel.
Which a young Francis DuPont
would steal from him.
It was a 100 percent legal transaction,
a sale--
It was highway robbery.
A measly 5 grand for an idea
that generated millions of dollars?
You exploited Forsythe, Mr. DuPont.
You took advantage of a kid
from the wrong side of the tracks.
And if that secret ever came out,
can you imagine the damage that would do
to the very valuable
Baxter Brothers brand?
[exhales] Hell...
someone might kill to keep that secret.
Which is exactly what we thought
happened with Mr. Chipping.
I told Chipping about my gramps.
Then he talked to you, Mr. DuPont.
And the very next day, well...
I think we all remember
his dive out the window.
I thought you had urged him to do it,
that you had some leverage over Chipping.
You guys were part of the same
secret society, Quill and Skull.
But it was actually you guys.
It was your... blank expressions
as you watched him jump.
Call an ambulance!
I just couldn't shake it.
That's when I knew
there was a deeper game afoot.
No, Chipping suicided because
he was messing around with Donna.
-She ended it and he short-circuited.
-Except...
they never really had
a physical relationship.
Isn't that right, Donna?
-We had an affair, and it got out of hand.
-Mm-hm.
Yes, an affair that went down exactly
like the affair that you had with...
Mr. Kotter.
Except, I looked into it and...
turns out there is no Mr. Kotter.
-Rupert-- Rupert had demons.
-Oh, he did.
Mrs. Chipping filled us in
on all of those.
Yeah, she said that he had been
drinking more and having trouble sleeping.
Complaining about
the Baxter Brothers books.
Wishing he'd never gotten the contract.
So, then we started to ask ourselves,
what would turn
the opportunity of a lifetime,
winning the Baxter Brothers contract,
into a burden? An albatross?
Any ideas?
The ghostwriter challenge was
to devise the perfect murder.
What if the real challenge,
the real price that someone had to pay,
was to commit the perfect murder?
In order to prove that you could write it,
first you had to do it.
I mean, it kind of makes
a twisted pathological sense, no?
And that's what was tormenting
Mr. Chipping.
The guilt of what he had done,
the blood that he had shed
in order to win the contract.
Mr. Chipping invited Moose
to Stonewall Prep to be the next victim,
to be killed by the next ghostwriter,
one of you.
And Moose was the perfect candidate.
He was a messed-up kid, he had no family.
He couldn't handle the stresses of life.
After my dad was arrested
for impersonating the Gargoyle King,
it, uh... kind of blew up my life,
my family, everything.
I even ended up in a facility
for a couple months.
Chipping ran Moose out of town.
You said it yourself.
Good. You remembered. Okay.
We think Chipping couldn't go
through with it
and/or maybe he just wanted to atone
for what he had done.
Whatever the reason, he ran Moose
the hell away from Stonewall Prep
and then killed himself.
It was his only escape.
Pure demented conjecture.
Well, yes and no.
Chipping's behavior is hypothesis,
but if proven,
it shows a pattern of how the previous
ghostwriters won their contracts.
The same year, the same month
as Chipping was awarded his contract,
a Stonewall student disappeared.
One of the so-called Stonewall Four.
We believe this student was murdered
by Mr. Chipping.
Ryan Allan, the previous ghostwriter
who took up the mantle
the same month another one
of the Stonewall Four disappeared.
The sequence holds true
for every ghostwriter who preceded them.
It's actually incredibly simple.
Which brings us to a couple months ago
when I was awarded the contract.
But why?
To put a target on my back.
Probably because I was circling the truth,
so he gave you guys a new challenge:
To commit the perfect murder against me...
and be awarded the contract.
[Betty]
So, the million-dollar question is...
who was going to kill Jughead, and how?
So, which one of you
heartless bastards killed me?
It was actually Mr. DuPont
that gave me a clue.
When I asked who had rewritten
my Baxter Brothers novel,
you told me they all had a crack at it.
Well, actually, all of your classmates
collaborated on it.
And that suggested to me that
each one of you had a hand in my murder.
This should be good.
Donna, you kept Betty busy.
Oh, good, you made it.
[Jughead] Bret, you led me deeper
into the woods,
where I took off the bunny mask
I was wearing and put on my beanie.
And was it that beanie that kept my head
from being completely cracked open
when Joan crept up behind me
and hit me with a baseball-sized rock?
What? How do you know it was me?
Why couldn't it have been Jonathan?
Well, I don't recall
Jonathan wearing your perfume.
Yeah, where--?
Where is Jonathan again?
Or did you kill him because he started
to develop a conscience?
He had food poisoning.
-He still has food poisoning.
-Okay.
Jonathan aside, you had a foolproof plan,
airtight alibis.
It all should have worked so perfectly,
but it didn't.
-Why?
-Because in all your plotting,
all of your lurid conspiring
and your brilliance, you didn't kill me.
Whose job was it to check my pulse?
Jonathan!
Oh, you Einsteins, all you had to do
was hit me in the back of the head
hard enough with the rock.
You failed, spectacularly.
Yeah, meanwhile, Donna was blowing
Devil's Breath in my face
to set me up as the ultimate fall girl.
Devil's Breath? Really?
Yeah, the technical term
being scopolamine,
which leaves a person highly suggestive
and in a drunken state,
which is why I don't remember
when Donna led me into the clearing
where Jughead's body was
and placed the bloody rock in my hand,
leaving me literally red-handed
with the murder weapon.
After which, the four of you returned
to the party,
and ran into Archie and Veronica.
Hey.
Have you guys seen Betty and Jughead?
I think they went that way,
into the clearing behind those trees.
Thanks.
[Betty] And pointed them
to where you knew they would find me...
standing over Jughead's corpse.
-Oh, my God. Betty, what happened?
-Jug!
Is he breathing?
He's dead.
At which point, one of two scenarios
could have played out.
One...
Archie and Veronica could turn me in.
Two...
they could help me cover up the murder
that I had just committed.
Either way, I'm damned if I do
and damned if I don't,
but honestly, you guys could have
gotten away with it, too.
Yeah, except, uh, again...
you guys didn't kill me.
-Archie.
-Oh, my God.
-Betty, what happened?
Arch, start pounding on his chest.
Right now, okay?
Vee, use the beanie
to stop the bleeding, go.
One, two, three, four, five.
-[Archie] One... Four, five.
-Come on, Jug.
-Wake up, wake up, Jug. Come on!
-[Veronica] He's dead.
Four...
-Betty, he's dead.
-Come back to me, Jug.
Jug! Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, we'll get you to a hospital, okay?
No. No hospital.
Jug...
Hey, stay awake. Stay with me please, Jug.
Hey, stay awake, okay?
Though I didn't regain consciousness
for another 36 hours.
The worst 36 hours of my life.
Why would you say that, Jones?
"No hospital." Why would a man
on death's door say that?
I honestly don't know.
Maybe I had some small feeling that
you were going to try and frame Betty,
and I wanted her to have
a fighting chance.
Um, I'm calling Charles.
I'm calling Charles.
-What? Why?
-We can trust him.
He'll help us, okay?
Hey, Jug.
Charles! I'm in the woods
with Archie and Veronica. Jughead,
he's hurt really badly.
We need-- We need help.
We need your help, please.
We carried Jug through the woods
to the old postal road
where my brother Charles was waiting
for us with an FBI med van.
-What happened to him, Betty?
-A head wound.
We slowed the bleeding.
We did chest compressions and CPR.
-You think he'll make it?
-We'll do everything we can.
[Veronica] And us? What do we do?
Go back to where you found him,
clean the scene.
Make absolutely certain that you don't
leave anything behind, all right?
Also, your clothes are covered with blood.
Get rid of those and get washed up, okay?
[all] Okay.
Come on.
[Betty] And then we did
what Charles asked.
We went back to the clearing...
threw the bloody rock
in the swimming hole...
took off our clothes,
and started a bonfire.
-What happens if he doesn't make it?
-He'll make it.
But what if he doesn't?
He will.
But if he doesn't...
then we...
Archie.
-Archie!
-Yeah, yeah.
-Are you listening to me?
-Yeah.
We have to burn all of our clothes,
including Jughead's beanie.
We'll rinse off the blood
in the swimming hole.
After tonight,
we never speak of this, ever.
Not to each other, not to our parents.
No one.
We'll finish our senior year, graduate,
and we'll go our separate ways.
That is the only way
that we won't get caught.
Do it.
That is how it'll have to be
if Jug doesn't make it.
But it won't come to that.
He will pull through.
He has to.
And then...
we went home.
And what happened next
was a waking nightmare.
Not knowing if or when Jughead
was going to wake up.
And wondering if I had actually
been responsible.
Wait, but we saw Jughead's corpse
at the coroner's office.
-Was he in on it?
-Who? Dr. Curdle Jr.?
Yeah. Mm-hm. Yeah. We go way back.
[Jughead] You see, Bret,
in a town like Riverdale,
everybody's got a price.
And that includes our friendly
neighborhood doctor of death.
And while Betty was keeping you guys busy
with a game of cat and mouse,
I was in the underground bunker
untangling this Gordian knot of a year.
And it is crazy how much untangling
you can get done
-when everyone thinks you're dead.
-Which brings us basically to today.
So, Mr. DuPont...
floor's open. What do you think?
Oh, Mr. Jones...
A for effort.
If nothing else, this fiction
is significantly more entertaining
than anything you ever produced
for my class.
Oh, did I forget to mention
that Betty and I went and saw
the Baxter Brothers ghostwriters?
And when we told them our theory,
they all asked for their lawyers.
What if you did track them down?
And even if you found one
who corroborated your wild theories
in some vague way,
then you will know that I never
explicitly directed my students
or mentees to do anything criminal.
Oh.
What a canny serial killer you are,
Mr. DuPont.
But we haven't even gotten
to the best part.
Specifically, the three members
of your original Literary Society
who you murdered.
Jane Dallas Brown, Charles W. Chickens,
Theodore Weisel.
There it is.
Let's loop back to the original sin,
shall we?
When Mr. DuPont stole,
and I do mean "stole,"
my grandfather's original
Baxter Brothers novel.
A fact known to you, Mr. DuPont,
and of course Jughead's grandfather,
but also to your inner circle,
your classmates.
The corrupt secret
at the heart of an empire.
[Jughead] Well, there wasn't
an empire just yet.
It was a house of cards that you built
over many decades.
And the bigger it got,
the more worried you became
that one little slip of the tongue
would send the whole thing tumbling down.
Your life's work would be revealed
as a lie
and you as a fraud and a thief,
a man of dishonor.
So, you started going after people
who knew the truth
and started staging
their accidental deaths.
You cut brakes.
You tampered with fuselages.
You compromised oxygen tanks.
Until there was only one living member
of your Literary Society left.
Betty...
I think it's time we let in our guest.
With pleasure.
[lock clicking]
Forsythe?
Live and in the flesh.
Hello, Francis.
Why don't you tell him
what you told us, Grandpa?
Weisel came to see me before he died.
He hadn't slept for days.
He told me
that you killed Charles and Jane
'cause they were gonna spill the truth
about the damn Baxter Brothers.
He said we knew too much,
and you were gonna off us, too.
You and I both know
Theodore was a paranoid drunk.
But two days later,
the expert diver drowned in shallow water.
So, he was right.
And I was next.
So, I went out for a pack of cigarettes...
and I never came back.
What were you doing off-grid
since 2002 exactly?
Collecting evidence
that linked Francis here
with the murders of Charles
and Jane and Theodore.
I started by calling hotels and motels
near the accident sites.
You know what the one thing I couldn't
figure out at first was, Mr. DuPont?
That if Moose was invited
to Stonewall Prep to be the next victim,
then why was I also invited?
I was bait.
To lure my grandfather out of hiding,
so you could finish the job
that you started.
Took off like a coward
after Jughead found me.
But to my old man's credit, when Charles
and I found him the second time
and he heard what happened
to his grandson...
he figured it was finally time
to take your ass down.
[Charles] While you were in here
playing Agatha Christie,
my team was combing through DuPont's house
for the last hour.
Given the trophies of your victims
that we found in your hollowed-out OED
and your ghostwriters lawyering up...
not to mention Forsythe's detective work,
well...
Why don't you tell him?
It's over, Francis.
You...
call me a thief and a coward?
Well, I'm not.
I'm a builder.
I built the Baxter Brothers franchise,
and with that money,
I helped build this school.
Without me, neither would exist.
Francis DuPont,
you have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in court.
Never.
A writer's power is in his words.
Only the meek and the timid
choose silence.
I am... a man of honor.
To the end.
[Jughead] After that, it was a matter
of dotting I's and crossing T's.
We obtained these text exchanges
between you and Donna.
Donna was manipulating you, Joan.
She tricked you into doing her dirty work
so her hands would remain clean.
Don't protect her. I'll see to it
that you get a reduced sentence--
Agent Smith, you have nothing to offer me.
Reminder, my father is an ambassador,
and I have diplomatic immunity.
If you leave the country now,
you won't ever be able to return.
And your friends,
they'll take all the heat.
They're not my friends.
Hey. Why did you lie to Jughead?
You told him Bret had diplomatic immunity,
but it was Joan.
I-- I lied to Jughead
because I was trying to keep him
from antagonizing Bret.
You know it was Bret's idea
to kill Jughead.
Uh-huh. How did you get
Mr. Chipping's tiepin?
And don't tell me
that you were having an affair.
No one's buying that story anymore.
Mr. DuPont gave it to me.
Said I had to lie to the headmaster
so that Mr. Chipping's death
would be ruled a suicide
and people would stop asking questions.
But I'm just glad
that the real monster behind all of this,
Mr. DuPont, has paid for his crimes.
[Charles] You have a known history
of antagonizing Jughead.
Witnesses saw you walking with him
into the woods the night he was attacked.
Have I actually been charged with a crime?
You're facing hard time
for both attempted murder
and the creation and possession
of illegally recorded sex tapes
featuring your fellow students,
including Jughead and Betty.
Now...
I'm willing to reduce your charge
to only attempted murder
if you turn over your collection
of videotapes.
Here's my counteroffer:
Reduce my charge to conspiracy
after the fact,
which my lawyer will plead down
to community service,
or Betty and Jughead's puerile sex tape
will be released to the World Wide Web.
Hm. Let me think it over.
[door closes]
-[door opens]
-That was quick.
[door closes]
What the hell is this?
-The counter to your counter.
-Wait--
[blow lands]
I understand that you've decided
to cooperate with our investigation
and reveal the location
of your illicit videotapes.
Is that correct?
[Alice] Hidden in a secret compartment
behind Stonewall's crest
was a treasure trove of dark secrets.
Illegally recorded videotapes.
More fuel to add to the firestorm
of controversy that is consuming
one of the country's oldest
and more prestigious prep schools.
For now,
Stonewall Prep's doors remain open,
but its secret society, Quill and Skull,
has been disbanded.
For RIVW news, this is Alice Smith.
It's good to be back, Riverdale.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Your report came out really good, Mom.
Oh, thanks, honey.
I had a lot of help from an inside source.
[both] Mm-hm.
[FP and Alice laugh]
-Okay, I'm gonna head out.
-Yeah.
Wait, where are you going?
We're about to have cake.
Um, I will be back soon, okay?
I just have one last T to cross.
Hello, Donna.
Going somewhere?
If you must know,
I'm transferring to a new school.
Well, I'm glad I caught you, then.
I wanted to congratulate you personally.
Jughead and I heard that you're
taking over the Baxter Brothers.
The brand is relaunching.
As Tracy True.
Jealous?
Your plan worked, Donna.
You managed to get everyone else
to do the actual dirty work.
Hell, even DuPont's dead.
You covered your tracks extremely well.
Betty...
are you really so delusional,
you would believe I would mastermind
some elaborate conspiracy
that caused the deaths of multiple people
just to win a YA book contract?
No.
But you would do it for revenge.
Oh, really?
-Revenge for what?
-The murder of your grandmother.
Jane Dallas Brown.
One of the classmates DuPont killed
to cover up the ugly truth
that he didn't create the Baxter Brothers.
She was your grandmother.
-How could you possibly know that?
-A friend of a friend told me.
You dedicated yourself
to getting into Stonewall Prep
and getting into Chipping's class,
and each step brought you ever-closer
to your grandmother's killer.
You wanted... revenge.
So, what was the original plan, Donna?
Win the contract,
no matter how many people had to die?
And then stage an accident
that would take care of DuPont
so you could tear down
the house that he built?
Fascinating theory, Betty.
You left out one minor detail.
DuPont didn't merely kill my grandmother.
He stole from her,
the same way he did from Forsythe.
Tracy True,
the female teen detective
who was introduced
in the Baxter Brothers books.
She was your grandmother's invention.
Now I've taken Tracy back
and DuPont is rotting in a grave.
Oh.
How did you really find out
about my grandmother?
A private investigator...
At my behest, Hermosa put
her private-eye skills to good use
and did some digging
on those Stonewall wasps.
And your gal-pal Donna is not so sweet.
...who supplied us with the medical files
that confirmed that you are
the granddaughter of Jane Dallas Brown,
which gives the police a motive
and links this entire web of death...
back to you.
It's circumstantial, at best.
But I'll play one last round.
What do you want, Betty?
I want you to walk away
from the Tracy True contract.
Why in God's name would I do that?
Fictional though she may be,
Tracy deserves better.
As does the memory of your grandmother.
And you certainly don't deserve to profit
off the near-death of my boyfriend.
Or...
don't walk away.
That's fine.
But I will make sure
every newspaper of every major city
gets a copy of that medical file.
You play nice from now on, Donna.
I'll be keeping an eye on you.
Months at Stonewall Prep,
away from you guys,
-what a waste.
-Jug. Okay.
We put a stop to DuPont,
we solved eight murders,
and we gave closure to every family
of every missing child.
I would not call that a waste of time.
I know. It's just...
I feel...
Cheated?
I know.
I know. You'll find a meaning
to all of this...
at some point, okay?
So, Jughead Jones, back from the dead.
Color me completely not surprised.
[bell ringing]
You're not?
No one ever really dies in Riverdale,
do they?
But... what about
you and Archie canoodling then?
Yeah, that was just pretend.
I don't know, cousin,
that looked pretty real to me.
Well, yeah, that was the point.
Right.
All I'm saying is,
your secret's safe with me.
Toodles!
-What did Cheryl want?
-Nothing.
What did Mr. Honey say?
He isn't happy, but he legally has
to let me back to Riverdale High.
-That's great.
-Yeah, I just hope my credits transfer.
On the bright side, no one's going
to try to kill me while I'm here.
Don't jinx yourself.
[FP] Hey, boy.
-Betty.
-[Betty] Hey.
Um, I'll be right down.
Grandpa.
-I thought you left.
-No, no. Not yet.
You joining us for dinner?
Betty and I are actually going to meet
Archie and Veronica at Pop's, so...
-Unless you want me to stay.
-No, go have fun.
Yeah.
Should I... say goodbye?
Oh, no, no.
I expect your father and I will
still be talking when you get back.
Hey, hold on.
I don't know what's gonna happen
with him and me,
but we're talking, so that's something.
So... thank you.
You made all this happen.
Have fun.
-[Jughead] Ready?
-Mm-hm.
[Jughead] Maybe something good did
come out of this whole Stonewall mess.
My dad and my grandfather talking again
for the first time in 30 years.
Who would've thought of that?
-Do you think your dad will forgive him?
-Oh, I don't know.
I mean, they have a lot of bad history
between each other, but... I hope so.
All right, guys.
-Let's make a vow.
-Ugh.
-[Archie] I know.
-[Veronica] Mm.
I know.
The last time we made a vow
to have a normal senior year,
everything went to hell pretty quick.
But we only have two, three months left.
Let's end it on a high note.
Are we gonna ignore the fact
that Archie and I
will probably not be graduating
with you guys?
Jug, okay. Do you really think
Vee and I are going to sit idly by
and not help our boyfriends graduate?
Archie Andrews and Jughead Jones,
you will graduate.
Even if it takes a thousand tutors,
you will set aside everything,
no more mysteries,
and make graduating
your sole purpose in life.
-Why does that sound like a threat?
-[Veronica] Because it is.
To going out on top. Together.
-Cheers.
-Cheers to that.
Guys, guys, just a reminder,
I'm posting the sign-up sheet
for the variety show tomorrow.
You all have to perform.
Even you, Jughead.
Count us in, Kev.
Oh, no.
Yes.
Check out this list of local names.
[inaudible dialogue]
You make it look way too good