[Jughead] Spirit Week had arrived
at Riverdale High.
And for the first time in years,
the students had something to celebrate.
The long-suffering Bulldogs, in large part
thanks to breakout star Munroe Moore,
were finally going to the state finals
where they would take on
the undisputed titans of the gridiron,
the Stonewall Stallions.
For Principal Honey,
who commissioned an article about the game
from ace reporter Betty Cooper,
the championship was, at last,
something positive to promote.
But for Riverdale's star QB,
Archie Andrews,
this Spirit Week was special
for a different reason.
It would be the last of his career.
Jones.
How long have you had that machine?
Feels like forever. Why?
Think it's about time for an upgrade?
No, keys are used to my fingertips.
-Plus I'm sentimental and superstitious.
-[chuckles]
[computer chimes]
Oh, crap. I gotta go.
Mr. DuPont's summoned me for some reason.
[door opens, then closes]
How did I get an interview with Yale?
I didn't even apply.
Yes, but the recruiter is a friend of mine
so I slipped him your short stories
and he was quite impressed.
I assume you're interested?
Yale is my girlfriend's dream school
and she didn't get in, so...
Yes, well, the heart can be
a difficult minefield to navigate,
but take my advice:
Figure it out, don't be foolish.
[Reggie] Mm. Gotta go with number three.
It's damn good, Ronnie.
It's my special shimmy
on Abuelita's recipe.
I thought your dad patented
the recipe so you couldn't use it.
Daddy may have patented
our family recipe for his own profit,
but this is a modified spiced rum,
with a unique flavor profile.
Now it's time to introduce Luna Rum
to the outside world.
[school bell rings]
[Honey] Cheryl.
Girls, how fortuitous.
-I'd like you to meet someone.
-[Cheryl] No time to chat.
We're on our way to practice
our Spirit Week musical routine,
which will, naturally, be epic.
On that subject,
as was discussed with Mrs. Burble,
I have brought in Miss Appleyard
to be your new coach.
But cheer season is almost done,
Mr. Honey.
I can handle this, Holden.
Hmm.
I'm not sure what Honey has told you,
but we don't need a coach.
I run the show around here.
Howevs,
we are looking for a launder woman.
From now on, we're gonna change things up.
The Vixens are a cheer squad,
so we'll be focusing on cheers,
not singing and dancing to pop songs.
Now, gather the rest of the girls
and meet me out on the field
so we can practice some drills, okay?
I'm sorry, am I hallucinating,
or did you just give me an order?
I led my last team to nationals
three years in a row.
I think I know what I'm doing here.
That's right, Munroe.
Okay. So, last game of the season.
-[exhales sharply]
-How do you feel, Arch?
Honestly? Like we're gonna win.
-[Munroe] Mm-hm.
-Hmm. Munroe, what about you?
I'm just happy to be playing
for the championship.
-[whoops]
-He's being humble, Betty.
A recruiter from Notre Dame
is coming just to see him.
Reggie, care to comment?
-You want a quote, Betts?
-[Betty] Sure.
I'll give you a quote:
-Stonewall sucks.
-[Munroe] Mmm.
The only reason why they're undefeated
is because they play dirty.
Dirty. Mm-hm.
Every team that's gone up against them
this year has suffered a horrible injury.
-What do you mean?
-I mean, they don't play to win.
They play to hurt.
But... they haven't gone up
against our guy.
Munroe.
-So, you excited for the big game?
-Everyone's pumped.
Can't wait to see you play.
If your arm's half as good
as your dad's was,
I bet you got a hell of a throw.
Hey, Uncle Frank.
-I've been thinking.
-Mm-hm.
Yeah, me, too. Look...
I really appreciate you putting me up
here for the last couple weeks.
Getting to meet you, getting to know you.
You're a great kid, Archie.
Your dad raised you well.
But, uh...
I think it's time I moved on.
I've paid my respects.
I was actually wondering...
what if you didn't leave?
You could help out here
or Andrews Construction.
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't interested.
Problem is, that means telling--
-Telling my mom you're in town.
-Yeah.
Like I've said,
not a lot of love lost there.
Whatever happened
between you guys in the past,
I'm sure you can work it out.
Hell, she'll probably be happy to see you.
Let me ask you, Frank, have you
even visited your brother's grave?
You didn't bother to show up
for the funeral.
I was on a crab boat, Mary.
I didn't get the news till a month ago.
Mom, I was thinking maybe Uncle Frank
could get a job at Andrews Construction.
-You asked my son for a job?
-No, Mom, the job was my idea.
[exhales sharply] Okay, fine.
But mark my words, Archie.
The second your uncle has to do
even an ounce of hard work,
he will bolt so fast, your head will spin.
[down-tempo music playing over speakers]
Jug.
You've been dipping that fry in ketchup
for five minutes. What's going on?
[sighs]
I have an interview
with a college recruiter.
For Yale.
I hope that's okay.
Yeah. Why wouldn't it be?
Because I got rejected?
Well... yeah, kind of.
Well, I would never ask you
to turn down an opportunity like that
that was life-changing.
So, you're obviously gonna go
and ace that interview.
Meanwhile, I'll be working on my article
for Mr. Honey.
How's that going?
It's a puff piece.
Have you thought about interviewing
the opposing team?
-You know, Bret's team captain.
-Yeah, I know.
He's also the guy who attacked us
in a bunny mask.
You really want me to interview that jerk?
It could mean drama for your piece.
What can I do for you, Cheryl?
We got off
on the wrong Repetto-covered foot.
I'd like us to find a way
to work together in blissful harmony.
Cheryl, I'm the coach. You're the athlete.
The power structure couldn't be clearer.
As for your muffins,
can I suggest a little less time baking
and a little more time in the weight room?
My body is perfection, you crone!
And you may be the coach,
but I think you'll find the Vixens
are mine forever more.
[door closes]
Full disclosure, Bret,
I wasn't going to interview you.
But then I heard rumors
that your team plays dirty.
"They don't play to win.
They play to hurt."
Betty...
have you ever really watched
or studied football?
Because, sweetheart,
it's not a knitting circle.
It's social Darwinism in uniforms.
Football is... a sport of gladiators.
And you win by debilitating
and slaughtering your enemies.
Mm.
Gosh, I have to go, but...
you can quote me on that.
You can bet your ass I will, psycho.
[Veronica] As restaurant owners,
you know the importance of quality
in every dish and glass you serve.
Luna Rum is a small-batch operation,
focused on making each bottle special.
The name Luna comes from my abuelita and
generations of rum-making women
in my family.
Interesting. Is that cardamom?
Among other things.
It's my own special blend.
Luna is all about valuing tradition,
while adding a touch of modern sabor.
I'll take a case. This is special.
Wonderful.
Your customers will not be disappointed.
[exhales sharply]
A good writer needs the best tools.
Did you get me this?
It's a welcome gift
from the Quill and Skull.
Speaking of which, meet us
in the basement tonight, 10:00 sharp.
Dare I ask why?
You'll see.
How can I help you, Cheryl?
We're going on strike.
During Spirit Week, no less.
You must fire Miss Appleyard.
She's a rotten scourge
who has afflicted our divine sisterhood.
I'd hate for there to be
a big Vixens-shaped hole
during the most important football game
of the year.
Nay, the century.
Hm.
I usually don't respond well to threats.
But in this case, I'll consider it.
Thank you for meeting with me.
Like I said on the phone,
I'm writing a story
about the Stonewall Stallions,
about the rumors that they play dirty.
I've been studying game tape
and there's a pattern of violence.
Wanton violence.
-Those Stonewall guys are maniacs.
-"Maniacs"? How so?
The Stonewall linemen broke my arm
while I was in the pile.
-Do you mean on purpose?
-Definitely on purpose.
The hit came out of nowhere.
-After the whistle.
-And did the refs do anything?
They pay off the refs
to look the other way.
-This is huge.
-The worse the injury...
-Yeah?
-The bigger the bounty.
I'm sorry, did you just say "bounty"?
The Stonewall coach pays his players
to hurt the other team.
At least that's what I heard.
[rock music playing over speakers]
♪ I'll take a better bullet
The farthest train ♪
♪ I'll take a better bullet... ♪
-I'm headed home. Later, guys.
-See you, dude.
♪ And I just keep on pulling your chain ♪
♪ You keep on holding on and on
Until you're... ♪
[can clatters]
[thumping]
Oh, hell, no.
[Munroe] Get away from me!
[Munroe groans]
Munroe, what happened?
Some guys jumped me.
-One of them swung a golf club at my knee.
-I'm gonna call an ambulance.
-Did you see their faces?
-No, they were wearing masks.
We don't need to have seen their faces.
-We know exactly who they are.
-[line ringing]
[Munroe groans]
[Jughead] Hello?
Bret?
[Donna] We're in here, Forsythe.
[Jughead] Where's Bret?
[Bret] Sorry I'm late.
I had a prior obligation.
What exactly are we doing?
Final part of your initiation.
Where we really get to know you.
When you tell us your deepest,
darkest secret.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
And we are recording this
for the archives.
We'll tell you ours first.
[sighs]
When I was 13...
my uncle made a pass at me.
And when I told my mom,
she didn't believe me.
And that's...
when I started cutting myself.
When I was 14...
my father got me a hooker and said,
"Now it's your time to be a man."
I cried the whole time I was with her.
But I never...
told my father because the truth is...
I was afraid he'd kill me.
For real.
I used to be homeless.
And I would crash underneath this bridge
by the dock on the Southside.
It was kind of a rough place.
There was this one guy named Doc.
He would stay up all night just to make
sure the junkies didn't mess with me.
Then one day...
these drunken businessmen
who had heard about our little shantytown,
they found Doc.
They beat the life out of him.
I didn't move. I didn't say anything.
And I watched.
I just watched it.
It's probably my greatest shame.
I've never even told that story.
Not even to Betty.
[Toni] Babe.
Tee-Tee.
Whyfor the long face?
Babe, don't lose your mind,
but we've got a major problem.
[girl gasps]
What villainy is this?
Speak, fiends!
Mr. Honey threatened to ban us all
from prom if we refused to cheer.
He said we'd ruin Spirit Week.
So, you caved and betrayed me?
Well, you may redeem yourselves yet.
Now, who shucketh off
the imposter Appleyard?
Come on, babe.
This isn't over.
Not by a long shot.
[Appleyard] Ladies, eyes up front.
-[Bret] The dog says, "Mine."
-[boy] Totally. Hey, man...
[Bret] I just came up with that.
-[Bret laughs]
-Hey.
Oh, somebody call animal control.
The Bulldogs are here.
You couldn't even wait
to play dirty on the field, could you?
Heh-heh. That's how scared you were
of Munroe.
Hey, what's going on?
Jones, are you friends
with these welfare cases?
What did you just call me?
I called you a--
-[boy 1] No.
-[boy 2] Get him!
-[keys jingle]
-[cell door opens]
[Frank] Hey.
You all right, Archie?
I've been in worse fights.
Thanks for coming, Uncle Frank.
Couldn't call Mom.
She's got enough to worry about.
That makes sense.
Forsythe Jones, I presume.
I'm Gerald Brooks from Yale admissions.
Have a seat.
I'd like to start
by complimenting your writing.
I'm sensing
H.P. Lovecraft is an influence.
Yeah, a major one.
I'm sorry. I'm--
I guess I'm just not used to people
actually treating me like a real writer.
Yeah, well, at Yale,
everyone earns their spot.
Should you be accepted, you will succeed
or fail on your own merits, Mr. Jones.
Understood.
["Crush Culture" playing]
[Frank] Wanna tell me what happened?
Those Stonewall bastards
attacked my friend Munroe.
-Busted up his knee so he can't play.
-So, you went looking for payback.
♪ Quit checking your volume... ♪
Don't be ashamed.
I'm the last person that
should be judging anyone, Archie.
Especially when it comes
to fighting for your friends.
Your dad was the same way.
What do you mean?
I mean that your dad was pretty
level-headed, all things considered,
except when someone came
after a friend or a family member,
he'd turn into a bit of a madman.
Yeah, he could be brutal in a bar fight.
I can't even imagine
my dad throwing punches.
I mean, he taught me every sport,
but not boxing.
-Wait, you box?
-Yeah. I was serious about it for a while.
Damn. Me, too. I boxed in the Army.
-What weight class?
-Welterweight.
You any good at it?
-[Archie] This one time, I boxed a bear.
-[Frank chuckles]
[Betty] I need a huge favor, V.
Munroe was jumped
outside of Archie's gym last night.
I know. Archie told me. Poor Munroe.
He thinks Munroe was attacked
by someone from Stonewall Prep,
and based on the masks
those creeps were wearing, I agree.
Probably it was Bret.
And I want to break the story
in The Blue and Gold,
but I need proof or a confession.
Reggie says he heard
Stonewall's throwing a party tonight
to get everyone psyched for the game.
Do I smell another classic B and V caper?
Just a V caper, unfortunately.
I can't get close to Bret. He knows me.
But I was hoping maybe you could go,
turn on your femme fatale charm?
-I'm down.
-Great.
-Would you be willing to wear a wire?
-Absolutely.
And I think I have just the tonic
to help loosen Bret's lips.
["Healer" playing over speakers]
Anything interesting happen today?
♪ Healer... ♪
Uh...
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-F.P. told me everything, so don't.
[sighs] And, Archie,
what's really upsetting...
is that when you needed someone,
you called Frank and not me.
Mom, please. What is your deal with him?
Your Uncle Frank is
your classic ne'er-do-well.
The straw that broke the camel's back
was when your father
took the blame for Frank's DUI.
What?
You're saying the DUI
on Dad's record wasn't his fault?
According to the official police report,
it was,
but your father wasn't
behind the wheel that night.
After Frank went on a bender,
he crashed our car
into a telephone pole on Sycamore.
It was the third strike against him,
so he would have done jail time.
So your father covered for him.
And you know how Frank repaid him?
By skipping town the next day.
That's the kind of man that Frank is.
Oh, and Archie?
You can play in the football game,
but otherwise, you're grounded.
No car privileges for a month.
[sighs]
[Veronica] B, from what people are saying,
this isn't just a football party.
It's a football party hosted
by Stonewall's lame-ass secret society.
Ah. And there's Bret.
["Vagabond" playing over speakers]
God, I can smell his privilege
from across the room.
Okay. I'm going in.
♪ Years that I walked
As the earth was turning... ♪
Hi, fellas. I'm Monica.
You wouldn't happen to be rum drinkers,
by any chance?
Because if you are, I'm taking orders.
Go back to my room, undress,
and wait for me.
-Excuse me?
-You said you were taking orders.
[laughing]
[Veronica laughs]
Would you like some rum or not?
It's spiced.
Yeah, sure. Pour away.
[Bret] The Stallions are undefeated.
Fifteen and 0. And that winning streak's
gonna continue. Right, boys?
[all] Yeah!
Oh, thank you.
Especially now that Riverdale's top dog
is out of the mix.
It's all over social media.
Attagirl. Set the trap.
Star player on the opposing team,
randomly victimized
right before the big game?
-It's quite a stroke of luck for you.
-Nah, doll.
We make our own luck.
["Unstoppable" playing]
♪ Even when my ears are ringing... ♪
[whispers] Come here.
[Jughead] Veronica?
-Jughead?
Veronica? I thought your name was--
Monica, yes, it is. Uh...
Excuse us.
-What the hell are you doing here?
-What are you doing here?
I go to school here. Why are you in a wig?
Since when are you part
of a secret society?
-What?
-Does Betty know?
Because if not, she just found out.
♪ You won't see me flinch ♪
I didn't tell you
because it's a secret society.
Four months ago, you hated those guys,
you wanted to drop out
and come back to Riverdale.
Yeah, but I stayed.
You know what? I'm glad I stayed.
I got a book contract.
Don't forget about your Yale interview,
thanks to your new friends.
Yeah, okay, I got an interview with Yale
because I'm a member of this society.
If I get accepted,
it's because of my writing.
Does that really make me
such a horrible person?
-No.
But I hate that we're keeping secrets
from each other.
-I thought we were done with that.
-Yeah.
Okay, that's where I messed up.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you
about Quill and Skull.
That's fine.
-What was Veronica even doing there?
-She was helping me.
With what?
She was trying to get Bret
to brag about attacking Munroe.
Some much-needed proof for my article.
Did Bret confess?
Not quite.
He was dancing around it,
but then you blew her cover.
Oh. So I messed up a classic B and V scam?
-Mm-hm.
-How can I make it up to you?
I don't think there's anything
you could do.
I'll just have to file my story
with quotes from unnamed sources,
-which I have plenty of.
-Is it gonna be enough?
Truthfully, I'm not very hopeful.
[door opens, then closes]
-Uncle Frank.
-Yeah?
-We should talk.
-Yeah, sure thing, Arch.
Everything all right?
Mom told me about the DUI.
Look...
I was going through a rough patch.
I was back in Riverdale in between tours.
I was just having trouble... dealing.
This is before I realized
I needed counseling
for what I went through in Desert Storm.
I don't remember much of that night.
That's not surprising.
When I woke up the next morning,
your dad had already taken the blame.
I never would have asked Fred
to do that for me, Archie. Never.
But he did it, because...
Because that's who he was.
And I took off, because that's who I was.
I was angry. I was messed up.
I figured I needed to clear my head
before I could make things right
with your dad. And guess what.
[voice breaking] I never got that chance.
[Hiram] It's quite the operation
you have here.
And you already secured some sales
from restaurants, I hear.
With a touching story
about your abuelita, no less.
Don't worry, Daddy.
I may not be able to serve rum
at La Bonne Nuit, but I can make it here.
About that...
Veronica Luna,
you are hereby served
with a cease-and-desist order
due to patent infringement.
One of the restaurant owners
you gave a bottle to is a friend of mine.
I had my chemist compare
your concoction to Lodge Rum.
And while you've embellished
the recipe I own with all those spices,
the core remains the same, which means...
if you make another bottle, I will sue you
and shut this whole operation down.
Or...
we could team up.
That would be a "hell no" for me, thanks.
Why are you so stubborn, mija?
You wanted me to go straight, I have.
And yet you won't accept my help.
Why?
Out of spite?
Maybe it's too late. Maybe...
too much damage has been done...
Daddy.
That's what it feels like.
Okay.
Well, if that's how you feel, I should go.
Good luck with everything.
[knock on door]
Yeah.
-Mr. DuPont.
-Mr. Jones. May I come in?
Uh, yeah. Sorry it's so messy in here.
I've heard from one of your classmates
that your girlfriend
is working on some salacious article
that could be a stain on our school.
And I'm wondering
if you couldn't possibly...
discourage her.
[sighs] Uh...
Mr. DuPont, I'm not gonna tell Betty
what she can and can't write. That's--
It's just not the way
our relationship works.
If that's gonna affect
my chances at Yale...
Nonsense. I appreciate the candor.
And in fact, the other reason I stopped by
was to invite you to sit
with myself and Mr. Brooks
in the alumni section of the game.
Hope to see you there.
[Archie] How bad does it hurt?
If I stand on it more than 10 minutes,
it's like someone's hitting my knee
with a hammer.
Doctor said if I play,
I could cause permanent damage.
Damn, dude. I'm sorry.
[Frank] Let me ask you...
if you had a way to play through the pain,
would you?
Are you kidding?
-[grunts] In a heartbeat.
-Well, in that case...
I have some pills. Meds from the VA.
They won't fix anything,
but numb you long enough for a game.
Uncle Frank, no.
He's not taking any pills from you.
Hold on.
-What kind of pills are we talking about?
-No.
No way.
Frank, you're not a doctor.
And, Munroe, you can't do this.
-What are you doing?
-I'm just trying to help.
Not this way.
I'll see you at the game.
This is not the piece
I asked you to write.
No, it's better.
It's an exposé about a culture of violence
that's fostered at Stonewall Prep.
We cannot publish a story
based on hearsay.
Now, I advise you to write the article
that you agreed to deliver.
A story that celebrates
your classmates and your school.
Or don't.
There's no way in hell
we're printing this.
[softly sighs]
Dude.
Munroe, what are you doing here?
I'm not gonna fight you, Red.
-I'm not sitting this one out. I can't.
-Why aren't you limping?
-Did my uncle give you those pills?
-He did.
This is it for me.
A scholarship to Notre Dame?
That would change my life,
my family's life.
If I go pro, they're set.
And if you get hurt,
maybe you don't ever play again.
Damn it, Red.
This is my choice to make, not yours.
-[whoops] Yeah!
-Yeah!
[crowd cheering]
Excuse me, are you lost?
Shouldn't you be on the Stonewall side
with all the Yalies?
Uh... I don't think Yale
is gonna happen anymore.
Plus, I've already been a Bulldog.
How'd it go with Honey?
Well, as you can see,
the game's still happening, so...
I tried.
[crowd cheering]
Hey, Ronnie.
Wanna get back at your dad
for ruining your business?
-Any way I can, Reggie.
-Parking lot. Halftime.
Meet me.
Whatever happens out there,
we have to protect Munroe.
I don't need any special treatment.
Yes, you do.
They already tried to go after you once.
I'm sure it's a safe bet
they'll try again.
-And we're gonna win this. Right?
-[in unison] Yeah!
Hell yeah, we are. "Bulldogs" on three.
-One, two, three.
-[in unison] Bulldogs!
-[air horn blowing nearby]
-[crowd cheering nearby]
Hello?
Who's out there?
[Appleyard grunts]
-Let me out!
-[Cheryl] Listen up, bitches.
Appleyard is...
indisposed, so consider this a coup.
And before any of you reptiles object,
a word to the wise.
You owe me this.
I've been your fellow Vixen and HBIC
for four grueling years.
And I've never turned my back on you.
-Not like you did to me.
-Fact.
Now, without further ado...
let's cheer our Bulldog brethren
onto victory...
and slay.
Yeah.
["Cherry Bomb" playing]
♪ Can't stay at home
Can't stay at school ♪
♪ Old folks say, "You poor little fool" ♪
♪ Down the streets
I'm the girl next door ♪
♪ I'm the fox you've been waiting for ♪
♪ Hello, Daddy
Hello, Mom ♪
[Archie] Down, set! Hut!
♪ Cherry bomb! ♪
♪ Hello, world, I'm your wild girl ♪
♪ I'm your
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb! ♪
♪ Stone-age love and strange sounds, too ♪
♪ Come on, baby, let me get to you ♪
-♪ Bad nights causing teenage blues ♪
-Yeah!
♪ Get down, ladies
You've got nothin' to lose ♪
♪ Hello, Daddy
Hello, Mom ♪
♪ I'm your
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb! ♪
♪ Hello, world, I'm your wild girl ♪
♪ I'm your
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb! ♪
♪ Hey, street boy, want some style? ♪
♪ Your dead-end dreams
Don't make you smile ♪
♪ I'll give you something to live for ♪
♪ Take you and shake you
To your core ♪
♪ Hello, Daddy
Hello, Mom ♪
♪ I'm your
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb! ♪
♪ Hello, world, I'm your wild girl ♪
♪ I'm your
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb! ♪
♪ Cherry bomb, cherry bomb, cherry bomb! ♪
♪ Cherry bomb! ♪
-[whistle blows]
-♪ Cherry bomb! ♪
[crowd cheering]
[cheering and shouting]
-Munroe, how you holding up?
-I'm good.
Good. Then we got this.
Coach wants us to go
for the two-point conversion.
Last play of the year, boys.
Let's finish strong.
-On three. One, two, three.
-[in unison] Bulldogs!
[announcer] Here we go.
Last play of the championship game
between the Bulldogs and the Stallions.
Bulldogs are going
for the two-point conversion and the win.
[breathing heavily]
Down, set! Hut!
[crowd cheering]
-[whistle blows]
-Get off him!
Munroe.
Did we get it?
Come on, man.
[players chattering and cheering]
[players chanting]
Stonewall! Stonewall! Stonewall!
[chanting continues]
Archie, I don't care
what that scoreboard says.
-You guys played your hearts out.
-You gave Munroe drugs, Uncle Frank?
After I told you not to.
He's a grown man. He came to me.
It was his decision.
And you almost won.
It could've been the last game he played
because of you, and that's the truth.
Guys like you and me and Munroe
have to take what we can get
however we can. Even your dad knew that.
And, yeah, it was a risk.
But where I come from, you respect
when a man chooses for himself.
-[door opens]
-[Munroe whoops]
Archie?
Mr. Andrews.
I just got cornered
by the recruiter from Notre Dame.
Said he wants me to visit
in Indiana next week.
He wants me to play ball for them!
That's great news, son. Congrats.
No one deserves it more, Munroe.
[Munroe] Guys.
-I'm going to Notre Dame!
-[all cheering]
Hey, Betty!
Hey!
Betty!
-I heard your article got killed.
-Just take the win, Bret.
That's exactly what we did today.
We took the win.
You know, actually,
my article wasn't killed, Bret.
I only just started digging,
so who knows what I'll find.
I'll see you in class, Forsythe.
And, Betty, let's do this again.
I really like winning against you.
[Betty scoffs]
[Cheryl] Care for a lick?
Sure.
-Is that maple?
-Yeah. Blossom maple.
It's not exactly memory foam.
Well, it's better than the cot at the gym.
You sure your mom's okay with this?
She's not exactly happy about it,
but I told her it was temporary.
Just until you got back on your feet.
-I'll go grab you some pillows.
-Hang on a second.
You were pretty pissed off at me
after the game.
Why the change of heart?
Everything's a risk.
You giving Munroe the pills,
Munroe playing, but...
it paid off.
And I saw how happy he was.
A year ago, he was in juvie,
fighting to stay alive. But now..
Who knows,
maybe you helped change his life.
[Veronica] Cheryl.
The reason I wanted us to meet:
That snow cone I licked at the game
gave me a wicked idea.
-But I need your help with it.
-"Wicked"? Do tell.
[Veronica] Try this.
Yum.
What is this delightsome elixir?
It's my rum...
mixed with your maple syrup.
It tastes like... breakfast on the beach.
No, Cheryl.
It tastes like money.
I'm very pleased you came around, Betty.
Very pleased, indeed. This...
is a stellar article.
It's great press for our school,
even though we lost.
We may have lost the game,
but we haven't lost the war.
I've been doing more and more research
on Stonewall Prep.
And did you know that they have
a world-class quiz team?
And the captain of that team
is none other than
athlete-scholar-scumbag
Bret Weston Wallis?
Yes.
But that championship is only a few weeks
away and Riverdale doesn't even...
have a team.
Miss Cooper...
are you volunteering?
Because I would love to get my hands
on at least one trophy this year.
Principal Honey...
at this point in time,
there is nothing that I would enjoy more
than to give Stonewall Prep
a royal ass-kicking.
[exhales sharply]
Then you have my full support, captain.
[breathes deeply]
[Jughead] Dad?
What's going on?
I felt it only appropriate
that your father be here
to celebrate with us.
Celebrate what?
You'll be receiving official word
by the end of next week, but, uh--
You got into Yale, boy.
Yeah. First Jones to go to college.
And an Ivy League one at that. Here.
I don't understand.
To Jughead.
And to Bret, as well.
Yeah, I got into Yale, too.
And who knows...
maybe if we're lucky,
we'll be roomies again.
Save your tears.
No one's watching.
Bret.
You got your wish, Ponytail.
Forsythe isn't going to Yale.
So I guess it'll just be
you and me in New Haven.