[Jughead] The week started like any other.
[clock ticking]
Who would've guessed
where I'd be by the end?
["Someone Tonight" playing]
[alarm blaring]
[alarm stops]
♪ Lone passenger ♪
♪ Out on the road ♪
♪ With a million more miles to go ♪
[inaudible dialogue]
♪ An ache deep inside
And wide as the sky ♪
Thank you for watching the center
during the day, Ms. Moore.
I promise it's only temporary.
Hell, after you helped get my baby Munroe
into Notre Dame, it's the least I can do.
I'll be back after school, once I've
checked in on Andrews Construction.
A young man like you must have
colleges knocking down your door.
How can I help you, Mr. Andrews?
Mr. Honey, I know it's late in the game,
but is there any way
I can still apply to college?
The application period closed months ago.
And moreover, based on your grades
from the past two years,
I have serious doubts about whether or not
you'll graduate with your class.
Can I at least walk with my friends
at the graduation ceremony?
I find the notion
of an undeserving student being allowed
to walk with his peers,
without fulfilling the basic requirements
to graduate, quite absurd.
It is dishonest,
and it is a hollow gesture.
Wouldn't you agree, Mr. Andrews?
[Hermione squeals]
-Daddy, let me get that for you.
-I got it. I don't need your help.
No, of course not. Which is why
I'll never offer it to you again.
["Belong to You" playing]
What's up, Ronnie?
Good morning to you, too.
Less talking, more touching, Andrews.
♪ You ♪
♪ I belong to you ♪
Thanks for the early morning delight.
I'm not complaining,
but what's the occasion?
As much as I loved visiting NYC,
it reminded me of how...
little time we have left together.
We haven't really talked about
what we're doing after graduation.
What are you saying, Ronnie?
I'm saying...
I don't really wanna think
about the future right now.
I just wanna enjoy these last few months
at Riverdale High with you.
And I wanna have fun.
Can we do that, Archie?
Can we just have fun?
That's music to my ears.
You rang?
I won't mince words with you, Forsythe.
You're out of Quill and Skull.
Why?
Because Betty broke
into the sanctum sanctorum?
Well, as a matter of fact, yes.
That's a violation of our code.
That's not all, I'm afraid.
We're also terminating
your Baxter Brothers contract,
for failure to deliver
satisfactory material by March 15th.
This Friday? As in the Ides of March?
It's only Monday, I still have time.
Your rejected novel took you months
to write.
What makes you think you could write
an entirely new one in five days?
Watch me.
[line rings]
-[Betty] Hello?
-I'm in need of my real-life Tracy True.
How quickly can you get to Stonewall Prep?
I have to write the best damn
Baxter Brother novel ever by Friday,
which, coincidentally,
is the Ides of March.
Stonewall Prep celebrates the holiday
by throwing a big blowout in the woods.
Okay, well, then...
Why don't you write about what's been
happening to you here at Stonewall?
-Like a roman à clef, let's say.
-Yeah.
-Like a prep school thriller.
-Sure.
We could start with my--
We could start with Moose's arrival.
-Exactly.
-You're brilliant. You know that?
I like what you've done
with the place, Archie.
Mr. Lodge.
What's up?
I'm here to work out. Train.
Don't you have a nice gym
at The Pembrooke?
-And belong to Solstice?
-Yeah, but I'm looking for a real gym.
Like here.
Gotten away from myself, Archie.
Spent too much time in suits,
behind desks, but no more.
No more weakness.
Okay, Mr. Lodge. Sure.
You can make your check out
to Fred Andrews Community Center.
[Jughead] "The boys themselves
couldn't see it yet,
but it was a suspicious coincidence,
to say the least.
Two new scholarship students arrived
at Brickbridge Prep
after being recruited
by the same teacher, Mr. Shepherd.
The old acquaintances settled
into their new lives,
unaware that one or both of them
were destined to be a sacrificial Iamb.
The perfect victim to the perfect murder."
That's where the chapter ends.
Mr. Jones...
ten pages of autobiographical hokum
won't save you.
Well, just you wait.
I'll have more tomorrow.
[phone rings]
Ellie's Essential Oils.
Don't hate, alleviate. How can I help you?
And who is she?
Don't worry, we'll vet her.
What was that, babe?
There's a high roller at La Bonne Nuit
who's caught wind of the Maple Club
and wields a blank check
with our name on it.
I hate to ask, Tee-Tee, but will you
scrutinize this enigmatic patron?
-Sure.
-Great.
You'll find a frosty haired woman
at the bar tonight.
I'm on it. And I'll be sure
to lay on the charm.
["Who Do U Love?" playing]
-Love you.
♪ I'm just trying to say ♪
♪ Who do you love? ♪
[over speakers] ♪ Is it him or me?... ♪
I'm Antoinette.
I understand you've been asking
about our other establishment.
Why, yes. I'm Rosa Jevön.
I consider myself a connoisseur of rum,
and I've heard rumblings
of a secret rum bar with ties
to this establishment.
Needless to say,
I'm intrigued.
Tell you what,
since I like your vibe so much,
I'll talk to my partner about it.
She'll wanna meet you, too.
Maybe tomorrow night?
Right here?
It's a date.
♪ 'Cause I can't take the pressure
Anymore ♪
♪ Who do you love? ♪
♪ Girl, it's killin' me ♪
♪ If you can't say that I'm the one
For sure ♪
♪ Then I'm walkin' out the door, yeah ♪
♪ Who do you love?
Who do you love? ♪
♪ Said, who do you love?... ♪
Two Cokes, please.
-Okay, I needed that.
-We're just getting started, Archiekins.
Ronnie, I have to be at the site
by 5 tomorrow morning.
Boo! I thought you said
we were gonna have fun?
Good night, Veronica.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Fine.
[Jughead] "It was All Hallows' Eve
at Brickbridge Prep.
Jarhead was burning the midnight oil,
studying, when suddenly,
his vision narrowed.
He crumpled to the ground
and awoke to a real-life nightmare.
He was locked in a solid oak coffin.
'My classmates drugged me,'
he realized groggily.
But why?
The truth was sinisterly simple.
It was so he wouldn't be a witness
to the perfect murder.
For you see...
the seminar students
were plotting to kill his roommate Bison
on that very Devil's Night."
[paper rustling]
Admit it.
You guys are on the edge of your seats,
aren't you?
Can I ask you something, Mr. Lodge?
It's actually a business question.
Really?
Interesting.
Shoot.
I'm not as good as your daughter,
Mr. Lodge.
I can't... run multiple businesses
and do well in school
and everything else Veronica's so good at.
If you're talking about this place
and Andrews Construction,
-have you thought about shedding one?
-Yeah.
But my Grandpa Artie founded
Andrews Construction
and passed it down to my dad.
It's my legacy.
Well, both of your businesses bear
your father's name.
You'll be keeping his legacy alive,
no matter what.
[Archie]
Thanks for meeting with me, Mr. Keller.
Yeah, of course, Archie.
So, what's been going on?
Truthfully, a lot.
I've been thinking about the future
of Andrews Construction
and the community center recently.
Vic has offered to buy
Andrews Construction a few times.
I don't like the guy, personally,
but my dad did.
If I sold it, I could use that money
to pay you a proper salary
to help me run the center full-time.
If that's something
you'd be interested in.
Well, I've been hopping from job to job
since I lost my post as sheriff.
A more permanent gig
would be a nice change of pace.
I'd like that, Arch.
Does anyone know why DuPont summoned us?
No need to wonder, Ms. Berkeley.
I will tell you.
The headmaster has just given me
some very unsettling news.
One of you has been accused
of the worst crime a writer can commit.
Plagiarism.
Mr. Jones,
it seems that the short story
that qualified you for Yale,
"On Featherless Wings,"
was in fact written by another student.
In this seminar.
Let me guess who accused me. Was it Bret?
No. It was me.
-What? Why?
-Because I wrote "On Featherless Wings."
-No, you didn't.
-Yes, I did.
And I've got a time stamp on my computer
proving that I wrote it two months ago.
I wrote it during the summer.
It's on my computer.
The story you wrote last summer is
on the laptop I gave you three weeks ago?
No, it's on my old one. It's in my room.
Can I get it, please?
Go and get it. We shall wait.
What the hell?
Jones, so, where's this magical,
exonerating laptop?
It's not in there
because someone stole it.
That seems rather convenient.
Mr. DuPont, I'm going to fight
these accusations tooth and nail.
You had better.
Stonewall Prep takes the crime
of plagiarism very seriously.
As such, you will go before the headmaster
and disciplinary committee on Friday.
On the Ides of March,
fittingly enough.
Mr. DuPont's turning out to be worse
than any villain
in his precious Baxter Brothers series.
It's clear he wants me expelled.
You can't let your name be tarnished
by these trust-fund brats.
Hell, it's my name. It's our family name.
If I let my reputation be destroyed
by a baseless accusation,
my career as a writer is going to be over
before it even begins.
There's no way that's happening, Jug.
I think I have an idea.
[Kevin sighs] That test was brutal.
Why does anybody need to know
what primogeniture is?
-Wait, that was one of the questions?
-[snaps fingers]
Ms. Lodge.
During a routine search, I found
this flask of rum in your locker.
Excuse me.
When did Riverdale High become a fascist
police state, Principal Mussolini?
It is my responsibility to look after
my students' well-being.
How do you think Barnard will react
when they hear about this incident?
The recruiter already saw me drinking
at my speakeasy.
They're not a bunch of prissy,
power-tripping asshats.
Stop. You don't have to do this.
You don't have to protect me.
[gasps]
Principal Honey, I'm so sorry.
The lock on my locker broke,
and I know Veronica's combination...
so I stashed that flask, my flask,
in there before the test.
So, this is your liquor, Mr. Andrews?
It's been a rough year, sir, as you know.
Sometimes I need to take the edge off.
Archie...
You'll have a week's detention.
-I'm gonna call your mother about this.
-I understand.
Yeah.
[sighs]
[chattering]
-Maybe because he isn't there.
-I don't know.
-Exactly.
-Jones.
And, Betty, to what do we owe
the pleasure?
We know Jonathan's lying
about writing "On Featherless Wings."
And we know that one
or all of you stole my laptop
and are conspiring against me.
-So, we're here to prove it.
-With a lie detector test?
[laughs] Okay, well, I refuse
to participate in this charade.
Fine.
Then you all can watch
while Jughead takes the test.
Is your name Forsythe Pendleton Jones III?
Yes.
When did you start writing
"On Featherless Wings"?
At the end of last summer,
before I'd even heard of Stonewall Prep.
Did you get rid of your old laptop because
it contained incriminating evidence?
Of course not. It was stolen.
And what, exactly,
do you think this is proving?
Well, Jonathan's guilt,
by process of elimination.
I hate to break it to you, sweetie,
but this isn't gonna prove
Jughead's innocence.
Do you think I don't know that, bitch?
This lie detector test is only
the beginning.
Once we're done
with all of you one-percenters,
none of you will be left standing.
-Hey, handsome.
-What are you doing here?
Just wanted to say thanks
for your gallant gesture earlier.
I was happy to do it.
I got nothing to lose. But you do.
You have everything.
Ronnie...
Ronnie, stop.
Dr. Beaker could be back any minute.
[sighs]
What's going on with you?
-What do you mean?
-This isn't you.
What's happening?
Nothing. We made a vow that we would make
the most of our time together.
And now clearly you're backing out
of that deal, so...
If you don't want to have fun,
then I'll just go have fun by myself.
-Ronnie, I...
-I have to meet Cheryl and Toni anyway.
[door opens, then closes]
["Don't Start Now" playing]
[over speakers] ♪ I'm all good already
So moved on, it's scary... ♪
You came.
Well, when a beautiful vixen calls,
I have no choice but to answer.
Did you talk to your partner?
-She's on her way.
-Mm.
-[groans] I love this song.
-Hm.
I know exactly what we can do
while we wait.
♪ Don't show up, don't come out ♪
♪ Don't start caring about me now ♪
♪ Walk away, you know how ♪
♪ Aren't you the guy who ♪
♪ Tried to
Hurt me with the word "goodbye"? ♪
♪ Though it took some time to
Survive you ♪
♪ I'm better on the other side ♪
♪ I'm all good already ♪
♪ So moved on, it's scary ♪
♪ I'm not where you left me at all, so ♪
♪ If you don't wanna see me
Dancing with somebody ♪
♪ If you wanna believe that
Anything could stop me ♪
♪ Don't show up, don't come out
Don't start caring... ♪
Babe, this is the woman
I was telling you about. Rosa.
Rosa, has anyone ever told you
how beguiling your eyes are?
I get that a lot.
How about we get out of here?
We have somewhere special
we'd like to bring you.
[Laura] Excuse me, Ms. Lodge.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but I have
a message from Ms. Blossom.
It's fine. Just polishing off
my maple-jito. Thank you.
All right, Laura.
Prepare the suite.
It's time to... snap a trap.
I'll get the lights.
[Rosa] Hmm...
[Veronica] Hermosa.
Veronica.
What are you doing here?
[Veronica] It's an emboscada...
my darling half sister.
An ambush.
And they say journalism is a dying art.
I marked you as soon as I saw you
at La Bonne Nuit.
How dare you try and seduce my dear
Tee-Tee like she's some backwater fool.
As if Cheryl and Toni would expose you
to the Maple Club, our rum operation?
I have no idea
what you're talking about, hermana.
The gall you have coming into town,
trying to ruin our business,
my livelihood.
I bet Daddy put you up to this, didn't he?
Do a little recon.
Scope out the competition.
I don't know what he's told you
about his condition.
Everything.
He also told me you didn't know.
He told you?
And not me?
He trusted you?
Can you blame him?
[Veronica grunts]
[softly] All right, let's hurry up.
Donna and Joan were in film studies,
but they could be back any moment.
I never should have taken that laptop
from Bret.
We'll get it back, Jug.
You take Joan's side, I'll take Donna's.
[Jughead] "Ready for print"?
The Boy in the River?
This is the novel that I submitted to win
the Baxter Brothers contract.
-About Jason Blossom?
-Yeah.
DuPont told me that
the Baxter Brotherhood rejected it
because it wasn't dark
or sociopathic enough.
It's definitely been rewritten.
But this is my book.
-What do you wanna do?
-Well, the only thing we can do.
I thought the Brotherhood didn't want
my novel.
-We didn't and we don't.
-Then, what the hell is this?
You really think I wouldn't recognize
my own story
after someone did a polish on it?
Ah, you should have had a lawyer take
a much closer look at your contract.
You see, the Brotherhood owns
everything you submit.
We kept the elements we liked
and then let another ghostwriter try
their hand at it.
Oh, yeah? Who?
[chuckles] Well, actually,
all of your classmates collaborated on it.
[knock on door]
Archie, what are you doing here?
I came to make sure you're okay.
I'm worried about you, Veronica.
What are you doing?
Drinking at school?
Acting like this crazy party girl?
You're pushing people away.
Tell me what's really going on.
He's dying, Archie.
-Who is?
-[sobbing] My dad.
He's been diagnosed
with a debilitating disease...
and I don't know what to do.
I feel... completely lost.
[continues sobbing]
I'm sorry, Veronica.
I know there's not much that I can say...
but one of the worst parts
about my dad dying...
was that I was never able to say goodbye.
Even in the months before.
I didn't know
what little time we had left,
and I regret not spending
more of it with him.
I don't know if I can sit by
and watch him waste away to nothing.
I don't want to see that.
Veronica, you're the strongest person
that I know.
And right now you have to give
some of that strength to your dad.
You know better than anyone
how to get him fired up.
That's what he needs.
Happy Friday, you soul-sucking vampires.
Good morning to you, too, mija.
Before you crawl back into your coffins
for the day,
I've got a little presentation
I've been working on.
Red Raven's newest ad campaign.
[Veronica clears throat]
Consumers are now more interested
in quality than name brands,
which is why we conducted
a blind taste test,
in which nine out of ten test subjects
picked Red Raven Rum
over the competitors Lodge Rum
and Lodge Spiced Rum.
As we like to say at Red Raven,
"Quality always."
And this is only the first wave.
We'll run print ads
in the Riverdale Register,
the Greendale Gazette
and the Seaside Sentinel to start.
Mija, do you really think
you'll get the upper hand?
Over me?
You're a little specialty brand.
Oh, haven't you heard?
Cheryl's already begun renovations
on her family's maple factory.
We'll be producing 300 percent
more maple rum by the end of the year.
Well, then I only have
one thing left to say.
-Congratulations, mija.
-Hmm.
You have successfully awoken the dragon.
Prepare to be eaten.
What is wrong with you?
Why would you intentionally provoke him?
You know how ill he is.
In times like these, family members
should be supporting each other,
not antagonizing one another.
Seems to me that Daddy's doing just fine.
Just one minor ad campaign
and he's more fired up
than he's been in days.
So don't for a second think
you understand Daddy better than me.
If anybody is going to save Daddy
from this crippling disease,
it's going to be me...
Veronica Lodge.
Now stand back and watch, ladies.
You might learn something.
[Betty] I've been thinking
about Mr. Chipping's tie pin, Jug.
And how Donna had it. It doesn't add up.
If the affair with Chipping was just
another one of Donna's fabricated stories,
then how did she get it?
Let's assume that someone else took
Mr. Chipping's tie pin.
Someone like Mr. DuPont?
Exactly.
It's possible he gave it to Donna
to add credibility to her story
about them having an affair.
Then she would have the tie pin
and the story of the affair at the ready
in case anyone got too close to the truth.
Hmm. That Mr. Chipping was driven
to suicide by Mr. DuPont.
[Betty] It's a theory, by any rate.
I wanted to clear the air
between us, Donna.
And hopefully resolve
this whole Jughead witch-hunt thing.
Just the two of us.
See, I think that you and Bret,
Joan and Jonathan...
are just pawns
being manipulated by Mr. DuPont,
who I think is the real villain here.
I'm intrigued.
Go on.
I don't think you had an affair
with Chipping.
["I Can't Bring Myself To Smile" playing]
If I'm right and you didn't
and DuPont somehow put you up
to saying that you did...
I implore you...
come forward.
Don't let yourself be a victim
of his machinations, Donna.
You think you're close to the truth,
don't you?
You and Jughead, teen detectives?
Are we?
I guess we'll see.
[Bret] Still working on that book, huh?
Hm. Well...
I do hope you enjoy your last night
in this room.
You are so smug, it just hurts, Bret.
You don't know what I'm going to say
at the tribunal,
but I promise you, it's not just going
to be about some short story
I didn't plagiarize, Bret.
It's going to be about everything
that is going on here.
It's going to be about Chipping,
and Moose, and Quill and Skull,
and about my novel.
I am going to let all these
toxic little genies out of their bottles.
Do you understand me?
No, you're not gonna say a damn thing.
Do you know how I know?
Because as it turns out, I do have a tape
of you and Ponytail doing the nasty.
[Betty giggling]
And if you so much as utter
a single j'accuse,
I will release it, wide.
You think blackmail is gonna stop me?
Yes, because you're a hopeless romantic.
That tape might not hurt you, Jones.
But it will destroy Betty.
Something like that will haunt her
for the rest of her life.
So, what's it gonna be?
You wanna continue this sad attempt
at martyrdom,
or are you gonna protect the honor
of your precious girlfriend?
[Archie] Wait.
Something wrong, Arch?
I can't do it.
What the hell?
Vic, my grandpa started this company.
And my dad kept it going.
It's not gonna be sold on my watch.
[DuPont] Make no mistake,
the stealing of another student's work
will not be tolerated at Stonewall Prep.
If the accusation is found to be true,
the penalty is immediate expulsion.
But we're going to give you
a choice today.
One that you do not deserve.
Nevertheless...
you can either gracefully,
quietly withdraw from Stonewall Prep,
which will save yourself
and us the embarrassment of a hearing.
Or you can stay and fight the accusation
of plagiarism in a public forum,
where you could win,
but most likely you'll lose...
tarnishing Stonewall's name
and destroying your future.
I'll leave.
What the hell happened in there, huh?
I thought you were gonna bring down
the temple,
and instead, you let them run roughshod
all over you.
What choice did I have?
Not like you to walk away from a fight,
a fight you could win.
You don't know that,
you don't know these people.
This game is fixed.
It's been fixed from the beginning.
There was no way I was winning that today.
[sighs]
-How does it look, Mr. Lodge?
-Like it's always been there.
-Vic let you keep the sign, huh?
-I didn't end up selling the company.
I couldn't. I made Mr. Keller foreman.
He said he'd work on a reduced salary
until we get a few more contracts in.
Good.
It was the sex tape, wasn't it?
Bret threatened to release it
if you didn't back off.
What does it matter, Betty?
To hell with Bret.
To hell with this entire school.
Couldn't have been all bad, Forsythe.
Yeah, we hope there aren't
any hard feelings.
There's a party tonight in the woods
behind the school.
-We're celebrating the Ides of March.
-You should come.
One last hurrah before you pack up
your things and are gone forever.
-You're deranged.
-We'll be there.
-What?
-One last hurrah.
Great. And bring your friends, too.
The more the merrier.
-Like hell we're going to that, Jug.
-You trust me, right?
-Of course. Why?
-I have a plan.
But first I'm going to need to take care
of that leverage Bret has over us
and then I will tell you everything.
It's all gonna be okay, I promise.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Penny for your thoughts?
["Lookalike" playing]
I won't be able to walk with everyone
at graduation.
What?
Mr. Honey told me on Monday.
I have a plan.
Okay.
I'll go to summer school for my diploma.
Take a skip year.
And apply to colleges for spring semester.
What do you think?
That sounds like an outstanding plan,
Archie.
♪ I know in your head
You see me instead ♪
♪ 'Cause he looks a lot like I did... ♪
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
It's B.
She's inviting us
to a Stonewall Prep party.
[sighs]
You wanna go?
Seriously? Those people suck.
Right you are, Archiekins,
but when's the last time
all four of us hung out together?
And we did vow to have more fun.
Okay.
["Kill For Love" playing]
[Veronica] Oh, God.
It's like A Midsummer Night's Dream had
a baby with Euphoria.
I gotta hand it to these jerks,
they know how to throw a party.
You guys see Jughead? I said
we'd meet up with him once we got here.
I'm gonna do a lap, okay?
See if I can find him.
-Here.
-Great.
Want to move closer to the fire?
I have a way more fun idea
of how you could keep me warm.
When's the last time we made it
in the woods?
Let's go.
♪ While the world just stayed the same ♪
Friends, Romans, countrymen,
lend me your beers. [chuckles]
[boys chattering]
[laughing] Yeah.
Oh, thou bleeding piece of earth...
What do we got here?
I knew you and Ponytail were into, um...
some weird kinks, but, uh...
I mean, what is this, Freaky Friday or...?
Gentlemen, would you excuse us?
Uh, the bunny and I have
some unfinished business.
You want to settle this?
All right.
But not here.
Follow me.
[Betty] Donna.
Oh, good, you made it.
Yeah, I know Jughead didn't speak up
at his tribunal
because Bret's blackmailing him.
But I do not care what you do to me.
So what, you have a tape?
Of me and Jughead?
I am the daughter of the Black Hood.
It's gonna take a lot more than that
to get me and Jughead off your case.
I promise you,
we are going to find out and expose
all of your dirty secrets,
up to and including Chipping's murder.
Do you have anything to say about that?
Actually, I do.
You see, I've been doing
a little investigating of my own.
And I found out some fascinating things
about you, Betty.
I even took a field trip
to Shankshaw Prison
to see your old friend Evelyn Evernever.
And you know what Evelyn told me?
The magic word.
Oh, you mean "tangerine"
repeated three times?
Yeah, you're a little late to that party.
"Tangerine" doesn't work on me anymore.
No, she told me the other magic word.
The one that makes you fugue
and hurt the people who you love.
You wanna hear it?
["Desensitize" playing in distance]
Okay.
Hey, have you guys seen Betty and Jughead?
I think they went that way,
into the clearing behind those trees.
Thanks.
-Oh, my God! Betty, what happened?
-Jug!
Is he breathing?
[Jughead] It started out
like any other week.
There's no pulse.
Who would have guessed
that by Friday night...?
He's dead.
What did you do, Betty?