Previously Riverdale...
Do you see those people
over there?
They're Dodger's family.
I'm not sure
what you're here for,
but you and your boys
need to leave.
We've got kids here,
we don't want any trouble.
Mr. DuPont, the first book
in the Baxter Brothers series,
was written by my grandfather.
I killed Caramel.
No, Betty, that wasn't you,
that was your deeply
screwed-up dad.
Someone is trying
to drive me mad.
But, once I find out
who this depraved monster is,
I will unleash a wrath
upon them so wicked,
they will wish they had been
consumed in their mother's womb.
You've reached
the Riverdale hotline.
If you wish to report a problem in
your neighborhood, leave a message.
Anonymity is your choice.
We're here to help.
"And as Buddy and Bobby Baxter sat
down at the dining room table,"
exhausted and bruised,
they felt satisfaction.
The Case of the Boy
in the River had been solved.
Tomorrow, there would be
another mystery.
But tonight, their only concern
"was dinner."
Outstanding, Mr. Jones.
I believe the Baxter Brothers has
found their newest ghostwriter.
Wait, I won the contract?
Like, right this second?
That is correct.
Professor DuPont,
you can't actually believe
that garbage was better
than my submission.
Oh, I can and I do.
Your contract, Mr. Jones.
Your first step into
a larger, better life.
Provided you play by the rules.
I don't understand.
Dartmouth was my safety school.
I guess you should've
accepted Harvard's invitation.
Nice try, Daddy,
but I still have
my interview with Columbia.
Interview, huh?
Good luck with that.
Columbia's
extremely competitive.
But, I believe
Riverdale Community College
has a rolling admission policy.
So if you study there,
you could launch your rum empire.
If that's still happening.
Oh, it's happening, Daddy.
Hey, wake up, Red.
Mr. Jones? Ah!
What are you doing here?
Investigating a vigilante.
Now be honest with me.
Is that you?
Yeah, it is.
You're not gonna
arrest me, are you?
I should.
What the hell do you think
you're doing, huh?
Helping.
People are too scared to call you
or the cops, so I set up a hotline.
What happens if you get hurt?
Or worse?
People die changing tires on
the side of the road, Mr. Jones.
At least I'd die with
a shred of honor.
[SCOFFS] What a load of smug BS.
You think that's gonna
comfort your mom?
Why aren't you focused
on the center,
- protecting these kids?
- I am.
But trouble shows up here
about every other day,
starting with the Dickensons who
are still out there, by the way.
You're doing
good work here, Red.
Here. Honorable work.
Maybe I can help you.
[JUGHEAD] What do you say, Chuck.
Can you help me?
So you want me
to use FBI resources
to track down your...
Sorry, our grandfather.
Why the sudden urgency?
Well, look, it's probably something
I should have done months ago, but...
I have an important
decision to make.
And I can't until I know the truth.
His truth.
Can you help me?
What's wrong, Pop?
Our liquor license
has been revoked.
As of Sunday, the speakeasy won't
be allowed to serve alcohol.
What? According to whom?
The mayor's office.
Figures.
This is payback
for me vowing to challenge.
Daddy's precious rum empire.
Long-term,
we're fighting this injunction.
Short-term,
we're hosting
a no-holds barred blow-out
at La Bonne Nuit
before the boom falls.
No offense, Veronica,
but your father,
he wasn't raised right.
Actually,
he was.
And you've just given me
a great idea.
[CREAKING]
Betty. Betty, wake up.
What? What's happening?
Honey, it's your sister.
She mutilated a nurse
at Shady Grove.
She almost clawed her face off.
[BETTY] Maybe this is a mistake.
Polly's messed up,
but she's not a literal monster.
This is security footage
from Shady Grove.
[BETTY SIGHS]
Okay, Polly is sitting there, looking
like a zombie, but she's not hurt...
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
What the hell happened?
She attacked that nurse for no reason.
She'll only talk to you,
she says.
And alone.
Okay. Well then
I'll go talk to her.
First, there's one more thing
you should know.
The nurse that Polly disfigured,
her name is Betty.
Heard you wanted to speak to me.
Betty. Oh, thank God.
You're the one I can trust.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Polly, can you tell me
what's going on?
You attacked
a nurse named Betty.
That's impossible.
I can't remember
any of what they're saying.
I was in the rec room,
and the next thing I remember,
I'm in here
and I'm chained to this bed.
Please, Betty.
You have to believe me,
Betty, please.
I didn't do this.
Please believe me.
I didn't do it, Betty.
I didn't do it, it wasn't me. [CRYING]
Please, I didn't do it.
I didn't do this, Betty.
I didn't do it.
Damn, Mr. Jones,
where did you get a metal detector?
From Southside High
when they shut it down,
but between that,
and the security cameras we're hooking up,
think you're in
pretty good shape, Red.
Yeah, well, I'll be
in even better shape
once Dodger and his family
are in jail or out of town.
But all this is awesome.
Thank you, sir.
Hey, uh, I can
help you find Dodger.
I know the alleys,
and a bunch of us used to work for him.
We're good, Eddie.
The last thing I need is you
out there kicking up dust, okay?
[VERONICA] Abuelita.
[LORDES] You've been so busy
mi ahijada.
- Godmother.
- Mm?
I've been thinking about
expanding my business,
getting into rum production.
But there's a real craft to it,
and my father
refuses to teach me.
- How did he learn?
- From me.
It is my recipe that he's using.
Could you tell me the recipe?
[CHUCKLING] Of course!
But what about college?
Have you heard back
from Harvard?
Abuelita,
you won't even believe,
the things that your son
has been doing.
What kind of things?
[PHONE VIBRATES]
Hey, Charles, any luck?
Yeah. I found him.
More specifically,
the U.S. Postal Service did.
Wait, seriously? How?
Evidently, Forsythe has
a P.O. box in Seaside.
He checks it once a month when
he comes in from the forest.
Wait, did you say forest?
The crazy thing is,
I actually believe her.
Honey, we saw it
with our own eyes.
Well, no, obviously,
she did it, but...
not consciously.
It's like she was fuguing or something.
Wait a minute.
The doctors at Shady Grove said
Polly received a phone call
about an hour or so
before the incident.
[PHONE RINGING]
Charles is trying to figure
out the caller's identity.
[PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
Cooper-Jones residence.
What? Was it about Polly?
What are you doing?
Mom.
Listen to... Mom!
You're acting just like Polly.
You're acting hypnotized.
[CLAPS HANDS]
What's going on?
Why am I holding a knife?
You don't remember?
Did somebody...
Did the phone ring,
or did I imagine it?
No, it rang, you answered...
Whoever called must have
said something that...
I don't know, triggered you
into attacking me.
Is that even possible?
We need Charles
to trace that phone call.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
Mami.
What a surprise.
When did you get here?
[SHOUTS IN SPANISH]
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
Picking fights
with your daughter.
Your father is turning over
in his grave.
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
Really?
Turning my own mother
against me.
Oh.
And guess what
she shared with me.
Our family's secret rum recipe.
So brace yourself, Daddy.
It's on.
Archie, I need
for you to sit down for this.
Vic, your dad's foreman,
came by earlier today
and he wants to buy us
out of Andrews Construction.
Well, tough, Mom,
'cause we're not selling.
[PHONE RINGING] I'll tell Vic that
myself right after I fire his ass.
Toby, now is not a good time.
It's about Eddie. He and Malcolm went
looking for Dodger and his brothers.
- And they found him.
- What? Where are they?
They're beat up, Archie. Bad.
Eddie's in the hospital. Again.
What'd you find out, Charles?
Our hunch was right.
The calls received by Polly and
Alice came from the same place.
Shankshaw Prison.
Charles, something must have
been said on those calls
that made Mom and Polly
enter a trance-like state
that turned them
into deranged killers.
As if they were hypnotized.
I thought the same thing.
And who do we know that uses
auditory cues and hypnotism
to control its members?
The Farm.
Edgar may be dead,
but his lovesick lackey Evelyn
sure isn't.
She's in prison.
Any chance that prison
is Shankshaw?
[MAN] You hold it
right there, boy.
Now, you are trespassing
on private property.
If you're Forsythe Jones
the First,
then I'm your grandson.
I... I... I... I guess...
you'd better come in, then.
Jason,
Julian,
thank you for
joining me, brothers.
[SIGHS] The day
has finally come.
I'm ending our
collective misery today.
The Chernobyl-grade roach bombs
I've set up throughout Thistlehouse
are discharging a toxin
strong enough to kill anything
that crawls within these walls.
I was born in poison...
and I shall die in poison.
[GAS HISSING]
[CREAKING]
[COUGHING]
Mumzie,
what a surprise.
[BODY THUDS]
Whatever your dad said about me
is probably true.
I'm actually not here
to talk about that.
Yet.
I'm here to talk about
one of your old classmates,
Francis DuPont.
Well, I remember Francis,
all right.
Look, I think you wrote the
original Baxter Brothers book,
not DuPont.
I think he stole your idea
and then he published it
under his name.
Oh, you got it all figured
out, haven't you, boy?
Except your facts,
little mixed up.
Well, why don't you help me
sort them out?
Eddie and Malcolm
are in the hospital.
Munroe is with them,
they went after the Dickenson brothers.
Bill and Fagan beat the
living hell out of those kids.
- I'm not gonna let that go.
- All right.
All right, then.
Your dad would
pound the tar out of me
if I let you do this on your
own, but this is it.
We handle these Dickenson boys
and then you're putting this
vigilante business to bed, all of it.
If I agree, will you help me?
Yeah.
Just let me get changed first.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Well, lookie here.
Bill and Fagan Dickenson.
You guys are the scum of the earth.
Going after kids.
[SPITS]
[FP] Big man, huh?
Beating up teenagers.
Let's see how you do against
someone your own size.
I'll break your bones, old man.
Not before we break yours.
[GRUNTS]
Time to
rise and shine, mother dear.
[COUGHS]
Cheryl. What...
Did you really think I was
gassing myself to an early grave?
No. That was a ruse.
But riddle me this, Mumzie.
Do you remember
when I was a little girl,
and you used to read me Alice's
Adventures in Wonderland?
Cheryl, you release me
this minute!
You would ask me
if I thought I was Alice.
And I would say, "No,
Mother, I'm the Red Queen."
So as the Red Queen
did to Alice,
I am putting you on trial.
Lunatic child.
What are the charges?
They are as follows.
Prolonged gaslighting in hopes
of driving me cuckoo-bananas,
attempted murder of Archie,
Betty, Veronica and Jughead,
and actual murder of my father,
Clifford Blossom,
Claudius Blossom,
and Hal Cooper among others.
How do you plead,
mother most foul?
I got to say,
that felt good.
Yeah?
- We kicked ass, Mr. Jones.
- Mm-hmm.
It's been a while since these fists
delivered some proper street justice.
The old jacket
still fits like a glove.
- [CHUCKLES]
- And your old man,
he's looking down on us,
probably shaking his head, but...
still...
he'd be glad your
crime-fighting days are over.
[FORSYTHE] And I always
loved detective stories,
so, uh, I come up
with this notion
to write a book
about teenage detectives.
Right, the Baxter Brothers.
So how did
DuPont steal it from you?
[SCOFFS] You're getting
ahead of the story here.
You see, I was burning out
at Stonewall,
so, uh, I quit.
The only thing I had
to show for it all is this
one Baxter Brothers story.
I didn't know what to do with it.
Francis said he did.
He offered to buy it from me.
How much?
$5,000.
$5,000?
That franchise is worth
millions now.
Over the years, When I saw how
popular Baxter Brothers became,
I grew bitter,
started drinking and took
my anger out on the world,
and on my son.
Eventually I figured it'd be best
for all concerned if I just...
Went out for a pack of
cigarettes and didn't come back?
Yeah.
[SCOFFS]
Mr. DuPont asked me
to be the next ghostwriter.
Is that a fact?
All this time, I...
I had thought that Mr. DuPont
was killing people
in order to keep the secret
that he stole the book from you.
[CHUCKLES] That's quite
the theory there.
If that was the case,
he would have killed me too, wouldn't he?
Yeah. Yes.
A word of advice for you.
I messed up my life.
I messed up your father's life.
You seize the opportunities
you're being given.
- [PRISON DOOR BUZZES]
- Took you long enough.
You weaponized
my family against me
by calling them and triggering
some post-hypnotic suggestion.
What's the directive?
How exactly are you getting
your sleeper cells to turn?
When I deliver the activation,
the receiver turns
into you.
What the hell does that mean?
They become Betty.
As in, Betty Cooper,
as in,
you.
Why did Polly attack
a nurse named Betty?
Why did my mom come after me?
When triggered,
they become Betty.
They try to kill dark Betty,
evil Betty, other Betty.
You mean they try to murder me.
Elegant, isn't it?
It was Edgar's idea.
When they hear the trigger word,
they become you.
And therefore, try to kill you.
You're a psycho.
[EVELYN] Mm-hmm.
So what exactly is
the trigger word, Evelyn?
Tangerine.
Repeated three times in a row.
Tan...
- What do you say we call it a night, Red?
- [SHOP BELL JINGLES]
You need a ride
back to the center?
Mr. Jones.
[GUN COCKS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[FP GROANING]
I can't believe it.
Mr. Jones, I'm so sorry.
For what? Hey.
It'll take a whole lot more
than a flesh wound
for me to regret
what we did tonight.
It was Dodger Dickenson.
We don't know that.
Yeah, we do.
Word on the street,
it was Dodger and his crazy-ass mom Darla.
That was a parting shot before
the Dickensons get out of town.
So they're still in Riverdale?
Yep. Loading out the arcade.
How about you keep
your damn mouth shut, Fangs?
You're already on thin ice with me.
And you,
you don't even think about it, Red.
We talked about this.
You agreed to
hang it up for good. Hey!
They're leaving town. Archie!
I left before she could
say it a third time.
But what the hell would happen if I
heard the trigger word three times?
Would I be activated
and wanna kill myself?
One way to find out.
We try it here.
Tangerine. Tangerine.
Tangerine.
I don't understand.
Nothing happened.
Maybe because
you're already Betty?
Well, the good news is,
you're officially not a ticking time bomb.
Why must we endure this farce?
It's clear no matter what I say,
you're just looking for
a reason to kill me, Cheryl.
On the contrary, Mumzie,
despite your
wicked machinations,
I'm looking for
a reason to spare
your life.
You're my mother.
And yet, you've always
been so cruel to me...
For why?
You brutalized me
my entire life.
You tried to kill my friends,
and then you hid in Thistlehouse
to keep torturing me.
You saw me happy with Toni and you
couldn't let that be, could you?
[LAUGHS]
It wasn't your happiness
with the she-goblin
that I wanted to destroy.
It was your happiness
with Jason.
How can I live knowing
that you are happy
with my dead son?
You don't get what I can't have!
In that case, Mumzie,
you're guilty of
the worst crime of all:
Being hateful to
your rotten core.
Hmm. So, there.
You've condemned me.
[SIGHS]
Execute me, then.
Or cart me off to prison.
Oh no.
Not jail. At least not
in the traditional sense.
You're going to a place
so vile, so revolting,
you'll wish you were bricked up
in Thistlehouse's walls.
TT, prepare the chloroform.
[MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY]
Thanks.
You're dressed to kill me, huh?
Am I in any danger?
Not tonight.
Just cutting loose before
the clock strikes 12.
- [HIRAM] Mm.
- [REGGIE] Hey, Ronnie.
You got someone asking for you.
Says it's official.
Are you a bourbon gal?
I can whip you up a killer old-fashioned.
Veronica Luna,
I'm Shoshana Rutherford.
The recruiter from Columbia?
What are you doing here? I...
My interview's on Monday.
Your assistant
called my assistant,
and requested that I come down
and see your thriving business
in action tonight.
I'm so sorry, Miss Rutherford,
for the miscommunication,
but can we talk in a bit? Um...
I promised the crowd
a floor show.
No!
You don't get to hurt my kids,
shoot somebody in front of me
and leave without any payback.
Dodgy,
care to pump this bozo
full of lead
so we can take
his truck with us?
No, Mom. It's all right.
Look at him.
Bill and Fagan got their licks
in, didn't they?
But if it's a fight
you're after,
let's have ourselves
a good old-fashioned brawl.
["SATURDAY NIGHT'S ALRIGHT
FOR FIGHTING" PLAYING]
♪ It's getting late
Have you seen my mates? ♪
♪ Ma, tell me
When the boys get here ♪
♪ It's seven o'clock
And I want to rock ♪
♪ Wanna get
A belly full of beer ♪
♪ My old man's drunker
Than a barrel full of monkeys ♪
♪ And my old lady
She don't care ♪
♪ My sister looks cute
In her braces and boots ♪
♪ A handful of grease
In her hair ♪
♪ Oh, don't give us none
Of your aggravation ♪
♪ We had it
With your discipline ♪
♪ Oh, Saturday night's
All right for fighting ♪
♪ Get a little action in ♪
♪ Get about as oiled
As a diesel train ♪
♪ Gonna set this dance alight ♪
♪ Well, they're packed
Pretty tight in here tonight ♪
♪ I'm looking for a dolly
Who will see me right ♪
♪ I may use a little muscle
To get what I need ♪
♪ I may sink a little drink And
shout out "She's with me!" ♪
♪ A couple of the sounds
That I really like ♪
♪ Are the sounds of
A switchblade and a motorbike ♪
♪ I'm a juvenile product
Of the working class ♪
♪ Whose best friend floats
In the bottom of a glass ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Don't give us none
Of your aggravation ♪
♪ We had it
With your discipline ♪
♪ Saturday night's
All right for fighting ♪
♪ Get a little action in ♪
♪ Get about as oiled
As a diesel train ♪
♪ Gonna set
This dance alight... ♪
Stop!
You'll kill him!
I told Dodger,
if we ever fought again,
he wouldn't be able to walk.
So you drag his ass
out of here, Darla.
And if you or any of your sons
step foot in this town
ever again,
I'll kill all of you.
[BOY] Archie.
♪ Saturday, Saturday, Saturday
Saturday night's all right ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[ALL CHEERING]
[MAN] Love you!
Well, I hope
the song and dance was fun,
'cause at midnight,
you turn back into Cenicienta.
And all this, it goes away.
I may not be able to serve rum,
but that won't stop me
from making it
and burying you.
Hmm. About that.
Do you know what this is?
It's a patent.
That rum recipe that my
mother so graciously gave you,
I own it.
So if you use it to make rum,
I will sue you
for everything you have.
Oh, and good luck
with your interview.
I can't wait to hear
what Columbia thinks about
underage party girl
Veronica Luna.
Mm.
Hello.
Are you here to kill me
like I killed Caramel?
I leave you alone for one day
and you get shot.
Well, I've had worse and I'll
be home tomorrow morning.
Where you been anyway?
I should probably
sit down for this.
I, uh...
I found Grandpa.
He's living in Seaside.
He's in a converted bus.
Sounds about right.
What'd you do that for?
Mr. DuPont offered me
the Baxter Brothers contract.
[SCOFFS]
I wanted to talk to Grandpa
before I signed or not.
- And now that you have?
- It turns out I was wrong.
DuPont did steal the idea from
Grandpa, but he did it legally.
And for what it's worth,
he feels bad about the
way he treated you.
He knows what he did
to you and Grandma.
And he knows that
he was a bad father.
Yeah, that he was.
But maybe this wild goose chase I
went on could be worth something.
Like what?
Would you be willing to talk
to him if I brought him here?
Doc has me here overnight.
I guess if he wanted to stop by,
couldn't exactly say no...
could I?
Oh.
Hello, Mumzie.
Cheryl?
What is this?
I trust you approve
of this bunker.
After all, it's larger than the cell
you would have gotten at Shankshaw.
With food,
electricity, plumbing.
You wretched child.
You can't keep me... Oh.
On the contrary, Mother,
you need time and solitude
to seek penance
for your crimes and cruelty.
Toodles.
Cheryl. Cheryl.
Chery!
[BETTY] It was terrifying,
Charles.
When I saw the red door,
I fugued.
I slipped into a trance. Why?
I don't know, maybe a combination
of hearing the trigger earlier
and then returning to
a familiar setting.
What I saw,
me about to kill Caramel,
I think that's when the
dark part of me was born.
If that's true,
if you can go back to the
moment of dark Betty's birth
and stop it from happening,
it will essentially be...
Killing my shadow self
before she was even born.
We could try it.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Tangerine.
Tangerine. Tangerine.
Wait.
Let me take that from you.
But what am I gonna do now?
You can go play.
Really? I can go and play?
Yeah, go ahead.
Thank you.
[CHARLES] Betty.
I... I...
I'm not sure,
but I think I did it.
Well, that's great news.
You're all right.
You're okay now.
I'm sorry I kept you
waiting, Miss Rutherford.
I'm guessing my shot at
Columbia is pretty much blown.
Not necessarily.
At Columbia, we're always looking
for people with good stories.
I don't know
what happened here tonight,
but I'll bet it's a good story.
It is indeed.
Well, how about
you tell it to me?
[INHALES]
[TONI] Babe, are you okay?
Are you having second
thoughts about your mom?
No, but...
I was ruminating that perhaps...
[SIGHS]
It's time to bury Jason.
Cheryl, are you sure?
Yes.
[SIGHS]
There's been so much pain
and poison in this house.
And Jason, more than any of us,
deserves the peace my mother
spent years denying me.
Archie?
What's going on, honey?
Why are you sitting in the dark?
What happened?
Who did this to you?
I did.
I did it to me, Mom.
The Dickensons
were leaving town.
They were done with Riverdale.
But I wanted to hurt them,
to hurt Dodger.
Maybe even kill him.
Archie.
Doesn't make
any sense to me, Mom,
how predators like Dodger
get to live,
but Dad, he...
[SIGHS]
And the worst part about it is, some
of the kids from the center were there,
and they saw me
standing over him, angry,
bloody,
- and a monster.
- No.
You're not a monster.
You're just...
still hurting.
When will this end, Mom?
How does this end?
I've never felt further
from Dad than I do now.
[MARY SIGHS]
Let me guess, my old man
didn't wanna come.
No.
He ran away.
I'm so sorry.
I feel like a fool.
No, you're not.
You would be if you turned
down that contract, though.
No, I'm signing it.
[SIGHS]
I think it's time
to let go of the past.
Evening, Forsythe.
Oh.
This is the part
where you kill me?
No, you ass.
It's an initiation.
Welcome to the Quill and
Skull Society, Jones.
[ALL APPLAUD]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Cheryl, what's up?
[CHERYL] Thank you all
for coming.
You all were here last
time I was at this river.
When I tried
to take my own life.
It's only fitting
that you're here now.
[TEARFULLY] My beloved Toni,
as I give Jason,
at long last,
the funeral he deserves.
[CRYING]
[CONTINUES CRYING]
He was a good brother to me.
I wish you could have
met him for real.
I know.
[DOOR BEEPS, OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[ARCHIE] Yeah?
Can I help you?
Archie? Archie Andrews?
I am.
It's good to see you, son.
My name is Frank.
I'm, uh...
I'm your dad's brother.
Tangerine.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Betty.
Honey.
What happened?
I wanted to make sure
that it was gone.
The dark part of myself.
And it was.
He's dead.
What did you do, Betty?