[VERONICA] Previously on Riverdale...
Now that the doll's
back, the spirit of Julian
is haunting Thistlehouse?
What other explanation
could there possibly be?
These kids, they're good kids.
Reg, we're thinking maybe the Bulldogs
could be like big brothers to them.
Did you happen to know my grandfather?
[FRANCIS] Your grandfather
was an excellent writer.
[BETTY] We don't actually
know anything about Charles.
I'm interested in, "Is he
a serial killer or not?"
You see, our father needed help,
"Our father?"
Leave town
or the next time we meet,
you won't be driving away.
You won't even be walking.
[GUN COCKING]
You're a dead man, you hear me?
You're a dead man!
[JUGHEAD] This is what
happens in Riverdale.
Once the sun sets,
Dodger's minions go to work.
He recruits hungry and homeless kids,
so that if they're arrested,
they do some time in juvie,
but then, they're back on the streets...
...working for Dodger again.
They're chewed up by the system.
[METAL CLANKING]
Except that recently,
someone's thrown a tire
iron into the system.
You'll thank me someday.
[MUFFLED] Let me go. Come on, man.
[JUGHEAD] Usually, Dodger or the police
would go to the kid next, but
tonight's his lucky night.
Instead of getting sucked
back into the system
then spat out again...
...these kids,
they've got someone
looking out for 'em now.
People that ask themselves,
"How do you save a town?"
And who know the answer...
Welcome to the team.
..."One kid at a time."
For every kid saved,
there was one less hustling for Dodger,
and that would not do at all.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[JUGHEAD] Meanwhile, in existential hell,
I was facing the tyranny of a blank page.
[DIAL PAD BEEPS]
I need my anchor.
[CELL PHONE DIALING]
Hey, I didn't wake you, did I?
[BELL DINGING]
- Hi.
- Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I just can't write.
Mr. Chipping gave the
class this assignment
where we're supposed
to write our own version
of a Baxter Brothers novel,
which should be a dream come true,
but for the first time in my life,
I'm having writer's block.
Why?
My advice, just take a break.
Okay? Take a walk. Look at some art.
Kiss your girlfriend.
I keep thinking I should be breaking
the Baxter Brothers novels down
like, scientifically, or something.
That could work, but you could also...
...kiss your girlfriend.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
- I'm sorry.
[INDISTINCT VOICES]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STAMMERS] What are you all doing here?
[SPOOKY TONE] Julian
needs a body, Cheryl.
So we're giving him yours.
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC INCREASES IN TEMPO]
[DOOR OPENS]
What?
Andrews, you asked
us to be big brothers,
not soldiers in a turf war.
Who did this?
I got a pretty good idea.
It was definitely Dodger.
He's been coming after us for weeks.
We've been chipping away at his gang,
there's more kids
getting off the streets,
but there's only so much we can do
until Dodger himself is behind bars.
I can add Sketch Alley to
the nightly patrol area.
That's great, but go after Dodger.
He works out of the Wipeout Arcade.
[BETTY] So, based on the last
few days of following Charles,
this is what I've logged.
7:00 a.m. he leaves the Five Seasons
where he has a suite
and goes to the FBI field office.
He has all of his meals
at Pop's or our house.
And then rounding out his daily routine,
he goes to the Casa Grande
Gym for a 90-minute-workout,
including weekends,
and then he goes back
to the Five seasons.
Well, um...
I'm no expert, Betty, but...
...it doesn't sound like
Charles is a serial killer.
Kinda just sounds like,
he's a... a lonely gay guy.
Or maybe he's both.
Oh, my God.
Of course.
Now that the trials are over,
I think it's time to
let bygones be bygones.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[HIRAM] I want us to move forward.
No more secrets, no more lies.
Speaking of secrets and lies,
how many more secret children
should we be expecting?
Hermosa is your one
and only half-sibling.
I swear.
If we did decide to
move forward together...
...what exactly would that look like?
Well, now that the prison
is bringing in a good income,
I'd like to return to my true passion.
Extortion?
Murder?
Rum.
Papi's passion is rum.
Rum has been in our
family for generations,
and Hermosa, who runs
our clubs in Miami,
will be staying in Riverdale,
to establish a rum outpost here.
I also thought she could
help out at the Speakeasy.
No.
I don't need any more
help at La Bonne Nuit.
With the exception of my newest hostess.
And seeing as how this is our house,
you two can show yourselves out.
Are you sure it's safe
out here in the night?
I'll be all right, Mr. Jones.
What's up?
Well, after your intel
and probable cause,
we raided the Wipeout Arcade,
turned over every Pinball
and Pac-Man machine in it.
Found plenty of contraband but...
...none on Dodger.
He was clean.
And let me guess, you
found it on a bunch of kids?
That scumbag is using them, Mr. Jones.
Even so, I can't arrest Dodger
unless I find evidence on him.
You're not going to.
Not as long as he has
these kids working for him.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[SIGHS]
[JUGHEAD] I think there's a real
life mystery in these books.
Now, I've gone and
re-read the entire series
and I noticed something strange.
Where there is a hoarse
voice and an overall tone,
sure, you can tell when a
new ghostwriter takes over.
Oh, yeah, a writer can't
completely suppress their own style.
Exactly. The verbiage, the phrasing,
these things are like
literary fingerprints.
And when I went back
to read the first book,
its fingerprint is unlike
any of the rest of them.
It's raw, it's real.
The characters have tension.
There's political commentary
woven throughout it.
They mention the war,
the boys have summer jobs,
and none of the rest of
them are this grounded.
Meaning?
Well, allegedly, Mr. DuPont
wrote the first five books
before passing the series off.
But after my analysis,
the stylistic differences
from book one to book two
are too distinct to ignore.
There's no way that whoever
wrote the first novel
wrote the following.
There's just no way.
Okay, well, who wrote it then?
This is gonna sound crazy, okay?
What if it was my grandfather?
Jug, your conspiracy theories
are usually... spot on,
but this one feels like a real stretch.
I know.
This is the one missing puzzle piece
I have of my grandfather.
Think about it, Betty.
He sent me a first edition,
first Baxter Brothers book.
And if that's not coincidental enough,
he wrote inside...
..."Never let them
take anything from you."
Does that not imply that
something was stolen from him?
Implies, yes.
Proves, no.
You need proof, Jug.
Yeah, you're right.
I'll get proof.
I know I'm onto something. I know it.
Meanwhile,
how's the mystery of our
suspicious brother going?
I'm following a hunch, too.
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
Hello, Chic.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
I want to know about Charles.
That story you told us about him.
Is it true that you lived together
at the Last Resort Youth Hostel?
Yes, it is.
When I went there,
a neighbor told me
about seeing bloody
sheets in the dumpster
and Charles mysteriously vanishing.
Does any of that ring a bell?
Charles, your brother
and I, we were together.
One time, we brought
a friend home with us,
and we were doing Jingle-Jangle
a little too much,
and things got out of control.
Charles snapped.
It was like some darkness took over.
He grabbed a pair of scissors
and he stabbed the guy to death.
How do I know that
you're telling the truth?
Why would I lie at this point, Betty?
What does Charles say happened?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Babe, what gives?
I thought you were
going to school today.
[SIGHS]
I was.
For realsies.
But...
I can't leave Nana and the
twins here alone with...
[MOUTHING] you know who.
[SIGHS] Cheryl, this has to end.
You've missed way too much school.
Okay, so get up,
or I'm gonna drag you there myself.
Okay, T.T.
[EXHALES]
But there's one thing
we need to do first.
Fact, evil spirits can't
cross a circle of salt.
It's a barrier against
all forms of malevolence.
Okay.
All done.
I'll get dressed and off we go.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Wait, you went and saw Chic about me?
Why not just ask me, if
you're so damn curious?
Because I don't trust you. All right?
All I know is that you're
predisposed to being a serial killer
and I've been burned before.
What did he even say to you?
Oh, he spun quite the yarn.
Yeah. About how you stabbed a man
with a pair of scissors
when you were high on Jingle-Jangle.
Oh.
Now I take everything Chic
says with a grain of salt...
...but do you have a polygraph machine
we can use here?
Yes.
Why?
[ARCHIE] Toby, Eddie.
Tell me, why do you guys
keep running with Dodger?
Well, he pays us.
Yeah, in... in Wipeout coinage.
So you're giving your
money right back to him?
Plus, we get all the
free pizza that we want.
You guys realize you're
risking everything,
your entire future, your lives,
for pizza and arcade games?
You guys don't have any spare
arcade games lying around, do you?
What's this now, Archiekins?
[SIGHS] I'm trying to get these
kids away from Dodger's Arcade.
Step one, give them another option.
What you're doing at the El Royale
is so inspiring, Archie,
but not enough people know about it.
Well, I can write about the center
in the Blue and Gold.
And I'll ask my vendors
to see if they can help
rustle up some arcade games.
[ANNOUNCER ON P.A.]
Will Cheryl Blossom
please report to the principal's office?
Cheryl Blossom to the principal's office.
What for was I summoned Ms. Bell?
Cheryl... [SIGHS]
...there's been an
accident at Thistlehouse.
One of the twins, Dagwood,
[BREATH TREMBLING]
swallowed a ping-pong ball
- and started to choke.
- What?
He was taken to the hospital
where Dr. Saperstein
performed a tracheotomy.
On Dagwood?
Oh, he's doing very well, I'm told.
Your grandmother's at
the hospital with Juniper,
waiting for you.
I'll get to the hospital posthaste
but there's one thing I
need to take care of first.
[VERONICA] In the words
of Dame Julie Andrews,
"Let's start at the very beginning."
So, hostess details to track.
Who's coming, where to seat them.
Ms. Danbers near Bob Potter, always.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Where not to seat them.
Booth 11 is the worst. Enemies only.
Okay, hold... hold on.
I'm gonna need a pen.
- Mom...
- [SIGHS]
...don't worry.
I'll be right behind
the bar if you need me.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
Damn you, Demon Doll.
Of course, you'd be here.
How dare you go after
Dagwood to get to me?
- [WOOD CREAKING]
- [FOOTSTEPS]
Don't move. Either of you.
[CHERYL] Aunt Cricket, Uncle Bedford?
Cheryl, we let ourselves
in. Hope that's all right.
- [MOANS]
- [THUDS]
[HIRAM] Veronica.
Oh, God.
Daddy.
Hermosa.
You're not on the reservation list.
Well, I couldn't miss your mother's
re-entry into the workforce, could I?
At the clubs I run in Miami,
I always keep a table
reserved for special guests.
Same.
Mark them down for booth 11.
Shall we begin?
[CLICKS]
You claimed you and
Chic met on the streets.
True or false?
True.
When we were both at our lowest.
Yes or no?
Someone was murdered
in the room you shared at the hostel?
Yes.
I came home from the
grocery store one day
and found a dead man in our bed.
Chic covered in his blood.
Some trick that he had brought home.
My instincts took over.
I dissolved the body with
lime in the bathroom tub,
threw out the sheets,
scrubbed the room clean with bleach.
Chic watched.
It was the end of us.
I left him.
Started over.
[BETTY] Next question.
Are you hiding anything from us?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
Tell me what, Charles.
I'm a recovering addict.
I attend weekly Narcotics
Anonymous meetings.
Here, in Riverdale,
they're held at my gym.
Charles I...
- [POLYGRAPH CLICKS OFF]
- That's my big secret, Betty.
[VELCRO RIPPING]
Hope you're satisfied.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Mr. Lodge.
What the hell are you doing here?
I came because I never
had the chance to, er...
...tell you that I'm sorry
for your loss, Archie.
Your father was a good man...
...and he'd be proud of you.
Thank you, sir.
And in his honor,
I'd like to make a charitable donation.
[CHECK TEARING]
I hear this place could use the help.
Oh, no, no. We're all good here.
Thanks.
It's a blank check, Archie.
All your problems, your
money woes, they go away.
Nothing's that simple with you.
Like I said, we're all good.
Thanks.
Oh.
Oh, T.T.
I had the most horrible, phantasmagoria.
Dagwood swallowed a ping-pong ball
and my accursed family
came to Thistlehouse.
Oh, good, she's up.
Cheryl dear,
we'd love to see you downstairs,
once you've collected yourself.
My attorney tells me
you're here to discuss
our maple syrup business?
Yes. We want to sell it.
The rest of the family is in agreement.
With your father dead
and Penelope in the wind,
we need your participation
and signature to move forward.
And why, pray tell, do
you vipers want to sell
what's left of our family's legacy?
The business hasn't
been profitable in years.
It's bleeding us dry.
[SCOFFS]
Babe, it's up to you.
This house has caused
you nothing but pain.
If you sold it,
we could start somewhere
new, somewhere fresh.
Your proposal makes a modicum of sense.
I'll consider it.
That's wonderful news.
Now, would you mind if
we went down to the chapel
to light a votive candle of
thanksgiving to celebrate?
Excuse you?
[STAMMERS] Go where?
To the chapel.
We always visit with the ancestors
whenever we come to Thistlehouse.
Absolutely not. You're
not going down there.
Now be gone!
All of you.
You won't be getting my signature,
nor will you ever
visit that chapel again.
It is off limits to anyone but me.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Mi amor.
Hiram?
What the hell are you doing here?
I want to come home.
But you don't live here anymore.
Now just... stop.
Veronica and I are finally free of you.
Is that what freedom looks like?
Playing hostess at a
teenager's gin joint.
Let me back in.
You don't have to work
another day ever again.
You'd be my wife again.
[SCOFFS]
Over my dead body.
That can be arranged.
Was that foreplay or punishment?
Punishment.
For having Tall Boy take potshots at me.
Like you do with Minetta?
Now you know.
Some couples, they...
...tie each other up to spice things up.
[WHISPERS] But you and me, we oder hits.
That's why we keep
doing this little dance.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Now...
...I need you.
I need you by my side.
I need you in my bed.
[HERMIONE GASPS]
[WHISPERS] So say yes
and we'll start over.
We'll always be married.
- We'll always be man and wife.
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
I already regret this.
[INHALES]
[JUGHEAD] So, I've been
doing some digging.
I pulled copies of Stonewall
Prep's literary magazine
from the year that my grandpa
and Mr. DuPont attended.
In the table of contents, it lists,
"A story written by Forsythe the First,"
but it was torn out.
It's like every trace of his writing
at Stonewall Prep is just gone.
Jug, where did your grandpa go to school
after Stonewall Prep?
Riverdale High.
Wasn't there a literary magazine
here, too, back in the day?
I'll be on the next train.
[VERONICA] I see you got my arcade games
but where are the kids?
A good question.
Toby. Eddie.
Where are your boys?
Didn't you tell them
we've got arcade games?
They can play for free.
Yeah, but Dodger's still
giving them free pizza.
All right, well, you can tell your boys
that, tonight, it's not just video games
that are free at El Royale.
It's burgers, and fries,
and milkshakes from Pop's.
We'll get the word out.
Come on.
Voila.
I love you, Ronnie.
Same, Archiekins. Same.
T.T... [SIGHS]
...this doll has conspired to bring
my extended family upon
us for some devilish work.
We'll stop Julian...
...and my hated family.
There.
Drown, spirit.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[CREAKING]
Mom?
I have a surprise for you.
Are those...
[HIRAM] Mine.
I am moving back in.
- Your mother and I...
- No.
I wanna hear it from her.
Veronica...
Mom.
...I have invited your father back.
Why?
He's a murderer.
And what am I?
I can't believe you.
We were done with him.
Mija, can we talk about
what this is really about?
[SIGHS]
Your sister. But you
don't need to worry.
You're still my favorite.
The apple of my eye.
My special little girl.
So, rest assured, there is no reason
for you to be jealous of her.
Are you deranged?
I'm not...
- ...jealous of her.
- Yes, you are.
And it's natural.
You are unbelievable. Both of you.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[JUGHEAD] Wait, hold on.
The story in this one
written by Frosty Pajamas.
What? That sounds like a joke.
Or it's a pen name.
Think about it.
Frosty is almost an
anagram for Forsythe.
And pajamas for PJs.
P and J, Pendleton and Jones?
Betty, this is totally the same writing.
The syntax, the word choice,
even the character names.
There's a character in
here named Bitsy Bane.
Wait, that sounds vaguely familiar.
Bitsy Bane is the next door
neighbor of the Baxter Brothers.
This was written years before
the first Baxter Brothers book.
Is that enough proof for you?
I would say so.
How could you, Betty?
How could I what?
You visited that
miscreant imposter, Chic.
Well, that's my business, isn't it?
Yes, except afterwards,
he used his lawyer
to contact the FBI, to report a murder
that happened in The Black Hood's house.
Not committed by him
but by a woman named Alice Cooper.
He said the man was bludgeoned
to death in the kitchen.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
A shady man?
Yes.
He also claims to know the location
of the murder victim's burial site.
All that evidence is still out there.
Why, Betty? Why kick this hornet's nest?
I'll take the lead
on this investigation.
Maybe with assist from
the local town sheriff.
See if the remains
are where Chic claims.
Don't wait up for us.
[DOOR SLAMS]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [MUSIC BLARING]
Hey, jump in, jump in.
[EXCLAIMS]
Well, what do you think, Archie?
I think you're amazing.
[VERONICA CHUCKLES]
It's a good cause.
Archie. Archie.
There's some guy named Dodger
outside who wants to see you.
All right, let me see what this
clown wants. I'll be back.
Reg, make sure everyone stays inside.
What the hell did I tell
you last time, Dodger?
You're not welcome here.
You're costing me my work force.
They're kids.
They're happy to work for me.
Or they were...
...till you showed up.
All right, what do you want?
Huh?
You want to fight me?
Sure.
But don't you need to
put your mask on first?
What are you talk... What
are you talking about?
See, I told you.
I told you he's that guy in the mask.
The one making trouble for us.
Aren't you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I think you do.
I think you know exactly
what I'm talking about.
Cops are on their way, asshat.
No need for them to come.
I got the confirmation I need.
[WHISTLES]
I'll be seeing you, friend.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[ALICE] So?
How... How'd it go?
[FP] We're okay, Alice.
We're gonna be okay.
We, uh...
Charles and I took care of that.
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
Thank you.
Thank you, Charles.
Well...
...we should go file the report then.
Wait, Charles.
You don't have to go.
If you're willing to go
out on a limb for my...
For our family,
then I should be able
to do that for you.
And I'm sorry. Okay?
Okay.
[SIGHS] Thank you for
meeting with me, Mr. DuPont.
Like I said, I wanted to have this
conversation with you in person.
Oh, not at all, Mr. Jones, son.
How can I help you?
I wanted to talk to you about
the first book in the
Baxter Brothers series.
What about it?
You didn't write it.
Pardon me?
I found a short story that
my grandfather had written
in an old Riverdale
High literary magazine.
It has a lot,
actually, the same elements,
and it was published years before
the first Baxter Brothers book.
I assure you, Mr. Jones,
I wrote the first five books myself.
No, sir, you wrote
books two through five.
The first one was
written by my grandfather.
That book has the same
tone as his short story.
It has the syntax, it has his voice...
Let me stop you right there.
Do you know what the worst thing
you can accuse a writer of being?
A plagiarist.
And based on what?
A story written by some
bottom-feeding dropout
in a third rate school's
so-called literary magazine?
The text doesn't lie.
I'm not a thief.
But your father,
the Sheriff,
he's a thief.
Oh, yes.
And much, much worse.
A vagabond.
What is it with you people?
You're given an inch and
you want the whole field.
For God's sake,
do you know who the hell I am?
Do you know what the Baxter Brothers
franchise means to Stonewall Prep?
It built Stonewall Prep.
I built Stonewall Prep.
The record deserves to be set straight.
Get out of my sight now,
while I'm still willing
to forget that you had...
...the audacity to summon me.
You're very lucky
I don't take you to the Headmaster
and get you expelled
for this vicious and slanderous attack.
Now get out.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[BELL CHIMES]
It's open seating.
Specials are on the board.
Actually, I came to have a little chat.
Sister to sister.
Let me guess.
Daddy sent you.
One last valiant tactic
to get me back into the family fold.
You're very smart, Veronica.
You don't know our father
as well as you think you do.
There is literally
nothing you could tell me
about Hiram Lodge
that would surprise me.
My mommy was a singer
at one of Papi's Miami clubs,
Sala de Oro...
...where they met.
They had a fling.
Mmm-hmm.
Tale as old as time.
He took advantage of
her, she got pregnant,
he left her high and dry.
Actually, he took care of her,
until she died.
And then he took care of me.
Papi and your mother
are renewing their vows tomorrow,
and they'd like for you to come.
You're kidding.
Come, or don't.
I'm just the messenger.
Look,
you're entitled to your opinion of him,
but the father I know...
...there's good in him.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Okay?
[CHERYL] Clearly I'm going to
have to get the locks changed.
Explain to us, Cheryl,
why is there a chain
on the chapel's gate?
I told you, Uncle Bedford,
no one is allowed in there but me.
As we suspected,
you're clearly having a psychotic break.
What?
As soon as we have you declared unfit,
we're selling the factory,
the grounds, everything.
Get out.
Get out, you parasites!
We're going.
Oh, and we will find out
whatever it is you're
hiding in our chapel.
[JUGHEAD] You see it, don't you?
[SIGHS]
Certainly appears to be
your grandfather's writing.
It's undeniable.
Mr. Chipping, you have to help me
bring this to light.
We have to prove to everyone
that Mr. DuPont's a fraud.
Look, I understand that your
reputation is on the line,
and maybe even your
position here at Stonewall.
But it's the truth, Mr. Chipping.
Yes, I'll help you.
How could I look myself in the mirror
as a teacher, as a
writer, if I didn't...
[EXHALES]
What the hell?
Mom, we got to go.
What do you mean? Go where?
I don't know, the Five seasons, maybe.
But you got to pack your bag
and we got to get out of here.
At least until things cool down.
What things, Archie? You're scaring me.
It's the Rec center.
Mom, not everyone's happy
about what we are doing there,
and I've made some enemies.
- [BRAKES SCREECH]
- [ARCHIE] Get down!
[GUN FIRING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [CAR PULLING AWAY]
Hermosa?
What the hell is that?
A painting Papi had commissioned for me.
Papi said to put it in a place of honor.
He said,
"Only the best for the apple of my eye."
Of course, he did.
I should have known.
You know what?
I was going to tell
Papi, as you call him,
that I'd be attending
his bogus vow renewal,
but instead...
...tell him I'll be skipping it.
My mom can roll out the welcome mat
for you two rum-sucking
leeches, if she wants.
But I'm not giving up my space
nor my place in this family.
I'm not giving an inch.
Not to you.
Not ever.
[HIRAM] I have to admit,
I'm surprised you called, Archie.
There is this criminal
working out of the Wipeout Arcade
named Dodger.
He's a loose cannon.
He needs to be stopped.
And what did this Dodger do, exactly?
He shot at my house and my mom.
Well, that sounds like a job for FP.
I reported what happened, Mr. Lodge,
but Dodger's slippery.
And you know as well as I do,
some things have to
be handled another way.
This is about protecting
what's left of my family.
Of course.
[SIGHS] But...
I hope you're not suggesting
that I commit an act of violence
against this thug.
I'm really sorry
about what happened to your mother.
But... [SIGHS]
Yeah, there's nothing I
can do for you, Archie.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Scholars, uh, as you know,
today, we will be discussing
Joseph Conrad's Heart of Darkness.
About the loss of a man's moral...
[SIGHS]
Mr. Chipping?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Jughead.
I couldn't help you.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Mr. Chipping!
My God, he's...
Call 911. Call an ambulance.
Call an ambulance!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[CREAKING]
[WHISPERS] T.T., T.T., awaken.
[TONI MOANS]
Do you hear that?
I...
I think it's Julian
trying to escape from the chapel.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
He's escaped.
Uncle Bedford?
[BREATH TREMBLING]
I... I always knew that there was a...
A certain sickness in our bloodline.
But this...
...this is monstrous.
- You...
- [WHIMPERS]
...are going away for a
long, long time, Cheryl.
[TONI] Let go of her, you monster.
[GRUNTING]
You are a sick girl, Cheryl,
and I'm taking you to the
authorities this instant.
[YELPS]
- Maybe...
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
...I'll save them the trouble.
- [YELLS]
- [GROANS]
[GASPS]
[PANTING] T.T?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Hi.
How did it all go?
Smooth as cream, babe.
FP led me right to
where he buried the body,
we moved what was left,
and everyone was appropriately grateful.
Even Betty?
Even Betty.
That's great.
I love you, babe.
I love you, too.
[CHERYL] Why, Aunt Cricket,
whatever can we do to you?
It's Bedford, Cheryl dear.
He didn't come home last night,
and I was wondering if you'd seen him.
He said he might come
around Thistlehouse.
Why, no. We didn't see him.
Oh, well, you wouldn't mind if I
had a peek around then, would you?
Actually, Auntie,
I would mind.
Unless you have a search warrant
from the local constable in hand.
I don't.
But I'll get one.
Good luck with that.
Now, you remember
where the door is, yes?
[DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS] When's Monroe back?
Next week.
Cool.
Crap, Andrews.
What's that?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
Holy hell!
Is he dead?
We got to get him to
a hospital, right now.
- [MOANS]
- [CELL PHONE DIALS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
What's going on?
Well, I heard that
seminar's been canceled
for the rest of the semester
and we're all getting automatic 4.0s
on account of Chipping's
fall from grace.
Well, I heard we're
getting a new teacher,
Celeste Ang.
I heard Ian McEwan
Be still, my heart.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hello, students.
I will be taking over
Mr. Chipping's seminar
this semester.
I've been told you're the
best and the brightest.
I look forward to
putting that to the test.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0