-[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
-[Kevin] The Farm left me.
The worthy ascended.
-Where's my mom and Polly?
-Gone. Everyone is.
I'm Charles. Your brother.
It's vital that we find your mom ASAP.
-Is there anything we can do to help?
-Thought you might ask.
Welcome home, Jay-Jay.
-We want your father, not you.
-Understood, Agent Ordelia.
-You're under arrest.
-For what?
For conducting illegal activities
at your establishments.
Hermione Lodge, you're under arrest
for conspiracy to commit murder.
Your own husband's.
This is what I got when I asked my dad
about that stupid game.
Been thinking about making some changes
to this place.
-I want you to help me run it.
-Oh, yeah.
[Archie] Fred Andrews will always be
a part of Riverdale.
I love you so much, Dad.
[Jughead] After Mr. Andrews' funeral,
the rest of summer vacation passed
in a surreal haze.
Betty, Veronica and I spent as much time
as we could with Archie.
We had dinner at Pop's every night.
And every day, you could tell
he was getting better and better.
I'm not saying he wasn't still
heartbroken, the entire town was,
but my pal Archie's a fighter.
And by the last day of summer vacation,
while the football field was being mowed
for the new season
and the school floors
were being buffed to a shine
and banners for the first
dance of the year were being hung...
Archie was doing what he does best.
You know, Mad Dog, I was thinking,
school starts tomorrow.
What if you came with me?
-Why would I do that?
-I don't know, to get your diploma.
Don't you want it?
-Hell, yeah.
-Okay, then this is your chance.
-Isn't your brother gonna be a freshman?
-I don't know.
After everything I've lived through,
I don't think going back to textbooks
and cafeteria politics is really my scene.
Yeah, it's not mine, either.
But getting that diploma
is what my dad wanted, so I'll do it.
Look, we could do it together.
-You could try out for the Bulldogs.
-Ooh. A little pigskin.
[both laugh]
-Really?
-Really.
[Betty] So, Mom missed
another check-in with you?
Yes. But like I said, don't panic.
This isn't the first time she's been late
with reports.
Well, Charles, what if that means
she's been found out?
Listen, until she contacts us, you should
just focus on being a high school student.
I'll reach out if anything changes.
Now that your parents' court date has
been set, you need to make a decision.
Are you testifying on behalf
of your mother or your father, or both?
Or neither.
I can be Switzerland.
At the very minimum, I recommend
you issue a statement of support.
-The press will want to know where you--
-No comment. That's my statement.
Now if you'll excuse me, Mr. Sowerberry,
I have some last-minute
school supply shopping I need to do.
Well, Jay-Jay,
which one for the first day of school?
Rebellious white after Labor Day
or my signature red?
I agree 100 percent.
[Betty] I really can't imagine
a better way
to spend our last night
of summer vacation.
Isn't it crazy?
In just nine months,
life as we know it will be over.
No more high school.
No more Blue and Gold.
No more heart-to-hearts at the lockers.
Oh, B. Don't be sad.
I'm sorry, guys.
I can't help but think,
life goes by so fast.
And none of us are very good
at stopping to savor it.
-But tonight we will be.
-Mm-hm.
I think that's our cue, Archiekins.
[chuckles]
♪ Don't be cautious, don't be kind ♪
♪ You committed, I'm your crime ♪
♪ Push my button anytime ♪
♪ You got your finger on the trigger
But your trigger finger's mine ♪
♪ By the way ♪
♪ You've been uninvited ♪
♪ 'Cause all you say ♪
♪ Are all the same things I did ♪
♪ Copycat trying to cop my manner ♪
♪ Watch your back
When you can't watch mine ♪
♪ Copycat trying to cop my glamour ♪
♪ Why so sad, bunny,
You can't have mine? ♪
Archie! I forgot to set the alarm.
Get up. We're gonna be late.
-You guys! Wake up!
-[Jughead] Huh?
We're gonna be late for the first day
of senior year. Hurry up.
You're late.
-And you are?
-I'm Principal Weatherbee's replacement.
Mr. Honey.
We apologize for the tardiness, Mr. Honey.
It won't happen again.
I don't know what kind of a ship
Waldo Weatherbee was running around here.
Things are gonna be different this year.
We'll have order, discipline...
consequences.
Now, get out of my sight.
Okay.
He sets up the bubble screen for you.
You catch, bam. You run like hell.
-You're one of the fastest we've got.
-Coach.
Any chance we can make room
for one more Bulldog?
Our lineup's pretty much set.
Are you looking to play?
Definitely. If you'll have me on the team.
-So, what's your name?
-Munroe. Munroe Moore.
-Come to practice. Show us what you got.
-For sure. I'll be there.
This is gonna be the best season ever.
I'm not too late, am I? To sign up for...
I don't know,
I was thinking maybe an arts reporter.
Kevin.
Betty...
I'm also here because...
I've been doing a lot of work on myself
ever since I was left behind by the Farm
and it's helped me to realize
that I don't--
I don't need the Farm
to make me feel whole,
but I do need my friends,
especially my former best friend.
I am... so sorry for the way I treated you
while I was under Edgar's spell.
Oh, you mean like when you dragged me
by my ankles to get a lobotomy?
Yeah, I--
I'm most ashamed of that.
I hope that I can show you
how much I've changed
and I hope...
that I prove to you that you can--
You can trust me again.
I-- I'm so, so sorry, Betty.
Just fill out an application, Kev.
And then we'll see.
[Doris] Jughead Jones,
please report to the principal's office.
-Jughead Jones, to the principal's office.
-[knock on door]
-Am I in trouble again?
-No. In fact, you have a visitor.
I'm Mr. Chipping.
It's nice to meet you, Jughead.
Nice to meet you, too.
Over the summer, you submitted
a short story to a writing contest.
-[sighs] Yeah, I didn't win.
-Yeah, I know. I was one of the judges.
I was very impressed with your voice.
And while I couldn't sway
my fellow judges,
I can offer you an opportunity
to come study writing with me.
I am a teacher at Stonewall Prep.
You want me to transfer to Stonewall Prep?
-It's a tremendous offer, Mr. Jones.
-I'm good.
But thank you for the visit
and for liking my story.
[Veronica] My good news of the day is,
Mrs. Burble said I'm a shoo-in
for Harvard.
I mean, obviously. Damn.
Guess I better start looking at community
colleges in-- Where is Harvard?
Veronica! You think your mother tried
to have your father killed?
-Back off.
-Whose side will you choose?
Oh, hell no.
[man] What do you think of
your father's claims that he's innocent?
I'm not having my senior year ruined
by a bunch of blood-sucking paparazzi.
[reporters clamoring]
Screw it.
[alarm ringing]
Archie.
So much for a quiet senior year.
[bell ringing]
[reporters clamoring]
Mr. Honey, thank you for meeting with us.
I, Cheryl Blossom,
as student body president,
and Antoinette Topaz,
as acting student body vice president,
would like to personally welcome you
to Riverdale High.
Thank you, ladies.
I was actually going to reach out to you
regarding that back-to-school dance
that you've organized.
Let's cancel.
For why?
At the last student dance,
multiple students were murdered.
Yes, but that's exactly
why we need this dance.
To heal.
Mr. Honey, if I may speak
from personal experience,
the back-to-school dance,
after my brother Jason's death,
provided much-needed catharsis.
Well, I disagree.
Now, I will only repeat myself once.
There will be no back-to-school dance.
[Archie] Huddle up, guys.
All right, Munroe,
let's see if we can catch them napping.
-On one. Ready?
-[all] Break.
Watch your man!
Attaboy, Reggie! Don't give him
an ounce of daylight, all right?
Come on, you hear me?
Blue 34.
Down, set. Hut!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Marty] Come on!
-Whoo!
-[laughs]
Hey! Get over here!
Now!
Get over here. What are you doing?
That guy just made you look
like a damn fool.
He's fast.
[Marty] It's unacceptable.
That was an embarrassing display.
Go out there. Come on, man!
Show me something!
[camera flash clicks]
What the hell?
-Oh, you have gotta be kidding me!
-I was...
Vixens!
This pervert was taking pictures of us
while we changed.
Collecting photos for your sad
pubescent spank bank, are you?
No. No.
A reporter from Rumordale.com reached out
and he told me he would pay 500 bucks
for a photo of Veronica.
-How am I supposed to say no to that?
-You just say it, you worm.
-Nice job out there, Mad Dog.
-Thanks. It's Munroe actually.
Oh, my bad. I thought it was Mad Dog.
Or is that just what they called you
in jail?
It was juvie. And your boy Archie
was right there with me.
-Is there a problem, guys?
-No, bro. We're cool.
Let's settle a bet.
In prison showers, is it true
what they say about dropping the soap?
Hey, he's not worth it, dude. Trust me.
-What the hell is wrong with you?
-What do you think, Andrews?
I've been captain of the Bulldogs
since sophomore year.
I don't need some ex-con who showed up
last minute stealing my thunder.
I saw your dad giving you a hard time,
but man up, you're supposed to be captain.
-Hey.
-[FP] Hey.
Jug. You know Mr. Chipping.
He was telling me
about an offer that he made you.
Yeah. My answer still hasn't changed.
I'm sorry, but I can't go to your school.
If this is about money,
I got a few bucks socked away.
No, it's not just about money.
Boy, look me in the eye and tell me
you don't wanna go to a school
that recognizes your talent.
Jug, how about this?
How about you come take a tour,
see the place for yourself
and then make the decision?
-I-- No. I just don't wanna waste--
-You're taking the damn tour.
Have a seat.
[Betty] Charles, I'm back.
They ran out of fortune cookies,
if you can believe that.
Charles?
Wait, what?
Is this what you do when I'm not around,
Betty? You read classified information?
When were you gonna tell me
that you had Kevin under surveillance?
I wasn't. From the get-go, I suspected
Kevin hadn't fully cut ties with the Farm.
I started monitoring his phone activity
and it turns out he's been texting
with Fangs Fogarty.
I mean, I was hoping
that Kevin was done... with the Farm.
It seemed like he was done.
This might be a blessing in disguise.
We could use their relationship
to our advantage.
In his text,
Kevin keeps pushing to meet in person,
but Fangs has been holding him off,
saying he can't risk it
unless he has something useful
to offer in return.
So, what if we accidentally let slip--
Some fake intel about our investigation
in front of Kevin.
Exactly. Something that'll lure Fangs
out of hiding.
The first step is to develop Kevin
as an asset.
You think you can do that?
One hundred percent.
Cheryl?
You scared me.
What were you doing in there?
I was... praying.
Since when are you religious?
I was looking for some divine guidance
on how to handle this...
discord with Mr. Honey.
And the spirits didn't fail to deliver
a hellaciously simple idea.
Instead of throwing
a back-to-school dance,
we are hosting a back-to-school party...
right here at Thistlehouse.
["Archie's Party" playing]
♪ Archie's gonna be there ♪
♪ Jughead's gonna be there ♪
♪ Reggie's gonna be there too ♪
-♪ Archie's parties are out of sight ♪
-♪ Out of sight ♪
-♪ He's gonna have one on Friday night ♪
-♪ Friday night ♪
♪ Pick you up about half past eight ♪
Your name may be Honey,
but I will always be the queen bee.
You have no power over me.
♪ Reggie's gonna be there too ♪
♪ Betty's gonna to be there ♪
♪ You and me will be there too ♪
-Hey, are you Forsythe?
-Yeah.
Bret Weston Wallis. Mr. Chipping
asked me to roll out the red carpet.
-You can just call me Jughead.
-I prefer Forsythe.
-Who's your friend?
-Betty Cooper.
Cute. Very Sweet Valley High.
Let me give you some stats.
Our faculty holds 132 masters degrees
and 28 doctoral degrees,
which sounds impressive, but the truth is
most of our teachers
are hopelessly out of touch.
Except for Mr. Chipping, he's cool.
And I'm not just saying that
because he's coming.
Mr. Chipping, how's it hanging?
Bret, don't let me interrupt you,
but I wanted to invite Jughead
to sit in on a salon with us.
If I'm not mistaken,
we're focusing on Moby-Dick tomorrow.
Great. That's one of my favorites.
-See you tomorrow, Mr. Jones.
-Definitely.
Betty, you can come, too. I bet
you've got a lot to say about Moby-Dick.
No. No, I don't.
And I think I've gotten my fill
of this place already, so...
It is a lot to digest.
Speaking of which, the cafeteria.
We've got vegan, keto vegan,
raw keto vegan...
I don't like drama, Miss Lodge.
Neither do I, Mr. Honey.
And yet there's this article Rumordale.com
published about you this morning
promising drama.
-I'm assuming you've read that.
-No.
I've been avoiding the tabloids
these past few months.
An unnamed inside source
that worked at your night club
is claiming that you, in fact,
are responsible for the crimes
that your father allegedly committed.
Fascinating.
Your point, Mr. Honey?
I was just wondering if you shouldn't
take a sabbatical from Riverdale High.
Until you can get all these
personal matters of yours... sorted.
[laughing]
Oh, man.
I have missed hanging out with you, Betty.
I was thinking back to freshman year.
You talked about crushing on Archie
and I would talk about
whatever weird Grind'em hookup I just had.
-Or not had.
-That I remember.
Kev, I think the reason
I was cold earlier...
I mean, as you know, my mom
and Polly are still at the Farm.
And my half-brother is investigating them.
-Yeah. Charles?
-Yeah.
-Right? Yeah.
-Anyways, today, finally...
there was a break in the case.
Really? What?
The FBI found a witness
who's willing to testify against the Farm.
Charles says it may finally
break open the case.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
That is...
Cheers.
Kevin.
[laughs] Fangs. Hey.
Can I at least hug you?
I miss you so much.
I've missed you, too.
But first, you said
you had some information for me?
Yeah, there's a...
There's a witness.
The FBI found someone who is ready
to come forward against Edgar.
Who's the witness?
I-- I don't-- I don't know.
I didn't get a name. But...
Information's not the only reason
why you wanted to meet me, right?
Kevin, Edgar and the rest of the Farm
don't think you can be trusted.
Of course, I mean, if you found out
who the witness was,
I mean, that might change things.
Get the name...
and then we can be together.
Yeah. I'll try.
Good.
You know how to reach me.
-Betty...
-You are so messed up, Kevin.
Reggie, Mr. Honey is riding my ass
about this article on Rumordale.com.
About me, about La Bonne Nuit.
An inside source
with intimate knowledge of my business
claims that I'm the criminal kingpin,
not my father.
Was it you, Reggie?
Are you the quote-unquote "inside source"?
Is that why you're hiding
behind those shades?
I didn't say a word to the press.
Oh, my God. Reggie, your eye.
But maybe you should ask your old man.
[Archie] So, did Reggie
admit to leaking the story?
No.
He didn't do it.
Archie...
Reggie had a black eye.
And it wasn't the first time, either.
-Oh, from practice you mean?
-No.
No, I think...
No, I know.
Reggie's dad hits him.
Kevin, you lied to me.
You told me
that you wanted to be my friend,
and then you go out into the woods
for some secret tryst
with your cult boyfriend.
I'm-- I'm sorry for-- For everything.
I-- I truly do miss being your friend.
You betrayed Betty
after she gave you a chance.
Yeah, I-- I wasn't thinking clearly.
I just wanted to see Fangs.
No, you wanted to trade information
so you could get back
-in the good graces of the Farm.
-No.
-You're still one of them.
-I'm not. I swear, I'm not a part
of anything. And you, you, Betty,
you ignored me all summer, okay?
And I-- I understand.
But I was alone.
At least Fangs texted me back.
He's all I have.
Can we have a word?
He's useless. We gotta cut him loose.
No, Charles, I-- I believe Kevin, okay?
I saw them in the woods.
I think he'll help us.
No. We're not gonna get anywhere with him.
He's traumatized.
-He's lonely.
-Listen, I'm sorry, Betty.
We'll find another way to get Alice back.
[whistle blows]
-[girls cheering]
-[Marty] Let's go, Reggie!
Blue 18.
Down, set, hut!
Get it, get it, get it!
-[Marty] Come on!
-[whistle blows]
All right, guys, hit the shower.
Practice is over.
[Marty] Hey! Get over here!
-What the hell are you doing?
-Dad, Dad, it just slipped.
It slipped?
It won't happen again, I promise.
-If it does, so help me. I will come--
-[Archie] What?
You're gonna hit him again?
Give him another black eye?
-What have you been saying?
-Nothing, Dad.
Andrews, this is none of your business.
Reggie works his ass off on this field
while you stand here and yell.
We all have to listen to it.
So, get the hell out of here.
-Go, or I'll throw you out myself.
-[Reggie] Back off, Andrews!
Reggie, your dad has no right
to treat you like this.
[Munroe] Hey! Hey! Knock it off, you two.
Hey, knock it off! Knock it off!
You're dead to me, Andrews! Dead!
Go. Go!
[bell rings]
[Bret] Hey, Forsythe.
Guys, this is that kid from Riverdale.
Forsythe, this is Donna, Jonathan, Joan.
Good afternoon, seekers of knowledge.
Why are we not sitting?
Now then, Moby-Dick...
-Hmm?
-It's well-done, obviously,
but it highlights a problem
that I have with the syllabus.
Do we really need
to hear this narrative again?
Right. Because the only authors
we're allowed to like now
are those who've lived
an unblemished life.
I'm fine with that.
Guys, guys, guys, let's get back on topic.
Now, what do you think
that the whale symbolizes?
Nothing.
Care to elaborate on that, Mr. Jones?
Well, it's pretty well-established
that Melville hated allegory.
I mean, he's quoted as saying
that his biggest fear was Moby-Dick
-would be seen as a fable.
-[Chipping] Any rebuttals?
-[buzzer sounds]
-[door opens]
[door thuds]
Breaking out the blond wig, I see.
Yes. That's the only way I can get around
without being harassed by the paparazzi.
But then you'd know all about that,
wouldn't you?
Oh, are you receiving some blowback
from lying through your teeth
to get me arrested? How unfortunate.
Why'd you leak the story?
Was it a desperate ploy
to get me to come see you?
Mija, I'm not paying for your crimes.
I merely told the truth.
I told the world what you are.
A Lodge... through and through.
Deal with it.
[replaces receiver]
-[door opens]
-[buzzer sounds]
♪ Just know, if you cross her
Then you cross me ♪
♪ Cross me, cross me
If you, if you, if you ♪
♪ If you cross her
Then you cross me ♪
♪ And nobody's coming close, yeah ♪
♪ And I think that you should know that
If you cross her ♪
[tapping on glass]
My esteemed guests,
may I have your attention, please?
Students of Riverdale,
we have a new enemy in our midst.
This killjoy is our new principal,
Mr. Honey.
[students murmuring and booing]
However, never fear.
I, as your student body president,
will make sure
that he's beheaded by homecoming...
or my name isn't Cheryl Marjorie Blossom.
[all cheering]
♪ Better do that shit without a flirt
Gotta respect... ♪
-[Jughead] Your drinks, ladies.
-Thank you.
[Veronica speaks in French]
So... what's this I hear
about you transferring?
Jug is being recruited by Stonewall Prep.
How was the salon today, by the way?
Shocked to say, I actually enjoyed it.
And the kids have actually read Moby-Dick.
Jughead, there is no school
more nihilistic
and/or privileged than Stonewall.
Besides, why would you wanna leave
your lovely girlfriend here?
Jug, we would make anything work. Okay?
But I would miss you.
Trust me when I say
you would be miserable.
I'm just trying
to keep an open mind, is all.
Excuse me. What are you doing down here?
-What's up?
-This hallway is off-limits.
The locked door at the top of the stairs
should have been a hint.
Yeah, the line to the bathroom
was too long.
-I was looking for another one.
-Then get thee to the barn
with the other animals.
[crowd chattering and music playing]
-Kev. Hey.
-Hey.
I'm sorry that we interrogated you.
It's okay. I get it.
You're trying to save your mom.
Yeah.
What I'm about to tell you...
puts everything on the line.
But I believe in you.
What are you talking about?
My mom isn't just at the Farm.
She's undercover at the Farm.
She's been sending us messages
all summer, but she stopped
and I'm worried
that she may be in trouble.
Oh, my God, Betty.
And I know that you can turn around
and tell Fangs everything,
but I'm choosing to believe
that our friendship runs deeper
than Edgar's brainwashing.
It-- It-- It does.
Kev, I need you to ask Fangs
to meet with you again
so he can tell you where Edgar is hiding.
-He won't.
-He will if you have information
to give him.
Like the name of the FBI witness
who doesn't actually exist, by the way,
but we can give him a fake name.
-Like who?
-Like Penelope Blossom.
Kev, will you do this? Will you help me?
Will you help my mom?
Of course, Betty.
[crowd chattering and music playing]
Yo.
Who invited you, new guy?
Dude, Reggie, lay off.
Cheryl, you know this guy?
No. But I certainly don't object
to him being here.
Which is more than I can say for you.
So, what you're saying is,
Mad Dog here crashed.
-[tires screech]
-[sirens wailing]
Wonderful. And now the po-po has arrived.
[FP] Party's over. Everybody go home.
Go home! Move!
Jughead, boy, you better not be drinking
whatever's in that cup.
Sheriff Jones.
Someone get this man a beer.
You wanna see the inside
of the drunk tank tonight, Mantle?
I'll take him home, Mr. Jones.
What are the charges, Sheriff Jones,
if one might ask?
Someone called the station
about the noise.
Impossible.
All of Thistlehouse's neighbors
are either deaf or dead.
-Who exactly made this absurd complaint?
-Someone named... Honey.
Party's over, Cheryl.
Reg, I think I already know,
but how'd you get the black eye?
What do you want me to say, huh?
That my dad hits me?
That he beats the crap out of me
over the stupidest things?
That he's been doing it
for as long as I can remember?
I'm sorry, Reg. I really am.
I was always so jealous
of the relationship you had with your dad.
No matter what you wanted to do,
he always stuck by you.
I have no idea what that feels like.
And when your dad died...
all I kept thinking was,
what if it had been my old man instead?
So, what can we do? Or what can I do?
You've already done enough, man.
You called him out.
Now it's on me.
I gotta take a stand.
So, what are you thinking?
[door rattling]
[Archie] Bro, are you sure about this?
Sometimes I think he loves this car
more than he does me.
I mean, you could just--
You could talk to him.
I've tried.
He doesn't listen.
It's time he starts to listen.
Holy hell, Reg.
That'll bring this to a head.
It's okay, Archie.
I outweigh him by 50 pounds.
Okay, everyone, I trust you all completed
your summer reading.
Who wants to read the first section
out loud for us?
Anyone?
Alrighty then.
I'll start and you follow along.
"Understanding Literature.
Chapter 6, English Drama.
One of the great works
of the Elizabethan age, Romeo and Juliet,
is a tragic romance...
emblematic...
-of both Shakespeare's early period...
-I can't take this.
Come with me right now.
...and of Western drama...
in the 16th and 17th centuries.
Basic..."
Okay. What's going on?
You should go to Stonewall Prep, Jug.
I hate saying that,
but it's the chance of a lifetime,
and you should take it, okay?
So, you should go before I change my mind.
-What about--?
-Don't worry about us. We'll make it work.
We've been through way worse.
Just go pack up your stuff.
I'll handle everything here, okay?
Go. Run.
How'd your old man react to his car?
Uh...
It... It did what it was supposed to do.
It got us talking.
And I said some things he needed to hear.
And I don't think he'll be coming around
to practices anymore.
Bros?
Bros for life.
-Veronica...
-[reporters clamoring]
[pounding on door]
[muffled reporters clamoring]
[pounding on door continues]
-Okay.
-[reporters clamoring]
Fine. You win.
You wanna know where I stand? All right.
I will give my first, last
and only press conference
on the subject of my parents tonight
at La Bonne Nuit speakeasy.
After a special performance.
["All That Jazz" playing]
♪ Come on, babe
Why don't we paint the town ♪
♪ And all that jazz
I'm gonna rouge my knees ♪
♪ And roll my stockings down ♪
♪ And all that jazz ♪
♪ Start the car
I know a whoopie spot ♪
♪ Where the gin is cold
But the piano's hot ♪
♪ It's just a noisy hall
Where there's a nightly brawl ♪
♪ And all ♪
♪ That jazz ♪
I'm no stranger to scandal.
That's what it means to be a Lodge.
I love my parents.
And because I love them, I trusted them.
And all those nefarious things
Rumordale.com accused me of doing,
yes, I did them.
I did them under duress
because my father threatened me.
And like the good, dutiful daughter,
I did what I was told by Hiram Lodge.
♪ Find a flask
We're playing fast and loose ♪
♪ And all that jazz
♪ Right up here
Is where I store the juice ♪
♪ And all that jazz
Come on, babe ♪
♪ We're gonna brush the sky ♪
♪ I bet you lucky Lindy
Never flew so high ♪
♪ 'Cause in the stratosphere
How could he lend an ear ♪
♪ To all that ♪
♪ Jazz ♪
You wanna know who I'm standing with
in the upcoming trials?
Neither of them.
From this day forward,
I stand only with and for myself.
♪ No, I'm no one's wife ♪
♪ But, oh, I love my life ♪
♪ And all ♪
♪ That ♪
♪ Jazz ♪
♪ That jazz ♪
-Is that your Harvard application?
-It is.
But I'm thinking of making a change
before sending it in.
The Lodge name is tainted,
like Madoff or Corleone.
But my mother's maiden name, Gomez,
I think I could work with that.
So, I would be dating Veronica Gomez now?
-Mm-hm.
-Yeah? What's she like?
I don't know.
We're gonna find out.
Why, what's the matter, Miss Bell?
Just be careful, Cheryl.
[bees buzzing]
Golly, what a mess.
Hope you're not allergic, Mr. Honey.
Toodles.
What's happening? Have you heard from Mom?
No. Maybe I was wrong.
Maybe we should roll the dice with Kevin.
Um, I already have.
I gave him the name of our fake witness,
Penelope Blossom.
Betty... you didn't say anything
about Alice, did you?
You revealed the name
of an active undercover FBI agent
to a screwed-up kid? Why?
Because I trust Kevin, okay?
I wanted to be honest with him.
-He will find out where Edgar is--
-Betty, it worked.
-Kev, you're back. Hey.
-Yeah.
I connected with Fangs,
told him about Penelope Blossom
and he led me to where the Farm
is staying. It's an abandoned motel
beyond the Maple Barrens.
-Okay, did you see my mom? Is she okay?
-I didn't. I'm sorry. But I did see Edgar.
And Betty, he's armed.
There were guns,
and he's building something and--
Edgar's digging in.
He's getting ready for war.
Well, we have to go.
We have to get in there and save our mom.
Well, well, well...
[sighs]
-Do I look like a jerk?
-No, you look like a gentleman.
Stonewall's not too far
and I'll be back every weekend.
Hey. I'm glad you accepted
Chipping's offer.
-You're sort of a legacy there, you know?
-What do you mean?
Well, your grandpa, Forsythe I,
actually went to Stonewall Prep
for a couple of months
till he dropped out.
What happened?
Why didn't you tell me this sooner?
Well, it's ancient history.
But he quit at everything, including me.
Went out for a pack of smokes
and never came back.
Anyway, I didn't mention it
because I wanted this to be your decision
without my old man's shadow
hanging over you.
It's a chance for you
to do something good... for yourself.
And I'm proud of you, son.
It's gonna be a good year,
a really good year.
[dogs barking]
-Jughead!
-[all] Jughead!
-[FP] Jug!
-Jug!
-Jughead!
Jughead, where are you, man?
[all] Jughead!
[all yelling]
Jug! Jughead!