There's this old folk tale I
think would make for a good story.
It's called
"The Devil's Holiday."
And in it the devil
visits a small town
in order to collect lost souls
and sow the seeds
of destruction and despair.
Yeah, here it is.
Now, there are many different
versions of this folk tale,
but in the one I'm imagining,
the name of the town is
Rivervale,
and the devil that visits it
can take any number of guises.
No, no, you keep that
and pay me next time, Jim.
Thank you, Pop.
God bless you.
You have the biggest heart
I know, Grandpa.
Well, I don't know about that.
Grandpa. Oh, my God. Grandpa!
Reggie, what are you doing?
Can't sleep.
Are you nervous
about the casino opening?
Must be, yeah.
Don't worry.
This is gonna be the biggest thing to
happen to Rivervale since maple syrup.
I love you.
I love you, Veronica.
I love you, too, Reggie.
Hello.
We got him, Betty.
Go on. Got who?
TBK. The Trash Bag Killer.
Where... where... where is he?
Being transported to Rivervale
as we're speaking.
I need to get you two
in the same room.
Hold on. What? Why? Why me?
I need a confession out of him.
And he says you're the
only one he'll speak to.
You, and you alone.
Are you up for this?
Yeah. Yes, I'm in.
Our call with the Gaming Control
Board got moved till 2:00.
So you'll have to take lead
at the staff meeting.
No problem, Ronnie,
but we need to hear this.
Rivervale's new casino,
aptly named Babylonium,
is nothing short
of an abomination.
If this house of sin
is allowed to open as planned,
our fair town will be
damned and doomed.
You think she's going
to be a problem?
Oh, spare me the spin, Veronica.
Casinos breed evildoing.
First come the gamblers, then the
harlots, and then the whore mongers.
Alice, we're running this casino
like a corporation, which it is.
It's completely legitimate.
None of what we do here
is legit.
This place was built
for one reason alone,
to separate the players
and their money.
Every table, wheel,
and slot machine
has been calibrated
to maximize profits.
Truly, we're following every rule
and regulation to the letter.
Tipped roulette wheels, phony
dice, magnetized slot machines.
We put limits on drinks.
Ply them with booze
all night long.
And, of course,
Gaming Control Board agents
will be checking our receipts
every month.
When delivering the chips to the counting
room, scoop one third off the top,
that's our weekly skim money.
What we use
to pay the politicians,
banks and union leaders
to look the other way.
Here's an idea. Why don't you
come to our soft opening tonight?
Check out the place,
see what we're really about.
I think you'll find we're not quite the
house of the devil you're imagining.
Hmm.
Good evening, Ms. Tate.
It's a pleasure to
finally meet you.
I'm sorry, but who are you?
I go by many names.
Today it's Mr. Cypher.
But since I'm such an old family
friend, you can call me Lou.
I'm here for
your grandfather's soul.
His... soul?
So what, that would make you...
Prince of Darkness. Yes.
My grandfather would never
sell his soul to you.
True. Terrence Tate wouldn't.
However, his father, your
greatgrandfather, was less principled.
He sold his eternal soul to ensure
the success of your family diner.
Okay, but what does that have
to do with my grandfather?
When Terrence learned
what his father had done,
he couldn't bear the thought of
dear old Dad spending eternity
in the fiery pits of hell, so...
So he offered his soul
to save his father's.
Yes. Which leads us... to you.
You want my soul
in exchange for Pop's?
Not at all. Just the diner.
And then your sweet grandfather will
be free of his obligation to me.
The diner.
That's it?
That's it.
Think it over, Ms. Tate,
and let me know.
But don't take too long.
Your grandfather's heart is
liable to give out at any minute.
Hey, you.
Hi.
How's Pop?
He's stable, at least.
How are you? Are you okay?
Unsettled.
This stranger showed up at the
hospital with a claim on Pop's soul.
Does this mean he's...
So it would appear.
But he's willing to release Pop's
soul in exchange for the diner.
What does the devil want
with the Chock'lit Shoppe?
I have no idea.
Mind if I ask him?
Maybe some other questions.
By all means.
Now, remember, this isn't
our official opening,
but we still
need to be on point.
Any questions?
Good. It's go time, then.
Let's go place them bets.
Right this way.
Hello. Hi, welcome. This way.
Alice, welcome to Wonderland.
You look divine.
Cute. Let's get you a drink and
over to the blackjack table.
Oh, I'm not here
to drink or gamble, Veronica.
I'm here to sniff out evil.
In that case, how about we
seat you close to the stage
and get you
a cranberry spritzer?
You'll want a prime seat
for the floorshow.
I'm sorry. I don't mean to
intrude, but are you Kevin Keller?
In the flesh.
Ah, I thought it was you.
I caught a performance of yours
in New York
a few years back.
You were terrific.
You should be on Broadway.
Or Vegas.
Yeah. Fat chance.
I don't even have an agent.
That's absurd.
What if I say that I could
make that happen for you?
Fame, money, being a star.
Why don't I give you a taste? Then
we can discuss the finer details.
♪ It's not unusual
To be loved by anyone ♪
To have fun with anyone ♪
♪ But when I see you
Hanging about with anyone ♪
♪ It's not unusual
To see me cry ♪
♪ I want to die...
Okay, I just confirmed
your schedule.
You are going to be finishing your
engagement here at the Babylonium.
Then you're off to New York
for your sixweek run
of the Boy from Oz
opposite Hugh Jackman.
I'm sorry, Fangs.
What are you doing?
Very funny, Kev. I'm Finn, your
manager and your boyfriend.
Typically, I tell you
your schedule
and then we go have amazing sex in the
Babylonium Champagne Suite. Remember?
Oh. Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course I do. Right.
♪ Love will never do
♪ What you want it to
♪ Why can't this crazy love
Be mine? ♪
♪ Oh, oh
Hey, superstar.
How's it all feeling?
If this is what what my life would
look like from now on, I am all in.
Read it over if you like,
but essentially it's
Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, we're...
we're... We're all good.
I'll catch you later.
Cool.
♪ Whoa, whoa!
You win again. Well played.
Blackjack, table 13. First base.
He's won the last 20 hands.
Oh, hell, no.
Where's Reggie?
Hi, friend.
You might not be aware, but tonight
Babylonium is by invitation only.
Hi, Ms. Lodge.
Yes, I know. I'm an investor.
No.
I know all of our investors.
Louis Cypher. I made my investment
with your partner, Reggie.
Where is he, I wonder.
It doesn't matter.
You're dealing with me now, and
I'm shutting this table down.
That's no problem.
There's plenty more for me
to do in town.
I'll get my due here
at midnight on Saturday.
And what's your due?
Oh, not much.
A soul.
Ah, I see.
Louis Cypher. Lucifer. Cute.
Now, I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave. Quietly.
Always.
But I'll be back on Saturday.
Reggie, there was a shark
bleeding us dry tonight.
Who was he?
You tell me.
He claimed to be an investor.
As well as the devil...
looking to claim a soul.
Ronnie, that guy is the devil.
What? When we were looking for investors,
I got an incoming call from him.
He said he could provide us
with the rest of
the money we needed
in exchange for... a soul.
My soul.
And he's here to collect it
this Saturday night at midnight.
You've got to help me.
If anyone can outwit
the devil, Ronnie, it's you.
Well, you're right about that.
Okay. I'm gonna
think of something.
But in the meantime, do you
have his number by any chance?
I'm happy to see you again, Betty.
It's being too long.
But don't you want
to see my real face?
This is your real face.
But if you mean your human face,
that will come soon enough.
My boss wants a
confession from you. Hmm.
He wants you to admit to all of
the atrocious things in here.
That's what your boss wants.
But what do you want, Betty?
I don't give a damn
about a confession.
I know you did these things.
I just want to know...
does evil,
absolute evil... exist?
And are you it?
Ask your real question, Betty,
and then I will confess my sins.
I don't have to play
these mind games with you.
No one cares that you're here.
So you can sit in your filth
for all I care.
And I'll just
come back tomorrow.
Yes, Betty,
absolute evil exists.
And yes, there's a part of you
that is absolutely 100% evil.
You're caked in it. It's
what draws us to each other.
You've got to get this guy
out of Rivervale, Glen.
I'm not getting
any information out of him.
Uh, he's toying with me, and I
just won't be his plaything again.
Betty, what in God's name
are you talking about?
Who's toying with you?
TBK, Glen.
Or is there another serial killer in
custody that you want me to interview?
Betty, the Trash Bag Killer
is not in custody.
Hey, are you okay? Do...
Do I need to come up to
Rivervale and check on you?
I'll call you back, Glen.
Grandpa, you're awake.
Did you see him?
Yes.
But I'm making
a new deal with him.
Your soul
in exchange for the diner.
You... can't sell
the diner, Tabitha.
Grandpa, it's bricks
and plaster.
It's so much more
than that, honey.
Over the years, it's become a
refuge for the lost and persecuted.
That's why the devil wants it.
Pops is the soul of Rivervale,
which he wants to destroy,
and that's why
you cannot let him have it.
Mr. Cypher.
Hi, Veronica Lodge calling
with a counter proposal.
There's an old friend of mine who
I've invited to Babylonium tonight,
and I suspect
you'll find his soul
much more deserving
of damnation than Reggie's.
Color me intrigued, Ms. Lodge.
I'll see you tonight.
Are you surprised that I
called you here, Mr. Cypher?
Nothing surprises me
these days, Mr. Jones.
I've been looking for something
to inspire my writing,
to get my
creative juices flowing.
And I figured an interview with
the devil would do just that,
but I'm... I'm... I'm not
gonna sell my soul for it.
Okay?
I see.
Well, huh,
I'll grant you this exclusive
if you agree
to one of these terms.
We do the interview,
you publish it,
you receive all the fame
and notoriety we all yearn for.
But afterwards,
you'll never be able
to write again.
Or?
Or I'll give you this raw,
mindblowing tellall,
but everything I say
remains between us.
You can't publish a word.
In fact, you may never
publish anything again,
but you'll find
your creative juices
flowing like Niagara Falls.
I agree to your terms.
I only ask that you allow me
to choose my option
after we conclude the interview.
That seems fair.
Please start at the beginning.
He's here, Ronnie.
Nick St. Clair. All grown up,
but still a sleazeball.
We'll just let him get nice
and liquored up first.
And there you have it,
the story of my life
and all the universe's
mysteries revealed.
So, what'll it be?
Publish and never write again,
or file it away forever
and happily scribble away in
obscurity for the rest of your days?
Option one. I need
to publish this interview.
And receive all the fame and
glory that will come from it.
Fabulous.
Darling Nicky, you made it.
Of course.
You know I could never turn down
an invitation from you, Ronnie.
Even though
I am happily married.
Remember, Senator, what happens in
Babylonium... stays in Babylonium.
So, catch me up, Nicky.
It's been years.
I'm assuming you're still
a very naughty boy.
I plead the Fifth.
Come on, Nicky.
Don't get shy on me.
What can I say?
Details are a turnon for me.
The more specific you are, the
more hot and bothered I get.
Well, in that case,
I haven't paid taxes in years.
And I drink and drive
two to three times a week.
Any hitandruns?
Three.
All covered up.
What about harassment?
Oh, I've lost count of how many
NDAs my lawyers have arranged
for my staff and interns.
Affairs?
You mean, besides the one
I'm about to start with you?
Cutting to the chase, would you say that
you deserve the hot burning fires of hell?
As long as
you're holding the pitchfork.
Would you sell your soul
to the devil for me?
Whatever it takes.
Is that good enough?
Is what good enough?
Yes.
In this instance,
that qualifies
as a verbal binding agreement.
Goodbye, Senator.
I'm glad our deal
worked out, Mr. Cypher.
Indeed. I will not touch
a hair on Reginald's head.
But you and I are still on
for tomorrow, of course.
What do you mean?
Our business is done.
Reginald's soul
was never on the table,
it was your soul
that I was promised.
Mine?
How is that possible?
Hmm. You might want to ask
your partner that question.
Publish...
or perish?
New question.
Who are you?
Because you're sure as hell
not TBK.
I'm the devil, Betty.
Okay. So if evil exists,
and you're the devil... Mmm.
Hell is a real place then?
Oh, yes.
Well, tell me, is my dad there?
He is.
So, if I asked you
to prove to me
that what you're saying
is true...
could I speak to my father?
Betty?
Betty, what's happening? Dad.
Betty, where am I?
You have to get me out of here.
Betty, it hurts.
It hurts so bad!
If it's really you, Dad,
I need you to focus, okay?
Where would you always take me
after my Little League games?
You... you...
you mean Chaz E. Cheddar's
on Route 18?
Reggie!
Oh, crap.
I want the truth, Reginald.
Now. Okay.
I offered my soul to Mr. Cypher
and he didn't want it.
He said it was
a miserable, paltry thing.
It is.
So, then you
offered mine instead?
He asked for it.
He said yours would be
the real prize.
Oh, my God. So you sold me
down the River Styx?
How did this happen?
I didn't even sign a contract.
You know those, uh,
weekly invoices you sign?
I slipped a contract
in one of those stacks
and gave you Mr. Cypher's pen
to use.
Ronnie, I'm sorry. Forgive me.
I only agreed to it because I
knew you'd figure a way out.
Get out
of my sight.
You've done enough.
Out! Now!
Mr. Cypher.
Ms. Lodge.
So, listen.
I might be open
to a renegotiation.
A soul in exchange for yours.
But not another of those
Nick St. Clair types.
What about that
holy roller that's
trying to shut you down?
Alice?
You get me her signature
using my pen,
and I'll release your soul.
Otherwise, you and I
have a date at midnight.
Hello?
Is this
Forsythe Pendleton Jones III?
Yeah.
Hi. David Fenwick
with The Associated Press.
We read your
interview with the devil.
It's incredible.
We'd love to pick it up.
The entire world needs
to read what you wrote.
So, after the AP picked up
my story,
my phone wouldn't stop ringing.
Hang on, let me call you back.
I even got a call from...
Samm?
Kid, your article's amazing.
I never should have dropped you
as a client. I apologize.
But will you please
let me be your agent again?
Before you answer, hear me out.
I've been in touch
with the Pulitzer people.
Now, because I'm me,
I gotta ask.
What are you writing next?
Oh. Mr. Hubbard.
Hi.
What can I get you?
I don't have any money.
But I thought,
in exchange for a bowl of soup,
I could wash some dishes.
You do not need
to wash any dishes.
Just have a seat.
I will bring you a bowl of soup.
Bless you. Thank you
That was very kind of you.
Oh, well,
that's just what we do
here at Pop's.
Yes.
Even when facing
the direst of circumstances,
you show compassion
and kindness.
Such a virtue should be
rewarded, don't you think?
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
I'm a great admirer of your
grandfather and all his good deeds.
Forgive me.
I don't quite understand.
You might say
I'm one of the good guys.
My name is Rafael.
And my boss
likes what you and your family
are doing here.
And He wants to make sure you're
prepared for a battle that's coming.
One in which your diner
will play an important role.
He wanted you to have this.
Alice.
Thank you for coming in
on such short notice.
I know how busy you are.
I am.
But you said
you had an offer for me.
I do.
I want to donate
a percentage of Babylonium's weekly
earnings to the town of Rivervale.
To be allocated
at your discretion.
My discretion?
I want you to be my pointperson
on this, discreetly.
And I have a direct
deposit here ready to sign,
if this sounds
at all amenable to you.
As a matter of fact, it does.
You know, I knew you weren't
all bad, Veronica.
Alice, stop!
What? What's wrong?
What's wrong...
is that...
you're a pain in the ass.
But you don't deserve
to burn in hell.
I've changed my mind.
Leave.
If you thought that I was
a thorn in your side before,
get ready
for what's coming next.
It was...
a dark and stormy night.
Who knew the devil
would be so literal?
Back for more, Betty?
If you're the devil... Mmm.
And you've come to me, it's
because you want something from me.
So what is it?
Your loyalty.
There is a war brewing, Betty.
The one between good and evil.
Pledge your allegiance to me
and I'll release your father
from endless suffering.
Why do you need me?
Because it is foretold.
"I saw a woman sit upon
a scarletcolored beast,"
full of blasphemy, and that
woman was Babylon the Great,
"mother of all destruction
and abomination."
You are that woman, Betty.
Really?
I'm the whore of Babylon
from the Book of Revelation?
I don't think so.
And as for my
father's suffering,
I don't care about it.
What if I told you
Polly's in hell, too?
Uh...
I wouldn't believe you
because Polly doesn't deserve
to be there.
Doesn't she though?
Betty.
Betty, make it stop!
It burns, Betty!
It burns so, so much!
My skin! My skin...
Betty, it's coming off.
Everything hurts so much.
Stop it.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop torturing her!
Stop it!
And let me guess.
The face of evil is mine, right?
Glen?
Yes, it's Glen.
And when I called him
using your voice,
saying I needed him...
well, he couldn't come
any faster.
He must've
really cared about you.
Hey, Ronnie,
sorry to bother you.
I know you've got
a lot on your plate...
but the weekly skim guys
are here to collect their cut.
Um...
do you want me to handle it?
Actually, no.
Let them in.
I want to thank them personally.
For what?
For giving me...
a hope in hell.
Oh, and tell Kevin
to take the night off.
I'll be delivering
our eleven o'clock number.
My swansong.
Ending right at
the stroke of midnight.
You called me, Mr. Jones.
I came.
What seems to be the problem?
I don't want it.
I don't want the Pulitzer.
I... I don't want the fame. I don't
want the fortune. Please, take it back.
Please, take it back. I need
to be able to write again.
Of course.
I understand.
And I could do that.
But it would cost you.
My soul, right?
Take it.
I'm nothing if I'm not a writer.
♪ I'm gonna marry the night ♪
♪ I won't give up on my life
♪ I'm a warrior queen
♪ Live passionately tonight
♪ I'm gonna marry the night ♪
♪ I'm not gonna cry anymore
♪ Leave nothing on these
Streets to explore ♪
♪ Mmmmarry, mmmmarry
♪ Mmmmarry the night
♪ Oh, mmmarry, mmmmarry
I was so pleased to hear that
you'd accepted my offer, Tabitha.
And how nice to see you
on the mend, Terrence.
I wanted him here.
Well...
we all need to sign anyway.
But before we do,
I want to make sure that
this contract is ironclad.
And that after we sign,
my grandfather's soul
is free and clear
forever.
Cross my heart and hope to die.
Terrence,
will you get us started?
What will you do with Pop's now?
The bulldozers will
be here in the morning.
If this is Pop's last night,
then I want a milkshake
to remember it by.
Delightful idea.
Make enough for three.
♪ Come and run
♪ Turn the car round and run
To eternal darkness.
How does it taste?
Now that you mention it,
the flavor is a little...
off.
Oh. Well, yeah.
That would be
the secret ingredient I added.
What secret ingredient?
Tears that the Virgin Mary shed
at the Crucifixion.
Where did you get that?
My guardian angel.
And since we have consumed
the tears as well,
we are now protected
by their holy properties.
But our deal...
Oh, yes. About that...
From this moment on,
Pop's is consecrated.
Protected from you
and any other force of evil.
Now, why don't you get
the hell out of our town?
♪ I'm gonna marry the night ♪
♪ I'm gonna burn a hole
In the road ♪
♪ I'm gonna marry the night ♪
♪ Leave nothing on these
Streets to explore ♪
♪ Mmmmarry, mmmmarry
♪ Mmmmarry the night
♪ Oh, mmmarry, mmmmarry
Hello?
Hello, Agent Cooper?
This is Foster
from Agent Scot's office.
Have you heard
from Glen recently?
His wife reported him missing,
and no one can get a hold of him.
No, I haven't heard from him.
But I'll give you a call
if I do.
Hope he's okay.
Reggiekins.
Veronica?
You're still here?
But it's after midnight.
What happened? Well...
after I finished my number,
to wild applause, might I add,
I went to the cash room
to meet with Mr. Cypher. And...
we brokered a better deal.
That's amazing.
What kind of deal?
Let's just say
the devil will be joining
our little skim at the casino.
Only instead of collecting cash,
I'll be his expediter,
supplying him with one lost
soul from our floor each week
for the rest of my natural life.
You're a genius, Ronnie.
You did it.
You beat the devil.
Did you expect anything less?
You should get that, Reggie.
I think it's for you.
Who is it?
You know who it is.
His weekly skim begins tonight.
Or actually...
Sunday morning.
But You shouldn't have
doublecrossed me, Reggie.
And you should have been more
careful about what pen you use
when signing
for liquor deliveries.
As you did earlier today.
No.
Go on, Reggie.
Be a man about it.
Or he'll drag you out
kicking and screaming
like a little bitch.
For people like Veronica Lodge,
this is their lot in life.
Living bet to bet,
skim to skim, scam to scam.
Always chasing
that next best deal.
And so what if it costs
a few hundred
or a thousand souls
along the way?
Because if Rivervale
really is going to be
the final battleground
between good and evil...
is anybody's soul safe?