Everything has shifted.
There was an explosion
at Archie's house
and I lost my ability to hear.
Some things
I could do as before.
Read, eat hamburgers,
kiss Tabitha.
But there are other things
that I may never be able
to do again.
The fact of the matter is,
my world shattered.
The question now was
how do I rebuild?
All right, guys, listen up.
Frank and I have reinforced
the infrastructure of the house,
so it's safe to work.
But please,
keep your helmets on.
Let's have
a good productive shift, okay?
So much for your safety meeting.
Keep going.
I'm already going.
Well, go harder.
I'm pressing as hard as I can.
My God.
You don't feel it at all?
No. Nothing.
Not one bit.
Okay, well, it's confirmed.
You're still invulnerable.
Well, Betty, I don't know what
happened to us in that explosion,
but all of my childhood dreams
about becoming a superhero
are somehow... coming true.
Mmm-hmm.
Have you talked to Jughead
about any of this?
He was third closest
to the explosion.
Fourth closest.
Don't forget Bingo.
Who's driving my mother crazy.
No. Yeah, I just left Jughead
a couple of messages.
He hasn't answered me.
I'll check up on him.
A little later.
Okay.
Grand Mistress Rose.
I just had
the strangest encounter
with Master Cheryl upstairs.
She seemed...
less like herself than usual.
That's because I transferred
Abigail's soul from your body
into my granddaughter's,
via an arcane ritual.
But where did
Mistress Cheryl's soul go?
Oh, once untethered,
it dissipated into the ether.
Into nothingness.
There is no more Cheryl Blossom.
There is only...
Abigail.
Roseanne, do all the ladies
dress like harlots these days?
Indeed, we live in fallen times.
That is why
I brought you back, Abigail.
To lift us up.
To restore the Blossom family
to our former glory.
And how, pray tell,
am I meant to do that?
Riverdale once belonged
to the Blossoms.
I think it's time
we took it back, don't you?
Of course.
I should like to get
a lay of the land first.
Well, the town is governed,
inaptly I might add,
by a Council of Four.
We'll start there.
Archie just found out
that I lost my ability to hear.
Then he asked me
a curious question.
He wants to know if anything
weird happened to me
after the explosion.
"You mean beside
losing my hearing?", I say.
"Why do you ask?"
"Just curious", he says.
I'm not sure I believe him.
Reggie, I need
to tell you something.
Okay.
Three days ago,
my father's body was found
in a shallow grave
in the New Jersey Pine Barrens.
What? How'd he die?
His hands were zip-tied,
and he'd been shot four times
in the back of the head.
His body was then burned.
Could it be a fake-out?
No, Reggie.
He's dead.
I'm sure he's dead.
Wait. You lied to me.
You told me
you called off the hit.
I... I didn't want to
be judged.
In what universe.
Am I not supposed to judge you?
Well...
Brace yourself
because there's more.
We are hosting
a memorial service
for my father
right here at the casino.
My grandmother is coming.
Some of my father's associates,
my mom.
Does your mom and grandma
know the truth?
No.
I may tell my mom, but...
Not Abuelita.
She'd never forgive me.
Copy. So, should I...
say I'm sorry for your loss
or congratulations?
I don't know, Reggie.
I just don't know.
The long and short of it is
I'm staying to take care
of Baby Anthony.
And I was... I was thinking,
if I'm gonna be in town
for a while longer...
Maybe I'll take you up on
your offer to be your deputy.
I'd love that.
You sure that's something
that you want to do?
Yeah, I do.
Well, in that case,
I would be honored.
Yeah.
All right. Thanks, Dad.
Hey, cheers.
To my new deputy.
Poor Jug.
Yeah.
Well, at least he's got Tabitha.
- Hello.
- Agent Cooper.
I wanted to let you know ASAP.
Glen's car was found
outside Pop's diner.
And where's Glen?
No one's heard from him
since he was supposed to
be leaving Riverdale.
Okay. Thanks
for letting me know, Agent Lin.
I'll be in soon.
That's weird.
Glen's MIA.
Abuelita.
How are you holding up?
What a tragedy upon your papa.
I know it's awful.
Your father and his business.
I knew it would end up this way.
In bloodshed, one dark night.
Veronica, I would like to
introduce you to Heraldo,
my godson.
He takes good care of me.
Nice to meet you, Heraldo.
Pleased to meet you.
Abuelita, I'd like you to meet
my business partner and...
boyfriend, Reginald Mantle.
It's a pleasure
and an honor, ma'am.
It's very good to meet you.
Can I give this to you?
It's a guest list
for the funeral.
Is there anything else
you want me to do?
Si, your abuelitahas requested
that you deliver the eulogy.
No. I...
I wouldn't know what to say.
Who will be better
than you, Nieta?
Your papiloved you so much.
Please, do this for me.
I told Tabitha
what the ENT doctor said,
that I had to wait
at least six months
before getting an implant.
Then she asked me
about learning ASL.
I told her I wouldn't need ASL
once I got the implants.
Then she asked me
if I wrote today.
I told her that I always
listen to music when I write,
and when I tried to write
without it today, I just...
I couldn't hear the clack
of my keyboard's keys.
Everything about writing
suddenly became alien to me.
I told her
there's nothing she could do,
that somehow we just have to
get through this.
Everything all right,
Agent Cooper?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just have, like,
a brutal headache
directly behind my eyes.
Sounds like a migraine.
I've never had migraines before.
Also this came for you today.
Thank you.
Now we'd like
to open up the floor
to all members of the community.
Oh.
Why, that must be some relation
to Archibald Andrews.
Can I get an extension
on the permit
for the dumpsters
in front of house?
Permission granted, Archie.
Uh, who's next?
I have an announcement.
My father, Hiram Lodge...
is dead.
He died under mysterious,
violent circumstances.
I'm fine.
But please rejoice.
Riverdale's Big Bad will be
tormenting us no longer.
Any other announcements?
Hello.
Uh, my name is Percival Pickens.
I recently moved to Riverdale,
and I just wanted you all
to know...
how excited I am
to be joining your community.
Pickens.
In the earliest of early days,
did we Blossoms not have
a fellowship
with the Pickens family?
Yes. And it did not end well.
Welcome, Percival.
By any chance, are you related
to General Augustus Pickens?
Oh.
Goodness. Yes, but, uh,
don't worry.
I'm... I'm not here
to cause trouble.
I simply believe that
with a little bit of luck
and some hard work,
Riverdale could become
one of the greatest
and most-prosperous communities
in America.
Now, I have lots of ideas
I'd be happy to share
with the council.
Starting with the removal...
Sorry. So sorry I'm late.
I was busy trying to stop
a gang war from erupting
on the streets,
but what else is new, right?
Why, that is the spitting image
of my beloved Thomasina.
That's Miss Topaz. Toni Topaz.
Topaz?
That was my paramour's surname.
You must tell me everything
about this Toni Topaz.
Tabitha was
at a town hall meeting.
I didn't go.
I couldn't face people's pity.
So I stayed home
and tried to write,
but again, nothing came to me.
And then... suddenly I knew
exactly what I wanted to do.
Hey, how you doin'? Really.
I'm okay.
I mean, after all,
it wasn't too long ago
you and I were in your car
plotting to take Daddy out
in a similarly gruesome manner.
We were angry.
It's not like we actually would
have gone through with it.
I guess we'll never know.
All right, Britannia.
Wherefore does this Toni
spent her days?
Miss Topaz
works at Riverdale High.
She's our guidance counselor
and she teaches
the history of social justice.
Fittingly, yes. Thomasina was
a teacher as well.
And this Riverdale High,
- that's a school?
- Exactly.
You will take me there tomorrow.
And you, little lamb,
will be my Trojan horse.
But tell me, why were Tony
and Cheryl torn asunder?
To be honest, I don't know.
And they were together
as two women out in the open?
Yes.
What a brave new world this is.
This is insane, Betty.
Now TBK is in Riverdale
and he murdered Glen.
No, I don't think
he killed Glen.
I think he's keeping him
alive somewhere.
Dismembering him piece by piece.
What makes you think that?
Because that's his
preferred method of killing.
Slowly.
So it takes days, if not weeks,
so they suffer.
But you don't think
he's going to come after you?
I don't know. But if he does,
even without a mask,
I should be able to see
his aura if it's a threat,
like I did with Glen
and the orderly right?
I'm more worried about
everyone else in Riverdale.
I'll have my mom
spread the word on RIVW.
And I'll have my team
out on the streets
canvassing the neighborhoods.
I couldn't hear
what Tabitha was saying,
but I knew she was pissed at me,
as well as she should have been.
I took my motorcycle
out for a ride.
Sure enough, I wiped out.
But how could I tell Tabitha
that for those brief moments
when I was cruising,
all was right in the world?
We're getting the word out
through local media and social,
but more than 50%
of TBK's victims
are from
historically disenfranchised
vulnerable communities.
He preys on the unhoused
because no one misses them.
So we're gonna focus on
those neighborhoods
with these flyers.
To anyone
you come in contact with,
tell them if they see TBK,
do not approach him.
Call us
and we'll take it from there.
I'll hit Sketch Alley,
Agent Lin's
got your assignments.
Okay. You're gonna
come with me...
- Veronica Lodge?
- Yes. How can I help you?
This is a release that states
you're okay with us
filming you and using
your likeness on television.
Oh, right. Sure.
All right.
Oh. Okay.
Okay. If you can just
take a step towards me,
find your light.
Perfect.
All right, let's bring her in.
Baby.
Oh. It's okay.
I'm here. Let it out.
Mommy is here.
Hi, Mom.
Hey, boss.
Found this while I was
clearing out the basement.
Holy crap.
You know what this is, right?
No.
Palladium.
I got to keep a couple pieces
after I did all that mining
for Cheryl Blossom.
It's worth
a hefty chunk of change.
Hey, as a reward for finding it,
I'll split it with you.
No, I couldn't. It's yours.
I'll tell you what.
If you find the other piece,
you can keep that one.
Break time, people.
Alice has coffee brewing
next door.
Freshly brewed coffee.
Bingo, down.
Get down, get down.
Oh.
Archie, how the hell
are you drinking that?
Isn't that too hot?
Yeah, yeah. Yes, it's hot.
It's really hot.
So talk to me, Cheryl.
You said that you need
some help with Britta.
I would like to
formally adopt her.
Well, great.
Um, but, Cheryl...
there's a bunch of hoops
we're going to have to
jump through.
Well, Antoinette,
why don't you come by
Thornhill this eventide
and walk me through those steps?
Slowly and methodically.
Actually, I'm going to
be bartending
at the Whyte Wyrm tonight.
In that case,
perchance I will pay you
a visit instead.
By the way, thank you so much
for inviting me, Hermione.
Oh, not at all, Kevin.
I know you're a super fan.
And this is going to be
an extra special episode
of reality television.
All about how Veronica and I
are dealing
with the emotional fallout
of Hiram's tragic death.
Wait, is that what
we're doing here?
Don't worry, honey.
I'll guide you through it.
Do you remember where you were
when you first heard the news
of Hiram's tragic death?
Mom, I'm not gonna
reduce my feelings
to sound bites for your show.
How did you feel
when Daddy died?
- Did you cry?
- Nope.
Because the man I loved
died many years ago.
I cried when I mourned
the death of my marriage.
But I am through shedding tears
for that man.
All right. Kevin, Abuelita,
Heraldo, camera crew,
please clear the room.
I need to talk to my mom.
Alone.
Veronica,
what is it, sweetheart?
It was me.
I put it bounty on Daddy's head.
I'm the reason he died.
You know what...
I sort of suspected.
When I heard
how your father was found,
I thought,
"What if Veronica was the one
who finally did it?"
- His favorite partner.
- What do you mean?
I don't like admitting this,
but...
Sometimes I was
a little jealous of you two.
I mean, the special
relationship that you two had?
I always knew that he loved you
more than he loved me.
I just... I was afraid that
the same was true of you.
You loved him
more than you loved me.
No.
After all he did,
Daddy infuriated me.
Exactly. And he had all of
your attention because of it.
Do you know that the happiest
I ever was
was when it was just us
living in this apartment?
Just us Lodge women
together against the world.
And then your father came home,
and it was Hiram
and his best girl.
That was you, Veronica.
Not me. Never me.
I'm so sorry, Mom.
I was so caught up in
drama with Daddy
that I wasn't a good daughter
to you.
But I want to be one now.
Honey...
I can't tell you how happy
it makes me
to hear you say that.
There's nothing I want more.
Tabitha found him.
Like me, Daniel experienced
late-life deafness.
He learned a sign and read lips
in his 20s.
Now he helps people
on journeys similar to his own.
He wanted to help me.
I nodded "yes,"
and we made an appointment
for me to go to his office.
Hello, pretty Betty.
Working late, I see.
How did you get in here?
Glen's access card.
Glen. Is he still...
Yes. He's proven
extremely hardy.
Why are you here?
I came after reading
you were nearly killed
in an explosion.
You and Archie
are getting close.
Don't make me go after him next.
Try it. He'll kick your ass.
And so will I.
Get out of here.
Oh.
Betty, I've missed this.
It's a tad tart.
Might I have
some more butter in it?
I don't have any butter, Cheryl.
And since when do you
drink beer, anyways?
Quite right.
And in truth,
I didn't come to drink.
Lately, I've been thinking
about the past.
My past, this town's past...
- Your past.
- My past? What about it?
How much do you know
about your ancestor, Thomasina?
She was a great, great aunt
of mine.
And, from what I can remember,
a spinster schoolmarm...
That is falsehood.
Thomasina lived
her life passionately
and drank deeply
from the juices of the world.
Until she was murdered
by a warlock-pirate.
What are you talking about?
There's no such thing
as warlock-pirates.
Hey, Cheryl.
- Hey, babe.
- Hey.
Oh, I'm... sorry, Cheryl.
We told Kevin,
but we just haven't
got around to telling you yet.
Fangs and I are together now.
Together?
And how did that... transpire?
We've known each other
since we were kids.
And after having
a baby together...
A baby?
Yeah. Baby Anthony, our son.
Of course.
And quite the cherub he is.
I have to get back
to fair Britannia.
A mother's work is never done,
after all.
What was that about?
I have no idea.
But Cheryl doesn't even seem
like Cheryl to me.
I can't believe
TBK came to see you
at the FBI office.
But what's scaring me
most right now is
I couldn't see his aura.
How could he not be
a threat to me?
Unless he's in
my blind spot somehow?
I don't know.
I keep getting
these headaches, too.
It feels like someone's
taking a pickaxe to my brain.
Something has been
happening to me, too.
I fell through
the landing earlier.
And... I got hurt, Betty.
Like, my invulnerability
is fading.
But what's changed?
TBK might be my blind spot,
but what's
your weakness, Superman?
What's your kryptonite?
Oh, my God.
One of my guys
found this piece of palladium,
and I've been carrying it
on me ever since.
What if this is my kryptonite?
- You take it.
- Okay.
Keep it away from me.
Let's see what happens
if it's not near me.
Maybe I'll go back
to being indestructible
Either way,
you really need to be
super careful right now, Arch.
TBK is a jealous serial killer.
You don't need to be a hero
right now.
At least not until your...
powers come back.
So I went to Daniel's office.
I told him that
one of my biggest worries
was that I'd never write again,
and he said that I should sit
in his office alone
for five hours, and to just
start writing down my thoughts,
that it would help me get
comfortable with the silence.
I said I'd do my best,
and then he left me alone.
- Wow, Mom, you really went all out.
- Mmm-mmm.
Is this food I can
actually eat or are we filming?
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
How would you feel about
recreating a version
of our conversation
that we had last night
on camera today?
I mean, not the part about you
killing your father, of course.
But the emotional part,
you know, our core wound
about you...
taking me for granted.
But, Mom, I...
I mean, all of that
was real for me.
That's why I want it on camera.
It was just so raw.
What do you think?
- Of course.
- Oh.
- Let's do it.
- Really?
Yeah.
Wonderful.
Mistress Abigail,
are you all right?
No, Britannia.
Clearly I am not all right.
I cannot fathom
that my beloved Thomasina
is in love
with a descendant of...
Fenn Fogarty.
Her very murderer.
I'm positively bereft.
Miss Topaz is dating
Fangs Fogarty?
Well, I, for one, am relieved.
I reincarnated you to get back
what is ours.
Riverdale.
Not so you can consort
with some Serpent trash.
Did you just refer
to my beloved Thomasina
as "Serpent trash"?
I did.
You forget yourself, old woman.
But don't worry.
Abigail is here to remind you.
I will have Riverdale
back in my thrall.
I will have my revenge
on the offspring of my enemies.
But first...
I will have Thomasina back
by my side.
And death to anyone
who stands in my way.
Five hours later,
Daniel came back.
I hadn't written a word.
"It takes time," he said,
without any trace of judgment.
And then he gave me
a graphic novel to read.
One he'd written and drawn
about his experiences
navigating deafness.
He said it might help me.
I said I would read it.
Good evening, Miss Lodge.
Did I startle you?
Anatol, what the hell
do you want?
I paid you your blood money.
Yes, you did.
But I'm here on another job.
What, to kill me?
Right before
my father's funeral? Seriously?
You American women.
You think you're so tough,
but you don't have
the slightest idea
of what you're doing.
And in the end,
you just turn on each other
like rats and kill each other.
Wait, who hired you?
Was it...
I'll clean up the body at night
and dispose of it tomorrow.
Who sent the Russian, you think?
If I had to guess...
my sister Hermosa.
She's pretty pissed at me,
I think.
For ordering
the hit on your father?
Wait, you know about that?
Oh, my God, does Abuelitaknow?
No, she doesn't.
Look, I make it my business
to know about everything
that happens in this family.
And I make sure none of it
touches your abuelita.
How do you do what you do
and then...
sit down to dinner with
Abuelitalike nothing happened?
Are you just
a really good actor?
Yes, but...
it also helps that I don't see
the world in black and white.
It's all just shades of gray.
No person is just one thing.
When Tabitha
came home from Pop's,
I surprised her by showing her
the pages I'd written that day.
I explained that Daniel's
graphic novel had been the key.
I used to write
by hearing words, auditory.
But Daniel's graphic novel
showed me a workaround.
I could write
from a visual space,
seeing words and actions,
then describing them.
And then I kissed her
for not giving up on me.
For never giving up on me.
Dennis, what's going on?
Hey, guess what I found.
Holy crap.
You must have done some digging.
Where do you find this?
- Hello.
- Agent Cooper.
I'm calling the number
you listed on those flyers.
I think the Trash Bag Killer
is at the end of Sketch Alley.
I'm on my way.
He's down there,
at the end of the alley.
Keep everyone back.
Hey! Put your hands up!
On your knees.
Don't move.
Please don't shoot me.
Take off your mask.
I'm not TBK, I'm just a guy.
Who gave you that mask?
Some man who came by earlier.
He gave me 50 bucks
and told me to wear the mask
and to deliver a message
to a blonde woman
when she showed up.
What's the message?
"Check the trash cans," he said.
Glen.
Thank you all for being here.
I won't stand here and wax
sentimental about my father.
He did horrible,
unspeakable things
to my mother, to my sister,
to my lover at the time,
Archie Andrews,
to my friends, to this town.
And to me.
But I'm also making room for
the fact that, on occasion...
He did a few
not-so-horrible things, too
He was a proud state champion
wrestler for Riverdale High.
He donated money to
the research of rare diseases.
He covered the funeral expense
of Fred Andrews,
with whom he did not see
eye to eye,
without hesitation.
And he was a dutiful son
to my abuelita.
The truth is...
I loved him till the end.
Make no mistake,
I wish my father hadn't done
those awful things,
and I wish I could
sort my feelings more cleanly.
But I can't.
And maybe
there's something to be said
about a child's willingness
to forgive their fathers
for the terrible things
they might have done.
But for what Hiram Lodge
did to all of you...
I apologize.
And I also apologize
for the fact that...
that I will always...
always love... my Daddykins.
I wish I didn't,
but... I do.
Thank you.
Good. You're awake.
Hey. Hey, who are you?
I'm the bogeyman.
I'm Betty's blind spot.
I've heard every one of your
secret whispered conversations,
and I'm not sure why,
but I know
that piece of rock there
makes your flesh
weak and vulnerable.
So I'm going to get ready,
and then we're gonna have
a grand old time
chopping you up
into little chunks.
Archie?
Archie, where are you?
Get rid of her,
or I'll hack her up too.
Do it now.
Alice.
I'm just cleaning.
I'll come by later.
Well, you can,
but your dog can't.
He got into my closet again
and ruined
my favorite kitten heels.
It's fine. Just go, please.
I'm leaving him here.
We'll talk
about compensation later.
Well done.
But don't worry.
We'll be visiting Alice later.
Bingo...
Bingo, kill!
Good boy.
Bingo. Bingo. Come here, boy.
Hey, come here.
Come here. Yes.
Good boy. Good boy.
Good boy. Yes, good boy.
It was great seeing you, Mom.
Circumstances notwithstanding.
I love you, honey.
I'm so, so proud of you.
Okay. Thanksgiving at
the Barefoot Contessa's, huh?
Anderson and Andy will be there.
That sounds nice, Mom.
I can take your abuelita
to the airport if you want.
Thanks, Reggie.
Thanks for coming
to the funeral.
You were the only one
from the gang who did.
I'm sure everyone else was busy.
I really enjoyed your eulogy.
It resonated with me.
And I don't think
I really ever understood
what you had with your dad.
If I didn't understand it,
what gives me the right
to judge it in the first place?
What you did doesn't matter,
because I love you.
Thank you, Reggie.
Sorry to ruin the moment.
Damn, dude's super quiet.
I have something for you,
Miss Lodge.
Found it among
the Russian's personal effects.
What is it?
It's a recording...
that Hiram made
during his final moments.
Give it a listen.
I still can't wrap my brain
around the fact
that TBK was here
the whole time
right under our noses.
I mean, where did you even
hire Dennis,
if that's his name?
He saw my ad for crew
in Jug's newspaper.
He must have been trying
to keep tabs on you through me.
God knows how long
he's been spying on me for.
Long enough to know
that Glen was being a dick.
And to know that we were
manifesting our powers.
And weaknesses.
And side effects,
like my headaches.
Well, at least now we know
what he looks like
without a mask on.
Yeah.
Though, he could have
really hurt you.
Luckily, Bingo remembers
his commands
from his old dog-fighting days.
He saved my life.
Pushed TBK
right out that window,
and then TBK ran off.
Yeah, he does that.
What about Glen, Betty?
I found most of him.
Including his head.
So now I need to leave.
I need to get out of Riverdale.
I don't understand. Why?
Because I brought TBK here.
He went after Glen,
he went after you.
If I leave, he will follow me.
I know he will.
Betty, if you're a target...
Well, better to be
a moving target
than one standing still.
I'll lead TBK out of Riverdale,
and then I'll circle back.
Something will distract him.
Something always distracts him.
Are you...
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Just keep that palladium
away from me.
Hmm.
And come back in one piece.
Deal.
Mija,
I don't have much time left.
But I need you to know one thing
Whatever I may have said
about wishing I had a son,
all of that changed the moment
I first held you in my arms.
You became
my treasure instantly.
And I want you to know that,
despite our troubles,
you have always been
the apple of my eye.
Everything I did,
no matter how heartless
or inexplicable
or unjustifiable was...
for you.
I think perhaps I was testing
the limits of love a daughter
can have for her father,
and you, mija amada,
never faltered, never failed.
I never felt anything less than
love for you or from you.
I hope you believe that.
One last thing.
I'm leaving you my rum business,
the crown jewel of my empire.
I don't think I was ever happier
than when we were
in the middle of our rum war.
Do you remember?
Those were good times,
weren't they?
I always wanted to be
a good father to you, Veronica.
I love you so much.
We'll have no more of that,
I think.
So the story hasn't been about
things I can't do anymore.
It's about the things
I've learned to do differently.
And what new possibilities
lie before me.
Did I leave
the oven on at Pop's?
Tabitha.
Did you just say something?
I'm sure I turned the oven off.
But did I lock the door
behind me?
Tabby.
Are you wondering
if you left the door unlocked?