Oh. Hello there.
And welcome to Thornhill,
the Blossom family's
ancestral home.
A house
of secrets and mysteries,
and the most haunted place
in Rivervale.
Is it haunted by ghosts
or memories?
Or something else? A curse?
Perhaps all three.
Well, would you
look at the time?
It's 7:00 am.
And the women of Thornhill,
past and present,
are waking up
across the decades.
In the here and now,
Cheryl Blossom wakes up
from a dreamless sleep.
As 65 years ago,
Poppy Blossom stirs awake
in the same room,
in the same bed.
And while further back still,
Abigail Blossom opens her eyes
to meet the day.
Three blossom women,
one story
echoing across time,
burning as bright and eternal
as a comet's tail
in the night sky.
December's sale Live TV £60 and more!
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK
Today, we will
be discussing comets,
in particular, periodic comets.
Bailey's comet passes through
the inner workings
of our solar system
once every 65 years.
Tonight's a momentous night.
You lucky girls will be able
to marvel
at the comet's beauty
on the North hill
as it streaks through
the night sky
and over Rivervale.
- Mm-hmm?
- Mistress Cheryl,
will Nana Blossom be able
to join us
for the viewing tonight?
She's feeling quite weak today,
so I'm afraid not.
And I will not be with you
at the North hill either.
I will be by my Nana's bedside,
conducting certain rituals
to help her transition
into the afterlife.
- I have some good news, Nana.
- Oh.
Tonight's the night
we've been planning
for all these years.
Bailey's comet returns
to our skies.
Oh. You bring me such relief,
dear child.
Now I must ask you again
while you are
in your right mind.
Roseanne Blossom,
are you certain
you wish to continue
down this road?
Once done, it cannot be undone,
and there is risk.
There's always a risk
when spellcasting.
I have never been more certain.
Very well then.
Let's begin with the ritual.
To walk in their shoes,
you must first
know their stories,
their histories.
Who do you wish to begin with?
Both. For their stories,
as you know, are intertwined.
All right. Let's see.
Ah. Yes.
Poppy had just hosted
one of her delightful salons.
Thanks for letting me
stick around
- and bend your ear alone, Poppy.
- Of course, Tamtam.
And you did seem quiet
during our discussion
of Lady Chatterley's Lover.
Oh, it's so silly, Poppy.
I want to start working
at the diner,
but my husband is
dead set against it.
Home is where I belong,
he says.
But I know I would do
a better job of managing Pop's
than he does.
Hmm.
What's this?
Some herbs from my garden.
Sprinkle them in your hubby's
eggs Benedict
and he will come down
with a nasty stomach bug.
And then you can be the heroine
and step up and run Pop's
for the day.
Oh, Poppy,
I don't know
what we'd do without you.
I see here from your resume
that you have
five years teaching experience.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
When I came across
your hiring announcement
in the paper,
I was moved to apply.
My old school was
shut down, you see,
and turned into a hospital
after the war began.
A wretched affair, isn't it?
My own dear brother James
is fighting
on the western front.
Tell me, the pox is rampant
throughout our land,
have you been afflicted by it?
Yes, when I was but a babe.
I too survived
that hellish plague.
Are you married?
- No, ma'am.
- Good.
I have no need
for women with husbands.
You're hired.
Is it Thomasina or Miss Topaz?
Which do you prefer?
Thomasina.
Very good.
- Where did you say you were from again?
- Nearby.
Greendale.
Today, ladies,
we shall be discussing
proper table etiquette,
especially in regards
to shared plates
and clear soups.
Actually, Ms. Blossom,
I had a notion
about today's lesson.
Bailey's comet is set
to pass over Rivervale
in a few days' time,
and it offers an excellent
scientific opportunity
for the girls.
Firstly, Thomasina,
it is quite unladylike
to be traipsing
around the woods after dark.
But, more importantly,
the Thornhill Academy for Girls
is a finishing school.
But a comet,
like any celestial body,
is fundamental to the
understanding of our lives.
It's much like a poem, you see.
Everything, the stars, time,
and even you and I,
we're all part of
an intertwining cosmic fabric.
I see.
And I suppose next you'll be
wanting to teach my girls other similarly
impolite topics
from the world of men.
Indeed, I will.
Because men have all the power,
and the world
need not be that way.
That's quite enough
of that talk, Thomasina.
So long as you teach at my
school, you will follow my curriculum.
Class dismissed.
All right, ladies, if you could
please take your seats.
So, for this week's salon,
I was thinking
maybe we discuss
Bailey's Comet,
which I just read
will be passing over
our little town
later this year.
What do we think?
We should have a viewing party,
set up on the roof of Pop's.
That's a swell idea, Tammy.
Though I can't imagine
Jack would be
very interested in a comet.
Oh, by the way, Poppy,
guess who's working the diner's
register these days.
Curious timing, this comet.
Didn't the Soviets
just launch Sputnik?
Wait, is that the missile
I keep hearing about?
It's the Russian
space satellite, Velma,
for spying on us Americans.
You're absolutely right, Bitsy.
Can they really do that?
Oh, by the way, did you hear?
Wendy Weatherbee
was just arrested
for conspiracy.
- No.
- Yes.
Wendy is as red-blooded
American as the rest of us.
Well, apparently now
she's just red.
My question is,
are our children safe
at school?
Ladies, ladies,
no need to fret.
My opinion is,
if people discuss their
different ideas in the privacy
of their own homes,
well, what's the harm?
Poppy Seed Blossom,
do you really mean that?
I truly do.
I suppose I'm just not a fan
of witch hunts.
Of any kind.
Thank you for letting me
stay behind, Poppy.
I promise I won't take up
too much of your time.
Oh pooh, Bitsy,
time spent with you
is always
the highlight of my week.
But what's going on?
The truth is, I'm not happy
in my marriage, Poppy.
I've wondered.
Jack thinks the answer
is to have another child.
Even though my first pregnancy
was...
Well, you remember
how hard that was on me.
Have you considered divorce?
Divorce? Jack?
No, I couldn't, Poppy.
Jack's Catholic.
Well, maybe it's just about
not getting pregnant right now.
Have you ever
looked into birth control?
Oh, I couldn't
possibly ask Dr. Curdle
- for something like that.
- Not to worry.
I have just the thing.
Take this special ginger root
from my garden.
A few flakes
every day in the morning
will make sure you don't start
baking a bun in the oven.
Poppy...
I'm so grateful to you
for listening
and understanding.
What would I do without you?
Oh, my.
What the devil am I doing?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Poppy.
Oh, Bitsy, Bitsy,
everything's fine.
Nothing bad happened.
Everything will work out.
You'll see. Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Thomasina.
Yes.
I...
I wanted to apologize
for my outburst earlier.
I'm afraid I should be
the one to apologize.
After all, it is
your curriculum, not mine.
True. But...
after some quiet reflection,
I've realized you're right.
From now on, we're going
to teach these young women
hard truths,
tough knowledge.
Prepare them for a world
that might not exist yet,
- but someday will.
- Yes, Abigail.
What can I do to help?
Earth to Poppy.
Velma, I am so sorry.
You were telling me
about your husband.
Yes. It's just that...
lately, things have
been a bit...
- vanilla in the bedroom.
- Hmm.
And I want to spice things up
a bit with the mister.
But I don't know
how to, exactly.
Hmm. Well,
I have got some spice for you.
The Kama-sutra.
Oh, it's the bee's knees.
Oh, also.
What's this?
My own special aphrodisiac mix.
Sprinkle that
into his roast beef and...
he'll never want
to leave your bed.
Abigail,
why didn't you wake me?
Because you are so beautiful
when you sleep.
Thomasina,
how I wish we can live in this
little perfect world
of ours forever.
Who could that be?
Only trouble comes knocking
at this hour.
Abigail Blossom, open up.
I'm here on official business.
Constable Keller,
state your business, sir.
I'm looking
for a murderess.
The harlot's name
is Thomasina Topaz.
There's no one here
by that name. Now, please go.
For your own good.
We have a confirmed case
of the pox here.
There's a plague
upon this house.
Thomasina Topaz,
I would have the truth
from you.
Don't say a word.
I know what you did
with my wife.
I beg your pardon.
Don't you play coy
with me, Poppy.
Well, go on, tell her.
I might have given you
the wrong idea about us, Poppy.
I've never been happier
in my marriage.
And I would be very lucky
to have another child
with Jack.
So just butt out, okay?
You hear that?
Keep out of my marriage, woman.
And so help me,
if you get anywhere
near Bitsy again,
I will kill you.
Why did Constable Keller
call you a murderess?
When I came seeking employment,
you asked if I had a husband.
I said I did not,
which is true.
But once I did.
It was an arranged marriage.
He was a cruel man.
He didn't like my ideas
of educating womenkind.
He didn't like my rituals.
He just sought to control me
with the back of his hand
and his belt.
Men are such monsters.
One night...
I saw a look in his eyes...
and I knew it was
either his life or mine.
So I choose mine.
I chose to live.
Stay here.
Stay with me forever.
Mistress Cheryl,
may I come in?
Britannia?
What are you doing here?
And where are the other girls?
They left.
To see the comet
from the North hill.
And why, pray tell,
aren't you with him?
Please, Mistress Cheryl.
I notice things.
I know you and Nana Rose
have been planning something
in secret.
I just don't know what it is.
But I'd like to be here for it.
Oh.
Let the child stay.
Oh. Very well then,
you can stay.
But not a word out of you.
Pull up a chair.
I was just about to tell Nana
what happened to poor Poppy.
Well, hello, boys.
Excuse me. This is my home!
Who the hell
do you think you are,
telling our wives
we can't satisfy them?
I see.
So that's why none
of your wives came today.
You bullied them
into submission.
Pathetic, if you ask me.
Well, we're not asking you.
In fact, we want you
to leave Rivervale ASAP.
The Blossoms have
outstayed their welcome here.
And if I don't leave?
Don't push us on this, Poppy.
You know what I do
for a living.
Kirk Keller,
Thornhill is my home.
I'll never leave it.
Okay, suit yourself.
But don't say
we didn't warn you.
Who is it? Who's there?
My name's Fen Fogarty, ma'am.
I'm a friend of your brother's.
I come with news of him.
Mr. Fogarty,
come in and warm yourself
by the fire.
- Welcome.
- Yeah.
Miss Blossom,
it is my sad duty to inform you
that your dear brother James
was killed
during our last battle.
He gave me this letter
to give to you,
right before he passed.
"In the midst
of this brutal war,
it is my dying wish
that you,
my beloved sister, Abigail,
would take the hand
of my dearest friend,
Fen Fogarty...
in marriage."
"Dearest friend."
How intimately
did you and James
know one another?
War makes all men bedfellows.
Abigail, you cannot marry
this man, this stranger.
Thomasina,
you don't understand.
My brother was my twin,
my soul mate.
If this was his dying wish,
I must honor it.
There is a darkness in Fen.
I do not know what,
but I have a sixth sense
about these things.
And my intuition tells me
he means you harm.
Nonsense.
He was my brother's confidant.
Letters can be forged.
Tomorrow, when he goes hunting,
we will search his room
for proof
of his true intentions.
I'm certain that man
is not who he says he is.
I will not let
any harm come to you.
I swear it.
Hello, Tammy.
It's nice
to see you working here.
I'll have my usual, please.
A patty melt with a side of
coleslaw and a glass of buttermilk.
Do you maybe want that
to go, Poppy?
No. I'd like to eat it here.
Thank you very much.
Fine.
What's the meaning of this?
What are you doing here, Kirk?
We've received an anonymous tip
that you, Miss Blossom,
are a subversive.
A suspected
communist sympathizer.
That's an outrageous lie,
and you know it.
Is it?
What about
the closed-door meetings
you've been coercing
the unsuspecting wives
of Rivervale to attend?
What are you doing? Those are
my precious heirlooms.
You've left us no choice.
I'm sorry, Poppy.
We're taking you in
for questioning.
What, pray tell,
are we looking for?
Evidence of his malfeasance.
This isn't
my brother's hand.
This is someone practicing
My family seal.
This is the official
Blossom crest.
Thomasina, I think
you were right.
The betrothal letter
was forged.
Which means you don't have
to marry that imposter.
Objects of the occult.
I knew he was
trafficking in the dark arts.
Abigail, I'm afraid
it's worse than I feared.
Fen Fogarty
is not just a scoundrel,
he's a warlock.
What?
But how could you know that?
I have knowledge
about these things.
Heaven protect us.
These are
death portraits, Thomasina.
I think he's a murderer.
My lord.
I think he murdered
my brother James.
Women, I'm back with supper.
What the devil
are you two doing in here?
Be gone from my house
this instant.
You do not
give me orders, woman.
Once we are married,
I will become
the Lord of this manor.
- Will you now?
- Abigail, get back!
Stop!
Do it, you devil!
Obey me or I slit her throat
where she stands.
Fen, please.
I'll marry you, Fen.
I'll marry you.
Good.
Yes.
We'll do it tonight. Legally.
Properly.
We'll need a vicar then,
to perform the ceremony
and bear witness.
You'll have to fetch one
in town.
Oh, no, you'll go fetch him.
If I leave,
you two will collude
to kill me
and run off together.
I'll lock
this saucy sapphic wench
in the chapel
if you're not back
within an hour with the vicar!
I'll kill her.
All right.
All you have to do
is cooperate.
We know you're a communist.
Just admit it so I can
let you out of here.
I won't admit to a lie.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Is it true
you once visited Russia?
Yes.
To participate
in a chess tournament.
Are you loyal to this country?
This government? The flag?
Yes, yes and yes.
Are you against God, religion?
I'm against witch hunts
and group think.
And yet,
you organize gatherings,
unsegregated I might add,
where you read banned books.
Is it true
you use contraceptives?
What is it you really want
from me?
Admit you're a commie,
sign the confession,
or I will put you in jail
to rot.
Do what you want.
I'm not signing anything.
I'm surprised they let you in
to see the red devil.
You're not the devil, Poppy.
But you do need
to sign their confession.
It's just your name.
But what else do I have
other than my name?
My principles.
All the things those men
are terrified of.
If you want
to stay in here
and suffer for your principles,
then go ahead.
But I thought you
cared a little bit more...
about...
you know, about us.
But, Bitsy, don't you see?
I am doing this for us.
For you.
For womankind.
For all the free-thinking,
independent daughters
who will come after us.
Bitsy...
don't tell me you're pregnant.
We'll get through this somehow.
No. This baby is exactly
what Jack and I need.
I can't believe
I let you fill my head
with your silly, stupid ideas.
Jack was right about you.
You're just a sad, jealous,
sexually repressed spinster.
I know you don't mean that.
Well, you don't know
anything about me.
After Bitsy visited Poppy
in jail,
they didn't see each other
for the next nine months.
Why so long?
And what brought them
together again?
Poppy, I need your help.
It's about Bitsy.
Did something happen to her?
She's gone into labor.
She's convinced herself
that something is wrong and says
you're the only person that can help.
If you do this, you will not
return to this cell.
I swear it.
Okay, yeah.
Interestingly,
in a confluence
that can only be called cosmic,
the night Bitsy's baby
was to be born
and the night Abigail Blossom
was to be married,
were both nights
when Bailey's comet
passed over Rivervale.
Same as tonight.
So Abigail did marry Fen?
She didn't have
much of a choice, did she?
But fret not, dear Britta,
for Abigail's story
is far from over.
An idea for how to catch Fen
at his most vulnerable
was already taking shape
in her mind.
Say hello to your
beautiful baby girl, Bitsy.
She's perfect.
I just wish I were bringing her
into a better world.
Actually,
this little one was born
under Bailey's comet,
Bitsy.
It's a sign
of great things to come.
Nothing will hold her back.
Before I forget.
It was in my pocket book.
Something for when the time
is right.
You'll know when to use it.
Come now, dear one, join me.
Hurry.
It's time to fulfill
your wifely duties.
Did you ever hear, Fen,
of that terrible case
in Fall River, Massachusetts,
about the young woman,
Lizzie Borden,
and what she did
to her tormentors?
Ugh. What's this now?
She killed them with an axe.
Thomasina, my love.
Thomasina.
Thomasina, please help.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Wake up. Please wake up.
She was the perfect
addition to my collection.
You monster.
You're going to burn in hell
for what you've done.
How right you are, Abigail.
The comet.
What perfect timing.
Calling upon my dark knowledge,
fueled by the midnight light,
I curse you, Abigail Blossom.
May your life be as everlasting
and solitary as the comet's.
May...
you remain unloved
and alone
for all your miserable days.
Thomasina...
Oh.
Well?
Both mother and daughter
are fine.
Okay, let's get you
out of here.
What are those for?
You told me if I helped,
I'd be free.
No. We said you wouldn't have
to go back to your cell,
and you don't. You are
however under house arrest.
- What?
- At Thornhill.
- For how long?
- Indefinitely.
Now come on, Poppy,
don't make a fuss.
And so,
Poppy was shut away.
Doomed to spend
the rest of her days
haunting the halls
of Thornhill.
Okay,
so Poppy was arrested,
but what happened to Abigail?
She too lived out her days
in this house,
forever alone.
I'm afraid to ask
what happened to Bitsy.
Funnily enough,
her husband died
under mysterious circumstances
about a year after
their second child was born.
Some say he was poisoned,
though the coroner
didn't find any poison
during his autopsy.
Then again,
some plant-based toxins
don't leave a trace.
Oh. Is that her?
Is she finally here?
Well, well, well.
Look at what the black cat
dragged in.
If it isn't Sabrina Spellman.
Cheryl Blossom.
Feels like it's been centuries,
doesn't it?
Thank you for coming.
My Nana and I are
forever in your debt.
Oh, don't be ridic.
You know I'd do anything
to help a fellow witch.
Nana, Britta,
there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
Hey, ladies. What's happenin'?
Sabrina is a dear old friend,
and she's come here to help us
with our little ceremony.
How do you know each other?
Oh, we have
a lot of mutual friends,
share a lot
of the same interests.
And our covens are
in the same softball league.
Sabrina is
the first person who told me
about performing
a transference.
Yes, indeed.
My cousin Ambrose
taught me how to do it.
Essentially, a transference
is a very tricky spell
that can only be performed
on a night of great
cosmic significance,
like tonight, with
Bailey's Comet approaching.
Speaking of, it's nearly time.
Britannia, we witches must
spell cast alone. Do you mind?
Yeah.
Are you ready?
Okay. Let's begin.
Our flesh and blood
are but a cage
that withers
as we wear our age.
But there is a way to switch
to willing souls
with one we wished.
Let asunder body and soul,
to exchange to spirits,
new and old.
Our flesh and blood
are but a cage
that withers
as we wear our age.
But there is a way to switch
to them souls
with one we wished.
Let asunder body and soul,
to exchange to spirits,
new and old.
It... it worked,
the transference.
How do you feel, Abigail?
Free.
At long last.
Fen's curse
is broken.
Let it go, Abigail.
Let it go,
and finally be at peace.
Reunite with
your dearest, Thomasina.
Happy-sad endings
are the best.
Did Nana Rose pass,
Mistress Cheryl?
- Um...
- I'll take this one.
Nana Rose's body did die,
but not before we transferred
her soul into...
Mistress Blossom's body?
Yes. And vice versa.
It was a classic body swap,
Freaky Friday style.
But you should know this,
there was no Cheryl.
Not really.
Or there was,
but she was also Poppy.
And before that,
she was Abigail Blossom.
I don't understand.
When the warlock,
Fen Fogarty, died,
he cursed Abigail
with immortality.
To hide that fact,
she created the persona
of Poppy Blossom,
then Cheryl Blossom,
so that no one would
suspect the truth.
But Abigail was
forever haunted by the loss
of her first true love,
Thomasina.
She wanted more than anything
to be reunited with her.
The only way
to do that
was to move her soul
into a body
no longer meant to be
in this world.
And tonight,
that's what we did.
The soul that once inhabited
this body,
Abigail's soul,
has moved on
to a peaceful eternity
in the sweet hereafter.
And now, I, Roseanne Blossom,
can once again
enjoy my precious youth.
And Cheryl, Poppy, Abigail...
- she's really dead?
- No.
No.
There is no death for witches.
Only transformation.
I mean, I died and came back.
Abigail was a witch?
She was.
As was Thomasina.
Which we can
definitely talk you through.
But how about we do it over
a milk shake at Pop's?
I feel like the twenty-something
witch, Sabrina Spellman,
visiting Rivervale from the
neighboring township of Greendale,
summed it up perfectly.
Happy-sad endings
are the best.
Enough said?