Well, it's not every day you
learn that you're at ground zero
of an extinction-level event.
In less than 18 hours,
Bailey's Comet was going to
obliterate Riverdale,
one last twist of the knife,
courtesy of Percival Pickens.
And there was nothing
we could do to stop it
or apparently escape.
What did you find out?
I've had the Serpents out
all night,
on every road and every highway.
And all along the town's limits,
there's some sort of
invisible barrier
completely surrounding
Riverdale,
and it's keeping us
from leaving it.
Yeah, it gets crazier, though.
When we were out there on the
highway, a car drove into town.
Like there was no barrier.
So it's basically, like,
we're trapped in a roach motel.
You can get in,
but you can't get out.
Jughead, what about
opening up a portal?
I mean, I'll take any dimension
over this one at the moment.
I tried. I can only open
portals within town limits.
No other dimension.
Tabitha, what about you?
Have you tried to time travel?
Every time line I've gone to,
past and future,
there's always a comet that's about
to destroy Riverdale imminently.
- How the hell is this happening?
- It's Percival.
But was he
really powerful enough
to get Bailey's Comet
to change course?
- I mean, it's a comet.
- He is
and powerful enough
to weave the binding spell
that's keeping us all
trapped here.
Shouldn't, like, the government try to shoot
the comet out of the sky or something?
Why isn't this
all over the Internet?
It's a facet of the spell.
Percival doesn't want
anyone to help us,
so as far as the world is
concerned, Bailey's Comet is passing
over Riverdale tonight,
as it has every 65 years.
Great. So that's it then.
We're all going to die.
I'm so happy
I moved here sophomore year.
Well, not everyone's
going to die.
Archie's invulnerable.
What about Big Anthony?
- He's immortal.
- Archie and I have already talked about that.
They might be the only ones
that survive this,
especially if they're in the
bunker when the comet hits.
Uh, let's not go there yet.
We have enough time
to make sure we all survive.
Percival was a sorcerer
and pulling down the comet and making
this barrier are all spells he cast.
They are spells, Archie,
incredibly elaborate ones rooted in
dark, arcane magics honed over centuries.
- Far beyond my knowledge.
- And mine.
But there might be someone
we can consult
with ancient knowledge
that rivals Percival's.
Okay, great. In the meantime,
Frank and I
and anyone else who wants to help,
we're going to go into the mines.
If we dig deep enough, maybe we'll find
a tunnel that passes under the barrier.
Whatever happens,
I'm just so grateful
that we can face it together
as a family.
But I am so sorry
that I can't protect you girls
from what's coming.
It's a comet, Mom.
And I am so sorry
that I wasn't a better mother.
- I was awful.
- No.
Mom, we're okay.
We know that you would do
anything for us.
And we love you.
So, so, so much.
I love you, too.
How does it feel to be back?
Unsettling, but I'm still hoping
for an eleventh-hour save.
Speaking of,
I have something for you.
I saved it from Percival's shop
before we burned it down.
I really can't seem to get
rid of this thing, can I?
Thank you, Reggie.
You know, all things considered,
there are definitely more
banal ways to go out
than being obliterated
by a giant magic comet.
And I've actually completed almost
everything on my bucket list.
Alexandra Cabot?
Tabitha Tate?
What are you doing here?
Well, I am here to make
all your dreams come true.
Mmm.
Every time.
Okay, so...
You've heard
of Tommy Comet's, right?
The diner chain
that went belly up.
Yeah, well,
I have just closed a deal
to buy all of their facilities,
which means
that we can take them over and open up
Pop's diners across the country ASAP.
Instant franchising.
Investors are lined up and
we're good on the financials.
So all I need from you,
Tabitha, is an immediate yes.
Alexandra, this is amazing news.
But what? Just say yes.
The thing is, your timing...
I just think it's a lot
to take in right now.
Okay. And this is
one of my investors right now.
Um, I'm staying
at the Five Seasons.
Think on it. But you
have ten hours to decide.
And I promise you this is truly
the opportunity of a lifetime.
Hi, this is Alexandra.
There you go.
All done.
So does this mean
I'm a real Serpent now?
Not just the Serpent.
Serpent King.
Anthony, you're our son.
And you've got the best shot
of surviving whatever's coming.
And it's up to you to make sure
the Serpents don't die out,
and being king
is your birthright,
and that's why it's up to you to make sure
that that legacy, our legacy, continues, okay?
Yes, Mom.
Return to us,
Spirit from beyond.
Abigail Blossom,
we asked to correspond.
We seek your wisdom, help
an insight appear before us,
sister of the night.
Pray tell, why have I
been conjured?
Abigail, hi.
We need your help.
An evil sorcerer has called
a comet down upon us
- and bound us to this town so that no one can leave it.
- Good.
Why for should I help you?
Listen, I think we may have
gotten off on the wrong foot.
So, yes, I'm asking you
to show a little mercy.
Also I'll free you
from that ceramic hell doll.
A long, long time ago,
when I was still alive,
I spent the most sublime evening
with my beloved Thomasina.
She was an astronomer and a
scientist as well as a witch.
It's called Bailey's Comet.
It's... beautiful.
Just like you.
What's it made of?
Ice, my love.
Comets are made of ice.
I hear what goes on
in this house.
You possess the power
of the Phoenix, don't you?
As soon as the comet gets close enough
to Earth, project your power at it.
And melt it?
That's kind of basic,
but also kind of genius.
But if it is to work, it will
require all of your Phoenix power.
And such an effort
will come at a cost.
What about Percival's trap?
Can you help us
undo his binding spell?
Mayhap, though that will take
a greater effort to undo.
Therefore, in exchange,
I will require
something more
than an appeal and my freedom.
Okay, we're listening.
All my underworlders!
Any luck finding
a safe passageway out?
Not yet.
Every time we follow a tunnel
that leads us
to what should be the edge
of town, we hit the barrier.
Luckily, I may have divined a
pathway through our little conundrum.
Come, come. Everyone's
gathered at Thornhill.
Listen up, Riverdalians.
Thanks to some ancestral advice,
I believe I might,
might be able to melt the
comet with my Phoenix powers.
Whoa, that's incredible news.
And there may also be a way to
undo Percival's binding spells
so that we can evacuate
the town.
But, Toni, you and I need
to speak about that privately.
Okay.
Hold on. Is it really as easy
as melting the comet?
No, Veronica.
There is one huge catch.
It will take all of my Phoenix
energies to extinguish Bailey's Comet,
which means if I successfully
melt the comet,
one or more of the dead I've
resurrected will surely perish.
What? Wait. Why?
Because it is my powers that are
keeping the resurrected dead alive.
Who knew?
So, who is on the chopping block
exactly?
Archie.
Jughead.
Polly.
My Nana.
Dagwood.
Alice.
Frank, Sheriff Keller,
Fangs and Toni,
if Riverdale is to live,
one or many of you
or your loved ones, must die.
What can I do to help, Cheryl?
My ancestor, the witch,
Abigail Blossom,
is going to help us figure out
a way to break Percival's spell
and escape Riverdale's borders.
But first, she wants to spend
one final evening
with her beloved in carnal form,
and we need two vessels
to make that happen.
I would be Abigail's
and you, pending your agreement,
would be her beloved
Thomasina Topaz, your ancestor
who was also a witch.
Okay, but what about Fangs
and Heather?
Well, Heather's a witch.
So she's kind of fine
with whatevs. As for Fangs...
it isn't technically cheating.
I mean,
our souls will be elsewhere.
Okay. And where would
our souls be, exactly?
Not to worry.
Heather will keep our spirits in
a jar until the lovemaking ends.
There you are.
Mom, you, you shouldn't be here.
What are you talking about?
Why are you covered in dirt?
I'm on a job.
Let me get cleaned up.
Archie,
one of the reasons
why I came back was
I want to tell you that Brooke
and I are getting a divorce.
What? What happened?
I thought
you two got along great.
Oh, we do get along.
Just we also both realize
that we don't want to spend
the rest of our lives together,
and it's okay.
You know, it happens.
But life... life is precious.
And you don't want to waste
a single minute.
You know?
Cheers, Daddy.
And hopefully, whatever happens,
we don't cross paths
in the afterlife.
What's going on?
Good news about the comet,
I hope?
No, um...
personal news actually.
I'm going to ask Betty
to marry me.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Today?
- I was going to use a ring my dad gave me,
but I lost it,
probably in the explosion.
So since I don't have
a lot of time,
I was wondering if you might
still have some rings
from the jewelry shop
you used to run.
- Uh...
- I'm sorry if that's a weird thing to ask.
No, no, not at all.
Um, actually...
Yeah.
You're in luck, Archie.
I have an amazing diamond ring in my
personal stash that Betty would flip for.
But franchising Pop's
has been your dream.
You've been protecting
the diner all year.
This is the best way
to ensure its longevity.
Honestly, as long as there's a giant
hunk of ice hurtling towards us,
I'm not committing to anything,
though, I do appreciate you
willing to be the Jack to my Rose.
Who?
Jack and Rose,
from Titanic, Leonardo
DiCaprio, Kate Winslet.
- Oh.
- Jack dies so that Rose can fulfill all of her dreams
like flying solo
around the world.
Never seen the Titanic.
- What?
- I know, I know.
I'm more partial to, like,
early James Cameron.
Jughead,
you've gotta be kidding.
The Titanic is one of my favorite
movies of, like, all time.
We have to watch it.
- We have to watch it.
- Yes.
Isn't that, like,
four hours long?
Three hours and 14 minutes.
Look, I know
the clock is ticking.
But trust me,
we need to do this.
If you're ready, let's begin.
Hear ye, hear ye, great above.
Send two spirits deep in love.
Take these vessels for the night
and earthly realm to reunite.
Switch the souls,
let flesh remain,
shake thy broom,
that love of flame.
Abigail, can this truly
be happening?
Yes.
Yes, my love. This is real.
Come. We have oh so much
to catch up on.
♪ I don't know
♪ I just wanna
Beg for your love ♪
♪ Tearing through the pines
♪ Just to feel somethin' more
♪ Baby, I know
What it's like to feel alone ♪
♪ Waiting for a spark
Just to light up the cold ♪
♪ Wait on the edge
Of the dark ♪
♪ Can't get enough
♪ Sittin' here watchin' you ♪
♪ Wait on the edge
Of the dark ♪
♪ Thinkin' 'bout us ♪
♪ Sittin' here watching you ♪
And my mom's here.
She's in Riverdale.
Oh, my God, Did you tell her
about the comet?
I didn't. I mean,
where would I even start?
Arch, you got to tell her.
Yeah, maybe.
But first...
What are you doing?
We may not have much time,
but I know what
I want to do with it.
Marry me.
There's a comet coming.
- And I want to be with you for it.
- Then be with me.
Arch,
I love you so much.
That's not part of my
hesitation, okay?
But can we talk about what's
going on with you right now?
You put so much pressure
on yourself to be a hero,
when you already are one.
Sometimes you
can't save everyone.
Sometimes you can
just be scared.
And that's okay.
It's human.
Do you remember
when we were kids
and you asked me to marry you?
And I told you to ask me again
when we turned 18.
So how about this?
Ask me again
after Cheryl melts that comet
and you and me
and everyone else survives.
Or we find another way out
of Riverdale.
Deal?
I'm gonna do that for us.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna break through
that barrier
so I can marry you,
Betty Cooper.
- Cheryl?
- Yes, Toni.
Do you remember anything?
No.
- You?
- No.
No, um... Neither do I.
Toni?
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Anything to possibly
save the town.
So tell me, dearest ancestor, how
was your tryst with Thomasina?
Beyond my wildest imaginings.
- Thank you, Cheryl.
- Of course.
But now tell me, how do we
undo Percival's binding spell?
Look there on the altar.
What is that?
The knots represent the various
mystical barriers surrounding the town.
Once the rope is untied completely,
you and the others should be
able to leave Riverdale.
Agent Cooper,
it's been a minute.
Drake, hi.
Yeah. Things have only gotten
more insane since TBK.
If you can believe that.
What's up?
Director Wilcox wants us to head
up the FBI serial killer division.
Oh, my God.
That's quite the promotion.
The thing is,
there's a lot going on
in my life right now.
I'm, sort of,
in a transitional period.
You know, weighing my options
for the future.
But, Betty, there's no better
hunter of hunters than you are.
I think that chapter of my life
is over.
Being a hunter of hunters,
I mean, I don't want that
carved on my gravestone.
I hate asking,
but is this because of Archie
or because TBK messed
with your head?
No.
This has nothing to do
with TBK or Archie.
This is all... This is me.
It's my decision about how I want
to spend the rest of my life,
- for however long that might be.
- Doing what?
I'm moving towards the light.
Take care, Drake.
And don't be a stranger.
Bye.
So, Ronnie, if we survive,
- what's the first thing you're gonna do, you think?
- Hmm.
- Maybe a shopping spree in Paris with Katie.
- Oh.
- You?
- Get a dog.
- Aw.
- I always wanted one.
Name him... Vader.
- Yeah.
- That's sweet.
Reggie, the reason
I asked you over,
should we still be here
this time tomorrow,
I want you to have
the Babylonium. Sole ownership.
- Wait. Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
- How come?
- The casino was your idea.
Your baby.
The only thing that's
really mine is my absinthe.
Maybe I'll focus on that.
And should the sun
rise tomorrow,
and we find ourselves
no longer business partners,
any chance you and I
get back together?
Tempting, but no.
I think it's good we're off
that carousel ride, don't you?
Mmm-hmm.
And besides, if there is
another chapter for me still,
I think it's time
for a hard reboot.
On all fronts.
Instead of being
so relationship focused,
I'll be single and fabulous
and date a lot,
work on my friendship skills.
Starting with,
if you're amenable, you, Reggie.
Yeah, I'm down to be friend
zoned by you, Ronnie.
Good.
Cheers to that, Reggie.
And if you want, when it's
comet time, you can come over
and we can watch
the fireworks together.
Sounds good.
- As...
- Yes, Reggie, as friends.
Okay. Just checking.
I had no idea.
Right! It's amazing,
isn't it?
You know, you know
how it's going to end.
But... it's still a gut punch.
Couldn't they have both held on to
the drift wood of the end, though?
No, because it wouldn't
have supported them both.
Jack knew that
they would have sunk, so...
he let go
so that Rose could live.
I mean,
the resonances are startling.
Only you're
a lot cuter than Leo.
In my opinion.
Can you just make me a promise?
No matter what happens,
if Cheryl stops this comet
or if I live or I die, that you
take Alexandra up on her offer.
Take Pop's national.
- Jughead.
- I won't be able to die
or live peacefully. If you don't
swear to me, and you're an angel.
So I'm pretty sure
that means you can't lie.
- Can you just swear, no matter what happens...
- Okay, I swear.
But in exchange,
I just want you to agree
to go on one
last epic date with me.
Okay, but define epic because
we're trapped in Riverdale
and time
is now appallingly finite.
Not for me.
I'm chronokinetic, remember?
All I need is one minute.
- One minute?
- That's all we'll need.
Archie, why didn't you pick up?
I've been calling you.
Mom, you shouldn't be here.
- You don't understand.
- I do. Betty told me everything.
About Percival, about you dying and
Cheryl bringing you back to life.
I mean, my God, Archie.
- Did she also tell you...
- About the comet?
Yes, Yes, she did.
And about how now,
I'm... I'm trapped, too.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry you got caught up
in all this insanity.
Archie, none of what
is happening is your fault.
Mom, if you... If anyone dies because
of me, I couldn't live with myself.
Archie, shouldering this guilt,
this responsibility,
it's crazy. Like Betty said,
it's okay to be scared.
But it's not okay to be out
here hiding from the world.
No one loved this
town more than Dad.
He built so much of it
with his own two hands.
What do you think he'd be doing
right now if he were me?
Probably exactly what you're
doing, fighting till the end.
But your dad also knew
when to put down his tools
and come home to the people
he loved and who loved him.
We should all be together
for whatever's coming.
Well, Daddykins,
it's just you and me.
Figures, it's been
a hell of a year.
Your entire body is basically
one giant bio-dialysis machine.
There's a reason
you stayed in Riverdale.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Sorry, Daddy, but I just
figured out a way to save my friends.
Amazing.
Well, I can't wait
to start working together.
- Which would be when exactly?
- Tomorrow.
Bright and early,
I thought we could take out
the food truck
and post updates on social.
That sounds like a great idea.
Then why the long faces?
What? What am I missing?
Cheryl, in the event
that you melt the comet,
I believe I should head back to
Greendale, resume my life there.
Why for would you do that?
Because I saw something.
When we were doing the ritual.
I adore you, Cheryl.
But you and Toni
are forever soulmates.
How could
you possibly know that?
I'm a witch, silly.
I know these things.
Heather...
you opened my heart again.
Toni's with Fangs anyway.
For now, but you and Toni,
your fate
is written in the stars.
It transcends time.
Thanks for sending my mom to me.
Yeah, it kind of seemed like
a mom-tervention was necessary.
Yeah, my mom thinks
I have a hero complex.
She's probably right.
I think it comes from me feeling like
I'll never be able to live up to my dad.
Your dad would
be so beyond proud of you.
You've been such a rock for everyone
this year, especially for me.
You supported me.
You comforted me.
You loved me unconditionally.
So thank you for that.
I'm sorry for proposing to you in
the middle of all this insanity.
So end of the world or not,
we're on your timeline.
No pressure ever again.
Well, about that, Archie.
Been thinking about my life.
My future, if I have one...
and what I want.
- And?
- And I know I said I wanted to wait...
but will you marry me?
Are you serious?
As serious as a comet
hurtling towards Riverdale,
- yeah.
- Yes!
Yes, I'll marry you.
Okay, this is a crazy Hail Mary,
but I may have an idea for
how to bolster Cheryl's power
to, one, improve our chances
of taking down that comet
and, two, augment
her Phoenix energies
so that when she uses them up,
no one has to die.
I am so happy you uttered
that sentence and not me.
I'm a human dialysis
machine, right?
I pulled the sepsis from Charles'
blood and leached the chemical thujone
out of wormwood to distil
my poison free absinthe.
- Randomly, yes.
- No, not randomly, Bee.
Everything has
happened for a reason.
What if I can use my gift
to absorb all of our abilities,
our strengths and give them to
Cheryl to augment her Phoenix power.
Again, the stronger she is, the less
chance her powers will be used up.
And the less chance
one or more of us will die.
But, V, our powers aren't poison
or sepsis that need to be removed.
It's semantics.
Poison, strength, superpowers.
Whatever you want to call them.
It's what you said, Tabitha.
This is why
I stayed in Riverdale,
so that I can do this right now
at this exact moment
and maybe maybe the multiverse
gave each of us our specific powers
so that they could come
together, combine and save us.
How would you absorb them?
I would need access to where your
powers are most potent and present,
your blood.
Remember when we all went
to see It at the Bijou?
How the losers club cut their palms
and all held hands in a circle?
We need to do the same.
Wound to wound, blood to blood.
And I will take in
our collective life force.
I can't cut my hand.
I present to you,
one dagger of Megiddo.
Fine, but no one is cutting
into my alabaster flesh.
Sorry, there are limits.
Don't worry, Cheryl, I will be
transferring our powers to you via a kiss.
A, that's queer baiting and B,
won't your poison kiss kill me?
A, it's not queer baiting,
it's saving the world and B, pretty sure
your Phoenix power trumps my poison power.
I don't say what I'm thinking
that for all we know,
giving Cheryl our powers
and her trying to use them all at the
same time may actually make things worse
or have unintended,
devastating consequences.
We simply don't know.
♪ Rrraaa
♪ She know me know me
♪ Kraaa
♪ She hold me hold me
♪ Kraaaa
♪ She show me show me
♪ Just rock and then sway
♪ Look her eyes
Mmm.
Did it work?
Only one way to find out.
- Whoa!
- Whoa, V.
Interesting.
You're threatening me, Veronica,
and I can see an aura around you.
- And I can't.
- Let's go two for two.
The bullet didn't penetrate.
I'm invulnerable.
I guess that means I'm not.
Veronica is nuts!
What if that hadn't worked?
I should have stayed in Chicago.
I can hear your thoughts.
I think your
dialysis worked, Veronica.
In that case, you're as ready
as you'll ever be, Cheryl.
For all our sakes,
I pray you're right.
Toodles.
Mom, Dad.
- I'm scared.
- Hey.
♪ Breathe the air again
♪ It's a beautiful day
♪ I wish this moment
Would stay ♪
♪ With the earth ♪
- ♪ Some primal paradise
- ♪ Paradise
♪ But there you go again
♪ Saying everything ends
♪ Saying you can't depend
On anything ♪
♪ Or anyone ♪
♪ If the end of the world
Was near ♪
♪ Where would you
Choose to be? ♪
♪ If there was
Five more minutes ♪
♪ Of air
♪ Would you panic and hide?
♪ Or run for your life? ♪
♪ Or stand here
And spend it with me? ♪
♪ If we had five more minutes
♪ Would I, could I
Make you happy? ♪
♪ And we would live again
♪ In the simplest of ways
♪ Living day after day like
- ♪ Like some primal animals
- ♪ Animals
♪ We will love again
♪ Under glorious suns
♪ With the freedom
That comes with the truth ♪
♪ If the end of the world
Was near ♪
♪ Where would you
Choose to be? ♪
♪ If there was
Five more minutes ♪
♪ Of air
♪ Would you panic and hide?
♪ Or run for your life? ♪
♪ Or stand here
And spend it with me? ♪
♪ If we had five more minutes
♪ Would I, could I
Make you happy? ♪
♪ So it finally came to pass
♪ I saw the end of the world
♪ Saw the madness unfold
♪ Like some primal burial
♪ And I looked back upon
♪ Armageddon
♪ And the moment of truth
Between you and me ♪
♪ If we had five more minutes
♪ Of air to breathe
♪ And we cried all through it
♪ But you spend them with me
♪ On our last few drags
♪ Of air we agree ♪
♪ I was, and you were, happy
Let the fire within me
blaze in glory
and project upon
what's come before me,
combined with the gifts
from each of my allies,
keep this comet from
falling out of the skies.
Let the fire within me
blaze in glory
and project upon
what's come before me,
combined with the gifts
from each of my allies,
keep this comet from
falling out of the skies.
Let the fire within me
blaze in glory,
and project upon
what's come before me,
combined with the gifts
from each of my allies,
keep this comet from
falling from the skies.
Let the fire within me
blaze in glory,
keep this comet from
falling out of the skies.
So what happened next?
Did Cheryl, with our combined
strengths, melt the comet?
And did Veronica's last-minute plan
to augment Cheryl's Phoenix powers
save our loved ones' lives?
The answer is yes.
♪ Only you
But I suspect that the milkshake-like
combination of all of our gifts
arcane magic, time-traveling,
opening portals into other dimensions
did something wholly unexpected
and yet also utterly inevitable.
Riverdale and its citizens survived the
ultimate battle between good and evil
and it was still our Riverdale.
But somehow,
we were in a different time.
Maybe to survive
we had to go back
to a simpler time.
Before Jason Blossom's murder before the
Black Hood, back to a truly innocent time.
Mom, what's wrong,
what's going on?
I just heard
the news on the radio.
And it's in the morning paper.
It's so awful, Archie.
He died.
He was so talented and so young.
Who's dead?
Who died?
James Dean.
It was true.
The night before, the actor
and teen idol James Dean
had died
in a car crash in California.
Somehow the year is 1955,
and somehow Archie Andrews
and all of his friends, me
included, are teenagers again
and I'm the only one who remembers
what our lives were like BC.
Before the comet.