Oh, hell, no.
- When I was back there.
- Right.
What are you doing in my house?
Archie, don't be rude.
I was just talking
to your uncle about the, uh,
the town-wide census
I'm conducting.
Census?
Under what authority?
With council approval.
Well, Alice and Frank.
I can assure you,
the questions are standard.
How long have you
lived in Riverdale?
What problems are you most
concerned with in your neighborhood?
And people's answers
will help guide the council.
And of course, I'll get
to meet my neighbors.
Door by door. Face by face.
Tell me, Archie. Would you
like to answer some questions?
No.
I would not.
And I'd like you to leave.
Now.
I gotta say I'm shocked, Archie.
He is not a good guy.
Oh, good grief, Archie!
You've clearly made up
your mind against Percival.
It's a shame.
He has a lot of great ideas
about how to make Riverdale
a better place to live.
It's damp and chilly,
Mistress Abigail.
Why don't we
go back to Thornhill?
I'll brew you some of that
yummy tea that you like,
and we'll get you warm and cozy.
No, as restorative
as your tea is,
it's time to vanquish my enemies
and be reunited
with my Thomasina.
How?
I shall reincarnate
Thomasina's soul
into Toni Topaz's body.
The blood moon
will be rising soon.
Perfect time
for reincarnation spell.
And once my beloved
has returned to me,
together, we will slay
Fangs Fogarty.
And seal our love
for all eternity.
And is Mr. Fogarty
the only, um,
enemy you wish to vanquish?
No. There are still the three
descendants of my assassins.
Come along, Brittania.
Ah!
You're in a good mood today.
I am.
I just spoke to my dad and
he wants to visit the casino.
Really? How's his health?
He's on the mend,
but it's like he lost his mojo.
The truth is,
my dad's always wanted to
feel like the big shot.
That's what's most important.
To make him feel like one.
Well, in that case,
leave it to me.
The Sheriff's Department
is pleased to announce
that the town-wide census
is complete,
and the people
of Riverdale have spoken.
And since the unhoused problem
has been dealt with,
their main source of anxiety
is the ongoing gang warfare
between the Serpents
and the Ghoulies.
Miss Topaz,
since you're a member of the
Council of Four and Serpent Queen,
what have you got
to say about that?
Well, to begin with,
there is no war
between the Serpents
and the Ghoulies.
Actually, I've been in constant
contact with the Ghoulies' leader,
Twyla Twyst, in efforts
to de-escalate tension.
And I believe we're very close
to declaring a ceasefire.
Well, I wonder, have you
considered disbanding the Serpents?
Okay, if I could just
interject here,
Miss Topaz is not on trial.
Your point has been noted,
Mr. Pickens.
Now let's please move on
to the next item on our agenda.
What the hell was that?
An ambush.
Percival went after
the folks in Sketch Alley
and now he's coming after us.
Hey, Toni. Fangs.
Oh, hey, Prince!
How is my baby boy doing?
Yeah, he's great. He's great.
I'm bummed to let him go.
Nervous, given
everything going on.
Oh, don't be.
I gotta be honest.
I'm having second thoughts
about Baby Anthony being raised
around gang culture.
You mean as a Serpent?
Kevin, I was raised
as a Serpent.
So was Fangs.
I know. I know. I'm just...
concerned for his safety.
That's all.
Welcome to
Babylonium, Mr. Mantle.
And here we are, our best table,
and our best dealer,
Ryan. He's one of my favorites.
Is there anything else
we can get for you, Mr. Mantle?
No. This is all
very impressive.
We aim to please.
I'll come by
to check on you later.
But in the meantime, have fun.
Thanks for
hanging back, you guys.
Something very, very weird
is happening in Riverdale.
You mean, besides us suddenly
developing mutant abilities?
I'm talking
about Percival Pickens.
You heard him. He's been
going around door to door
meeting with everyone in town,
trying to recruit them.
Your mom, my Uncle Frank,
Sheriff Keller.
God knows who else.
Ever since Percival
sensed me in his mind,
I've been doing some...
research on heightened
psychic abilities.
You know, some people think that
mind control is a real thing,
like a skill,
the power of persuasion.
But persuading people
to do what?
What does Percival want
with Riverdale?
His family was one of the
original settlers of the town.
Maybe he feels like
he has a claim to it?
Whatever it is, it's not good.
Jug, if he really made
your friend Doc attack Kev,
what's to say
he didn't compel the people
of Sketch Alley to up
and leave the same way?
I mean, if he really can control
people's thoughts, and actions...
Yeah, he needs to be stopped.
Classic superhero narrative.
Okay, Betty, can we
throw this guy in jail?
- You're the FBI.
- Yeah,
but not if we can't prove
he's breaking any laws.
All right, then.
Archie, you are invulnerable.
Let's beat this guy up.
Break every bone in his body.
I can't do that, Jug.
I'd be just as bad as he is.
Besides, we tried both of those
things with Hiram repeatedly.
They're temporary solutions
at best.
Percival is going around recruiting
people for whatever big play he's got.
What if we do the same thing?
We go to our friends,
the people we trust,
make sure that he's not
turning them to his side.
In the short term,
it would stop Percival
from amassing
too much power too quickly.
We'd be concerned citizens
talking to our neighbors.
Guys, what if this is why
we were given our powers?
To protect the town
from Percival.
Okay, relax, Professor Xavier.
Who do we start with?
Well, isn't this fortuitous?
Cheryl, have you had any
private contact
with Percival Pickens?
Did he stop by to interview you?
For his census?
Yes, but I was taking
a buttermilk bath,
so I couldn't receive him.
Why for?
We're worried that his intentions
for Riverdale may not be above board.
We think he is recruiting
people to his side.
For some nefarious agenda?
Honestly, I'd be more worried
about an angry mob dragging me
into the forest in the middle of the
night and burning me at the stake.
As Archibald Andrews,
Jedediah Jones
and Beatrice Cooper
did to my ancestor.
Not this again.
Yes, again.
That transgression hasn't
been settled or forgotten.
Okay, will you just
let us know if Percival
tries to influence you
in any way?
And for what?
Regarding Mr. Pickens,
I'll keep my own counsel
as I always have.
And as for you three, my patience,
and this audience is at an end.
Come on, Cheryl.
We're the good guys.
Spoken like a true villain.
Let me show you the door.
Stoke the fires
and heat the ovens, Brittania.
We're preparing
arsenic-laced scones.
For who?
For that unholy trinity
of self-obsessed malefactors.
The timing couldn't be
more perfect.
I need a corpse
for my reincarnation ritual.
Hurry now. Lest we bake
a scone for you, too.
Toni, where are you right now?
At school. Why? What's up?
Don't tell me more trouble
with the Ghoulies.
Not the Ghoulies.
But I just got
a call from Alice.
She and Frank are convening an
emergency meeting of the council.
Why wasn't I told about this?
It's because the meeting is to
remove you from the council.
What? Why?
It's Percival's idea,
says Alice.
He's using the drive-by
last night as an excuse.
What's his grudge with me?
I don't know. I mean, you're
a pillar of the community,
and maybe he sees you
as a threat.
At any rate, it is
classic fear mongering,
and that is why you need to
come with me to this meeting.
I'm on my way.
What's going on?
We want to talk
about Percival Pickens.
We don't think he's a good guy.
Did he come by here
for his census
to put ideas into your head
or try to shift
your point of view?
Or to recruit you for anything?
No and no.
But...
the male Mary Poppins is definitely
up to some serious shadiness.
Why do you say that?
I had one of my associates
look into him for me.
And Percival...
doesn't exist.
There's literally
no trace of him
before he showed up
in Riverdale.
And this sounds crazy, but...
he said something
to one of our clients.
I don't know what.
And then that client...
killed himself.
Okay. Now, can we
beat this guy up?
Get him thrown in jail?
How does he even have powers?
We were in that explosion.
Not that that makes sense.
None of this makes sense.
But how can Percival
control people's minds?
It's Tabitha. She says we need
to go to the El Royale.
Thank you for assembling.
We've all heard about the act
of gang violence that happened
at Pop's just last night.
And in response
to that incident,
Percival Pickens would like
to submit a motion.
My motion is for the immediate
removal of Antoinette Topaz
from the Council of Four.
How can Riverdale feel safe
with a known gang member
shaping town policy?
I think Toni can
and should speak for herself.
Thank you, Tabitha.
Mr. Pickens,
I know you're new here.
But I have spent my entire life
in service to Riverdale.
After high school, I graduated
college with a degree in social work.
I then became guidance
counselor at Riverdale High.
I kept its doors open as Hiram
Lodge fought to shut us down.
I then used my position
as a small business owner
and proud member
of the LGBTQIA+ community.
To help with various
charities and organizations.
And if there's any doubt
about my integrity,
just know that
I'm raising my son here,
and I'm invested in Riverdale
because of him.
And I hope you all let me
continue to advocate
for you and this town.
Thank you.
Well, let's put it to a vote.
See what happens.
Miss Lodge,
sorry to interrupt,
but Mister Mantle is back
at table 12
and he's in pretty deep.
To the tune of $7,000.
All right. I will deal with it.
Thank you.
Mom.
- Oh, hey, honey.
- Hey, uh, what's going on?
We heard from Tabitha
that there was a meeting.
Uh, yeah, there was.
Unfortunately, Toni
was voted off the council.
And let me guess, Alice.
This was Percival's idea?
Except for Tabitha, it was
a unanimous vote, Archie.
Unanimous?
Against Toni?
How is that possible?
Ah!
How are you boys doing
over here?
The House is calling
for a break.
How are you feeling, Mr. Mantle?
Are you doing okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Um...
I'm a little bit down,
but my luck is turning.
I can... I can feel it.
As a matter of fact, I was
wondering whether or not
you guys could float me,
maybe $5,000?
Oh, uh, we don't really
do that here.
But maybe you should
step away from the table
and slow down a bit,
you know, cut your losses.
So, you're throwing me
out of my own son's casino?
You're going to embarrass me
in front of these guys.
♪ Baby did a bad bad thing
♪ You ever love
Someone so much ♪
♪ You thought
Your little heart... ♪
Archie Andrews.
Just the he-man
I was looking for.
I'm sorry I was so cold to you
at Thornhill yesterday.
May I interest you
in an apology treat?
Dearest Jug-Jug,
may I offer you
a sugary sweet mea culpa
for my foul mood yesterday?
Sweet cousin.
I come bearing gifts
to mend hurt feelings.
What are you doing, Cheryl?
Offering you an olive branch.
Why won't you take one
like your cohorts did?
What did you put
in those scones?
Are you trying to poison me?
"Cohorts."
Jug. Archie.
Don't eat that scone.
I already did.
What's the problem?
I think she poisoned them.
Okay. Well,
I'm invulnerable, remember?
Okay, well, Jughead isn't.
So get a glass of water
and a salt shaker
and meet me
by the bathrooms, okay?
Don't take another bite!
Bathroom. Now.
Cheryl gave us poisoned scones?
- Yeah, we think so.
- Well, yes, I saw her aura, okay?
So drink this and then throw up.
Just go.
- I have been thinking, Fangs.
- Mmm-hmm.
What if the Serpents
shed their skin
and rebranded a little bit?
So we no longer be a gang,
which is triggering,
but a political activist group,
like the Black Panthers.
We'd focus more
on community-driven programs
helping the town's youth
and seniors.
Wouldn't we be handing the town
over to the Ghoulies
at that point?
Well, we could ask Betty
for help from the FBI.
You want the FBI
to fight our battles for us?
Where's all this coming from?
Becoming
a political activist group?
It would take the wind
out of the witch hunter sails.
I gotta be honest.
I don't think the Serpents
are gonna go for it, Toni.
They will if we stay
united on this.
Fangs.
Are we?
United?
Oh, my God!
Kevin?
What the hell?
You can't just come in here.
We got a warrant, Fangs.
We received reports
there's illegal weapons
being stored in this apartment.
Weapons?
Absolutely not.
And reports from whom?
- I'll check the baby's room.
- The hell you will!
That's it. He's done.
Come on.
What the hell? Let him go.
Kevin, why are you doing this?
Fangs, I'm going to get you
out of here no matter what.
But I need to know.
Where did the weapons come from?
They were mine.
Fangs, why?
In our house?
With Baby Anthony?
I was storing them.
For a battle royale
with the Ghoulies.
You stopped talking
to Twyla Twyst,
but she reached out to me,
challenged me to a rumble.
The other Serpents?
They want to fight.
I'm sorry, Toni.
- Hey.
How's the scene at the casino?
Dad said he had a blast again.
To be honest...
We kind of had a moment.
He was losing a lot of money.
And I asked him
if he wanted to step away.
He didn't
and it's not a big deal, but...
it kind of got me wondering,
how did your dad
get into debt with my dad?
Was it gambling?
He was making capital
improvements to the car lot
and the bank didn't want
to give him a loan.
Damn, Ronnie.
The guy's finally having a good
time, and you want to squash that?
Not at all.
I only wanted to make sure
he was okay.
Trust me, he's fine.
Horrid news about Archie,
Betty and Jughead.
Oh, no. Are they?
Very much alive, I'm afraid.
How, I have no clue.
No matter.
Tomorrow I shall
pay Toni a visit.
I need some of her blood
for my rituals.
Does that mean that you're done
trying to kill the others?
Of course not.
I still hate them,
and I still need a body.
It's just a matter of devising how
I might go about vanquishing them.
How are you feeling, Jug?
Like I swam in the ocean
and swallowed
a bunch of sea water.
It was the best way
to flush Cheryl's
poison out of your system.
Why is Cheryl trying
to kill us all of a sudden?
Because of something that
happened to Abigail centuries ago?
- Really?
- Or it was Percival.
I mean, maybe he got to her,
suggested that she take us out.
And what better way
to get rid of us
without leaving
any fingerprints?
Well, there's one way
to find out.
Jug, you can't read Percival's
mind because he'll sense it.
But maybe try reading Cheryl's?
Maybe you'll pick up
some trace of Percival?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Just let me get
my sea legs back first.
Behold. A bouquet of roses
so beautiful,
they needed your presence
to keep them company.
Cheryl, what's the occasion?
Oh, I just had a sixth sense
that you need a pick-me-up.
Was I wrong?
No, on the contrary, I...
Ow!
Oh, no.
Do those roses
still have thorns?
Poor hand. Let me see.
Pray, tell, what ails you?
I got voted off the council.
Fangs is in jail,
and the Ghoulies
are determined to start a war
with the Serpents.
Remind me again,
what is the origin
of your troubles
with, um, the Ghoulies?
Most recently?
Well, Archie
went ballistic on them
after they blew up his house.
For all I know, they're still
trying to kill him.
Probably planning
another drive by
even as we speak.
The Ghoulies wish
to kill Archie?
Tell me more about that.
You called, Dad?
I'm in trouble, Reg.
I lost the car lot.
The dealership?
How? When?
Last night.
After we left the casino,
these wise guys invited me
to a private poker game
at Cucina's Casa.
You went with them?
We were having a great time.
Okay.
And one thing led to another,
and... and it was like
that time at the race track.
Remember?
You know, I... I...
I couldn't stop.
The more I lost, the more
I had to keep on playing.
I was wondering, um...
Maybe you could talk to Veronica
and she could talk
to the wise guys.
They're sort of her crowd,
aren't they?
Let me see, Dad.
Janet. What can I
help you with?
I hate having to do this, Toni,
but I'm here conducting
a wellness check.
I've been informed this may be
an unsafe environment
for Baby Anthony.
I received
an anonymous complaint.
I'm here on
a wellness check, Toni.
For Baby Anthony.
Toni?
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
Yeah. I was
just having deja vu.
Janet, I don't know
what you've heard,
but I would never do anything
to put Baby Anthony
in harm's way. Ever.
Of course.
But as a social worker, I have
to investigate every claim.
Where is he now? Can I see him?
Sure, follow me.
He's asleep in his bedroom.
Wait. Where is he?
Toni, the window.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Archibald.
All right, everybody, listen up.
The Sheriff's department
and the FBI
are leading their own search
for Baby Anthony.
But here in Riverdale,
we take care of our own.
We've divided the town
into a grid,
so we'll hit every house
on every block
until we find Baby Anthony.
This is a 24/7 operation
and we'll be working in shifts.
Let's bring Baby Anthony home.
- Poor kid.
- I hope he's okay.
She's not fit to be a mother.
She's the leader of a gang.
Put her child in harm's way.
No one's safe
in this town anymore.
Picking up on anything?
Nothing.
I mean, if the kidnappers
are keeping tabs on the search,
they're not doing it nearby.
But I'll keep looking.
Okay. I'll take a break. Archie
just texted me. He's outside.
Cheryl, dressed as a Ghoulie,
threw a Molotov cocktail at you?
It's hard to mistake
Cheryl, Betty.
No matter what she's wearing.
We'll stay here and join
the search for Baby Anthony,
will you please
go read Cheryl's mind now?
Yeah, definitely.
And hope I don't get killed.
We've got a problem.
My dad lost Mantle Motors
to one of Heraldo's
wise guys in a game of poker.
What can we do?
I'll talk to Heraldo's pals.
But now can you admit
that your dad has a problem?
And needs to be cut off?
What?
Your dad killed people
and blew up the entire town
and you hung up his portrait.
But my dad has
a streak of bad luck, and you
want to bar him from my casino?
You know what?
This is my dad's mess.
I'll handle it.
Hello.
Toni Topaz,
it's your old friend,
Twyla Twyst.
You'll never guess what cutie
patootie I'm looking at right now.
You have Anthony?
Where are you?
It's time to end this, Topaz.
The Serpents versus the Ghoulies.
The winner gets Riverdale.
And this little heartbreaker
right here.
Name the place
and I'll be there.
Under one condition.
You deliver Anthony to Pops.
And I'm not going to fight until
I get word from my friend Tabitha
that Anthony's safe.
- Deal?
- Deal.
See you at 10:00 in front of the
tuna fish warehouse in the docks.
And come armed.
Because we will be.
I'm not comfortable
with this, Toni.
Can't we at least loop in Betty?
No. This is how it works.
And this is how it has to be.
And Twyla doesn't want
to hurt Baby Anthony.
She wants bragging rights
that she took me down.
Or the Serpents. Or both.
Okay. Okay, then I will
wait for Baby Anthony,
and then I will call you.
What year
do you think it is? 1922?
Having a good time, fellas?
What's it look like, pal?
Can I ask you about a game
you played yesterday
with my father, Marty Mantle?
Yeah.
How's he doing?
To be honest,
he's heartbroken that our
family business is gone.
I was wondering
if I could buy it back.
Yeah, that may not work for us,
as it's already gone up
in value.
See, we're expanding
some of our operations,
and we've been looking for a
business like your dad's car lot.
So if you were to buy it off us,
the price would now include the
projected income for the next five years,
not just the $100,000.
What sort of operation
are you planning for?
I don't think it'd be
your cup of tea.
Are we talking a chop shop?
Running contraband, money
laundering, counterfeit play, what?
- Get a load of this guy, will you?
- -Please.
I was boot licking him
when I was in high school.
And you might want someone
to interface with the public.
Someone trustworthy and
familiar with how car lots work,
to keep the trains running,
so no one gets suspicious.
What I'm saying is,
maybe we can help each other.
Oh. Hi.
Britta, right?
Can I see Cheryl?
Uh, no. Um...
Mistress Cheryl is getting
ready for something.
For what?
A ritual.
I...
I... I can't say.
She made me promise,
and she knows...
She knows when I'm lying.
Okay. Listen to me.
If you think it really loudly,
I might be able to hear it.
You understand?
I'm living
a captive existence here.
I'm sure you won't believe me,
but Mistress Cheryl is asleep,
and her ancestor Abigail
Blossom has possessed her body.
And she's been trying
to kill people.
Including you and your friends
on the eve of the blood moon,
so Ms. Topaz's soul
will go into the corpse
and Thomasina can be reincarnated into Ms.
Topaz's empty body.
Are you going to be okay?
Until the blood moon?
I can't believe Keller put
us on patrol duty tonight
When everyone else gets be
part of the turkey shoot.
I want to see some action, man.
Exterminate those Serpents
once and for all.
Would you shut
your damn mouth, Walker?
What are you talking about?
What turkey shoot?
With the Serpents?
Kevin, whatever else
is happening,
Toni is still
the mother of your child.
Tell me.
What is going on?
Hey, Tabitha, what's up?
The Ghoulies haven't
shown up yet.
Do you have Baby Anthony?
No, and Toni,
you have to get out there.
I think you walked into a trap.
What?
It's the Sheriff and his deputies.
They're out for blood.
Kevin told me it's going to be
a turkey shoot.
Don't let it become one.
I'll call you right back.
Everyone, we gotta go. We gotta
get out of here right now.
Hands in the air,
guns to the ground!
Serpents,
put your weapons on the ground
and put your hands in the air.
Don't give them
a reason to shoot,
that's exactly what they want.
You heard her. The Serpents
are resisting arrest.
The hell we are.
And I'm live streaming this
right now, you scumbag!
So be careful what you do, because
the whole world is watching.
Reggie.
How are things going?
I cleaned up my dad's mess
and I got the dealership back.
Oh, and also you don't have to
worry about my dad coming back.
I told him he has a problem and
barred him from the Babylonium.
That's not what I wanted, but...
okay.
Is he gonna get help?
He's fine.
That's all you need to know.
Hey.
- Hey.
Your mom isn't here, right?
No, she's at another one
of her secret Council meetings,
Yeah, which we have to go.
I actually think that
Cheryl needs our help more.
Cousin?
Why for this crying?
Have you heard about Archie?
He's dead.
He was burned alive
by a Ghoulie.
Oh, dear.
Can I come in?
Of course.
Follow me into the parlor
and I'll put on the kettle.
Cheryl, if you can hear me,
help is on the way.
Ms. Topaz,
are you comfortable?
I'm fine.
Are you sorry your turkey shoot
didn't happen?
I can't think what you mean.
I've got good news for you.
Your bail's been posted
by Tabitha Tate.
You're being released.
In the morning.
I don't suppose
I can appeal to you
as a mother who's looking
for her child.
Oh, you mustn't worry
about Anthony.
We raided a Ghoulie lair
earlier this evening
and we found your son.
- Luckily,
we got him out safely.
Alas, the same can't be said
about the Ghoulies.
It was an absolute bloodbath.
Unfortunately, only
one of them survived.
Twyla Twyst.
She escaped.
Like the roach that she is.
And where the hell
is my son now?
Safe and sound...
with his father.
You... Villains.
You'll never get me out of this body.
It's mine now.
Mine!
We'll see how long you last
once this fire gets going.
You dare burn me again?
As many times
as it takes, bitch.
By the power of fire,
the element of your
original destruction.
- So too are you banished...
- I'll kill you all!
From this fleshy vessel.
Spirit, we compel you.
Leave her.
Friends,
as you've no doubt heard,
Percival Pickens has been
nominated for emergency election
to the Town Council,
filling the vacancy left
by the currently incarcerated
Antoinette Topaz.
All those in favor.
And with that,
a huge congratulations
to the newest member
of the Riverdale Town Council,
Percival Pickens.
You're all gonna die for this!
Whoo!
It twitched...
in my hands.
Mistress Cheryl?
Cheryl, is that you?
Yeah.
But where's Abigail?
- Oh!
- Oh, thank God.
Oh, honey.
I'm so, so sorry.
He's... he's okay.
Yeah, we got lucky this time.
But now he is safe.
And exactly where he should be.
I should tell you, Toni,
it's not easy for me
to say this,
but I'm filing for primary
custody of Baby Anthony.
No, Kevin, please don't do this.
I've been talking
with Ms. Weiss.
Given Fangs
and your recent behavior,
it shouldn't be hard for me
to win guardianship.
Kevin, why the hell
are you doing this?
I don't understand.
My only concern
is for Anthony's safety.
How's it going, Dad?
Oh, it's great.
Everything's great.
Glad to hear.
You look happy, Dad.
Oh, yeah. Having the time
of my life, son.
Time of my life.
It's not looking good,
I'm afraid.
Your father is
on the donor list,
but at this point,
it is highly unlikely
he'll get a transplant in time.
Barring that,
what do you think, Doc?
He's looking at a year.
Maybe two, if he's lucky,
Is there anything I can do?
Not at this point.
Except maybe just make sure
your dad enjoys
what little time he's got left.
This is Agent Cooper.
Miss Cooper,
so sorry to bother you.
Have you heard
about the Ghoulies' slaughter?
Yeah, I did.
Twenty-two Ghoulies dead.
It's horrible.
I'm sure you've got
your hands full.
I do.
But there is something...
off about the bodies.
Off in what way?
According to the Sheriff report,
the Ghoulies were killed in a gun
fight with deputies on the scene.
But I would say
the Ghoulies wounds
were self-inflicted.
Hang on. They...
They shot themselves?
Yes, I believe the Ghoulies
turned their guns on themselves.
There.
Sealed away.
Forever.
One more thing, Nana.
It falls to us three women to
keep the eternal flames burning
so that Abigail
will never escape
or lay claim to my body again.
Well, at least we saved Cheryl
from being possessed.
So that's a win, right?
Yeah. But while
we were doing that,
Percival got himself
elected on the town council.
The council that we formed.
After killing 22 Ghoulies,
and almost killing
the Serpents, maybe.
So... what? He wants
to take over the town?
Like Hiram Lodge? We stopped Hiram.
We can stop Percival.
I don't think Percival
wants to take over Riverdale.
Something tells me
he wants to destroy it.