[eerie music]
[muffled voices]
[loud, distorted banging]
He's got a good pulse.
Maintain head stabilization
and flip him over.
My count, guys.
Ready. Go.
[groans]
Sir, we're paramedics.
The mailman saw you
having a seizure.
We had to break down
your door.
Do you know
what your name is?
On my count.
One, two, three. Up.
[exhales]
We're taking you
to the hospital.
[mumbling incoherently]
[mumbling]
No, I can't--
No. No, I can't...
[roars]
Hey.
Hey, buddy.
- Buddy, we're trying to help.
Sir!
Stay out of my house!
You just had a seizure.
You could have a stroke.
A bleed in your brain.
Leave me alone!
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
# #
35-year-old male--
crushing headache
and three seizures
in the last two days.
(house)
So it's a bleed, clot, tumor,
metabolic, or infection.
Stick him in a CT.
- Can't.
I'm assuming
he has a giant head.
Severe agoraphobe.
The world scares
the hell out of him.
So we can only test him
with whatever we can take to him.
- Fun.
Agoraphobia a symptom?
Only of being shot.
He and his girlfriend
were mugged seven years ago.
That's when it started.
Anybody can hate humanity
after getting shot.
Takes a big man
to hate it beforehand.
How'd you get this case
if he didn't come to the ER?
I talked to him through his door
when he had flu last year.
I run the community
outreach program now.
See? Perfectly reasonable
explanation.
She's definitely not here
trying to work her way back
on the team and steal your job
or anything.
It's a legitimate question.
He agreed to meet
with us.
But even if I can get
inside his house,
his brain is a black box.
We can pick this up
in a minute.
(House)
What's this?
Take-out menus.
But I'm hoping you'll come up
with a better answer
when everyone asks
what we're talking about.
Last night--
Forget it.
I know this is awkward,
but we need to talk.
There's a reason
that we've evolved
a feeling of awkwardness.
It tells us not
to talk about things.
I was emotional
because of the adoption
falling through.
And you actually let
your human side
show for a moment.
That is why we kissed.
I just want to say thank you
for not...taking advantage.
You're welcome.
Any time you want
to stop kissing,
I'm there for you.
Portable equipment
can't distinguish a bleed
or a tumor.
Can't see vasculitis.
What did Cuddy want?
I kinda hit that
last night,
so now she's all
on my jock.
Wow. She looks pretty good
for someone on roofies.
The only equipment we have
is a sonogram
and a portable x-ray.
What part of olivine,
pyroxene, and amphibole
don't you understand?
(Kutner)
Pyroxene.
Pyro means "fire"...
(Cameron)
They're indicator minerals.
You can't see diamonds
so you look
for the indicator minerals.
I assume the diamond
is the tumor or bleed
or whatever it is.
(Foreman)
We provoke a seizure.
The indicator is the increased
electrical activity
focused around
the abnormality.
We do an EEG,
see the focus,
see where the problem is,
which tells us
what the problem is.
[clicks tongue]
The formster and the camster.
Kickin' it old school.
Thank god she's not trying
to steal your job.
Go do it.
And search the home for toxins.
(man) I agreed to talk,
not let you in.
You could be very sick.
We need access.
(man)
I'm just not ready.
Why does he have
two locked doors?
He must use this room
as an airlock.
Deliveries in.
Garbage out.
He never
has to go outside.
Just tell us when you are.
We're not going away.
Seriously?
You want her to admit
that all he has to do
is ignore us for a few minutes
and we'll take off?
- He was shot.
Girlfriend killed.
He probably has post traumatic
stress disorder.
He doesn't believe
a just universe.
He doesn't trust anyone.
Give him some honesty.
I shouldn't have implied
we'd wait forever.
We've got a whole hospital
full of patients.
We can give you
a few minutes.
but eventually,
if you don't let us in,
we're gonna have to leave.
(man)
Just one person comes in.
No.
We've got to search
the whole house for toxins.
How about I examine you
in one room
and my colleagues
will do the search?
[door unlocks]
I'm gonna try
to provoke a seizure.
I need you
to look straight ahead, okay?
You all right?
- Yeah.
Uh, I just, um,
I haven't been in a room
with anyone for a while.
Um, can you just give me
a second?
Sure.
You're the, uh,
uh, person I talked to
through the door last year,
right?
- Yeah.
You were, uh, you were nice...
and smart.
Kind of made me expect
someone older.
I'm not that young.
Must've been scary
being shot.
Don't do that.
Okay?
You d--you don't know me.
I've got everything
I want here.
I-I-make a lot of money
writing tech manuals.
I get stuff delivered.
I work out.
I see anything I want
over the web.
Um, I'm--I'm happy here.
You don't seem
very happy.
Well, right now I'm not.
Go away.
Did you speak
to Cuddy last night?
She's fine.
Why would it take anyone
more than a few hours
to get over
misplacing a baby?
You spoke to her?
Kinda hit that.
So she's all on my jock.
Whoa.
Wha--what?
Huh.
Everyone else
thought I was kidding.
You hit?
Like making out
or full-on sex or--
Got a chart laid out
with all the bases.
I'll take you through it.
Wh--what are you
gonna do?
What can I do?
I'm going to ignore her
for the rest of my life.
This mosquito bite
kept me awake.
Don't care
about the bug bite.
She's your boss.
So now I have two reasons
to ignore her.
It was just a kiss.
There's a reason.
Yes. Those large things
in her bra.
You were hiding it from me
means it meant something
to you.
Yeah, I fiendishly
concealed it
within the phrase
"I hit that."
Stop scratching.
You'll draw blood.
Finally you said
something useful.
If I actually break
the skin,
it'll let
the poison out.
[cell phone rings]
If you...
dated Cuddy...
there would--
Sorry. I get better reception
when you're not here.
What do you got?
(Taub)
His place is totally clean.
No animals.
No hidden drugs or alcohol.
No lead in the paint.
(House) And since
you're not breathing hard,
I assume you're not holding
Cameron aloft in triumph.
Which means no seizures.
[beep]
Hey. Speaking
of breathing hard,
Cameron, you engaged
to Chase yet?
(Thirteen)
Sorry, we should have clarified.
we're calling
about the patient,
not Dr. Cameron's
love life.
We aren't engaged.
Moves things along
much faster
to just give him
the answers.
Seizures can also
be induced through--
After six years?
A year and a half.
Through sleep
deprivation or--
sleep deprivation
would take too long.
You living together?
We spend most nights
together.
There's a bunch of drugs
that can lower a seizure
threshold.
And cloud the diagnosis
with side effects.
His place or yours?
His usually.
Interesting.
You would've said
interesting
no matter
what the answer.
And no matter
what the answer,
it would've been
interesting.
No engagement.
Commitment issues.
His place, control issues.
Not sure whose,
but interesting.
Yeah, moves much faster
this way.
Where was the patient
when he had his first seizure?
In his entry hallway
getting his mail.
Getting close to the outdoors
spooked him,
raised his BP.
Use that fear.
Bring him outside.
He punched out a fireman.
We're doctors,
not bouncers.
Okay. So bring the outside
to him.
Floor is genuine wood.
Why are they here?
They overheard me announce
the half price bank foreclosure
in the ER waiting room.
Where's everybody?
Cameron's
with the patient.
Uh, everybody else
went home.
Because they don't need
to be here.
Neither do you.
And yet you are.
This way.
Molding's original?
Original? They were here
before the house.
The shut-in's
also original.
Come on.
Don't be shy.
House, get them
out of here.
(House)
Easy for you to say.
You're not gonna be making
some serious capital gains.
This is cruel.
And leaving him undiagnosed
is what, altruistic?
Procedure worked.
He's seizing.
What do you see?
Normal theta.
Normal delta.
This isn't a seizure.
It's something.
Mr. Nozick,
are you okay?
Stomach's killing me.
See? It's something.
[machine beeps]
(Kutner)
Partial small bowel obstruction.
Blockage explains
the pain.
What explains
the blockage plus seizures?
Atrial fibrillation
throwing emboli.
Crohn's causing an abscess.
Could be
a million things.
There's no way to know
unless we get him in
for an MRI on his head
or exploratory surgery
so we can biopsy his bowels,
which he won't let us do.
Wouldn't.
Pain changes things.
House.
He told you to stay
out of here.
He can Chase me out
once he's done
doubling up in agony.
Whatever your
big problem is,
it's caused a complication
we call "colon FOS."
"FO," full of.
Since we're in mixed company,
"S" is stool.
Nothing's coming out
so the pain's
gonna get worse and worse.
We need to stick
a pooper scooper in you.
We also need to take a look
at your bowel.
I made my wishes clear.
Uh-huh. And if the crazy fairy
were here,
she could grant them.
I'm not insane.
I-I feel pain
when I go outside.
So it--it's rational
to avoid that pain.
Except now you're
feeling pain inside.
Not as bad.
Nowhere near.
We can give him drugs
for the blockage.
And if it doesn't work?
That blockage will rupture
your intestines,
spew sewage throughout
your body.
Whatever you're scared of
out there,
aren't you more scared
of death?
You obviously
can't stand people.
But for me, it's worse.
All right?
I'd rather die in here
than live out there.
If you don't mind
floppy hair
and an annoying
accent,
I know a surgeon
who will operate in your home.
Thank you.
With the risk of infection,
Chase won't actually--
He's not gonna do surgery
in some crazy dude's house.
You just said--
what I said was that
Chase would put him under
at the house,
we'd take him
to the hospital,
open him up,
do our thing,
then slip him back
into his room
for the post-op
without him ever finding out
that we tricked him.
Some of that was implied.
It's unethical.
He'll be asleep.
He gets to make
his own calls
even if he's asleep.
Why are you siding
with him?
Oh, yeah, you're that girl
who likes broken people
because her husband died.
And since Chase isn't
all that broken--
Hey, why don't we operate
on his infarcted leg
while we're at it?
Who cares if he said no.
I was risking my life
to avoid becoming a cripple.
He's doing it to avoid
sunlight and fresh air.
We've got to make it
look good.
I know I'm a pain
in the ass.
I know it would have been easy
just to walk away, but...
you're a good person.
Count down from 10.
(Nozick)
10, 9,
8...
Let's go!
How you doin'?
- Better.
Great.
Everything else good?
Uh, everything involving me
kissing House is good.
Oh, god, you dragged it
out of me.
You're a genius.
It's no big deal.
He's a friend.
And I leaned on him.
It's funny.
I've leaned on friends
in the past.
Never leaned so far my tongue
fell into their mouths.
I don't think of House
that way.
I never have.
Why not?
You know exactly
how it would go.
It'd start off exciting.
We'd get caught up
in the novelty and the hostility
and the
forbidden forbidden-nessness.
And then we'd realize
that the flirty hostility
is just hostility
and his inability
to open up
is no longer exciting,
it's just frustrating.
And--and then it's
the inevitable blowup
and the recriminations
and we don't talk
for two months.
Yeah.
Well, it certainly proves
you've never thought
about House that way.
I get your point.
I will be more careful
with my tongue in the future.
That's not my point.
Maybe novelty and hostility
and forbidden-ness
doesn't have to end bad.
[pager beeps]
Gotta go.
What time you done?
We could try
that new sushi place
next to my house.
Why don't we stay
at my house tonight?
We always stay
at mine.
That's what I mean.
We--we used to split it.
What happened?
I don't know.
Closer to work.
- By five minutes.
And my house doesn't look
like it was decorated
by a drunk rugby player.
Well, we can discuss it.
- I hadn't really--
Why does it have
to be a discussion?
Can't you just
stay over?
You do know
they page me when that much
surgical equipment
is signed out.
He didn't consent.
He consented
to the surgery.
You think he's gonna
sue over where?
He won't even know where.
He'll wake up in his house.
He won't know a thing
about what happened.
Until he catches
a post-surgical infection
in his dirty apartment
and finds out we tricked him
and winds up owning
the hospital.
Why aren't you arguing
with her?
Because she's right.
I don't care where he gets
the post-op,
Just that he gets it.
Keep him here.
House.
You okay?
Yes.
We don't need to talk.
Your hand.
Huh. That's weird.
I usually don't get
the stigmata until Easter.
Please tell Dr. Chase
the patient's ready for him now.
Stewart, wake up.
It's Dr. Cameron.
If you can hear me, blink.
We were concerned
for your safety
so we brought you
to the hospital.
No, it's okay.
Why--why?
- Why...
I just wanted
to keep you informed.
I didn't want you
to have a bad shock
while you were recovering
from surgery.
Gotta get outta of here.
[machine beeps]
It's okay, Stewart.
Calm down.
Calm down. Stewart.
[machine beeping]
Stewart,
I'm gonna sedate you.
[machine beeping]
No!
Calm down.
Ah!
- I need some help in here!
Damn it!
Somebody get in here!
[machine beeping]
What did you do?
(Cuddy)
Well done.
Your patient
called his lawyer,
threatened to sue us.
He's now heading home
completely undiagnosed.
He'll soon be
on his way back.
He's sick.
He'll crash.
He'll lose consciousness.
I'll declare an emergency,
bring him back in.
Not anymore you won't.
His lawyer now holds
his health care proxy.
The next time we have
an emergency,
Larry Ruseckas, Esquire,
will be calling the shots.
(Cameron)
I made the right call.
If he'd flipped out
after major surgery,
it would've been worse.
The benefit of being boss
is that I don't have to argue.
You're all off the case.
What's going on between
you and Cuddy?
Bad lovin' gone bad.
Seriously. Why didn't
you argue with her?
She just threw us
off the case.
Because ignoring her
is a lot easier.
Convince the patient
to let us back in again.
See if you can clear
his blockage with lactulose.
If this thing kills him
before we can diagnose,
it won't be fun anymore.
Okay.
You gonna keep
working on this?
Yeah. I brought in
the case.
There is no case.
He's gone.
You've been tossed.
This is totally nuts.
He's incredibly sick.
We don't know--
Forget about the patient.
What is going on with you?
This is why we left
House's team
to avoid this constant flood
of pure craziness.
That's why I left House.
You got fired.
I'm sorry.
I know I let you down.
But you know who else
I let down,
pretty much everyone
who's important to me.
My boss, my old boss,
my boyfriend.
I did that for you.
I'm not gonna
let you down again.
It's like the red badge
of idiocy.
If the confederacy
had mosquitoes,
we'd all have southern accents
and I'd be paying Foreman less.
She kicked you
off the case.
This is what happens
when you don't address it.
She acts weird,
things get different.
You understand that different
implies difference.
She's tossed me
a million times before.
No, she always
chastises you.
And you'd always come running
to me to complain.
So you're acting
different too.
You're scared.
You are scared
to get involved.
How is that "scared"?
It's rational.
Emotionally mature people
who work together
should not date.
Guaranteed breakup.
Guaranteed ugliness.
Any relationship
that doesn't end in a breakup
ends in death.
Everything falls apart
in the end.
That's your worldview.
The corollary,
which you keep forgetting,
is that you have to grab
any chance for happiness.
Why does this matter
so much to you?
Cuddy and I are fine.
The only person
getting worked up here is you.
I don't want you
to be fine.
I want you to be happy.
I think if you dated her---
Are you familiar
with the adverb "vicariously"?
If I wanted to ask her out--
You did ask her out.
Last year.
Whatever happened there?
I don't know.
I wasn't interested.
Wrong. You were interested.
But Amber grabbed
your genitals first.
But now you're single,
and that makes you miserable
because you think it's too soon
for another relationship.
So you're gonna
make me miserable.
Please, get a girlfriend,
or a life, or something.
For me.
Better or worse?
(Cameron)
Worse. Drugs aren't working.
I think we should do
the surgery in his house
like we planned.
Well, then one of us
wasn't paying attention
because i thought that surgery
thing was just a trick.
We prepared the room.
We Hung the drapes.
It's probably ten times
as sterile
as any mobile
operating theater
you'd find in a battlefield.
We still need Trapper John.
Chase doesn't want
anywhere near this surgery.
Maybe you could talk
to him.
I can't understand
a word he says. Taub.
Doing anything later?
Blood in the field.
Not where I'm looking.
How am I supposed
to know where you're looking?
Here's a hint.
It's the bloody part.
The whole thing's
bloody.
It's a guy with a hole
in his body.
It's like you've never
done this before.
Use the suction.
I will.
And in fact I've
never done this before
because I went to med school,
not nurse school.
Hey, wanna see if your client's
actually made of money?
Cutting out last piece
of bowel.
Suture.
Mucosa's pink.
Flattened villi.
Intestinal atrophy.
It's Whipple's Disease.
Explains the seizure
and the stomach pain.
Little bleeder here.
Cautery.
Hey, wait.
The gas--
[gas flares]
That always happens
during surgery.
Just the gas buildup
in the blockage.
Nothing to sue about.
Treat him for the burns.
Put him on antibiotics
for the Whipple's.
He'll be fine.
Hey. That's nice
of you.
Hi.
He doing good?
Uh, burns are healing fine.
He's stable otherwise.
Good.
So, uh, I could stay
at your place tonight
if you'd like.
- I can't.
Well, you're not gonna
sleep here again.
You might have noticed
the lack of nurses.
Because you're not
on the case.
You can't really use that
as an excuse...
(Nozick)
Dr. Cameron!
Wait here.
Your stomach?
My legs are numb.
I can't feel them at all.
New symptom.
Peripheral neuropathy.
Got worse on antibiotics.
It's not Whipple's.
(Kutner)
Porphyria.
(Thirteen)
Liver's fine.
Amyloidosis.
We would've seen it
on the intestines.
What did we see
on the intestines?
Pink mucosa,
flattened villi.
It's not Whipple's,
it's gotta be Celiac.
Wheat allergy means
he's not absorbing nutrients.
Explains the seizures,
stomach, and now the nerves.
(Thirteen) We should run
a blood test for Celiac.
Not fast enough.
Not accurate enough.
Force-feed him wheat
then do an endoscopy
as it hits his duodenum.
See if there's an allergic
reaction.
His test just exploded.
It might be a tad painful
to make him eat.
That's House's point.
There's nothing diagnostic
about it.
He's trying to put
the patient in pain,
force him to come in.
It is a valid test.
So is the blood test,
which is painless.
(House) Foreman, listen to
that little voice in your head
that's coming
from the telephone.
Force-feed him.
Don't. You know House.
You know I'm right.
We'll do both tests.
I'm not here to play
matchmaker.
Okay.
House basically...
well, he accused me
of being interested
in you.
Oh, he's just trying
to change the subject.
I know.
But I do have...
I've always...
had...
some feelings for you.
Are you saying
you want to date me?
No. I-I--it wouldn't
be fair to House
and it's too soon
after Amber.
But you thought
you should just say it.
Yeah.
I thought you should know.
Let's have dinner
tomorrow night.
Okay.
Or maybe it would be better
if we just...
had sex.
Pardon me?
In front of House's office.
I mean, I don't want
to take any chances.
I assume the point of this
is to make him jealous
and make him realize
that he does want
a relationship with me?
Yes.
You think it'll work?
You're an idiot.
Trust me.
Everybody will be happier
if House and I
aren't dating.
You sure this is
the best test?
No. But you've kind
of tied our hands.
Soon as this hits
your intestines,
I'll look at it
through an endoscope.
Stewart, I know you don't want
to talk about this, but...
people who get shot
often get PTSD.
It's nothing
to be ashamed of.
It's very treatable
with drugs and therapy.
It's not PTSD.
My girlfriend was with me
when I got shot
and she died.
[groans]
I'm sorry.
But that's what I mean.
I lost someone myself.
I know it's traumatic.
No, what--what--what I'm trying
to say is that...
I was like this
before the shooting.
Since I was a kid.
Everything was
hard for me.
I--I didn't go out
that much.
And--and when I did...
I had panic attacks.
Like physical pain.
No, it was, like, worse.
It was like I was dying.
Then I met Angela.
She was the only reason
that I ever wanted
to go out.
But then she died.
and...
[groaning]
Blood test
will be done soon.
I'm guessing
that's a new technique.
Hey, you remember
that idea that Cameron had
about trying
to torture the patient
into admitting himself?
Pretty sure
it was your idea.
You want me to slow down
the test?
Wow. Everyone's got all these
great ideas today.
So you're thinking
patient won't leave
because leaving causes pain,
so we gotta make staying
more painful.
That actually makes sense.
You'll increase his pain,
but not enough
to make a difference.
He's on morphine.
- He's on morphine now.
Pretty soon he'll be
on less-phine.
'cause when you restock,
you'll actually be giving
Cameron IV bags of saline.
And why do you think
I'll be doing this?
Same reason you DDI
the surgery.
That was because
it was an emergency.
No.
It was because your marriage
is falling apart.
When you confess adultery,
things tend to go bad.
When one part of your life
does a Titanic,
you make a life raft
out of whatever's left,
which makes your job
more significant,
which is why you did
the surgery,
why you pulled
an all-nighter,
and why you'll do this.
She's having me sleep
on the Couch.
Just for a few nights.
I'm not doing this
to save my job.
I'm doing this to save
his life.
Right.
That's what we'll tell
everyone.
[mosquito buzzing]
[propane hissing]
Huh.
[explosion]
[incessant knocking at door]
Bzzz.
Have you considered
that it's not my place
you really want to be walking
into right now?
Ric Ocasek would kill me
if I--
Oh, you mean Cuddy.
Yeah, she's a little nuts.
But she's beautiful,
smart, funny,
and most important,
she can stand you.
Yeah. I came here to have
you lecture me on Cuddy,
not because there's
a killer mosquito
chasing me around
my apartment.
House,
there is no mosquito.
This is all about Cuddy.
Ah, she's bugging me.
Poetic.
Have you seen this bug?
Have you seen this bite?
No. What I've seen
is a suppurating wound
that you've scratched
and mutilated
into a gangrenous state.
Delusional parasitosis.
I am not imagining things.
House, you're
a drug addict.
You're always
imagining things.
You got bitten
the night you kissed her.
Your itching always gets worse
when you think about her.
You need to address this.
She's my boss.
No, you're not afraid
of authority.
You're afraid she actually
is right for you.
You're afraid
to take a chance
because it's too big
a chance.
If it doesn't work
with her,
then maybe there's
no one out there.
I am not rationalizing.
I'm better off alone.
Also, you seen her ass
recently?
You're not staying here.
Oh, come on.
- No.
You can go home.
Or you're going
to Cuddy's,
gonna ring her doorbell,
and you're gonna ask her
out on a date
like regular people do.
At 3:00 in the morning?
When do regular
people sleep?
Buh-bye.
Is he in enough pain
to come in yet?
No. Antibody tests back?
Inconclusive.
Then why are you here?
I missed you.
Endoscopy?
- Inconclusive.
Well, then do it again.
I know it sucks,
but I need to test
your stomach again.
(Nozick)
It's really hurting.
(Cameron)
I know. I'm sorry.
Try to get you
on your back
and have you open
your mouth.
I can't...
Oh. Oh, whoa.
He's out.
Anything?
No pulse.
Start CPR.
- Get the paddles.
[cell phone beeps]
Get the paddles!
Who are you calling?
Pizza. You like anchovies?
I'm calling the lawyer.
Genuine emergency.
He'll okay admission.
He's dying.
Exactly.
Hi. Sorry to wake you.
Your introvert
is having a heart attack.
If we don't restart
his heart...
He can survive 15 minutes
on oxygen and CPR.
We can get him
to the hospital in five.
[paddles charging]
Lawyer says yes.
Continue CPR.
2123 Holden green.
Patient with P.E.A.
- Clear.
Wait!
I got a pulse.
Cancel the ambulance.
He's stable enough
to stay here.
(Foreman)
His heart's back to sinus rhythm,
but it's bradycardic.
Taub's putting in
a temporary pacemaker.
It'll keep his heart
beating for now.
(House)
Hey, Cameron,
how would you like
your old job back?
I'm asking 'cause it's
the only way I can fire you.
Sorry. In ER, we like
to actually resuscitate
dying people,
Not just let them
flop around.
Could be Lymphoma.
We'd have seen it
on the abdomen.
It has to be a poison.
Organophosphates.
(Thirteen) We checked
the place over and over.
It's completely clean.
There are rose petals
in the front entry.
Unless he's eating
a bouquet a day,
he couldn't--
How clean?
- Very.
He probably has
a little OCD.
How often do you wash
your tub?
Every couple days.
Bleach and ammonia?
Yeah.
You know how kids
play toy soldiers
in the bath?
He likes to re-enact
the Battle of Cypress.
Three times a week
with real gas.
Ammonia and bleach
makes chlorine gas.
Highly fat soluble.
He lost weight
after the stomach pain.
Explains why his symptoms
kept getting worse.
Put him on parenteral steroids
and sodium bicarbonate.
(Taub)
Even if you're right,
that external pacemaker's
gonna fail eventually.
And I don't have the skills
to put in a permanent one.
Well, maybe the poison hasn't
completely shot his heart.
And you won't have
to feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
How am I gonna place
the leads in the exact spot
on the right ventricle
without fluoroscopy?
The force?
Taub put in
the temporary one.
You can do that playing
pin the tail on the donkey.
Permanent pacemakers
need precision.
So we can use
the portable X-ray.
It's not real time.
- Sonogram.
And what happens
when I put him into V-tach
because the sonogram
isn't precise enough?
He's dying.
Exactly why I don't
want to be the one
to kill him.
Thanks.
You knew I'd have
to say no.
But you came anyway.
You just wanted a reason
to be angry at me.
If there's something wrong
between us, then--
Forget it.
You know why
we spend nights
at my house?
Because when we spend them
at yours...
I could tell
you didn't want me there.
Why would I keep
inviting you over
if i didn't
want you there?
You always kicked me out
every morning.
You never offered me
a drawer.
You never cleared out
your closet for me.
I was just a visitor.
How long have you felt
like this?
From the start.
I know it's hard for you
because you lost your husband,
but...
I can't keep chasing you
forever.
[cell phone rings]
I just tried your house.
Where are you?
Clubbing. Good or bad?
Bad. Vitals are dropping.
The abdominal pain
keeps getting worse.
Means we were too late
with the treatment.
Tell the lawyer
he's off the clock.
We're done.
- You're giving up?
Call Taub. Tell him to pick up
some morphine.
There's no need
for the patient to be in pain.
He's on morphine.
No. He's on saline.
I figured you put him
on saline
so i switched him back
to morphine.
I love you.
When you reach puberty,
give me--
His abdominal pain.
That was on morphine?
Yes.
Is there something
that causes abdominal pain
that doesn't respond
to morphine?
I was right.
He is being poisoned.
What's this density
on his hip?
Just bone.
Think less boney.
[House snaps on
rubber gloves]
You think he's got
lead poisoning?
Explains the constipation,
the nerves, seizures.
Hold him down.
You're not gonna feel
a thing...
except excruciating pain.
[Nozick moaning]
[bullet shard bounces
off bowl]
[groans]
[bullet shard bounces
off bowl]
The mugger
used hollow points.
They exploded
and left fragments.
Your doctors missed a couple
hiding behind your hip bone.
It's no biggie.
Except years later,
they started to dissolve,
and then, biggie,
you started to dissolve.
(Cameron)
I'll start him on chelation.
The agoraphobia,
could it--
No. Lead wouldn't have started
to disintegrate
till years after.
But it could have
exacerbated the fear.
(Nozick)
I don't need to change.
(Cameron)
I know you think that.
But your life
could be better.
You--you--you'd
have choices.
He's lying.
About what?
About everything.
About his life.
He doesn't even think
he's happy here.
He's miserable.
I've got everything
I need.
Yeah?
Well, then why did Taub
find rose petals
in your entry hallway?
Struck me
as a little weird.
Thought it might be
medically relevant.
But it actually just told me
that you were pathetic.
The day you crashed
in your entryway...
was your girlfriend's
birthday.
You weren't there
for the mail.
You were trying to go
lay flowers on her grave.
Yeah, he's got PTSD.
Yeah, he's agoraphobic.
He's also a coward.
You want to change
your life, do something.
Don't believe your own
rationalizations.
Don't lock yourself up,
pretend you're happy.
Hi.
You were right.
About my husband.
It affected me.
It still affects me.
If you're saying
you'll never be able to--
I cleaned out
a drawer for you.
Like a
big one.
[strumming]
[flat key]
Subtitles by LeapinLar
Uploaded By
:: w e R c z ::
www.subscene.com