We're starting a fund.
Then you don't need me.
The man's injured.
He can't work.
His fault.
We're family.
We depend on each other.
We're not family.
We're co-workers.
He's not even
that anymore.
I can't believe
you just said that.
Can't come between a
man and his beer money.
See the big,
heavy machinery?
I'm sorry,
but he should give.
You gave.
Go back to work.
Paolo is the one who got you
off the night shift.
It's not
like I asked him.
Also covered for you
labor day weekend.
But hey,
it's America.
If you don't want
to contribu--
If you don't want to cont--
Oh, God!
Get an ambulance.
Good morning.
Don't wanna hear it.
So I take it you
did not ask Cuddy out.
Yeah.
- Yeah "I didn't" or yeah "I did"?
Whichever one means
you almost had me convinced
it was a good idea.
Oh.
Nothing to say?
- No.
No, you don't.
Or no, you don't don't?
Whichever one means no.
Is this some kind
of reverse--
No.
House?
16-year-old girl
with fluid in her lungs.
No previous trauma, lung,
or cardiac issues.
Gram stain was negative.
No bacteria, no pneumonia.
She's a factory worker.
Means she probably
works close
to a lot
of recent immigrants.
Thank God some of those
offshore sweat shop jobs
are coming back
to America.
She's an emancipated minor.
In a factory?
Either an Olympic gymnast
who busted her leg,
a child star who blew
all her sequel money on drugs,
or she's just
a lying runaway.
Her parents died last year.
No relatives.
To avoid foster care,
she got a G.E.D.
and got emancipated.
Could have picked up a parasite
from a co-worker.
She'd be having
G.I. problems.
Pregnancy's more likely.
Sparks a fluid overload,
hits the lungs,
causes the
pulmonary edema.
Her history says
she's not sexually active.
And our history says
she could be lying.
But not every teenager
is having sex.
But every teenager
is stupid.
Teenagers on their own
are stupider.
The girl's holding down a job,
makes her rent.
On the one hand,
Kutner's right.
Maybe she's
a sweet young thing,
not a screw-up
lying through her teeth.
On the two hand,
a pregnancy test
only takes five minutes,
and we no longer
kill rabbits.
So in conclusion,
shut up,
do the tests.
What else?
- Drugs could damage the heart.
Pressure imbalance allows fluid
to build up in the lungs.
Tox screen's clean.
For drugs used recently.
Not for drugs used
before recently.
16 doesn't automatically mean
a risky lifestyle.
Didn't we just have
this conversation?
Kutner trusts her.
Someone else doesn't.
So, in conclusion,
shut up.
Check her home and work
for toxins or drugs.
Kutner and Foreman,
do an echo.
Find the extent
of the heart damage.
Kutner can do
the echo on his own.
Yes...But he'll be
very lonely.
So I have to ask why?
I've been asked to help run
a clinical trial.
That okay with you?
Good for your career.
Great for your street cred.
What's in it for me?
You have four doctors
and never more
than one case.
It means I have time
to work on other things.
And they'll have
more chances to step up.
Stand on their own
and if there's
an emergency with Annie,
should she wait until
you finish grooming lab rats?
If there's a problem
with Sophia
or any other patient,
you know I'll be there.
The patient is
my priority.
No.
Oh, do you want a reason?
Clinical trials take time.
Your time is my time.
I told you,
I don't do drugs.
Still a good idea
to check your heart.
Something else
could have damaged it.
You find it hard
being all on your own?
Having to do
everything without--
drugs to ease my pain?
That's not what--
teenager on her own?
I wouldn't trust me either.
I meant it must be hard.
No one there
to back you up.
I know you're trying
to be nice,
but I'm not into
the whole pity thing.
I was actually doing
the "I get it" thing.
I lost my parents
when I was six.
It doesn't go away.
But it gets easier.
You learn to deal.
I still get nervous when there's
a knock on the door.
Always think
it's the State Trooper...
with more bad news.
You already got the worst news
and survived.
That's sorta the upside.
Your heart's healthy.
Isn't that good news?
For your heart, yeah.
But it also means we still
don't know what's wrong.
Checkbook balanced,
place spotless.
Looks like she builds
her own furniture.
If you're this grown up at 16,
what happens at 30?
You turn back into a kid.
Like Kutner.
Kutner's not that bad.
He needs everything
to be nice.
He wants to see
the best in everyone.
Kitchen's clear.
Yeah, friendly is
a dangerous thing.
There is such a thing
as too trusting.
Corollary is there is
such a thing
as not trusting enough.
Too much, you get hurt.
Not enough, you don't live.
So the object in life
is to get hurt
just the right amount?
Excuse me if I don't go
out of my way
to take relationship advice
from you.
And trust...
should be earned.
Bong means nothing.
Drugs are irrelevant.
Relevant if
she's taking them.
Even if she is:
irrelevant.
Echo showed no heart damage.
Would that be the echo
that Foreman chose
not to run with you
after I dashed his
new drug discovery dreams?
You mad at me because you think
Kutner screwed up the echo?
I didn't screw up
the echo.
I know.
No structural heart damage.
So if it's not the heart...
- It's the heart.
Didn't you just say it's not?
Not all heart damage
has to be structural.
Drugs could have caused
intermittent tachycardia.
Irregular heartbeat would
account for the pulmonary edema.
The edema was acute.
Vasculitis makes more sense.
There's no sign
in her blood work.
And if she had vasculitis,
she'd be too weak
to work in a factory.
She builds her own furniture.
You think she skips work
because she's feeling
a little weak?
She needs steroids.
Steroids could cause
an irregular heartbeat,
making her current one
irregular-er-er.
Foreman.
Start her on beta-blockers.
The rest of you,
do anything
that isn't starting her
on beta-blockers.
Start her
on the treatment.
Page me if you need me.
Irregular heartbeat causes blood
to back up behind the heart
and into the lungs.
The beta-blockers
keep this from happening.
I thought the test showed
my heart was fine.
It's tricky.
An arrhythmia can come and go.
So you don't believe me
or the test.
You guys are more cynical
than I am.
We found the bong
in your apartment.
You went into my apartment?
Extended drug use
can damage--
The bong belongs
to my ex.
It's why he's ex.
That doesn't mean
you didn't use it.
No.
You have no reason
to trust me.
You have to do your treatment.
The other possibility is
you have vasculitis.
The treatment
for that is steroids.
If you've been using drugs,
if they've damaged your heart
and I start you on steroids,
they could kill you.
I haven't used drugs.
I'll get the steroids.
Why are you here?
I owe clinic hours.
No, you don't.
I'm here because House
doesn't want me to be here.
I'm guessing he said no
to the clinical trials.
He didn't need to say no.
He just wanted
to say no.
House did something solely
out of self-interest?
That's freaky.
Don't suppose
you'd want to override?
No.
What do you think
this is gonna prove?
Does it matter?
Just figured you could use
some help down here.
And you spending two hours
wiping noses will annoy House.
If that is your dream,
God bless.
If you want to prove
you can do his job
And something more...
his puke is red.
That's blood, right?
That hurt?
What about that?
Four days he's been like this.
It's just getting worse.
Maybe he just needs to poop.
Evan!
- What?
Worked last time
I had a stomach ache.
It's actually
a smart idea.
Which is why that's
the first thing
the other doctors checked.
His insides are clear.
Anyone else sick
in daycare?
No.
How 'bout his friends?
- No. No one.
What's happening
to him?
Not sure yet.
Don't worry.
I've got an idea.
You can make him better, right?
That's my plan.
You need to make him better.
Stay the hell away
from me!
Just calm down.
What happened?
- I adjusted her IV,
and she went crazy.
Don't touch me!
Leave me alone!
Sophia, it's okay.
We're here to help you.
Just stay away from me!
Don't touch me!
I said, don't--
Get your hands off of me!
Get your hands--
Beta-blockers don't cause
psychotic breaks.
She's not on beta-blockers.
We started her on
haloperidol. She's stable.
Lab tests showed
the delirium wasn't caused
by a metabolic problem.
Means we still don't know what caused it.
- Yeah, we do.
Nice job, Foreman.
I didn't switch her meds.
But your decision
to stick it to the man
clearly inspired Oliver Twist.
I treated her based
on the symptoms she presented.
You treated her based on
empathetic orphan syndrome,
and almost killed her
in the process.
She wasn't on steroids
long enough
for it to cause the delirium--
it's a new symptom.
One that rules out
vasculitis.
And arrhythmia.
The psychotic break caused
a surge of adrenaline,
but no irregular
heartbeat.
Heart's not the problem.
We're both wrong.
So what causes lung issues
and delirium?
And is not based
on wishful thinking
That she's safe and happy?
Prinzmetal Angina.
Silent and unhappy is better
than vocal and unhelpful.
If you'd run the echo
that you didn't run
before giving her
the beta-blockers
That you didn't give her--
if you'd listened
to what Kutner just said,
you'd know it's not
a heart problem.
I'm not talking about her heart.
I'm talking about her head.
Prinzmetal Angina
doesn't affect--
No reason it couldn't cause
an artery in the brain to spasm.
Leads to the delirium
and the pulmonary edema.
Foreman, give her ergonovine
to cause vasospasms,
and run an MRI to see
which artery's dancing.
And when I say Foreman,
I mean...Foreman.
I want his signature
on the paperwork.
I want videotape.
I want photographs of him
with the patient
and today's newspaper.
Set her up.
When you're ready--
House wants you
to do the procedure.
When you get everything set up,
page me.
That's really a camera?
Pretty cool, huh?
This can go places
the other scopes can't.
Jonah,
I need you to swallow
this pill.
Don't wanna.
It doesn't hurt. Promise.
Jonah, please.
To help make you better.
I don't want to be mean,
but if you don't do this,
we'll have to make you.
It's a power pill.
It's not just a camera.
It makes your muscles grow.
Like the vitamins we take.
Except this was made
with a secret formula.
You did great, sweetheart.
You're very brave.
Jonah's lucky.
I was pretty cruel
to my little brother
When I was your age.
Why?
I guess I thought
that's what big brothers did.
Obviously, I was wrong.
Is he a doctor too?
No.
Does the pill tickle,
sweetie?
He can't feel it.
What's funny, your brother?
What's happening??
I don't know.
How you guys getting along?
And you suddenly
care why?
House was asking questions
last week.
I assume Foreman needs us,
and he's worried
that if we're sniping,
we might be distracted.
That's kind of insulting, isn't it?
- Very.
You're obviously fine.
I need a differential
for uncontrollable giggling.
He's four.
They laugh.
Yeah.
Nothing like diarrhea
and bloody vomit
to put you in the mood
to goof around.
I've looked down one end
and up the other.
All the tests came back clean.
I can't figure this out.
- You can't?
Don't you work
with three other doctors
and a grouchy gimp?
This isn't House's case.
Just so you know,
whatever you're trying to prove,
it won't be enough.
Gotta go.
Sorry.
You didn't miss much.
No spasms yet.
Nothing in the anterior
or posterior cerebral arteries.
How much longer?
Just a few more minutes.
Were your foster homes
all around here,
or did you have
to change schools?
Is chatting about
lousy foster parents
Supposed to relax me?
Left middle cerebral artery
looks good.
My foster parents were great.
I think most
foster parents do it
because they want to do
something decent.
which is why you didn't
get emancipated.
Nothing around
the vertebral artery.
No sign of spasms.
But that's odd.
How'd you find out
about your parents?
I told you.
State Trooper.
Look at that.
Arteries are fine.
You can stop.
Not that.
I forget,
did he come to your house
or call you down
to the station?
Came to my house.
I cried into the guy's shirt
for an hour.
Wow.
FMRIs tell us
where the blood flow is.
You were using
your limbic region.
It lights up
when we use our imagination.
It doesn't light up
when we're telling the truth.
Your parents aren't dead,
are they?
I risked my job, put you
on a different treatment--
I didn't lie about the drugs.
- Then why lie about your parents?
Because I wish
they were dead.
I got emancipated
because my dad raped me.
And my mom pretended
it didn't happen.
No signs of spasm,
impeded blood flow,
or brain dysfunction.
It's not Prinzmetals.
All the FMRI showed is
House was right.
She was lying.
Only relevant if it can cause
pulmonary edema and delirium.
We find out
our patient's been raped,
and that's your response?
Is she a psych patient?
Rape could mean STD.
Thank goodness one of you
doesn't have a heart.
Maybe if we all stopped
wringing our hands,
we could solve this thing
and let her live to have
a few more nightmares.
Gonococcal endocarditis
would explain
the pulmonary edema,
the delirium.
No sign in her bloodwork.
Could be lying about the rape.
Yesterday,
you were all BFF.
Now you think
she's pathological.
Yesterday I had no reason
to doubt her.
If she'd been honest with us
from the beginning--
She lied about dead parents
because it's better
than rapist parents.
You find that unsympathetic?
That's it.
What's it?
Her whole life's a mess.
What rhymes with mess?
It's not stress. She has none
of the usual manifestations.
No hormone imbalance,
no cardiac--
Yeah, she's drowning
in her own lungs,
and she's delirious.
She's a picture
of emotional health.
Severe emotional stress
can lead to asymmetric function
of the midbrain.
Explains the delirium.
Interruption
of the brain-heart coupling
could cause pulmonary edema.
Even if House is wrong,
the treatment's basically
anti-anxiety meds.
Hard to argue with.
Yes. I agree.
It does explain everything.
Thirteen, load her up
on diazepam.
Foreman, make sure she does it.
Thirteen, make sure
he makes sure.
I went to Cuddy's house.
But I didn't go in.
Went home without ringing either
her metaphorical or actual bell.
Huh.
You're processing.
I'm scrubbing.
"Huh" means processing.
"Huh" means acknowledging.
If you prefer, I could say
"ha," or "hmm," or--
No insights?
No opinions?
You're disappointed.
- You made the decision.
I can't tell you
what's right for you.
Seriously?
'Cause last week you could.
Last year you could.
Seems to come
pretty easy to you.
Do you want me to tell you
what you should do?
I want you to stop thinking
that acting inscrutable
makes you anything
other than annoying.
Interesting.
Holding things in
can give you cancer!
Kid's in daycare.
Could be meningitis.
No fever,
no stiffness, no rash.
You check his thyroid?
TSH and 3 T4
were within range.
Ruled out all
the usual suspects.
Nothing's usual
for a four-year-old,
and as fun as this is,
it feels like we're your goomah.
Your feelings are hurt?
Either you can handle
both these cases or you can't.
If you can't,
it's dangerous and stupid.
On the other hand,
stomach cancer.
Leiomyosarcoma.
Long shot.
Altered mental status means
porphyria's more likely.
No abdominal pain?
Cancer explains
the lethargy,
The GI symptoms-
neither's perfect.
Then we test for both.
And by "we," you mean
the collective "not you."
Thanks.
Severe stress scrambles
the way the brain
communicates with the rest
of the body.
I have a problem
with my brain?
Not exactly.
The problem would be
with your body chemistry.
Where's Dr. Kutner?
There's four of us.
It's my turn.
I'm sorry I lied
about my parents.
You did what you thought
you had to do
to protect yourself.
If we're right,
we should see
a change in your lungs
pretty fast.
Then we can figure out
how to manage your stress.
It might help to turn him in.
File a police report,
get closure.
Won't help.
Not addressing what happened
won't make it go away.
Yeah?
What do I have to do
to make it go away?
I didn't mean that.
I just mean that you--
I addressed it.
I got away from him.
Reporting it
just labels me.
"Girl raped by dad."
It doesn't
have to define you.
It's how you see me.
That's why you're treating me
with tranquilizers.
Not anymore.
Stress wouldn't change
your urine color.
Labs show the brown urine
was caused by shredded red cells.
So what messes with her lungs,
her mental status,
and runs her blood
through a wood chipper?
Factory lunch rooms
aren't the cleanest places.
Coulda picked up e. Coli.
Or Shigella
from the restroom.
Either would account
for the red cells, the delirium.
But not the original
lung symptoms.
Legionnaire's could,
and cause delirium.
No, her sodium's normal.
What does her furniture
look like?
Said it was homemade.
Old boxes, what?
It was wood
nailed together.
The wood have
little dents or holes?
I didn't see any
in the bookshelves,
But they were painted.
The desk did.
Looked like she had stapled
stuff all over it.
Holes means that it
was pressure-treated.
Sawing or burning it releases
arsenic into the air.
Into her lungs.
Tests didn't show--
because it found a cloak
of invisibility hiding--
Arsenic gets absorbed
in the internal organs
so it doesn't show up
in the blood tests.
Test her hair.
If it's positive,
chelate it out of her blood.
No cancer, no porphyria.
You paged me
with negative test results?
Yes, because it means
we're done.
Since we still don't know
what's wrong,
this kid has
a real problem.
Talk to House?
Not his case.
There's a point when Cameron
and I aren't enough.
We're not there.
We need to run
some more tests.
A week ago, he was
a happy little boy
playing with his brother,
and now he can barely lift
his head.
We'll figure this out. I just need--
Mom!
Help!
We need a crash cart!
What's going on?
He's in cardiac arrest.
Get them outta here.
Clear.
Nothing. Go again.
He's back.
Foreman.
We're there.
Chelation's complete.
You're arsenic-free.
So I can get outta here?
In the morning.
That's it?
No advice?
No "be careful
out there, kiddo?"
You want my advice?
Want is one thing,
expect's another.
I wish I could tell you
what to do.
But you're strong.
You've make good choices.
You'll be fine.
Thanks.
Need four milligrams lorazepam!
After the seizure,
we ran a new MRI.
This is Sophia's brain
three days ago,
this is her brain today.
Lesions.
Magical lesions,
which appear out of nowhere.
She was cured,
then she wasn't.
Lesions grew
too fast for cancer.
Could be infection. MRSA.
WBC count would be
through the roof.
Put the arsenic back.
You wanna treat a patient
nearly poisoned to death
by giving her more poison?
Just because we call
something a poison
doesn't mean
it's bad for you.
It was killing her.
But since she's still dying,
the arsenic obviously
wasn't killing her.
And since she's
now getting worse,
the arsenic was obviously
fighting the killer.
It's a hero.
We should be organizing
a parade.
so what does arsenic treat?
Syphis.
Before penicillin,
the treatment was arsenic.
We already ruled out STDs,
and even if we were wrong,
that much arsenic
in her system
would've wiped out
the syphilis.
Acute promyelocytic leukemia's
still treated with arsenic.
APL explains the lesions
and why they appeared
after we took the arsenic out.
So, put the arsenic back.
We still have
a problem.
Arsenic slows leukemia,
but it can't cure it.
If she wants to see 17,
she's gonna need
a bone marrow transplant.
Best match would be
a sibling or a parent.
Biopsy a lesion,
confirm that she's dying,
then load her up
with arsenic.
Keep her alive till you can
convince her that rapist marrow
and rapist-enabling marrow
work just as well
as the unleaded stuff.
We need to talk.
This about the case you
didn't want me to know about?
Cuddy?
Foreman.
You didn't flinch
when you found out
about a sixteen-year-old
who could be dying
in the next few days.
Means you're here about someone
even younger dying even faster.
He needs you.
But he has you.
This boy is going to die.
You selfish enough
to let it happen?
Pot calling
a kettle a pot?
You're a hypocrite.
If our job is to find out
what's killing patients,
you'd help this kid.
But you'd rather play
mind games
to prove you're the only one
with magical powers.
Wanted something all your own?
Now you got it.
Your disengagement won't work.
I can see that.
You think that when you tell me
what I should do,
my instincts are
to push back,
so that by not telling me
what you think I should do,
I'll do what you think
I should do.
I sound convoluted.
Disengagement is neither
artful nor effective.
So my not doing anything isn't
causing you to do anything?
Right.
I'm okay with that.
No, you're not.
You are designed
to have opinions
and to force them on people.
I'm starting
to sound desperate.
Don't screw
with my stuff.
I just need a donor
with the same blood type
or something, right?
Actually, bone marrow's
a little more complex.
The best donors
are immediate family.
But those donor banks
have thousands of names.
Your parents' similar DNA
gives you a much better Chan--
No.
If I do this,
I'll owe my life to them.
It'd mean everything else that
had happened was somehow okay.
They don't deserve that.
They're not in my life.
If that means I'm dead,
then I'm dead.
I have Huntington's Disease.
I'm dying.
I don't know when it'll happen,
but it'll be sooner
than I ever planned.
And I'd do anything
to stop it.
Because the only way
to make anything right,
the only way
to make your life matter
is to live as long
and as well
as you possibly can.
Have you ever been raped?
No.
Don't try to walk
in my shoes
and I won't try
to walk in yours.
You had no right.
To try to convince her
to do the right thing?
To lie to her.
- It's a true story.
Who cares
if it's not my story?
It's my life.
- It's her life.
Point wasn't I'm dying.
Point was she should live.
You should have told her.
Instead you tell her
to call the cops,
give her stats
on DNA markers.
Everything's by the book.
Nothing's ever personal.
Trying to sleep here!
Biopsy confirmed APL.
She needs
a bone marrow transplant.
Run the donor banks.
I'm going home.
We need to track down
her parents.
I assume she's already said no
to that idea,
or there'd be no need
to screw up your courage
before saying it.
Children who've been through
trauma can't think clearly.
trauma and are dying--
guess I'm the only one
who cares about patient rights.
What she wants
could kill her.
What she needs
could save her.
Our job is to find out
what's killing patients,
not treat them
for chronic idiocy.
Idiocy is what's killing her.
And since we can't cure that,
I'm going home.
We could save
this patient,
but all you care about
is getting your answer.
Your point being?
Taub and Kutner can check
the donor banks.
I'm gonna find
her parents.
Can't see
why you're surprised.
You push against House,
he's gonna push back.
Against me, I get.
His ego's killing
my patient.
You liked this case because
he wasn't looming over you.
The decisions were yours.
Only difference now is
he decided not to loom.
Doesn't change the fact
that your patient's dying.
What are we missing?
What's not in the file?
The mother, overburdened
at the end of her rope.
Makes her kid sick
so someone else
will take care of him.
Sympathize with her.
Munchauseny proxy?
She brought him
into the clinic,
was with him when he went
into cardiac arrest.
The brother
would have noticed,
said something.
Evan's even more protective
than she is.
Then maybe
it's the brother.
He's eight.
Could be jealous.
He's the opposite
of jealous.
He includes Jonah
in everything he does.
Makes sure he eats,
brushes his teeth.
I think we gave him
an idea.
Either that or he's off
to kill House.
Mr. Velez?
Yeah?
I'm Dr. Remy Hadley from
Princeton-Plainsboro Hospital.
We're treating your
daughter Sophia for leukemia
and we need to test
both you and your wife
for bone marrow donation.
I'm sorry, you said you
were from Princeton-Plainsboro?
I know this is unexpected,
but time is short and--
What's going on?
This doctor says
you have leukemia.
I don't have leukemia.
Sophia Velez?
Yeah?
Sophia Isabel Velez?
Yeah.
Do you know
something I don't?
Just that liars lie.
You stole her identity.
To protect myself.
So they can't find me.
We can protect you.
But we need to find
your parents.
Why?
You have my blood.
You don't need my name
to find a donor.
You're a minor.
You obviously forged
the emancipation papers.
Even if we had a donor,
we'd still need your parents'
consent to treat you.
Can't you just pretend
you didn't go to that house?
That you didn't find
that girl?
Calling your parents
doesn't mean a family reunion.
You don't even
have to see them.
When I get sick enough,
it'll be an emergency.
You'll have
to give me a transplant.
Even without consent.
An iron overdose?
From his vitamins.
If I'm right,
we can treat him tonight.
He'll be back to his old self
in the morning.
But...
They're children's vitamins.
I--I only give him one.
I know.
I thought more
would make him strong.
I didn't mean
to make him sick.
He's gonna be okay.
He's gonna hate me.
Well, that's the great thing
about brothers.
You can make mistakes,
and they'll still love you.
Donor list turned up
a partial match.
So treat her.
It's only a three
out of six.
So don't treat her.
She may not last
the week.
Partial's better
than nothing.
So treat her.
She'll reject it.
And she'll be too weak
to try again
when a better match
turns up.
It's my turn now,
right?
If a better match
turns up.
Well, when you decide,
get back to me.
She's scared.
Not scared enough.
Tell her the thing
about emotional reactions
is they're definitionally
irrational.
Or stupid.
Might wanna phrase that
in your own words.
She wants to deny her parents
the satisfaction
of saving her life.
That's your rational explanation
of her emotional response.
That was
her explanation.
That makes sense.
How long did it take her
to come up with that?
It was her immediate reaction.
That doesn't make sense.
The fact that it makes sense
doesn't make sense?
Emotional is immediate.
She went to rational first.
Means there was
no emotional to process.
You're saying she's lying
about being raped?
Wouldn't be her first.
She lied about one trauma
to cover a worse trauma.
So...what's worse than rape?
Hi, I'm Dr. House.
What did you do?
I don't--
Something happened,
but it wasn't rape.
Believe whatever you want.
You're scared,
and stubborn,
and you don't like people
feeling sorry for you.
Why not?
I don't want pity.
I just wanna be normal.
But you know you're not.
You need people to see
how independent you are,
how well you're coping.
So they won't see the lost,
hurt little girl.
Because that's not
what you see.
You see someone
who did something terrible...
who deserves to suffer.
Who doesn't deserve
to live.
What did you do?
Eventually,
we'll find your parents...
if only
to deliver the body.
Then they won't care.
You're an idiot.
You'd rather die
than face your parents
because, what,
you broke their Faberge Egg?
I killed their son.
I killed my brother.
I was supposed
to watch him.
He was in the bath.
I could hear him laughing.
Every time they look at me,
it's like I kill him again.
If you don't take
your parents' bone marrow...
you'd be killing
their other child.
If they don't hate you now,
they will then.
I don't care.
Sure you do.
You want someone to tell you
it was just an accident.
That it's not that bad,
but it is that bad.
And you know it.
There's nothing you can do
to change that.
But there is one thing you
can do to not make it worse.
# someone #
# reaching for me now #
# through #
# the dark reaching for me now #
# you need #
# someone to hear you
when you sigh #
# someone #
# to wipe away
those tears you cried #
# someone to hold #
# you 'neath the darkened sky #
# someone #
# to love you more than I #
If you're here to celebrate
the kid's bone marrow
transplant working,
you missed cake.
I want to do
clinical trials.
Already had
this conversation.
I've proved that I can work
two cases at once.
I can do this.
And I'm doing it.
Okay.
Okay?
Just like that?
Can I give
my reasons later...or never?
Three days ago
you said no.
you asked me.
Now you told me.
Can't say no
if it's not a question.
Nice thing you did
for Foreman.
He speaks.
He deflects.
I almost cost
a four-year-old his life.
Well, you knew Foreman
would figure it out.
Did I?
You just needed
to prove it to him.
You're an ass.
But a noble one.
I sound clever.
Thank you.
Your little game
didn't work.
I'm not Foreman,
and you're not me.
You wanna talk about her?
Nope.
All right.
You're gonna be okay,
House.
Good to know.
Edited by LeapinLar