I still can't believe
you talked me into this.
[Chuckling]
come on, honey.
You're gonna throw him off.
It's okay.
I'm almost done.
A little more light
on your hips.
Oh, god.
Why couldn't you have
come up with this
Before I had two kids?
[Laughs]
you look amazing.
Okay, I think...
Yeah, I'm done.
Wanna come take a look?
[Laughing nervously]
I can't.
You first.
No, we'll look together.
I don't understand.
I--I thought--
What the hell is that?
Honey.
It's okay.
This is not
what we discussed,
Or what I paid for.
I don't understand.
I think this is one
of the best I've ever done.
I want my money back.
I'm sorry,
but this is not
Some department store
photo studio.
And this is not my wife.
Yes, it is.
You asked me to paint her
Exactly as she looks.
That's exactly what I did.
Uhh!
Honey!
Oh, stop it!
What's going on?
Brandon!
That check...
Better be
in my mailbox by friday.
Or I'll be back.
Come on!
What happened?
I don't know.
They saw the painting
and they just freaked out.
Brandon, what is this?
What do you mean?
It's her portrait.
What's wrong with it?
Why's this in here?
First column, last entry.
Today is going to be
a good day.
This him?
Yes.
No.
She means are you
the private investigator
Whose bills I've tried
to slip through
As medical expenses?
Oh. Hi.
I'm lucas douglas, p.I.
This hospital's not putting
a private investigator on retainer.
Nor is it gonna pay
any more phony repairs on vending machines,
Cryostats, or elevators.
Information
saves lives.
Saving lives saves money.
No, saving lives
costs money,
Which is why
I'm trying to make sure</I there's still some left!
You want your own
personal p.I.,
You're gonna have to pay
for him yourself.
Sorry.
No, I understand.
Hey, I--I like
the shoes, by the way.
Thank...you.
You don't like her shoes.
You like her legs.
It sounds less creepy
If you say shoes.
Less creepy, more gay.
That's my firm's motto.
What is a cryostat?
No idea.
Whoever fixed ours
is about to get stiffed.
There's
no distorted perspective in any of his
other recent works.
Not much talent,
either.
So the symptoms
just came on.
Acute onset visual agnosia  points to a stroke
or brain tumor.
(Taub)
m.R.I. Revealed no stroke
or brain tumor.
We should do another
with contrast.
If he's like the other
struggling artists I've known,
He's also into drugs.
We should--
What are you looking at?
Apparently a moron.
One--E.R. Routinely tests
for drugs.
If it was positive,
We wouldn't be looking
at this file.
Two--Who pays 12% interest
on a car loan?
How did you--
Did you run
a credit check on me?
No...that would be illegal.
Interestingly enough,
Paying someone
to run it for me, though...
What?
It's part of my job.
Your job
is to diagnose patients.
Which I do
with the team.
How am I supposed to know
how best to utilize
That team if I don't know
everything about them?
Say the van gogh turns out
to have neurosyphilis,
And our last vial of penicillin
is in a storeroom
At the end
of a 20-Mile hallway with a two-Foot high ceiling.
With a two-Foot high ceiling.
You've discovered
that one of us has been
Hiding the ability
to stretch or shrink themselves?
No.
I would never out someone's
super powers.
This, on the other hand...
You crawled 20 miles?
My name's
in the guinness book.
I'll bet that really
impresses the babes.
I didn't do it
to get the babes.
No, that would cheapen
the purity of your achievement.
(Foreman)
sorry to interrupt,
but we have a patientwith a probable
brain tumor.
Who needs an m.R.I.
With contrast,
We've established that.
What do you got on taub?
I got nothing on taub.
(Thirteen)
could also
be environmental.
We should check his studio
for toxins, mold, fungus.
Taub's wife,
on the other hand--
(Foreman)
house...
That's enough.
Dad's right.
This is no time for gossip.
A patient desperately needs
our help.
Check his head
and his house.
Can't lucas--
Nope.
He's very busy.
(Foreman)
if there is a tumor,
this test will show us--
Is that stuff dangerous?
This is just
the contrast material.
There is a small risk
of an anaphylactic reaction.
I could stop breathing?
Don't worry.
We're prepared to dealwith whatever happens.
You know, I did some drawings
this morning,
And they seemed fine.
So maybe it was just a reaction
to something I ate.
How many people you know
have reactions like that
To something
they ate for breakfast?
But if I'm
getting better--
You will continue
to get better.
If you're not,
we need to know why not
So we can start treatment
immediately.
Baby, let them
do the test.
Can lead poisoning
cause visual agnosia?
(Taub)
not without lead
showing up in the blood work.
Nothing
in the medicine cabinetexcept some harmless
toiletries.
No signs of mold
or fungus anywhere, either.
You think house really
got something on your wife?
No. Not that
I'd care if he did.
Wait, your wife's
doing the doorman in your bed,
And they're
sweating all over the sheets
that you paid for and--
My wife's not doing
the doorman.
How do you know?
We don't have a doorman.
And I just do, okay?
Drop it.
In college,
my friends and I came up
with an inverse-Square law.
Sounds like
a real fun group.
The girls who you think
are the most inhibited...
Straight arrows...
They're the ones
you hook up with.
Are you saying
my wife's a slut?
I'm saying if my wife
was a slut, I'd wanna know.
(Kutner)
his place was clean.
(House)
so is his head.
Even with contrast,
no masses, no lesions.
A neurological symptom with no apparent
neurological cause.
Time course means
we can rule out cancer and m.S.
Just leaves toxins
or drugs.
You called thirteen
a moron  for thinking
it was drugs.
Yeah, but when she said it,
she had other options.
And I really
just wanted to segue into her stupid loan
and your--
A cavernous angioma
in the brain could leak.
Once the blood
gets reabsorbed,
The pressure goes down,
the symptom goes away.
He'll never consent
to petrosal vein sampling.
Really?
He was nervous about
an injection of contrast.
Is his girlfriend hot?
And I'm not talking
fever here.
I mean, is she all
curvy and perky?
Very...and if he dies,
It's good news
for all of us, but--
That explains
why all his paintings suck.
And what's wrong with him.
Where are you going?
To tell him he may have
a massive brain tumor.
But he doesn't.
I know.
I'm not a moron.
It's drugs.
You seem to have
a massive brain tumor.
Who are you?
He's dr. House.
He's pleased to meet you.
We found no trace
on any of your imaging,
So we need to cut
your head open.
It's risky,
But it's the only way
to save your life.
No.
Wrong answer.
I'm not allowed
to say no?
You're not allowed
to not be terrified.
There's only
two good reasons not to be terrified
in a hospital.
You're delusional.
But then you're not afraid
of contrast material either.
Or you know you're fine.
Since we haven't told you
you're fine,
You obviously have
information we don't have.
What drugs are you on?
His drug tests
were clean.
Drug tests only test for drugs
they've made tests for.
What are you
talking about?
Hottie thinks
that he's a great artist,
Selling art
to the rich and tasteful.
She's stupid enough to be fooled
by the canvases,
But bank accounts
don't lie.
He needed money.
There's not many jobs
you can do
That don't require time,
training, and intelligence.
And I know
you're not a news anchor  or a supermodel,
'Cause those jobs
seldom cause agnosia.
He's a guinea pig.
Companies pay him to test
their untested drugs.
Did hottie go for a pee
or coffee?
Either way,
I don't think you should waste any time on denials.
The clinical trials
were supposed to be safe.
The drugs are about
to be approved by the fda.
Drugs?
How many trials are you on?
Three.
Admirable.
Not many idiots
have that much ambition.
You've been symptom-Free
since your admission,
So whatever you took has probably
cleared your system now.
You'll be fine.
Keep him overnight,
just to make sure,
And get the names
of all the trials he's been in.
You gonna tell heather?
Couldn't, even if I cared enough
to want to.
Not bad.
You almost made it
the whole day.
What'd you find out?
The point is to see
how everyone reacts.
I'm gonna go get
the rest of the gang.
Cut the crap, house.
Your wife has
a separate bank account
In her name only.
She's been making
weekly cash deposits
For about a year now.
No withdrawals...yet.
That's it?
A bank account?
A secret bank account.
What makes you think
it's a secret?
Because if it wasn't,
You'd call it
"the" bank account.
Damn.
Always forget to use
the right article when lying.
It's not secret.
We're refurnishing.
We set the budget,
set up an account.
I just couldn't make it
to the bank the day we opened it.
You're spending almost
$100,000 on furniture?
Yes.
What happened?
I don't know.
He was fine, then all of
a sudden, he started seizing.
He said you told him
he was better.
What's happening?
What's wrong with him?
She is hot.
Obviously the drugs
weren't out of his system.
None of these drugs,
Nor the drugs
that they're derived from,
Are known
for causing seizures.
By themselves, no.
But three unproven,
untested drugs?
This is like the mod squad.
No one could stop them.
Ridiculous
that they let people take potentially dangerous drugs
for money.
Just to short circuit
that discussion,
People should not be testing
drugs because they're desperate.
But people won't test drugs
unless they're desperate.
We need drugs
to save children and puppies.
Ergo, we need
desperate people.
Ergo, welfare kills
sick children.
First drug--
Why don't we call it
bisexidrine?
Clinical trials
involve experimental drugs.
Means they don't have
comforting, catchy names yet.
Just random, unmemorable
trial numbers.
Go ahead.
Bisexidrine is designed
as an anticoagulant.
Phase one indicated
some risk of nausea,
E.D., and insomnia.
Second drug.
Cuckoldisol.
She is having an affair?
Worse.
Sex can be dismissed
as hormonal or emotional.
Can be easily regretted.
Money is always
a calculated decision.
My wife has
her own bank account
That house doesn't think
I know about.
Shocking.
Discuss.
Drug b
is an autoimmune treatment.
Almost no side effects.
But even if it's doing
what it's supposed to be doing,
It doesn't mix well
with anticoagulants or anticonvulsives.
(Kutner)
which is the third drug?
World's-Sorest-Knees-Isil.
Cuddy used to have
that title, by the way.
(Foreman)
there's a million ways
these drugs could interact
If they're doing
what they're supposed to.
If they're not,
two million.
And it'd be interesting to know
which of those interactions
Was causing the problem.
Unfortunately,
we don't have to.
We just have to stop
the interacting.
If we don't know which--
Stop them all.
Put him on dialysis.
Clear out his system.
Rapid detox
risks arrhythmia,
Another seizure,
hepatic failure.
Difference is, we know
what those risks are.
Put him on dialysis.
Dialysis.
Use that for kidney failure,
right?
Don't worry.
Your kidneys are fine.
He's not worried
about his kidneys.
He's worried about how
He's going to explain
the dialysis to his girlfriend.
I just don't want her
to worry.
You mean you don't want her
to leave you?
What's wrong with that?
I love her.
It's not like I've lied to her
about anything important.
I am an artist.
I've sold plenty of paintings
in the past.
It's just...
I've hit a bit of
a dry spell lately, is all.
So tell her that.
He can't.
He wants her
to be happy too.
He's telling her
what she wants to hear.
You didn't know?
No.
What are you gonna do?
She's not sleeping around.
She's not gambling it away.
She hasn't even spent
any of it.
So I don't see a reason
to do anything.
You don't think
a conversation might--
How many people
do you know
In completely happy
and fulfilled relationships?
None.
I am.
Most people cling to some storybook notion
of what a relationship is.
You can't have
an imperfect thought.
a private zone.
You can't--
Steal money
and hide it away in a secret account?
She makes me happy.
I make her happy.
It works.
Because we
don't do storybook.
And I don't plan to poke
into her business.
You were right
about the dialysis.
He made it
through the night without any more seizures
or visual symptoms.
And I am going to be
just as rightafter breakfast
up in my office.
The only difference is I'm gonna be right
in front of other people.
Which means you're not here
to talk about the medicine.
You can screw with me
all you want at work,
But stay out
of my personal life.
What did she say?
Did you just hear
what I said?
I heard the part about you can screw with me
at work all you want.
Want my advice?
Of course not.
Good, 'cause I have no idea
what you should do.
I only know
what you're going to do.
You're gonna--
I said I didn't want
your advice.
I said this is not advice.
You are going to forgive her
for opening that account,
And you're going to confess
everything you've done,
And then you're gonna beg her
to forgive you.
What purpose
could that possibly serve?
None...which is why
I'm not saying you should.
But you will.
(Lucas)
what's your end game?
Where are you?
At the track.
That's, like, six miles away.
How cool are these things?
I feel like an idiot.
I'm not giving you
any more of my stuff.
You have those
night vision goggles?
No.
You're lying.
You like making him
miserable.
You like driving people
away from you.
He deserved
to know the truth.
There was no truth
until you dug it up.
You do know
that stuff exists
Even when
you can't see it, right?
It was a truth
that mattered to him
And a truth
that mattered to her.
Why did it matter to you?
(House)
first of all,
stop saying "a" truth.
There is only one truth.
That may be true for you.
Miserable people
save more lives.
If your life has meaning,
Your job doesn't
have to have meaning.
Screw-Ups
are more palatable
If you have someone's arms
to go cry in.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Usually I have more of a fight
on that one.
So why are you
Making taub miserable?
I just said!
He left his last job
to save his marriage.
If his marriage falls apart,
You think he'll be
working harder for you?
Or you think he won't be working
for you at all?
(Foreman)
his head and neck
are completely swollen.
I need a trache kit.
His throat's closing.
Can't find any landmarks.
Just start cutting.
An exploratory trache?
We don't have a choice.
Got it.
Here.
(Kutner)
his face is so swollen it squeezed
his tear ducts shut.
We've been lubricating
his eyes by hand.
We started him on steroids,
iv and cream,
To reduce the swelling,
But it's having
limited effect.
Negative for thrombosis
and chagas.
Could be infection.
Culture's
still negative.
Could be his immune system's
on hyperdrive.
Cytokine storm.
Why would you pay
for a three-Year gym membership
And only go twice?
Sorry.
You guys still diagnosing?
Thought we'd finished
hours ago.
You remember, when we decided
it was the unproven,
Unapproved cocktail of drugs
he's been downing like...
Like a cocktail.
He just completed
a total dialysis.
If it was the drugs,
he'd be better.
Or he'd be worse.
I take it none of you
saw trainspotting.
You think swelling
is a symptom of withdrawal?
You think it's a coincidence that three new symptoms
cropped up
As soon as we
took him off the drugs?
It's possible
some of the symptoms--
Either the drugs
are the answer,
Or the drugs
are a coincidence.
If it's one, we have to find
a better way to detox him.
If it's two,
we have to know
Which symptoms
are withdrawal-Related
Before we can formulate
a diagnosis.
Which means we have to find
a better way to detox him.
So how do we do it?
Hair of the drug
that bit him.
That's ridiculous.
If it is the drugs,
they're dangerous,
And they've already caused--
That's why we're gonna put him
back on the drugs,
And then
wean him off again.
Just much slower.
Why are you looking at him?
Try it out.
You heard the boss!
Go!
Taub--
I didn't talk to her.
Why are you--
Excuse me.
Uh, sorry.
He does look like me,
doesn't he?
You gave him your hat.
I needed you out of here,
so I could go through your desk.
Of course.
Nice blouse.
I really like
that color on you.
Tell house that if he wants
to know what I'm doing,
All he has to do--
It's not house, it's--
It's me.
I was--I don't know.
I was thinking
maybe we could get together
For a drink or something.
I wasn't sure exactly
what you like to do.
So I thought...
you'd spy on me.
No. No.
Not spying.
More like research.
I think it's a good idea
To get to know
a little bit more about a woman before you ask her out.
Show you care about more
than just what she looks like.
As romantic
as you make that sound,
I'm pretty sure that
what you're doing is...
Not so much caring
as creepy.
That's not fair.
You were scrounging
through my desk.
What the hell
am I gonna find out?
You went to michigan.
You like your sandwiches
a little light on mayo.
You stay in touch
with your mother.
You rented
the english patient
And you gave money
to amnesty international.
There's not one thing
I can find out in here
That you wouldn't tell
a coworker while riding
in an elevator.
I'm not a creep.
I just thought
you seemed interesting.
[Whispering]
I'll go now.
Yeah, these, um...
I'll give you
embarrassing info on house.
In exchange for--
No, no need for a date.
You'd be employing me,
So I'd have all the time
in the world to ask you all about you,
And it would fall under
the category of socializing
Instead of creepy stalking.
And I'd be paying you?
I know it's weird.
But if you pay me
while I check you out,
It's--It's all cool.
And you get value,
you get leverage against him.
Help you keep him in line.
You think I need help
keeping house in line?
No.
Nope. Sorry.
This hospital can't afford--
Oh, whatever
you can afford.
How'd you know
I liked roses?
I was in your house
last night.
No! I'm kidding.
Who the hell
doesn't like roses?
I forgot to tell you.
The parker quartet's gonna play
at the library fundraiser.
That's it?
It was your idea.
They'll be great.
You okay?
I couldn't find
the letter opener.
I went through some
of the drawers in your desk  looking for it.
There were a bunch
of statements  in there from
Jefferson mutual.
I was so close.
To what?
You've got $83,000
Socked away
in a secret account.
Not anymore.
I wanted to keep it
a surprise, but...
I bought you a car.
The one that...
That I...
I knew you would never
buy it yourself,
So...
I've been saving.
And it's gonna be delivered
on friday.
You are amazing.
Lucky you.
We've gradually
reduced your dosage.
You're actually
drug-Free now.
I feel great.
Thanks to you.
All part of the job.
Your blood pressure's
normal.
Can you sit up?
Hey!
What are you--Ohh!
What happened to his face?
Question is what happened
to his hormones?
We're gonna need
an ice pack in here!
(Kutner)
we can rule out the clinical
trial drugs at this point.
His system has been
completely cleaned twice.
Unless the drugs found
a hiding place under the stairs.
Drugs could have set offa dormant neurological
condition.
Good point.
Coming clean
can cause a lot of damage.
Alienation, divorce.
My wife's buying me a car.
I was talking
about the patient.
You were wrong.
Divorce was metaphorical.
(Foreman)
what about kluver-Bucy
syndrome?
Bilateral lesions
in the temporal lobes,
Visual agnosia
and hyper-Sexualityare the key symptoms.
Good thing he's got
that girlfriend.
If it's kluver-Bucy,
his brain'll melt down,
He'll try to swallow
his own hands,
And she can
take care of him
For the rest
of his talentless life.
You owe me an apology.
Any rationalization
you had for meddling
in my private life
Disappeared when
she had good reason--
You're right.
Fact is,
nothing I said applies.
You had no reason
to forgive her.
Therefore, no reason
to seek forgiveness.
No reason to be an idiot.
Kluver-Bucy
wouldn't explain the seizure or the cytokine storm.
Withdrawal complications.
Then again, she is handing you
a giant gift that you don't think
you deserve.
The fact that the m.R.I. Showed
no lesions on the temporal lobe
Tends to rule out your lesions
on the temporal lobe theory.
The damage can be
a circulatory issue rather than structural.
We wouldn't see that
on the m.R.I.
Foreman's right.
Go call your wife,
Tell her
you're not coming home
'Cause you have
to give the patient a cranial m.R. Angiogram.
Then say good night
and hang up.
Odd that a man
who can't run would own so many pairs
of sneakers.
You mind hanging this up
when you're done?
I have to find something
embarrassing about you.
No, you don't.
I ordered us indian.
Not too embarrassing,
Just something credible.
Well, if you
hand her that...
She's not gonna
need you anymore.
Well, if I don't
hand her anything,
She'll think
I'm incompetent.
I don't care if she thinks
you're incompetent.
This isn't gonna work.
It's worked so far.
No, I'm no good at lying.
I know.
That's why your cover
Is that you
want to do her.
I like her.
I don't wanna do her.
Then what's the point
of liking her?
I meant I don't just
want to do her.
I like her.
What do you think
you're gonna find out about her?
Something...personal.
Something embarrassing.
I've spent half my life
negotiating with that woman.
Anything I can use
to scare her into saying yes.
Okay.
Okay?
You're okay
with being paid twice to facilitate blackmail?
I'm okay.
I don't believe you,
but I'm okay.
You're doing this
for the same reason I'm doing this.
We'll see
who gets there first.
(Kutner)
here it is.
Circle of willis,
the vessels are narrow.
Narrow for you,
normal for him.
If there were problems
with the vessels,
He'd have had symptoms
long ago.
Not if something else
changed.
Like?
His heart.
He could have recently gotten
an intermittent arrhythmia.
I know "heart" and "head" start
with the same three letters,
But you gotta read
all the way to the end.
The experimental drug is causing arrhythmia,
which causes low blood pressure.
Combine that
with those narrow vessels,
The brain
doesn't get enough blood.
That causes
all of his symptoms.
If we can trigger the arrhythmia
and identify it,
We might be able
to stop it from killing him.
Been home?
No.
Good.
Do an e.P. Study.
Find the arrhythmia.
We're gonna insert
three electrocatheters into your heart.
Tell dr. Hadley
I'm sorry.
She understands.
And you should
tell her yourself.
Maybe I should
tell heather about--
You're gonna be fine.
She's just so supportive.
And so great.
All I do is lie to her.
What happens
if you tell her?
I don't know.
You love her, right?
More than anything,
and she loves me.
If you open your mouth,
one of two things happens.
She either forgives you
or she leaves you.
At best, you wind up exactly
where you are right now.
It's noble
to want to confess.
Really, it is.
But if the result's
just damage and pain,
That's not noble.
That's selfish.
(Taub)
stimulate right atrium.
No more conduction.
How long you plan
on keeping me from going home?
Until you're convinced
I'm a different person,
One who won't
do anything stupid?
Guilt fades quickly.
By wednesday,
you'll be fine.
Right ventricle.
And why do you
want it to fade?
Why do you suddenly care
about my marriage?
Because...
if it ain't broke--
You obviously think
it is broke.
it ain't.
Your marriage is like
a broken toaster.
The bread keeps popping out,
and you keep calling it toast.
Which is weird,
because you've put your bread in a lot of toasters.
And apparently,
you don't see any difference.
It's kind of fascinating.
[Rapid beeping]
he's going into v-Tach.
What's wrong?
Good news--
The test is working.
Your heart's freaking out,
But it's cool
that you're still conscious.
Try to overdrive.
[Beep]
didn't work.
(Kutner)
this might burn a little bit.
Charging to 60.
Clear.
Going again,
charging to 120.
Are you dyeing your hair?
No.
House, clear.
Right.
The hair is growing in red.
(Taub)
his heart rate
is stabilized.
Does your theory include
any genetic mutations
That could cause his hair
to change color?
Either he's lying
about dyeing...
Or just...dying.
Red hair means
it's not kluver-Bucy.
Melanin affects hair color.
What affects melanin?
Hormones.
Hormone panels
were all normal.
Age.
He's turning
prematurely crimson?
A genetic disorder.
Waardenburg syndrome
causes arrhythmias
And can change
hair color.
And make you deaf.
Next.
Found a long
qt interval.
I think it's
romano-Ward syndrome.
Explains the irregular
heart rhythms.
But not the ginger nut.
If he's got romano's,
He's got at least
five gene mutations.
Not a big leap to think
He has others
that would give him the hair.
It also gives him
the likelihood
Of sudden
and unexpected death.
Beta blockers don't work.
His heart can't handle
an I.C.D.
Pete best.
Good god!
Has none of you ever read
a history book?
The original
beatles drummer.
A bunch of nerves
Controls the tempo
of the heart.
They're all playing in time,
Except one dude
can't keep the beat.
Wrecks the whole thing.
So we hire ringo.
Pete best was actually
a great drummer,
But I assume
you mean the patient needs a cardiac sympathectomy?
Probably should have
just said that, huh?
Start cutting nerves,
you risk his swallowing,
Vocal cords, sweating.
So he saves a fortune
on karaoke machines and deodorant.
You think he's stable enough
for surgery?
If he was,
he wouldn't need it.
Do you have
any brothers and sisters?
One sister.
He told me he was
on the lacrosse team.
In high school.
In college, he just cheered
the lacrosse team on to victory.
How was your relationship
with your dad?
Fine.
You have
three more questions.
How was your relationship
with your mom?
Fine.
When did you lose
your virginity?
Not something
I'd discuss with coworkers
In an elevator.
And...
You know, don't you?
A bit of a wasted
third question.
'Cause the answer
is "know what?"
Okay, bear with me here.
Because some people
sometimes consider my thought processes
complicated.
I'm into you,
'cause you're hot.
And smart.
In that order,
but both are needed.
Photos can be retouched.
And house
is an evil genius,
Which makes this photo
suspicious.
And yet you're
not suspicious.
Which means either you're not
smart enough to be suspicious,
In which case,
I am less interested in you,
Or you're
not suspicious because
You know this is actually
a doctored photo of house.
In which case,
I am more interested in you.
But I am wasting my time,
because you know
This is a game
we are playing on you,
And I am busted.
And I'm screwed.
I know the photo's a fake.
And I know this is a game.
I'm sorry.
Too bad.
Good-Bye.
So you knew
that I wasn't
Gonna give you
anything worthwhile?
A-And you were never gonna
give me anything worthwhile.
Then why did you bother
coming out with me?
I...wanted to screw
with house.
By wasting my time?
That doesn't make sense.
No, uh...
There must be
another reason.
Is it okay if I sit
back down here?
(Hadley)
your heartbeat's
out of control.
We need to surgically
sever the connection between your heart
and brain.
We believe it's necessary,
But you need to know
the ramifications.
You'll never be able
to feel angina.
You may not know
if you have a heart attack.
You may not be able
to get help in time.
Where are my
regular doctors?
Regular doctors?
Dr. Taub
and dr. Hadley.
Why aren't they
telling me this?
Brandon, I am
dr. Hadley.
And this is dr. Taub.
What are you
talking about?
I've never seen you before
in my life.
(Taub)
we can't do the surgery.
We're back to where
we started.
Visual agnosia.
We need to reexamine
neurological disorders.
Something's
slowly progressing.
This isn't progressing.
It's there, then it's not,
then it is.
It's a new symptom,
intermittence.
It's irrelevant.
Since when
is a new symptom irrelevant?
Since it points
towards the same disease.
Intermittence can fit
with romano-Ward.
We still need to do
a sympathectomy.
(Taub)
maybe we missed something.
Toxins.
When?
When you checked
every bottle,
Every can,
every tube of paint?
Or when you
detoxed him twice?
Maybe there is a batch
of toxic paint that he used up
a few months ago.
Then he would have been
sick months ago, not now.
He's lost weight
since he got here.
That's a symptom of trying
to cram hospital food
Down a throat
he can barely get air down.
It's not a symptom,
But what if the toxins
were stored in his fat cells
A year ago,
And now they're being released
into his bloodstream?
So where you gonna get
this old paint?
City dump?
On his old paintings.
We know he
hasn't sold one in ages.
But there weren't many
in his studio.
He's hid them somewhere.
If you're wrong...
He could drop dead
from romano-Ward at any moment.
You okay with that?
Just give me a few hours.
You got one.
I need to talk
to him alone.
It's about your work.
Your paintings.
I need to look at
All the ones
you've sold recently.
Honey, can you
give us a minute?
To talk
about your paintings?
Brandon, please.
Tell me what's going on.
I've only sold two paintings
in the last...three years.
Since we met.
One was to my cousin.
I've been making money
enrolling in drug trials.
Two, three at a time.
Why did you lie to me?
I wanna be, uh...
The way you look at me.
The way it makes me feel.
Uh, I wanna be...
What you see...
When you look at me.
You think
I'm that shallow?
When I look at you...
I see you.
So...
Where are the ones
you didn't sell?
It's not the paint,
it's the drugs.
He's not on the drugs.
I know it doesn't
make sense,
But I'm looking at his paintings
for the last six months.
They're normal
april, june, and august.
But they're distorted
may, july, september.
Every other month,
he was having visual agnosia,
Because every other month
He was on all three drugs
simultaneously.
The statinwas one month on,
one month off.
I don't know why the symptoms
keep coming and going,
But it is the drugs.
They're hiding
under the stairs.
In the fat?
That doesn't make sense.
These drugs
aren't fat soluble.
I said stairs,
not closet.
What was the last drug
he was on before
the drugs he was on
When the symptoms
started?
I'm not sure.
I think--
Antacid.
How do you know?
It makes sense.
Also, I'm looking
at the file.
Yes?
It's dr. House.
Uh, wake him up.
We're done.
No, no--He says
he needs surgery,
But not this one.
Did he give
any specifics?
Abdominal surgery
to remove a...bezoar.
It's like a hairball,
But it's made up
of undigested food.
You can get it
if your stomach acid's low,
Which brandon's was because
of an experimental antacid.
Fruit and vegetable fibers
and skins
Get stuck together
and form a ball.
It gets sticky,
ferments, grows.
It starts sucking up
some of the pills he'd taken.
Some are never
heard from again.
But some get released.
For the last week,
it's basically been giving him
Massive doses
of all three at once.
And that...
Is why I won't let cameron
buy a cat.
He should be fine.
Are you glad
he told you the truth?
Yes...of course.
But...
Were you happier
before you knew?
About ten more feet.
I do know
what it looks like,
So maybe this whole
blindfold thing--
Shh--My gift,
My rules.
Bump.
All right, if you don't like
the color,
Apparently we can
exchange it.
But I'm hoping.
You ready?
Do you like it?
Baby, are you okay?
We need to talk.
She didn't buy it.
Damn.
So you didn't get anything.
Nothin'.
We probably overstepped.
You're really not
the cheerleader type.
On the other hand,
I figured she probably
wouldn't figure me as the "photoshopping
"A photo and planting it
in an obscurecollege paper" type either.
Heh, yeah.
About that.
I took a little trip
to your alma mater.
You took a little trip 150 miles.
Online, by phone.
I meant I did research.
That's a real photo,
isn't it?
Wow, that is humiliating.
There was a girl.
Even more so.
That's too bad.
You wanted her to see you
in a different light,
And...not only
didn't she see it...
She didn't even believe
it was possible.
You know,
people hate people who have theories
about people.
You want me to back off?
Would you?
I barely know you.