Excuse me.
I've been waiting here
for over an hour.
All I need is a refill
on my migraine medication.
We'll get to you
as soon as we can.
You can get to me now.
It'll only take you
two minutes.
You're not an emergency.
This isn't
an emergency room.
And it's not gonna go
any faster
By pissing me off.
- Got a minute?
- No.
A routine checkup can wait.
What else you got?
I'm consulting
on some clinical trials
That involve
C.N.S. Compounds.
While it's true
that no sometimes means yes,
In this context...
One's a new Huntington's drug.
Phase three trials
are showing real results
Delaying neuronal
degeneration.
I can probably get you in.
No, thanks.
Are you doing anything
about your disease,
Following any kind
of program?
No. Nor am I looking
for a consult.
Lisa cuddy, M.D.
Dean of medicine
Excuse me, I'm looking
for dr. Cuddy.
Well, she's either not here,
or she's under the desk.
Either way, you're gonna have
to wait outside
Until I'm finished.
Do you know when
she'll be back?
Yes, which is why
I need you to get out
And leave me alone.
Sorry.
Nice try.
Love to help.
Shut up!
You wanted to see doctor-
I said shut up.
I'm sick,
and I want to know why.
I want the best doctor
in this hospital here, now...
Or I'm gonna start
killing people.
What seems to be
the problem?
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷³¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
House 509
-=Ææàãðü×öä»×é=-
·­òë: ð³¶ô:
ê±¾äöá:îò°®ê¨ðäð¡s
Close those blinds.
You, push the sofa
in front of that door.
You, move that table
in front of the other door.
Now!
- Okay,
- Okay.
Just move it.
You know, you don't have
to point the gun man.
We're gonna do
whatever you want.
No, we're not.
House...
That's a bathroom
you're barricading.
It might come in handy,
Especially since
you've cleverly decided
To take a bunch
of sick people hostage.
Do it!
My medical records.
I need you to read them.
You really think that
reenacting dog day afternoon
Is the best way
to get diagnosed?
I'm sure you've been waiting
for hours
In an uncomfortable chair,
But you should watch the movie
all the way through.
I've been to 16 doctors
in the last two years.
Had three full-Body cts
And two mris,
Seven blood panels,
and one homeopathic consult.
And all that was missing
Was the threat of violence.
What's missing is an answer!
I can't breathe!
I'm tired...
all the time.
I get skin rashes,
and heart palpitations,
And insomnia.
That's a cool constellation
of symptoms.
It could be
something minor.
At least compared to life
in prison,
Which is what you seem
to prefer
To seeing
16 more specialists.
Shut up and do your job.
You barely looked
at the file.
No need.
Symptoms...
Those are the things
you keep whining about.
Tests-Negative,
or you wouldn't be here.
History-Shy, quiet kid.
Kept to himself.
Collected comic books
and missing children.
Excuse me, my wife feels sick
to her stomach.
Next time pack some heat,
and maybe we'll look into it.
I'll be okay.
If you ask me,
Keeping an open line
of communication
Is the best way
to resolve conflict.
What kind of breathing
problems?
Shortness of breath.
And sharp pain
when I inhale.
So you figured
your wife left you
Because you couldn't breathe,
right?
Me, I rarely
kidnap someone
Unless I've got
a serious health problem.
Since you're not almost dead,
it means you're armed
Because you're blaming something
other than your health
On your health.
I've never been married.
Got a match?
Why?
Because I'd rather not
stand here
While you try and negotiate
a hostage trade
For an incentive spirometer.
- I'll look in cuddy's desk.
- Stay out of the desk!
Cuddy doesn't smoke.
But he does.
- No, I-I don't.
- Right.
You just brush your teeth
with coffee grounds.
Look, sir, I've never smoked
in my life, okay?
Jerk.
Hey!
You figure that two people
snuck weapons
Into the clinic today?
I'm sorry.
It's just...
I got a lighter.
Slowly.
Hold it out
as far as you can.
Try to blow it out.
Decreased lung volume.
Heart palpitations,
fatigue, stomach pain.
An intermittent rash-
Could be 100 things.
If you add on
that final symptom,
It can only be
pulmonary scleroderma.
What final symptom?
Those were all my symptoms.
Last one is the 16 doctors
who missed it.
Simple alkylating agent,
case solved.
See you on visitor's day.
Crime scene!
House,
what's going on in there?
- Is everyone all right?
- About to be.
Assuming he's not lying.
But he seems like
a pretty straight arrow to me.
I'm gonna need
some propofol
To prove that it's
pulmonary scleroderma.
Then we all get
to go home.
Propofol?
- You sure
- Have one of the guards bring it in.
No, no guards.
No cops.
Uh, I'll go get it.
No one's leaving.
She's not a cop?
Dr. Cuddy brings in
the drugs.
Alone.
She might be armed.
I'd have her deliver it
shirtless.
Who is it?
Oh, god, House.
Maybe we should wait for-
Guys
with even bigger guns?
Who know how to talk
to armed-
Say good-Bye
or I shoot her.
Roll up your sleeve.
Give it to someone else first.
You're the only one
who needs it.
Give it to someone else.
If it goes in okay,
You can give
a second dose to me.
I don't care who.
Just pick someone.
Again, had your brilliant plan
included a roomful of hostages
That don't have fetuses,
bacterial and fungal infections,
Leaving their immune systems
too week to deal
With the metabolic strain,
Or are already
on pain killers
That have fatal interactions...
He's not on pain killers.
I heard him tell her
in the clinic.
Aw, come on, man.
Don't take it out
on us.
You got a problem
with doctors?
Take it out
on the doctors.
Give it to her.
She's sick.
You are a very large creep.
Take off your shirt.
Satisfied?
Fine.
Roll up your sleeve.
You think I'm an idiot?!
Huh?!
That's what you think?!
I thought I had
a little more time
With a guy that size.
You're not gonna do
anything.
You still need me.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Come on!
What are you doing?
He didn't do anything.
You're right.
I need you.
I also need you to know
you can't screw with me.
It's for you.
Lieutenant bowman,
princeton swat.
Dr. Lisa cuddy,
dean of medicine.
We just heard a gunshot,
But I haven't been able
to make contact.
We'll handle that
once we secure our perimeter
And set up
our positions.
By "perimeters,"
I assume you mean snipers?
We have to put an end
to this.
Got a husband in there
or a loved one?
Uh, no.
Don't worry, we'll decide
when to start shooting.
House is gonna get
someone killed.
The guy's ready to kill
for a diagnosis,
I can't think
of a better doctor
To be trapped in there
with him.
How 'bout someone
who's not gonna
Keep pushing
the whack job's buttons
Until he cracks?
It's House.
- Joe's bar and grill.
- It's foreman,
And every fellow you've had
in the last five years.
What causes
low lung volume,
Heart palpitations, fatigue,
stomach pain,
Insomnia, and a rash?
This is pathetic.
If I strap a bomb
to my chest,
Do I get seven doctors
attending to me?
Dr. Robert chase.
On the off chance you have
some brilliant escape plan
And are the vengeful type.
Do you think he's
the only guy in new jersey
With an unsolved illness
and a pistol?
I'm not playing this game.
Seriously?
You're walking out?
No, he's just kidding.
He's right here.
Throw me that marker,
will you?
Chest pain,
the lung problems,
Fatigue, rash.
Sounds like chronic
lung infection.
Heart palpitations
and fatigue-
Could be a cancer
that's spread from the lungs.
Next!
If his diaphragm's
not working,
Maybe his nerves
are freezing up.
I think he's going
into shock.
???
Guys with guns go first.
Next!
The shortest distance between
stomach pain and insomnia
Is bad circulation.
Plus troubled breathing.
Could be a heart defect.
You needed to write
four things down to remember 'em?
It's not my wall.
You're gonna get
some special deliveries.
Foreman,
we're gonna draw blood.
Run tests for infection
and cancer.
Cameron, comb through
his medical records.
See if any of his past
900 medications
Could have screwed up
his heart.
Taub and kutner,
Go to his apartment,
Check for neurotoxins.
873 marshall,
south brunswick.
Back window's unlocked.
Giving out your address.
Clearly you're not going
back there.
Means you do have
an end game.
I'm lieutenant bowman.
How's everyone doing
in there?
Got one lower limb
flesh wound,
Another guy unconscious.
Unfortunately,
not the guy we hoped.
We're gonna need someone
to deliver his blood.
It's gonna be hard
to play doctor-
Shut up.
Open that blind.
Just a few inches.
- Why me?
- Just open it. Open it!
Why me? Anyone can do it.
Why pick me?
Get back!
I will kill her
Unless you back the hell
out of there now!
Interesting.
Anybody else hear those guys
outside?
Anybody?
He's got hyperacusis.
What does that mean?
It means we have
a favorite.
It's nerve related.
Amped-Up hearing
could be linked
To nerve palsy.
Puff out your cheeks.
Come on.
Big mug shot smile.
Left side
facial weakness.
Seventh nerve palsy.
Plus intermittent
rashes.
Plus migraines.
It's post-Herpetic neuralgia.
Herpetic?
You think I have herpes?
I'm not judging here.
This thing is just as likely
to be caused by chicken pox.
I need proof now.
There is a test.
It's dangerous and painful
While the treatment
is safe and painless.
But you make a good point.
You need proof now.
I'll order up the test.
If you have neuralgia,
you won't feel it going in.
It only hurts
if your diagnosis is wrong?
Win-Win.
Jason,
Don't hang up the phone again.
You're gonna send in...
Capsaicin.
200 micrograms.
And two syringes this time.
And we'll give you the blood
and his records.
No more meds, jason,
And no deliveries
without something in return.
You've gotta give us
a hostage.
You can have two.
Great.
Then I'll send an officer
right in with the transfer.
Everything gets brought in
by dr. Cuddy.
Jason, I'm not gonna let her
do that.
First-Don't use his name
so much.
It doesn't sound reassuring,
it just sounds creepy.
Second-Come on,
he's not gonna shoot
The one person he trusts
to bring in his medication.
He's gonna shoot hostages
if she doesn't bring it in.
I'll get back to you.
The guy's demanding that
you do all the transfers.
Okay.
Okay?
What am I supposed to say?
You're supposed to say no.
It's not your job.
If you got a conflict here,
If you have stakes in this that
you're not telling me about,
Then I can't trust you.
Got it.
I'm okay.
Can you tell him
I'm coming in now?
Who's taking
the first dose?
Anybody here got a long-Standing
case of neuralgia
That's killed their nerves
so this won't hurt at all?
How bad does it hurt?
You're looking to be
the hero?
Well, I've been beaten up
a lot,
And I can handle pain.
How old are you?
The guy's got a gun.
I think that covers
the parental consent issue.
And that stuff
can also cause
Nerve
and muscle damage.
No way am I taking
that crap.
- Come on.
- You have to.
It's the rules.
I'll do it.
This is a level
of risk taking beyond anonymous
girl-On-Girl action.
They're patients.
I'm a doctor.
With a degenerative,
drug-Unfriendly illness.
Everything's not some
fascinating character flaw.
This is a genetic flaw.
This is your
Huntington's speaking.
This is you waving
a white flag at the world.
Yes, I have
a shortened lifespan.
Another reason why I'm
objectively the right choice.
I would have laid money
you had herpes.
Your turn.
So why are we here?
We've ruled out
immediate risk of death,
Lost love.
That just leaves...
Work?
You're defined
by your work.
But you kept seeing doctors,
kept missing time.
Couldn't focus.
Maybe you made
a huge mistake...
Got fired.
I just want an answer.
I know.
I'm asking why.
Nerve paral
Guy knew he wasn't
coming back.
Everything's laid out
for us.
I'll check for toxins
in the kitchen.
He must have $6,000, $7,000
in unpaid medical bills.
I've got debt too-You don't
see me acting like a lunatic.
There's no excuse
for what he's doing,
But you've got
millions of people
Thousands of dollars in debt
because they're sick-
At least one of them's
gonna do something inexcusable.
Especially if it works.
White blood cell count's
normal.
It's not infection.
Lung infection
So either his heart's
on the fritz,
Or he's got cancer.
Found a picture of his mom.
She's got a droopy eye,
fat face, thick neck.
Classic signs
of an upper-Lobe tumor.
Or she's just ugly.
There are also classic signs
of an adrenal problem.
It's his heart.
- You can't be sure what
- His neck. Distended jugular.
What are you doing?
I am going to try
to strangle you
Faster than you
can pull a trigger.
He needs to check your pulse.
It's racing. 160.
We need to get paddles.
Or maybe we could
just do nothing.
If I get any weaker...
And they don't fix it...
- I'll shoot... you!
- Don't.
- He didn't mean to-
- Shut up!
All of you.
What are-
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?!
- Carotid massage...
Gotta slow your heart.
It's 200.
- Well, get the paddles.
- Uh-Uh.
Whole point of those things is
to make your muscles contract.
They don't discriminate
against trigger fingers.
Nobody gets my gun.
- Send in paddles!
- Don't!
Get the damn paddles!
Or I'll shoot you.
Threatening to shoot the guy
who's diagnosing you
Makes a lot of sense.
Actually doing it,
not so much.
Give him your gun
so he can save you.
Just let him die.
Bill, stop.
We can cardiovert chemically.
If we don't know what kind
of heart rhythm it is-
If we don't try something,
he's gonna kill someone.
- I'm gonna get the drugs.
- No one goes anywhere!
If she doesn't come back,
???
You, come here.
All right...
30 seconds.
She's gonna go.
She's gonna come back.
She should go.
He'll kill him.
But not her.
That your version
of morality?
If you don't think your life is
worth more than someone else's,
Sign your donor card
and kill yourself.
Shoot me.
- You really want-
- Yes.
No, no!
She just needs time!
She just needs more time
to find the right-
- The right drug-
- It's me.
She takes it first.
Adenosine slows the heart.
Which is fine,
if it's beating fast like yours.
Not fine if it's normal,
like hers.
Following the math on this?
She takes everything
I take.
I don't want anything
that cross-Reacts.
The martyr's heart is
beating dangerously slow.
Are we good to go?
Your heart's back to normal.
No tachycardia.
No sign of a heart defect
at all.
But you're sweating.
I nearly had a heart attack.
You're surprised
I'm sweating?
On one side of your face,
but not the other.
What does that mean?
A tumor is pressing
on your sympathetic nerves.
You have lung cancer.
Pulse is down below 50.
So's her I.Q.
Help her up.
Get her heart going faster.
I need proof it's cancer.
Of course you do!
It's gotta be
a pancoast tumor.
Patient's got dyspnea,
Seventh-Nerve palsy.
He's sweating on one side
of his face.
Everything okay in there?
Take your time.
It's not like I've got a gun
to my head.
Lung cancer usually shows up
lower than the seventh nerve.
Did you check his throat?
Spit on the floor.
What?
If I do it,
I can't tell cuddy
That it was
medically necessary.
I'm gonna ask you to piss
on her chair next.
Dry mouth.
His parotid glands
aren't working.
It there's swelling,
it's a pancoast tumor
That's metastasized.
Feel that.
Right there.
If it's cancer,
there must be a test.
You just did it.
What about an x-Ray
or something?
Good idea.
Oh, damn.
I left my ct machine
in my other pants.
How many hostages
do you think it would cost me
For a trip to radiology?
So...
What made you snap?
- Hmos?
- Shut up.
Nah, you saw 16 doctors.
How bad could they
have been?
Shut up!
Humiliation?
Doctors treating you
like a piece of meat?
Too many fingers and tubes
up your holes.
You hate doctors.
You want to take back control.
If so, I apologize
for the fact that
You are a piece of meat.
I just want an answer.
That's all.
Everyone stays in here
with me.
If you need anything
from in there, get it now.
Move around.
Anyone moves... I fire.
That's not all.
Curiosity's not enough.
There's gotta be
a deeper reason.
You never did anything
Just because
you had to know?
Never shot anyone.
You're not me.
This is my body.
This is my life.
And there's a truth
out there.
I'd rather rot
in jail knowing than...
I can't handle not knowing.
Yeah.
Hold that.
You want your answer,
you gotta give me the gun.
What's this?
Starburst artifact.
The metal from the gun
is ruining the image.
Show him.
Starburst.
Now, unless you think
we pre-Arranged that,
Just in case
we were ever held hostage
By a guy who needs
a ct,
We're not lying.
So you have two choices.
You can give me the gun
and get your answer.
Or you can shoot me.
I'm not gonna give you
the gun.
Why did he release you?
House got him
to give up his gun.
We just ran.
Why are you still here?
Curious.
It's safe now, right?
They're gonna be
through that door any moment.
Just show me the tumor.
There isn't one.
I don't know
what you have.
So...
It's over.
Thanks for trying.
You had four theories.
You ruled out four theories.
Maybe no one can cure me.
He overpowered me
and got the gun back.
You're a coward.
You need to know everything
Because you're afraid
to be wrong.
You're so afraid
of being ordinary,
Of being
just another doctor,
Just another human being,
That you'll risk
other people's lives.
I'm arrogant.
You're the coward.
You're terrified
of death.
You just want to cheat it
by making it come sooner.
Gives you the illusion
of control.
Can I go?
Sorry.
We might need you.
How do they expect me
to think?
Is he lying?
Why would he do that?
Over time, hostages
start to root for the captor.
House isn't the rooting kind.
No, he's the obsessive,
defiant kind.
Mic the door.
Get a frame charge.
I hope your boyfriend knows
what he's doing.
Are you insane?
He's quick
for a sick guy.
Dyspnea,
Anemia,
seventh-Nerve palsy,
Tachycardia.
Long passes.
Anything.
- Go.
- I don't believe it.
Chase was right.
You're gonna kill someone.
I don't want to be
a part of it.
Loa loa filariasis.
You ever been to cameroon
Or on the ogowe river?
Next.
Could be q fever if he's had
exposure to goats.
No goats.
Histiocytosis x
Explains
the lung involvement and-
We have a new symptom.
He is turning his head,
favoring his left ear.
Means he's partially deaf
in the right.
Three hours ago,
he had superhero hearing.
Cushing's causes fatigue,
breathing problems,
Fluctuating hearing.
Even increased aggression
and risk-Taking.
I'm doing this by choice.
It's not a symptom.
We'll keep that between us
till you talk to your lawyer.
I need dexamethasone
And enough time to provoke
a respiratory reaction
And confirm
cushing's syndrome.
You need more time?
House, we're not negotiating
with you.
Actually,
we're through negotiating.
I've still got
three hostages left.
I'll give you one.
And no more testing drugs
on a sick doctor.
Fine.
Send in the drugs.
Son, come here,
come here.
House, you can't-
If you have cushing's,
this will slow your breathing.
Give it to her first.
Those were not the terms.
I lied.
These drugs
could be fake.
Why would I do that?
I gave you back the gun!
You wouldn't.
They would.
She has Huntington's.
If these drugs are real,
it could screw up her liver.
Chances are slim.
Chances of him shooting
one of us,
- On the other hand-
- Don't do-
How long do you have
to live?
Eight, ten years.
Killing her is your chance
to get personal?
Huntington's
doesn't have-
Doesn't have a cure?
No.
So if we get
out of here-
If she were clinging
to hope,
She wouldn't be
standing in line
Waiting for you
to order up more drugs.
Take a deep breath.
Not knowing what was wrong
with me...
Made me miserable.
Maybe that's insane.
Doing this... yeah.
Insane.
But I had something
to gain.
You can't take risks
with no upside at all.
I can't decide
which is riskier,
Taking crazy risks
Or taking advice
on crazy risks
From a crazed risk-Taker.
Heart's racing.
Fever.
And your breathing's
unchanged.
That means...
Means I was wrong.
Her kidneys are shutting down
Because of the meds
you made her take.
We have to get her
out of here.
The dexamethasone is making
Thirteen's kidneys fail,
But not the patient's--
Why?
This guy's been
on 50 different medications.
Maybe his kidneys
should be failing,
But something's
protecting them.
I need to slap you.
For diagnostic purposes.
Seriously.
If I was jerking you around,
I'd say I needed to kick you
in the groin.
That twitch
Is chvostek's sign.
Don't ask me how chvostek
discovered it.
He has calcium deficiency.
Drugs that block calcium
Tend to shield
against kidney damage.
He's been on protein pump
inhibitors for years
For his stomach pain.
Those drugs have been protecting
his kidneys for years.
He has something that has
a long incubation period.
Something that should have
wrecked his kidneys.
Something that explains
breathing problems,
Heart problems,
jumpy nerves,
And weak blood.
Leishmaniasis.
Would make perfect sense
If our patient was
an arabian bedouin.
Melioidosis.
Bacteria gets into the lungs,
spreads to the heart.
It explains everything.
Except that if you read
the history,
You'd know that our patient
has never been
To a tropical climate!
Is he absolutely sure of that?
Mexico. Costa rica.
You've never been-
I've never been anywhere
south of florida.
You idiot.
Florida counts?
Well, not to
the supreme court.
But it's warm enough
for germs.
You keep blaming doctors
When you can't even give
a halfway decent history.
Negotiation's over.
It will be as soon as you get us
three grams of ceftazidime.
He comes out, he gets
all the medicine he wants.
You can have dr. House.
Why are you getting rid of me?
I need to trade you
for the answer.
You're gonna give her
the meds.
No...
Come on, give 'em to me
instead.
She's taken everything
I've taken.
The combination of meds
could knock me out.
Her kidneys are failing.
You give her those drugs,
She'll be dead by the time
they get the cuffs on you.
I need my answer.
Your obsession
is gonna kill her!
gave me back the gun!
It is pointless
to give her those drugs.
Even if they are
screwing with you,
This is your last diagnosis.
Only if you're right.
House,
get out of here.
Shut up.
I'm not leaving.
Who's the martyr now?
Either the drugs kill me
Or he kills me.
Doesn't seem to make
a lot of difference.
You really don't feel bad
about killing me?
Not if you don't feel bad
about killing yourself.
I don't want to die.
Yeah, you do.
You just don't have the nerve
to actually do it.
You just want it
out of your control.
Well, it is.
'Cause I've got a gun.
Don't do this.
Either I do this
with you alive, or...
Please.
Sometimes you just have
to trust people.
Please.
I don't want to die!
Why are you still alive?
He didn't make me take it.
A week of temporary dialysis,
your kidneys will be okay.
I'm sorry I backed out
of the differential.
About that Huntington's
drug trial...
Test confirmed
melioidosis.
Easy to miss
on a stain.
Scans and X-rays
vary widely.
Is that all
you care about?
A moron storms the clinic,
Bullies his way
into life without parole,
You enabling him
every step.
If he hadn't done
what he did,
He'd be dead.
Good thing you enabled
my every medical move.
You think I handled this
differently because you were in here?
I don't know.
Let's try it again
without me.
This is why you and I
can't be a... thing.
If you're suggesting
that you screwed up
Because of a non-Relationship
with me,
I don't know how
I can help you.
'Cause the only change
you can make
From a non-Relationship is...
You want a relationship?
God, no.
Just trying to follow
your logic.
ææàãðü×öä»×é
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
»¶ó­¾óèë