(BIRDSONG)
Hello and welcome
to the sweat box...
that is Cambodia.
(HORNS BEEPING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLASTS)
Now, there are many ways
we could get across
this fascinating country.
We could use horses
or tuk-tuks or tractors.
But Mr Wilman decided we
should meet at this very spot
with three boats.
And that hasn't gone down
very well with my colleagues.
-No.
-There we go.
Because I hate... I'm from
Birmingham, I've explained.
Which is as far as you can
get from the sea in the UK--
-Full of canals!
-We don't do boats.
People from Birmingham
are always saying,
"It's the Venice
of the North,"
like Venetians always say,
"We live in the Birmingham
of the South."
Canals are just for
moving coal around.
I don't want
to do that either.
I'm from Birmingham,
I don't ski and I don't
do boats. End of.
-I signed up for a car show.
-Yes.
Not cookery, not restoring
frescoes and not boats.
-I don't like boats.
You can't trust a boat.
-That's exactly the right word.
You can't trust any vehicle
that isn't necessarily where
it was when you last parked it.
Problem No.1.
They can sink.
Cars can't do that.
-What are the viewers
gonna think?
-What?
What if you turned on
Jamie Oliver,
you thought, "I love that
cooking show...
Oh, he's doing some
watercolor painting."
-We did it in lorries--
-Lorries are vehicles.
They go on the road.
-We've been on horses.
-Oh, that went well!
Anyway, listen,
let's not get bogged down
with your prejudices.
Because the challenge
is actually quite simple.
We are here, yes,
near Siem Reap in
the north of Cambodia.
And we've got to
use all these waterways,
well, not all of them...
we've got to find a path
through them,
to Vung Tau, which is at the
bottom of the Mekong Delta,
in Vietnam.
There is, however,
one small problem.
RICHARD: As I've said, I'm no
expert on boats and boating.
-But...there's no water.
JEREMY: No, there isn't.
Is that pontoon thing there,
is that where Mr Wilman
thought we should meet?
-JEREMY: Yes, in a field.
-JAMES: He's a half-wit,
isn't he?
Anyway, the problem is...
there isn't enough water
in there to drown a witch.
RICHARD: No.
So, why don't we get
some wheels
and go and find some water
and then we'll launch
our boats there?
Right.
JEREMY:
Having found some wheels,
we began our search.
Oh, how the mighty
are fallen.
(RICHARD CHUCKLES)
JAMES: We are in tune
with the times, though.
Exactly right. Exactly right.
There is global warming,
there is climate change.
And if you hosted
a car show now,
I think you'd feel foolish.
-(HORN TOOTS)
-Bloody car, you maniac!
What's up with you,
you lunatic?
-You selfish maniac!
-Hit him! Hit the car!
Mad man!
JEREMY: Several
exhausting miles later,
the river was still
depressingly empty.
The problem we've got is
it's June
and it's supposed to be
raining here, really raining,
pouring down constantly.
And it isn't.
And it hasn't for months.
And when we reached
a fishing village,
the scale of the issue
became clear.
These houses, as you can see,
are on stilts
because that's where
the river should be.
Just stop here. Look.
That's where
the water level is.
JAMES: That's incredibly
gone, isn't it?
JEREMY: And it's
not just climate change
that's to blame,
because there's
another problem.
China.
They've dammed the river
that feeds all the water
systems round here.
How much sense
does that make, sitting here,
in your house on stilts
with no water around it,
to learn that the Chinese
have nicked all your water?
A funny world, isn't it?
The really funny thing is,
China builds a coal-fired
power station every
20 minutes or something
and everyone shouts at them,
saying,
"Oh, you're killing
the planet."
When they build a clean,
green, hydro-electric dam,
everyone shouts at them,
saying, "Now, look,
you're killing the planet!"
Well, it'd be nice if they
could do it without nicking
somebody else's water.
JEREMY: Eventually, though,
we found a lake.
-Oh, look at that!
-Hello.
But as we launched
our boats and headed
for a nearby pontoon...
...the rainy season
arrived...
with a vengeance.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
God above!
Erm...I don't know
how to park a boat.
I'm not gonna lie.
Trying to park.
-(SCRAPING AND CRASHING)
-Ooh! How do I stop it?
Having another attempt.
Wait a minute,
my engines are...
Oh, no, that one.
-(HEAVY THUD)
-Yeah.
I think that went well.
Right.
Stop moving around!
I've parked you!
Well, I was gonna leap
from my boat and say,
"And fresh from
Miami Vice...
a boat."
It's pointy,
which means it's a fast boat.
Oh, I've got my leg caught.
At this point, Jeremy
emerged from the gloom.
And as he's the only
qualified boat driver
on the team,
I was expecting
a smoother arrival.
JEREMY: Here we go.
Parking a PBR.
(CRUNCHING AND GRINDING)
-Argh!
-No, no, no!
Oh, brilliant!
It's really windy!
I'm backing in.
Oh, no, that's...
-(HEAVY THUD)
-Totally uncontrollable.
This is better, this angle.
-Argh!
-(HEAVY THUD)
-OK.
-Could you help
and get that rope?
Can you pull me along?
Please pull me along!
This is no time
for cocking about!
This is dangerous work
we're doing!
(HEAVY THUD)
I'm glad you got here cos
I think it looks like rain.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(BLEEP) me!
-Erm...
-What?
Isn't that like the boat out
of Apocalypse Now?
Exactly what it is, PBR -
Patrol Boat, River.
-Mark II.
-Yeah.
Is that entirely tactful?
We're going to Vietnam.
-You can't drive that around!
-You can! Because...
You probably don't know this,
but... Vietnam won.
So driving that
through Vietnam
is like walking through Old
Trafford, which is where
Manchester United play,
in a Charlton Athletic shirt.
It doesn't matter,
cos you're a loser.
They don't mind.
You believe that?
Is that...
Is that a Scarab?
RICHARD: Yeah.
Hammond, you have
accidentally chosen
-quite a good boat...
-Have I?
...if you were on the
inter-coastal waterway
in Miami.
You see, that's cool.
I've got two V8s in that.
-I've got two V8s in there.
-How many horsepower?
850 in total, 425 per engine.
-It's too much.
-What have you got?
350 a side.
I've got 700 in total.
-850.
-Yeah, but that's better.
It's not.
What do you think
May will have?
-Some.
-Probably,
with a bit of luck.
JEREMY: Soon, his
late arrival was explained.
He'd come from
the 18th century.
RICHARD: Look at that!
That's the world's least
appropriate thing!
JEREMY:
What was he thinking of?
How old is that thing?
James? About 60.
You ready with this rope?
Hang on,
it's going backwards.
Why's it doing that?
He is absolutely hopeless.
(ENGINE REVS)
He's got one knob
and one wheel.
Oh, here he comes.
He's trying a new technique
here.
He's broken his flagpole.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
-James?
-Yes?
That's the most inappropriate
thing I've ever seen.
What do you mean?
Well, it's entirely not
designed for where we are.
It's a river boat.
-We're on a lake.
-It's a pleasure craft.
But we're gonna be on rivers.
And it's only a gentle lake.
It's not stormy or anything.
Really?
-Have you got a big V8?
-No, of course I haven't.
JEREMY: What is it?
-It's a four-cylinder diesel.
-Power?
-Yes?
(CLEARS THROAT)
99 horsepower.
-When was your boat built?
-1939.
-Sorry...it's 80 years old?
-Yes.
-It's 80?
-It's older than
the Battle of Britain.
RICHARD: So it's an antique.
JAMES: It is an antique, yes.
RICHARD: You're sailing
in a sideboard.
JAMES: Pretty much.
-How much was it?
-£16,000, inc--
What? You paid 16 for that?
That's chea...
That's a Ford Focus. And
it's got a new engine in it.
Is that vulgar-looking thing
that I don't even want to
look at yours?
-Yeah.
-How much was that?
-Er, 23.
-(SPLUTTERS)
-Really?
JEREMY: That's reasonable.
That's how much boats cost.
-£23,000?
-Yes.
-How much was that?
-What, the PBR?
Mine, how much was it?
-It's, er...(MUMBLES)
-What?
-(MUMBLES)
-How much?
100,000.
-$100,000?
-100,000 what?
-No, pounds.
-£100,000?
-Yes, it was.
-You spent 100 grand on that?
Mm-hm.
But it's...
Is that because of
its provenance?
No, I had to build it.
-What, it's not real?
-No.
Hold on, hold on.
It's incredibly complicated.
They had to find the original
designs of the original hull,
work out where the engines
went, why it's mid-engined...
It was an immensely
complicated thing to do
and I've done it.
And I bought a little bit of
history, at great expense,
back to Southeast Asia.
It's a fake, though.
That's essentially a kit car.
Is it based on the chassis of
a Beetle or a Triumph Herald?
-It's a purpose-made chassis.
-A two-litre Pinto engine.
-Yes, exactly.
It's a purpose-made chassis.
And a brand-new engine.
100 grand on a...
What we've got here...
Can we do some car stuff?
What we've got is a Corvette,
definitely.
That is a Corvette.
Nothing wrong with them.
RICHARD: Big engine,
inexpensive.
JEREMY: Yes,
plastic and inexpensive.
A Mercedes G Wagon,
which it is...and a Rover 90.
RICHARD: Yeah,
I'll actually go with that.
I've just thought
of something.
I haven't christened my boat.
So I quickly organised
an official ceremony.
May God bless this ship
and all who sail in her.
(CLATTERING)
JAMES: That's what it's like
when the Queen does it.
(RICHARD SNIGGERS)
I've now got a bottle of wine
on my boat,
which is called Du Ma,
by the way.
-Is it?
-Yeah, means "boat machine".
(ENGINE STARTS)
JEREMY: With the christening
ceremony complete
and the rainy season over,
it was time to begin
our epic 500-mile voyage.
-Thank you.
-Oh, sorry.
We are underway.
The Du Ma is mobile.
I've just noticed Hammond's
boat's called Razzle Dazzle.
That's sophisticated,
isn't it?
JEREMY: The first leg
of our aquatic road trip
involved a sprint
across the Tonlé Sap Lake.
And I'd been
looking forward to unleashing
some speed and power.
Sadly, though,
that wasn't possible.
OK, the problem is -
and it is a big one -
despite
that massive rainstorm,
this lake is 80 miles across.
And at this time of year,
it should be five times
more than that.
This is not the best
camerawork you've
ever seen and I apologise.
But I think it makes
the point.
This road here,
this is the road
that goes round the lake.
But the lake at the moment
is only that big.
It just isn't big enough.
Which means
it isn't deep enough.
And don't worry,
the irony is not lost on me.
The man who hosted a car
programme for 30 years,
limited to seven miles
an hour by global warming.
Is your boat...
How can I put this?
...having a dump?
RICHARD: Is that mud?
Yes, that's mud.
You're grounding out.
I'm basically using
a boat in a field.
This did not happen
in Miami Vice.
RICHARD: Shallowness
wasn't the only problem.
We also had to deal with
an underwater labyrinth of
hidden fishing nets.
It doesn't feel good.
(ENGINE SPLUTTERING)
Doesn't sound good.
Turning round.
Oh, he's done...
What's he done, 100 yards?
-What the hell have you done?
-I don't know.
-(HEAVY THUD)
-Oh, you just...
JAMES: Hammond?
What? Everybody stop
crashing into me!
JAMES: Are you stuck?
No, I just thought
I'd stop here!
I've caught a net.
Why don't you just
go and cut it off?
Why isn't this
happening to you?
JAMES: What?
-Why aren't you catching
your props in nets?
JEREMY: I haven't got
any props. It's a PBR!
It's a jet boat.
I've got two jets.
JAMES: Really?
(SIGHS) Right.
JEREMY: Leaving Hammond
to clear his props...
There! That is the problem.
...I sailed onwards
with Rear Admiral Slow.
James May's boat
is the sort of thing
I can imagine they gave
to Prince Charles
when he was a boy
to play with in the bath.
My boat, on the other hand,
was designed for fighting.
See, when the American
military realised
in the mid-'60s
that they needed
some kind of fast patrol boat
for the shallow rivers
of Southeast Asia,
they went to Hatteras,
which was a very respectable
boat builder in America
and said,
"You know that pleasure craft
you make,
the 31-footer, plastic hull,
Mum and Dad boat?
Could you convert that, move
the engines further forward,
fit it with jets
instead of propellers,
give it a range of 250 miles
and a cruising speed
of 25 knots?"
Massive job, really massive.
And Hatteras had it ready
in six days!
Six days!
What they created was epic.
But even so, I had to have
this made because today,
there are no working
PBRs left.
And I find
that extraordinary.
They've saved all
the other memorabilia
from the Vietnam War -
Hueys and guns and
fighter planes and so on,
but nobody thought to say,
"Let's save a PBR."
It's a brilliant
bit of design,
it really genuinely is.
Original PBRs had two
Detroit diesel engines,
no electrics,
better with water.
And jets made by...
Jacuzzi.
I kid you not,
they were Jacuzzi jets.
Yes, the jets make it
very difficult to steer
at slow speed.
But apart from that, I was
able to cross Cambodia's
giant paddling pool
without any issues.
JAMES: Oh, that's not good.
JEREMY: Things, however,
were rather different
for my colleagues.
James had snagged
a net too.
Yeah!
Take that, you bastard.
JEREMY:
And as Aquaman struggled
to get back on board...
Bollocks!
...the cooling system on
Hammond's pointy Scarab
filled with mud.
(RICHARD GROANS)
This is a lot worse than...
nets round the props.
JEREMY: And just after
James had dried off...
he was back under
his boat again,
because his intakes had
also filled up with sludge.
This meant I had to go back
and become a tow truck.
Ready for the dead stop?
You'll like this.
-(ENGINE REVS)
-Shit.
-(HEAVY THUD)
-Sorry.
JAMES: Clarkson!
JEREMY: Right, I've got you.
James insisted on taking
charge of tying the boats
together.
Which meant I was free
to film some scenery.
But eventually
we were tethered,
and set off in search
of Hammond.
-There he is!
-Yep.
Hammond ahoy!
RICHARD:
I (BLEEP) hate boats!
-(AMERICAN ACCENT)
Turning on the horn.
-(SIREN BLARES)
RICHARD: International
Crap Rescue is coming.
I wonder how many low-grade
pornographical movies
have been made
on Hammond's boat.
(AMERICAN ACCENT)
Hey, you wanna come out
rootin' and tootin'?
Hammond, how much semen
have you found on that boat?
Please, I've tried to block
the thought from my mind.
Every...
Honestly, going below
is like climbing into
a teenager's sock.
(JEREMY CHUCKLES)
JEREMY: With both
broken boats hitched up
to Thunderbird 2,
we trundled on,
until eventually we were
swamped by the night.
JAMES: Have you got, like,
a military searchlight
on your boat?
Yes, I have.
Oh-hoo-hoo!
Hello!
JEREMY:
Many hours later, having
covered only ten miles,
we were feeling
a bit unhappy.
But then...
James, are they lights?
Oh, yeah.
JEREMY: I think that
is the town of Pursat.
It's not completely
the bottom of the lake,
but we should be able
to find a hotel there.
Having parked up...
Shit!
...we checked into
the town's only guesthouse
and then,
absolutely famished,
sat down for dinner.
Sadly, though, there wasn't
much on the menu for Hammond.
So this is...
Well, these are dragonflies.
Don't eat dragonflies.
-You've never tried one?
-Nobody eats dragonflies.
This is...crickets.
These are water beetles.
-I don't eat water beetles.
-They're tarantulas.
I especially don't eat
tarantulas.
JEREMY:
Or big spiders, anyway.
The thing is...
during the time of Pol Pot,
they were starving
and they had to.
And they actually discovered
that they're lovely.
Do you know
what Pol Pot means?
-Everyone thinks
it's his name.
-Bad menu?
It stands for
Political Potential.
Same as Jeremy Corbyn.
Same policies.
You're eating a taran...
No, it's a dragonfly.
-What do they taste like?
-Dragonflies.
-Oh!
-I knew you'd have a problem.
So I got you some
hard-boiled eggs, Hammond.
Is this a...
This is a cricket, look.
Can you see that?
JAMES: Do you eat it
or do you disembowel it
and then eat the flesh?
Oh, my God!
It's got a bird in it!
JEREMY: What?
That may be beyond my line...
RICHARD: I'm just looking
at it, thinking, "Really?"
JAMES:
That is pretty revolting.
It is, I know, but if you've
got a socialist running,
you know, like Britain
when we've got Corbyn...
this is what
we're going to be eating.
After our feast,
it was time for bed.
And we were shown to
the best rooms in the house.
(MOTOR CHUGGING)
Hang on, is that... That
generator goes all the time?
The noise - da, da, da, da...
Can you make it, like, off?
No?
Off? Da, da, da, da...
OK.
It's impossible to think
how this could be worse.
(GENERATOR CHUGGING)
(TECHNO MUSIC POUNDING)
And there it is.
This...
What's this? Why...
Why?
Why are they...
What's that,
in a grown man's bedroom?
(TECHNO MUSIC BLARING)
JEREMY:
Dawn was magnificent.
And there was no need to wake
the cameramen to film it.
Because they, like us,
hadn't had a wink of sleep.
(BOAT ENGINE PUTTING)
(DOG BARKING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(COCKEREL CROWS)
That. That...4:26.
-Yeah.
-4:26.
At midnight...
2am, music stops.
And the dog-barking
competition starts.
JAMES: Yeah.
-Till 4:26, cockerel starts.
Till five.
Fishing boats go out.
(ENGINE PUTTING)
Why don't they invent
the silencer?
JAMES:
They haven't got silencers
for those or generators.
It simply hasn't reached
this bit of the world
for some reason.
RICHARD:
Why do we do this?
JEREMY:
This is a boating holiday.
-Yeah. Brilliant.
-Life afloat. The glamour.
JEREMY: To cheer
ourselves up,
we decided to shop
for provisions.
And we were in
for a bit of a surprise,
because this town was
the Venice of the East.
There were floating houses
with satellite TV,
floating workshops,
floating supermarkets,
a hospital
and even a church.
Look at this!
It's a high street.
JEREMY:
So they've moved the town
to where...
Well, wherever
the lake is, the town is
always at the edge of it.
Well, it moves itself.
So what do we need?
JEREMY: We need earplugs,
we need sleeping pills,
something to wash
the sleeping pills down,
I'm thinking strong beer...
Yeah.
Maybe so strong
it's called whisky.
RICHARD: Yeah, that beer.
If nobody minds,
I'd like to buy
some cleaning products.
Oh, because of the
pornography that's gone on
on your boat?
RICHARD: Eugh! What's gone on
down there does not bear
thinking about.
JEREMY: Unfortunately,
trying to navigate
through the busy streets
exposed the PBR's
Achilles heel:
its mind-of-its-own steering
at slow speeds.
Oh, God!
JEREMY:
Look at it. Full left lock.
-(HEAVY THUD)
RICHARD: Just
concentrate on--
Don't do that!
This one is now going...
This one's back.
And that one's forwards.
-No, that hasn't worked.
-Backwards, backwards.
Anything you want to buy
from this shop?
Cos we're arriving at it.
RICHARD: Oh, oh!
-(HEAVY THUD)
JEREMY: Having
finally crashed into
the correct shop...
we set about loading up
with supplies.
-Got mops.
-That says beer.
Do you have, erm...
tablet for...
RICHARD: Yeah, but for...
for sleeping...
(TRUMPETS)
..elephant.
So, big.
JAMES: But not for...
Well, it could kill him.
RICHARD: That's what I mean.
JAMES: Oh, right, OK.
JAMES:
With the shopping done,
we resumed our journey
across the shallow,
net-infested lake.
I am under my own power
for now.
Ts and Ps looking good.
Hammond too
had mended his engines.
But he daren't fire them up
for fear of destroying them
in the mud.
So he was still being towed.
I found a very kind and
generous local fisherman
to pull me along
behind his little boat,
that doesn't have
a silencer on it.
(ENGINE PUTTING)
That boat wasn't
powerful enough,
so he found a mate
and then another mate,
and they've tied
all their boats together.
None of their engines
have silencers.
(ENGINES CHUGGING)
And we are now travelling at
a speed too slow to register
on any device.
Bo-o-o-ored!
JEREMY: Unlike my colleagues,
I wasn't struggling with a
Dickensian propulsion system.
JAMES: Thank you.
But even so,
I had run into a problem.
Right, this is
the end of the lake.
I've made it.
And there's the river,
I think, over there.
However, between me and it...
there is a small obstacle.
The mouth of the river was
absolutely jammed with
densely packed weed.
So, to get through it,
I decided to ditch
Slow and Careful,
and call on my old friends
Speed and Power.
Come on!
Rise!
Ye-e-e-eees!
No! No! No!
It's all gone wrong!
Yeah, we're stuck.
I think I filled my intakes
up with leaves.
Aarg!
JAMES: Meanwhile,
back on the lake...
...my life was
getting even worse.
Right, situation update.
I've run aground.
I can't even turn my boat
into wind cos it's stuck.
And there's a storm coming.
And it wasn't like
my camera boat could help
because that
was beached as well.
Oh, look at those poor sods.
And then,
to rub salt in the wounds...
(ENGINE REVVING)
(LAUGHS)
Are you stuck?
I thought you were
waiting for me.
No, I'm stuck.
But my boat's not powerful
enough to tow--
Nothing I can do. I thought
you were waiting for me.
I didn't know you were stuck.
I'm really sorry.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(GROANS)
Oh, hell.
Oh, God.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
JEREMY: Back in the lettuce
field, I'd enlisted the help
of the few remaining locals
not being employed by
James and Richard.
It is actually moving.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
The mighty PBR has been
freed by the local chaps.
JAMES:
Soon, I was also being towed.
So I had time to reflect
on the awfulness
of our boating holiday.
I mean, it's farcical.
We've got half of
Cambodia in the water
freeing us from
fishing nets and ropes,
and trying to pull out
the camera crew boats.
They're all stuck.
It's rubbish!
Are you stuck?
Yeah?
Is he stuck?
Right.
They're all stuck.
Eventually, though, Hammond
and I found deeper water,
and were able to proceed
under own own steam.
(CACKLES)
I have two engines!
It's Clarkson.
JAMES OVER RADIO:
Calling Commander Clarkson.
JEREMY OVER RADIO:
Right, chaps? Er...welcome,
first of all.
Nice to have you here.
No time for
pleasantries, though.
The problem we have is
that is a very significant
chunk of weeds,
and this can do everything
except go through them.
The issue was that my giant
V8s would suck the leaves
into the jets
and clog them up.
So Hammond and May
decided to slice a path
through the veg patch
using their old-fashioned
props.
Here we go into the reeds.
Hand on throttle.
JEREMY: I was then
towed through by a local.
Here I am going
through the salad,
pre-minced by Hammond
and May with their
19th-century propellers.
RICHARD: Ooh,
it's not liking this at all.
Watching my temperatures.
They're climbing already.
Bit snaggy.
Oh, come on.
Come on, boat.
Nevertheless, our salad
mincers kept chopping away.
JEREMY OVER RADIO: Hammond,
it opens up down there.
Can you see?
About 200 yards.
RICHARD: Yes, clear water.
Oh, yes.
Yes!
I'm weed free!
What a victory
for the antique, eh?
We then sailed down
a narrow channel
created by the fishermen.
Do you know
what's the most amazing thing
about these reeds,
apart from that they look
like giant flat-leaf parsley?
It's that, according to
a local, if I understood
him correctly,
they weren't even here
ten days ago.
And now there are
miles of them.
Ten days!
Imagine if you could grow
vegetables that quickly.
JEREMY: Joyfully, though, the
river eventually opened up.
And, finally, after
two days of frustration,
all of us
were able to open the taps.
For me especially,
this was great
because it meant
I finally had some steering.
Oh, yes! Look at this!
The speed!
RICHARD: Oh-ho-ho!
Oh, my word!
(RICHARD WHOOPS)
Come on, boat machine!
Du Ma!
Mind you, when I say all of
us had opened the taps...
(ENGINE PUTTING GENTLY)
Fuel and temperature's good.
Oil pressure is excellent.
I believe I am boating.
JEREMY: We were now
on the Tonlé Sap,
the only river in the world
where the flow
changes direction
according to the season.
And straightaway,
Hammond and I had
important work to do.
Do you wanna see who's
got the quicker boat?
Oh, this is so inevitable!
Right, what we're gonna
have now is a drag race.
And that's when he will see
the vast superiority
of the jet,
the instant torque and
acceleration of jet power.
JEREMY: With a far-off bridge
chosen as the finish point,
we lined up for a run.
Three...two...one...
Go.
Oh, no!
There you go, there's the
difference. Trimming my jets.
And that's goodbye,
Mr Hammond.
I'm up on the plane now.
Ha-ha!
Oh, no, he... Look at him.
And here he's coming back
at me.
Come on! Come on!
No! Come on, boat machine,
you can do this!
(RICHARD CACKLES)
No! No! I won't have this!
I'm gonna do it!
Come on!
Here's the finish line!
Yea-aaah!
JEREMY: No! No!
-(BOAT'S HORN BLARES)
Ghastly little Brummie
in his HMS Pornography.
Having lost
the ridiculous drag race,
I proposed
a high-speed brake test.
Ready? We're in full
forward thrust with my jets.
And I'm about to go
into full reverse thrust.
Instantly.
Just lowers some buckets down
and the water shoots forwards
instead of back.
What Hammond didn't know
is that this is a PBR party
piece.
Three...two...one...
Go.
Jesus Christ!
(WHOOPS WITH LAUGHTER)
No, I-I will give you that!
You won that!
That was quite a soaking.
Famously, these PBRs can stop
from top speed to a dead stop
in their own length, 31 feet.
There's water still dribbling
down that camera, look,
from that wave!
I think I just proved...
that story's true.
JAMES: Meanwhile,
several miles back,
I'd pinned my engine
to try and catch up
with the other two.
Oh, cock!
My cushion's in the water.
Bollocks!
So, if I go full-right
steering...
Stop.
What the bloody hell is...?
Hammond, you've gotta try
a bit of wave jumping,
it's hilarious.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, I like that game!
There's Richard Hammond
playing in the waves.
What could possibly go wrong?
Unlikely to be a fire
for once.
(SQUEALS DELIGHTEDLY)
Damn it, I'm enjoying it!
Must not enjoy boating.
Ya-ha-ha-hay!
(BLEEP)
JEREMY: While May
entertained the locals,
Hammond and I were nearing
Cambodia's capital city.
Yes! Phnom Penh.
There's Phnom Penh
dead ahead.
I am in slight wonderment.
Nobody told me
when I failed my A Levels
that one day
I'd be driving a PBR
down the Tonlé Sap River
into Phnom Penh.
Mainly because back
then Cambodia was...
...entirely impossible
to get into
because it was run by
the biggest lunatic
the world's ever seen,
Pol Pot.
The man killed 25 per cent
of the Cambodian population.
25 per cent.
He just said that anybody
who could speak
a foreign language,
or who had soft hands,
or wore glasses...
Anyone remotely intelligent
had to be killed.
If you haven't seen the movie
The Killing Fields,
please watch it, please.
You'll get an idea from that
of the horror.
Having parked up, we decided
to wait for James at the FCC.
I reckon this is
one of the coolest bars
anywhere in the world.
Back in the day
when Cambodia was,
let's say, a troubled nation,
this is where all the foreign
correspondents for all of
the world's media outlets
used to meet for a drink,
hence FCC, Foreign
Correspondents' Club.
RICHARD: It's when there was
some romance in journalism.
Oh, and expense accounts.
And drinking.
They drank a lot.
-You can feel it in the room.
-You can.
You can sense
ruined cirrhosis.
Some intelligent,
hammered minds.
They used to come in here
with guns they'd found,
get absolutely slaughtered,
and then just shoot
guns from the balconies.
You could do clay beer-bottle
shoots but with AKs!
"I've drunk 17 beers."
"And we're going to have
a considerable fight."
"And then I'm going to write
my copy with a broken nose."
JEREMY: After
we'd raised a glass or ten
to the ghosts of the past,
James finally arrived.
And we decided
to buy some things
to make our lives on board
more comfortable.
Oooh, missed 'em.
Why don't we go to the market
first of all?
A real local market
for local people?
-Yes.
-Yeah, let's go there.
-Come on!
-Yeah!
That's using internal
combustion.
What about global warming?
Eventually, we found
the local market.
And immediately
we were distracted
by all the pretty watches.
That's a Breitling.
I thought Breitling would
take better care of
their display than this.
Look at the Hublot.
That's a tasteful watch.
And so light
for such exquisite quality.
And all these diamonds.
-Omega.
-Omega?
See, that is my Omega.
And this one is orange but in
every other way, identical.
Jezza?
They haven't realised it,
but there's
a gold Rolex there
and there's a Planet Ocean
Omega there.
I just asked how much
a Seamaster is.
These are about £3,000
in the UK, yes?
-Yes.
-Guess how much
they are here.
I don't know, 2,000.
-£50.
-£50?
I mean, I know their
overheads are low,
but that's extraordinary.
-That must mean the mark-up
on those watches is enormous.
-Exactly.
Oh, hello. Hello!
Is that a real Jaguar belt?
I've got a Ja-a-ag.
How much is this?
22 Dollars.
25. And here,
because you're a nice chap...
-Yeah?
-Erm...keep it. Thank you.
Nothing on God's green earth
annoys me more
than European people
haggling in places like this.
Cos they're haggling
over a dollar...
It doesn't matter to you,
it doesn't matter,
and it matters a lot
to them.
Just pay the price.
-How much?
-75.
Ow! I was thinking 25.
JEREMY: Having stocked up
on luxury goods,
we went in search of
some more practical items.
Oh, hello!
Cooking, cooking.
Yes.
Something for
getting rid of flies.
Here.
-Flies, zz.
-(LAUGHS)
-Taser.
-Taser?
-(CRACKLES)
-Oh, gee.
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
-(LAUGHS WHEEZILY)
Thank you.
You're a life saver.
It's very hot.
(AEROSOL HISSES)
(JEREMY GRUNTS)
What's that woman
with the gold outfit?
That looks Hindu.
-Is it very old?
-Yes.
It is? Oh.
-Are these old as well?
-Yes.
(AEROSOL HISSES)
(HISSING STOPS)
Can I have another one
for the other armpit?
Having bought all we needed
to make a night afloat
more comfortable,
we immediately checked
into a five-star hotel...
-Good evening.
Oh, of course,
that's very kind. Thank you.
...and then went
to the rooftop bar.
So, that is the government
building down there.
Which I...
Look at the lighting on that.
It's one of the cleverest...
Cos it looks like curtains.
JAMES: It looks like theatre
curtains closing or opening.
Is that where the Prime
Minister hangs out?
-No, no, don't, don't, don't.
-He's not there?
No, don't call him
Prime Minister.
Well, what is he, then?
Well, weirdly, I was reading
the Financial Times.
And I've saved it.
Hang on.
Mr Hun Sen,
a ruler of 31 years,
who insists on
being referred to as:
"Lord Prime Minister and
Supreme Military Commander."
So, if you are referring
to him, you must say,
"Lord Prime Minister and
Supreme Military Commander."
His wife, Bun Rany,
she is officially known as:
"Most glorious and upright
person of genius."
I want to be called...
In fact, I want--
Most glorious and upright
person of genius.
I want you two
to start calling me that.
After a bit more
conversation, we went to bed.
Well, one of us did.
I've got paint,
paint brushes,
and then I've got
spray paint.
Where's the bicycles?
Oh, they're here.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
I love to follow you.
JEREMY: The next morning,
I fitted my new lavatory seat
and air-conditioning unit.
James installed
his drinks fridge.
And after Hammond had
slipped into his new shirt...
we set off.
And immediately, it was hard
to keep a straight face.
We have played jokes
on one another before,
but I'm not sure we've ever
pulled one as good as this.
From where Richard Hammond
is standing,
he has no idea what
James and I have done.
JEREMY OVER RADIO:
Hey, guys?
This is the first time
we've run under our
own steam as a three.
RICHARD: Yeah, it feels good.
I'm not sure it feels that
good, though, does it?
Do you know
what might feel better?
(ENGINES REVVING)
JAMES: Thank you.
Very funny.
JEREMY: We were now
150 miles into our journey
and leaving the Tonlé Sap
to join the world's
most iconic river -
the mighty Mekong.
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ I'm coming ♪
♪ I'm goin' my way... ♪
And I was going down it
at full chat in a jet boat.
These jets, they're
New Zealand jets,
and they are epic.
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ I'm coming ♪
The jet skis
you rent on holiday,
they have one impeller
in a tube,
suck water in, shoot it out
the back and go along.
The jets in this
are a bit different.
They're two-stage impellers.
One sucks the water in
and gets it spinning,
fires it into the second one
that properly hammers it
out the back.
Instant acceleration,
and a lot of it.
Speed boating.
There really was one of these
in Miami Vice.
Don Johnson drove around
in it with his sleeves
rolled up, looking cool.
And, in fact,
this is a Scarab Thunder,
and it was built specially
for a television series
called Thunder
starring Hulk Hogan.
It lasted one season.
It was crap.
But the boat exists.
JEREMY: Another funny thing
about boats.
When you have a car,
you never, ever run it
at max revs all day.
But with boats,
that's what you do.
Have you ever driven a car
where you've just...
maxed it from the moment
you start in the morning
and left it maxed all day?
Yeah, I had a company
Renault Clio for a while
and that's how I drove it.
JAMES: Meanwhile,
a long way further back,
I was contemplating
the enormity of
this incredible river.
JAMES: Here's a stat for you.
The volume of fish
caught in the Mekong
is 13 times greater
than the volume of fish
caught in all of America's
inland waterways combined.
60 million people depend on
the Mekong for food or
their livelihood.
60 million people.
So messing this up
with things like damming
could be as bad
as nuclear war.
RICHARD: Up ahead, Jeremy
and I were trying to create
a professional impression
at the Vietnamese
border checkpoint.
-Oh, that hasn't worked.
-(HEAVY THUD)
-Oh.
JEREMY: Yeah.
-Hi.
-Thank you.
We're experienced travellers
passing through.
Yeah, we were born in boats,
really.
Hammond, I'm really sorry,
but the customs man's dog
has died.
Oh, no. Oh, what
a terrible time to arrive.
I'm not sure
he's gonna be very happy.
Hello.
I'm beginning to suspect
there may be man-made fibres
involved in this
shirt of mine.
It's uncomfortable.
JEREMY:
With the paperwork done,
I observed nautical courtesy
with the flags,
donned a PBR-crew
black beret...
Right.
...and roared into the Nam.
♪ Some folks are born,
made to wave the flag ♪
♪ Ooh, they're red,
white and blue ♪
♪ And when the band plays
Hail To The Chief ♪
♪ Ooh, they point
the cannon at you... ♪
Suddenly, the PBR is
feeling alive and sprightly.
♪ It ain't me ♪
♪ I ain't no
senator's son, son ♪
This is what
it was built to do,
hammer down
the Mekong River in Vietnam.
♪ Some folks are born,
silver spoon in hand ♪
♪ Lord, don't they help
themselves, oh ♪
♪ But when the taxman
comes to the door ♪
♪ Lord, the house looks like
a rummage sale, yeah ♪
Cambodia, Mekong River
virtually empty.
In Vietnam now, Mekong River
very full of commerce.
♪ It ain't me, it ain't me ♪
♪ I'm no fortunate one, no ♪
JAMES: I, too, was
in Vietnam at this point,
and something was
dawning on me.
Strikes me I'm being
a bit of a mug because
I'm thrashing this boat,
but it only does 23 km/h,
about 11.5 knots,
and I'm trying to catch up
with people I don't even
want to be with anyway.
So, I decided to ease off and
break out my new fishing rod.
That is working a treat.
I should really have
a spinner on
or something like that, but...
Yeah, that's fishing.
In the most densely
fish-populated
fishing place in the world.
JEREMY: After a few miles,
I turned off the Mekong
and asked Hammond to follow
me to the town of Chau Doc.
And this time, when we
arrived under the watchful
gaze of yet more officials,
we were determined
to park well.
Jeremy? You've now got
my boat and I'm not on it!
JEREMY: What?
I'm not on it
and it's no longer tied on!
- It's not tied on
on that end?
-No, it's come off!
-Why didn't you tie it on?
-I thought I had!
Oh, for God's sake. Your
boat's got free, Hammond.
I quickly picked up Richard
so he could re-acquire
his boat.
-(ALARM BLARES)
-OK, that's
that test concluded,
"Where would it go?" test.
It went to there.
JEREMY: Yeah, exactly.
So we now know--
That's the drift,
we've established the drift,
it goes that way.
Everything we need to know.
JEREMY: Finally,
we managed to tie
ourselves to some land.
And that is how we do that.
And it was at this point
Hammond got the joke.
(RICHARD LAUGHS)
-I've just seen it!
-What?
What you've done to my boat.
-Have I been...
-Yes, all day.
-How have I not seen that?
-You haven't seen it all day.
You've been through
Cambodian customs,
Vietnamese immigration,
-Vietnamese customs.
-Oh, my God!
You've driven probably
100 miles down the Mekong.
-I waved at people. "Hi!"
-The thing is, Hammond,
it's very bad luck to change
the name of a boat.
Oh, God.
Anyway, I'll leave you
to ponder that.
The reason why...
we've parked here
in this quite tight spot
and come to this town
is because
I want to tell you
a little story.
On January 31st, 1968
the town of Chau Doc
was overrun...
as part of
the Tet Offensive.
(GUNFIRE)
A flotilla of PBRs set about
rescuing Americans
whilst others covered the
evacuation with a stream
of heavy machine-gun fire.
It then turned out that in
a house near the hospital,
a 24-year-old American nurse
called Maggie Frankot
was stranded.
Her Jeep was shot to pieces.
The fighting was everywhere.
There were Viet Cong soldiers
all around her house.
Some of them were even in it.
(GUNFIRE)
Special Forces soldiers
brought in by the PBRs
eventually reached
Maggie's location.
And after a massive battle,
she was dragged from the
house with an injured knee
and carried to one
of the waiting boats.
Afterwards, the Special
Forces soldier responsible
for these heroics,
Sergeant Drew Dix,
was honoured with
a Presidential Citation.
But the captain of the PBR
that sped her away
from the town and to safety,
a man called Lieutenant
William H Buddy O'Brien,
did even better because,
a year later...
she married him.
I should call this thing
The Love Boat.
As it was getting late,
I decided to pull over
and use my improvised kitchen
to produce something I'd
learned on a recent holiday.
-I came to Vietnam,
as you know...
-Yes.
And in the mornings,
I learnt Vietnamese,
and then in the afternoons,
I did a cookery course
on how to make Pho.
I mean, a lot of people think
I'm just this big,
blundering idiot
that can't wire a plug.
-That's the fella
I'm thinking about.
-Absolutely right, I am.
-Do you like onions?
-Yeah.
Now,
this is good-quality beef.
I'm tempted to cook it
a bit on the ladle.
In Pho, there are 124
different herbs and spices.
Erm...the...
the car element
of our car show is less
prominent at the moment.
Because we're on a boat
talking about cooking.
-But in a minute...
-Yes?
...or a second,
they'll cut back to James
who will be talking about
some mechanical thing.
You're right.
Oh, listen to that
interesting beat.
(ENGINE HUMMING)
My engine goes in and out
of phase with the engine
on the camera boat.
Can you hear it?
If I change the revs
by a tiny amount...
Whir, whir, whir...
-Right, we are good to go.
-Thank you.
Oh, I say!
This is not half bad.
Seriously? Or are you
just being nice to me?
No, it is...
It is genuinely very good.
Look at that view.
RICHARD: Mm.
JEREMY:
After we'd had our fill,
it was time to clear up.
-That's really hot!
-Yeah, it is hot.
-Yeah.
-Let go.
Observe the genius that I am.
We're not polluting
the river, by the way.
That all adds to the
nutrients, doesn't it?
-That's biodegradable.
-That is not polluting
the river.
Anyone who writes in
and says you're
polluting the river,
-I shall write back and go,
"No, we're just not."
-"You're an arse!"
There they are, I think.
Yes.
May, is that you
coming out of the gloom?
Yes, it is. Ahoy.
Perfect timing, mate,
we're leaving.
We've gotta go find
the Mekong.
Hang on, I thought
we were having a Pho?
RICHARD OVER RADIO: We did
have one. It was brilliant.
JEREMY OVER RADIO: Yeah,
sorry, I tried to save you some
but Richard
threw it in the river,
literally threw your
portion in the river.
Well, thanks very much
after my very arduous day.
JEREMY: Sadly, his
day was about to get
even more arduous
because we had to
re-find the Mekong,
and I was the only one
equipped for night running.
JAMES: My situation update.
I am steering by
my head torch
strapped to the flagpole
thing on the front.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Why do I always
end up with no headlights?
Every bloody trip.
RICHARD:
And to make things worse...
Gentlemen,
I have a poorly engine.
It's overheating badly.
It's starting to backfire
and cough.
The reason you're having
all these problems
is because you've changed
the name of your boat.
RICHARD OVER RADIO:
Yes, well,
I didn't change it, did I?
JEREMY: As I was
the only one with sat nav
and a proper light,
it was up to me to navigate.
And I just saw a little
passageway. Hang on.
There is,
there is a passageway.
Follow me.
JEREMY OVER RADIO:
I know this looks dodgy
but this is
the way back to the Mekong.
Ooh.
JEREMY: However, as
soon as I made the turn,
I realised I had a problem.
Not more weeds.
Please God, no.
Any minute now,
I'm under the boat,
picking bits of
lettuce out of my jets.
And, sure enough,
100 yards later...
(ENGINE REVS)
That's me dead.
I have no drive.
I solved this by paying
a local to clear the intakes.
And then I soldiered
on with him and our
translator for company.
This was useful because
it meant I could
clear up something
that had been puzzling me.
Could you answer this for me?
My boat is called...
(RAISED INFLEXION): Du Ma.
(LAUGHS)
And everybody laughs
when I go, "Du Ma."
Everybody laughs for a reason.
But it means "Boat Machine."
Boat Machine?
Du: boat.
Ma: machine.
So, why is that funny?
It's a similar
pronunciation to
"f*** your mother"
in Vietnamese.
-What?
-Mmm. (LAUGHS)
-Yes.
-You're joking?
Oh, right.
I'm losing drive.
-(HEAVY THUD)
-Oh, shit.
I'm in a tree. Big problem.
As it was late
and Hammond's boat
was poorly,
and I was in a tree,
we decided to make camp.
And we woke the next morning
in a blanket of drizzle
with no idea where we were.
It's all gone a bit
English-boating-holiday,
hasn't it?
Yeah.
Why did he turn off
the Mekong, anyway?
He wanted to stop off
and make a history
programme or something.
No, listen, he did a cooking
show last night as well.
You missed that.
My pho was so light
and beautiful...
Oh, this man's
going to see me!
RICHARD: They're gonna
be scarred for life.
-Morning.
-(DOGS BARKING)
If he falls in
and follows his own turd--
-Trousers.
-..into the lavatory bowl...
and emerges with it
stuck to his head...
Someone would say, "There's
a particularly massive turd
in the river this morning."
JAMES: With the morning
ablutions complete,
it was time to move on.
And, since it was Jeremy
who'd got us lost,
we decided it was up to him
to get us un-lost.
You're in charge of charts.
Lead the way.
We shall reacquire
the Mekong very soon.
Yeah, I hope so.
For your sake, really.
JEREMY: I admit
we are entirely lost
and none of these canals
are marked on the map.
(SNIFFS) Ooh.
JEREMY:
A few miles later, while
still not on the Mekong,
we came across
a floating market...
(LIVELY CHATTER)
...and decided
to buy some breakfast.
RICHARD: It's not really
a supermarket, is it?
Where do I...
What do I do?
JEREMY: You drive in there,
pull up alongside a boat
where you like the look of
the produce, and then buy it.
For Richard and James,
this turned out to be easy.
-Thank you.
But for me,
in the unruly PBR...
Oh, my God!
(BLEEP) hell!
I can't steer it.
-Oh, my giddy aunt.
-(CRASHING)
-(WOMAN CALLS OUT)
-Sorry. Sorry.
I'm just... I'm gonna have...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
-(CRASHING)
-Hammond, I've smashed
your window.
Yeah, I can see that.
-Yeah.
-(BEEPING)
-Stop beeping!
JAMES: Hello, hello.
Hello. What's that?
-(SHE LAUGHS) Yes.
-50 cents. OK.
-OK. OK.
-I've bought...
What are they?
-Move the...!
-(THUD)
Ooh. Sorry.
I'll go over here. I meant...
-(THUD)
-Don't...
Don't spin around again.
Oh, no!
-(THUD)
-Sorry.
JAMES: Tomatoes.
Excellent. And an onion.
Thank you.
No idea what that is.
JEREMY: Wait a minute.
This is looking good.
I think, for once...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
-It's gone wrong.
-(THUD)
Oh, God. Sorry.
I'm gonna break his rudder.
Oh... Yeah.
JEREMY: I eventually left
empty-handed.
But, as James
prepared his breakfast...
Ahh!
...we found the Mekong.
Sadly, however,
it didn't end our problems.
If we followed this
particular bit of the Mekong,
or this one,
or any of the others,
we'd end up in the sea,
and avoiding any form of sea
in our riverboats
was critical.
So, we had to find another
path through the delta.
This meant turning off
the Mekong again
and onto another canal,
which made Hammond very angry.
RICHARD OVER RADIO:
Oh, this looks weird!
We're on another
bloody canal!
Oh, for God's sake.
Hammond, if I still had
50 cals on the front of this,
I promise I would open up
on you right now.
RICHARD OVER RADIO:
Yes, well, you haven't.
And there's a reason for that.
Because you'd probably
lose them the same way
you lost the massive river.
You'd lose
your massive machine gun.
It cannot be this way.
JEREMY: I was convinced
we were going in
the right direction
and for the right reasons.
But, still, none of
these canals appeared
on my sat-nav system.
OK. So, we're going south.
We're going the wrong way.
If I do a left and a right...
we'll wiggle about
and I'll be fine.
I think there's
a left turn here.
If we take this,
I think that'll help us
find the correct Mekong.
Or just get us more lost.
Jeremy Clarkson, would you
like to rethink this?
This is your chance.
(EXHALES) Calm.
Eventually, we came to
an aquatic T-junction.
So, which way is it?
Right, chaps,
we're gonna go...
Take a right, James.
RICHARD: I followed James,
which meant Jeremy was
directing us from the back.
So this right turn
that you announced
with absolute confidence
is based on what?
JEREMY OVER RADIO:
Hope.
Hammond, when you
get through that,
could you just look back
and see if I can?
-What?
-Hammond! Hammond! Hammond!
Oh, oh, oh,
that's not gonna work!
(THUDDING)
Ah, that didn't fit.
-Thanks, Hammond!
-Well, I was... I... I...
I was getting through
before I could turn round.
Do you know what that means,
Hammond? The nav's gone.
Oh, well, it's done us
a lot of bloody good
so far, hasn't it!
Oh, we've lost the thing
that's got us lost!
RICHARD: As we continued,
the problems started
to come not from above
but from below.
(DULL THUDDING)
I think I'm bumping
the bottom here occasionally.
I think I did just now,
as well.
(DULL THUDDING)
Oh, I am hitting the bottom.
(DULL THUDDING CONTINUES)
Oh, wait a minute.
Hammond, it's a dead end.
It's a dead end,
for God's sake.
(DULL THUDDING)
-(ENGINE WHINING)
-(HIGH-PITCHED TONE)
Sod it, I'm beached.
Completely beached.
RICHARD: You what?
-And I can't turn round.
Save yourself.
RICHARD: But it was
too late for that.
-(DULL THUDDING)
-Oh, for God's sake.
JEREMY: I could have
turned round, but...
I'm weeded up.
I'm losing drive.
And you're looking for what?
Sympathy?
JEREMY: Now all three of us
were beached.
RICHARD:
Well, this is crap, isn't it!
JEREMY: OK, chaps,
here is the situation.
Using my intellect
and genius,
I've deduced this is tidal.
We can see
where the tide was,
so we simply have to wait
for it to come back up again.
-Yeah, but it's going down.
-Yes, that's my worry.
Whatever happens,
we are definitely stuck here
for a little while.
JEREMY: It's actually
a really nice spot, weirdly.
Apart from the slowly-exposed
bucket of fetid mud.
JAMES: Do you want a tomato?
-No.
-Do you want a potato?
-Would you like an onion?
-No.
Guys. I've got my iPad.
I can watch a movie.
There's a show
on Prime Video here,
it's called The Grand Tour.
RICHARD: I don't like it.
JAMES: It's rubbish.
RICHARD: There's this one
bloke on it I can't stand.
What are the locals thinking
right now about us?
"They're making a movie
and they've (BLEEP) it up
completely."
(LAUGHS)
JEREMY: Another hour passed,
and with the water
still draining away,
it went dark.
Having waited
most of the night,
in a cloud of mosquitos,
for the tide to refloat us,
we retraced our steps
and suffered more damage
in the process.
(BARKING)
So, the bridge that
ruined the radar dome
on the way in,
on the way out,
knocked off my nav lights,
my spotlight,
and bent my roof here.
Which means every time
I walk past, I hit my head.
So...I'm gonna tie this on
as a reminder
to not hit my head.
On the up-side, I had found
the correct canal -
a route that would
keep us away from
the South China Sea.
Unfortunately, everyone else
had found it too.
(HORNS HONKING)
Holy cow!
This like a motorway
for water lorries.
-(HORN HONKS)
-I have never seen the like.
And in order to have
any steering in the PBR,
I had to go down
the motorway...
as fast as possible.
♪ WAGNER:
Ride Of The Valkyries
Jinking to miss the cargo.
Oh, no, wait.
I'm gonna go right.
Going right.
Changed my mind.
This is a head-on.
I'm heading for a head-on.
-(HORN TOOTS)
-(JEREMY CHUCKLES)
Look how loaded
that barge is.
If you saw that anywhere else
in the world, you'd say,
"Oh, my God!
That's about to sink!"
But, no, it's just
plodding along.
What the hell's
happened here?
Holy cow.
I think what's happened
is he's beached
the back end of it
and now he's spun round...
Oh, this is just hilarious.
Oh, dear, oh, dear.
That's really bad.
How did he do that?
Mind you, you'd say that
looking at us lot last night.
JAMES: Soon, however,
this wasn't the only boat
in trouble.
(ENGINE SPLUTTERING)
Oh, that smells terrible now
and there's a lot of smoke.
Ohh...
My right-hand engine
is overheating.
I think, actually,
it might be on fire.
Still, at least
it then rained,
so I didn't have to worry
about the fire spreading.
(THUNDER)
Oh, God almighty!
JEREMY: Being a caring soul,
I decided to go back
to see if I could help.
Switching to
wet weather mode.
And I'll give James a fly-by.
I know he enjoys them.
Here we go.
(THUDDING)
JAMES: Clarkson!
(LAUGHS)
(ENGINE SPLUTTERING)
JEREMY: What's the matter?
Uh, I've lost drive
on both sides, pretty much.
Oh, actually,
I know how to...
fix a slipping prop shaft.
-How?
-Get the boat
out of the water,
send for new parts
from America,
and then ask a man
to fit them.
JEREMY:
With that advice dispensed,
I was on my way back.
(CLINKING)
JAMES: Oh, no.
We're hoping to reach
the finish point today.
We're only 100 kilometres now
from Vung Tau.
But, at this rate, I'm not
sure that's gonna happen.
RICHARD: In order to hold us
up as little as possible,
I attached myself
to a camera boat,
so I could do repairs
on the move.
This one is not firing
on all cylinders.
That one's not good either.
I'm gonna change all of
the plugs, all of the leads.
The fuel is filthy
around here,
so I'm gonna change
the fuel filters.
I'm gonna clean
the air filters.
There is a leak coming
through the exhaust stack
at the back,
with a blown hose.
I've got to change that
or I'll sink.
To work!
JAMES: Leaving Richard
to try and mend
his burning colander...
I finally sailed clear
of the rain.
Oh, no!
My expensive Bell & Ross
is all fogged up.
That's going back.
JEREMY: Even further ahead,
I'd left the canal
and was entering one of
the delta's giant estuaries.
This one's a long way
from home,
taking a lot of Vietnamese
training shoes to Panama.
Power is good.
Temperature's good.
Fuel is very... Ooh, Christ,
fuel is very low. Oh, dear.
JEREMY:
But, actually, that was OK
because in busy,
industrious Vietnam
you can summon
a Deliveroo-style
refuelling boat.
I'm heading at 120 degrees.
OK, I'll keep my eye open.
And, sure enough,
half an hour later...
-(HORN TOOTS)
-Oh, here he is.
You see, this is service,
from this
environmentally-friendly
boat that's arrived.
I've been joined
by the Rainbow Warrior.
Actually creating
a lake of soot.
Once I'd refuelled,
I sailed into what is -
for my boat at least...
home.
Today, this particular
area is known as
the National Biosphere.
This is one of the most
fertile places on Earth.
Anything grows here.
You could plant
Richard Hammond
and in the morning
he'd be three feet taller.
But the Americans used to
call it something different.
They called it The Forest
of the Assassins.
And it was the job
of the PBR boys
to root those assassins out.
That was no easy task
'cause we're talking about
500 square miles of forest,
criss-crossed by 3,000
miles of rivers and creeks.
It was the perfect place
for the Viet Cong
to wage guerrilla warfare...
against America's little
unarmoured war boats.
Initially, the crews
were trained in America
by the army,
and then they were
trained by the navy,
and then they were told
to just come out here
and get on with it.
They literally put four
teenagers, as often as not,
on an armed speedboat
and sent them out here
to do fighting.
Armaments?
Well, all of the boats
had twin 50 cals upfront...
and a single 50
at the back.
But, beyond that, the captain
could fit what he wanted.
Some went for 40-millimetre
grenade launchers.
Some had
60-millimetre mortars.
Some had rocket launchers.
Some carried Claymore mines
to leave on the banks.
And it was
the same free-for-all
when it came to air support.
Some PBR captains
called in fast jets
when they were attacked.
And some preferred
to work in tandem
with helicopter gunships.
Some guys, however,
liked to handle the fight
on their own.
There was one guy
called James E Williams.
He came round a corner.
His route was blocked
by eight enemy boats
all firing at him.
So, he ordered his front
machine-gunner to fire back,
and then engaged full speed
and rammed into
the enemy boats.
Then he turned round,
engaged full speed again,
and rammed into the ones
that hadn't been turned
into matchwood
on his first pass.
He got the Congressional
Medal of Honor for that one.
And I'm not surprised.
Of course, you'd imagine
that a plastic boat
would be easy pickings
for a sniper hiding
in the undergrowth.
But that's not so,
as I shall now demonstrate.
(ENGINE REVS)
PBR captains
would always drive very fast,
so they had steering,
and very close to the bank.
If it was the bank where
the sniper was hiding...
I mean, if you're in there,
you've got no chance.
All you have to do
is keep the hammer down
and keep close to a bank.
Then you're
a sniper's nightmare.
-(THUD)
-Oh, shit.
(SCRAPING)
Right, what I've just done
is - there's no other word -
I've crashed.
(GROANS)
(MOTOR CHUGGING)
How have you done that?
OK, what happened was I came
round this corner here,
there were some
school children swimming,
and a shark
was homing in for an attack.
So, I ran the shark down,
and then got stuck
in my own wake.
And it's just...
Well, I've crashed now.
But the school children
are all fine.
At first, a camera crew
tried to pull me off,
but the PBR was too heavy.
Now what are you gonna do?
JEREMY OVER RADIO:
Well, that's a good question.
JEREMY:
We were all stumped.
And that's because we
hadn't reckoned on
the ingenuity of the locals,
who decided to pull the boat
from the front.
(LOCALS CALL OUT)
Right, um...
Ooh, it's moving. Is it?
It's actually...
Uh, we're moving.
I'm moving. I am moving.
I am absolutely staggered.
Look at this!
This is a four-ton boat.
Yes!
You are a genius!
I must admit,
that was a fantastic effort.
I didn't think
that was gonna shift.
You know, people always say,
"How did the Vietnamese beat
the French, the Chinese,
and the Americans?"
I think we've just seen
an example of it.
And, many miles back,
on the porn set,
there was more good news.
There it is!
I'm back in the running!
Both engines running on eight
cylinders and running well.
Plus, I'm no longer
on fire or sinking.
JEREMY: All of us
were running well, in fact.
The finish line
was in striking distance
and even though our
weird collection of boats
had been captained
by two terrible sailors
and a hopeless navigator,
they had, nevertheless,
survived this epic adventure.
-(THUNDER)
-Oh-oh!
It's really windy!
Ooh-ooh!
(ANGUISHED CRY)
-(MOTOR CHUGGING)
-(MIMICS MOTOR)
No?
Come on! Come on! Come on!
-No, I won't have this!
-Yeah!
Oh, God.
Here we go into the reeds.
Sleeping...
(TRUMPETS) ...elephant.
Oh, my God.
-(THUD)
-Sorry.
Oh, cock.
JEREMY: Hammond!
Hammond! Hammond!
(THUDDING)
Ah, that didn't fit.
Oh, we've lost the thing
that's got us lost.
RICHARD:
Well, this is crap, isn't it?
(CLATTERING)
(LAUGHS)
Oh, shit!
20 miles to go.
What can possibly go wrong?
As it turned out,
just about everything.
(THUNDERCLAP)
(THUNDER)
This time, the rain was
the heaviest we'd seen.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
This is grim.
(THUNDER)
(BLEEP) hell,
I can't see a thing.
JEREMY: Soon,
we were completely lost.
Have I overtaken you?
Have you seen me go by?
JAMES: I can't see a (BLEEP)
thing and I can't steer.
JEREMY: When the rain
did eventually clear,
we realised we had emerged
into the one thing
I'd been trying
so desperately to avoid.
OK, well, now,
what we've done...
what I'm doing here...
That's the sea.
30 miles of open ocean
lay between us
and the finishing line
at Vung Tau.
But, as the water
didn't look too rough...
we decided to put on some
life jackets and go for it.
I've been thinking. Jeremy?
The sea is in some ways
a lawless place,
but in others there is
a strict code, isn't there?
You stick together
through thick and thin,
face perils as one.
Yeah. Thing is, though,
to operate efficiently
as a team,
each team member
has to be at their optimum.
At this speed,
I'm not at my best.
I have no steering.
JEREMY: And so...
Three, two, one... Go.
Funny.
JEREMY: As it turned out,
that would be the last
funny moment of the day.
Oh, my God!
-(THUD)
-Argh, fuck!
I'll try standing up,
see if that helps.
With bent knee.
-(THUD)
-Oh, no! Oh, God.
God above,
this is just awful.
-(RATTLING)
-Oh!
(COUGHS AND SPLUTTERS)
I'm gonna throw up
at this rate,
not because of sea sickness
but because of
the amount of salt water
in my mouth.
(THUDDING)
No!
(GROANS)
This is a lot worse than
I thought it was going to be.
It wasn't just
the rough seas.
(HORN HONKS)
We also had to weave our way
through the shipping lanes.
There's a large tanker
dead ahead.
Trawler off to my right.
Sheez.
I've managed to miss
that massive container ship.
That's something.
$3.5 trillion worth of trade
comes through these waters
every year.
God knows how it isn't
all smashed to pieces
when it gets to its destination.
Jesus Christ.
If one big wave goes
in there, I'm gonna get
very nose-heavy.
And I cannot realistically
get up there to put it back.
RICHARD: Meanwhile,
I'd finally managed
to put my roof up...
Oh, yes. There's a chance.
There's a chance.
...which was time well spent.
Holy shit!
Ohh, bollocks.
(GROANS)
Stop...doing...that!
JEREMY OVER RADIO:
The good news is, Hammond,
it can't be worse than this.
JEREMY: But it did get worse.
Ohh! (BLEEP) Nora.
Sheez. This is stupid.
It's gonna snap.
I just pissed myself
standing up where I was.
Anything else
is not an option.
Oh! Freezing
and (BLEEP) wet.
(GROANS)
This is getting sketchy.
I'm not sure we can do this.
JEREMY: Certainly,
one of our camera boats
was in very big trouble.
MAN: Bloody hell.
We're taking in too much water.
I don't know
if it's dangerous.
We'll never get there
at this rate.
JEREMY:
And James had completely
lost control of his antique.
Oh! No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no!
Oh, (BLEEP) sake!
No!
Argh.
JEREMY: After 15 miles, the
sea started to calm a little
and I decided
to increase speed.
Come on,
you brave little soldier.
Come on, bite.
Bite, bite, bite.
Bite.
I can't stand
much more of this.
It's only a few miles!
(WHIRRING)
Come on. I'm running in
fast now. I want this over.
Argh!
The top three worst things
I've ever done.
JEREMY:
Mercifully, the finish line,
Vung Tau harbour,
then hoved into view.
Come on.
It can't be more than a mile.
(SNAP)
Well, that's brilliant.
These last couple of hours
have damn nearly killed me.
They probably have
James and Richard.
I can't raise either
of them on the radio.
I don't know where they are.
I reached the jetty
very much alone.
Sorry, there's no
film crews with me.
Um, I don't know
where they are either.
But Richard Hammond
is arriving.
He's made it.
Normally we'd celebrate
the end of a journey,
but I'm not celebrating that.
Beyond brutal.
Yeah, that was the hardest
thing I've ever done.
Easily the hardest thing
I've ever done.
The most dangerous.
JEREMY:
After a film crew arrived,
we disembarked.
Have you really not heard
from James at all?
No, nothing.
But then, the Rover 90
hoved into view.
It could be coming
with nobody on it,
like the Marie Celeste.
Well, I did wo...
No, he is there.
Look, there's a very
bedraggled dog at the helm.
Yeah.
Right.
We've been very worried
about you.
Have you? I was very worried
about me. But thank you.
-(RATTLING)
-Jeez.
(GROANS)
I'm absolutely staggered
it's still there.
-But we have survived.
-Yeah.
And on that
terrible disappointment...
-for Top Gear...
-(CHUCKLING)
...it's time to say goodbye.
We'll be back.
-See you very soon.
-See you soon.