♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Stupid junk mail.
"You may have already won."
Yeah. Win this.
"Here's good news for
Homer Simpsoy..."
(scoffs)
I'll see that he gets it.
How dumb
do they think I am?
Huh?! A check?
(gasps)
One million dollars.
I'm rich!
(shuddering)
Mr. Simpson,
I can assure you.
This check of yours
is non-negotiable.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what makes you
so damn sure?
You see where it says
"Void, void, void,"
and "This is not a check.
Cash value 1/20th of a cent.
Mr. Banker, do not honor."
Shut up.
I had a feeling
it was too good to be true.
Every time you get
$1 million
something queers
the deal.
I don't think real checks
have exclamation points.
Well, at least we got a free
sample of "Reading Digest."
Marge, I never read a
magazine in my life
and I'm not gonna start now.
Hey, a cartoon!
(Homer reading)
(laughs)
Ain't it the truth?
No, it's not
the truth, Homer.
It's well-documented
that women are
safer drivers than men.
Oh, Marge, cartoons don't have
any deep meaning.
They're just stupid drawings
that give you
a cheap laugh.
Hey Einstein,
put down your reading,
it's lunch time.
-Nah, you go ahead.
-You don't wanna eat?
What did you do?
Get one of them stomach staples?
As Tolstoy said
in Quotable Notables,
"Give me learning, sir,
and you may keep
your black bread."
Who is that bookworm,
Smithers?
Homer Simpson, sir.
Simpson, eh?
How very strange.
His job description clearly
specifies an illiterate.
ANNOUNCER: We now return to
Troy McClure and Delores Montenegro
in "Preacher With a Shovel."
MAN: But irrigation
can save your people,
Chief Smiling Bear.
Marge, look at them staring
at that idiot box.
God forbid they would
ever read something
and improve their minds.
You've certainly taken a shine
to that magazine.
It's not just
one magazine, Marge,
they take hundreds of magazines,
filter out the crap
and leave you with something
that fits right
in your front pocket.
(grunting)
Those kids don't know
what they're missing.
Dad!
Hey, what gives, man?
We're all gonna sit down
as a family
and listen to an inspiring story
of wilderness survival.
"Then I heard the sound
"that all arctic explorers
dread--
the pitiless bark
of the sea lion."
He'll be killed!
Homer, he obviously got out
alive if he wrote the article.
Don't be so--
Oh, you're right.
Homie, put down
your magazine
for a minute.
Huh?
Mmm, I thought
you might want to snuggle.
That reminds me.
"Seven Ways to Spice Up
Your Marriage."
(clearing throat)
Marge, "You have a nice body
"and if you'd like to
see me in a costume,
you have only to ask."
Thank you, Homie.
Wow! Little meat loaf men!
Where did you get
the idea for this, Mom?
Where do you think?
This baby never
steers you wrong,
and it was free. Free!
It certainly has
enriched our lives.
Wow.
"Win a trip to Washington, D.C.
"All expenses paid.
V.I.P. Tour."
Oh, it's for kids.
Wait, Dad!
Hmm...
an essay contest.
Children under 12, 300 words...
fiercely pro-American.
Sounds interesting.
Bart, maybe this is something
you'd like to do too.
Mom, it's a nice thought
but we both know that
this is the pony to bet on.
What would Ben Franklin say
if he were alive today?
He'd say, uh...
think of a better opening.
How's it going, honey?
Not very well.
Well, when I used to get
stuck like this,
I'd go for a bike ride.
Do kids go
on bike rides anymore?
Yes!
I don't know.
I thought maybe bikes
weren't cool anymore.
Do kids still use
that word? "Cool?"
Yes, Mom!
Okay, America, inspire me.
Wow, a bald eagle.
Hmm...
Thanks for driving me
to the contest, Dad.
Sweetheart, there's nothing
I wouldn't do
for that magazine.
"So burn the flag if you must,
but before you do,
"you better burn
a few other things.
"You better burn your shirt
and your pants.
"Be sure to burn
your TV and car.
"Oh, yes, and don't forget
to burn your house
"because none of those things
"could exist
without six white stripes
seven red stripes
and a hell of a lot of stars."
-(cheering, applause)
-Thank you very much.
Yeah! Damn right!
(cheering)
"Recipe for a free country:
"Mix one cup liberty with
three teaspoons of justice.
"Add one informed electorate.
Baste well with veto power."
"My back is spineless.
"My belly is yellow.
I am the American nonvoter."
"Stir in two cups of checks,
sprinkle liberally
with balances."
"Ding, dong.
"The sounds of
the Liberty Bell.
"Ding-- freedom.
"Dong-- opportunity.
"Ding-- excellent schools.
Dong-- quality hospitals."
"When America was born
on that hot July day in 1776,
"the trees in
Springfield forest
"were tiny saplings
trembling towards the sun.
"And as they were nourished
by mother Earth,
"so too did our fledgling nation
find strength
"in the simple ideals
of equality and justice.
"Who would have thought
such mighty oaks
"or such a powerful nation
could grow
out of something
so fragile, so pure."
(voice cracking)
Thank you.
(applause)
What do you think?
It's good. A little too good
for an eight-year-old.
Methinks I detect
the sickly scent
of the daddy.
Mr. Simpson,
I'd like to ask you
a few questions
about your daughter's essay.
Lisa, will you excuse us?
Okay.
"We the purple"?
What the hell was that?
Are you a professional writer?
Mm-mm.
Are you interested
in politics or government?
Mmm-mm.
Are you interested
in anything?
Mmm-mm.
Could you touch
your nose for me?
-Mm. Mm.
-Hmm.
Lisa, after meeting
your father,
I've decided to award you
an additional five points.
Congratulations. You and your family
are going to Washington.
Whoo-hoo!
Who would have guessed
reading and writing
would pay off?
(bell dinging)
Yes, sir, can I
get you something?
Playing cards,
note pad, aspirin,
sewing kit,
pilot's wing pin,
propeller-shaped swizzle stick,
sleeping mask,
and anything else
I've got coming to me.
I'll see what I can do.
Hm... hmph.
(laughing)
-Hmph.
-(laughing)
Steward!
Little boy, I bet you'd
like to visit the cockpit.
Ooh-ooh, baby!
And this control stick is like
the handlebars on your tricycle.
Now, would you like to see
where we hang our coats?
No, thank you, I'd rather
push this button.
No!
(screams)
We're all gonna die!
(all screaming)
Look, Marge, that guy has
the same last name we do.
Taxi!
Ooh, look, Homer,
the I.R.S.
Boo!
Oh, boo yourself.
MARGE:
Here we are, kids.
The Watergate!
(humming)
(soft chuckle)
Hey!
(laughing)
MARGE: Homer, look!
They give you a shower cap
and body gel
and bathrobes.
And a welcoming mint
on your pillow.
Wow, a shoe horn.
Just like in the movies.
Shoe goes on, shoe goes off,
shoe goes on, shoe goes off.
Shoe goes on,
shoe goes off.
Hey, I call first bedsies.
Bart, there's no such thing
as first bedsies.
You just made that up.
Well, okay, which one
do you want?
I... want...
that one.
Really? You want
that one?
It's all yours.
Whatever you say.
Why? What's wrong with it?
Nothing.
Have a good night's sleep, Lisa.
-No really. What?
-Nothing.
-What did you do to it?
Mom!
(phone ringing)
D'oh!
Stupid welcoming mint!
Hello?
BART: Good morning,
this is your wake-up call.
Wake-up call?
It's 2:00 a.m.
Sorry, fatso.
(laughing)
HOMER: Free food?
Lisa, I'm Faith Crowley,
Patriotism Editor
of Reading Digest.
Ooh, I love your magazine.
My favorite section is
"How to Increase
Your Word Power."
That things is really,
really, really... good.
Well good.
Lisa, I'd like you to meet
some of the other finalists.
This is Trong Van Dinh
and Maria Dominguez.
-Hello.
FAITH: Maria is the National
Spelling Bee Champion.
and Trong has won both
the Westinghouse
Talent Search,
and the N.F.L. Punt,
Pass and Kick Competition.
Have either of you ever run
into any problems
because of your
superior ability?
-Mmm...
-Sure, I guess.
Oh, me too.
These are special
V.I.P. badges.
They'll get you into places
other tourists never see.
Miss, what does the "I"
stand for?
Important.
Ooh... How about the "V"?
Very.
Oh... and miss?
Just one more question.
-Person.
-Ahh....
What does the "I"
stand for again?
Oh!
"On this spot, Richard Nixon
bowled back-to-back 300 games."
Yeah, right.
Wow, the President's bathroom.
(gasps)
Do you mind?
Barbara Bush!
Oh, you have
those damn badges.
Okay.
This tub was installed
in 1894...
Mmm... money.
Ahhh.
Hey, watch it, Chief.
Folks, we print more than
18 million bills a day.
Oh, and in case
you were wondering,
no, we don't give out
free samples.
(laughing)
Lousy, cheap country.
(imitating a machine gun)
Bart, get out of
the Spirit of St. Louis!
(imitating airplane engine)
(chuckling)
Hey, what's so funny?
(whispers)
Oh, Marge, grow up!
MAN: Congressman, this is
Springfield National Forest.
Now, basically, what we
want to do is cut her down.
-Uh-huh.
-As you can see in our artist's rendition,
it's full of old growth,
just aging and festering away.
In comes our logging company
to thin out the clutter.
It's all part of nature's,
you know, cycle.
Well, Jerry, you're
a whale of a lobbyist
and I'd like to give you
a logging permit, I would,
but, uh, this isn't
like burying toxic waste.
People are gonna notice
those trees are gone.
Congressman, this is where
it gets awkward.
I-- I never quite know
how to put this.
I just want to--
Offer me a bribe?
-(laughing)
-(intercom buzzing)
(sighs)
What is it?
WOMAN: It's that little girl
from Springfield
who wrote the essay.
Could be a good photo-op.
Uh, sure, fine.
So where do we--
Not here. I've got a
little place that I use
for these,
uh... matters.
Call me tonight.
Well, hi there.
You must be Lisa Simpson.
Hello, sir.
Lisa, you're a doer.
And who knows?
Maybe someday you'll be
a congressman or a senator.
We have quite a few
women senators, you know.
Only two. I checked.
(chuckling)
You're a sharp one.
Well, how about
a few pictures?
Tot shot always plays
in the sticks.
Oh, isn't that nice?
Now there is a politician
who cares.
If I ever vote,
it will be for him.
(burping)
Mom?
(groans)
Lisa, the contest isn't for three hours.
I'm too excited
to sleep.
Anyone up for the Winifred
Beecher Howe Memorial?
Who's that?
An early crusader
for women's rights.
She led the Floor Mop
Rebellion of 1910.
Later she appeared on
the highly unpopular
75-cent piece.
(groans)
Okay, but you don't know
what you're missing.
Oh.
"I will iron your sheets
when you iron out
the inequities
in your labor laws."
Amen, sister.
I told you
no one ever came here.
(chuckles) So Bob, where do we
stand on Springfield Forest?
Do I get
my logging permit?
Let me put it
this way, Jerry.
Timber!
(both laughing)
Whoo!
What a pooch.
Woof-woof!
(sobbing)
How could I read my essay now?
I don't believe my own words.
LISA: Honest Abe--
he'll show me the way.
Mr. Lincoln--
MAN: Mr. Lincoln,
I need your advice.
What can I do to make this
a better country?
Is this a good time
to buy a house?
I can't get my boy
to brush properly.
Would I look good
with a moustache?
I tried using turpentine,
but that just made it worse.
(indistinct chatter)
(shouting)
Mr. Lincoln
My name is Lisa Simpson,
and I have a problem!
Mr. Jefferson,
my name is Lisa Simpson
and I have a problem.
I know your problem.
The Lincoln Memorial
was too crowded.
Sorry, sir,
it's just--
No one ever comes to see me.
I don't blame them.
I never did anything important--
just The Declaration
of Independence,
the Louisiana Purchase,
the dumbwaiter--
Uh, maybe I should be going.
I caught you at a bad time.
Wait!
Please don't go.
I get so lonely.
(indistinct chatter)
(laughing)
The truth must be told.
(Bart moaning)
Rudy, my man,
you're a miracle worker.
Your laundry, sir.
There you go.
Buy yourself
something nice.
Thank you!
Bart, are you ready to go to--
(screams)
I'll room service you!
Before you kill me,
remember, this trip
is all expenses paid.
(both chuckling)
♪ The deficit rag ♪
♪ Oh, yeah,
the deficit rag ♪
♪ Those budget gaps can be
a 12-digit drag ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
♪ That's the deficit ♪
♪ They really made
a mess of it ♪
♪ That's the deficit rag ♪
Thank you!
Oh, this guy is awful.
I know, honey,
but just sit still.
Welcome, everyone,
to the awards luncheon.
I'd like to introduce
our distinguished judges
who will select
our scholarship winner.
Former Redskins great,
Alonzo Flowers,
perennial third party candidate,
Wilson DeFarge,
senate page Brad Fletcher,
skin care consultant Rowena,
and wealthy gadabout
Chilton Gaines.
Our first essayist
will be Lisa Simpson.
Lisa?
(audience gasping)
Oh, there she is.
Lisa Simpson will now read
her essay...
I would like to read
a different essay, if I may?
Um... okay.
The city of Washington was built
on a stagnant swamp
some 200 years ago,
and very little has changed.
It stank then and it stinks now.
Only today, it is
the fetid stench of corruption
that hangs in the air.
Cool! A ruckus.
Hmm!
LISA:
...and who did I see
taking a bribe
but the "honorable" Bob Arnold.
(gasping)
But don't worry, Congressman.
I'm sure you can buy
all the votes you need
with your dirty money
and this will be one nation
under the dollar
with liberty
and justice for none.
(audience booing)
(gasping)
Senator, there's a problem at
the essay contest.
Please, son,
I'm very busy.
A little girl is
losing faith in democracy.
Good Lord!
Congressman,
we want to drill for oil
in Teddy Roosevelt's head.
Well...
Teddy who?
(laughing)
Congressman...
you're under arrest.
You work fast.
I work for Uncle Sam.
We will now vote
on the House Bill 1022--
The expulsion of Bob Arnold.
Mr. Speaker,
I'm all for the bill, but...
shouldn't we tack on
a pay raise for ourselves?
ALL: No!
Okay, this should make
my bosses very happy.
Your bosses?
Yep. All 250 million of them.
When my family arrived
in this country four months ago
we spoke no English and had
no money in our pockets.
Today, we own a nationwide chain
of wheel-balancing centers.
Where else but in America--
or possibly Canada--
could our family find
such opportunity?
That's why whenever I see
the stars and stripes,
I'll always be reminded of
that wonderful word, "flag."
(cheering)
There will be a brief recess
while the judges tabulate
their votes.
Lisa,
what's gotten into you?
Yeah, your other speech was
a little more crowd pleasing.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I couldn't think of a nice way
to say America stinks.
Extra! Extra!
Feds nab rotten rep!
Give me one of those.
MARGE:
"Imprisoned congressman
becomes
born-again Christian."
I can't believe it.
The system works.
♪ The trading gap shuffle ♪
♪ We're in
a heap of trouble ♪
♪ Doing the trading gap
shuffle, yes, sir ♪
He already sang this song.
No, that was about
the budget gap.
This is the trading gap.
(applause)
And now the moment of truth.
Will the winning essay be
"Bubble On, Oh, Melting Pot,"
"Lift High Your Lamp,
Green Lady,"
"U.S.A. A-Okay,"
or "Cesspool on the Potomac"?
Cesspool! Cesspool!
Cesspool! Cesspool! Cesspool!
And now the winner is...
"U.S.A. A-Okay"
by Trong Van Dinh.
D'oh!
Miss Crowley, thank you
for this oversized
novelty check.
I would like
to share this honor
with all
of my fellow essayists,
particularly
the courageous Lisa Simpson
whose inflammatory
rhetoric reminded us
that the price of freedom
is eternal vigilance.
Give her the check!
(laughing)
I was serious.
♪ Say, let me tell you
about Lisa S. ♪
♪ She's that little
8-year-old muckrakeress ♪
♪ She caught a crook
and really made him pay ♪
♪ She did it all
in just one day ♪
♪ That's what I would call
being on the ball! ♪
SINGER: Ow!
Bart!
Lis, you taught me to stand up
for what I believe in.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.