♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
I hold in my hand
the final ax.
(kids cheering)
(grunts)
Ah, heh...
(laughing)
Well, kids, that's all the time
we have for today.
I'd like to thank Sideshow Mel,
Corporal Punishment,
Tina Ballerina,
oh, and from Knots Landing,
Miss Donna Mills.
Oh, she was a sport.
♪ We've had lots and lots ♪
♪ and lots and lots
and lots of fun ♪
♪ But now the time
has come... to go ♪
♪ If this old clown
was found dead in his bed ♪
♪ Tomorrow
I'd be in heaven ♪
♪ Still doing this show ♪
See you some other time!
(laughing)
(cheering)
(groans)
Great show, Krusty.
I really laughed when you--
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where's my nicotine gum?
Ah, that's the stuff!
Damn, I'm exhausted.
Those kids were like
ice out there.
You've got
a 4:30 merchandising meeting.
-Cancel it!
-Therapist?
-Personal trainer?
-Cancel it!
-The opening line on the Giants is 5 1/2.
Put a dime on it.
"Thank you" dinner
with Bart Simpson?
I don't know any
Bart Simpson.
Krusty, he's the boy
who saved you from jail.
Well, we made a terrible,
terrible mistake.
Uh...
won't happen again.
Well, there was one boy
who trusted me all along.
-Bart?
-Yes, sir?
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Cancel it!
(phone ringing)
-Hello?
-Mrs. Simpson?
This is Lois Pennycandy,
Krusty the Clown's
executive assistant.
Oh, hello, Mrs. Pennycandy.
(sighs)
It's Miss Pennycandy, I can assure you.
I'm sorry to inform you
that Krusty will once again,
not be joining Bart for dinner.
Oh, dear, this is the
fifth time he's cancelled.
How can he hurt someone
who loves him so?
Oh, Mrs. Simpson,
I've wasted my womanhood
asking that same question.
I apologize for him.
Something really important
came up at the last minute.
Lousy mildew!
(grumbles)
That's good enough.
Well, thank you for calling.
Good-bye.
(groans)
Okay, Milhouse, how many Krusty
autographs should I put you down for?
-A hundred.
-Consider it done.
♪ You're walkin'
along the street ♪
♪ Or you're at a party ♪
♪ Or else you're alone ♪
♪ And then you suddenly
dig, dig, dig ♪
♪ This could be the start
of something big ♪
Sweetie, I'm sorry
but Krusty isn't coming
to dinner again.
Oh, man.
"Dear Krusty,
This is Bart Simpson,
"Krusty Buddy number 16302
"respectfully returning
his badge.
"I always suspected that
nothing in life mattered.
"Now I know for sure.
Get bent. Bart Simpson."
Ooh, sex-chat!
WOMAN: You've reached
the party line.
In a moment,
you'll be connected to a hot party
with some of the world's
most beautiful women.
Now let's join the party.
Hello?
Are there
any women here?
Hello?!
Are you a
beautiful woman?
Do I sound like
a beautiful woman?!
This is not as hot
a party as I had anticipated.
Read this!
Uh... I, um...
uh... uh...
"Dee..." uh...
"deee..."
"Dear...
"Krus-s-s-t...
Why..?"
It says that the little boy
who never lost faith in you
has lost faith in you.
Krusty, you are going to Bart Simpson's
house for dinner tonight!
But I have plans.
Hey! Not the face!
Why, you maddening,
impossible man!
If you don't go tonight,
I won't be here tomorrow.
Oh, all right, I'll go.
Oh, Krusty!
But I sure hate missing
Schnapps Night at the Friar's Club.
Bart, wipe your feet.
Why bother?
They'll just
get dirty again.
I've got some good news.
Krusty the Clown is coming
to dinner tonight.
-He is? For sure?
-Yes.
God bless that clown.
-(rhythmic knocking)
-(horn honks)
-(Krusty laughing)
-You think it's him?
Hi, kids!
Hey, hey!
(laughs)
-Cute kid.
-(doorbell rings)
Oh, hi, Bart.
I was just in
the neighborhood--
What? Krusty the Clown!
What a surprise!
Milhouse, you can come in,
and drop the charade.
-Whoa!
-(laughing)
BART: Krusty, you don't have
to be on tonight.
What are you
talking about?
Of course, he does.
No, Dad. Krusty
is our guest.
Your pratfalls
and Punchinello antics
aren't necessary here.
Really?
Yeah. Just relax
and be yourself.
Oh, that's a relief.
-(screeches)
-Go wait in the car.
(hooting)
Aw! We could have seen
a monkey.
Who wants
to say grace?
Why don't we
let our guest do it.
Bless us, oh, Lord--
Hey!
Krusty, would you
do the honors?
Well, all right.
I'm a little rusty,
but, um... I'll try.
Baruch ata adonai
eloheinu melech ha-olam
ha-motzi lechem
min ha-aretz.
(laughs)
He's talking
funny talk.
No, Dad,
that's Hebrew.
Krusty must be Jewish.
A Jewish entertainer?
Get out of here!
Dad, there are many prominent
Jewish entertainers
including Lauren Bacall,
Dinah Shore, William Shatner,
and Mel Brooks.
Mel Brooks
is Jewish?!
(crying)
Krusty, are you all right?
Yes, it's just that saying
the Brucha brings back
a lot of
painful memories.
The old days...
my-- my father.
Hey, Krusty, you
going to finish
that meat loaf,
or what?
(sobbing)
Poor Krusty.
He's like a black velvet
painting come to life.
Krusty, why don't you
tell us what's wrong?
You'll feel better.
-Yeah, spill your guts, man.
-Yeah, yeah, come on.
Krusty, tell us.
Well, okay.
First of all,
my real name isn't
Krusty the Clown.
It's Herschel Krustofski.
My father was a rabbi.
His father was a rabbi.
His father's father--
Well, you get the idea.
My father was
the most respected man
in the lower east side
of Springfield.
People would come
from miles around
to ask his advice.
Reb Krustofski,
should I finish college?
Yes. No one is poor except
he who lacks knowledge.
Rabbi, should I have
another child?
Yes. Another child would be
a blessing on your house.
Rabbi, should I
buy a Chrysler?
Could you rephrase that
as an ethical question?
Um... is it right
to buy a Chrysler?
Yes-- for great is the car
with power steering
and Dyna-Flo suspension.
Papa?
When I grow up,
can I be a clown?
No! A clown is not respected
member of the community.
But I wanna make people laugh.
Herschel, life is not fun.
Life is serious.
Seltzer is for drinking,
not for spraying.
Pie is for noshing,
not for throwing.
-But, Papa--
-But nothing!
You'll do as I say
or you'll get
such a zetz
that you won't even know
what hit you.
Dad wanted me to follow
in his footsteps,
but the pull of clowning
was too strong.
I got my first big laughs
at Yeshiva
impersonating my father.
Blah, blah, blah... Moses!
Blah, blah, blah...
(laughing)
(children gasping)
(choking)
Boy, you don't have to follow
in my footsteps.
Don't worry.
I don't even like using
the bathroom after you.
Why, you little--!
Krusty,
please continue.
Okay.
My father tried to extinguish
the comedy bug,
but it was no use.
What are you doing
in that bathroom?
Go away.
Open the door this instant!
-Oy, gevalt!
-Close the door!
Then came my big break.
A Talmudic conference
in the Catskills,
and I was the entertainment.
(applause)
But the Lord works
in mysterious ways.
(oohs and ahhs)
(gasps)
Do you know that
my son, Herschel,
was first
in his Yeshiva class.
As a matter of fact,
he was voted
the most likely
to hear God.
Oh, go on, Hyman,
you're exaggerating again.
You're so proud of your son.
A rabbi would
never exaggerate.
A rabbi composes.
He creates thoughts.
He tells stories that
may never have happened,
but he does not exaggerate.
My father would have
never suspected a thing
were it not for
one, rowdy rabbi.
Hey, funny man!
No, no, no!
(crowd laughing)
Herschel?
Herschel,
oy vey iz mir!
You have brought shame
on our family.
If you were a musician
or a jazz singer
this I could forgive,
but this?
I never want
to see you again...
you-- you clown!
(sobbing)
I haven't seen
my father since.
That is so sad.
Krusty, do you think about
your father a lot?
All the time.
Except when I'm at the track.
Then it's all business.
KRUSTY: Oh, look...
Aww... hmm.
Oh, look at you, Bart.
Oh, isn't that fun!
Ooh, hey! Whoa!
Oh, Fourth of July.
I can't believe that little boy
in the pictures is you, Bart.
Yeah. I got a lot
of fond memories.
Well, look at the time.
Almost midnight.
Do you have any yearbooks?
No, that's it.
You've seen everything.
So, Milhouse, know any
"knock, knock" jokes?
(crying)
I want to go home.
Homer, maybe you better
take Milhouse home.
Gladly.
Wow! The Concert For Bangladesh.
BART: Good night, Krusty.
Sorry about
your Dad.
Don't worry about me--
I'm a survivor.
Hey, did I leave
my keys inside?
ALL: No!
Oh, yeah. Here they are.
(laughing)
Ehh...
KRUSTY:
Hmm... ah... uh... ohh!
(gasps)
(groans)
(crying)
ANNOUNCER:
Academy Award Playhouse
now returns you to
"Hercules Versus
the Martians."
MAN: Welcome to our spaceship,
mighty Hercules. Heh-heh.
(phone ringing)
Hello? Hello?!
Anybody there?
What's this?
I hear a phone ring,
and all of a sudden,
there's nothing.
I'm listening,
and there's no talking.
Hello. Mister?
Who are ya'?
Why would they call ya if
they don't want to talk to ya?
(sigh)
(phone disconnects)
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy
Show! ♪
(grunting)
Huh?
Hee-hee-hee!
BOTH: Aahh!
(grunting)
(laughing)
Didn't Itchy Junior
look happy
playing with his father?
And didn't Scratchy Junior
look happy
playing with his Dad
until they got run over
by the thresher?
Wasn't that
a beautiful cartoon?
(sobbing)
For the love of God,
cut to a commercial!
Poor Krusty!
The man who envies
our family
is the man
who needs help.
We've got
to do something.
Let's move.
Reverend Lovejoy,
we need you to help
us find a rabbi.
Well, before you make
any rash decisions,
let me just remind you
that the church is changing
to meet the needs of
today's young Christians.
No, no.
We're not converting.
We just want to find
a Rabbi Krustofski.
Rabbi Krustofski.
Wh--
I do a radio call-in show
with him every Sunday night.
-Really?
-I didn't know that.
I mention it
in my sermon every week.
Oh, that radio show.
Oh yeah, it's all
the kids talk about
on Monday at school.
Well, why don't you have
a free T-shirt?
You'll be the coolest kids
on the playground.
We'll put them on later.
Now, can you give us
the rabbi's address?
Oh, sure thing.
Let me check my
non-Christian Rolodex.
LISA: I bet the rabbi
misses Krusty.
BART: He'll be so happy,
he'll be crying in his beard.
(muttering in Hebrew)
Oh, yes, yes.
LISA: Excuse us,
Rabbi Krustofski?
What can I do for you,
my young friend?
We came to talk to you
about your son.
I have no son!
Oh great, we came all this way,
and it's the wrong guy.
I didn't mean that
literally!
♪ KBBL, talk radio ♪
DEEJAY: And, in order to keep
our broadcasting license,
we devote
Sunday night dead time
to public service shows
of limited appeal.
In that spirit, we bring you
Gabbin' About God,
sponsored by Ace Religious Supply,
where they say
"If we don't got it,
it ain't holy."
With us tonight, once again,
our very own three wise men,
Reverend Timothy Lovejoy,
Monsignor Kenneth Daly
and Rabbi
Hyman Krustofski.
-Good to see you again.
-Nice to see you.
Okay, our first caller
is from Shelbyville Heights.
MAN: Yes, hi. With all the
suffering and injustice in the world,
do you ever wonder
if God really exists?
-No.
-Not for a second.
Not at all.
Great.
Good conversation there.
Our next call now is
for the good rabbi.
Hello?
-(heavy breathing)
-Anybody there?
I hear breathing,
but I don't hear talking.
What's going on here?
Hello, mister? Hello? Hello?
(heavy sighing)
Some people got nothing to do
but call people and hang up.
There's all kinds of
mishagoyim in the world.
Okay, let's clear the board.
Our next caller is
a young boy from
right here in Springfield.
BART:
Hello. My name is Dmitri.
I'm a first-time caller,
long-time listener.
My question is...
if a son defies his father
and chooses a career
that makes millions
of children happy,
shouldn't the father
forgive the son?
-I think so.
-Yes, of course.
No way! Absolutely not!
Never, never!
Who screens these calls? Who's
in charge here? There's nobody in charge?
They leave a building
without people watching it? And anybody--
Don't worry, Lis,
I got a plan that can't fail.
Yiddle, my man,
you're a genius.
I love my work.
Oh, the best charity is to give
and not let other people know.
But what if your example
encourages others to give?
MEN: Ahh.
Speaking of charity,
Rabbi Krustofski,
don't you think it's time
you forgave your son?
Don't you understand
that my boy broke my heart!
He turned his back
on our traditions,
on our faith, and on me.
Get out of here,
you little pisher.
Oy, this guy's tough.
Bart, we're gonna have to
outsmart him.
I don't know.
He's pretty sharp.
He saw right through
this disguise.
What? Saul Bellow?
The Nobel Prize-winning
Jewish novelist?
He wants to have
lunch with me?
Ha ha! It's a date.
Izzy's Deli, 1:00.
I'll be there.
The French government
wants to give me
the Legion of Honor?
Where do I receive
this prestigious award?
Izzy's Deli, 1:00.
Thank you, Monsieur President.
Au revoir.
Are you kids ready
to order yet?
Sorry, no.
Just get us another bowl
of complimentary pickles.
Watch how fast
I go.
And for you, sir?
I want a nice sandwich,
but the Joey Bishop--
Too fatty.
The Jackie Mason-- I don't know.
Sauerkraut makes me gassy.
The Bruce Willis?
I don't even
like his work.
What is this--
a Krusty the Clown?
Ham, sausage and bacon,
with a smidge of mayo.
-What?
-On white bread.
Listen! You tell
Mr. Saul Bellow
the Nobel Prize-winning
Jewish novelist
that I lost my appetite.
(Krusty humming
"The Marseilles")
Could you direct me to President
Francois Mitterand's table?
You think you're funny?
50 million Frenchmen
can't be wrong.
(groans)
Bart, we've been going
about this all wrong.
What's the one thing rabbis
prize above everything else?
Those stupid hats?
No, Bart-- knowledge.
LISA: We're gonna hit him
where it hurts--
right in the Judaica.
(imitates thunder)
Glub, glub, glub.
"Oh, Noah, Noah,
save us, save us!"
"No!"
This looks good, Bart.
Take it to him.
You I told to go away.
But-- But Rabbi, does it not say
in the Babylonian Talmud,
and I quote:
"A child should be pushed aside
with the left hand
and drawn closer
with the right."?
Yes.
Then doesn't your
religion command you
to make up with Krusty?
But in Exodus,
the Fifth Commandment says,
"Honor thy father
and thy mother."
End of story.
-Oh, it's hopeless.
-Not quite.
I got some dynamite stuff
from Rabbi Simon Ben-Eliazar.
"At all times let a man
be supple as a reed
and not rigid
as a cedar."
Bart, my short, learned friend,
the Book of Joshua says,
"You shall meditate on the Torah
all day and all night."
(murmured approval)
(yawning)
Hmm...
Is it not written
in the Talmud,
"Who will bring
redemption?
The jesters."
Sorry my friend,
I'm still not convinced,
and this is hardly the time
or place to discuss it.
Here you go, Bart.
It's a long shot,
but that's all I can do
without learning
ancient Hebrew.
Bart, I am not gonna learn
Rabbi, did not
a great man say,
and I quote, "The Jews are
a swinging bunch of people.
"I mean, I've heard
of persecution
"but what they went through
is ridiculous.
"But the great thing is
after thousands of years
"of waiting and
holding on and fighting,
they finally made it."
End quote.
Oh, I never heard
the plight of my people
phrased so eloquently.
Who said that?
Rabbi Hillel?
-Nope.
-Judah the Pious?
-Maimonides?
-Nope
-Ooh, I got it!
-The Dead Sea Scrolls!
-I'm afraid not, Rabbi.
It's from "Yes, I Can,"
by Sammy Davis, Jr.
An entertainer,
like your son.
(gasps)
The Candy Man?
If a performer can
think that way,
maybe I'm completely upside
down on this whole problem.
All the years of joy
that I've lost.
Why? Because of
my stubborn ways.
(crying)
There, there, Rabbi.
It's not too late.
(grunting)
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Hi, kids.
Today's show's gonna be
the funniest, side-splittingest
cavalcade of...
Aw, the hell with it.
Roll the cartoon.
♪ They bite and fight ♪
♪ They fight
and fight and bite ♪
♪ Fight, fight, fight,
bight, bight, bight ♪
♪ The Itchy-- ♪
Oh, yeah. My old friends,
right next to my heart.
Hey, such
a filthy habit.
Who asked you?
Father?
-Son.
-Papa!
-Herschel!
-Daddy!
Boychick!
Oh, Daddy!
You're on, Krusty.
Oh, uh...
Boys and girls,
I'd like to be serious
for a moment, if I may.
Spotlight, please.
I just wanted--
I just want--
Come on, guys.
I'm not doing
the spotlight bit.
Let's have a warm Krusty welcome
for my estranged father
Rabbi Hyman Krustofski.
(cheering)
Lenny,
a little reconciliation
music, if you please.
♪ Oh, mein papa ♪
♪ To me he was
so wonderful ♪
♪ Oh, mein papa ♪
Come on, Dad.
♪ To me he was so good ♪
You know the words.
♪ No one could be ♪
♪ So gentle
and so loveable ♪
I got something in my eye.
Here, take my hankie.
Ehh!
♪ He always understood ♪♪
We haven't seen each other
in 25 years!
Oh, I love you, son.
I love you, too, Daddy.
Oy, a klop tsu deer!
(laughing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.