Twelve Cylon models
Seven are known
Four live in secret
One will be revealed
Previously on Battlestar Galactica.
I think the nova does look like
the mandala inside this temple.
Maybe it was a road sign
on the path to Earth.
It was on the temple.
But where'd you get the
idea to paint yours?
It was just something I've been
doodling since I was a kid.
I liked the pattern.
Starbuck, you're getting too low.
Come on, Lee. Get her out of there.
You come back!
Just let me go.
They're waiting for me.
No!
Gaius Baltar, after carefully
weighing the evidence,
this tribunal finds you not guilty.
Get him back!
Get him out of here!
Gaius, it's okay.
Come with me.
Where are you taking me to?
To your new life.
We're going to the Ionian nebula.
- Sitrep!
- Sensors show major power fluctuations.
Checking on fleet.
It's true.
We're Cylons.
And we have been from the start.
Dradis contact!
Massive Cylon fleet on intercept course.
I want emergency jump, the entire fleet.
Sir, all fleet ships were powered
down during the outage.
It'll take at least 20 minutes to
spool up the FTL drives.
We just don't have 20 minutes.
Action stations.
Set condition one throughout the ship.
This is not a drill.
All viper pilots report
to vipers immediately.
I have a bogey at my ten.
I'm gonna go check it out.
Whoa! What the frak?
Hi, Lee.
Kara?
I've been to Earth.
I know where it is.
And I'm gonna take us there.
No.
No, no, this is frakkin' crazy.
I saw your ship blow up.
Afraid not.
Did you not hear me?
I've been to Earth.
Earth.
Big blue oceans, fluffy white clouds.
You're gonna love it.
I promise.
Identify that ship immediately.
Sir, I'm checking for
colonial recognition codes.
Get Lee online!
I'm trying, sir.
I'm picking up her ship's signature.
- That's her voice all right.
- Hold on, hold on.
It is not real. It is a trick.
- Duplicate verification.
- Checking.
Hostiles inbound!
200 plus!
Cag, take 'em out!
All players, Galactica.
Threat b-r-3-5-0 carom 2-1-1.
Raptors, lean back as missile pickets.
Weapons free.
Don't lose me this time, Apollo.
Oh, not a chance.
Splash one!
Take that, you frakkin' toasters!
Admiral, it's a Cylon trick.
The vipers have stopped
the main Cylon thrust,
But the reserves have
broken through, sir.
I want everything that can
fly up there immediately.
Saul.
Saul!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Nothing, Bill.
Never felt better in my life.
Colonel Tigh!
I gave you an order.
Everybody that's ever held a stick,
I want them up there now.
Get 'em out!
- Put 'em up there!
- Sir.
Attention.
This is the XO.
All pilots, man your aircraft.
- All right, let's go!
Get out there and kill those bastards.
Get that bird over to 2
Where the frak are these nuggets?
Come on, mama's not gonna
save you today! Let's go!
You want to fly or not?
Come on, ready or not, let's go.
Hey, hey, this is crazy.
What if I get up there
and another switch...
flips in my head and
turns me against my own?
What the frak is wrong with you?
Shut the frak up.
It's like the colonel said, okay?
Just think of that.
Be the man you want to
be till the day you die.
That's all easier said than done,
because I don't know what
the frak I am right now.
You're Samuel T. Anders.
That's all you gotta remember.
Samuel T. Anders. Now get
the frak in your ship.
- Who else would he be?
- Hey.
Hey, rook.
Stay cool out there, all right?
Yeah.
You'll lock in and do what
you've been trained to do.
Guess it's just like suiting up for
a championship game, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Good hunting.
Well, if she didn't notice anything,
maybe the other Cylons won't either.
Yeah, well, don't wait to find out.
Shoot first.
Get the frak in there.
Go kill something.
Let's go! Let's load these birds!
- Anders, get the frak in your viper!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where are you taking me?
It's a place we found.
An unused compartment.
Sir, we've lost Sphyxis!
Oh, my gods, captain Tarney.
600 souls on that ship.
How did they find us?
That's the question, isn't it?
Base ships launching missiles.
40--correction, 50 plus inbound.
Half targeted on us, half on the fleet.
Have triple-a target only missiles
going towards the fleet.
We can handle the hits.
- They can't.
- Sir.
All forces, priority intercept enemy
missiles targeting civilian vessels.
Okay.
I am Samuel T. Anders.
I was born on Picon.
I went to Noyce elementary school.
Get your thumb off the
transmit button, Sam.
- You're blocking the freq.
- Copy that.
Oh, frak me.
Longshot, hardball.
Turkey, right four low
at three, committing.
Longshot, I got the--
Tally, I got your back.
Seelix, there's a raider on you!
Shoot, Anders!
I'm trying to.
Gods, Come on!
Sir, the Cylon strike force has
just turned back to their ships.
Base ships are spinning up.
They're pulling out.
We're gonna do the same damn thing
before they change their mind.
Helo, have our fighters
cover our withdrawal.
Yes, sir.
- All fighters assume
rear cover formation.
They had us.
Game over.
Why the hell did they let us go?
Maybe something's changed.
Like what?
I have no idea, madame president.
No idea.
-=www.Ydy.Com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET - »ð¼ý
Battlestar Galactica
Season 4 Episode 1
You'll be safe here, Gaius.
Right.
Chief, I'm gonna need you to develop
my gun camera footage asap.
I've got a hell of a set
of vacation pictures.
I'll take my post-flight checklist.
I want to sign out so I
can get in the showers.
I don't have one for you.
What's up?
Okay.
Okay, me too. It's okay, it's okay.
Do you believe in miracles?
No.
I told everyone that you were
too frakkin' mean to kill.
Okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
What the hell are you
doing in a jock smock?
I just finished viper transition
a week ago, and I started ACM.
- How the...?
- Starbuck!
I did it, boss.
I found Earth.
Everybody move back.
Move in. Step away!
I need you in sickbay.
Cottle's gonna give you a
complete physical examination.
Okay, what the hell's going on?
I'm off the ship for a few hours
- and everybody's acting--
- A few hours?
Kara, you were gone for over two months.
That's impossible.
My ship's clock reads
six hours and change.
Then your clock's wrong, Kara.
Sam's telling you the truth.
We thought you were dead.
What?
Gaius, I just wanted you to know
that we'll be back soon.
Whatever you do, please don't
go anywhere by yourself.
It's not safe.
Tracey's here for anything you need.
We'll be back as soon as
we've looked in on Derrick.
Okay?
- Right...
- oh, Derrick.
That's your little boy, isn't it?
The one in sickbay.
Right.
Yes, I--I'm praying for his recovery.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
It's a pleasure.
Thank you.
So what's the game plan, ladies?
Game plan?
Well, this place is brilliant really.
You know, it's beautiful.
Just when am I getting out of here?
When I am getting off the ship?
Well, security's too tight.
- Besides...
- Besides what?
You're just trying
to keep me here and--
Gaius,
None of the other ships will have you.
We'll be back.
Yesterday, you were facing execution.
Today you're free.
Why the long face?
Oh, gee, I don't know.
From president of the colonies to this.
King of fools.
Probably best to be hated by
everyone than loved by this lot.
Doomed to live out the rest of
my life in this loony bin.
I don't know, that might have something
to do with my rather savage mood swings.
Relax, Gaius.
You think I've brought you this
far just to let it end here?
I need some encouragement.
A ray of hope about the future.
- An inkling...
- You've got me.
I'm here for you.
That is so beautiful.
Hello. Sorry, what?
The way you were praying.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Oh, thank you, yeah.
Not some hollow ritual.
No, no.
It's as if the gods are
right here beside you.
Well, yeah.
When I pray to the gods, I feel...
empty.
Do you? That's a shame, isn't it?
Her gods are false.
Tell her.
Well, if you feel empty when you pray
to Zeus or Poseidon or Aphrodite,
it's because it is empty.
It's a totally empty experience.
They're...they're not real.
They've been promulgated by...
a ruling elite,
to stop you from learning the truth.
And what truth is that?
Um, that's a very good question.
- What is the--the
- There's only one god.
There is only one god.
In a nutshell, that's the truth.
We're alone here, aren't we?
The others aren't coming back soon.
And the door is locked.
All right, good.
Can you feel god's presence?
You know what? I think I do.
- So do I.
- Do you? Do you too?
We both--we both feel--
So what's Cottle's verdict?
Everything checks out.
So I'm me, not a Cylon?
That is why you had me tested, right?
- Kara, nobody said you were Cylon.
- But you were thinking it.
We had to be sure, Kara.
Fair enough.
Let's go through it again.
How many times do you want to hear it?
As many times as it takes to make sense.
I followed a heavy
raider into the storm.
Took some hits, passed out.
When I came to, I was
orbiting this planet.
It's yellow moon and star matches
the description in Pythia.
I took these pictures in orbit.
The star patterns match what we
saw in the tomb of Athena.
How did you get here?
I told you I don't know exactly.
Well, that's just not
good enough, captain.
Tell us everything you remember.
I remember taking the photos.
Turning my ship in a reciprocal heading.
And then I'm not sure.
I must've blacked out again.
I remember a giant
gas planet with rings.
I remember a flashing triple star
and a comet.
And then I was back with the fleet.
And for you, all of this took six hours.
I do not understand the time
discrepancy either, okay?
All I know is I was there.
I took the pictures.
I didn't imagine it!
I had my crew clean it up.
There's not a ding or a scratch on it.
It's the got same tail number
as the one she flew out on.
But I've been fixing up that
old bird since day one,
And this thing looks like it's been
rolled off the showroom floor.
So it's not the same ship.
Unless she found a hell of a body shop
out there, no, ma'am, it's not.
Admiral, it's just not
the outside either.
This is the data from the nav computer.
There isn't any.
It's blank.
There's no record of
where this ship has been.
Okay.
Put her in the brig.
What?
So some things don't add up, and we're
back to thinking she's a Cylon?
- What about Cottle's test?
- Cottle's test doesn't prove anything.
Even if her dna's the same,
she could still be a Cylon.
She could've been one
from the beginning.
Baltar's Cylon detector was a crock.
It failed to I.D. Boomer.
I know how you feel about her, Bill,
But that is exactly what the Cylons
could be counting on here.
Then we're back where we started from.
There could be Cylons right here,
and we wouldn't know it till they
put a bullet in our heads.
Or lead us into an ambush.
They Cylon fleet had enough firepower
to blow us out of the sky,
but instead they ran and jumped.
And there's Kara Thrace suddenly back
from the dead, having found Earth.
If Kara Thrace can lead
us off our course--
Course? What course?
The nebula was supposed to be another
clue on the way to Earth, but it--
The nebula is only a road sign
along the way to Earth.
And we need to continue
to follow its path.
Well, what if Kara is the clue that
we were supposed to find?
And what if she's playing you?
And all of us?
Gaius, please, can you help me?
- Uh, what's going on?
- Okay.
- Oh, god, um...
- Watch his head.
It's Derrick.
Derrick, is it?
Uh, Derrick, I see.
Where are my clothes?
- It's okay.
- Is it?
Well, did they give you a diagnosis?
- They said he's got,
um, viral encephalitis.
Viral?
I don't know, it's some
inflammation of the brain.
Can't the doctors do something?
Well, not if it's viral, no.
I'm afraid it's up to
Derrick's immune system.
Uh, and he has to be strong.
And we have to be strong for him.
I didn't want him to die
in that sickbay, so...
So I brought him here.
So he can be with us.
All of us.
Yeah, all of us.
Give me your hand, please.
I wish there was--
You know I prayed for him, don't you?
- I know.
- I prayed for him.
I know.
I guess.
I guess that the one true god just
doesn't want him to live, right?
Anybody still hearing
that frakkin' song?
Nope.
Maybe it stopped when we figured
out who...what we are.
Could it have been some kind of trigger?
To switch us on?
You know, after that raider scanned
me with that red light,
damn thing just cut and ran.
They all did.
You think it recognized you as a Cylon?
I don't know.
Maybe that's why it didn't shoot me.
More important, why didn't I shoot him?
Racetrack was right.
- You just made a dumb nugget mistake.
- Did I?
Maybe I was programmed to
leave my gun safeties on.
Those bastards can't
program me to help them.
No way.
Boomer thought the same thing.
And then she shot the old man.
Boomer didn't know what she was.
We do.
That is not gonna happen.
Agreed?
I don't know why I'm here.
Yes, I do.
I'm here because of the
things that we've shared
- and the things that we've seen.
- The visions in the opera house.
You went inside. You
saw more than I did.
I thought that maybe you could help me.
Help you how?
I need to know about the other five.
The types we've never seen.
The ones that Baltar
calls the final five.
And you want to know if
Kara Thrace is one of them.
Yes.
I've been programmed
never to think about them.
Well, your programming isn't working,
because you're thinking
about them right now.
I try not to.
Trying not to is thinking about them.
How do you rationalize that?
All right, no.
Back off.
Don't leave, back off.
The five are close.
What?
I can feel them.
What about this one?
It's a protoplanetary system.
So?
Nothing but rocks.
No ringed gas giants like
you claimed you saw.
I did see it, lieutenant.
If you say so, sir.
And what are you saying, Mr. Gaeta?
I'm not saying anything, sir.
I'm just following orders.
Well, I'm ordering you to help me.
- You're ordering me?
- Mr. Gaeta, take a break.
With pleasure, sir.
Jump clock is running, Dee.
Take us out of here.
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
I see it on his face.
On all of their faces.
No one believes me.
You want people to believe you?
Find that star system.
It's a big waste of time.
Hey, we've only been at it a few hours.
Found maybe a dozen trinaries.
Baltar's calculations took months.
It doesn't work like that.
How does it work, Kara?
It's a feeling.
An intuition.
I didn't use nav fixes
to get there and back.
When we were at that nebula,
it was so clear to me.
But every jump we take farther
away, the clarity fades.
If we keep jumping like this,
I won't be able to find our way back.
That'll be all.
All hands, prepare for jump in ten.
The president's adamant.
We're gonna continue on the course
laid out by the eye of jupiter.
Five, four, three, two, jump.
We're going the wrong way.
If we keep jumping like this,
I'm gonna lose the feeling completely,
never be able to take us back.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to go to
Laura Roslin, tell her...
forget Pythia and the Eye of Jupiter,
because Kara has some feeling
about where Earth is?
Yes.
I can't.
I just left your ship.
There's not a scratch on it.
It's brand-new.
How do you explain that, Kara?
Look at me.
Look at me!
I swear to gods.
It's me, Kara.
I can do this.
You once said you loved
me like a daughter.
If you still do, you've
gotta trust me on this one.
I can't afford to.
They're waiting for me.
No! No!
What should I believe?
Should I believe my heart?
Or my eyes?
They're waiting for me.
Well, you know where I stand.
I want to believe her.
But the president's right.
It's exactly what the Cylons
would be counting on.
So I guess you're not changing course.
For the time being,
we follow the president's lead.
She still staying in your quarters?
Just till we find a place to put her up...
to finish threst of
her doloxan treatment.
I want to thank you for suiting
up during the fight.
We needed everyone up there.
We still do.
I took those off for the wrong reasons.
Put them back on.
Baltar's trial may have
been the trigger, but, um...
This is a feeling I've
been having for a while.
It's time for a change.
I need to move on.
I've had some feelers
from the government.
There's a position opening up.
And I think I can make a
valuable contribution there.
Maybe even more than in the cockpit.
Dad, what if Zach had come
back to us in that viper?
If my brother had climbed
out of that cockpit.
Would it matter if he were a Cylon?
If he always had been?
When all's said and done,
would that change how we
really feel about him?
Please, god.
I'm only asking you this one last time.
Don't let this child die.
Has he sinned against you?
He can't have sinned against you.
He's not even had a life yet.
How can you take him and let me live?
After all I've done?
Really, if you want
someone to suffer, take me.
We both know I deserve it.
I have been selfish and weak.
I have failed so many people.
And I have killed.
I'm not asking for your forgiveness.
I'm just asking that you spare
the life of this innocent child.
Don't take him.
Take me.
Take me, take me please.
We were all very moved by the
way you prayed for Derrick.
Fat lot of good it did him.
Unfortunately, he's worse,
if you hadn't realized.
Doesn't mean god didn't hear you.
I'm sure he's looking after
Derrick's immortal soul.
Yes, I wish I shared your
confidence on that one.
I really do.
But you have to keep the faith.
- We all look to you for guidance
- well, you shouldn't, should you?
I mean, you're just--
Well, you're very young and--
What are we doing here exactly?
Thank you.
Mr. President.
Gaius, let's go.
- We should get back, okay?
- Good to see you again.
I'm sorry.
I can't--
We met at the groundbreaking
ceremony on New Caprica.
Introduced you to my son Kevin.
He told you he wanted to be
president when he grew up.
You told him that he could be
if he stuck to his schoolwork.
He's a redhead little boy, isn't he?
- About eight or nine years old.
- Seven.
- Seven years old.
How is, um...
- Kevin.
- Kevin?
- How is he?
- He's dead.
Your police shot him.
Come on, Gaius, let's get out of here.
Leave her alone!
- Look at me!
- Leave her alone!
Look at me!
Go on, scream.
Come on, scream!
I want to see if anyone
comes to help you.
Aah!
Scream!
Beg.
I bet you begged the Cylons.
Why don't you beg for me?
Come on, beg!
Get up! Get on your knees!
Get up!
You asked god to take your
life instead of the boy's.
- Did you mean it?
- Yes.
Do it.
Take my life.
Please.
Please take my life.
No.
You see?
Gaius, I knew god wouldn't desert you.
I mean, I felt his love
course through me,
Giving me the strength to smite them.
A little less smiting next time,
Unless you want to be held
up on murder charges.
Gaius!
- You two, watch the door.
- Gaius...
Are you all right?
I cut myself shaving.
Okay.
Well, you have to come.
You have to come and see Derrick.
Derrick?
Derrick, oh, yes.
God answered your prayers.
- You have to see.
- What?
Look.
Look at him.
Hi.
And no trace of a fever.
It's a miracle.
No one took it down.
Not the old man.
Not Lee.
Not even you, Sam.
You just got back, Kara.
We're all still trying
to get a handle on this.
You know, you gotta
cut people some slack.
Cut yourself some too.
When I woke up orbiting Earth,
I just figured it was
some crazy dream, but...
I went in following a heavy raider.
I mean, maybe the Cylons
pulled me out of the soup.
Captured me, brainwashed me.
On Caprica, and the experiment on me.
I mean, did they take pieces of me?
I mean, is it possible
that they grew me,
another me in a petri dish,
and they embedded me with the memories,
or it with the memories,
Or-- I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, hey, no.
Kara, no. Listen to me.
If you were a Cylon, then you've
been one from the beginning.
Like Boomer.
Spend my entire life
thinking I'm one thing--
Yeah, and then you wake up one day
and discover you're another.
Still doesn't change who you really are.
Still doesn't change the fact that
I love you no matter what.
You are a better person than I am, Sam,
because if I found out
that you were a Cylon,
I would put a bullet between your eyes.
All hands, prepare for jump
in four, three, two, jump.
Damn it, they're still going
in the wrong direction.
Oh, one more jump and I'm gonna
lose my way altogether.
All right, we gotta find you a rack.
Okay, take it easy.
It's Roslin.
The old man's not gonna listen
to me as along as she's--
I gotta get to her.
No, you can't do that.
- Is that a fact?
- Yeah.
No, no, wait!
What the hell are you doing, Kara?
Where's the president, Sam?
Kara, come on.
-=www.Ydy.Com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET - »ð¼ý, edit by rogard
To be continued...