TWELVE CYLON MODELS
SEVEN ARE KNOWN
FOUR LIVE IN SECRET
ONE WILL BE REVEALED
Previously on Battlestar Galactica
Aurora, goddess of the dawn.
I thought that it would be a nice
figurehead for your model ship.
A fresh start.
Thank you.
Starbuck, you're getting too low!
Come on, Lee, get her out of there.
You come back!
Just let me go.
No!
Baltar's trial may
have been the trigger,
but this is a feeling
I've been having for a while.
It's time for a change.
Please, God, don't let this child die.
How can you take him and let me live?
God answered your prayers.
You have to see.
Look at him.
And no trace of a fever.
It's a miracle.
I need to know about the other five.
The types we've never seen.
It's true.
We're cylons.
And we have been from the start.
Even after that raider scanned
me with that red light,
Damn thing just cut and ran.
You think it recognized you as a cylon?
Maybe that's why it didn't shoot me.
More important, why didn't I shoot him?
Okay, what the hell's going on?
I'm off the ship for a few hours,
- and everybody's acting--
- A few hours?
Kara, you were gone for over two months.
That's impossible.
How did you get here?
I told you, I don't know exactly.
Damn it, they're still going
in the wrong direction.
Another jump and
I'm gonna lose my way all together.
It's Roslin.
The old man's not gonna listen to me.
I gotta get to her.
No, no, wait!
Look alive!
And for frak sake,
don't shoot the godsdamned president!
Just let me talk to her.
Talk all you want,
but it ends with the first bang.
We're rollin' down here.
Starbuck's got the president.
Gaeta, take the com.
Move.
Move!
Come on.
Move, come on!
Over by the couch.
Now!
I want to hate you so much.
So much.
You had a vision.
Remember?
The arrow, the temple.
I went down to that planet with you,
and it was a frakkin' toaster party.
A lot of good people died. Remember?
Yes, I do.
I trusted you.
On a vision.
That's it.
A vision!
I saw.
Earth.
I saw it with my own eyes.
And it's calling me back.
We're going the wrong way.
Why can't you trust me?
Shoot me.
If you think I'm a cylon,
them I'm your enemy.
Shoot your enemy.
Take it!
I'm no more a cylon than you are.
And you know it.
I wish I did.
I've put my life on the line
for this frakkin' ship.
I have ate, slept, and fought next
to the people that I love.
I have pissed off my friends!
I have broken more rules
than I've followed!
I frakked up, okay!
I messed up!
But it's all that I have.
Those people are my family.
And none of us belong here.
Two down.
We've got two down!
Shoot me--if I'm a cylon, then shoot me!
They made you perfect, didn't they?
Down on the floor.
Down on the floor now! Now!
Let go of me!
What are-- get off me!
What are you doing?
I am not a cylon, Mathias!
- Madam president.
- Mathias! Gods!
- I don't...
- What the frak's going on here?
I thought you were on the move.
We were--she's out of her frakkin' mind!
- Gods!
- You all right?
Get off me!
Get off!
Listen to me, please.
I'm losing it.
The ringing.
The way to earth.
It's getting weaker.
Don't you understand?
Don't any of you understand?
It was so-- it was so clear.
Like it was coming from the next room.
Stop looking at me like that.
I can feel it slipping away.
Even without jumping as we move,
it's half of what it
was when I got here.
Half.
If we keep jumping, it'll be gone,
and we'll never find it again.
I thought that's what we wanted.
A way to earth.
Do you hear me?
- Get her out of here.
- Yes, let's go.
You better work on your aim,
because I'm not gonna stop!
You're gonna have to kill me!
One more jump and it'll be gone!
Admiral.
-=www.Ydy.Com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: »ð¼ý angie, edited by rogard
39,676 SURVIVORS
IN SEARCH OF A HOME
CALLED EARTH
Battlestar Galactica
Season 4 Episode 2
The excited state decays
by vibrational...
relaxation into the first
excited similar state
Yes yes and merrily we go
Reduce atmosphere nitrogen
by 0.03 percents.
It is not much consolation that
society will pick up the bits,
leaving us at** modern where punishment
rather than interdiction is paramount.
Please cut the fuse.
They will not harm their own.
End of Line. Limiting diffusions
to two dimensions and...
increases the number of evolutionary
jumps within the species.
Rise and measure the temple of the five.
Transformation is the goal.
They will not harm their own.
That...
The hybrid is clearly
telling us something.
The hybrid is always
They are supposed to maintain
operations on each ship,
Not vomiting metaphysics.
All right.
I give up. What? What is
she trying to tell us?
They're in the colonial
fleet with the humans.
They...? They who?
The Final Five.
The raiders refused to
fight because they sensed...
the Final Five might be
in the colonial fleet.
They could have been caught.
They could be in hiding.
No.... Stop.
Stop right now.
Turn around. Go and
take a cleansing walk...
and I am going to try and
forget what I've just heard.
The Final Five, Cavil, they are near!
This is far more important...
But their eyes must have
seen, witnessed over time...
- Do they look anything like us?
- That's enough.
Don't you realize what you are doing?
You'are openly discussing the Final Five.
That's forbidden.
You're toying with our survival.
Look at yourselves.
Look, there's millions of
Twos that have that nose...
millions of Sixes that possess that mouth,
Eights share those breasts
and Ones have this brain.
We're mechanized copies.
There's a reason the original programmers
clearly felt
that it's a mistake for us to
contact the Final Five!
No.
Violating that programming
threatens our survival!
Something has changed.
Thoughts have changed.
Yes, they change.
The raiders changed.
That's where all this started, with them.
Somehow they exceeded their programming,
and unlike us, they
can't correct themselves.
So we're gonna have to do it for them.
Do what?
We'll reconfigure their neural architecture,
and shave down their heuristic responses.
Dumb them down? Lobotomize them?
They're tools, not pets.
But in any case, it has to be done.
Says who?
Says God Almighty,
the voice of reason, that's who!
When are you gonna hear it?
You don't have the authority to make
any change without a majority vote.
Well, we'll vote.
The Fours and Fives will be on my side.
There will be a vote.
The raiders hear what we hear.
The raiders are simple machines.
No.
Something extraordinary has happened.
Something is calling to us.
Pushing us to discover our origins,
to understand our place in the universe.
The raiders are part of that,
- and the Final Five--
- Are anywhere but with the humans.
You're late.
I had to wait for Cally to nod off, okay?
She's having trouble sleeping.
- Did you see Kara?
- I saw her.
She's crazy as a latrine rat.
If anything, she's more
like Starbuck than ever.
She's my wife!
And the president nearly
put a bullet in her skull
because she suspected
her of being a cylon.
You are one!
We bring attention to ourselves,
we're frakked!
If Starbuck is one of us,
she's playing it big the other way.
The four of us heard the music
and sought each other out.
She hasn't.
We're still missing one.
Baltar.
Not Baltar, but when I found him
in the temple on the algae planet,
he was with one of those skin jobs.
The one they call D'Anna.
She saw something in there--
I don't know what it is.
But they talked.
He might know something.
He's got those one-god nut cases
believing he's some kind of healer.
He brought some boy out from a coma.
Maybe he knows who the fifth is.
Yeah, maybe he knows who we are.
Then we gotta get in close and find out.
How do you propose we do that?
Take him out for drinks?
Well, he is accomplished at two things.
Lying in his cell, and lying in a woman.
He'd poke a skin job.
He racked up a Six, that's a given.
There is no way.
You don't have to get on
your back for him, but--
Oh, gee, thanks.
What were you doing?
What were you thinking?
What happened to you?
I saw...
Earth.
The shape of it, the smell of it.
The feel of it on my skin in my pores,
and I swear to you, it was like
I'd been there before.
Like I never left.
You're too stupid to figure out you just
screwed over the one ally you had.
You didn't have the guts to hold on.
Tell me.
Who's gonna help you?
Yeah, frak me, huh?
It sure as hell isn't gonna be you.
You've gotta remind yourself
that you're somebody else.
You're the president's wet nurse.
You're the one who
doesn't have the guts.
Nice to know you still care, admiral.
We're going the wrong way!
We have all conferred with our models,
and the results are in.
The Fours and the Fives
have joined us Ones,
and they voted to
reconfigure the raiders.
Gee, what a surprise.
Well, the Twos, Sixes and Eights
voted against it,
so we're deadlocked.
Hopelessly... but you were right.
And I'm machine enough to admit
that I was wrong.
What are you talking about?
Something extraordinary has happened.
Eight.
What's going on?
Boomer.
I'm not going to sugarcoat this.
I'll just say that this Eight
has voted to reconfigure.
- What?
- Shocked? I was shocked too.
But no one has ever voted
against their model.
No one. Is this true?
We have to be able to defend ourselves.
No, this is unconscionable.
This is wrong. She can't.
You had something to do with this.
No, it was her decision totally.
- You cannot allow this.
- There is no law. There's no edict.
There's nothing that forbids it.
It's just-- it's never happened before.
Yeah, try and remember you said
that when he boxes your line.
Now, don't be a sore loser.
If you do this, we all lose.
We think it's for the best.
The best?
Have you lost your mind?
Our identities are
determined by our models.
Each model is unique.
We belong together.
You know this better than anyone.
Mechanized copies.
Those are your very words.
Something has changed.
Those are your very words,
and I wholeheartedly agree.
The raiders are sentient,
just as we are.
There was a plan,
a divine plan in our design.
You're butchering them.
We're reconfiguring them.
You are not God.
No.
I'm a mechanic.
And raiders were designed
to do a specific job.
They stopped doing it. I'm fixing that.
And when the cutting's all done,
they'll go back to being happy warriors.
So let's move on, all right?
I'll pray for you.
I'll pray hard.
All right, you hooch hounds!
Lock it up!
- It's time.
- Shut the frak up! Pay attention.
Pay attention.
Hey! We're saying good-bye.
To the best damn jock you-- you pink
ass cones will ever hope to see.
Oh, shut up.
Major?
Let's go! Come on!
I have a drink. Let's do this.
Come on now.
I'm not thirsty.
To Galactica!
To the men and women of Galactica.
To the admiral.
Who commands the men
and women of Galactica.
And to our sweethearts,
husbands, and wives.
Sweethearts.
To our sweethearts.
To absent friends.
Absent friends.
Excuse me.
- Watch yourself.
- Excuse me.
You're spying on me, Tory.
I've seen you here.
No, no. I heard about the miracle.
The child?
Yes.
You mean Laura Roslin
has heard about it.
All right, I have been spying on you.
Well, it's lucky I was
sitting down, isn't it?
I've been watching these people.
The way they look at you.
Of course,
if you go screaming to the president
that my newfound popularity
borders on the phenomenal,
then she should be very worried.
I came here on my own.
And I slept with the boss last night.
Oh, come on, be nice.
What's it gonna cost you?
Oh, my God. Oh, my giddy-od!
Get a grip, Gaius.
She's not lying-- she really could
be a wonderful source of information.
Why don't you feel her out?
- Feel her what?
- What?
I'm not talking to you, actually.
Try and forget me for a moment.
Ask her what she's doing here.
I am talking to you.
Why did you come here?
Maybe it was a mistake.
Well, I can't stop thinking
about what's happened.
You were found innocent
when everyone hated you.
I hated you.
And this healed boy, the
return of Kara Thrace.
I mean, everyone thought she was dead.
So perhaps there are miracles.
Perhaps.
Thing is, somehow you seem
to be at the center of them.
Yes, I do, don't I?
I don't understand myself,
to be honest. Just, uh...
Well, it seems that
god has chosen me to sing his song.
- A song?
- Music. Did you say music?
No.
Yeah, you know, it's funny.
It's a lot like that.
It's like the distant chaos
of an orchestra tuning up.
And then somebody waves a magic wand,
and all of those notes
start to slide into place.
A grotesque, screeching cacophony
becomes a single melody.
I really shouldn't be seen here.
Who the frak are you?
What, am I supposed to be impressed?
I mean, you're me.
Obviously you're me, so--
unless you're not me. Huh?
Six?
Is it you, Six, in disguise?
Now, why would she need to
disguise herself from you?
Well, you've got a very good point.
- Let's talk about Tory.
- Where is she?
Now, we should talk about Tory.
'Cause we both know
where this is heading.
You like here, don't you?
Yeah, well, you know, she's,
uh-- she's a sexy lady.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know, hot.
- You slay me. You really do, Gaius.
- Why?
She's more than all these things.
She's special.
And you feel it.
- Yeah, fragile.
- Fragile.
Yeah, I sense that too.
You're very observant.
Fragile.
- Handle with care.
- Oh, I'd love to.
You're enjoying that more than usual.
Hair of the dog. Lee's party.
What do we do now? Put her on trial?
Find Romo Lampkin? Take a show of hands?
I don't know.
Follow her into an ambush?
- She is driven.
- Yeah.
You gonna keep waltzing,
or are you gonna sit down and talk?
What's going on? Sit.
What if she's telling the truth?
She was supposed to die out there.
She didn't. I can't explain it.
What if she was meant to help us?
And this was a--
A what? A miracle?
Is that what you want to call this?
Go ahead, say it.
Grab your piece of the golden arrow.
I want to hear admiral atheist
say that a miracle happened.
You shot at her and
missed at close range.
Doloxan fraks with your aim.
So does doubt.
I pulled the trigger
and I'd do it again.
She put her life in front of a bullet
as if it had no meaning.
You drop an egg, you reach for another.
Maybe convincing you meant
more to her than her own life.
Is that your miracle?
You want to talk about miracles?
The very same day
that a very pale doctor informed me
that I had terminal cancer,
most of humanity was
annihilated, and I survived.
And by some mathematical absurdity,
I became president.
And then my cancer disappeared.
Long enough for us to
find a way to earth.
You can call it whatever you want.
And now I'm dying.
Don't talk that way.
Bill. You've gotta face this.
My life is coming to an end soon enough,
and I am not going to apologize
to you for not trusting her.
And I am not-- I am not going to
trust her with the fate of this fleet.
You are so buckled up inside.
You can't take any more loss.
Your son's leaving--
this, me-- I know it.
No one's going anywhere.
Okay.
Here's the truth.
This is what's going on.
You want to believe Kara.
You would rather be wrong about her
and face your own demise
than risk losing her again.
You can stay in the room.
Get out of my head.
You're so afraid to live alone.
And you're afraid to die that way.
You're afraid that you may not be
the dying leader you thought you were.
Or that your death may be
as meaningless as everyone else's.
Zarek nominated me for
the vacant quorum spot, so I...
You're Zarek's wing man.
All right, all right,
you know, stow it, okay.
I've heard it all before.
The guy's a piece of work, I know.
His head's as bit as
the house I grew up in.
I'm-- I'm pretty new to all this.
I could use the help.
Besides, I never really
could say no to anything.
Except me.
Especially you.
You know, I think I finally understand
what you meant about having a destiny.
I've got to do this.
And the fact that I don't have
an explanation why doesn't--
doesn't really seem to matter anymore.
So say we all.
Good luck on your journey, Lee Adama.
You too, Kara Thrace.
- Okay.
- All right.
Lee.
I believe you.
Red and blue sections will go first,
yellow and green will follow.
Skid's up in ten minutes.
Starbuck, if you've got a problem,
I don't want to hear about it.
My only problem is that...
you didn't preach that
sermon a week ago.
Keep your ears open.
Any cylon contact has
shut down and bugged out.
Questions.
Yeah, when are you coming
back to the card game?
- We're on tomorrow night!
- Hey, all right, all right.
Good luck. Man, be careful out there.
Attention to orders!
In recognition of honorable, loyal,
and faithful service,
Madam president, admiral
of the colonial fleet,
Ladies and gentlemen, major Lee Adama.
Salute!
Good luck.
Thank you.
Well, it looks like you got the house.
- I'll miss you.
- Good-bye, Lee.
Look after yourself.
We want you to stop
lobotomizing the raiders, Cavil.
Raiders with free will?
Not going to happen.
Do you know what just
really rankles my ass?!
You've been pointing fingers,
falsely accusing me...
of manipulation just short of tyranny,
when you're the one
that's been leading the charge here.
We want you to stop.
You're not in charge. We had a vote.
For the last time,
will you stop lobotomizing the raiders?
It's unbelievable, isn't it?
Unbelievable.
For the last time...
No.
I was afraid you'd say that.
Come in.
This is cute.
Centurions can't vote, Six.
Oh, they're not here to vote, Cavil.
- Am I hurting you?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
What do you mean, nothing? You're crying.
It's just something I do during sex.
- All... all the time?
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry.
Don't be sorry.
Why should you apologize?
You should be thankful.
You have an abundance of feeling.
I've never really
thought of it like that.
Well, I mean, you're
blessed, aren't you?
I don't know. I guess.
I suppose I could be a cylon.
Well, I don't know about that.
Human beings don't exclusively
hold the patent on suffering.
Cylons can feel.
- You believe that?
- Yeah, I do, actually. Yeah.
I've spent time amongst them.
Man may have made them, but God is...
at the beginning of
the string, isn't he?
It's God who made the real soul.
The one true God.
One God?
You know, I'm becoming increasingly
tired of holding that in.
Of denying that essential truth.
Now, this, uh, this isn't funny.
Leave.
I said leave!
Why don't they leave?
The telencephalic inhibitor that...
restricts higher functions
in the centurions...
- we had them removed.
- Say what?
You dumbed down the raiders.
We the Leobens, the Sharons,
gave the centurions the gift of reason.
You have no authority to do this. None.
You can't do anything without a vote!
No, we can't do anything with one,
so we're finished voting.
What have you done?
First thing they learned is
what you were doing to the raiders.
You can imagine how they felt.
Oh, no.
Sir, the fleet is prepped
and ready for jump.
Execute jump.
Go back!
Go back.
Cuff her.
So.
You quietly cut me loose in deep space.
I'm not afraid to die.
Little easier after you've
been through it once.
Harder.
Especially now that I'm
seeing things so clearly.
You're making a mistake.
Maybe I am.
But I can't take the chance...
that you're right and not
do something about it.
Helo hand-picked a crew for you.
I'm giving you a ship.
I hope you can stand the smell.
We liberated the Demetrius.
It's a sewage recycling ship.
The party line will be
that we're going...
for a scouting mission.
Looking for food.
So you think I'm right.
Maybe. Maybe not.
But I know she is-- the president.
She's been right all along.
I'm tired of losing.
I'm tired of turning
away from the things...
that I want to believe in.
And I believe you when you say
that you'll die before you stop trying.
And I won't lose you again.
Now go.
Find a way to earth.
-=WWW.YDY.COM/BBS=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: »ð¼ý angie
- =www.Ydy.Com/bbs=-
Battlestar Galactica
Season 4 Episode 2