Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
Hera!
Were you with us
a moment ago?
In the lobby of
the opera house?
I don't know. I was there,
too. And so was Hera.
If that's me lying there,
then what am I?
She took these
from her own mortal remains.
The blood on these dog tags
is a 100% proof-positive match
for one Kara Thrace.
Sam!
We tried hooking him up
to the main power grid,
thought it might
reset his neural net.
This has been
happening all over the ship.
Power surges,
temperature fluctuations.
And now you're telling me
it's been him all along?
That for me?
Hera wrote the notes
to a song that
my father used to play
to me when I was a child.
The same song
that led us to Earth.
There's a pattern
that I can't see.
But I think
that you can.
So we are going to pick it
apart until we figure it out.
That's impossible.
Somebody saw her.
What the hell is
going on up there?
Boomer took Hera. Just walked
right out of the daycare.
Job well done.
You go get some rest.
Don't worry.
We'll take good care of her.
Boomer.
No. Boomer.
If Cavil's plan all along was to
steal Hera so he could study her,
he'll take her
to the colony.
It's where we and the Centurions
went after the first war.
We're abandoning ship, Tigh.
Put out the orders.
I want the crew
to start
stripping down Galactica.
Pack in all
the weapons and gear.
Let's start off-loading
civilians by tomorrow.
Full crews and ordinances
transferred by the end of the week.
To Galactica,
best ship in the fleet.
To Galactica.
I've commanded
two Battlestars
and three escorts
before that.
Come on, Bill.
Don't be like that.
There's nothing to
get all upset about.
Billions of cubits worth of
equipment entrusted to me,
not to mention
thousands of lives.
It's one hour of your life.
Look, sometimes there are things
you just gotta do, all right?
Do you always
drink and drive?
I drink. He drives.
You like having things
done for you, don't you?
It certainly beats having
to do them for yourself.
Don't you?
No, I prefer not to rely on
others as much as possible.
Less chance of
being let down that way.
Well, since you've
allowed yourself
to be in my capable
hands for this evening,
here's hoping
I won't let you down.
I'll drink
to that, Doctor.
You can... You can call me
Gaius, actually. If you want.
This is crazy, but I've
actually forgotten your name.
Hello? Yes, it is.
Hello. How are you?
What? What?
Oh, my Gods.
When was this?
Well, listen, just...
I'm so sorry.
If you just wait there, and I'll
be around as soon as I can...
No, please. You have to wait.
You have to... You can't...
You will wait there, or
I'll sue you for abandonment.
Yeah, I will.
Well, I don't know how long
it's going to take. Just wait.
I'm coming.
I'm coming right now.
Give our love to Sidney.
I will. Goodbye.
Bye.
That was a great shower.
Oh, my Gods.
That was amazing. I'm just
gonna clean up a little bit here.
Okay, Laura,
no cleaning.
Just a little. No,
this is the last bottle,
and you and I
have to share it.
You promised me we'd
finish all the champagne.
All right. Oh, boy,
we drank a lot.
Well, they did.
They did.
What about me?
No. Pregnant girls
only get gifts.
Just a sip.
A sip?
All right.
Just one. Little.
Little.
Go ahead. Stop!
Enough.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh!
That was lovely,
Laura. Thank you.
Well, it's the least I could
do for my little sister.
Hey, I thought I was
your little sister.
Okay, you are my
really little sister.
Oh, boy.
How about that woman
with Mrs. Anderson?
Why did she bring those?
What was that?
I don't know, but, you
know, there's always one.
Frak me. He's early.
Just a second!
Coming!
Hi, I'm...
You must be...
Lee, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm Kara. Come on in.
That's very nice.
You didn't have to do that.
I'll take those.
Put them in some water.
Zak!
Nice place.
It's a rattrap,
but the rent's cheap.
No, it's...
It's got real charm.
And you're a terrible
liar. We should play cards.
I hold my own.
I'm sure you do. Zak!
You just get uglier every
day. Hey, there he is.
How are you?
I see you've met
my better half,
and this one's mine.
Keep your hands off.
And a girlfriend stealer
for a brother. Nice!
Never stole his girlfriend.
Mmm-hmm.
Really bad liar
right here.
Yeah, no, we figured that out already.
Zak, get the drinks.
Dinner's almost ready.
Yes, sir.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sure it was a mistake.
Nothing in my contract about
being stabbed with a steak knife.
She been stealing. She been
stealing while I've been sleeping.
No one is stealing
from you, Dad, all right?
Now you just shut up. You're
in enough trouble already.
I'm out of here. You're
lucky I don't call the cops.
Yes. Yes, we are,
Nurse Barbara.
Thank you. Now, listen,
I'll pay you double, triple.
I thought I asked
you to wait in the car.
This be the new one
you be banging, eh?
None of your bloody business. Nurse
Barbara, please. I've got 500 cubits, 1,000.
1,000 frakking cubits
for you to stay the night!
Please! I'll take
all the knives away!
He'll be on
liquid diet forever.
Just spend one
frakking night!
How about you, love?
Bet you charge a lot
more than that, eh?
Shut your filthy mouth.
Stop being so disgusting.
This is your father, Gaius.
Not that you'd ever know it.
You see, Gaius is ashamed
of his family. I need this.
I need this like a frakking hole
in the head. Even his accent.
Stupid bastard actually changed
his accent. Would you believe that?
That is the third
nurse in a row now, Dad.
The third nurse.
Do you have any idea
how much this is costing me?
How much it costs, that's
all he cares about now.
Not the way he was
brought up, I can tell you.
But he don't like
to think about that.
No, he don't like to think
about living on a farm
and doing a day's honest,
hard work.
All right.
All right. All right.
Enough! Enough! Shut up!
Shut up right now!
I won't stand here
one moment longer
and listen to your ridiculous
working-class-hero rant.
Look at you! Look at your
shirt that I bought you.
How you dribble and
treat these things.
I'll break it
down for you, Dad!
You're an obnoxious,
spiteful, cantankerous old git,
and you're frakking lucky you're
not living on the frakking street!
Big man cursing his father.
Makes you feel
important, don't it?
Gaius, maybe we should... Maybe
you should've stayed in the car,
which is what I
asked you to do.
I'm afraid that I'm going to
have to ask you to leave now.
I'm sure that the driver
can see you to your home.
I'm gonna spend the rest of
this lovely evening with my dad.
Good night.
Good morning.
I'm Officer Stephanie
and this is Officer Shawn
with the
Caprica City Police.
Are you Laura Roslin?
Yes, I am.
We need to
speak with you.
May we come inside?
Yes, please do.
We're so sorry.
We have to inform you
there's been
a terrible accident.
Late last night, your sisters
and your father were all killed.
We weren't able to
verify the identity
of the bodies
until a few hours ago.
The driver of the other
vehicle is in stable condition,
and preliminary tests
indicate he was intoxicated
when he sideswiped the car with
your father and your sisters.
Thank you. Please
show yourselves out.
We're sorry
for your loss.
I don't know. I don't
know what she's doing.
I think she wants us
to cut the pain medication.
I don't think she
knows what she wants.
Doctor...
Okay, go ahead
and shut it off.
There's only so much of
Galactica to go around.
You'd think we were
retiring 10 Battlestars.
Excuse me, Mr. President,
sir. One second.
Tell the captains they
are padding their requests.
Send it back. Sir, if you have a minute.
Just one second.
Yes, Specialist,
what is it?
I know this is not
your problem, sir,
but they want us to tear the mag
cellerators from the launch tubes.
Well, the civilian ships
can use them as auto-loaders.
Sir, it's like we're tearing
the old girl's heart out.
A Battlestar's whole purpose
is to launch Vipers.
I kind of know how you feel.
Part of my heart's here, too.
Tell you what,
make the cellerators
the last thing
your men take out.
Then turn out the lights and
let the old girl die in peace.
Yes, sir.
Well, after the blast, everyone
else's numbers are down,
which gives us
solid majority
on over half the civilian
ships in the fleet.
I mean, no one else comes even close
to having that kind
of political power.
Our time is here, Gaius.
She's right, Gaius. The
end times are approaching.
Humanity's final chapter
is about to be written,
and you...
You will be its author.
Gaius, did you hear me?
This is it.
This is it, Gaius.
There's never enough,
you know.
Never enough money,
fame...
Women.
The more you want, the more
you need, the more you want.
There's always
a hunger for
more money,
greater fame...
Different women.
Oh, yeah?
It's a tragedy, your life.
The point I'm trying to make, Calvin,
the point
you're missing,
is that there's
a certain futility
in centering
one's entire life
around trying to
satisfy appetites
that can truly
never be sated.
So, if you could
do your life over,
what would you change?
Sorry, sir.
As I was saying,
the old man intends to fly the
last Viper off ship himself.
Tell the deck gang to leave
one launch tube intact,
set to remote pilot launch. Yes, sir.
You'll never make
admiral like that.
Eat it.
You haven't
eaten in days.
You have to
eat it now, all.
No!
You're in big trouble.
So, you wonder how
to prevent gimbal lock
in a turn, lateral turn,
of greater than 6 G's.
It's quite easy, actually.
You just weld
this baby at the
T- joint at the medial axis...
Lieutenant...
Wait, wait, wait...
We can get in
a lot of trouble.
Do you know
what you're doing?
Yes.
As long as you know!
They're all
the same, Karl.
No, they're different.
You know they're different.
How you felt about Boomer,
that was different.
That's why you
did what you did.
I did what I did because
I'm a frakking idiot.
A 2,000-year-old idiot who
cannot learn the simplest lesson.
Machines are not people.
They're just machines.
My wife, Athena,
is a person. She's a blow-up
doll, Karl. They all are.
Athena, Sharon, Boomer. Call them
what you will. They're all the same.
They're all the same,
because we made them the same.
Don't blame yourself,
but you can't trust them.
You can't trust any of them.
Frak. You didn't hear that,
all right? Let me help you.
These are...
Pilots from
the memorial wall.
We wanted to take
them with us, you know,
so we wouldn't leave them
behind with the others.
The others? Lot of
photos still down there.
Nobody knows who
they are anymore.
Probably friends and relatives
of people on Galactica
who died somewhere
along the way.
Admiral?
As you were.
Bear it in mind?
Well, when will
you bear it in mind?
You haven't even
listened to my proposal.
I'm not even saying
it'll necessarily be me.
My people deserve a
voice in the government.
Now, I'm literally
talking about the lives
and well-being of thousands
of people in the fleet.
Is that what you
were thinking about
when you outted
Starbuck's secret?
The well-being of
thousands of people?
Or the political gain
of Gaius Baltar, again?
Is that what this is about?
Does everything
have to be reduced to
your personal feelings
about Kara Thrace?
Listen to me, Mr. Adama.
Lee.
I'm asking to have
a genuine conversation.
Please.
Five minutes.
I'll be back
in five minutes.
Five minutes inside.
And you think there's some kind
of meaning in these musical notes?
I don't know.
I'm just groping, mostly,
looking for patterns, trying
to see what comes to me.
I thought that if I assigned
numbers to the notes...
I don't know.
What Baltar said the
other day, is it the truth?
Yeah.
I found my body,
and I burned it on Earth.
I don't know what I am.
I have to ask him a question.
Do you know how
to plug him in?
Yeah.
Hey.
I know what you are.
You're my daughter.
Don't forget it.
You're on pace to land in
the hall of fame someday,
but you still haven't
won a championship,
and now the C-Bucks
are in a rebuilding year.
If you don't get to hoist
the cup before you retire,
will you consider your
career to be incomplete?
Well, right now, I'm just
focused on getting stronger
and helping out the
team any way I can.
Um...
I...
Yeah.
Hmm.
Look, you want to
know the truth?
I don't really care
about the stats or the cup
or the trophy,
or anything like that.
In fact, even the games aren't
that important to me, not really.
What matters to me
is the perfect throw, okay?
Making the perfect catch,
the perfect step and block,
it's perfection.
That's what it's about.
It's about those
moments when you...
When you can feel
the perfection of creation,
the beauty of physics, the wonder
of mathematics. You know, the elation
of action and reaction,
and that is
the kind of perfection
that I want to
be connected to.
Spins and turns.
Angles and curves.
The shape of
dreams half-remembered.
Slip the surly bonds of earth
and touch the face of perfection.
A perfect face.
Perfect lace.
Find a perfect world for the
end of Kara Thrace. End of line.
He says a lot of things.
Go ahead.
Ask your question.
You ask him.
Let's forget for one moment that
you're the son of the admiral...
Shut the frak up.
Get to the frakking point.
You got five minutes. Speak.
Galactica has been
more than our guardian.
She's literally a vessel
into which we have poured
all of our hopes and dreams,
and when she's gone, when we
can no longer derive the security
from looking out a window and
seeing her massive bulk gliding by,
then this life will be over
and a new life
will have begun,
a new life that requires
a new way of thinking.
Now, I am willing
to do anything,
anything I can to make
this new life a good one.
All I am asking
is that my people
have a voice in
the government.
I represent
thousands of people.
They deserve to
be enfranchised
just as much as anyone else.
I'm not talking about myself.
This is not
for me personally.
Come on, Lee.
It makes sense.
You know it's
the right thing to do.
What I know
is that in all the years that I've
known you, I've never seen you make
one truly selfless act.
Right.
Never seen you do something
that didn't, on some level,
serve the greater needs
of Gaius frakking Baltar.
So, no, I won't
take your hand.
And I won't bring you
or any representative
from your movement
into the government.
Right. So, that's
what it boils down to.
My people can't
get representation
because I personally
haven't passed
Lee Adama's
selfless altruism test.
I haven't been a goody-goody
and worn a badge of honor.
I don't think you've
passed Gaius Baltar's test.
Go ahead, look me in the eye
and tell me about the time
that you made a truly
heroic act of conscience
which helped you not
even in the slightest.
Tell me!
I'll even believe you.
You're right.
I wouldn't trust me, either.
Holy frak.
I dare you.
I double-dog dare you.
Get out of here!
Come on! Come on.
Come on.
Come on!
Attaboy. Attaboy!
Frak.
Stupid frakking bird.
Can I have your
attention, please?
I'm sure you're all aware
that a child was abducted
from this ship recently.
I thought that a rescue
mission was impractical.
Well, I was wrong.
He didn't say where
he got the information,
but Starbuck was there,
so I bet he talked to Anders.
Yeah. I know.
Pretty freaky.
He thought that
a rescue mission
was impractical
because he didn't know
where she was being held. But
that's changed now, I guess,
because he does know
where she's being held.
Of course, knowing where the colony
is is not nearly the same thing
as being able to
actually get her out.
This is insane.
You know that, right?
What I know is that
Hera has some meaning
that transcends
the here and now.
She is meant to fulfill
a role, just as we were.
So we're going,
the five of us.
Oh, you're making decisions
for all of us now.
You'll go, Tory.
Truth is,
you never could be alone.
Yeah, the mission is to
be strictly volunteer only.
Any man or woman
over the age of 15.
And the Admiral also wants any
former colonial officer or crewman
incarcerated after
the recent mutiny.
Yeah. Yeah, that's it.
Everyone has to
make their own choice,
and they have to
do it in person.
The old man is
waiting on the hangar deck.
Set in-port watch
until you get back.
Watch-keepers report
to the admiral's quarters
to declare
yourselves in person.
Move.
You know what
you're gonna do?
Not exactly.
Well, take your time.
It takes approximately four
minutes to get down there.
It's really happening.
We're going after her.
Or what's left of her.
Cavil's probably had
her sliced and diced
and cut up into
1,000 specimens...
Stop it. Just stop it, okay?
She's still alive, and she's still
out there, and we're gonna get her,
and everything's
gonna be all right.
It's not gonna be
all right, Karl.
No. You're wrong.
You're wrong.
Dots. Lots and
lots and lots of dots.
She's clearly very gifted.
She hasn't
eaten in days.
I think we should begin
intravenous nutritional supplements
to build up her strength
before we begin testing.
She wants her mother.
Well, she can't have
her mother, now, can she?
I'm sorry. I forgot to
sound all soppy and soft
when speaking of the child. She
is a child, a frightened one.
She's a half-human,
half-machine object of curiosity
that holds the key
to our continued existence
somewhere in
her genetic code.
So let's get a tube in
her and get her ready.
Just don't get us bounced
out of here, all right?
Galactica's the end of
the line for pilot teams.
We get kicked out of here, we're
boots on the ground from now on.
I know.
I know it's crazy.
I should stop.
I should stop, yes.
I will, I will.
But you can't stop, right?
Right. I just feel so
alive when I'm with him!
Like the way you're supposed to
always feel but you just never do.
Yeah, I know
what that's like.
I know it's been three
months. I know that.
I do too go out. I do.
I do.
Uh-uh.
No.
No, I'm not joining
Adar's presidential campaign.
I don't care.
Because I don't like
politics to begin with,
and a national campaign
is just so blah.
Oh, Gods.
You are relentless.
Okay, okay.
I'll make a deal.
I'll go on the date if you'll stop
bugging me about this campaign.
How young is he?
I know. Okay. I made a deal.
What's Mr. Perfect's name?
Sean. I like that name. Sean what?
Sean Ellison?
Sounds familiar.
Okay. All right. Bye.
No one should feel obligated
to join this mission in any way!
This is a decision
I have made for myself.
If it turns out that there
are not enough personnel
to crew Galactica,
I will lead a Raptor assault with
anyone who is willing to join me.
Let there be no illusions!
This is likely to
be a one-way trip.
So don't volunteer out
of sentiment or emotion.
There is a line
running down this deck.
Volunteers,
move to the starboard side!
Everyone else to the port.
Make your choice.
Doc.
The Fleet can't afford
to lose a doctor.
Go on back, Sherman,
and thank you.
Like you got
something better to do.
Excuse me. Thank you.
You didn't think you were gonna take
off without me, Admiral, did you?
It never crossed my mind,
Madam President.
Jump complete. Frak!
Plot us a way the
hell back out of here.
Right. You got it.
Figures that a brain-damaged
Cylon would send us hunting
in the middle of
an asteroid field.
The more things change,
the more they stay the same.
You got a recon mission
where someone needs
to hang their ass
over the edge
and wait for a bite,
send Racetrack and Skulls.
Well, beats sitting
in a cell.
Long-range dradis
just picked something up.
Holy frak, we're right
on top of a singularity.
A black hole? Where away?
7-3-8 carom 8-8-2. We're
already sliding toward it.
Spin up the FTL.
We're getting out of here.
Frak me.
What?
You're not
gonna believe this.
Based on the
coordinates we got from Sam,
we have determined that the
Cylon colony is located here.
It's within our jump range,
but there's a sizable catch.
It's located within an accretion
disk of a naked singularity.
It's a strategically-sound
position.
The colony's bound within the
gravity well of the black hole,
but maintains a stable orbit.
How do we get in there?
Look at all the crap
floating around
in that current.
There is no way
to navigate that current.
The tidal stresses
are too strong.
It would rip the ship apart
before we got within 10 SU.
But there is one
safe jump spot.
It's where they bring
their baseships in and out.
We got lucky. Two
baseships jumped in and out
while the Raptor
was taking pictures.
This right here is
our only parking spot.
That's right on top
of the frakking thing.
Less than one click,
by our estimates.
One click?
Point-blank range.
And you can bet that they will
have every gun in that colony
pointed at that
parking spot of yours.
That's what I'd do.
Leave only one
way in and out,
then make it impossible
to get past the gates.
All right.
Let's get to work.
40? I've never paid
more than 30 on Picon.
This ain't Picon.
All right,
you got me there.
This ain't Picon.
All right, 40.
Show him a good time.
I don't want
a lap dance, okay?
Try it!
You'll like it.
Keep the 40, he deserves it. Thank you.
So, are you gonna
take the job or not?
Maybe I should
just do it.
Letting my pride
get in the way.
Now you're talking.
I mean, who cares? It's
one hour of your time,
and then you have
a whole new life,
a life without midnight watches
or drills or Fleet politics
or the inspections
or any of that crap.
Life! You could be
here every night.
He won't be
Can hardly
get him here once.
To retirement?
What do you say?
To retirement.
Yeah!
Yes!
You're fired up.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
Help me up, boys.
Help me up.
Yeah!
Look at that.
She's the finest kind,
my Ellen, the finest kind.
If you don't participate in
the political conversation,
then you are
giving up your voice.
You're giving up
your right to have a say
in the way that
our society is run.
What?
You've really bought into
all that crap, haven't you?
I do, proudly.
And so have you, by
the way. Yeah. Really?
'Cause that's what the uniform stands
for. It's what we train to defend.
Oh, you didn't.
It's true.
No, no, no, no. That's
sad. That's sad. Yes!
It's cute,
but it's sad.
Let me guess,
he's going on about voting
and its importance to a
democratic way of life again.
So, you were listening.
You didn't tell me that your
brother's an idealistic dreamer.
Dreamer? The sad truth is, he's not.
Beneath that
romantic exterior
lies the heart
of a true cynic.
Really? This is going to be
fascinating. Things are looking up.
Yeah, it's one of the
many, many, many reasons
that him and Dad aren't on
speaking terms anymore.
Oh, come on. Family angst
and drama. I love it.
Come on, boys, let's
open up some old wounds.
No, let's not. Dad
believes in the system,
believes in the uniform, believes
in something greater than himself.
Correction.
Dad believes in himself,
his uniform, his
system, his way of life,
and if you're not with him
in that tiny little bubble,
then you might
as well not exist.
If you hate him so much, why'd
you follow in his footsteps?
Touché.
Service gave me
four years of college.
I gave the service
four years in return.
Simple as that.
See? A cynic.
Right through to that big empty
space that used to hold his heart.
Honey, I think I'm starting
to like your brother.
You must be Sean.
Yeah, I must be.
I hope so.
I'll take these. They're beautiful.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Do you like white wine? I do.
Kind of awkward, huh?
Blind date and all?
No, it's not, really.
It's just that I have this
feeling that I know you.
Oh?
Mmm-hmm.
Really?
There you go, Sean.
Thank you.
Welcome.
So, wait a minute.
You were
one of my students.
Yeah, guilty as charged.
I mean, as soon as Marcy
mentioned your name I knew,
but I didn't
want to tell her.
And you knew I was old
enough to be your...
Teacher? Yeah.
But I graduated
some time ago.
Should I go?
Did I say you should go?
I didn't say
you should go.
The night's young. Apparently, so
are you. Let's see what happens.
Sean.
Thank you.
You wouldn't do it.
For that kind of money?
Gods damn right I would.
No, you wouldn't.
Look me in the eye and
tell me that you'd do it,
that you'd do it for
a civilian desk job.
I want to hear it come
out of your mouth. Say it!
I frakking knew it.
Yeah!
Come on, soldier.
I love you guys.
Yeah.
You guys are my family.
Oh, my Gods. Oh, my Gods. Come on.
I love you, brother.
Come on, big boy.
Legs.
All right. In you go.
You want out? Yes. Please. Thank you.
Well, he never
could hold his liquor.
Unlike his brother.
Hey, I'm still standing.
Which means
it's time for shots.
Yes!
Where is Bill?
He took a walk.
Look at
all my rent money.
I will never
have to work again.
Tell me again you're
really quitting this time.
Well, that depends
on the old man.
But you're older
than him, you know.
Saul!
When are you gonna
strap on your own pair
and stop following him around
like some lovesick kid?
You always have to go one
step too far, don't you, Ellen?
It's the truth, Saul!
You wanna know something?
That man has ten
times more integrity
and guts than
anyone I've ever met.
And if that is
not worth following,
then I don't know
what the frak is.
Fine. Go ahead
with your real lover.
You'll come back to me,
Saul, you always do.
There's no need to
torture yourself, Gaius.
Just trust in
God's plan for you.
What is God's plan for me?
Well, you're
following it right now.
Am I?
By taking charge of
mankind's remnants
and guiding them
to their end.
End of what?
Gaius.
We're ready to go.
Five seconds, Paulla.
Okay.
I'm just...
I'm already taken
care of, actually.
I didn't say
it was for you.
A woman of many talents.
With a whole bag of tricks.
Right.
Are you thirsty before...
What the hell
are you doing here?
No, I'm sorry,
what exactly is...
What exactly is...
How did you get in here?
Your friend
let me in.
Yeah, I see you've poured some
ambrosia, thank you, Calvin.
Should I go? What you
should do is go upstairs,
turn left, hit the
bedroom and get ready.
Round the mountain
we shall go
We shall go, we shall go
I think you ought to run along
home now, Calvin, don't you?
You are in big frakking
trouble, you better believe me.
You don't think I'm gonna
tell your mom about this?
Total abuse
of my respect.
It's very touching.
Befriending
the neighbor's geek son.
You're intruding
in my home.
He worships you,
you know that?
Look, I think it would be
a good idea if you left
before I inform
the authorities.
Fine, fine. If that's the
way you want to play it,
then you see, I'm ringing
the police. I'm dialing.
Hello,
police department, please.
I found your father
a new place to live.
Yeah, I'd like to...
What?
The Regency.
Down by the wharf.
Very tony address.
Full-time care, social
activities, medical staff.
And the best part,
they encourage residents to
garden and grow their own food.
Julius will be
a farmer again.
His things are being moved
this very moment by the staff.
They'll be set up
in his new room
exactly how he had
them in the apartment.
He loves it.
Loves?
Once I showed him
around the facility.
Your father's a very
complicated man, Gaius,
but there's a few simple
things that make him very happy.
The last time I saw him,
he seemed happy.
I'm leaving Ishay enough for
two more rounds of injections.
That should keep you on your
feet for another 48 hours.
Two days. Okay.
That should be enough.
You're using up the last little bit of
life you got. You realize that, don't you?
Yes. You've made that
clear to me several times.
Mmm.
Right. That's it.
You're done.
Thank you. Thank you.
Enough.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'm just doing my job.
No.
You've done much more than that. You've
taken a patient who should've died
years ago, and you've
given her a chance,
despite cancer and the Cylons
and her own obstinate nature.
And you've given me the
little time I have left,
and for
that, you have my...
My heartfelt gratitude
and my thanks.
Well, I don't know
what to say.
No, no, don't, don't.
Don't spoil your image. Just light
a cigarette and go and grumble.
She's your patient
now, Ishay.
Ishay, I can barely
see straight.
I'm not surprised.
You're so pumped full of drugs
you could float off this bed.
Okay. Two days?
All right, two days.
The plan's just starting to take
shape, but one thing's clear.
Raptors get the toughest job, as usual.
This will require some special
piloting skills, and I mean special,
threading a needle while you're
on a rollercoaster special.
While it seems a little
redundant at this point,
the word's come down that it's
a volunteer assignment, so...
That's my Raptor
wranglers.
Always looking for new and
interesting ways to get killed.
I'm not going to lie to you boys.
We are thin on intel on this one.
The Cylons believe that the most logical
place for Cavil to have taken the girl
is deep into the
interior of the colony.
Best guess. Right here.
We'll be in too close for nukes.
Same thing goes for missiles.
No, this is going to be
strictly a gun battle.
Like two old ships on the line,
slugging it out at point-blank range.
I want the gun captains to do their
job and start firing immediately
and to continue to fire
until they run out of ammo.
Then, I want them to
start throwing rocks.
They're gonna have every gun trained
directly on us as soon as we jump in.
If we have any
shot at this,
we're gonna have to interrupt
their fire control systems.
And just how the hell is Sam
supposed to help with that?
If we can plug him into Galactica's
dradis, FTL and C3 systems,
his mind should then be able to directly
communicate with the colony's Hybrids
once we jump in.
Theoretically, his mind should still
be able to control their commands
and slow down
their response time.
Okay.
Let's do it,
I guess.
There's a catch.
Routing hardware connections from
all those systems all over the ship
into this room is
gonna take weeks.
It's a lot easier, faster if we
just move him to the existing lines.
Okay, where's that?
Well, the best place
is the CIC.
You're out of
your frakking minds.
It's the best and
fastest way to hook him up.
I'm not gonna hook up
a Cylon into the CIC.
Admiral, it is the only way. No.
And that means no.
I'm not crossing
that line.
You had us all cross a line.
Me, Sam, Lee,
the President, everyone.
We are out here on
this crazy-ass mission
because you couldn't leave
that little girl behind.
It is time for you
to cross that line.
This ship,
this precious hunk of metal,
hooked up to a Cylon,
that hits you where it hurts?
It's always
everyone else sacrificing
our blood,
our lives, our honor,
while you stand there on your
high horse and we bleed around you.
For you.
I'll come back in a bit.
Chief.
Hook Anders up to CIC.
I need someone
to lead this Fleet
who I trust and
demands universal respect.
So the Baseship and
the Fleet are yours.
Thank you, sir.
I won't let you down.
I know you won't.
And I'll see you
at the rendezvous.
If we're not there in 12
hours, we won't be coming.
Yes, sir.
Good hunting, sir.
Thank you,
Admiral Hoshi.
Still not too late to flush
them all out the airlock.
Take too much time.
I suppose this is what you
could call poetic justice.
Or what goes around,
comes around. Either way,
congratulations,
Mr. President.
Thank you, Mr. Adama,
and the best of luck.
Admiral Hoshi, sir.
Sir.
The "sir" has...
Right. Good luck.
You too, sir.
President of the Colonies,
Admiral of the Fleet, departing.
All right, last Raptor out,
people, last Raptor out.
Anyone left behind,
your ass belongs to us.
Great. Can we
tuck this in there?
Listen, I'm not
coming with you.
Gaius, please, Gaius, our people
need you. I've made up my mind.
I don't belong to you, Paulla.
I never belonged to you.
You appropriated me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry if
I led you to believe...
They're all yours now,
Paulla. Enjoy them.
Pilot,
you have your passengers.
Gaius. Don't do this.
Maybe I'll see you
in the next life.
Doctor.
This is so frakking crazy
I can barely stand it.
Have faith, Tory.
In what?
Human ingenuity?
Luck of the Gods?
Random chance?
We have to try.
That little girl may
very well hold the key
to the survival of
the entire Cylon nation.
If she can bear children... Children?
Who gives a frak?
What about us? What,
we're supposed to die happy
because Hera can have kids and the
entire Cylon nation can survive?
Come on. What good
does that do me?
Galactica.
Baseship actual.
Flag has been transferred
to the Baseship,
and our Vipers are ready to take
over CAP duties for the Fleet.
Roger that, Baseship.
You have the CAP.
Safe journey.
Godspeed, Galactica.
Let's go around the horn.
This is the XO.
All combat stations
prepare to report.
FTL.
Go.
We'll set up triage here. Just
prep the table the way that I do.
Weapons.
Go.
Tactical.
Separate out the wounded.
Go. Those we can save,
and those we can't.
Engineering.
Go.
How will I know?
Take this marker.
Damage control.
Go.
Put an "X" on the forehead of
those who are too badly hurt,
and you'll know
when you see them.
Main batteries.
Go.
Engine room.
We're next.
Sick bay.
Sick bay to go.
Viper wing.
Go.
Assault One.
Assault Two.
Go.
Reserve forces.
Com One.
Go.
Sorry.
Caprica.
Com Two.
Go.
What are you
doing here?
I don't think
you should be here.
Probably been in more
battles than you have.
Fair point.
Life support.
Emergency
systems standing by.
Yeah, I suppose the more pertinent
question is what am I doing here.
What the hell
was I thinking?
Secure blast doors
on all decks.
Ellen.
I think we're
a go up here.
All stations report, sir.
Connect me just
to the ship.
This is the Admiral.
Just so there'll be
no misunderstandings later,
Galactica's seen
a lot of history,
gone through
a lot of battles,
this will be her last.
She will not fail us
if we do not fail her.
If we succeed in our mission,
Galactica will bring us home.
If we don't,
it doesn't matter anyway.
Action stations!
Start the clock.
Jump on my mark.
Five, four, three,
two, one. Mark.
We can't take
much of this.
It's time, Sam.
Look through the eye
to know thyself.
One of the Final Five must
be disrupting our systems.
It's Anders.
Has to be.
He's hooked up to
the frakking Hybrids somehow.
We gotta do this
the hard way.
The colony
Hybrids are offline.
They'll be launching
Raiders any minute.
Go.
Launch all wings.
Birds are away.
All ahead, flank speed.
Three, two, one. Hit it!
All hands
brace for impact.
Assault One, standby.
Here they come,
let's take them!
Light it up.
Assault team, on me.
You guys scout
me out, okay?
Pressure. We've got
pressure, sir. One atmosphere.
Assault One,
we got pressure.
Alpha Team,
helmets off.
Move out.
I think we lost Cartwheel.
Dradis is almost
useless out here.
I hope that works both ways. Any
sign they've spotted our approach?
I haven't looked at the
instruments in a while.
I don't think you
want me to start now.
Maybe not.
Let's go weapons hot,
Skulls. We're getting close.
You sure about that?
No, but I don't wanna come out of
this crap with cold weapons, either.
Nukes are hot.
You know, this reminds me
of that time back during...
Battery Three, redirect your
fire 10 degrees starboard.
Concentrate on taking out
the Cylon batteries.
Hotdog and Ladykiller,
concentrate on taking out Cylon
Raiders coming in at 084 count...
All right, Galactica.
We got them.
We have
a hard seal. Go.
You're gonna just
keep doing the tests?
Even with the colony
coming down around your ears?
I think you overestimate
their chances.
They may have confused
our Hybrids temporarily,
but we have superior
firepower and superior numbers,
and in the end,
it's all about mathematics.
Sam. Sam, listen to me.
You're pushing too much
energy through the ACS.
You gotta back off, or you're gonna
blow the main bus, you hear me?
Sam!
There are secrets within
lies, answers within riddles.
Lay off the ACS,
you betcha, Galen.
Open your mind and hear what your
heart wants to deny. End of line.
You never should
have trusted her.
Trust didn't
enter into it.
I simply miscalculated her need
to engage in gestures of futility.
We have to assume that
she'll try to make contact
with the Colonial forces
aboard the colony.
It's time to go
on the offensive.
We must be cautious. Too much
force could risk killing the child.
Really? You think?
Please continue stating
the perfectly obvious.
It fills me
with confidence.
I'm proud of you.
What?
For doing this.
For being here when you
could've just walked away.
I don't think I ever said it before,
but I always wanted to be proud of you.
Guess I always felt that
was the only thing missing.
All the pieces are
falling into place.
You will hold the future of
Cylons and humans in your hands.
I will?
You see them?
Reconnect me!
Cylons just blew
a hole into Deck 21.
Frakking Centurions will be
pouring in at platoon strength.