TWELVE CYLON MODELS
SEVEN ARE KNOWN
FOUR LIVE IN SECRET
ONE WILL BE REVEALED
Previously on Battlestar Galactica:
"Thus shall it come to pass."
"The dying leader shall know the truth
of the opera house."
Where did you hear that?
Who told you that?
The Hybrid. On the baseship,
before they unplugged it.
I've got to find out
about these visions.
Plug it in.
It's time to get some answers.
Can I see what you drew?
Hera?
Get away from my child!
You are never gonna take her.
JUMP!
-Make Way! Make Way!
-Father.
Give me the strength...
Let's come along, come along.
Let's go.
Watch it, watch it.
Bay 2! Doc!
Coming your way!
Quickly.
All right.
On three:
One, two three.
Lift.
Keep some pressure on that wound
until I can get to the artery.
Mask on.
Kidnapped?
President--
Baltar?
I heard Baltar was with her.
Are you saying he's responsible?
- I heard it was the Cylons.
- No. My people say she was shot.
What are you talking about?
Roslin?
Now, one of Adama's Marines
shot a Cylon,
and that is how this entire
thing has begun.
- So then where is Zarek?
- I don't know!
- Where is Zarek
- Who is in charge here?
Sir, Vice President Zarek is
still waiting to talk to you.
What should I tell him?
Sir?
Deckard says they've just shipped over
the last of the Vipers,
means we're down to 40 birds
and almost as many jocks.
We're gonna have to reconfigure
the CAP, rethink our defense posture.
Where is she?
- Marines are holding her.
- My quarters.
- Nobody has told us anything.
No, no, no.
All right, everybody.
Please calm down.
Mr. Vice President,
I have some questions for you.
Thank you.
Just calm down, please.
Everybody!
Everybody just calm down, please.
Mr. Vice President,
it's really important that we know.
Is the President dead?
We...We have no information--
I heard she was assassinated by the Cylons.
No, there is no truth to that,
at least as far as we know.
But then what the hell
do we know?
Clearly, our first priority is
to get out as much
verifiable information
as we can to avoid exaggeration--
But what is it that--?
To that end, I asked Admiral Adama
to come and answer our questions directly.
Unfortunately, he wouldn't
take my call.
- At this time, when there is--
- However...
However...please.
Please, just a moment.
...on the right.
President Roslin is apparently
aboard the Cylon baseship,
along with Gaius Baltar and
many of Galactica's pilots
when it jumped away,
after one of their own leaders
was shot aboard Galactica.
We have no idea when or if
they'll return,
or if the President or the other
captives will be subject to reprisals.
For now, the powers granted me by law,
I have taken over as President.
Hear, hear.
By refusing even to meet with Zarek,
you're simply helping him
fan the Quorum's suspicions.
Their suspicions don't concern me.
Look, maybe he's not
the man we hoped for,
but he is next in line, and the fleet
needs reassurance and stability
exactly the kind that only its
military commander can offer.
If this fleet needs reassurance,
then you reassure them.
That's your job now.
You can tell Zarek,
he can go to hell.
- Why?
- Sir...?
Do you hate your people so much
that you look for any excuse to kill one?
What, did you deliberately try
to sabotage this truce?
No sir. Of course not.
Then you tell me why.
You make me understand
why you did this.
They were gonna take her.
The Six.
She was gonna take my child.
There were too many witnesses.
They all said the same thing:
Your daughter was lost.
The Cylon merely kneeled down,
was talking to her.
Maybe that's what it looked like
to the others, sir.
- But I know.
- Oh, you knew better...?
I had a vision, a vision where the Six
and Baltar were taking her away from me.
A vision.
It was more than just a vision, sir.
When I saw them together, I knew
that they would take her,
that they would take away
my child!
You murdered her.
An unarmed woman, and by doing so,
you put the lives of every
single person in this fleet at risk.
And quite possibly cost the lives
of the President and your husband.
You disobeyed the direct orders
of a superior officer,
but more importantly,
you betrayed a promise to me.
I trusted you.
Sir, I will accept any form of punishment
that you think I deserve.
I just ask that you please
don't take away Hera.
I'm afraid the brig
is no place for a little girl.
Guards!
- Get her out of my sight.
- Yes, sir.
At one time, Admiral Adama supported
Gaius Baltar's administration.
Isn't there a chance he'd support yours?
I'm afraid only Admiral Adama
can answer that.
Then I will address this question
to delegate Adama.
Do you honestly think that your father
will hand over power to this administration?
No.
39,674 SURVIVORS
IN SEARCH OF A HOME
CALLED EARTH
Transcript by rogard, with a
little help from others. Thanks guys.
Battlestar Galactica
Season 4 Episode 8
"Sine Qua Non"
Fine.
Yeah.
Recon Raptor just reported back.
The Resurrection Hub's gone.
No sign of the base ship
carrying the President,
assuming that's where they were headed.
They were determined to
resurrect the Three,
what we used to call D'Anna.
To do that, they gotta go
to a hub.
If we find it, we'll find them.
- Easier said than done.
- Maybe.
We got another problem, sir.
Starbuck's having trouble fielding
enough planes to fly a standard CAP.
Wants us to consider having the fleet
bunched up tighter,
so it's easier to defend.
Means counting on a bunch of
civvies flying close formation.
Yeah...
Organize it.
I got you appointed...
to this job. I pulled strings,
called in favours, all because
I thought you might do some good.
Now you're advising me
to step aside from a position
that by law...is mine.
A position I was elected to.
But you were never elected president.
But I was elected to office,
which is more than Roslin can claim.
Why do you think she kept me on
in the first place?
To thank me for rolling over?
No.
No, to help legitimize her coup.
In the military,
we used to talk about
facts on the ground.
Well, the facts on the ground
are these:
Right or wrong, Adama will never
recognize you as president,
and we need someone he will.
Now the Quorum has a legal authority
to appoint an interim president
in a time of crisis.
And I suppose you have someone in mind?
No.
No, not yet, Whis is why we need
to form a search committee
and start looking for candidates
as soon as possible.
Well...
good luck with that.
Mr. Vice President, sir.
You don't believe this
government's in danger?
Let's face facts here.
What we had these past five years
isn't a true government,
but a tacit agreement between a
military strongman and a political strongwoman
to rule together by fiat.
I've heard you asked
the Quorum to authorize
the creation of a civil defense force?
After what happened during the
last military coup,
we don't want to depend on Galactica's
marines to guarantee our safety.
You see the problem?
Lampkin's first rule of
legal dynamics:
When an irresistible force
meets an immovable object,
stand aside.
Might call for a class action suit.
Except I'm not sure if it's to
anyone's benefit if we just sit around,
waiting to pick up the pieces.
This thing's heading for a showdown.
There's gonna be bloodshed, unless--
Unless you can find someone else,
someone your father won't reject,
someone the Quorum would approve of,
someone to take Tom Zarek's place
as Interim President
until the next round of elections.
Don't take the case, Counselor.
It's a loser.
I have to.
We have to.
No one on the Quorum is going
to lift a finger.
Zarek's got them inhaling fear
and exhaling anger.
But you have taken the pulse of
the fleet and you know character.
And frankly, you need a reason
to get out of this room,
unless you want to start discussing
what's been keeping you here.
So you won't be dissuaded, will you?
Not even when you hear my fee?
Fee?
Appearances to the contrary,
I'm actually in this for the money.
I have a reputation to
maintain after all.
Okay, so what did Roslin offer
you to defend Baltar?
Room with a view.
I'm not sure I can
improve on that.
Then pro bono it is, Counselor.
Words of the wise:
"Sometimes it's better to settle
for what you've already got."
Colonel Tigh.
I understand you've developed a
relationship with the Cylon prisoner.
That's not the word I'd use, but she
has been more cooperative.
See if she'll tell you
anything about the Hub.
Bill.
We'll find her.
We'll find all of them.
Your Resurrection Hub.
How do we find it?
I'm sure the others have told you.
You tell me.
Only our Hybrids can locate it.
And then only after it completes a jump.
Even they can't anticipate
where it's going.
You're holding back something.
I know it.
- You're lying.
- I have never lied to you, Saul.
Why don't you trust me now?
Because there are too many
lives at stake, lady.
Your buddies took off with
half an air wing,
not to mention the President
of the frakking Colonies herself.
She's the real reason
you're so angry, so worried.
I can hear it in
your voice.
Why? Why is a dying woman
so important to you?
Not to me, godsdamnit.
To the old man.
Admiral Adama?
Saul.
- Do you love me?
- What?
Be honest with me.
I've been honest with you.
I don't believe this.
You're asking me--
Attention. Set Condition One
throughout the ship
This is not a drill.
This has gone too frakkin' far.
I don't know what kind of mind games
you are playing with me, lady,
but it ends here!
What do we got?
One of our missing Raptors
jumped into DRADIS range.
You're sure it's ours?
Transponder checks out, it's one of
the Raptors that boarded the rebel baseship.
No radiological signature.
Racetrack and Skulls are on their way
to intercept.
Actual, Racetrack.
I'm eyeballing our bird now.
Looks shot to hell.
Venting fuel and O2.
Still no response to hails.
Someone had to jump that bird.
I can't see a fracking thing from here.
Skulls, take the wheel,
I'm going for a walk.
Decompression check okay.
Opening hatch.
Safety line secured.
Moving toward the Raptor.
I see major damage to the canopy.
<>Looks empty inside.
I have the hatch open
but it's stuck.
Grav field's off.
It's Pike.
Dead.
[Searider Falcon]
This is the shuttle
she took over to the baseship.
Laird was able to salvage
the flight data recorder,
puts the originating jump point
deep in sector delta 9.
'President' Zarek called again.
He heard about the Raptor,
and he's waiting to be briefed.
Recall the CAP.
Spin up the FTLs.
- What about the fleet?
- Let's go.
We are essentially looking for
an understudy.
Quandary is, one doesn't generally
get the chance...
...to wield political power without the
ambition to actively seek it.
Easy, Lance.
That same ambition
often compromises...
...the unselfish motives
that begat the quest.
In other words, a battle of "id"
vs."ego", that "ego" rarely wins.
Roslin never sought power.
Exception that proves
the rule.
One could argue that Laura Roslin is
a study in repressed ambition.
Just like you, Mr. Adama.
Never seeking out a job
until it's handed to you.
Flight leader, Battlestar commander,
Quorum delegate.
A man doesn't carve out a path
like that through life without--
All right, enough of this
psychoanalysis.
Let's get back to the job
in hand.
Does your father have some another
place he wants to go?
What?
Where the hell did they go?
And why didn't they tell us?
Galactica, Racetrack.
We've located the source
of the transponder.
It's Sandmans's viper all right.
- But there's no Sandman's
- Affirmative. Keep searching.
We're getting radiation signatures
from multiple nukes.
Baseship fragments, other debris...
...indicative of Resurrection technology.
I'm afraid it paints
a pretty clear picture.
They found the Hub
and they destroyed it.
Looks like our pilots.
question is, where did they go from here.
Oh, Bill.
You are way too close to this.
The President's baseship
was destroyed.
It's a different baseship.
We'll search every square inch
of this debris field
until we come up with a clue.
What, and leave the rest
of the fleet back there...
...with their asses
hanging in the wind?
Detail four Raptors
to stay behind.
They'll keep searching
until they find something concrete.
Give my order.
Hey people, listen up.
What are we gonna do here?
- They've left 39,000 lives...
- All right, everybody. Gather round please.
-...completely undefended.
- Gather round.
- Uh, Mr. President.
- Please, please, please.
I'm sorry, Admiral Adama will not
be coming to answer your questions.
I did learn however, that they've
contacted the fleet's captains...
...to inform them that several of
their ships will be requisitioned...
...to expand the search for Laura
Roslin and the missing baseship.
while our tylium shipments will be
diverted to support that mission.
How do they bypassing us completely?
I understand. I understand.
We're doing the best--
I understand. We're trying to get
through communications--
- That is unconscionable!
- That makes no sense.
- Come on.
- That is nothing short of--
Captain Franks.
I was impressed by her gravitas
during her turn as judge
in the Baltar trial.
Got no vote,
naturally.
Yeah. She's already been
approached to run for office.
No interest in politics.
Sadly, now she really
impresses me.
Gods!
You ever feed that animal?
Where is he anyway?
Come on, Romo.
Let's put our heads together.
Who would Adama respect
as President?
What does this...
...search for paragons
matters anyway.
It's a greater guilt
to their own failings.
Or worse.
The idiot's illusion
of the clean slate.
- Fresh start.
- Whoa! Whoa!
We haven't ruled out
all these names yet.
This one's a loser.
An exercise in futility.
How is this gonna affect the
President? The break in her treatment.
Assuming no other changes in
her circumstances?
Yes.
Well, diloxin really kicks
your ass,
so she actually might
feel better at first.
But any break gives the cancer
a chance to regroup,
makes it that much harder to
beat it back,
plus she's taken a hit to
her immune systems
so she'll be vulnerable
to infections.
How long?
Well, let's just say, that the
sooner you get her back here,
the better her chances are.
And while you're
digesting that,
I have some other news.
I ran some tests on your
Cylon prisoner.
Guess what I've found.
Raptors are due back in a few hours.
Granted, if they'd found anything, we
would have heard about that by now.
- Still, once we correlate their reports--
- I'm not interested...
-...in the search.
- You're not?
I know that you've been spending
a lot of time interrogating the Six,
but now the brig guards tell me that
every time you order them out.
And you turn off the cameras.
I'm not torturing her, if that's
what you're worried about.
I'm not.
That I could almost understand.
This I can't.
Cottle tells me she's pregnant.
What the frak have you been
thinking here, colonel?
Do you deny it?
You don't.
You can't!
What the hell have you
been thinking?
Who was interrogating whom?
How many of our secrets have
you told this thing?
How can you even ask me that?
Question my loyalty?
Your loyalty?
I need more than your loyalty.
You're my first officer.
I need judgment.
I need your competence,
I'm through jeopardizing this ship,
putting it at risk because
of your weaknesses.
- My weaknesses?
- Yeah, your weaknesses!
You're risking all our lives
for what?
Our missing pilots?
No, for a woman!
For a frakkin' woman!
You watch what you frakking
say about that woman!
She's the President, not some
frakking skinjob that I've been banging.
What do you think
Ellen would say about all this?
Leave Ellen out of this.
What do you think Ellen would
say about her husband
impregnating a frakking
Cylon prisoner?
You motherfrakker!
You know how many times
I had to repair this thing?
What are you gonna do
with that woman?
What are you gonna do about Laura,
if you ever find her?
I don't know.
Have the Raptors and the civilian
ships begin the search
from Phantom's last known position.
Is that a problem?
Sir, respectfully...
I've already got two
missing pilots
and hardly enough birds
left to protect this fleet.
Now you're asking me to send the
remains of the Raptors out
on a blind search looking for a ship
that very well may have been destroyed.
My people are gonna feel like they're
being asked to go on suicide missions.
I'm not asking.
You're dismissed, captain.
...bunch of Sixes...
Admiral Adama?
Mr. Lampkin, what are
you doing here?
Writs of forfeiture for the
ships you borrowed.
The captains want to be absolved of any
blame should anything untoward happen.
One of the less ennobling consequences
of a legal culture:
No one wants responsibility.
Lee said you once gave him
something before a mission.
A lighter, was it?
It belonged to my father.
Foolish to think a hunk of metal...
...can keep 'em safe.
And yet, that's what we do, isn't it?
Hang on to hope,
in every hopelessly irrational
way that we can.
But not like those poor bastards,
giving away their luck,
just when they need it most.
It's like they've given up.
If you've never been in combat,
you have no idea what they're thinking.
I always imagined you were
a realist, Admiral,
not one to indulge a vain hope
at the cost of lives.
But then...
everyone has his limits.
Sine qua non, as they say.
- "Without which not".
- Yes.
Those things we deem essential,
without which we cannot bear living,
without which life in general
loses its specific value,
becomes abstract.
You may have a point, Counselor.
And while I'm on a roll:
Tom Zarek may not be
an ideal president,
but we could do worse.
You're right.
There are limits to
my realism.
Good bye, Counselor.
I can't give up on her.
I can't let her go.
I've lost my objectivity,
and now that I see that,
I have no choice.
Tell the Quorum that I am relinquishing
command, effective immediately.
No man is perfect.
No man is less perfect than a
candidate for high office.
Thus...
the ranks of likely suspects
is winnowed to none.
What if we're going about
this backwards, hey, Lance?
What if instead of picking names
and finding fault,
we'd ask ourselves the qualities
that we want, no,
...that we need...
...in your chief executive,
see who fits that bill.
Honesty, of course.
Wisdom to recognize.
Correct.
If unpopular choice,
as well as the courage...
...to see it through.
Experience.
When the wrong choices cost lives
and the right ones save.
It's all harder.
I might as well just
spell out one name.
Just one.
One we knew from the start.
Sometimes you take
on a losing case
and you make yourself a believer.
Other times,
no matter what you tell yourself,
in your heart you know
the outcome is fixed,
and the verdict inevitable.
Lance.
Defense rests.
C'mon.
Apologies.
- I couldn't wait to tell you.
- Tell me what?
We found our candidate.
Someone the Quorum won't
hesitate to approve,
even against Zarek's objections.
Someone the Admiral can't
help but accept.
Yeah? Who?
Congratulations,
Mr. President.
My name was never on that list.
Of course not!
That would be too blatant.
But it is everything you
always wanted, isn't it?
Why you had me cross 47
names off that list?
Come on...
admit it.
Savour your victory,
Mr. Adama,
'cause you'll never get
the chance to serve.
- What are you doing?
- Why?
'Cause you're perfect for the job,
of course.
'cause after the vicious separation
that was Baltar's presidency,
and the bitter disappointment
that was Roslin's,
you are a shining beacon of hope.
Only hope is the last thing we need.
We're a doomed race,
and it's time
that we made our peace with
that essential truth.
Romo, what the hell
are you talking about?
Why? You wanna know why?
Open it!
Frak.
That's right.
- They killed my cat!
- "They"?
"They"! Those debased dregs
of humanity out there!
Yeah, that lost tribe
in search of a new home,
so they can roost
and rot again.
For how long has the cat been dead?
How long?! It's irrelevant,
it's immaterial!
It wasn't even my cat!
Romo.
It's been dead for weeks.
It belonged to my wife.
I just retrieved it
from a vet on Gemini.
When the bombs started to fall,
and fate presented me
with a choice:
I could get back
on that shuttle or...
I could run home and...
try to save my family.
- How would you think I chose?
- Romo.
We've all had to make difficult
choices, you don't think I know?
Your wife's name was Faye.
You had two daughters,
Jennifer and Kate!
They were over 200 passengers
on that shuttle,
only a handful chose to stay behind.
Yeah. That's right,
it was in your file
when you headed the job
as Baltar's council.
But no one blamed you, Romo,
because at a certain point,
we all made decisions
that saved our lives
at the cost of others.
You think you're unique, Romo?
Think you're sins are so special?
Is that it, counselor?
You're gonna rest your entire
case on that pathetic...
little bit of insight?
No. Unless...
The clean slate. The fresh start.
Maybe they are illusions,
...like you said.
But at a certain point,
faith in ourselves,
in our right to survive as
a species, as a people
that's not a given,
that's a choice.
Well, I've made mine.
And if you can't stomach that,
then you had damn well better
squeeze that trigger right now.
Go on.
What are you waiting for?
Or you can make a choice:
Put your past behind you,
put the gun down
and help me, because
I'm telling you
I'm gonna make a difference
in this fleet.
Is that your final word?
That's up to you.
Then swear it.
I,
Leland Joseph Adama,
do now avow and affirm...
...that I take the office of
president of the 12 Colonies of Kobol
without any moral reservation
or mental evasion.
...that I take the office of
president of the 12 colonies of Kobol
without any moral reservation
or mental evasion.
This is a frakking joke.
You're the only man I can
trust to command this ship.
Well, maybe you're crazy enough
to pull a stunt like this,
but you can't be crazy enough
to leave me in charge.
In case you forgot, my last term
at the helm was a complete disaster.
That was a long time ago.
You're not the same
man you were.
You're not even the same man
that came back from New Caprica.
You've found out a lot
about yourself,
been tested in ways I can
barely begin to imagine.
You're ready.
Besides, don't count on
this being permanent.
What if it is?
Put these on.
Then you lead the people...
to Earth, the best way you can.
The fleet has stayed here
too long already.
Any other last orders?
Just one.
Give Athena back her daughter.
She needs her family.
We all need our family.
Take care of this one.
All right, let me see the changes
before you get this out to the press.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Mr. Lampkin.
Romo.
One day in office, and you've
already got a First Pet.
But Jake here is a genuine
hero of the resistance.
Why don't you check?
Unfortunately, his previous
owners had to let him go.
Jake, meet Romo.
Romo, meet Jake.
Your new best friend.
There's one thing I hate more
than cats. It's dogs.
See, a new pet for you to loathe.
I knew it would be the perfect gift.
Good luck, Jake.
I hear you're keeping
Zarek as vice president.
I can use the advice.
And as long as he knows
he's heard,
I think I can trust him.
Don't know if I agree
with your thinking, but...
Well, I could say the same
thing about yours.
The only difference is,
you are gonna be President,
I'm just getting in a plane.
Waiting alone in a Raptor, while
the rest of the fleet jumps away,
that's not just getting
in a plane.
That...that sounds a lot like--
Well, that sounds a lot
like suicide, Dad.
At least this time I'm
only risking my own neck.
So I guess it won't matter if, as
President, I order you not to do this?
I don't know if I ever
told you this, but...
one of my first missions was
a solo recon,
being alone in a Raptor
in enemy space,
I'm not gonna lie to you
I was scared.
I told myself that I was doing my duty
I'd have time to face my fear.
That's a good memory.
Why are you doing this?
Because I can't live without her.
And Laura is gonna get to rendezvous
point. I have to believe that.
- Admiral.
What do you hear, Starbuck?
Nothing but the rain, sir.
Grab your gun and
bring the cat in.
Yes, sir.
Keep a light on.
I'll be back.
You can count on it.
Galactica, this is Husker.
I'm in position.
Affirmative, Husker.
All fleet ships.
This is Galactica Actual.
- Commence jump.
- Yes, sir.
Transcript by rogard, with a little
help from others. Thanks guys.