On me, let's move!
Wait.
Tell the old man
I owed him one.
Doesn't change anything
you did, though.
No.
We all make
our choices.
Today I made a choice.
I think it's
my last one.
All right, this is really touching.
Can we get the hell out of here?
You should know that your
Raptor's been destroyed.
You can't go
back that way.
Yeah, well, that's not the plan.
Can you not
tell her the plan?
Right.
Missed the trap
seven times in two days.
There's
a new Galactica record.
Regs say that you've
washed out, Rook.
Time to look
for a new career.
What do you want
me to do, sir?
Do you want me to beg for my
billet? Do you want me to crawl?
I want you to land your frakking bird
without digging holes into my deck.
How's that, huh?
How about being a pilot, an
officer worthy of the uniform?
Take your job seriously. Don't let
your personal life get in the way.
I've read your jacket,
your whole story.
I know that your family's gone,
and I know that you have no home.
All you got is the service,
and it's slowly slipping away.
All because you're all
wrapped up in survivor's guilt,
and you're trying to find
a way to wash yourself out.
The doctor's in. Check
your neuroses at the door.
A lot of people have died on this ship.
There's a lot of ghosts running around here.
You don't want to pull them
into your cockpit with you,
because you won't come back
alive. Do you understand that?
Yes, sir.
I don't think you do, but
maybe someday you will.
For now,
make the trap
tomorrow, Rook.
Dismissed.
Thank you, sir.
I owe you one.
You and a lot of other
people owe me one,
but you know what, very
few people ever pay back,
especially the ones that
owe you their lives.
I'll pay you back one day, sir,
when it really means something.
You do that.
Okay, get this guy cross-checked
and set me up a large-bore IV.
I need a set of vitals
on this Marine over here.
I want a CT scan here on this one,
and get him the frak out of here.
Here we go. It's all right.
You're gonna be all right.
He's a goner.
All right, you'll be... You're
gonna be all right. Okay.
What took you
so long?
Stopped for coffee.
How many other Raptor teams made it?
Haven't seen
anybody else.
Okay, back
the way we came.
Guns, point.
Yes, sir.
We're retracing
our steps.
Say again,
Apollo!
I cannot copy your
last transmission.
This is the XO.
Red stripes to repel boarders,
Deck 21, portside, frame 10.
We got the prize.
Repeat, we have the prize.
Formed up with Assault Two
and are heading back to base.
Roger that. ETA five
minutes. Actual out.
Fire! We got
a fire up here!
Connect me to Command Unit. Yes, sir!
Move reserve forces
to guard airlock.
Assault force is en route.
ETA five minutes.
I repeat. ETA five minutes.
We're friendly!
Hold your fire!
Friendlies!
Rangel, Peters, form up!
Sorry about that.
Doc, you did good.
Thank you.
We'll take Hera.
Right. Come on.
Come on.
Bring Hera.
Get them out of here.
Fall back. Fall back!
Oh, my Gods. Hera.
Clear.
Gods.
Check his status.
Keep that belt tight on
and get back here!
Hang on.
Hera!
Hera! Come back
here. Hera!
Look at me.
Go.
No, you'll bleed out.
Go!
Okay.
I'm empty.
Two rounds.
Hera!
I've been here before.
Yes.
We're supposed to...
Go into the
opera house.
This one's
still alive.
Get him the hell
out of here!
They got the girl.
They've got
the little girl!
This makes it
a lot easier.
I just take the little
girl and I'm out of here.
Not a chance.
Cavil, we won't let you
take Hera. You know that.
I know nothing
of the kind.
I know I'm going to watch you
chase your tails across the universe
for another four years.
That's not
gonna happen.
This thing is the key
to my people's survival,
and I'm not leaving
without it.
Hera's not a thing.
She's a child,
and she holds the key to
humanity's survival, as well.
And how do
you know that?
I see angels,
angels in this
very room.
Now, I may be mad, but that
doesn't mean that I'm not right.
Because there's another
force at work here.
There always
has been.
It's undeniable.
We've all experienced it.
Everyone in this room has witnessed
events that they can't fathom,
let alone explain
away by rational means.
Puzzles deciphered
in prophecy.
Dreams given to
a chosen few.
Our loved ones,
dead,
risen.
Whether we want to call that God
or Gods or some sublime inspiration
or a divine force that we
can't know or understand,
it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
It's here. It exists,
and our two destinies
are entwined in its force.
If that were true,
and that's a big "if,"
how do I know this force has
our best interests in mind?
How do you know that God
is on your side, Doctor?
I don't.
God's not on
any one side.
God's a force of nature,
beyond good and evil.
Good and evil,
we created those.
You wanna break
the cycle?
Break the cycle of
birth? Death? Rebirth?
Destruction?
Escape? Death?
Well, that's
in our hands,
in our hands only.
It requires
a leap of faith.
It requires that
we live in hope,
not fear.
If I leave you this girl, that
means the destruction of my people.
How does our extinction
fit into this picture
that you want
us to believe in?
We'll give you
resurrection.
Saul!
You give us Hera and we
will give you resurrection.
But the war
ends here.
You leave humanity
in peace
and give up the pursuit
now and for all time.
Agreed.
How do we know we can
take your word for it?
You don't.
You have to make
a leap of faith.
It's your call, Bill.
I'll back you either way.
I'm losing a lot
of men out there.
I can do something
about that right now.
Give me that phone.
Patch him through.
Hello? Hello,
it's me, Cavil.
Stand down,
all forces!
Cease fire immediately!
Galactica, Hotdog.
They're pulling back.
Repeat, they're
pulling back!
Everyone,
stand down.
I'm as good as my word.
Admiral, Viper wings aboard.
We lost four birds.
Assault forces aboard,
and we've lost seven Raptors.
What are
they doing?
Each of them knows part of
the secret to resurrection,
and they're gonna interact
with the data flow in the water
and... I don't know.
It's a lot of complicated technical
talk about sharing the information
among the five of them
and then transferring
it over to the
colonies somehow.
Now, for a moment,
we're going to know everything
there is to know about one another.
I'm looking
forward to that.
There are certain
things that...
That we've all done,
certain things that
people would be
shocked to learn about.
Hey, I don't
mean to rush you,
but you are keeping
two civilizations waiting!
Let's just all
agree that no matter
what we learn
about each other,
we're all Cylons, and we're
all capable of making mistakes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're forgiven
for all your dark secrets.
Let's do this.
Any word?
We're getting
the data now.
It looks right.
They're downloading the
resurrection designs now.
They've broken
off the download!
It's a trick!
Open fire!
Frak!
We've gotta
get out of here!
Starbuck!
Jump the ship!
I don't have the
rendezvous coordinates!
It doesn't matter!
Just jump us out
of here now! Jump!
Just trust yourself.
There must be some
kind of way out of here.
I thought that if I assigned
numbers to the notes...
If that's me lying there,
then what am I?
I look at you now and
I don't see Kara Thrace.
I see an angel blazing with
the light of God. Angel.
Jump!
You're tempting fate.
Mmm.
If I have a fate then it is
set, and thinking about it
isn't gonna make it
happen any faster.
Okay. Fair enough.
But flying?
When you're
thinking about dying...
It's a bad
way of doing business.
You're gonna
get scared,
and you're gonna start
second-guessing yourself.
I'm not scared.
You said that you
think about dying
every time that you
get into a cockpit.
Uh-huh.
Well, hello!
Yeah, but it doesn't
scare me, Lee.
That's what
you don't get.
What, so it's Kara Thrace,
the fearless warrior?
Right?
No, I know...
I know fear,
and I get
scared, just...
Just not of dying.
So then, what
does scare you?
Mmm...
Sorry.
Being forgotten.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
XO.
Sir.
Sitrep.
Damage report.
I'm okay,
I'm okay, go.
Sir.
Wake the frak up!
What?
You're getting sloppy.
Careless.
Stupid.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm not an idiot.
Neither is the XO.
Just be careful, okay?
Okay. All right.
Thanks.
I appreciate the heads-up.
You're welcome.
You know, there's people you can
count on and people you can't.
It's good to know the
difference between the two.
We're mostly here.
The engines,
life support.
There's red lines through her
lateral structural members.
She's broke her back.
She'll never jump again.
Wherever we are is
where we're gonna stay.
Where have you
taken us, Kara?
Glad you could
join us, Admiral.
Lieutenant Hoshi suits
me just fine, sir.
Admiral stars turned out
to be a little heavy.
Happiest day of
my life when I saw
that Raptor jump in at
the rendezvous point.
Well, there you
have it, Admiral.
The most
advanced civilization
we could locate
on this planet.
I can't see them
talking to each other, sir.
Either they communicate a different
way, or they're pre-verbal.
Judging by the look
of their tools,
which are rudimentary,
to say the least,
I'd suggest that we found an
early, ritualistic tribal society.
They bury their dead.
I came across a grave a couple
of clicks back and ran some tests.
Their DNA is
compatible with ours.
Meaning we can
breed with them?
You got a one-track
mind, Doc.
What? Listen, I'm talking about the
survival of the human race, actually,
not some get-together
with the natives.
You also have no
sense of humor.
Right.
Right, I'm sorry.
How is
that possible?
Human beings naturally
evolved on a planet
one million
light years away.
The odds against
that are...
Astronomical, yeah.
One might even say there
was a divine hand at work.
Well, whoever's
responsible, we're here,
and here's where
we're gonna stay,
with our
new families.
My vote is that we clear
everything back to this ridge.
There's easy access to the
water down by the river.
In fact, the whole area
is ripe for cultivation.
We should be able to lay out
the preliminary lines for a city
within a day or two.
No.
No city.
Not this time.
What do you
propose we do?
We break the cycle.
We leave it all
behind and start over.
You're talking
about a little over
38,000 people,
the entire human race,
with nothing but the clothes on
their backs and some provisions.
It's not the
entire human race.
There are people
already here.
Tribal.
Without language, even.
Well, we can
give them that.
I mean, we can
give them the...
The best part
of ourselves.
And not the baggage,
not the ships,
the equipment, the
technology, the weapons.
If there's one thing that we
should have learned it's that...
You know, our brains have
always outraced our hearts.
Our science charges ahead,
our souls lag behind.
Let's start anew.
We'll land
civilians at various points
around the planet.
Our objective
will be to spread
the people out as
much as possible
to give them the best
possibility of survival.
Supplies will be evenly
distributed throughout the camps,
and locations will be
documented and given to everyone.
I have to say, I'm shocked at how
amenable everyone is to this notion.
I would have thought there'd be
a general uprising at the idea
of losing whatever little
creature comforts we had left.
Don't underestimate the desire
for a clean slate, Mr. Lampkin.
Have you made
a decision?
The Sixes, the Eights, and
the Twos have decided to stay.
See how we can contribute to a world
before we pass
into God's hands.
We'll give the Baseship
to the Centurions,
let them find
their own destiny.
I think they've
earned their freedom.
And what if they evolve
again on their own
and decide to come back in a few
hundred years and wipe us out?
It's a risk,
but I think setting
them free may be enough
to break the cycle
of violence.
Then it's
a risk worth taking.
And I agree.
They've earned it.
Now, once the civilians
have been offloaded,
the Fleet will
leave the orbit
and rendezvous
with Galactica.
The course of the
Fleet will be plotted
into the nav computer
ahead of time,
but the actual piloting
will be done by Mr. Anders.
He'll guide the entire
Fleet directly into the sun.
I love you.
Goodbye,
Sam.
I'll see you on
the other side.
Is your name
William Adama?
Yes.
Are you an officer
in the Colonial Fleet?
Yes.
Are you a Cylon?
I'm sorry, Bill. We're still
establishing tests for the control.
I need verifiable
yeses and nos.
No, I'm not
a Cylon.
Have you ever stolen
money from a cash drawer?
Have you ever
stolen money...
Enough of this crap.
Take this thing off of me
right now. No job is worth this,
no matter how fat
the paycheck is.
I'd rather spend the rest of
my career, or what's left of it,
in a broken-down
old ship,
than have someone sit
here and question my word.
Perfection.
That's what it's about.
It's those moments
when you can feel the
perfection of creation,
the beauty of physics, you
know, the wonder of mathematics
and the elation of
action and reaction,
and that is the
kind of perfection
that I want to
be connected to.
You're sure this is
what you want, Galen?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm just tired of people,
humans, Cylons, whatever.
Last Raptor out tomorrow is gonna
drop me off on this island that I found
off one of the
northern continents.
It's cold. It's up
in the highlands.
There's no people.
Good luck.
For what it's worth,
if what happened
to Cally had
happened to Ellen,
then I'd have done
the same frakking thing.
Hmm.
Hey!
Ah!
I thought Bill was coming.
He's taking a leak.
Oh, nice.
Hey, order me a drink,
honey, and keep them coming.
Tonight we are
celebrating your retirement
and all the time I'm about to
get to spend with my husband.
Are you good
with that?
Saul! All I've ever
wanted was to be with you.
Not just weekend liberties
or a two weeks' leave a year.
I mean full-time.
You and me, together
in a house, in a tent,
homeless and
on the street.
Just be together.
Mmm-hmm.
Excuse me.
Ah!
Oh! Don't drop me!
To us!
Mmm!
Yeah!
There are so many.
Wait, I wanna...
See more detail.
It's
a very beautiful world.
Does it have a name?
Earth.
It's not Earth.
Earth is a dream.
One we've been chasing for a long time.
We've earned it.
This is Earth.
Okay then.
Earth.
It's fine.
I'm having trouble
breathing.
Would you like to get
a better look at them?
Yes, I'd love it.
What... What
do you mean?
Watch.
What? Why?
What are you doing?
Watch me.
Put your arm around me.
Can you?
Dad?
I don't have
much time, Son.
I understand.
What do you
hear, Starbuck?
Nothing but the rain.
Grab your gun and
bring in the cat.
You should go.
You know, my very earliest
memory of my father
was him flying away
on a big plane
and wondering when
he was coming back.
He's not coming
back this time.
No, he's not.
Neither am I.
Where are
you going?
I don't know.
I just know that
I am done here.
I've completed
my journey,
and it feels good.
You and I,
right here,
right now.
On the table?
I dare you.
I double-dog
dare you.
Double-dog dare?
I double-dog
dare you.
Hmm.
All right.
Oops!
Something's broken.
I guess I better
get going.
Yeah.
It was nice
to meet you,
Lee Adama.
Likewise, Kara Thrace.
So what about you?
What are you gonna do?
Today is the first day of
the rest of your life, Lee.
Well,
I always thought when
this was all done I would
kick back,
relax,
spend the rest
of my days doing
the absolute minimum
humanly possible.
And now that
you're here?
I want to explore!
I wanna climb the mountains.
I wanna cross the oceans.
I wanna...
Gods, I can't believe
I'm saying this.
It sounds so exhausting.
I must be crazy...
Goodbye, Kara.
You won't be forgotten.
Laura?
You okay?
Hi.
Sean, it's been
a lovely evening.
Really lovely.
But what?
But I'm afraid we won't
be doing this again.
Did I...
No.
No, no, not you.
No, you're wonderful.
Come on, then...
No.
You can show
yourself out.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
Okay.
Hello, this is
Laura Roslin.
I'd like you to give
a message to Mayor Adar.
Tell him that I will
be joining
his campaign.
Thank you.
All the way
to the end.
No matter what.
All the way
to the end.
So much
life.
It's a rich continent.
More wildlife than all the
12 Colonies put together.
Just looking for a quiet
little place for that cabin.
Maybe a garden.
I don't have much of
a green thumb,
so I hope that you do...
Right there.
I'm gonna build it
right there, Laura.
Lot of game
on this planet.
I'm a pretty good hunter,
you know?
Yeah, right.
What are
you laughing at? What?
That buck on Caprica.
Okay, come on, now. That's not fair.
Hey, don't you listen to
Mommy. Daddy is a great hunter.
No, Mommy's gonna
teach you how to hunt.
No, no, no, no.
Real hunting.
No.
Yeah.
And I'm gonna teach you how to
build a house and how to plant crops.
Okay, maybe Mommy
will teach you that,
but Daddy's gonna
teach you how to hunt.
Hera!
Hera.
Will she be
all right?
She survived
thanks to you.
Both of you.
And that's it?
That's all God
wants of us?
God's plan is
never complete.
Great.
But I think
it's safe to say
that from now on,
your lives will be less
eventful.
I've been thinking I may be
able to help you out after all,
about that thing you
were asking about before,
getting a peek into
the defense mainframe.
That would mean
a lot to my employers.
Yeah, well, I'm not doing
it for your employers.
I'm doing it for you. How
would it make you feel?
I'd be very grateful.
We'll put that
to the test.
Because if anyone finds out,
I could get my head cut off.
So I'll count on
your discretion.
The things men
do for love.
Love?
Gaius!
Yeah, well...
You know
what I mean, don't you?
Over there, between those two peaks,
I saw some terrain that
looked good for cultivation.
Cultivation?
Yes.
You know, I know
about farming.
Hey.
I know.
I know you do.
I laid out
the cabin today.
It's gonna have
an easterly view.
You should see the
light that we get here.
When the sun comes from
behind those mountains,
it's almost heavenly.
It reminds me of you.
"At a scientific
conference this week
"at the Smithsonian
Institution in Washington,
"the startling announcement
was made
"that archeologists
believe they have found
"fossilized remains
of a young woman
"who may actually
be Mitochondrial Eve.
"Mitochondrial Eve is the
name scientists have given
"to the most recent
common ancestor
"for all human beings
now living on Earth.
"She lived in what
is now Tanzania,
"over 150,000
years ago. "
Along with her Cylon mother
and human father.
Commercialism, decadence,
technology run amok.
Remind you of anything?
Take your pick.
Kobol, Earth, the real
Earth, before this one.
Caprica before
the fall.
All of this has
happened before.
But the question
remains.
Does all of this
have to happen again?
This time, I bet no.
You know, I've never known
you to play the optimist.
Why the change of heart?
Mathematics, law of averages.
Let a complex system
repeat itself long enough,
eventually something
surprising might occur.
That, too, is
in God's plan.
You know it doesn't
like that name.
Silly me.
Silly, silly me.