We're trackinga serious storm,
equivalent toa Category 4 hurricane,
that's set to hammerthe Alaskan interior.
The remnants ofTyphoon Merbok,
moving throughthe Bering Sea,
are on courseto make landfall
in the next 24 hours.
And bring with it
strong winds,rain and snow.
Officials are expectingsevere floods
to hit many partsof Alaska.
Apparently, in the forecast
this is supposed to be
a five to 10 year event.
So, basically, it's
batten down the hatches
for the worst?
Yeah. That's what
they're calling for
in the next couple days.
It's that bad, huh?
- It's gonna be bad.
It rained all night.
- Real hard this morning.
- Yeah, it did.
I'm so
sick of this .
I can't tell what
this rain did to the creek.
So, we're about to go find out
what happened at the creek,
and what
happened to our stuff.
If it's flooding,
if we can dive,
if we can still
work in this stuff.
It doesn't seem like it.
We've got a weather
pattern coming so,
is it really feasible
to try to dredge today?
Well, what if this
is the last day
that we can dredge?
So, I say get in the water,
even if it's only
half a day.
Then you better hit it
while you can.
But we know we have
more rain coming,
so were gonna have to
pull the dredges up.
Yeah,
we're on the gold.
Snow's obviously
almost here,
and pushing us
out the door.
And we're on the verge.
We're about
to get caught out,
but I don't know
what to do, so...
Probably the foolish thing
to keep trying to get gold.
So, watch yourself out there.
Let's go find out
what it looks like.
See if we can
work there or not.
I don't know how
we would recover
from another wet storm
like we had before,
and they say it's
gonna be worse.
I just don't know
what to do.
If it rains too much,
it's gonna put us
out of business.
A massive storm
could end theirrecent run of luck.
I'm seeing gold!
For three weeks in a row...
- I knew
there was gold in here!
...both crews havebeen on a pay streak.
Right now, we're on gold.
We're finally starting
to see good gold.
Look at that!
Whoo, doggy!
Everyday we're getting gold,
so that's a great thing.
Pulling up nuggets...
There's a lot
of gold in here.
You knowwe're on a pay streak
when you still get
gold on a bad dive.
- We're getting it guys.
- Yeah.
- This is starting to
get exciting now.
And last weekthere was clear evidence...
Today was the most
gold that we've found so far.
...they're about to hitlife-changing gold.
We're on
the gold streak.
Like a little plunge pool,
and all that gold will be
lodged in those boulders.
This could be
our best season ever.
There's some hope.
This is going to
inspire everybody.
We're gonna get more gold
than we ever  thought.
If theycan keep dredging.
Holy , man.
Did it rain here?
Yeah. We were
expecting a flood
and we got no water.
I was not expecting this,
it rained all night.
and it must be mostly
snow up to the top,
'cause the water,
not only is it crystal clear,
it's low.
I expected this to be in,
uh, complete shambles.
I don't know what
the right move is.
This is like the best
dive days I've seen ever.
This is like
picture perfect right now.
We're on gold, we wanna
keep dredging,
but we can't afford to lose
all of our stuff either.
Are you
gonna sleep worse,
knowing that you missed out
on a good dive day,
having your  packed up,
or sleep better,
you had a good dive day,
couple of ounces of gold,
and nothing packed up?
What's the lesser
of the two evils?
I don't think
we have a choice,
but to dive.
I say we should do this.
I don't think it's
the right thing to do.
I think it's what
I want to do.
- We're gonna look for gold.
- All right.
I'm all with it, man.
I'mma dive.
The responsible
thing right now,
would be to pack this
place up right here,
and go pack up camp.
Do I do the responsible thing?
Or do I try to find gold?
Obviously,
I'm putting on my dive suit.
and, uh, not doing
the responsible thing.
Hopefully...
I can get us down
to the bottom of this thing.
I believe that Nugget Creek
still has a huge payload,
and I'm gonna keepdigging until I find it.
I'm gonna dig
as deep as I can.
Tell my guys
never to do it, but...
I dig straight down.
With a stormbearing down,
and only days left
before the Alaskan winterforces them out,
Dustin Hurt and his crew
are throwingcaution to the wind.
So, you guys
wanna just go that way.
One right here is
your deepest point, man.
Go suck that out.
There's a lot of
gold down there.
- All right.
- A lot of
rock moving.
It's probably
filled in right now,
but with gold.
Beneath the unstable
50-ton granite boulder,
they've discovereda rust-colored pay layer.
Now, if Dustincan clear the rocks,
and punch through,
he could hita massive pile
of the legendaryfour ounce chunks
that gaveNugget Creek its name.
I'm happy that
Dustin's getting in.
because ever day could be
one of our last dives.
Mother Nature's, uh,
rearing her head,
saying, "Winter's
coming early."
Everything good?
- All good?Have a good dive, man.
All right.Let's rock and roll.
Hello, old friend.
Let's see if Ican find some gold.
All right. I'm gonnaneed a basket.
It's a double-edged sword
we've got going on right now.
Do we keep trying
to find gold?
Or do we secure
our stuff at camp?
Water's down and clear.
We're gonna take
a chance today.
Man, there could be
a bonanza sitting right there.
We're gonna push it
to the limits now.
It's, uh, now or never.
Feel a bit jealous that
I'm not diving right now.
That water's so
dang clear.
There is big gold in there.
I know that for a fact.
He might be able
to actually see gold,
pick it out like we
used to back in
the old days, you know?
Start to take this out.
Missed thisman.
I missed diving.
I hope there's a lotof gold down here.
That's gotta be the clearest
I've seen the water yet.
I don't wanna be
a Debbie Downer,
but if this weather system
is as bad as they're
calling for,
there's a chance that today
might be the last dive.
I just want
a successful dive today
and get as much as we can.
With the way that this
weather forecast is looking,
I think I'm gonna
get in the water.
Only because if
it's the last dive
- I need a much material
moved as possible.
- Yeah.
So, it
needs to be a fast,
one-and-done type of thing.
Okay.
Work on getting
that other dredge
taken apart and pulled up.
We can
definitely do that.
But that way we're still
moving material,
making progress, but...
- we won't get caught
if the water starts coming up.
- No, I agree.
How's it going, Fred?
I'm gonna have these guys
start breaking down
the other dredge.
Get you with, uh, working
on the winch remotes.
- Yeah. All right.
- All right.
- So, everyone knows
what they're doing?
- Yup.
- We got a game plan in place?
Let's get it.
I'm gonna try to get
as much material
moved as possible
in a short amount of time,
'cause this very well
could be the last day
that we get to dredge
this season.
So, we need to make
the most of it, really.
Hopefully, there will
be a lot bigger gold
at the bottom.
Two days ago,
at 10 feet down,
Paul discovereda plunge pool,
that could holdthe deepest pointin the creek.
In just minutes,
he dredged up theirbest gold of the season.
Now, if Kaylacan remove the lastrocks from the bottom
and get to the lowest point,
there should bea golden payday
for the taking.
The pressure is
definitely on.
We definitely don't have
enough gold to show
for all of the hard work
that we've put in.
Hopefully, today
will change that.
Well, I wish her
a good day of, uh,
dredging today.
Hopefully uneventful.
Other than get some gold.
Hopefully at the event
happens at the end
when we all look
at the sluice box and...
- that's the event I want.
All right. You're good.Good luck.
Kayla is one of
the best divers we have.
So, we figured, get her in,
she's dredging that
nice, little plunge pool.
This could be one
hell of a gold cache.
Where should we start
breaking this down?
We'll pull
the sluice box out.
We'll take the engines off.
Anything that's
heavy on this dredge,
if we can get it off
and get it up there,
and then we're just down
to a frame with some floats.
That's gonna make it easier
trying to pick it up and out.
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
Man that was
wedged in there good.
Now that's a true Alaskan.
Short-sleeved shirt.
It's 38 degrees
out here and raining.
Justin's
gotta be awful tough
to do that, that's all
I got to say.
There's some rustystuff down here.
That's a good sign.
That's where all the gold is,in that rusty layer.
Hey, guys. I see a piece of gold in the bottom.
There's a crackin the bedrock
and can I seea piece of gold.
Seriously?
There'sa crack in the bedrock.
and I can see a nicepicker laying in it.
- Whoo!Nice.
Dig it out.Dig it out!
Hey guys,I see a piece of goldin the bottom.
There's a crackin the bedrock.
and I can see a nicepicker laying in it.
With a typhoonthreatening to wreak havoc
on southeast Alaska,
Kayla is running out of time
to uncover the big gold
Nugget Creek was named for.
So far, Kayla's diveis going pretty well.
She's kicking ass today,holy.
We know we've got
rain coming, but...
this is the start of it.
I just want the rain
to hold off for today
so we can finish this dive,
get to the bottom,
and, uh, see if we can
get a lot more gold.
The good news is
I went in that bedrockstraight down, but...
bad news I can't see anything.
Down creek,
Dustin is diving blind
beneath a 50-ton boulder.
His mission,remove the rocks
that stand in the wayof the bedrock gold.
Sorry,there's a rock right here
that is just notgonna give its way.
Carlos, can you grab mea choker, please?
Hell yeah!
I bet there'sgold down here
at the bottomof this damn hole.
Oh, there's some
gold right there! Gold!
There's gold inthe box already.
Go. Whatever you're doing,just keep doing it.
So, we aregetting gold, huh?
See a little something?
Yup. Alreadygot gold in the box,
that'sawesome, dude.
Good job!
Getting gold!
I have a good feeling
about, uh,
how much gold we're
gonna have in the box
at the end of the day.
Yeah, if he can get
deep enough, for sure,
hopefully.
There's a wholebunch of gold down here.
Can take any more of it.
This is a pile of rocks.
I'd love to get out of here.
You all right?
I justneed a second.
Scratched my hand.
Wow. That was something.
My thumb is destroyed, dude.
He  smashed it
between the rock
and the
edge of the dill
That  got him hard.
I just saw it.
That's a heavy
he just had right there.
That was something.
Yeah. There's anothergigantic boulder down there.
Imagine what's under these.
I wonder if these are
sitting on bedrock.
I think right here is
the deepest spot, right here.
All is takes is
that deep hole pocket.
- That's it.
- That's all it takes.
A coffee can full of nuggets
- is a lot of gold.
- Absolutely.
All right.Hopefully I got it.
Come on, baby.
Whoo!
Look at that boulder,
you see how red it is?
Oh, yeah.That rusty stuff?
That last
foot and a half of that
is supposed to
be full of gold.
Ooh!
Oh, my...
Can, uh...
think it'll pull up?
Woo-hoo!
Oh, mystill on.
See that?
- Lookat that.
- What.
- Dude, thatlooked likegold.
- Oh!
- Yeah,look at that.
I can't believe that held.
Look at it. That does notlook like it should've held.
If that boulder
was sitting on bedrock,
there should be
some nice gold.
The gold would be visible
if it was not encased
in all the orange rust.
I got all the bigboulders out, finally.
Now I've got bedrock
all the way to thisbig rock right here.
It's just oneboulder after another.
And they keep getting
larger as we go, so...
Sooner or later we
get under the right boulder,
that's just gonna have
a lot of gold there.
Ah! All right.
Pull up on the basket, please.
Up and out.
Up creek,Kayla inches closer
to bedrock.
That wason the very bottom.
Where you left off, Paul.
Oh, wow.
It waswedged in there.
That thing wasato get out.
Kayla's down there
moving them big ole rocks,
that, uh, 200 pound guys,
picking up and moving around,
just grabbing them
and moving them around
and, uh...
underwater, uh,
she's moving them up.
and getting them
into the basket.
Good for her.
You got somereally nice materialcoming through.
You know, it'sreally rusty down there.
That's whatwe're looking for.
Red-cloudedmyself out.
Lots of rust down here.
Hopefully there'sa good amountof gold in that material.
Four hours in,
Kayla has hit 13 feet,
the deepest point yetin the plunge pool.
I was under mine,some of the big rocks,
now, it's kindatunneled, so...
I'm running out ofmaterial I can work.
Pretty insane.
Kayla's desperate bid
to tunnel verticallydown to bedrock,
has left widowmakershanging up above.
Before they cango any deeper,
they'll need to widenthe mouth of the dive hole.
All righty.I'm gonna put this...
hose up and I'mgonna come up.
Copy that.
Nozzle is hooked.
Coming up.
I ran out ofmaterial to work.
without going fromthe top and expanding
and then coming back down.
I got some more depth though.
Good deal.
That's badass you saw
a piece of gold down there.
I like that.
The prettiest sight
would be some gold in the box.
How'd you make out?
- That's the piece I saw
in the bottom.
- There you go.
- Nice.
- There's some
pieces right there.
Yeah.
That the one
y'all saw earlier?
- Yeah.
- Ah, no .
- It was
stuck in a crack.
- Damn.
- There's a bunch of
other little pieces in there.
- Yeah there's a...
- a bunch right here.
- Quite a few of them.
There's one.
There's a bunch
of small stuff.
There's some
in the corner.
There's a bunch
stuck up here.
Looking pretty good.
Still have to look and see
what's in the fines.
The big stuff.
Really good.
If it stays like this
and that moisture river
just dumps a bunch
of snow upstream,
I think we'll get a few
more days of dredging.
And all that gold will be
locked in that plunge pool.
That would be nice.
I gotta get changed.
- 'Cause I'm cold.
- Yeah,
you get warmed up.
- I'm frozen.
- You put in
a good dive today.
Everybody was expecting
this to be flooded today.
But, uh, got some
dredging done.
picked up some gold.
And, uh, I think everybody's
pretty happy with it.
Tried to clean up
as much material
as possible today.
Hopefully,
the weather holds out.
The last thing
we need right now
is a huge flood.
We're preparing for the worst,
but hoping for the best.
Looks like they're
getting it ready to
haul it up the hill here.
I think
between the three of us
we should be able to
walk it over there.
Well, it's
definitely a good idea
to, uh, do a little
preventive maintenance.
Rather than coming out here
and doing a rescue mission.
That's so much
easier without those
side pontoons.
Oh, my .
That made
a world of difference.
- That should be good.
- Yup.
- Looking good.
Now tie off
every rope we got.
Everything's safe
and sound now, huh?
I think so.
- Good.
- I think we're
in good shape now.
We got both the dredges
pulled up and out,
just in case it floods.
Hopefully,
in the next day or so
once this storm passes,
we'll be able to
get back to work,
get back in the water,
and get back on the gold.
Up ahead...
That is some fast
moving water, man.
I finally realized
y'all are tougher than I am.
Is that all gold?
- There's gold.
- Whoo-hoo!
It's definitely
cold now.
Do we have enough time
to get to this point?
That is the question.
I don't know.
It's not that we're
not willing to do so,
it's all about what
Alaska will let us do.
We're fighting against
Alaska right now.
Mining 8 feet
beneath a 50-ton boulder,
Dustin is racing toput gold in the box
before a giant storm hits.
I cleaned off6 feet worth of bedrock
And I got this wall,until about here,completely cleaned.
It just goes down right here.
But I can't getunderneath this
big, giant rock right here.
It has to go away.
In order to continue,that rock has to move,
and we don't have time...
there's a storm coming.
It's time for meto get out of here.
Dustinwill need to blast
the large boulder.
But an explosionthis close to the...
to the 50 ton monstercould cause it to crash downinto their dive hole,
ending their season for good.
Good dive.
Good, good,
good dive.
Cleaned up under a whole
bunch of really big rocks,
all on bedrock.
So, if there's going to be
gold, it should be there.
Time to clean the dredge,
get all the mats out,
clean the box,
take it back to camp.
See what we got.
Dustin definitely moved
some frickin' big rocks.
So, if we get rid of this
big, big one right here,
and we're getting closer
and closer to the middle,
which I think is the deepest
point of this pool.
We're getting there.
We're getting there, actually
pretty quicker than I thought.
Oh, look at that.
Was that all gold?
That is gold.
Looks like about
an ounce or so a day,
maybe two,
if we can just continue
on with that, that's a great
haul.
There's still huge payload
down there, but we're
running out of time.
We're about to get really
hammered with some
water apparently.
I think we should prepare
for a flood.
- With any luck, it's just
snow on top.
- Yeah.
- But, if it doesn't rain,
storm is gonna wipe us out.
- Yeah.
- If we leave it in
a precarious situation.
- Mm-hmm.
- The dredge isn't safe.
- Okay.
I'm just trying to secure
the dredge as best I can
if we've got a flood comin'.
We don't really have
a way to pick it all
the way out.
So I'm just trying
to secure it, pick it up
the best I can
and hope for the best.
Both Kaylaand Dustin are onthe verge of unearthing
Nugget Creek's gold.
Just one more day of miningcould be all they need
to have the seasonof a lifetime.
We got another flood comin',
it's supposed to be
the biggest one of all of 'em.
So, trying to imagine
what's about to happen.
What is this place gonna
look like after the biggest
flood I've ever seen
comes through here?
Getting ready for the worst,
wrapping up my winches.
We can't afford to lose any
of the equipment.
It's .
It's... it's all the gears,
man...
- Yeah.
- ...that has to get
wrapped up, man.
That's good
right there, man.
That looks great.
I like the way it looks.
Okay, sounds good.
Are you ready?
Well, it looks like
our site's buttoned up,
ready for the worst,
the storm. Hopefully,
they are wrong about
what's coming in.
The weather, we don't
need it right now.
We do not need
another flood taking away
all of our stuff.
It's all buttoned up,
so hopefully we're good
I'll make a toast to you guys.
It has been a good time.
And I finally realized
- y'all are tougher than
I am.
Now, if you take my
direction you're gonna
get a lot of gold.
- It's about 20 feet from
where you're working.
- Wherever I'm digging.
- 20 feet away. Got it.
Appreciate your help,
Fred.
Y'all got one hell
of a storm coming
in here, soon.
There's a big storm
comin' right now.
- Huge.
- It's either gonna drop snow
or a ton of rain.
We'll see what happens.
Well, I got to catch
a plane.
This is not the best weather
for this, but we got to get
you back to town, Fred.
Again, thanks everybody.
I appreciate it.
All right, let's get down
to the boat, get it ready
to go.
Dustin, we're about ready
I think we're ready to rock.
You gotta get the hell
out of here.
That river don't look friendly
out there at all.
Have a safe trip, Fred.
We're waking up to reportsof flash flooding
and mudslides, as the effectsof Typhoon Merbok continueto hammer parts of Alaska.
The highest rainfallfor 50 years has beenrecorded
and a red weather warningremains in place for manyparts of the state.
Officials are recommendingall residents remain indoorsuntil the storm passes
It's been raining since
midnight, that's a lot of rain
in a short amount of time.
All that snow that was
up there is...
...is now melted too,
so that three inches of rain
plus all that snow melt.
A series of stormshas made the past six monthsthe wettest
in Alaska's recorded history.
Now, just as both crewsare back on the gold,
a monster typhoon hasdevastated Nugget Creek.
We've had multiple instances
of rain overnight,
so we're fixing to
head up to our site.
Only Paul, Kayla
and myself are here,
the rest of the guys,
we kind of split up
so they would only have
to make one boat ride
into town get supplies.
I'm not sure if they can
get back today.
So we're stuck out here
with just the three of us
to go to our site
and see what's going on.
All those boulders
get in our hole,
there's just...
- There's nothing--
- There's no time to get
them back out.
No, that would just be
stupidity to try to start
over again.
- Insanity.
- Stupidity at this point.
All right, let's get out
of here.
We're gotta go up there
and see what that boulder
we've got...
that Fred tied off for us did.
Yup.
With this kind of
, I could see it
washing that out.
We thought
that last flood was bad.
I think
this season's over.
Holy .
And that
is hauling ass.
Hear the boulders?
That's so
loud.
Holy crap. That's .
That's insane.
This is way worse
than that other flood.
Way worse.
In southeastAlaska, the remainsof a coastal typhoon
have slammed intoNugget Creek,
dropping over three inchesof rain in under 12 hours.
The first one
was bad but this one's
terrible.
When we finally
started getting on some gold,
now this.
I mean, you could hear
the boulders rolling down
the creek,
sounds like thunder,
sounds like I'm in a Texas
thunderstorm right now.
See all that
falling.
Rock slide
over there,
see it coming down.
That's crazy. Damn.
For 10 years I've been
up there I've never seen this.
No, no, no. There's not
a  thing we can
do here.
The power of this water
is just insane,
It'd be suicide to be
in the water right now.
You'd just get...
You'd get pulverized.
It'd eat you alive.
The thought of getting
in that water doesn't even
cross my mind.
No. I know, one wrong step
right now and you end up
in there, you're done.
This is a freaking
nightmare.
So I wonder what we can see
if we can at least get around
the corner and look
- up to where's your site,
- We can go look.
- Wanna look around
the corner?
- Yeah.
I'm going down.
Our
walk way is washed out.
I think it's safe to say
we are going to our site,
No.
So, either way, Mother
Nature always gives us
an end,
she either gives us gold,
or gives us .
This year, it's just a lot
of hard work and .
We can't even
get out to the dredge,
I hate to say it but I think
this is it.
I think this is the end.
I don't think there's any
coming back from this one.
Not this one.
I mean, all we can do
is just sit back and wait.
That sounds like
that just picked up in
intensity.
Let's get out here.
- Yeah, let's get off
this walk way.
- Yeah, let's go.
Let's get out of here.
This is tragic right
now. I mean, we are so
close to this large gold.
We thought we had figured
out how to mine this,
this creek, but Mother Nature
has shown us a different story
this year.
We can't even get to our site.
Right now it's a waiting game.
We just gotta let it run
its course and then check
the carnage afterwards.
- Let's get the hell
outta here.
- Get outta here.
All that  washing
away, there's nothing
we can do.
Well, that's depressing
as .
Seems like a good
day to just start drinking.
Holy .
- That's scary,
wild man.
Woah!
That is some
fast moving water, man.
- Is he gonna make it?
- man,
I hope so.
Holy crap.
Almost there.
- Yeah, buddy,
- That's what I'm talkin'
about.
- We made it.
- How many times did
you think you were gonna die?
Holy
Yeah,
that just happened.
Did all that just happen?
Are we still alive?
Am I dead?
I was hoping this thing
wouldn't freakin' lose power,
man.
Good driving, dude.
I just felt like a point where
I wasn't moving anymore.
Thank god that's over man.
Dude, that's scary water,
man.
I took it as easy
as I could now.
That is some scary
water, man.
That's going there,
what's happening here?
Ah, I'd agree.
Let's get to the site,
see what we got.
The current is ripping.
Gonna chew it out, bud.
Okay.
Torrential rainshave rerouted Nugget Creek
and washed out the ATV trailstranding the Whitewaterfilm crew.
- What are you doing,
.
- A little bump in the middle.
Yeah.
You wanna try and wheel it?
Yeah, as long as you have
two wheels on the dirt.
All right,
you guys ready?
Hang on tight.
Woo-hoo. Hello country.
All right.
Let's see what
those minors are up to.
About time you showed up.
You guys go look
at the site?
How's it look?
It's .
The dredges, got rocks
in front of it, it's got rocks
behind it,
the waters by shooting
six feet over the bridge.
I don't even think
the upstream winch is there.
That  is devastated,
dude, I think this is going
to be the end of our season.
I don't think we're coming
back from this
Did your equipment
make it?
We can't even get to our
site right now, that water's
raging so much,
it's over our walkway,
it doesn't look good.
Our dredges should be safe.
We got them up and out
of the water
but I don't think
anything else is gonna
survive that.
So what you're
saying is we're done.
I don't see a recovery
from this.
Dustin's investedeverything he owns to buythe claims at Nugget Creek.
Now, the worst typhoon to hit Alaska in over 50 years
threatens to bankrupt him.
I've been coming up
for almost 10 years
and I've never seen
anything like this.
- I have to wrap
my head around this.
- Yeah.
- I just, I, uh...
- It's devastating.
I'm freaking out a little
bit right now, yo.
Freakin' out.
All right, let's get up
the hill, I'll start assessing
what the problem is.
All right.
- Dammit.
Did we lose all that
damn gear?
Let's hope not, man.
I feel like I failed y'all.
No one can prepare
for something like this, dude,
no one can.
Freakin' out a little bit.
We only literally have
a couple of weeks
at the most left,
all this pain and crazy rain
is just frickin' unbelievable,
man.
I took Fred back
so he can catch his flight,
and overnight
it rained three or four
inches apparently.
And it sounds like
everything is devastated.
The site's gone.
The roads are gone.
The creek is over its...
... sides.
Sounds like we lost
everything and everything's
over.
- I'm freaking out right now.
- I know, I know
you are.
I'm trying to calm
myself down.
And the only way I know
how to do that is to go
get my eyes on everything,
and go find out
what is the deal.
you. Let me go.
No frickin' way.
Wow. Dude,
you see that road?
- yeah, I do.
- It's a
river now.
- This looks pretty bad.
- I don't know what to think,
I don't know what to do.
I'm doing
the only think I know
what to know,
charge at it and see
what happens.
Holy cow!
That's not
a creek anymore.
That's a river.
Holy .
Get the
outta here.
Holy .
This is scary.
Lotta hate, lotta destruction.
You'd not have known
that yesterday we were
diving in his water.
This is a nightmare.
It's beyond anything
I thought was possible
here.
Surging at speedsof over nine feet per second,
Nugget Creek is capableof hurling 100 poundboulders into the dive holes
they've spent weeksdigging out.
All our hard work just
flushed down the toilet,
just when we're starting
to see frickin' gold in
the box.
This is crazy.
I've never seen
a flood this bad.
I don't know how
we're gonna come back
on this one.
How is that board
sitting there like that?
- The walkway-- Yeah.
- The walkway got ripped
apart.
Looks like the winch
is half gone.
I hope everything
didn't get destroyed.
All right guys,
let's see what we can
salvage.
Carlos, see if you can find
another rope.
and figure out how
to tie that thing off.
- Okay, uh...
- Figure something out.
Right now it's kind of
a rescue mission.
We need to just try to save
everything that we can,
obviously, we won't be
able to save everything,
but we need to really
salvage what we can
so that next year
we still have equipment
to use.
- Can you clean that up,
collect the electronics...
- Yeah.
- and all that .
- Yeah. Yeah.
I gotcha.
James,
we should bring that
and tie that up here,
and that'll keep that
going forward.
Right now, the dredge
is flowin' down the river
so I'm just doing what I can
to try to save our dredge.
Uh, we prepared
for the worst, and this is it.
Think we'll be able
to dredge again?
I don't know.
This is the hardest place
we've ever dug,
this is more than I ever
thought could happen here.
And we thought
we were prepared.
Yeah.
This makes me very sad.
I'm having a hard time
trying to figure out if I
can salvage this.
After monthsof backbreaking work,
Dustin and his creware on their best goldof the season.
Now, he faces his toughestdecision, cut his losses,or attempt a fight back.
All right,
now we've got our
dredge secured.
Let's say we get
the  outta here before
the side come down on us.
I still wanna
dig this, I think we can.
I think the dredge
is all right.
The mechanical stuff looks
in good shape.
I don't think
we should hang out here.
I'd agree.
Let's just get out of here
before it's too dangerous
and we die.
Come back up and find out
what the devastation
is tomorrow.
What we can salvage.
We are so close to this
large gold, we don't want
to leave it till next year.
I think we can make it work.
There's a lot of devastation.
It's a huge flood,
but I think the water
will be down tomorrow.
We can find out what
the actual damage is.
Just caught me completely
off guard.
I thought we'd have us
a flood, we dig out
the kitty litter
and that'd be the end of it.
We thought we were prepared.
I've invested a lot,
this has to pay off.
It has to pay or else
I'm gonna going broke.
We'll find out tomorrow.
On the seasonfinale ofGold Rush:
White Water...
I need one of you
to tell me that we can
dig this.
Yeah, we can dig this.
Our walk way is completely
gone.
I'm gonna get my waders on
and see if I can find
a way across.
Let's go,
cowboy.
So you guys are done?
You're not gonna
dig there anymore?
It'll take us a week
to get setup.
We'll work for you
and give you guys
a hand.
It's all hands of deck...
When in doubt,
blow  up.
Fire in the hole!
That could be where
those big four ounce
nuggets
can be lurking out.
This is just the chunky stuff.
It's not all of it.
Holy, that's
good stuff.
- Dig a hole, man.
- You can do it,
Look out!
- Rock...
- Rock, rock, rock...
Move, move, move,
move...