Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
So far our killer has given us
three tableaus--
the intestines in the scale,
the snakes victim,
and the four horsemen.
What about the numbers
we found on the body,
1237 and 1242?
He's counting up to something.
Maybe it's to the end
of the world.
- Dexter.
- Sam, what are you doing here?
Brother Sam?
Are you guys, like, friends now?
We have a lead.
This revelation expert
James Gellar.
The professor from
the University of Tallahassee?
Looks like we just found our
number one person of interest.
You're going out
with that woman, aren't you?
You knew this was gonna happen.
She's part of God's plan now.
Is this Doomsday number two?
During the middle ages,
it was believed that the outcome
of nearly all earthly events
was decided by angels,
either light or dark.
I'm quite certain
that face I saw in the crowd
was of the dark variety.
Unfortunately, he's chosen
to remain anonymous.
He left no trace DNA,
no sweat, no saliva,
no prints.
A small repair.
Something skin-like.
Not your normal glue.
Despite his wish
to remain hidden,
I may find a way
to yank him out of the shadows
after all.
Eyes on God, not me.
And all God's people said...
Amen.
Help me up.
It's time to do
a little hunting.
I thought
that we had some time.
You still don't hear him.
I've been fasting and praying
for days, and all I can hear
is the sound of my own voice
banging around my head.
God remains silent to me.
It's a good thing I'm around.
'Cause we have to find
the whore of Babylon.
I was right about the glue--
a polyvinyl acetate polymer
dissolved in toluene.
And the backing is calfskin.
Together they're used in
ancient manuscript restoration.
Dude, your sister,
briefing room, now.
Okay, thanks.
I'll be there in a minute.
This is no amateur.
Thank you for joining us,
Dexter.
Okay, everyone,
let's get started.
Our victim is Erin Baer, 29.
She worked
at the glass house cafe
at the Miami Cultural Center.
Miami Cultural Center,
full of ancient artifacts
in need of repair.
I want unis plastering
Gellar's picture
all over the area.
Maybe someone got eyes
on him there.
I'll take lead on that.
Great. Where are we on
the revelation aspect of this?
Between the trumpet flowers
placed around her,
the locusts,
and the iconography of an angel,
our Doomsday killer
was most likely referencing
Revelation chapters
8 through 10.
Any idea why he changed it up?
Why our entrance
triggered her death?
Normally a serial killer
wants to do the kill themselves.
It's the whole point, right?
There's a passage which reads,
"You must go back
and report your message
"to many peoples and nations
and languages
and kings."
So I'm guessing
we're those people.
It seems his message is
more important than the thrill.
Tell me you got something
from the M.E.'s office.
She found traces of spermicide
in Erin Baer.
The M.E.'s take
is that the victim had sex
with someone who used
a spermicidal condom.
So what are we thinking,
that she just happened
to have sex
before she was kidnapped?
Or maybe she met Gellar,
had sex with him,
and things got ugly for her.
Or maybe
it was Gellar's accomplice.
Can't say for sure either way.
As far as we know,
she didn't know Gellar.
What did we get
on Gellar's last gig?
I've been trying to contact
his last teacher assistant
Carissa Porter.
But so far
University of Tallahassee
has given us shit-all.
University's
not exactly thrilled
to be linked
to Professor Nutbag.
Well, let's go up there
and make it clear to them
that we don't give a shit
whether they're thrilled or not.
I'm on it.
Lab boys, what do we have?
Um, I've got locusts.
But the necropsy on them
turned up jack and shit.
All they ate
was local greenery.
What about the dead fish
outside the angel crime scene?
All local.
You can catch them
off any pier,
buy them at any fish market.
But we did find--
ta-da--
another number.
This one lodged
in Erin's esophagus.
1,244.
Same paper and ink
as the other two.
1237, 1242, 1244.
I did a check
into that number's usage
in the Book of Revelation.
Excuse me.
- Who's this?
- Uh.
Louis Greene,
the latest and greatest intern
from my forensics class.
He's up to speed
on the whole Doomsday case.
- What happened to the blonde?
- She's gone.
Go on, Louis.
Yeah, well,
numerology
is all over revelation,
but the only number
that's repeatedly referenced
that's in the thousands
is 1,260.
1260. You think
that's what he's counting up to?
If so, we've only got
15 days left.
And then what?
I don't know.
End of the world,
the rapture, Armageddon.
More apocalyptic bullshit.
Dex, please tell me you have
something we can use.
I hate lying to my sister,
but--
Oh, sorry, nothing on the wings.
Okay, let's keep at it.
Let's find
this jizzbucket Gellar.
Class dismissed.
Hey.
All that tippy-tappy stuff
you do on your laptop,
you're kind of a whiz
with computers, aren't you?
I tool around.
I've done some consulting.
I've made a couple RPGs.
Oh, role-playing games.
Nice.
Any of them feature Amazon women
of immense strength,
by any chance?
- No.
- Oh, that's okay.
Anyway, um, you mind?
Oh, yeah.
- Ice Truck Killer?
- Shh.
Let's keep it down, all right?
It was stolen
from our evidence room,
and if word gets out
we're losing evidence,
this department's street cred
goes straight down the shitter.
Well, why don't you just
get it back from the seller?
I tried.
You have to give the site
what you're selling
before they agree
to auction it.
- Fuckers.
- I see.
So my question to you is...
Can I make this problem
go away?
I'll look into it.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
A minute.
This is awkward.
What?
The engagement ring.
Fuck me in the ear,
I never gave it back to you.
Yeah, it's just that I got
30 days to return it.
- And since we're not gonna use--
- I'll get it back to you.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I mean, you've had a lot
on your plate lately.
I better go.
Got some professors to harass.
- Hello?
- Jamie, it's Debra.
I need a little favor from you.
About two weeks ago,
I brought a ring box
home with an engagement ring
in it.
You lost an engagement ring?
I left it on Harrison's side
of the apartment.
- Have you seen it?
- Uh, no.
Do you think
you could look for it?
I really appreciate all the help
I can get right now.
Thank you.
Bye.
Hey, Dex.
- Sam.
- Hey.
Hey, how your little man doing?
Oh, he's doing great.
You should come by and see him.
Yeah, okay.
I'd love to.
Yeah.
Uh, how about tonight?
Uh, great, great.
You want to say 8:00?
- Perfect.
- Cool.
You didn't come
all the way out here
just to ask about Harrison,
did you?
Yeah, I wish.
Some of Nick's old crew,
they came by
and shot up the shop.
Anybody hurt?
No, it was
an after-hours thing.
There was just bullet holes
in the garage door.
That's about it.
I called the cops,
but nobody showed up,
so, without the cop report,
the insurance don't do shit.
You ever think of moving?
No.
God put me there
to do what I'm doing, man.
I don't scare off.
You're a brave man, Sam.
O.G. For G-O-D,
know what I'm saying?
Yep.
Nope.
See you tonight.
All right.
Excuse me, do you work here?
Read my tag.
I'm a docent.
How may I help you?
I accidentally poked a hole
in a painting
that belongs to my boss.
I put my elbow right through it.
I know.
I'm such an idiot.
- Is there someone I can talk to--
- Follow me.
Okay.
- Here at the museum...
- Right in here.
- Thank you.
- A lot of the action
is behind the scenes.
For nearly 35 years...
I'm sorry.
This isn't exactly--
Have you seen this before?
...restored works of art...
No.
Well, sit down and watch it.
It's very informative.
That's why we made it.
...staining, discolorations.
They can make the art
look almost exactly
the way the artist intended it,
all while using
the same materials
that the artist used
during his or her own lifetime.
You wouldn't believe
how people end up treating
what can end up being
priceless works of art,
especially in our paper
conservation laboratory
where we're equipped with...
It's him.
The face I'm looking for.
He works here.
That's how he knew
how to create those wings.
Morgan.
This is Detective Anderson.
Dispatch gave me your number.
We need a blood guy
on the double.
We're out at Miami shores.
1588, Northeast end
of 2nd Street.
Got it.
Using radiograms
and infrared imaging...
Do you happen
to know the name of--
Worst docent ever.
What do we got?
Male and female.
40s.
Pictures on the walls
and rings on their fingers
make them man and wife.
Three gunshots.
One to the chest,
two to the stomach.
The first cut on the face
not from a gunshot.
- Maybe the fall.
- No, he fell back.
It looks more
like a glancing blow.
Cell phone.
Maybe she threw it at him.
That's not the wife.
Single gunshot to the chest,
through and through,
shot at close range.
No gun in sight.
Give me a hand.
We have our shooter.
The husband leaves,
forgets his phone,
the wife finds the pictures...
Wife throws phone
at two-timing bastard.
And then shoots him,
boom, boom, boom,
three times.
She realizes what she did.
She's distraught.
She turns the gun to her chest
and blam.
Murder-suicide.
Took you all of 15 seconds
to solve that.
It was a pretty easy one.
Hey, how the hell does a pro
like you stand working
with the rest of these
Miami Homicide chuckleheads?
Well, they're actually
pretty good,
especially my sister Deb.
You probably know her
as Lieutenant Morgan.
- Excuse me, detective?
- Hey, you can't be in here.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's okay.
I own the place.
They just--
Oh, my God.
Can I help you?
I don't mean to sound crass,
but...
How long will they stay here?
Till we finish.
Then the M.E.
will remove the bodies.
And then how long will it take
for you to clean it up?
Do I look like your maid?
Try not to look, huh?
What?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
God gave man the desire
to look at women.
It's the devil who made them
dress like that.
That's not it.
What?
It's sad.
All of these people are doomed,
and they don't even know it.
It is sad.
You're very sensitive, Travis.
That's why you've been chosen.
Is that you?
It's not bad, huh?
They're calling you
the Doomsday killer.
It's kind of catchy.
I probably should stay
out of sight.
You may have to find
our whore without me.
By myself?
I can't.
Yes, you can.
I believe in you.
God believes in you.
Aah!
I have a face.
Now I just need a name.
Travis Marshall.
Ancient manuscript restoration
and conservation.
No arrests, no warrants.
No moving violations,
not even a parking ticket.
Appears you live
a quiet little life
on 1742 Victory Street.
Ready to see Brother Sam?
- Hey.
- Hey, Sam.
Come on in.
- Let me take those for you.
- Nice.
Nice place you got here, man.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, little man.
How you doing?
He's sleepy.
It's about his bedtime.
Right on time then, 'cause...
It's his bedtime too.
Maybe you could put him
to sleep for me?
Yeah?
Can you say thank you,
Harrison?
Thank you, Harrison,
for helping me
put my little man to sleep.
Either way,
it's very nice of you.
Not a problem.
How's he doing
after the surgery?
He's doing great.
That's good.
I'm gonna put him to bed.
I'll just be a few minutes.
All right.
Good night, little man.
- Make yourself at home.
- Thank you.
And now I guess
Sam and I are gonna hang out.
That's a cute boy
you got there, man.
Yeah, he's a keeper.
It must be kind of hard
for you, man.
Just get up every day,
leave, and go do what you do.
Do what I do?
Homicide every day.
How you end up in that, man?
My dad was a cop.
I just sort of fell into it.
Doesn't sound like the kind of
thing somebody just fall into.
What really happened?
I guess in a weird way
I was sort of drawn to it,
the blood work.
Why?
When I was three, I watched
my own mother get killed.
Something like that
stays with you.
That's rough, man.
I'm sorry.
Seeing that so young,
the darkness got in deep.
Never left me.
Never will.
You remember anything
before she died?
I don't know.
I remember at night
she would wrap me in a quilt
and sing songs to me.
Sometimes she'd trace her finger
along my ear.
Tickling me.
Must have made you feel good.
It did.
She was sharing that light
with you.
It's with you now.
It's inside you.
Think you got the wrong guy.
Well, the good book tells us
that there's no darkness
that the light can't overcome.
So all the darkness
that you think you got
- inside you--
- Yeah?
All it takes
is just a little bit of light
to keep it at bay.
Believe me.
I know.
It's like with your son, man.
And see?
I just mention him,
and you just light right up.
I guess I do.
And you're sharing
that light with him
every day all the time.
You really think so?
I see it.
You just got to let it out.
This is really nice, man.
We got to do this again
sometime.
Shh.
Hey.
Hey! Hey!
Put her down!
Get the fuck out of here!
Help me!
Help!
Travis.
Where you been?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't do it.
- I tried.
- It's okay.
Many heroes of the faith
have endured their failures.
God's grace prevailed then too.
I thought I could do it.
Hey, it's my fault really.
I shouldn't have let you
go do this alone.
Tomorrow night,
I'll be there with you.
What about the police?
Do you think God's gonna allow
anything to slow us down now?
You go home, get some rest.
Tomorrow night,
we'll start again.
Tomorrow night.
Brother Sam says we all have
a light inside us.
If I find Travis Marshall
to be guilty...
then I will snuff out his light.
He's neat.
Everything in its right place.
Masters degree in Art History
from the University
of Tallahassee,
the same place Gellar taught at
before he disappeared.
I understand the urge
to end someone's life,
but what is this fascination
with ending the world?
Looks like the same numbers
we found
in the Doomsday victims.
Defacing the Bible.
I'm probably breaking a rule.
Hello, Doomsday killer.
I swear to God,
you're the only cop I know
that drives the speed limit.
That car's not a toy.
In the right conditions,
it'll top 110 easy.
And these weren't
the right conditions?
No.
Is that our professor?
Professor Porter?
- Yes.
- Hi, I'm Detective Quinn.
This is Sergeant Batista.
Miami Metro Homicide.
Dr. Knudson, the department
head, said we'd find you here.
Right.
He told me you were coming.
So you knew Professor Gellar?
I did,
but I want to state upfront
that Professor Gellar
didn't have anything to do
with those crazy Revelation
killings.
And you know this how?
I was his teacher's assistant
for a year.
He even helped me get my job.
Have you seen him recently?
No, not since he left.
When was that?
Three years ago about.
What about his blog,
"The Beginning of the End"?
I mean, you have to admit,
there's some pretty crazy stuff
on there, and a lot of it
is in line with the killings.
He likes to stir up trouble,
make people think.
That's what made
everyone love him.
Oh, so you loved him?
Was he eccentric?
Yeah.
But he was also smart,
charismatic,
brilliant even.
He saw things
between lines of text
that nobody else could.
Being with him
was an incredible adventure.
So you did love him?
We were close.
Close, huh?
Smart woman like you
with your looks,
I bet he was hitting
on you all the time.
I mean, fuck,
if we worked together,
I'd have a hard time not wanting
to get close to you.
It was more
than just a flirtation.
We lived together.
For a while.
You're not together anymore.
My year as his T.A. ended,
he found another cute brunette,
did the same thing with her.
Gellar had a thing
for brunette students?
I found out I was one
in a long line of girls,
but, you know what,
it was no big deal.
I'm glad I got the chance
to know him.
He was good to me.
Erin, our angel,
was a brunette.
Well, if by some miracle,
he contacts you--
You'll be the first one I call,
if only to prove
you have the wrong guy.
Hey, Professor Porter,
we're gonna be stuck here
for the night.
You wouldn't happen to know
of any good spots
where we could get a drink
this evening, would you?
Like some place kind of quiet?
Maybe I do.
Jesus Christ.
Do you always bring your work
home with you?
I can't work for fuck
in my new office.
It's like Laguerta's perfume
seeped into the walls.
If she ever had a soul,
it's still in there.
Life was so much simpler
when all I had to do
was solve murders.
Red to black.
- What it's all about.
- Who did it?
Wife.
Murder-suicide.
That brother of yours solved it
like he was getting a message
from the dead.
Yeah, he's something special.
Ooh, nice place.
Right by the beach too.
Nothing like a murder-suicide
to fuck up a great house.
I've seen worse.
Male, 70s,
self-inflicted shotgun
in the brainpan,
which is bad enough,
but he had cats.
And they got hungry.
- Enough said.
- Ah, Chicago.
Miss it?
Miss the food.
I mean, you can't get
a decent hot dog anywhere.
But homicide is homicide.
Yeah. I see the way you look
at people around here.
You got
the world's youngest Lt,
Batista and his hot rod,
Masuka with--
I made the mistake
of going in his lab unannounced.
- He was--
- Enough said.
He's got some fucked-up shit
going on,
but he gets it done.
The same could be said
for you, huh?
Good night, Anderson.
I'm grading this paper,
when all of a sudden I realize
I've read this before.
No way.
This dumbass student
changed some words around,
but he plagiarized
C.S. Lewis.
I should arrest this guy
right now.
I've got my cuffs on me.
We can go.
I mean--
That sounds like fun.
Yeah?
You want another round?
You're not married, are you?
Definitely not.
Then I want another drink.
Another round, please.
Thank you.
Oh, who looks shows up
when I'm buying drinks, huh?
Hey, listen, we got a long ride
down to Miami tomorrow.
- You want to call it?
- One second.
You can call it if you want,
but I'm about to cross
a fucking college professor
off my bucket list.
Oh, be careful, partner.
She's part
of our investigation.
No, she's not.
She's just like a nice person
we talked to, you know.
There's like 20 other women
here you could fuck.
I've already spent
like 80 bucks on her, though,
you know, so it's, like,
I don't want to have
to start all over again.
Get out of here.
Come on.
We'll see each other
in the morning, all right?
- You're unbelievable.
- Yeah, go on, baby.
And there they are.
Thank you.
Here's to you.
Hi, buddy.
Are you going to sleep?
Are you going to bed?
Are you tired?
Found your ring.
Oh, jeez, you're a lifesaver.
Deb, really?
Ah, shit.
He came in here
to give you a good night kiss,
not look at pictures
of dead bodies.
Yeah, well, maybe if you
gave me a little warning.
Isn't there anywhere else
you can do this, Deb?
Right now?
No. Nowhere.
Really? The lieutenant
doesn't get an office?
I don't like my office.
- I like to work here.
- Oh.
Harrison's got an entire
goddamn apartment over there.
I've got jack shit.
He just wanted
to say good night.
I know that.
Next time, why don't you
call me over there?
I will.
From now on.
And maybe you could keep
the photos on Dexter's desk,
so Harrison won't see them.
Again,
if you were doing your job,
this wouldn't have happened
in the first place.
My job?
- Yes.
- Really?
You mean my job isn't to be
your fucking maid?
- Oh.
- Uh-oh.
- I found it.
- Thank you.
- In Harrison's toy box.
- Thanks.
You're really lucky
he didn't eat it.
Oh, please.
- Thank God you're home.
- Hello.
She needs to do a better job
of watching Harrison.
She is bringing home
all of these horrible pictures.
Would it be weird
if I just left?
Hey, Jamie,
if Harrison's down
for the night,
maybe you should
just go on home.
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
Are you taking her side
on this?
No, I'll talk to her too
tomorrow,
but, Deb...
You got to admit
this isn't good for Harrison.
Yeah.
I'm a mess.
Maybe I do need
to go to therapy.
No more than me.
Am I that fucked up?
Bet you they don't even know
each other's names.
No wonder he wants us
to end it all.
These two.
Follow them.
Are you sure?
He looks pretty big.
He's not as big as God.
Go on.
Get the girl
before somebody comes.
Put her in the trunk.
Help me.
I'm sorry.
See how easy it is?
Come on.
Hey.
Come on in.
Where's Quinn?
Bathroom.
I'll get him.
Joey, your friend's here.
The Alpha and Omega
of the Enesserette.
Professor Porter,
could you come out here?
Uh, excuse me,
what are you doing?
These drawings,
they were Gellar's?
You can't just start picking
through--
Did Gellar do this?
Whoa.
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
- Did he?
- Well, yeah.
Let me see.
Holy shit.
Can I help you?
Michelle Ross.
The therapist
you've been dodging for weeks.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
Happens more than you think.
I figured since you weren't
coming to my office--
That you would come to mine.
Believe me, I understand.
So we should probably get down
to business, right?
Right here, right now?
Is that okay?
Let's do this.
Okay, just to clarify,
this is in reference
to the shooting
at Don Aldo's?
Have you been experiencing
any lack of sleep
from the shooting in question?
From the shooting, no.
Have you found yourself
dwelling on that day?
No.
Who has time?
Have you found it hard
to concentrate
on day-to-day tasks
because of the incident?
No.
Find yourself drinking more
than you did
before the shooting?
Fuck, I don't drink enough.
That was a joke.
Hm.
Have you been experiencing
any guilt since the shooting?
No.
If he walked through that door,
I'd shoot him right now.
Great.
So it sounds
like everything's fine.
Yeah.
Everything's great
with the shooting.
It's just everything
that's happened since then
that's fucking me up.
Like what?
Like being lieutenant.
And all the day-to-day bullshit
that comes with it.
Got the Doomsday killer
doing his shit in my city,
and I try to do any work
in here,
and I can't,
and--
did I mention I just broke up
with my boyfriend
and I don't have a place
to live anymore,
so, at the end of the day,
I can't even go home?
I'm living with my brother
and his son, and...
Don't get me wrong,
I love them,
it's just...
There's a reason I'm an aunt
and not a parent and...
I just feel like I don't
have a space
to call my own right now.
So maybe you should get
some place that's your own.
Detective Anderson
and girlfriend.
Her?
No way.
I'm married.
She's my boss.
Lieutenant Debra Morgan,
Miami Metro Homicide.
I'm so sorry.
I thought that you two--
- Don't worry about it.
- My bad.
Can we get
this crime scene tape down?
Wow.
It takes a lieutenant
to tell me it's okay
to rent this place, huh?
- Can we go inside?
- By all means.
Thank you.
I wanted to come by and see if
I could possibly rent the place.
Oh?
The floors are a mess.
Yeah, they are, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
Might have to replace 'em.
I mean, the toxic damage.
Toxic?
Blood-borne antigens
can live for two weeks easy.
Of course,
hep C is always a risk.
I didn't know that.
Oh, God, just what I needed.
Look, it's no secret
you're gonna have a hell
of a time renting this place.
Legally, you're required
to disclose the murder/suicide.
But I already know about it.
And?
What if I was to give you
2/3 of the current rent
right now today?
Make that 3/4, two-year lease,
and you clean up the place.
Looks like you got yourself
a new tenant.
Ah, what's the--
what's the progress on the--
Yeah, all right,
I did everything
I know how, but I wasn't able
to get the hand back.
The buyer bought it using
an eSniper program
that firewalls the buyer,
so whoever's got it's
got it for good.
- Oh, fuck.
- However...
I do like the sound
of your however.
I erased any trace
of the sale from the Internet.
So I'm sorry,
that's the best I can do.
So if one were
to look online--
It's like it never happened.
And I never checked it
out of evidence.
There's no trail
coming back to here.
At the worst, the evidence room
fucked up, not us.
Our department's safe.
And while I was
on your computer,
I improved your credit rating,
installed a modded-up intel chip
to overclock your CPU,
and, most importantly,
I added a porn scrubber
to that thing.
My man.
Give it up, Lou.
Thank you.
Drive out
of the parking structure,
turn right on Flagler,
and then drive on
past the Miami River.
Nod if you understand.
You can take the car.
It's yours, my wallet,
whatever you want.
I want none of those things,
Travis.
What do you want?
I want your life.
Just like the ones you took.
Doomsday killer.
God. God!
Yeah, let's start with him.
I suppose it was God
who told you to kill
all those innocent people?
God doesn't talk to me.
Then how do you know?
He talks to Professor Gellar.
And how do you know
he talks to God?
'Cause I've seen it.
God speaks to the professor.
He speaks
through the professor.
Keep going.
Before I met him,
I was lost.
But then the professor,
he showed me the truth.
He showed me the way.
He's a prophet
filled with truth and light.
Bullshit!
You killed those people
because you like it.
Answer me.
I couldn't do it.
I'm a failure.
I'm failing God.
Do you have any idea
what that feels like?
Yes, yes, I wanted
to kill those people,
but I couldn't.
You're saying
Gellar does the killing.
He's so much stronger than me.
The thing is, there's no fear.
There's no regret.
But with me it's--
it's pathetic.
Gellar is pulling you
toward the darkness, Travis,
not the light.
No, you don't know.
Trust me, I know more
about darkness than most,
and Gellar is pure darkness.
You need to find someone else
to follow.
Pull over.
Get out of the car.
What?
Get out and start walking away.
You'll find your car
back at the museum.
One way or another,
Travis will lead me
to the one who really deserves
my table.
Where are you?
I'm on my way home.
What's going on?
I don't feel good.
I've got--
I just feel sick.
I should get some sleep.
Travis, what are you
not telling me?
Nothing.
I just--
I feel sick.
I'll see you tomorrow?
Hey, you remember the story
about Jonah and the great fish?
Jonah tried to run from God.
He didn't get too far.
Hope you're not trying to run
from God too.
Think about it.
I don't believe in angels,
but I do believe
there's a constant struggle
between light and dark
in the world.
Who knows?
Maybe Brother Sam is right.
Maybe sometimes
the light can win out.
But in my experience,
darkness usually prevails.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com