[Quirky music]
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
That takes us
to the snakes killing.
Maybe Brother Sam
was right about our victim.
Is this what I think it is?
Evidence from the
Ice Truck Killer investigation.
You think that
my becoming lieutenant
had anything to do
with what happened between us?
No, I'm sure it was just
a big fuckin' coincidence.
I don't know how to act.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know who to hire.
Deb, you're too smart to think
that this was gonna be easy.
I put my ass on the line
even considering you,
so stow the attitude.
Are you going to be saved?
It's up to you.
[Whimpers]
You got to cleanse me of--
of all my sins.
He's ready.
Do you undertake
to keep God's commandments
and the faith of his son,
our lord?
I do.
Some people think that religion
began as a way
for primitive cultures
to explain
natural phenomenon--
the fire, the wind, the rain.
They created a God
for each one.
I baptize you,
my brother, in Christ.
You are baptized
with Christ in death.
You'd think science would
have made religion obsolete.
But it hasn't.
Go for a swim,
come out a new man.
If only I believed
it were that simple.
But Brother Sam believes,
and because of that,
he's fulfilled.
It's written all over his face.
That's my son, Harrison.
Can you say hi?
Guess not.
It's all right.
Did you see Nick?
He wanted to thank you
for coming by.
Yeah, he can thank me
tomorrow at the shop
when I bring my car in.
What?
You had another accident?
Bad driving karma.
Man, somebody trying to tell
you to slow down, brother.
So what'd you think?
Uh, it was...interesting.
Don't get me wrong.
The spiritual stuff,
the second chances,
I think it's great...
for Nick.
But not for you, huh?
[Sighs]
I get it.
You take a dunk in the bay,
you fix all your problems.
It probably sounds
like bullshit to you.
That's one word for it.
But, you know,
it's not about the dunk.
It's about...
surrender to something
greater than yourself.
I don't get it.
Well, man, just look around.
You think you make the sun
come up in the morning?
You think you can make
the tide come in?
No, but that's the earth
rotating on its axis,
the pull of the moon.
So you do believe
in something
greater than yourself.
[Groans]
[Laughs]
[Cell phone vibrates]
Got to go.
Work.
Okay.
Harrison, get the car.
Yeah, somebody got to do
the driving with him.
Go ahead.
[Siren wails]
[Horse whinnies]
Jesus Christ.
What's with the wicked rodeo?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Some sick fuck sewed
body parts to mannequins
and then
strapped 'em to horses.
I mean, what the fuck?
Body parts?
This spectacle
makes me think of...
Brian. My brother.
Your brother?
Rudy the Ice Truck Killer?
- Sorry.
- No, it's okay.
I was thinking it too.
Just the idea that someone
would put this much...
imagination.
Brutality into killing.
Come here.
I want to show you something.
Lieutenant.
Hold on a sec.
Check it out.
Lieutenant.
I'm in the middle of something.
Remember this?
[Horse whinnies]
Oh, it's the same insignia
that was carved
into the stomach
of the snakes victim.
Looks like a signature.
[Horse nickering]
Same sick fuck.
Two different killings.
Hey, uh, lieutenant?
For the love of God, what?
Right.
One at a time.
Go.
Been calling around
the local stables.
There's one about a mile
north from here,
reported four horses
missing two days ago.
Quinn?
Mounted patrol's on the way.
They'll be here
within the hour.
I've been counting the body
parts and typing the blood,
and it's all B-positive,
so I think we're looking
at one victim here.
Jesus. Somebody went
to a lot of trouble.
He's trying
to tell us something.
Yeah.
"I'm a crazy piece of shit."
He's saying
it's the end of the world.
Something like that.
Four horsemen
of the Apocalypse--
white, red, pale, and black.
Doesn't take a genius
to figure it out.
And who are you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is Mike Anderson
from Chicago.
He's my replacement.
Mike, this is...everyone.
You were saying?
The killer's showing us a scene
from the Book of Revelation.
A killer with faith?
Damn, it's hot out here.
Yeah.
It's Miami, genius.
What about snakes?
- What about 'em?
- Seven snakes.
Any mention of them
in the Book of Revelation?
Don't know.
I'll look into it.
Do that.
In the meantime, you two,
go to the stable.
See if a surveillance tape
will give us a suspect.
Dexter, Masuka,
take shots of the horses
so we can start
taking this shit apart.
Whoever did this seems to be
a member of my tribe.
But this is a horse
of a different color.
What is this?
Masuka confirmed
that the body parts
all belonged
to the same victim.
We got an I.D. off the fingerprints--
Nathan Roberts.
Went for a jog a couple
of days ago and never came back.
Did you compare the kill wound
against the snakes victim?
- I did.
- And?
It's a perfect match.
Same signature,
same kill wound.
Same killer.
The M.E.'s report
said there was residue
in the wound.
It's being processed.
We should have it back
at the lab later today.
Any ideas for a murder weapon?
Some kind of
stabbing implement.
Won't know for sure
until we get the M.E.'s
measurements for the wound.
What about the cuts
on the body?
Hmm.
I'm guessing a bone saw.
What do we have here?
1-2-4-2.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
- Some kind of message?
- Another one?
Jesus.
How much does
this fucker have to say?
A lot apparently.
Want to bet he left one
on the snakes victim too?
Nothing behind his eyes.
What about the mouth
or the ears?
Already checked.
Well, what are we missing?
We're not.
It's what he's missing.
His intestines.
Ugh.
Kind of reminds me of looking
for the prize in a cereal box.
You were always
good at that too.
Jackpot.
1237, 1242.
What do you think it means?
That I've been lieutenant
for less than a week
and there's already
some game-playing,
sick-as-fuck serial killer
for me to catch?
Technically,
he's not a serial killer.
Yet.
Serial killing
involves the murder
of several people in three
or more separate events.
So far our guy's only done two.
Are you trying to make me
feel better or worse?
[Cell phone rings]
Sorry.
It's Jamie.
Hey, everything okay?
Oh, Harrison
isn't feeling so great.
What happened?
I don't know.
[Harrison crying]
He didn't--
he didn't eat breakfast.
But, I mean,
he seems okay otherwise.
Just a little tired.
I don't know.
Maybe it's a tummy ache, or--
Should I cancel his play date?
Yeah, absolutely.
It's better to be safe
than sorry.
- Okay.
- If he gets any worse--
I'll call you.
I promise.
[Phone beeps]
You wanted to see me?
Yeah, this four horsemen case,
it's all over the news.
We need to address the press.
Already two steps ahead of you.
I called the conference
for this afternoon,
and I'm working on
the statement.
Well, Morgan's
gonna make the statement.
But she doesn't
have any experience.
I've led hundreds
of press conferences,
and, really,
under the circumstances--
Morgan is the new face
of this department, Maria.
- I'm still--
- The old face.
No, set it up
for tomorrow afternoon.
Fine.
[Phone ringing]
Why the fuck would I
lead a press conference?
Isn't that your thing?
Uh, usually, yes,
but I made a strategic decision
to put you in the spotlight.
You'll give the public
the impression
that the situation's
less critical.
Besides, dealing with the press
is your responsibility
as lieutenant.
I thought my responsibility
was catching the horse fucker
that's killing people.
You'll have to learn
to multitask.
And while you're at it,
you still haven't finished
your fit for duty therapy.
The shooting
was over two weeks ago.
How am I supposed to find time
to go to a therapist?
Figure it out.
You're a liability
until you get cleared.
Fucking nightmare.
You okay?
Obviously.
You'll be fine.
Just--
Hey, never mind.
Not my place.
What? Tell me.
You just might want to...
dress a little more...
professional.
Like a lieutenant.
I mean, you know, uh,
skirt suit, heels.
What's wrong
with the way I dress?
I mean, you kind of
look like you're--
What?
A detective?
No, like you're
going to a hoedown.
Where should I put
the medical examiner's report
for the four horsemen's case?
Uh, wherever.
Uh, you busy later?
Thought we could have
our second date.
Sure, I have roller derby
practice until 9:00,
but we can totally hang after.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're a--
you're a derby girl?
Got the bruises to prove it.
I think my head just exploded.
I have an idea.
Why don't we have
our second date right now?
What are you thinking?
Little make out session
in the women's bathroom?
I was thinking
some show and tell
in the evidence room?
Even better.
Not the dirty kind.
You know, showing me
the Ice Truck Killer stuff
was so cool.
I was just thinking maybe you
could show me the Trinity stuff
or the Bay Harbor Butcher
evidence.
I can't.
The FBI has all those files.
But, um, I promise
to make it up to you later.
You better.
Now open the M.E.'s report.
I'm dying to know what it says.
When Brian sent messages,
they were tailor-made for me.
But I should still be able
to crack this guy's code.
- All right.
- Ready?
Okay.
Let's do this.
Most of you have already met
detective Mike Anderson.
He's working on a theory
that our killer
is reenacting scenes
from the Book of Revelation.
There's a lot
of brutal imagery here,
and our killer had
a lot to choose from.
I just the M.E. report
from the four horsemen vic.
And guess what it says?
Must be pretty important
for you to bust in here
like this.
Uh, he's a little bit
of a drama queen.
There were traces of
oxidized iron in the kill wound.
Rust.
I mean, nobody's used
iron to make weapons
since the Middle Ages,
which means our killer could
have used a ancient artifact.
What kind of artifact?
I'm not sure yet.
But the dimensions of the wound
suggest a sword.
Um, but there are hundreds
of varieties of swords.
Great. Stay on that.
Mike, you were saying?
So far our killer
has given us three tableaus.
The intestines on the scale,
the snakes victim,
and the four horsemen.
I'm sorry.
Uh, tableaus?
It's a theatrical term
referring to a picturesque
grouping of people or objects.
Oh, all this time
I just thought
they were called crime scenes.
No, it's more
than just a crime scene.
Everything he's showing us
has meaning.
From the positioning
of the bodies
to the clothes
he puts on his victims,
nothing's by accident.
Exactly.
He's communicating with us.
Mike's just helping
with the translation.
The four horsemen
of the apocalypse
are described in Revelation 6,
Verses one through eight.
As for the seven snakes murder,
Revelation 13.
"And I stood upon
the sand of the sea
"and saw a serpent
rise out of the sea,
having seven heads."
And what about the intestines?
There's no passage
on intestines,
but the scales of justice
are all over the Bible.
I figure he's referencing
God's judgment of mankind.
What about the numbers
we found on the body?
1237 and 1242.
Don't know.
But I can get in touch
with a Revelation expert
who might be able
to tell us more.
They happened five days apart.
The two murders happened
five days apart.
The difference between
1237 and 1242 is five.
I don't know why
I didn't see it before.
So the numbers are days.
He's counting up to something.
- To what?
- Don't know.
But if all this
Revelation stuff
has to do with doomsday,
maybe it's to the end
of the world.
Okay.
So we're looking
for a religious nutbag.
Quinn, Batista,
round up any end-times fanatics
that might have
criminal records.
Let's find this...Doomsday killer.
It's happening, Travis.
Look around us.
People are afraid.
Soon you'll start
to understand what we're--
Travis...
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
They're afraid.
Okay, I got it.
She's pretty.
Who?
The waitress.
You've been staring at her.
But we really have
to stay focused.
So you don't think
I should ask her out?
Is that what you want?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I think she likes me.
Hey, Trav.
Can I get you anything else?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Thank you.
I thought religion
was supposed to be comforting.
But swarms of locusts,
bowls of wrath?
Why would anybody want
to believe this stuff?
Be honest.
Professional or stupid?
Professional.
Ha.
But you don't look
much like you.
[Chuckles]
You want to tell me how
I'm supposed to catch Doomsday
if I'm spending all my time
writing press statements,
going to
court-ordered therapy,
and shopping
for ugly-ass clothes?
You'll figure it out.
You always do.
Quinn used to say that
when I was in meltdown mode.
He saw you in meltdown mode
and he still wanted
to marry you?
- Poop explosion.
- Harrison?
If it's Jamie,
you've got bigger problems.
Keep an eye on him while
I'm down in the laundry room?
His tummy still upset?
Yeah, it's probably just a bug,
but I can take him
to the doctor tomorrow.
Whew.
Hey, what's the matter,
little man?
You don't feel so good?
[Whimpers]
Wish I could make it
all better.
I guess there are some things
even daddies can't fix.
So I gave you
the friends and family rate,
and I can have that
to you ASAP.
Thanks.
The sooner the better.
I just want to let you know
I'm taking off, all right?
All right.
Dex, what's up?
'Sup?
So you headed off to class?
Hey, Sam's sending me
to computer class.
Gonna build him
a bomb website, yo.
Yeah, you better.
All right.
Laters.
Be safe. Later.
See you, Nick.
You really take care
of these guys.
Yeah, well, you know,
God's taking care of all of us.
Here go your estimate.
Again.
Are these your notes?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Every time I read it,
I'm finding something new.
You ever read it?
Yeah, I just started.
For work.
We're tracking this killer.
We think he's reenacting scenes
from the Book of Revelation.
That four horsemen case
from the news, yeah?
Lord have mercy.
Saying it's in the name
of God--
the devil is busy.
You think he's using God
as an excuse to kill?
People use God as an excuse
for a lot of things.
Just because he believes
in some crazy bullshit,
that don't mean his faith
is any less real.
But if faith makes people
do such crazy bullshit,
what's the point of having it?
It's human nature.
Gotta believe in something.
Right?
I mean, haven't you ever
had a problem so big
that you just couldn't
handle it on your own?
Yeah.
Well, who helped you?
My dad.
Hmm.
Well, you're lucky.
You're blessed.
That's a blessing.
Faith, man, you put it
in the wrong things...
fuck you up.
[Sighs] Ugh.
Goddamn pantyhose.
Has anyone ever died
from crotch asphyxiation?
You have now crossed the line
into inappropriate
brother-sister exchanges.
[Elevator bell dings]
Is that lieutenant Morgan
in a skirt?
I don't know.
I don't recognize her
without the man boots.
You'll recognize my foot
when it's kicking you
in the face.
But the Mayan
calendar says--
The Mayans weren't Christians.
Look, God told Noah
that the great flood
would be in seven days.
Batista and Quinn's
people of interest.
Even if none of them
is Doomsday,
they're all totally insane.
At 9:45 yesterday morning,
four horses were released
at the intersection...
Lieutenant...you ready
for the press conference?
Yeah, I'm just...
practicing my statement.
You want some honest advice?
I guess.
Lose the speech.
Just relax.
Have a conversation.
You're not a formal person,
so a formal statement
could come off as insincere.
So you're saying
I should just...
be myself?
Exactly.
Nice shoes, by the way.
They look better on.
Yeah, well, they hurt my feet.
You know what else
you could use?
Nice.
See you later.
Brother Sam reads
his Bible like I read blood,
and every time he comes away
with something new.
Maybe if I want answers
about this killer,
his work deserves
a second look.
Such aggressive, brutal cuts.
He butchered this body.
But that doesn't
make any sense.
Not when he was so meticulous
about composing
his crime scenes.
The complexity of the stitching
in the belly
of that fruit vendor,
the attention to detail,
attaching plastic to flesh.
So why would this same
fastidious craftsman
so carelessly hack and slash?
Unless it's not
the same killer.
You think one person
cut up the body
and another composed
the crime scene?
Maybe we're not looking
for one Doomsday killer.
Maybe we're looking for two.
[Phone rings]
This is Vince Masuka.
Hey, I've been bounced around
to, like, five people,
so I'm hoping
you could help me.
I can try.
What you need?
Uh, I'm a collector,
and there's a prosthetic hand
for auction
on buythistreasure.com.
Says it's from the
Ice Truck Killer investigation.
Is that real?
What? No.
Hang on a sec.
No, that's--
it's gotta be fake.
The only people with access
to our evidence room
are police employees and...
interns.
Fuck me.
So I shouldn't bid on it, or...
No.
Definitely not.
Ryan.
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
What's wrong?
[Pop music
playing in headphones]
You stole the hand from
the Ice Truck Killer evidence
and sold it online?
You said it was just
going to sit there.
The chain of custody is sacred.
I mean,
did you ever stop to think
what would happen
if we ever needed to go back?
I'm sorry.
I was short on rent,
and I needed the money.
Are you crazy?
I mean, I--I could lose
my job over this.
No one has to know.
Just...
Let me make it up to you.
I'm such an idiot.
For thinking you
were actually into me.
I was.
I am.
Get out.
We're done.
And we're live in three...
two...one.
My detectives are interviewing
several suspects,
but, uh,
we won't release a name
until a suspect
is officially charged.
Is it true
the four horsemen case
is connected to the murder
of the fruit vendor Omar Rivera?
We're not here to discuss
the Rivera case.
But the same
Alpha and Omega signature
was found at both crime scenes.
Isn't that right?
Come on, Deb.
Don't go into
meltdown mode now.
Actually, yes, we believe
that's our killer's signature.
So if you see something,
say something.
Call the department
with any information
that might help us
catch this killer.
We're all in this together.
I'm not gonna lie to you
about this investigation,
because I don't really
see the point.
I'm not into politics,
and I don't care about
press conferences or--
or public opinion.
All I care about is catching
the fucker that did this.
[Camera shutters snapping]
Shit.
That'll be all.
Lieutenant Morgan,
another question.
Is it me, or does our captain
look happy our lieutenant
just shit the bed?
It's not you.
Trust me.
I used to be married to her.
Hey, uh, we got one more
nut-job to interview.
This preacher, Jeremiah Allen.
So we got to make a house call.
All right. Let's go.
Please tell me
it wasn't that bad.
It was pretty bad.
Is that Laguerta's necklace?
I seriously hate you right now.
[Cell phone rings]
Deb, hold on a sec.
Hello?
[Ominous music]
I'll be right there.
Your son's temperature's 104.
We need to get him
into surgery ASAP.
His appendix is ruptured.
And what happens now?
We'll do our best
to make sure he's okay.
[Harrison crying]
Need you to sign
that parental consent.
He's gonna be okay, right?
We'll do everything we can.
[Crying continues]
Hey, buddy,
daddy's gonna wait right here
till the doctors
take good care of you, okay?
[Cell phone rings]
Hello.
Hey, it's, uh,
Sam from Good Shepherd.
Uh, your car's ready.
You said you needed it asap,
so it's here.
Yeah, can I
pick it up tomorrow?
I'm at St. Peter's
with my son.
Oh, is everything okay?
He just went into surgery.
Do you need me
to bring it to you, 'cause I--
I got to go.
[Phone beeps]
All available nurses
to pediatric O.R. 308.
You gave us the wrong address.
It was a sandwich shop.
The preacher, Jeremiah Allen.
He's unlisted.
Fine.
Call me back.
Should have taken my car.
Got the GPS.
Just finish up your frita
so we can head back
to the station.
We'd already be on the way
if you let me eat in the car.
No way.
You're not
getting grease on Norma.
What?
It was my mother's name.
Now I think I know
why you're divorced.
Fuckin' waste of an afternoon.
You got a little, like,
like, cilantro
or something in the--
What?
Is this yours?
No.
It belonged to the kid
that sold me the car.
I mean, the weed,
the Trans-Am.
I mean, if you're having
a mid-life crisis,
we can talk about it.
I'm not having
a mid-life crisis.
What's wrong with this car?
I think it's cool.
Yeah, it's...
What are you doing?
I'm making lemonade.
Put that shit away.
We're cops.
We're on-duty cops.
So what?
It's not like we're gonna
hear back from dispatch
today anyway.
I haven't smoked that shit
since I was 16.
Exactly, grandpa.
Don't you want to be cool?
Give me that.
[Eric Burdon and War's
Spill the Wine]
♪ ♪
[Coughs]
♪ I could feel
hot flames of fire ♪
♪ roaring at my back ♪
Dude, quit staring at me.
You're freaking me out.
It's sad.
I can feel how much
your heart hurts for Deb.
Oh, dude.
Get your big,
fuckin' sausage hands off me.
That's terrible.
[Cell phone rings]
Batista.
Got it.
Thanks.
[Phone beeps]
That was, uh, dispatch.
We got Jeremiah Allen's address.
Jeremiah who?
The guy. The dude.
The, um--
the preacher.
Right. Awesome.
Where's my hat?
♪ Spill the wine ♪
♪ dig that girl ♪
Did you know that children
who undergo anesthesia
under the age of three
are more likely to develop
learning disabilities?
Are you doing research?
And once the appendix bursts,
the complication rate
rises to 59%.
Maybe you should
get off the Internet.
You think we should
call Astor and Cody,
let them know
Harrison's in surgery?
No, not yet.
I don't want to worry them.
Uh, Deb, is that you on TV?
...Politics or public opinion.
All I care about is catching
the [bleep] that did this.
Oh, fuck.
[Sighs]
Sorry.
Dexter?
Sam, what are you doing here?
I figured if I had a son
who was going through surgery,
I'd probably want
some backup too, so.
Thanks.
Brother Sam?
You came in
on the Omar Rivera case.
Are you guys, like,
friends now?
Uh.
Yeah, well,
I have the auto shop.
We--yep.
I'm gonna go to the cafeteria,
see if anything's edible.
Any takers?
I'll browse.
How you holding up?
Honestly, not good.
I hate not knowing
if he's gonna be okay,
not being able to protect him.
Sometimes you just...
got to surrender.
I'm sorry, man.
That--that probably
wasn't the...
- It's okay.
- Best thing to say.
No, it's...
If I was in your situation,
I would not want
to hear that shit.
I'm--
I used to not always
be like this.
People used to talk to me
about God.
Man, used to make me
want to punch 'em in they face.
- Really?
- Yeah, yeah.
[Sighs]
I used to believe
in something else.
What?
The same as you.
My dad.
Whatever.
That--that didn't work out.
What happened?
[Exhales]
Hey, you got enough
on your mind, man.
You don't need to--
want to hear no stories
about me and my dad.
No, I appreciate a distraction.
When I was growing up,
my dad was a real popular guy.
Everybody knew him.
They used to
call him "mister."
He was always working,
but I never really knew
what he did.
So one day I asked him.
I said,
"Daddy, what do you do?"
He looked at me and said,
"Whatever I want,
whenever I need."
Like that.
Hmm.
He said he was going to...
see a friend of his.
So we get there.
He says, uh,
"Now go on up there
and ring that doorbell for me."
So I do it.
And this man comes to the door.
And he's staring at me,
not knowing who I am
or why I'm there.
And before I can turn around
and say I'm with mister,
my dad is standing
right there behind me
with a pistol in his hand.
And he takes his pistol
and he points it at this man,
and he shoots him in the face.
Killed him.
Blood everywhere.
[Sighs]
All on my Superman shirt.
My dad just calmly picks me up,
walks to the car,
drives off slowly.
And he says,
"You did a good job."
He used you.
No surprise
I ended up in prison.
So what changed?
[Sighs]
Well,
when I first got locked up,
them first few months,
I was just...
mad.
And I just wanted
to hurt somebody, anybody.
And this new guy comes in.
And he's just loud
and bragging,
and, "Yeah, yeah,
this, this, that."
I was this, this,
that in the street."
And so I'm just looking at him.
I'm thinking to myself,
"Okay, when I get a chance,
I'ma tune
this motherfucker up."
So we get yard time,
and I'm following him.
And he goes into the chapel.
I sneak up on him,
and I start choking him out.
I'm trying to kill him.
And then I see this light.
Like, figuratively, or--
No, no, like, for real.
Like, light.
Sunlight coming through
these chapel windows, and...
I could just see
everything around me.
I could see where I was at
and what I was doing, and...
I didn't want to do it no more.
And you think that was God?
Dexter, all I know
is that when I let
that man go...
I never felt that good
about nothing in my life.
[Breathes deeply]
I'm gonna grab some coffee.
Yeah.
[Machine whirring, struggling]
Come on.
Just let him be okay.
Please let him be okay.
I don't know how this works,
but if there's something
I need to do in return,
I'll do it.
Okay?
You going out
with that woman, aren't you?
Her name is Erin.
If you like, I could cancel.
I could stay here with you.
There's more work I could do.
No, we were given free will
for a reason, Travis.
You can do whatever you want...
as long as you're willing to...
accept the consequences
God gives you.
It's just dinner.
I'll be back home by 10:00.
Good night.
And your parents,
are you close?
Yes, we were.
They died when I was 14.
Car wreck.
I am so sorry.
That's terrible.
My sister pretty much
raised me after that.
Poor thing.
You guys are really lucky
that you had each other.
I want you, Travis.
Travis.
[Moaning softly]
[Door opens]
Kid's a champ.
Made it through
with flying colors.
Oh, thank God.
I mean, uh, thank you.
Thank you so much, doctor.
My pleasure.
Uh, they're taking him up
to recovery now.
You can see him
in a few minutes.
I knew he'd be okay.
I got to go.
Matthews wants to talk to me.
Probably about the conference.
I'm totally fucked.
Long day.
You should go home.
Are you sure?
I can hang.
No, go. I'll call you
if anything changes.
Okay.
Good night.
Night.
Thanks for staying.
You didn't have to.
Not a problem.
I wanted to.
I'm glad little man
is all right.
Yeah, me too.
I know.
"Thank God."
That's just an expression.
I know.
Just, uh...
Another marvel
of modern science.
Yeah,
you put your faith in God,
I put my faith in science.
It's cool.
We don't have to believe
in the same thing, but...
you got to keep an open mind.
You may say I can't prove
that God exists,
but, uh...
You can't prove he doesn't.
Hmm?
You take care, Dex.
[Knocks]
Deputy chief?
Morgan.
Did you see the news?
I been getting calls
about it all night.
I did, sir. Let me just say
that I am truly, deeply--
Everybody loves my new
sparkplug of a lieutenant.
They do?
You're direct.
No bullshit.
Well, I was just trying
to get the community--
You know, I took a big risk
when I promoted you, Morgan.
I took a lot of crap
from a lot of people.
But today--
today, you've made me
very, very proud.
Your dad would
have been proud too.
Keep up the good fucking work.
Thank you, sir.
Hey.
Which one of you characters
drives a Firebird?
Crockett or tubbs?
You park like a dick.
[Laughter]
You guys want
to go in my office,
tell me what you've been up to?
Well, we'll be right in.
I've been meaning to thank you
for that fashion advice.
Really upped
my professional factor.
Jesus, Anderson.
You have something to say,
say it?
With all due respect,
lieutenant,
you should probably
watch the language.
Well, for your information,
Matthews said people liked it.
[Clears throat]
We have a lead.
We been speaking to this
preacher, Jeremiah Allen.
Turns out he's obsessed
with this Revelation expert,
James Gellar.
The professor.
From the University of Tallahassee?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
Found this on a Google search
for "revelation expert."
It's all about end times.
Yeah.
Check this out.
The posts end on the day
of our very first crime scene.
I can try and get
in touch with him, but--
You--you can't
get in touch with him,
because he went underground.
Underground.
Why?
Ah, now look
who's behind the curtain.
I, uh, called the university.
Gellar disappeared three years
ago after he got fired.
- Ask me why.
- Why?
He got accused of stealing
an ancient sword.
Like the one Masuka
thinks our killer
could have used
in both murders?
Just like that.
Oh, and get this.
This isn't just
any Roman sword.
According to medieval legend,
this one belonged
to John the Revelator.
The guy who actually
wrote Revelation.
Huh?
Looks like we just found our
number one person of interest.
Good job.
Thank you.
[Seagulls calling]
[Muffled whimper]
You knew this was gonna happen.
No. Please.
Let her go.
I like her.
You should have
thought about that
before you defiled her.
It's the best thing for her.
She's part of God's plan now.
Looks like your prayers
were answered.
I was desperate.
Hey, no judgment.
You already talk
to an imaginary father figure.
It didn't mean anything.
Are you sure?
Harrison's okay,
and you did make that pact.
Come on.
You don't really think
there's someone out there
holding my I.O.U.
I don't know.
But if there is,
you'd better be ready
to pay the piper.
[Sighs]
[Cell phone ringing]
[Phone beeps] Hey.
Hey.
How's Harrison?
He's fine.
He's sleeping.
Are you sure? 'Cause I
wouldn't want to bother you--
Deb, just tell me what's up.
Got a call to a crime scene
in Coral Gables.
A gardner
at the botanical gardens
found an Alpha and an Omega
outside the greenhouse.
You think it's Doomsday?
Could be.
And we might have a suspect.
A middle-aged professor.
I'm not sure if I should leave.
Dexter. Sorry.
I didn't mean
to eavesdrop or anything,
but if that's work,
you should go.
- But Harrison--
- Harrison is sound asleep.
Between the pain killers
and the sedatives they gave him,
you can probably get there and
back before he even wakes up.
Dex, at the risk of sounding
like the world's worst aunt,
I could really use you on this.
There's blood.
I'll be there.
[Phone beeps]
Call me the minute he wakes up.
I will.
I was drawn to science
out of curiosity.
Any questions I had,
the answers were already there.
But even science
is never certain.
Even the soundest of theories
is subject to new data.
And there are some things
even science can't explain.
Brother Sam would say
it's not an accident
that I've stumbled
onto a killer
who seems to have
his own kind of faith.
And while I don't believe
in an unseen hand
creating his own tableau,
I do believe
I don't have all the answers.
Dex, thanks for coming.
What do we got?
Blood.
And fuckin' fish.
Catch of the day.
It didn't get here on its own.
So where did it come from?
Dex, where are you going?
Over here.
Check this out.
Handle.
[Dramatic note]
Holy shit.
In here!
[Muffled screams]
Mm-mm! Mm-mm!
No!
[Muffled scream]
Deb, wait!
Could be another trap.
Oh, God.
We have to help her.
Her jugular's punctured.
She's already gone.
Oh, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit.
Kill number three.
It's official.
He's a serial killer.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
everybody.
Listen.
[Distant screeching]
What the hell is that?
It's coming from over here.
[Speaking Spanish]
Locusts.
I'm not looking at Debra's
middle-aged professor.
Is this Doomsday number two?
But that's not the look
of a murderer.
That's the look of a man
with true faith.
I've seen it before
on Brother Sam.
Whatever this guy believes,
he knows it to be true.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com