Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
Is this doomsday number two?
Travis Marshall.
Press reporter. You wouldn't
happen to know of any good spots...
...where we could get a
drink this evening, would you?
Maybe I do.
These drawings...
...they were Gellar's?
No!
Seems Brother Sam's not
a changed man after all.
Please get off the property.
Not without our boy Nick.
You deaf?
See how easy it is?
Get out and start walking away.
One way or another,
Travis will lead me...
...to the one who
really deserves my table.
Most people believe
we have free will...
...that we all choose our path.
Sometimes the path is clear...
...sometimes not so much.
Every twist, every turn...
...can challenge our
sense of direction.
But it's the choices we make when
we reach a fork in the road...
...that defines who we are.
Deb, I'm kind of busy. Can...?
Dex, I'm sorry, I have bad news.
It's Brother Sam. He's been shot...
- ...at his garage.
- What?
EMTs are working on him now.
I'm on my way there.
I'll meet you there.
No, wait...
Shit.
I think this will be
sufficiently tawdry...
...for our purposes.
Pay the woman.
Ma'am.
We're almost ready.
About the woman...
She didn't die, did she?
No, but her arm is badly broken.
I'd like to get her
some painkillers.
No, Travis.
But she's in agony.
She's a whore.
She's an unrepentant sinner.
She deserves what she's gonna get.
Have you given her her mark?
No, not yet.
What's wrong with you, Travis?
What do you mean?
You're hesitating.
You're slacking off.
You better get yourself together.
You know what's at stake here.
We're the chosen ones.
We're the two witnesses.
But what if it's wrong?
What we're doing,
hurting these people...
God can be wrong?
I don't think so.
Do what you're told to do, Travis...
...or you're gonna be destroyed
along with the rest of the scum.
It's bad. There are
three entrance wounds...
...two in the chest,
one in the back.
No exit wounds.
Bullets bounced around,
really tore him up.
Whoever did this to Brother Sam...
...doesn't deserve to live.
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
My job.
I'm sorry, Dex, I
can't let you do that.
You and Sam are friends.
Deb, I'm fine.
Really.
The last thing you need
is another unsolved case...
...you need my help.
I need to do this.
Hey, hey!
Somebody get this dog out of here.
I got him.
What do we have?
Register's clean.
Looks like a robbery gone bad.
Or Julio's gang finally
got even with Brother Sam...
...for stealing Nick away.
I suppose it's too much to hope...
It is.
DVD's missing.
Whatever happened
to stupid criminals?
They're still stupid.
We'll catch this piece of shit.
The likely shooter is
Julio's replacement.
Taking out Brother Sam
would be a good way...
...to boost his cred as shot caller.
See, Louis, the art of dusting...
...lies in the caressing of
the powder over the print...
...so as not to corrupt it...
...as if one was trying
to... get a nipple erect.
Like this.
What's the blood telling you?
The spray pattern suggests
the shooter stood here.
Bang, bang.
Victim stumbled to the car...
...and fell here.
Frothy blood suggests
a tracheal hemorrhage...
...and the victim
fell to his knees...
...but the drainage from
the interior wounds...
...is pooled, not smeared...
...so he must have
rolled to his side...
...and the shooter steps
forward for the kill shot.
Bang.
Victim rolls to his back.
That's how we found him.
The awkward position of the
body causes the bullet...
...to miss the heart.
It's probably the only
reason he's still alive.
Guy's a fucking rock star.
Hey, this is Miami fucking metro.
We're all fuckin' rock stars.
Harrison seemed a
little off this morning.
It's all right if I
check in with Jamie?
Sure.
The night Julio and his
crew came for nick...
I hit one of them
with a baseball bat.
He seemed like Julio's number two...
...which could mean
he's now number one.
Blood.
If he's in the system,
I'll have a name.
We have a match.
Leo Hernandez.
Two felony arrests...
...as well as one for
failure to pay child support.
What are the odds you're
at your last known address?
Hello?
Yes, hello, I'm calling
for Leo Hernandez?
Who is this?
The department of social services.
Ah, Lieutenant, I ran the
prints from the garage.
I got 12 hits on afis.
All of them work for Brother Sam.
Well, that really
fucking narrows it down.
Maybe one of his ex-cons got
tired of working for a living.
Yale, Soderquist, I want
statements and alibis...
...from everyone on
the garage payroll.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
He sounds like a
horrible baby-daddy.
You and your children
deserve better.
She hasn't seen Leo in over a year.
Now what?
So I couldn't find his broke ass.
Any news on Brother Sam's condition?
Last I heard, he
was still in surgery.
Hey, I got something.
Eighth street locos
blame Brother Sam...
...for the disappearance of
their shot caller, Julio Benes.
I killed Julio.
Is it possible this is my fault?
And according to this
report filed two days ago...
Brother Sam suspected the
locos of shooting up his garage.
So maybe his motive was
revenge and not robbery.
Or revenge and robbery.
Hit the street. See if
you can't narrow it down...
...to a triggerman.
Got it.
Deb, if it's okay...
I'm gonna swing by the hospital
and check in on Brother Sam.
Sure.
Hey, what's up?
Just... getting some rocket fuel...
...keep the engines burning.
Me too.
Better get back to it.
Relax, I didn't come over
here to crack the whip.
I've just been going
so hard lately...
I haven't had a chance to catch up.
What's going on?
I'm good.
Me too.
Can we... get back to work now?
Yeah, fucking go.
I'm taking a lot
of heat on doomsday.
The commissioner,
the mayor's office...
...the media are all over me.
Are we making any headway?
Quinn and Batista are
going through our suspect...
...Professor Gellar's boxes.
I was about to get an update.
Good, do that.
And remember, you're Lieutenant
now, not one of the gang.
I'm realizing that.
Okay, well, I'd like
a briefing later today.
Okay.
If you're lying there because
of my dark passenger...
...I promise you, my dark
passenger will make amends.
The lord is my light
and my salvation.
Hey, Nick, how are you?
Whom should I fear?
The lord is my life's refuge.
Been trying to do good.
How could this
happen to Brother Sam?
It's a hard question to answer.
I'd rather focus on who did it.
One thing I ask of the lord.
This I seek...
Is Leo Hernandez the new
shot caller for the locos?
You here as a friend or a cop?
I'm not a cop.
I'm a forensic analyst...
...and a friend.
And you and I both know the
locos wanted Brother Sam dead.
Where can I find him?
I ain't no rat.
If Leo shot Brother Sam, he
doesn't deserve your loyalty.
Come on, Nick, if
you don't tell me...
...the cops are gonna
drag it out of you.
I'll keep your name
out of it, they won't.
He stays over on St. Andrew's.
The white house near romaine.
Brothers and sisters,
let us pray together...
...for our friend Brother Sam.
Please join hands.
Please hear our prayer, lord...
...as we gather in your name.
Lord, we ask you to
heal our Brother Sam...
...and bring him back to us...
...because we need him.
He's your shining light among us.
He helps us see the way. Amen.
Amen.
And now in the name
of forgiveness...
...let us say a silent prayer...
...for the misguided
sinner who shot Brother Sam.
Anger won't bring him back.
I'd rather prey on him.
Here's where we are.
Professor Gellar's former
T.A., Carissa Porter...
The one you got the boxes from.
Right. She told us that Gellar
was working on a theory...
...about an early A.D. cult,
the Enesserrette, who believed...
...that the book of revelations
was not only a biblical prophecy...
...but some kind of code to
bring about the end of the world.
I have no idea what that means.
According to Gellar's papers...
...he thought he had
deciphered the code.
Seven steps or keys, each
requiring a human sacrifice.
We think that the
doomsday tableaus...
...are an enactment of these keys.
Jesus.
I thought this crazy fuck
was trying to warn us...
...about the end of the world.
You're telling me he's
trying to cause it?
There's more.
We found a clipping from
a college newspaper...
...from a little over
three years ago...
...and it says that Gellar did an
artistic installation on campus...
...drawing attention to his
work on the Enesserrette cult.
It got him in hot water
with the university.
The dead lamb
represents sacrifice...
...the naked chick represents
sinfulness, blah blah blah.
It looks like a practice
run for his current work.
If we could find that
girl in the photo...
...who knows what she could tell us?
Is that marking on her lower
back part of the tableau?
Not sure. We just found
this before you walked in.
We haven't had a chance
to go over it in detail.
You got a magnifying glass?
Yeah.
Hm, looks like a tattoo.
One of those Hindu "Om" Dealios.
Wrong religion, sweetie.
Good find, Deb. Um...
...we'll, uh, take it from here.
Oh, I can help if you want.
No, no, no.
Um, you've got a lot
on your plate, so...
It's okay, Deb, we got this.
We'll get back to you.
What?
The chick in the photo
is Carissa Porter.
What? Are you sure?
The tat above her ass?
I was in the vicinity.
Shit.
She just became our key witness.
I told you not to go home
with her. Didn't I tell you?
Yes, you told me, mom.
The question is, what are
we gonna do about it now?
Well, we gotta find out what
else Carissa Porter knows.
That... that's fine.
But we can't let Deb
know about this...
'cause that could make
things a lot harder for me.
Lie to Deb? No way.
Oh, so you're just gonna turn
your back on your partner?
Oh, no, no. Do not
play the partner card.
Of course I'm gonna
Why wouldn't I play
the partner card?
Situations like this are
exactly why the partner card...
...is in the fucking deck!
I'm really not liking you right now.
Deb, you got a sec?
What's up?
Quinn and I have to go
to Tallahassee tomorrow...
...to question Carissa Porter.
I thought you already
interviewed her.
We did. We have reason to believe...
...that she's the naked
woman in the newspaper photo.
No shit, how'd you figure that out?
Uh... just meticulous police work.
Fuckin' A.
She's gotta be able to help
us get closer to Gellar.
But I can't spare you
guys for a whole day.
Have her come here.
What?
Bring her into the station.
Oh. Um...
I don't know if she's
gonna go for that.
She's a Professor.
She's got classes to teach.
Fuck her classes.
She's a material witness in
a serial murder investigation.
Tell her to get her
Om-tattooed ass...
...into this station
by tomorrow afternoon...
...or I'll have her hauled
in here in handcuffs.
Try it nicely first.
Fuck.
What if Carissa says something
about our night together?
I'll handle it.
You just stay the
hell away from her.
Hi, Jamie.
Hi.
Harrison go down easy?
Totally.
We went to the park this afternoon.
So it was like one page
of goodnight, moon...
...and then the sandman
dropped the whole bag on him.
You know, you don't have to do that.
Deb said she'd be by this weekend...
...to get the rest of her stuff.
Oh, no, I'm happy to do it.
There we go...
...all folded and packed
with very little hostility.
Guess I'll hit the road.
I heard about your
friend, Brother Sam.
How's he doing?
He's, uh... in a coma.
Doesn't look good.
I'm really sorry.
He seemed like a really nice guy.
Yeah, I didn't know
him... that well.
It definitely sucks.
Well, I'll... see
you in the morning.
Good night. Thanks.
Why is it so hard
for you to admit...
...you care about Brother Sam?
It doesn't make sense.
Who is he to me?
A fellow traveler.
He was a killer at one time.
But he found a new path,
a path I could never take.
It's because he's
traveled both roads...
...that he understands
the darkness in you...
...and he sees the light.
I wish I did.
Maybe things could
have been different.
"What if's" are a waste of time.
I've accepted my dark passenger.
But there's more to you than that.
Brother Sam sees it...
...and he's helped you see it.
That's what he is to you.
So is there anything else
you want to talk about?
Nope.
You sure?
Yep.
Okay.
Well, as far as the shooting at
Don Aldo's, you're good to go.
There's no need for
us to meet again.
There's one more thing.
Yes?
I feel like my whole world
has been turned upside down.
That's kind of more
than an afterthought.
Go on.
For the first time, I feel lost...
...in a place that's
always felt like home.
I look at my co-workers and I
see the doubt in their eyes...
...and it makes me doubt myself.
I mean, they used to be my friends.
Now they're my subordinates.
It used to be simple.
I feel like shit about Quinn.
I think he thinks that...
...I dumped him because I
think I'm better than him now.
And I used to be able
to talk to Batista...
...but that's awkward because
I made Lieutenant over him.
I still have Dexter.
We've always been close,
since we were kids.
But that's different too, because...
...it's weird to be
my big brother's boss.
I just don't know how to
act around anyone anymore.
So don't.
What?
Don't act.
Just be Debra.
You're too much in your head...
...you're... you're
thinking too much.
Just do the job, live your life...
...and give it all a
chance to sort itself out.
I don't know if I know
how to do that anymore.
What would you be doing right now...
...if you hadn't
gotten this promotion?
If I wasn't Lieutenant?
If I didn't have
briefings and reports...
...and meetings
coming out of my ass?
Yeah.
I would probably throw
a housewarming party...
...at my new beach house.
Well, that sounds
like a lot more fun...
...than worrying about
all this other stuff.
For a shrink, you're
not that annoying.
Thanks.
Not that you'd ever
need a shrink, but...
...you might need a bookmark.
I would guess it's obvious that
people who party all night...
...also don't get up in the morning.
But I'm finding it
very inconvenient.
Come on, Leo. Wake up.
Cops, man.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck you, man...
Hey, behave.
That's my little gentleman.
Now I know the Locos are the
supplier for this neighborhood.
And I'm guessing that you,
being a savvy consumer...
...have kept abreast on who's
running their operation now.
I don't know shit.
I just don't believe you.
I'm afraid you leave me no
choice but to flamingo your ass.
Ass... what?
It's a Chicago thing.
It's ironic.
Because we don't actually
have flamingos in Chicago.
You actually have
them here in Miami...
...and yet you don't
flamingo people.
I'll catch you later.
Wait!
Yeah.
The new locos shot
caller is Leo Hernandez.
Drives a black muscle car...
...similar to the vehicle
I.D.'d at the garage drive-by.
Operates out of a house...
...at the intersection of
St. Andrew's and romaine.
I'll send backup.
About time, Leo.
Police officer!
Hold it right there.
- He's coming out!
- Hands up.
Gun! Gun!
He's down. Hold your fire.
Get in to secure the weapon!
- Clear!
- Moving in!
Is this the locos' shot caller?
Yeah, recently retired.
Hey, Dexter, can I watch
you do the blood work?
Louis, we're learning fingerprints.
You're not ready for blood.
Come on.
Leo, you're not going
in my slide box...
...but justice has been done.
So why doesn't it feel better?
Think you got the right guy?
In the sense that he was
trying to blow my head off?
Definitely.
As to Brother Sam,
I'll know when I find...
...the 9 millimeter that
put the holes in him.
DVD player's on.
Security disc.
From the garage.
Okay.
It's not a slam dunk.
That looks like Leo.
He had on the same
sweatshirt when he was shot...
...he had the disc
in his possession...
...and Yale has two witnesses
who say Leo was bragging...
...he was gonna "smoke
that Brother Sam".
Sounds like it should hold.
Good work, Mike, everyone.
Oh, um, if you haven't heard...
...there's a party
at my place tonight.
B.Y.O.B. Not because I'm cheap.
It's just 'cause I don't
have time to buy booze.
This doesn't make
up for Brother Sam...
...but at least we got the bad guy.
Yeah.
Something's not right.
Eli isn't barking.
If Leo were the man in the hood,
the dog would be going crazy.
The only person other
than Brother Sam...
...Eli doesn't bark at... is Nick.
I'm sorry, but the Professor
said no painkillers.
Please just let me go.
I can't do that.
I have a son.
A little boy. He needs his mother.
Please.
I can tell you're a good person.
Please, help me.
Oh, well, look who's here!
Hey, Lisa.
Class, this is my brother Travis.
Can you say hello?
Hi.
This is such a surprise.
I mean, I mean, I'm... I'm thrilled.
But you've... you've never
visited me at school before.
Just needed to see you.
That's music to my ears.
You wanna paint with us?
Oh, no. I have to get going.
Come on. Class!
Travis is a very talented artist.
Don't you think he should join us?
Yeah!
Okay, okay, just a little bit.
Yay!
So what are we painting?
We're painting what we're
gonna be when we grow up.
I'm gonna be a nurse like my mom.
That's a great thing to be.
What about you?
I'm gonna be a transformer.
Oh, scary.
Don't you envy them?
So full of dreams.
And all the time in the
world to make them come true.
The night Brother Sam carried
Nick from his apartment...
Nick fired a shot at him.
From the couch, I'm
guessing, since he was stoned.
So the bullet should be...
...here.
9 millimeter.
Did it come from the same
gun that shot Brother Sam?
The striations match the
bullet taken from Brother Sam.
Nick shot Sam, the man
who tried to save him.
He's the ultimate Judas.
Thank you for coming down...
...on such short
notice, Professor Porter.
You didn't give me much choice.
I hope you understand that...
...we're trying to solve
a series of brutal murders.
Your cooperation is very important.
I don't see how.
I already told you
everything I know...
...and I gave you Gellar's boxes.
Professor Porter, are you
the woman in that photo?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell us about this?
Tell you the truth,
I'd forgotten about it.
Ma'am, you are lying naked
in the middle of campus...
...with a dead sheep on your head.
That's not the kind of thing
that just slips your mind.
Look, if that photo got out...
I would look like a total
flake to my... the faculty.
Quinn.
Why aren't you in
there with your witness?
I had, uh, paperwork backing
up, so Angel took this one.
Paperwork?
She's a material witness in
the fucking doomsday murders.
Come on, get in there.
Professor Porter,
did you... do you...
...share any of Professor
Gellar's religious beliefs?
I didn't know he had
any religious beliefs.
He was an academic.
Professor Porter.
Detective?
So that would be a no.
You're not a believer in
apocalyptic prophecies.
Of course not. Look...
I was just a prop. I was young.
I was trying to win
favor with my Professor.
Well, kind of an unorthodox
way to go about it.
He was an unorthodox man.
Has Gellar contacted you?
No. I told you.
I haven't seen or talked
to him in over three years.
Well, you didn't tell
us about the photo...
...so you can see how we
might be a little skeptical.
What the hell is going on here?
You think because I
posed for a photo once...
...that I'm somehow
involved in all of this?
No one said anything
about you being involved.
But you're acting like
I'm guilty of something.
Not at all, miss Porter.
We're just trying to
ascertain the full nature...
...of your relationship
with Professor Gellar.
I told you the full
nature of the relationship.
I was his T.A...
...and for a brief time, we
were lovers, but that's over.
Are you sure about that?
Jesus.
If we were still involved...
...would I have slept
with Mr. warmth over here?
Or are you implying
that I'm a whore...
...as well as an
accomplice to murder?
Professor Porter, can we
just stay on the subject here?
No. I've had enough of this.
I'm leaving now.
If you bother me again,
I'll get a lawyer.
Good-bye, Joey.
Leave us.
Are you out of your mind?
You fucked a person of interest?
Who fucks a person of non-interest?
This is no time to be a smart ass.
I could have you fired.
That woman was the key...
...to interpreting all
of the Gellar evidence.
She's never gonna fucking
cooperate with us now.
Is that really what's bothering you?
What? What...? What the fuck else?
Maybe you're jealous.
Are you kidding?
I could give a fuck who you fuck.
Just don't fuck with my
investigation, you fuck.
Well, I guess we're off.
You sure Deb invited me?
I really do not want to
crash a party with your son.
Yes, I'm sure, have fun.
I'll be there later, after
I take care of my business.
Mwah!
Sending Nick in pieces
to the bottom of the bay.
You wanna go to a party? Yay!
Hello?
Of course, right away.
Thank you for coming.
It was really important
to Sam that he talk to you.
This is good news, right?
That he's regained consciousness?
Probably not.
Doctor says sometimes people
come out of comas before...
...he doesn't have long.
Sam.
I'm here.
Don't worry.
I know it was Nick who shot you.
I'm gonna make sure he pays.
No.
Don't do that.
I don't understand.
I want you to...
...to give Nick a message for me.
Yes.
Tell him that I forgive him.
What?
You're the only one
that I trust to do it.
I didn't tell anybody.
The boys from the shop...
...they wouldn't...
...they... they're not ready.
You're wrong, I can't do this.
You can.
You don't know me.
Yes, I do.
I know about your darkness.
I also see your light.
If there's light in
me, I don't feel it.
I just wanna hurt Nick.
You don't know how
much I wanna hurt him.
You need to forgive him.
I don't know how.
Just let it go.
Can't live with the
hate in your heart.
Eat you up inside.
We gotta find some peace in life.
Nick doesn't deserve it.
It ain't about him.
Dexter, if you don't
let that darkness go...
...it won't let go of you.
Let it go.
For you.
You can just put it
on the poker table.
No, this... this
is a special bottle.
It's a housewarming/apology gift.
I should have told you about
Quinn and Carissa Porter.
Yeah, you should've.
I hope it doesn't
hurt us for doomsday.
Me too.
Why can't you trust me, Angel?
I do trust you. Of course I do.
It's just that...
Quinn's my partner...
...and you're the boss.
I guess I haven't adjusted yet.
Well, that makes two of us.
It was the wrong way to go.
It won't happen again. Here.
It better not.
And this bottle better
cost at least $50.
Not even close.
Harrison's out like
a light on your bed.
But if that's inconvenient,
I can totally move him.
It's fine.
Oh, and, uh, Dexter said to
tell you that he'll be late...
...but he'll be here.
- Okay, thanks.
- Sure.
Jamie, I feel like we
got off on the wrong foot.
What do you say we start over?
I'd like that.
Then how about we have some
of this fancy-ass tequila?
I never say no to
fancy-ass anything.
Let me ask you a question.
Um, is Dexter as cool
at home as he is at work?
Why? Is he, like,
your hero or something?
Yeah, right.
That... that would make me a nerd.
Which clearly I'm not.
Hey, you fucks.
Let's get the party started.
Oh, god.
Please tell me you didn't drive.
No, my lovely assistant did.
Debra, chick from bar.
Chick from bar, Debra.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant Debra,
her royal fucking majesty...
...Fifth Earl of Suffolk.
Cindy.
Feel free to hang
all over me, babe...
...because Debra here is
completely over my shit.
Wait a minute. This is your ex?
You brought me to your
ex-girlfriend's house?
No, actually, you brought me.
Have a nice life.
Damn, I just keep getting dumped.
Let go of the darkness.
How is that even possible?
Has Satan brought you
here, Travis, or has god?
God.
I'm glad to hear that.
Everything's ready
to mark the whore.
I have to go out and
do further preparation.
When I come back...
...I expect it to be done.
Who's there?
What's happening?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- What's happening?
- Get out.
Where are you taking me?
No, please.
You're free.
So were you hoping to become
a forensic analyst or whatever?
Uh, actually, I
already have a career.
Um, I create video games.
Wow, that's so cool.
So why are you a lab intern then?
Oh, I'm, uh... I'm developing
a new game about homicide.
I just figured it was a
great way to do research.
I'm sorry, but you must
be, like, a model, right?
Because there's just
no other explanation.
Hey, excuse me, we
were kind of talking.
Exactly. "Were".
Run along back to the lab, Igor.
I think I better go
check on Harrison.
- Yeah.
- Easy.
Sorry.
Move.
Hey, buddy.
Hey!
Why don't you give my
sister a little space?
I can't help it, she
has an outrageous ass.
That's enough.
I wanna have a
relationship with that ass.
I wanna have babies...
Okay, Quinn, I think it's
time we call you a cab.
You ever love me?
Now is not the time.
Come on, Deb.
It's not that hard of a question.
Did you ever love me?
All right.
That's what I thought.
I'm sorry.
He's gone.
That's it.
Brother Sam is gone.
Will you honor his dying wish?
Forgive Nick?
I want to.
What did Brother Sam say?
Just let it go.
Let go of the darkness
this one time...
...and show Nick the light.
I've accepted the path I'm on.
But can I take a detour with Nick...
...for Brother Sam?
One thing is certain.
There's no way to get
around the fork in the road.
Hey, Dexter.
Hey.
I'm glad I ran into you...
I was hoping we could talk.
Let's go for a ride.
Dexter Morgan.
Please leave a message at the tone.
Where are you, bro?
You gonna tell me
what this is about now?
Don't you recognize this place?
It's a beach.
It's the beach where
you were baptized.
So?
So I thought it would
be a good place...
...for you to explain yourself.
What are you talking about?
Brother Sam regained consciousness.
I know you shot him, Nick.
You gonna arrest me?
I keep telling you I'm not a cop.
What do you want?
I want to know why.
Why'd you do it?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You don't know why you put
three bullets in a man...
...who only wanted to help you?
Who believed in you?
Who sacrificed for you?
A man who gave you a home?
A man who baptized you.
Because he's full of shit!
He gave me hope.
But nothing changed.
My life was shit before he
dunked me under those waves...
...and it's still shit.
He lied to me.
My homies never did that.
So you went back to them.
They wouldn't take me.
Not unless I proved myself.
Leo wanted Sam dead.
That's why you gave
him the security disc.
Here I am. The fork in the road.
Brother Sam loved you, Nick.
Then why'd he rat me out to you?
He didn't.
He sent me to forgive you.
Brother Sam forgives you...
...for gunning him down like a dog.
Your life might not have changed...
...but his did.
Hey, look, I've gotta
talk to him, all right?
We can work this out.
I can't go back to jail.
He's dead.
What?
He died about an hour ago...
...which makes you a murderer.
Turn yourself in to the police.
They'll find you anyway.
No, they won't.
The only witness is dead.
There ain't nothing on that disc.
It's my word against yours.
They got no proof.
Nobody can do anything!
Sweet Jesus!
I can't believe
this worked out, man.
There's no light in you.
There's no light in me.
Hey, little brother.
Miss me?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com