Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
Gellar was pulling you
toward the darkness, Travis.
Not the light.
What's happening?
No, please.
You're free.
- I'm done.
- Done?
With you, with everything.
Oh, please.
God's will doesn't stop just
because you want to play house
with your sister.
You could have asked me
before you just took off.
You offered me some time off.
I meant the afternoon,
not five fucking days
to go wherever it is that you are.
Kids trust everybody.
For the little one.
Here you go.
They trust the food you're giving them
is safe to eat.
This way, buddy.
They trust you to lead the way.
Not the usual today.
Two coffees and...
What's good for an apology?
Male or female?
My sister.
I'd go with a cruller.
Okay.
They don't question your motives.
Give a kid a mouthful
of sugar and trans fat,
and he's your friend for life.
Thanks, Francisco.
Grown-ups are a lot harder.
My sister gave me a day off,
and I took five.
She has every right to be angry,
but I can't tell her
that I was in Nebraska...
Or why I was there.
Well, look what
the fucking cat dragged in.
The cat also brought
coffee and donuts.
You have five minutes.
Some of us actually
have to show up for work.
I see you're all moved in.
Now it's four minutes.
Right.
I'm sorry...
I took off like that, I...
really needed to get away.
I'm sorry about what
happened with Brother Sam.
And this whole Trinity thing
sucks, I get it.
And you want to blow me off?
That's fine too.
But you put me in a really
shitty position at work.
I know.
Everybody thinks I gave you a week off
in the middle of this DDK shitstorm,
which is only slightly better
than them knowing that
I didn't give you a week off!
I know.
I took advantage of you.
Yeah, you did.
I really am sorry.
Okay.
You're forgiven.
But it's only because I need
you in on this DDK shit.
What's going on?
Looks like this chick, Holly Benson,
was taken by DDK.
She got chained up, was held hostage,
but she ran away.
How?
They dumped her in some parking lot.
What--they?
That's the best part.
Turns out there are two of these
end-of-the-world
motherfuckers out there.
Gellar and some younger guy.
He's the one that let our vic go.
I think he might be a former student.
Seems like Travis Marshall
isn't my secret anymore.
Wow.
Two of them.
Why did they let her go?
Why did they tie body parts
to mannequins?
Why did they hang a waitress
from a spiked collar
in a greenhouse?
They're bat-shit.
That's why.
But it sounds like Travis
is having second thoughts.
Okay, I have to go.
I'll fill you in on the rest
when we get to the station.
Yeah, I'm going to be a little late.
You have got to be fucking kidding me.
Brother Sam's funeral is this morning.
I feel like I should...
Okay.
Fine.
Go.
Fucking funerals and donuts--
you're really good.
Sorry.
Travis?
Hey, just in time.
I got an egg white omelet,
your favorite kind
of veggie bacon,
and scones in the oven.
I can't believe you did all this.
Yeah, well, you're always
doing everything for me.
It's definitely my turn.
Go, sit down.
Just let me get dressed first.
All right, hurry up.
I remember that day.
What are you doing here?
You said I was free.
And you are.
But I can't say I'm impressed
with what you've done
with your freedom.
You traded your place in God's plan
for the pathetically mundane.
- I like mundane.
- Really?
Because when we met,
you had plenty of it.
Your sister treated you like a child.
You had no friends.
No faith.
Your life was of no consequence,
and were you happy?
It's not like that now.
No, now you have
garden gnomes and...
Ah, someone's
made you breakfast.
Want to see what I've made?
Beautiful, isn't it?
All it needs is the right whore.
Travis?
I bet she'd look lovely in red.
You stay the fuck away!
Are you taking that out?
Yeah, I'll just, uh--
I'll do it later.
Travis, you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, do you want to get out
of here for a couple of days?
We--we could go to Disney World.
- You mean now?
- Yeah.
Right now, let's just...
go.
Travis, you know
I-I can't leave.
I have school.
But maybe in a--in a couple
of weeks on my break.
That would be fun.
How many people here can say that
"Brother Sam changed my life"?
Let us always keep him in our hearts.
"For the lord is my Shepherd,
"I shall not be in want.
"He makes me lie down
in green pastures.
"He leads me beside quiet waters.
"He restores my soul.
"He guides me in the paths
of righteousness
"for his namesake.
"Even though I walk through the
valley of the shadow of death,
"I will fear no evil.
"For you are with me.
"Your rod and your staff,
they comfort me.
"You prepare a table before me
"in the presence of my enemies.
"You anoint my head with oil;
my cup overflows.
"Surely, goodness and love
will follow me
"all the days of my life,
and I will dwell in the house
of the lord forever."
- Thank you for coming.
- You're welcome.
Hey, Dexter.
Okay.
I have something for you.
Sorry about the blood.
He always had it close by, so...
when he was shot...
Last time I saw him, he said
he wanted you to have this.
Oh.
Wow.
There's probably someone else
who would get more use
out of it--
someone more religious.
I don't know.
Brother Sam used to always say
that no matter what the problem is,
the answer's in here.
You just have to figure out
the question.
Oh, hey.
Have you seen Nick lately?
Nick?
Yeah, disappeared
after Sam passed away.
None of us have seen him.
Maybe he wanted some time alone.
Or maybe I drowned him,
right where Brother Sam's
ashes are floating.
Is it possible
that Brother Sam changed me?
I didn't kill Jonah
when I had the chance.
Did Sam somehow bring out
a little bit of light in me?
And did I pass that light on
to Travis as well?
Is that why he let Holly go?
You did the right thing.
I know who you are.
I remember your voice.
I'm not here to hurt you.
You were in my car.
You tried to kill me.
And I let you go.
Just like you let Holly Benson go.
I want to know why.
I didn't want to see her suffer.
You've seen people suffer before.
What you said to me...
made me think.
Think what?
That I don't have to do what he says.
I told him I'm done.
I'm not working with him anymore.
How did Gellar take it?
Not very well.
He's angry.
He won't leave me alone.
Why not just tell the police?
I helped him do horrible things.
They'd--they'd arrest me.
They'd--
I am a good person.
I thought we were doing
the right thing.
I just--
I made a mistake getting involved
with all of this.
I can help you, Travis.
I can get him
out of your life for good.
The police will never know about you.
You just have to help me find him.
Just because I'm not working with him
does not mean
that I will work with you.
All you have to do
is tell me where he is.
I'll take care of the rest.
You don't know who
you're dealing with.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous he is?
He is crazy, I know that now.
He will finish his mission,
and he will kill anyone
who tries to stop him.
And then what?
Assuming the world doesn't end?
I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
Both of you need
to just leave me alone.
Travis has a Dark Passenger
all his own,
but unlike mine, his walks
and talks and breathes
and goes by the name Professor Gellar.
And most significantly,
his Dark Passenger can be killed.
Later.
What have we got?
Call girl
of the high-end variety.
I.D. says Jessica Morris.
The lobby bar downstairs
is a known hangout
for working girls.
Not that I would know that
for any reason.
Rings on her track marks
say it's heroin.
Maid must have wiped everything down
before she found her.
No prints anywhere
except hers on the tub.
Looks like she OD'd and hit her head,
if the drugs didn't kill her,
the blow to her skull sure did.
Probably an accidental death,
but the M.E.'ll tell us more.
What do you think?
Blood coming from her nose...
Consistent with an overdose.
Yeah, but look at the pattern,
sort of a zigzag?
It starts this way,
suggesting that
she fell in this position.
The blood dries, and then
it changes direction,
as though her head were turned
and then moved back,
suggesting the body was lifted
and then repositioned.
Heroin overdose
kills almost instantly.
Once her heart stopped beating,
there should have been
hardly any blood flow
from the head wound.
Unless...
Unless someone did chest compressions,
post-mortem.
Broken rib.
Could have been the EMTs.
She was long gone
when the maid found her.
The EMTs didn't attempt CPR.
What do you think?
I think it happened
pretty much like Vince said.
She OD's, hits her head, she dies.
Someone comes in, sees her.
He flips her over,
causing more blood
to come out of her nose.
Tries CPR, but he cracks her rib
because he's panicked.
And he realizes that
he's just causing more blood
to flow from the head wound,
so he stops.
Puts the body back where he found her,
then wipes everything clean.
Someone call the captain over here?
No, why?
Because she's here.
Captain.
Where's Sergeant Batista?
Downstairs.
What do we have here?
Looks like an overdose.
Okay, good.
Make sure to copy me
on the M.E.'s report.
I'm going downstairs.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Dexter.
You're back.
Louis.
Hey, uh--
I heard what you did
at that crime scene.
You know, the body was moved
and then repositioned.
So cool--you gotta show me how
you figure that stuff out.
Yeah, sure, we'll do that sometime,
but right now, I gotta...
Okay, I'm going to make this quick.
The whole city
is freaking out over DDK.
We're getting
over 100 calls a day--
people saying that
they've seen Gellar,
people asking if it's safe
to go out at night.
I need everyone's asses
on the fucking ball.
I'm going to keep rearranging
that sentence to make it hotter.
Holly Benson's experience with DDK...
And that's still my sister.
Suggests that Gellar
is working with an accomplice.
Now, thanks to Louis,
we have a list
of male Tallahassee graduates
living in the Miami area
that have taken classes with him.
We have over 200 names to investigate,
so I'm going to take some myself,
Batista, Quinn, Mike...
You guys can divide up the rest.
And let's not let on that we
know Gellar has an accomplice.
This fucker thinks
we don't know who he is?
Let's keep it that way.
How do I get Travis to trust me
before the cops
get to his name on the list?
Ah, I'm sorry I wasn't
at the crime scene this morning.
It's fine.
Mike was there.
I got a way to make it up to you.
There's a new place
opening on Washington.
Opening night's invitation only.
Guess who's got two of these?
I'll pass.
I've got Auri on Friday night.
Auri always cancels on you.
Take Masuka.
Your loss.
- Hey, sis.
- Hey.
What brings you here?
Oh, we were just
at Harrison's music class,
and he wanted to see his daddy.
Come on, admit it.
You wanted to say hi
to your big brother.
Hey.
I got your text.
Oh, yeah, we were
just in the neighborhood.
Want to maybe go for a walk with us?
Yeah, sure.
Let me just tell Mr. Masuka.
Okay.
You're still seeing that guy, huh?
You don't like him?
I don't really know him.
You know what?
You should come to dinner with us.
I don't know.
If you're going to judge him,
then maybe you should have some idea
who you're talking about first.
Okay, sure.
Why not?
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
Children trust that when
we put them to bed at night,
they'll live to see another day.
Adults are not always so fortunate.
Travis is my only way to Gellar.
I have to convince him to help me.
Maybe I need to learn
to speak his language.
Brother Sam did say
all the answers were in here.
I'm not sure he meant
the answers to my kinds of questions.
What are you doing here?
I told you--
No, no, you don't
want to get involved.
I understand that,
but you are responsible
for hurting a lot of people, Travis.
I'm sure you don't feel
good about that.
You wandered from God's path.
I was led astray.
I know.
The blood.
Long story.
But what's more important are
the words underneath the blood.
It says here, "Anyone then who
knows the good he ought to do--"
"And doesn't do, sins."
The "sin of omission."
James 4:17.
So?
So it sounds to me like
you're in some trouble, Travis.
If you allow Professor Gellar
to continue doing
what he's doing,
according to James here,
it's just as much of a sin
as doing the killings yourself.
I know.
I wish that I could take it all back.
But now, I can't risk
antagonizing him.
I can protect you.
It's not me that I'm worried about.
It's my sister.
Gellar's threatened her before,
and I can't let
anything happen to her.
Can I blame him?
As long as Gellar's out there.
She's still in danger.
I can protect her.
What if you can't?
Um...
Okay.
I'll try to convince Lisa
to go to her friend's
up in Pensacola for the weekend.
Gellar won't leave Miami.
Let me get her safe,
and then I promise,
I'll do whatever you say.
Sam was right about this book.
Hi, can I help you?
I'm Lieutenant Debra Morgan,
Miami Metro Homicide.
I'm looking for Travis Marshall.
His building manager said
that they were forwarding
his mail here.
Uh, Travis is my brother,
but he's not here right now.
Can I--can I help you
with something?
We're investigating
a college professor,
James Gellar, in connection
with three homicides.
The Doomsday Killer.
Oh, my God.
Travis...
Has something happened?
No, we're just looking
into former associates of his.
And according to our records,
Travis took some classes
with him up in Tallahassee.
We just want to ask him
a few questions.
Oh, I-I doubt
that Travis
would be able to help you much.
I don't think he stays in touch
with anyone from school.
He must have been pretty shaken up
when he found out an old professor
was a murder suspect.
I guess so.
He didn't mention it?
Well, Travis isn't really the type
to talk about how
he feels about things.
Not even to his sister.
So you aren't close.
Um...
Our parents died when Travis
was still a teenager,
so I pretty much raised him
the rest of the way, so...
Tragedy makes you tight, you know?
But, uh--with Travis,
I think it also made him
um, closed off,
I guess you would call it.
I don't know why
I'm telling you all this.
So you haven't noticed
any unusual behavior?
Nothing out of the ordinary?
No.
Same old Travis.
I actually have to get back to work.
Okay, if you could just have
him give me a call
the next time you see him
so we can check him off our list?
Okay.
I'm sorry I couldn't
have been more help.
No, thank you for your time.
Hey.
So any luck finding DDK's accomplice?
Um, no, not yet,
but I crossed five names off the list.
And I'm going to go back out there
as soon as I make
a couple of phone calls.
Thank you.
Sounds like detective work,
lieutenant.
Well, it's a team effort.
One of these names
is going to pan out.
Well, until it does,
I've got good news for you.
The M.E. report came back in
on Jessica Morris, the prostitute?
Cause of death was the overdose.
Why is that good news?
Because the case
can be closed as an accident,
which means you have one less
homicide to worry about.
Wait, why were you looking
at the M.E.'s report on that?
Your plate is so full
with DDK...
Came across my desk,
and I took a look at it.
Team effort, right?
Right.
Okay, so...
You can close the case now.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hey, where are you?
I'm on my way back from lunch.
Look, will you do me a favor
and put a rush on
Jessica Morris' blood report?
Laguerta's acting weird.
Weird how?
She's being helpful.
I just want to see what she's up to.
- I'm on it.
- Thank you.
Lisa.
Come on.
Hurry up, Lisa.
Stop following me!
Sorry, Travis.
We don't have time for your
little journey to find yourself.
We have to work to do.
You know, uh, when Jamie told
me you got the Trans Am,
I was jealous.
That is...one awesome car.
You drive a V.W., right?
Yeah, it's a limited edition.
Actually, it's very rare.
I'm going to go to the restroom.
You guys keep talking
about car things.
Wow.
She's amazing.
I can't believe that a girl like that
could be interested in a guy like me.
She's interested in a lot of people.
Oh.
My sister's a really nice girl.
She has a hard time saying no.
So she dates a lot of guys?
She's young.
She's in school.
She's not in a place in her life
to be taking anybody too seriously.
Okay.
I know you seem like a nice guy.
I just wouldn't want
to see you get hurt.
Hmm.
So when Jessica Morris OD'd,
there was definitely someone
in that hotel room with her.
No doubt.
Then why is Laguerta
on my ass to close this thing?
Maybe she wants to keep a low profile?
So what am I supposed to do?
If I do my job and I investigate
a possible homicide,
then--
I piss off captain close-it.
And if I close it, this guy walks.
Maybe you should talk to Laguerta.
Yeah.
Maybe I should.
Either way, I have to sign
this fucking blood report.
Do you have a pen?
Ah, here.
Why do you have a pen
from the Shady Lane Motel
at Kearney, Nebraska?
Uh...
Must have picked it up somewhere.
Yeah, at the Shady Lane Motel
in Kearney, Nebraska.
I can explain.
Kearney, Nebraska is where
Trinity's family was murdered.
Which you found out about the day
you took your little joyride.
So that is either one
motherfucker of a coincidence,
or you were "just driving"
to fucking Nebraska.
Okay, yes, I went to Nebraska.
Why?
Guess I just felt drawn there.
Did you talk to Jonah?
Yes.
Why?
I don't know, Deb.
We both lost people
we loved to the same killer.
I...
just felt a connection with him.
And I needed someone to talk to.
And you couldn't talk to me?
I didn't want to burden you.
Oh.
Burden me, my ass.
I burden you all the time.
It's not a burden for me
to be there for you.
It was a mistake.
I shouldn't have gone.
That's not the point.
The point is that
you lied to me about it.
you thought you had to go
to Butt-fuck-ville to talk
to somebody about Trinity.
Dexter, don't you think I get it?
I lost Lundy because of Trinity too.
Hey, guys, looks like
DDK struck again.
Janitor found this early this morning.
The Whore of Babylon.
The next tableau.
Shit!
I interviewed her yesterday.
Her brother was a student of Gellar's.
Travis.
Travis Marshall.
Find Travis Marshall
right the fuck now,
and if you can't find him,
put a B.O.L.O. out on him.
I think he's Gellar's accomplice.
Travis just shot to the top
of Miami Metro Homicide's
most wanted list.
Did Travis go back to Gellar,
or was this the price
Travis paid for defying him?
A ripped seam...
F.N. Galway.
This used to be some kind of vestment,
a robe, maybe.
What do you think the letters
on her forehead mean?
We'll find out.
Hey, I got something.
It's your card.
What the fuck?
What the fuck do you think means?
Maybe it doesn't mean anything.
These assholes are all about messages.
You think it's because
I talked to her?
Do you think it's to keep her quiet?
This isn't your fault, Deb.
But it could be mine.
Sorry for the chain.
I couldn't risk you
disappearing on me.
You know you're far too important.
What do you want?
Penance to cleanse your soul.
It's not your fault, Travis.
The devil comes in many forms.
Sometimes he tempts you with an apple,
or fame or riches...
or a mundane life with your family.
Do not talk about my sister.
Your sister whom you hold
in such high esteem...
talked to the police.
She betrayed you...
just like the Whore of Babylon.
What did you do to my sister?
No.
No!
She's part of it now.
Don't you get it, Travis?
She was doomed to hell on earth.
Tribulations.
But now, her soul is pure.
She can go to God.
Just like you wanted.
And you can come back to our mission.
I didn't want this!
I understand.
It'll take time.
Pray for your sister.
Do whatever it is you need to do.
And when I come back...
I sincerely hope you have
a change of heart.
I was just on my way up to see you.
I hear DDK has struck again.
We have a B.O.L.O. out
on Travis Marshall.
Everyone in the city is going
to know what he looks like.
Meanwhile, you now have two suspects
and no arrests.
Yes, I know.
Actually, I was coming to talk to you
about Jessica Morris.
The dead prostitute.
Why hasn't that case been closed?
Because I saw Dexter's report.
Someone else was in the room.
The woman overdosed, Debra.
What does it matter
who else was in the room?
Because some dickhead left
a dead woman in a bathroom.
Aren't we talking
involuntary manslaughter,
not to mention solicitation,
obstruction?
Hell, we could get murder two.
Stop.
Debra...
I'm going to level with you.
That compstat hearing
did not go very well
for either one of us.
Another open case will put
our clearance rate at 19%.
- But if we let a guilty man--
- 19%, Debra.
Do you understand what's happening?
We have a city
in an all-out panic.
Last night, a woman
tried to drive her car
into Biscayne Bay
with her infant son inside,
because she thinks
it's the end of the world
and she didn't want him
to go through the tribulations.
Now...
don't take this the wrong way,
but being young
and personable,
and saying bad words on TV
just is not going to cut it
right now, trust me.
Find the man who killed
four innocent people,
not some john who bailed
on a fucking junkie prostitute
who overdosed.
And that's an order, lieutenant.
Okay.
Fine.
I'll close it.
Good.
Yeah, it's me.
It's taken care of.
Yes, I'm sure you have nothing
more to worry about.
My search for F.N. Galway
has turned up nothing.
This is the last of them.
And there's not much I can do
with intern puppy dog
watching my every move.
You know, Google's kind
of five minutes ago, right?
Uh, try Eliot.
Yeah, it, uh,
uses a targeted algorithm
to aggregate content
without getting tripped up
by all that sneaky
S.E.O. bullshit.
Intern puppy dog has skills.
Oh, I'll let you do your thing.
Got the M.E.'s report.
Looks like Lisa Marshall
was killed the same way
as our our fruit vendor
and our jogger.
But get this:
The M.E. didn't find any
of those paper, 1,000--
whatever-the-fuck number things
anywhere on the body.
That's because it was Travis
who put the numbers there.
That means this kill was all Gellar.
Weird.
Any luck finding Travis Marshall?
Not yet.
But I found out he works
at the museum,
restoring old Bibles.
I'll fuck Masuka
if this isn't our guy.
Sounds like you're getting close.
Too close.
I'm going to have to work fast
if I want to save Travis.
Hey, listen.
You want to grab dinner
after work tonight?
You know, chat?
Talk?
Can we do another night?
I'm pretty tired,
and I just want to spend
some down time at home with Harrison.
Okay.
Sure, another night.
Definitely.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I saw the news.
I wasn't sure you'd be able to make
our session anyway today.
Yeah, I almost canceled.
But, uh, I could use the break.
That must have been
a difficult thing to see.
You could say that.
I mean, I show up, right,
to question her
about her brother and...
24 hours later...
I can't help but feel responsible.
You know, I knew that
there was something
that she wasn't telling me.
Do you think she knew that
her brother was involved?
I think she knew something
was up with him.
And I think she was trying
to protect him,
which is what a good sister does.
And then, he ends up killing her.
Oh, Jesus.
Are all brothers assholes?
Who are we talking about now?
Who else?
Dexter.
Ah. So you think
he might kill you?
No, I don't think he's going
to kill me, I just--
I think he treats me like shit.
Oh?
He shuts me out.
He won't tell me things, like...
really important things.
Sounds like you two are having
a little trouble communicating lately.
We aren't having trouble
communicating.
He's the one that's
keeping all the secrets.
But normally, you're pretty
open with each other.
Yes. I tell
him everything.
I tell him about boyfriends, work.
I tell him about everything.
Sounds like a lot
of talking about yourself.
Aren't you supposed to be on my side?
I'm just telling you what I'm hearing.
Okay, yeah.
We talk about me.
A lot.
But that's what I'm saying.
I can't get him to tell me
shit-all about jack shit.
Or maybe he doesn't think
there's any room
in the relationship for his needs.
Maybe next time you get together
you could just make
some effort to focus on him
and his issues.
Need another round?
Next one's on me.
Oh, I'm pacing myself.
I need to retain my ability...
Oh, yeah!
To...focus.
Sure, I get that.
Yeah.
All right.
Thanks, cutie.
Hey, be honest with me.
I wasn't your first choice
to bring here tonight, was I?
Not really, but does it matter?
Not really.
Excuse me.
Can I get a refill, please?
Uh-huh.
Wait, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't go anywhere.
If I said you had a beautiful body,
would you hold it against me?
Please.
Come on, it's a song.
I can sing it to you.
Yo, man.
Come on, relax.
Look, just look around
and enjoy the scenery, huh.
Look at that right there.
In the green thong.
That's a thing of beauty.
I'm going to marry her.
I'm going to marry green thong.
- Come on, Quinn.
- Sit down.
- Will you marry me?
- Fine.
No, I mean, of course
no one wants to marry me,
but can I at least
get a kiss from you?
Hey, back off, buddy.
All right?
Okay, we got to cut you off,
man, okay?
- Okay.
- But wait, she's not...
finished breaking my heart yet.
If you don't take him outta here,
I gotta take him out.
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We don't need that.
No problem, we out, we out, let's go.
Green thong!
I love you, green thong.
All right.
Let's get you home, come on.
Nah, man.
I ain't going anywhere.
I'm only getting started.
Louis' search engine
turned out to be useful.
Father Nicholas Galway,
retired catholic priest.
You understand that
Father Galway's dementia
has progressed extensively?
It isn't likely he'll remember you.
I'm not sure if that's good or bad.
Father?
Yes?
You have a visitor.
Thank you.
Father Galway?
Yes, that's me.
I'm having trouble
remembering your name.
Actually, we've never met.
- My name is--
- Francis Connolly!
Um...
You've come to apologize
for breaking the window
in the Narthex, I take it.
I'm sorry, Father.
I'm in the wrong place.
Oh, you're not going anywhere,
young man.
You must confess your sins.
Actually, I'm okay.
If I could just--
"Bless me, father,
for I have sinned."
My sins? Okay.
I've exceeded the speed limit
a few times.
Oh, who hasn't done that?
What other sins must you confess?
I lied to my sister.
The freckle-faced one,
Mary Grace, isn't that it?
She always had a cookie
in her hand, that one.
What else?
He's too far gone.
I really should get going, Father.
Son!
How do you expect to get into heaven,
unless you let me
absolve you of your sins?
You can do that?
Anything you confess,
God will forgive.
I'm waiting, Francis.
I've killed people.
Continue.
A lot of people.
Murder is a mortal sin.
You must...
Where were we?
Confession.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
I absolve you of all of your sins.
In the name of the Father,
Son, and the Holy Ghost.
Amen.
Thank you.
Hmm.
It's sad, isn't it?
He was a wonderful priest
back in the day.
Yes, he was.
Now half the time,
he doesn't know where he is.
Some Sunday mornings,
he asks to be driven
to his church because he thinks
he's supposed to lead mass.
His church?
Santa Maria de Loreto.
Right.
And that's in...
It's out in Davie.
But--but don't
waste your time.
It's been abandoned
for over 20 years now.
Not much left of it.
An abandoned church...
Very sad, huh?
If Gellar's at that church,
his hideout will
make an even better kill room.
I'll say good night to Harrison,
and then I'll be on my way.
Oh.
Hey, Dex.
Deb said I could take off
since she's here.
I told you tonight wasn't good.
I know.
You got to eat, right?
So you can just relax and kick back.
I'm making steaks.
Which is a big deal,
because I can't remember
the last time I cooked something
that didn't involve
"pierce film with fork."
Something came up.
I have to go out.
I just came to say
good night to Harrison.
I'm sorry
for the mix-up, Jamie.
Oh, that's okay.
I can stay.
- Daddy.
- Something came up?
What the fuck do you mean,
something came up?
Would you please watch
your language in front of him?
I'll go give him his bath.
- Night, buddy.
- Night, night.
So when you said you wanted
a quiet night at home,
you were just blowing me off.
I told you, something came up.
You're not going
to tell me what it is?
I can't talk about it right now.
You can't talk about it,
or you can't talk about it with me?
Deb, this isn't the time.
I gotta go.
Do you know why
I came over here tonight?
It was for you, asshole.
So you could talk to me.
Talk about what?
About whatever stuff you drove
to Nebraska to talk about.
Deb, please just let this go.
I am just trying to have
a conversation with you.
Is that so fucking hard?
Deb...
Fine.
I don't want to hurt you, Travis.
I think you do.
I think you like
watching people suffer.
There's only one way to get
the demons out of your head.
Who's out there?
Don't you say a word.
Did Gellar do this to you?
He killed my sister.
Where is he?
Travis, is he here?
Ah, damn it.
Gellar has seen me now.
This just got much harder.
I'll help you.
I'll help you kill him.
I've gotten Travis to trust me.
In my own way, I'm going to eliminate
a small bit of darkness
and let some light in.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com