(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney burps)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(tires screech)
Not again!
(classical music playing)
♪ The Simpsons 25x04 ♪
YOLO
Original Air Date on November 10, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Now, I, Bart Simpson,
shall send the first coaster
down the track.
Hmm.
(Milhouse grunts)
(gasping)
No, for once,
I want to go first.
But, Milhouse, I already
let you push me on the swings.
And it's an honor,
but I'm doing this.
Ow! Knock it off, Milhouse!
(grunting)
(yells)
Eat safety bar!
(muffled):
Why are we best friends?
Because your seat
was behind mine!
(both grunting)
(groans)
(both crying)
Feels like this playdate's
gone on forever.
I'll handle this.
"Dear Weirdo,
pick up weirdo kid."
And send.
Aah!
(gasps)
Did you eat a peanut?
No, I just sniffed a nectarine.
It's okay.
I can breathe
through my tear ducts.
(whistling)
Tell me if this
gets annoying.
(whistling continues)
I think I'm gonna throw up
the mac and cheese you fed me.
I'm not supposed to have it.
That's why I had so much.
HOMER:
What the...?!
If this kid's dad isn't
here in one second,
he's going in the garbage can.
(car honks)
Hey, guys!
Who wants a whiff
of New Kirk Smell?
"YOLO"?
You Only Live Once.
Once again, cats have it better.
Kirk Van Houten.
I hope you're not having
a midlife crisis.
Please.
Just 'cause I bought a new car,
lost a little weight
and started taking
a DJ class,
everyone thinks
I'm having a midlife crisis.
Dad! You got me
a skateboard?
It's for me.
Now get in the back.
And while you're there,
use this cream to
massage the leather.
(leather squeaking)
To the tooth-whitening kiosk!
(laughing)
I'm sorry, but does Kirk
know how silly he looks?
Look at me!
I'm afraid of dying.
(laughs)
Oh, Homie.
I'm so glad you're happy
with your life
just the way it is.
You've had the same
job, same car,
same house for 20 years.
And that's all
you'll ever have.
A cycle you'll never ever,
ever, ever, ever,
ever change.
And you're okay with it!
Like I say night after night
after night...
nighty-night.
(birds chirping)
Kent Brockman is here
for your interview.
So, Kent, what brings you here?
The miraculous tale
of how we lost, then found,
our Lost and Found box?
Actually, Principal Skinner,
I'm here to talk
about something else...
cheating!
(chuckles)
I thought this was a puff piece.
You're wearing a sweater.
This journalism just turned...
gotcha!
(gasps)
That's right, Channel 6
will uncover the truth
in a five-part series
two minutes a day.
People, make room for your local
Emmy nomination certificates.
No, do not make room.
Except for Mr. Largo
and his diet,
there's no cheating
in this school.
These 30 identical
"What I Did This Summer"
essays say different.
Um...
Myra, don't I have
another appointment?
Oh, this is your first
appointment ever.
Let's take a look
at this monitor.
This school is more corrupt
than the Italian parliament.
If these children
are our future,
then I, for one,
do not want to live.
(quietly):
Ha-ha.
Please don't air this.
I'll tell you the winners of
the kickball games in advance.
You can make a lot of cabbage
betting on K-ball.
And that's what we'll end
the story with.
No!
This is Kent Brockman.
Pleased with himself.
♪ You only
♪ Live once
♪ Or so it seems
♪ No life for yourself
♪ And none for your dreams
♪ You work
♪ Every day
♪ At a job so lame
♪ And every night
♪ The ending's the same.
♪ No dream will come true
♪ You only
♪ Live once.
(deep breath)
(crying to the tune of
"You Only Live Twice")
(higher-pitched crying)
Yeah, well, at least you
got your health, huh?
Now let's see if I can
take that away from you.
Your poison.
(groans)
I'm tired of living once.
I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but I'm starting to
regret saying "YOLO."
Marge, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna quit complaining
about my life and start
wallowing in the past.
Postage, marked in pesetas?
Who are those letters from?
My old pen pal from Spain.
Eduardo.
Hmm.
Back in fifth grade,
you either had to write
to a foreigner
or a prisoner.
I picked a foreigner
because the prisoners
wrote back too fast.
We'd write each other
with our dreams of the future.
I was gonna be
King of Cheeseburger Mountain.
(sighs)
Did I change or did they stop
making mountains
out of cheeseburgers?
Probably a little bit of both.
So sad.
(indistinct chatter)
(overlapping chatter)
What kind of moral example
is this dump for my boy?
(burps)
(crowd clamoring)
Please, calm down, everyone.
You know, maybe
this so-called cheating scandal
is actually
an opportunity to, uh...
(clears throat)
...initiate a-a dialogue
that would, uh, create
a teachable moment.
Uh, something, something
buzz word...
I got nothing.
Quick, get a picture
for the yearbook!
(crowd clamoring)
LISA:
I have a solution!
You took your sweet time
coming to our rescue, Lisa.
Maybe the best way to keep
students from cheating
is to trust them not to cheat.
(crowd murmuring)
That's it?
That's all you've got?
Something I can read
on a tea box?
What I'm suggesting is
we create an honor code.
Oh, swell, more work
for the teachers.
The students would do it.
Let her speak!
If every student pledges
not to cheat,
and to turn in any cheater,
no one will cheat the system
because they'll be the system.
ALL (chanting):
Honor code! Honor code!
I did it.
I saved the day.
The same way I won
that battle in Vietnam.
By fainting!
(doorbell rings)
If you're my wife's
secret lover, come in.
There's nothing
I can do for her anymore.
I am looking
for my amigo de la pluma.
Or "pen pal."
(gasps) Eduardo?
Is it really you?
Why are you here?
To save the soul
of Homer Simpson.
Now where is he, old man?
I'm Homer Simpson!
Ay, dios mio!
What has happened to you?
(speaking in Spanish)
Did your hair burn
off in a fire
that trapped you
in a candy factory?
I wish.
Marge Simpson.
It's so nice
to meet a friend
Homer met through the mail
who isn't a sea monkey.
Yes, Eduardo Barcelona.
Or in English, Eddie Miami.
Homie,
I thought a visit
from your old pen pal
would cheer you up.
Ah, how eagerly
I would wait for a letter
from the EstadosUnidos,
and Homer Simpson.
HOMER:
"Buenos días, Eduardo."
HOMER (continues):
(chuckles)
What happened
to us, Eduardo?
We had so many things
we were going to do.
And I, my friend,
have been doing them.
Yeah, well, listen, pal.
I have my treasure--
my wife and my children.
Ooh!
I've had eight wives
and 200 children!
Among them artists, doctors
and revolutionary chefs.
Do you have a
disrespectful son
who calls you by
your first name?
I cannot imagine
such a creature.
Hey, Homer.
Did you just fart?
Did you
just fart, sir.
Whatever.
Easy, easy, Homer.
I want to help you fulfill
some of your childhood dreams.
Really? Now?
I have two pizzas coming.
I wanted to see who
would get here first.
Now, Homer!
Get your coat.
I asked him here
to cheer you up.
But I didn't think
you'd drop everything
to go gallivanting
with some, no offense, Spaniard.
I promise you
one thing, madam.
When I return your husband,
he will be happy,
bringing a new sense
of adventure to your marriage...
and to the bedroom.
(panting)
I'm not used to strange men
saying the word
"bedroom" around me.
Would you prefer, uh,
"sala deamor"?
That's even worse.
Could you say it
one more time?
Sala de amor.
(gasps) Ooh!
Hello, children.
I hold before you a copy
of the school's new honor code.
(all groaning)
I know if I can get
the toughest kid in class
to sign it,
the rest of you will sign it.
Milhouse?
(grunts)
He's not the toughest kid, I am!
Mm-hmm!
Now, the smartest kid.
Milhouse?
He's not the smartest kid.
I am.
Now the class nerd.
Milhouse?
(sighs): Oh.
(snickers)
Homer, are you prepared
to achieve the dreams
of a ten year old?
I took the liberty of crossing
off the, uh, stupid ones.
Now, this book
of your childhood drawings
will come to life.
Why are you doing this?
Wait, are you in love with me?
In love
with the concept of you, yes.
Woo-hoo! I'm an attractive
concept like Liberty!
(siren wailing)
(tires screech)
One more ride?
All right.
Don't forget to ring the bell.
(bell ringing)
(laughing, grunting)
I'm sick of pirates
off the street ruining my play!
I'm going back to my old career!
Care to see a dessert menu?
We have the best cobbler
since Daniel Day-Lewis.
How much did this
cost to restage?
They rented everything from
Comic Book Guy for ten bucks.
Don't stink up
the Gorn head.
I need it
for a Bar Mitzvah later.
(birds chirping)
Now don't forget,
this is the first exam
under the new honor code.
They're doing it.
They're self-proctoring.
Can't you say anything
in a normal way?
The answer, sadly,
is not yes.
(crickets trilling)
I don't know what it is
about having
all my dreams fulfilled,
but I feel great!
Oh, if you're
happy I'm happy.
What?
That doesn't sound happy.
I feel kind of, oh...
melancholy.
Mmm, melon collie.
(barking)
That's not helping.
Well, what was
your childhood dream?
Jumping on the bed.
But I never disobeyed
my parents.
Till I married you.
Let's do it.
Oh, I'm a little tired.
Could we just snuggle again?
We do that every night!
Come on!
Jump on the bed!
(Homer giggling)
Ooh, okay!
(both laughing)
Can I help you, stranger?
I am just watching
my friend and his wife
innocently pleasure
themselves in bed.
That sounds salty,
but you seem sweet.
I'm gonna call you
Kettle Corn.
Eduardo, I haven't felt
this good in years.
You're like the Tooth Fairy.
Except you don't collect
human bones.
Yes, yes. Of course I don't.
Here.
So, that's it?
All my dreams, lived?
Eh... all but one.
Well, we've got to do it!
I never leave
a job unfinished.
It's as true now as that week
I worked
on the high school yearbook.
So much infighting.
I had to get out of there.
All right, Homer,
we shall do this thing.
The editor put in
like six pictures of this girl
'cause she was his girlfriend.
Everyone has a
bad yearbook story.
They spelled my name wrong!
Get over it! Ha!
D'oh!
(propellers churning)
So don't do what I did.
That concludes our safety video.
(grunts)
Just step out that door
and you can glide to earth
like your boyhood hero...
Rocky the Flying Squirrel.
Uh, actually,
my hero
was the actress
who provided Rocky's voice,
June Foray.
A true legend
in the voice-over community.
I'm just gonna stay on the plane
and think about her influence.
She has lived her life.
Now, you must live yours.
No!
Do not worry!
I will follow
the trail of your fear!
(Homer yells)
ANNOUNCER:
Will Homer make it?
Or will he leave
a crater the size
of the one
that destroyed the Yucatan?
Find out in our next
exciting installment:
Fat Splat...
or When You Squish
Upon a Car.
Mmm, it's amazing.
Every day has the peace
and serenity of a flu outbreak.
(laughs) Guess I'll be getting
some extra credit for this.
Lisa, I'm afraid you've gotten
all the extra credit
we can give out.
So Willie has been
growing you a nice pumpkin.
Here it is, lass.
You want me to carve it
into a thank-o'-lantern?
No, this is good.
Well, this knife's got
to carve something.
(menacing music playing)
(grunting)
Homer!
(grunts thrice)
You don't have to flap.
Just glide on the wind.
Uh, okay.
Flap! Flap! Flap!
(grunts twice)
Yes, good,
much better.
(groans)
I got Bart's backpack.
He got a hundred on his test?
That's impossible.
(gasps)
Is Bart cheating?
Are the Pope's tweets
infallible?
(laughs)
Bart, I'm gonna tell!
No, you're not.
Because if you tell people
I cheated,
that means your system failed.
Oh, my God,
you found a loophole!
Why don't you put this much
inventiveness into your work?
Because then I'd be the one
thing I swore I wouldn't.
You.
(whistling)
I'm doing it!
I'm flying like the squirrel
I always knew I was.
Ooh, indigo!
MARGE: Homer?
(yells gibberish)
It's me,
talking in your earphone.
Come down, Homie.
"You only live once"
also means when you die,
you die!
(cries out)
What's going on?
Hello?
(goose honks)
Hmm?
(honks)
Hmm? Hmm?
Are you mocking me?
You can listen to your
wife when you are dead.
Savor the moment.
Majestic eagle.
Just like me,
unashamed of his baldness.
(eagle cries)
So beautiful.
Aw, he probably sees a mouse
he wants to tear in half.
(grunts)
D'oh!
Stupid tallest building
in Springfield!
(grunting)
Hmm...
(grunts)
(grunting)
Ha!
Whoa!
You've presented me
with quite a conundrum.
A word you should know
since it was on a
vocabulary test you aced.
(giggles)
But after some thought,
all my worries went away.
I know the answer.
I'm gonna force you
to turn yourself in.
Good luck with that.
The only thing that'll change
my mind
is a sign from God.
(Bart grunts)
Son, it was so beautiful!
I went faster
than the speed of sound.
(Homer yelling)
(grunts)
Well, Bart, is that enough
of a sign for you?
All right, I'll turn myself in.
It'll give me a chance
to work some more
on the detention quilt.
(humming a tune)
(all grunting)
This patch is
for all the victims
of atomic wedgies.
My friend,
you've lived your dreams.
No matter what,
Homer Simpson has done it.
And soon I hope I remember
who Homer Simpson is
and his relationship to me.
But I have no regrets.
In fact, all this
has given me a sense of calm
I've never had before.
That's the morphine.
Can you give me the
morphine forever?
No way!
A person on morphine
all the time
would constantly dissolve
in inappropriate laughter.
(laughs)
(sighs)
Eduardo? Eduardo! Eduardo!
(grunts)
Oh.
It was all just a dream.
EDUARDO:
It was not just a dream.
And you said you'd drive me
to the airport.
Oh, yeah.
Great.
Um...
Do I drop you at the curb
or do I have to park
and walk you in?
Go as far as your heart
will take you.
You are a good friend.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ You only live once
♪ But that's okay
♪ You'll live quite long
♪ In the USA...
♪ But back to my point
♪ You only live once
♪ You've got years and years
♪ Unless it's just months.
Shh!