(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(gentle orchestral
music playing)
♪ The Simpsons 25x03 ♪
Four Regrettings and a Funeral
Original Air Date on October 6, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(wind whistling)
S-So lonely.
(raspy): No sex
without a ring.
Damn it!
(gentle orchestral music
continues, giants laughing)
(belches)
(creaking)
♪
Mm.
What the...?! Hey, whoa!
(ghostly moaning)
(crackling)
What about us, man?
Get your own couch.
♪
(soft organ music playing)
(organ music continues)
Poor Chip. Such a big part
of everyone's life.
People called him
the "sixth Simpson."
I'm not sure why.
Chip did such a wonderful job
with my biography.
(people murmuring)
Chip was the life of Sector 6-F
at the nuclear plant,
but Chip once confessed to me
he did have a few regrets.
(all gasp)
Chip regretted never ascending
Mount Springfield
from the south face.
He regretted that the high
school long jump record he set
was wind-aided.
He often spoke of that asterisk.
He never broke par on hole 17
at Springfield Mini Golf.
(organ music resumes)
Let us pray.
Eh, everyone has regrets.
Not me.
You? Your marriage
is a dead fish
floating in a tank
of stale beer.
Your baby's addicted
to pacifiers.
And your son is
out of control.
Let us kneel.
(pained groans)
Ow! My knees!
40 years of healing, gone!
(cackling)
He's such a little dickens.
Although Dickens
was pretty well behaved.
He's been screwed up since
the moment Homer's DNA
staggered into your womb.
I have no regrets about that.
It was a perfect pregnancy.
Didn't smoke, didn't drink,
lost three pounds.
And every night before bed,
Homer would give me
a little kiss...
music! (gasps)
Could Bart have been
prenatally screwed up
by the KISS music?
♪ Get up! Everybody's
gonna move their feet ♪
♪ Get down! Everybody's
gonna leave their seats ♪
♪ You got to lose your mind
in Detroit Rock City. ♪
Huh?
Man, this is the weirdest
pregnancy craving ever.
Well, for some reason
it relaxes me.
Now, do that thing
Gene Simmons does.
Overstay my welcome
for 40 years?
(whistling a tune)
KENT BROCKMAN: Regrets, eh?
This local newsman's had a few.
Covering a town
of backwater rubes
who, for some reason,
hate my guts.
This is Kent Brockman...
(sighs)
live at the Springfield
Peach Parade.
Sir, could you give us eight
seconds of your homespun wisdom?
It's a little-known fact
that you can get
head lice from peaches.
Uh, this is my
daughter Peaches.
(sighs) We'll have more regrets
at 11:00 tonight
following an all-new
bottle of scotch.
HOMER (scoffs):
You have regrets,
Mr. "I Get to See the
Weathergirl From the Side"!
I made the worst financial
decision of all time.
Oh, I can't think about it.
I won't think about it.
I don't want to think about it!
Oh, I'm thinking about it!
Mm...
Hmm.
Huh?
(shudders): Oh...
that's the coolest bowling ball
I've ever seen.
Hello, Bear Stearns?
I'd like to sell
all my Apple stock
so I can buy
a fancy bowling ball.
You heard me.
Technology is a fad.
Heavy, black balls
are the future.
Now let us text
on our ubiquitous
Apple tablets and phones.
(keys clicking)
Oh, you cost me a
piece of all that!
Oh, don't cry.
If it makes you
feel worse,
I'm the man who bought
the stock you sold.
I'll bet a rich man like you
has no regrets at all.
Just one.
The girl that got away.
She broke my first heart.
So, is there truly anyone
among us without regrets?
I have no regrets.
Really, Mother?
Oh, I didn't
see you there.
(Irish accent): I'm Father O'Greedy.
Dimes for the needy.
(Milhouse chuckles)
Milhouse, are you the bottom
half of that mischief?
MILHOUSE:
Uh... uh... uh...
Oh, my.
My pants, like the Lord,
work in mysterious ways.
Return those vestments.
Speaking of return
on investments,
my Apple stock
is up 3,500%.
Aw, you misheard that
on purpose!
(grunting)
Tithe denied!
Mm. Must find way...
to blame myself.
Um, it says I should
give you lumbar support.
Better go to
the lumber yard.
"Lum- bar."
It means "lower back."
How many times
will you make that mistake?
(groans) Just put on
the KISS record.
Which one?
Anything from Love Gun.
♪
Hey, book,
are you expecting this?
And while I'm at it...
Burn, dumb, helpful books.
That is a good fire.
(grunting)
(pants)
You're going down, Bart!
(grunts, groans)
Ah, reckless youth.
He'll be okay.
I was referring to him.
I had a spring in my
step like that once.
Back when I met Lilah.
Lilah ran a little crepe stand
in the seventh arrondissement.
Oh, Monty,
looking at you, I could lie
in this unheated garret forever.
There's heat.
I just don't turn it on.
Seeing you there, in the sweet
light of Paris between the wars,
there's a question I must pose.
I have something for you.
Oh! Not that.
(chuckles)
(grunts)
(bubbling)
(chuckles)
Wrong box. Lilah,
will you take that big step
from cousin to wife?
(gasps)
Oh, Monty, you must
promise me one thing.
Anything she wanted
I was willing to do.
Anything, except...
All I ask is that you set aside
five minutes a day
to think of others.
When you say "others,"
could they be bars of gold?
(crying):
I shall find another husband
as good as you are evil.
No one's that good.
(sobbing)
All I have left is my drawing.
Hm. It looked a lot better
in my memory.
Uh, but you know what, Smithers?
I will find Lilah
and win her back.
I'll just check
with the old gang.
Hemingway!
Picasso.
Matador Juan Belmonte.
And Stalin.
That man could really
put pressure on you.
Hello, Kent.
Well, well, well.
Rachel Maddow.
Everyone came back
for Chip's funeral.
I was flying from DC to New York
and, of course,
I had the layover
in Springfield.
How's the gang at Channel 6?
Look, let's get this out of the way--
just because we both
worked at Channel 6 and
you made it big and I didn't
doesn't mean I'm bitter.
Um, Is that your car?
Maybe.
Kent, I'm
gonna tell you
the most important
mistake you ever made...
after this break.
So, Kent, that
mistake you made,
that fundamental,
life-changing error,
that cosmic fail, that...
Just tell me already!
After this break.
You could have
come with me,
but you were suckling
the dual teats
of infotainment
and celebrifawning.
(upbeat theme plays)
So, tell us about
your new movie.
It's fantastic.
The studio let us play
in their sandbox.
Great. We have a clip.
No! No, don't show it.
There aren't five good seconds
in the whole film.
(car door closes,
tires screeching)
I'm not a newsman anymore,
I'm a geologist.
I keep discovering
a new rock bottom.
Kent, I think I found my
ticket out of this town.
Or at least to a
better Springfield.
You two newshounds
working on a story?
How about this?
Mario's down the street
found a rat in their pasta.
When did that happen?
Whenever you want. Eh?
Rachel, can I come?
We can share blazers.
Just follow me.
At Mario's, the picture
of Sinatra on the wall
is signed by Frank Junior.
The frame hides the "Junior"!
Someone's been dumping tires
in the forest.
Willikers!
In my three years of soft news,
I've never seen
anything like this.
Those are tires from my
ill-fated Krusty Town Car.
It would explode if people
gripped the wheel too tightly.
(laughs):
What a scoop!
You're not telling no one.
As the 4:00 p.m. clown,
I have complete control
of the Channel 6 news division.
Local news is a joke.
I'm going to cable.
Cable news!
Bah! People only want news
at 6:00 p.m.
from white guys on weekdays
and black guys on weekends.
We'll see about that.
Yes, we shall see.
About that,
things will be seen.
By us.
Kent, you coming?
He ain't comin'.
This little piggy's
afraid to leave his cushy
anchorman slop trough.
Could you, uh, phrase that
a little more nicely?
Sorry. He "isn't" coming.
You'll regret this, Kent.
When I have my own show
and you're stuck here
tracking Santa's flight
from the North Pole.
"Oh, look, he's
over Greenland!"
Don't worry, piggy,
you made the right choice.
Eh, it'll burn out
in an hour or so.
Grunting as he lifts
Bryce in the air.
Look, Burns, I've got the dope
on your sweetie.
She's still alive,
and she just got over
being mad at you last week.
Lilah's alive?
Yeah, well, uh,
she's alive,
but she's a nun.
Married to Jesus, eh?
Does he beat her?
Jesus? No, he's a real
Eagle Scout, that one.
But your penguin's not a Catholic,
she's a Buddhist nun--
spent her life expressing her
sexuality with a Zen garden.
Those raked rocks
could have been me.
Now, since you're so good at
finding things, find the exit.
There is the little
matter of my fee.
You're becoming very tiresome.
Who moved my desk?!
♪
Well, here I am.
Cable news alley.
(dog howls)
Fox News.
Is this really how I want
to get back in the big leagues?
Let's see how
print journalism is doing.
Sir, do you sell
The New York Times?
Sir, we are
The New York Times.
And in I go.
Why are you doing
this, Bart?
50% attention-seeking,
50% to drop things on people.
He's gonna visit
my sky granny.
To work at Fox News,
all you have to be able to do
is operate this device.
Now, when a Republican
is in trouble...
At the time,
I didn't know it was illegal
to sex up a cow
on the Capitol steps.
...we simply do this.
Now you try.
Sorry, but I just discovered
I have some scruples.
I'm going back to
my sweet little town
where I can decide
what news is.
Like a god.
We've had some good times.
♪ Memories
♪ Rest between the pages
of my mind ♪
♪ Memories
♪ See me through the ages
just like wine... ♪
And you sat on the gas pedal
when my foot fell asleep,
so I'm getting you
shined up nice.
What the...?
Oh!
That's a ball-proof
window, sir.
Would you like me to ask Siri
for a nearby hospital?
SIRI: I'm sorry, I don't see
any "hops petals" near you.
Deleting all
contact information.
No, no, I didn't ask you
to do that, Siri. I...
Delete confirmed.
BART (groans):
Oh. Okay, Bart, be cool.
Calm down, you're not
gonna die up here.
(indistinct chatter)
(whooping, gunfire)
(yells, whimpers)
Aw...
D'oh!
Oh, Monty, I can't
believe you found me
after all these years.
I've saved myself for you.
Well, then, uh...
(nervous chuckle)
I should disrobe at once.
Housekeeping? Send up a
Chinese dressing screen
and one of Firestone's finest
vulcanized prophylactics.
Be right back.
(laughs softly)
Smithers?
Which do I take first,
the rhino horn
or the tiger tongue?
I have my doubts
about both, sir.
Bah! I'll just do it
the old-fashioned way.
With my pump.
(engine sputtering)
(sputtering continues)
(chuckles):
Just powdering my nose, darling.
(engine continues sputtering)
Smithers, run down
to Sears, Roebuck
and get a five-eighths-inch
Phillips head bolt.
(tires screech)
(sighs) Here I am,
slowly dying every day
at 5:00, 6:00 and 11:00.
BART:
Help! Help!
Child in danger
with exciting visuals!
This kid's corpse could be
my magic carpet.
Get me a cameraman!
The movie Up has come horribly
to life over Springfield.
A local boy
clings to life in a story
that proves
this reporter's relevance.
BART:
Ay, caramba!
(gasps)
It's Bart!
Pray for a miracle, boy.
God can hear you
better from up there.
Dear Lord, please
help me land safely.
Or transform this basket
into a flying killer robot
that I control
with my mind. Amen.
That's not a prayer.
My God says it is.
Oh, I see you're ice-cold
with anticipation.
Dead?
Oh, Lilah.
Even at the end,
I waited too long.
What if I give her
the breath of life?
(soft exhale)
Oh, boy.
I guess one regret
just leads to another.
You know, sir, maybe it
would bring you peace
to honor the one thing
Lilah ever asked of you.
Here you are, my good man.
A little broth will cure
your mental illness. (chuckles)
Sir, that's
five minutes.
You can stop thinking
of other people now.
You know what, I think
I'll give it another five.
I'm proud of you, Monty.
(kissing)
I ain't
eatin' that.
Chief, what are you
doing to save our son?
Well, I've placed marksmen
on the roof
to shoot the balloons
one by one,
but frankly
they're not very good.
(gunshot)
(grunts)
(whining): Chief,
it happened again.
Aw, come on, guys,
spread out. Arm's length.
It's all my fault.
I should never have listened
to those KISS albums
when I was pregnant.
Marge, with all due respect,
that's ridiculous.
My Sarah listened to Mozart
and Churchill speeches
when she was pregnant
with Ralphie,
and he can't even
open a refrigerator.
Pushing, always...
always pushing.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
That kid's a mess.
Hey! Only I get
to criticize him, Lou.
Kid's scared to flush.
Think's it's his brother.
Can we focus on my
son up in the sky?
Oh, I've got
a long-shot idea.
By which I mean firing a shot
over a long distance.
(chuckling)
Yeah, you see, if we could fire
an exactly 12-and-a-half-pound
weight into the basket,
it would lower the boy
very gently to the ground.
Unfortunately, all our
cannonballs were melted down
to make a statue
of Joe Paterno,
which we changed
to look like Eugene Levy.
I think I just might have
what you're looking for.
♪
Today I'm glad that
I sold that stock.
Uh, Apple closed up
another 20 points today.
(whining):
Why does everyone know?
Because their terrific products
keep track of it for you.
And anything else
you could ever think of.
That kid's not
dying on my watch.
Which ends... right
now, fortunately.
(hums a tune)
(whimpers)
CROWD (chanting): Bart! Bart!
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
(laughing):
Hey.
CROWD: Bart! Bart!
Hmm. (yells)
Homer's rising faster
than Apple stock.
(laughter)
(Homer yells, grunts)
My boy's okay!
CROWD (chanting):
Bart! Bart! Bart!
I won the
science fair!
I get to go to Chicago!
CROWD:
Bart! Bart! Bart!
Ugh. Bart, Bart, Bart.
You know what I think
about regrets?
As long as your family
is together,
every choice you've ever made
is the right one.
And together we are.
(gunshot)
Would you guys knock it off?
He's down safe already.
(gunshot)
MAN: Sorry, Chief,
that was me putting it down.
And there you have it--
a family reunited.
And a grateful nation gives
thanks for some solid reporting.
Back to you, Rachel Maddow.
Great job, Kent.
I think we might have
an opening for you at MSNBC
between our weekend
prison documentary block
and the two hours it takes
to make up Joe Scarborough
on Monday morning.
(chuckles): No, thanks, Rachel Maddow.
I'm happy right here.
No regrets.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hah!
Shh!