(pilot screams)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(Bart chuckles)
(grunts, groans)
♪ The Simpsons 25x01 ♪
Homerland
Original Air Date on September 29, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪
America faces
an ominous new threat--
terrorism.
We must be vigilant,
secure every home,
every church,
every Kwik-E-Mart
and presidential library.
PRESIDENT CLINTON:
I grew up
in a little town in Arkansas,
whose name, ironically,
was Terrorism.
(loud explosion)
(explosion, television static)
Ooh, there's new marshmallows
in the Belfast Charms!
No! No, that's
Bart's cereal.
It's the only way
I can get him to take
his "vitamins."
(sighs)
Eat up.
The sum of the square roots
of any two sides
of an isosceles triangle
is equal
to the square root
of the remaining side.
That's not right.
Yes, it is.
They're my lines as the
Scarecrow in The Wizard of Oz.
Okay, I'm ready for
the Nuclear Workers Convention.
It's a little sad-- the guys who
did the funny skit last year,
well, they're all very sick.
Did you pack
everything you need?
Even better.
I never unpacked from the time
we went to Hawaii.
Whoo!
My lava's almost cooled!
(sizzling)
(thump)
I'm still cold.
Oh, a whole weekend
away from my family.
I can't believe
I have to miss taking the kids
to buy gym uniforms.
Send me a picture?
Poor guy.
Salt of the earth.
ALL (chanting):
Convention! Convention!
Convention!
STEWARDESS:
Oxygen masks on.
Convention!
(air horn blasting,
siren blasting)
Man I love conventions.
Yeah, they’re the perfect combination
of work and binge drinking.
Now look guys, we are here
for one important reason.
To get free swag.
Swag, I'm gonna
grab forever.
Somethin' I really don't need.
Swag!
I'm gonna have
40 key chains.
And I don't even
have 40 keys.
Swag!
Interested in learning
a procedure
that could save your life?
♪ More free stuff  ♪
Uh, all I have are these spec sheets.
♪ More free stuff,
more free stuff ♪
ALL:
♪ Swag!
(grunt, thud)
(gasps) There's that
woman I always have
a "same time next
year" affair with.
And she's with
her frumpy friend
I always have dinner with
when you two disappear.
Mm-hmm-hmm.
(slurps)
Put up your nukes!
(chuckles)
Halpern!
Hey-hey! The wild
man of Wichita!
I still haven't
forgiven you
for putting that dead goat
in my bed.
He wasn't dead till you
rolled over on him! Ha!
(laughing): Oh, yeah.
Take that.
In your face, boy.
Ow! Ow!
Hey!
(angry grunting)
I'll kill you!
You son of a...!
(deep panting)
Oh, come here, you.
Oh...
Ah, yeah.
It could be,
if we introduce
Halpern, what will you
think of next?
Nothing.
This is it.
(slurring): Hey,
here's a brainstorm for you.
Check if it's plugged in
before you call I.T.!
You think I like
talking you monkeys
through a password change?!
(grunts)
(laughter)
(slurring):
To texting!
Hello.
Where's Homer?
Homer, Homer-- when
did I see him last?
Geez, I
don't know.
(vomits)
Yeah, Homer's a great guy,
but that doesn't mean
I constantly think about
whether he's still alive or not.
You're taking a picture of
'em in their moment of grief?
It's okay.
This camera has
an "auto cheer" feature.
Aw...
Well, he's not
in the Boise morgue.
Maybe he was mistaken
for a dead elephant
and flown back to Kenya.
You're talking
about my husband.
To spare your feelings,
we'll just call him the Blob.
Two to one says the Blob is
stuck in the water-intake
pipe at the reservoir.
Please, I need people here
who are helpful and sensitive.
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
I had some trouble
getting the voice mails
off the 9-1-1 line.
Why does everyone have to talk
so fast and panicky?
MAN (slowly and clearly):
A man with a gun is in my house.
Gibberish.
(barking)
Hello, everyone.
Homie! What happened to you?
I overslept, lost my cell
phone, missed my flight.
Why didn't you call us?
Well, all the pay phones
at the airport
were replaced
by self-serve yogurt.
I ate all the cookie dough
toppings a man could want.
So many cookies
will never be born.
Well, I guess
all that matters is,
everything's
back to normal.
♪
(explosion)
Yes. Back to normal.
Dear Christian God...
Hey!
Sorry. Dear God--
you know which
one I mean--
thank you for
returning our Homie.
He's still got a lot of
unfinished business down here.
Amen.
I'm glad you're back, Dad.
It's hard to sleep
with one unkissed cheek.
Yeah, it's tough being man
of the house.
You left some big underpants
to fill.
I didn't know they made
Underoos in size 52.
They're called
Superoos, son.
With pictures of the cast
of The Expendables.
More like The Expandables.
(chuckles)
Why didn't you
strangle me?
That kind of small-scale
violence solves nothing.
Couldn't agree more.
Now to celebrate.
Ta-da! Pork chops
crusted with Cheeto dust.
Uh, I'll pass
on the pork.
(spits)
I'll just enjoy these green
beans with slivered almonds.
Mmm, so slivered.
Mmm.
(quietly): Bart, why is the dad I always
wished for creeping me out?
I don't know. 'Cause you're
incapable of experiencing joy?
Yay.
(groans)
Point taken.
Dad, what's that
on your lap?
A napkin.
(others gasp)
Glad you're back, buddy.
You got a lot
of catching up to do.
(grunting, panting)
Can I just get a glass of water?
Water? That stuff killed
my grandmother.
So sad.
I've been having
snuggle dreams.
Marge, I changed in Boise.
I'm not sure a man
who eats right and doesn't drink
can be good in bed.
Well, what made you...?
You're so beautiful
when I cut you off in
the middle of a question.
(both moaning)
(gasps)
Oh. Oh, my.
What's that thing
you're doing?
HOMER (sultrily):
Moving my body.
MARGE (chuckling):
Oh.
(humming happily)
Don't you think it's weird
that Dad stopped eating pork
and drinking beer?
Who cares
what happened?
Daddy's back.
(grunts)
(humming happily)
Something happened to Dad
on that trip.
This is worse than when he went
to New Orleans
and came back
with a Southern accent.
(deep Southern accent):
Uh, how y'all doin'?
(crunch)
(dog barking in distance)
Chief Wiggum, how come every
time there's a terrorist chatter
in this town, you come to me?
Lay off, Apu.
When I look at people,
I don't see colors.
I just see crackpot religions.
Chief, is there
really a terrorist threat
to Springfield?
Yeah. I got
a very important phone call.
(phone rings)
Yello?
MAN:
Is this line secure?
Uh, it's a little jiggly
but it'll hold.
We got intel-- uh, that's short
for a word I don't know...
Intelligence?
I don't believe so, no.
Anyway, this intel says that
someone in town has been turned
and they're working for terrorists.
(gasps)
Now, I got to go check
my other suspects.
Uh-huh.
But I may be back.
Huh?
(gasps)
Dad's kneeling on a prayer mat.
He doesn't believe in kneeling.
(chanting indistinctly)
Huh? It looks like he's praying.
To the east. The Middle East.
Mecca.
(quietly): He's targeting
the nuclear plant.
Meow?
If you are a cat, prove it.
Do you hate Mondays,
like Garfield? (screeches)
And do you love lasagna,
like me?
Meow.
Okay then.
(humming happily)
Mom, I have to tell you
something about Dad,
something big!
I know. He's changed.
Exactly.
For the better.
And men don't
change that way.
But-but...
Do you know what
we're doing on Sunday?
Brunch with the Hibberts.
Then the tile store.
He's like a husband
in a widow's memory-- perfect.
(grunting)
Perfect.
(beeping)
(phone rings)
FBI.
I think someone I love
is a terrorist.
Does that make me crazy?
No, no. Not at all.
It took me two hours to get
home. Traffic was crazy.
Are you people
talking about me?
No. We're not even
here right now.
742 Evergreen Terrace.
I'll be right there.
And don't believe what
you've heard about me.
I haven't heard anything
about you except from you.
Hanging up
the receiver, eh?
(gasps)
How much did you hear?
How much did you say?
Nothing, really.
So I heard half of nothing.
Dad, you're scary
when you're calm and focused.
Lisa, I'll miss you
when this is all over.
When what's all over?
This conversation.
(chuckles nervously)
See you on the other side.
What other side?
Of the house.
Where the fireplace is.
We're toasting marshmallows.
Marsh...
mallows.
I'm Bart Simpson.
Who the hell are you?
Agent Crawford, FBI.
You guys know I don't talk
to field agents.
Get your boss on the phone.
I'm not here for you.
I'm here for your dad.
What do you want
with his dad?
Go back to
sleep, Milhouse.
How do you know my name?
I didn't. But I do now.
Don't talk.
Okay.
I want you to know
I'm the best there is
at finding out
what you're up to.
Ooh.
I can torture you.
I can give you incredible sex.
Or you can just tell me
what I want to know.
What was the
first one again?
I see.
You're stupid.
Hey.
I'm the one in bed
with two beautiful women.
(gasps)
You think
I'm beautiful? Oh!
In a breaking-and-entering
kind of way.
Well, give me something,
or I'm not leaving.
(snoring)
Let's just say I've got
to get to work on time.
And if you knew me, you'd know
just how odd that sounds.
Who are you
talking to?
No one.
You're in too deep, Annie.
Get out.
Are you real, or my imagination?
Either way,
my advice is sound.
I love my job.
HOMER (à la Islamic call
to prayer): ♪ It is the climax
♪ What everything's been
♪ Buil...
♪ Di-ing to
♪ Hope it pays off for you
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh.
(beeping)
What you got there, Homer?
Weird thing
under a tarp.
That's what I thought.
Have a good one. (laughs)
You laugh now, but
you won't be laughing soon.
He's right,
because now I go back
to remembering
that my cat just died.
He's in.
(knocking)
One sunrise
burrito, please.
Fine!
FEMALE VOICE:
Facial recognition required.
(high-pitched whirring)
Welcome, Mr. Burns.
(grunts)
Dad?
Huh? How'd you get in here?
Girl Scout cookies
get you in anywhere.
Please don't do this, Dad.
I don't know what horrors
you saw in Boise,
but it's not worth
blowing up everyone you love.
I'm not blowing up the plant.
(chuckling):
Oh.
Just harmlessly stopping it
from doing more damage
to Mother Earth.
Is that something
your terrorist masters
told you to tell me?
(sighs)
Yes.
My terrorist masters are always
talking about you, Lisa.
I missed my flight,
so I got in a van...
...with some eco-friendly
activists.
They wanted gas, grass or ass,
and, brother, I had the ass.
They taught me something
I found shocking.
Pigs aren't happy
to be made into pork chops.
This T-shirt lied to me.
And they also gave me
an alcohol detox.
♪ Nothing's shakin'
on Shakedown Street ♪
♪ Used to be the heart of town
♪ Don't tell me this town
ain't got no heart... ♪
Oh! Oh!
Oh, I've been listening
to this song for three days,
and it's only the end
of the first verse!
LISA:
But I saw you praying to Mecca.
Lisa, I've never prayed
to a city in my life,
and if I did, it would be
Hershey, Pennsylvania.
I was kneeling on the
affirmation rug they gave me.
See?
(rhythmically): Ow, this rug is hard
on my knees.
Ow, this rug is
hard on my knees.
Ow, this rug is hard
on my knees.
But wait, wait, wait.
What is this?
Lisa, the most horrible truth
of all is,
the plant where I work poisons
our water and our air.
I've told you that
a million times.
Aw, sweetie, you told me a
thousand things a million times.
Even with a brain
the size of a dinosaur's,
I couldn't take that in.
Anyhoo, this canister
is full of spoiled milk
and utility-grade chicken,
both sold to me by Apu
this morning.
When I release it
into the AC system,
it'll stink up
the plant forever.
No one can use it,
but no one gets hurt.
Just like
when I smell up the toilet.
(knocking)
(gasps) Huh?
(grunting)
(door opens)
There he is.
Use your fattest handcuffs.
Hey. Uh, it's not
what you think, Lou.
Lou, Lou, Lou.
(ululating):
Lou-Lou-Lou-Lou-Lou...!
(groans)
I can complete my dad's mission
just like George W. Bush.
I can't shoot a little girl.
(gunshot)
Ah, damn it!
There's some things
they just don't teach you
in the police academy... movies.
(distorted grunting)
(electronic trilling)
(rhythmic chugging)
We did it, Dad. We did it.
We sure did.
(grunts)
You weren't shot.
No, I was just up late
watching a movie.
Something with
William Holden and...
(snoring)
Your plan failed.
Thank God this
plant has never had
a functioning
air conditioner.
Wait a minute, Burns.
You don't have a functioning
AC system at a nuclear plant?
That's against the law.
That's impossible.
Smithers, didn't we move
this plant to China?
Sir, that's two years from now,
and you're not supposed
to tell anyone.
Oopsie.
There isn't a prison made
that can hold me.
Prisons are still made
of mud and wattles, right?
No. Concrete.
(gasps loudly)
You know, Dad, just because
your mission's complete,
it doesn't mean you have
to go back to pork eating
and beer... drinking.
A beer from the sky!
It's a sign!
(laughing)
Yeah, this equipment will pay
for itself
in one night of binging.
I wish a mission could bring me
closer to someone, but it can't.
Okay, it's time for me
to walk alone into the sunset.
(gulps loudly)
That's better.
(groans)
Amazingly, the hamster's
older than I am.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Shh!