Now the story of a wealthy family
who lost everything...
and the one son
who had no choice...
but to keep them all together.
It's Arrested Development.
Michael Bluth was taking his son...
to an interview at the prestigious
Milford School...
an institution
once famous for its credo...
that children should be
"neither seen nor heard."
"Woman."
They're not getting in.
- I might not get in either, and that
wouldn't be the end of the world.
- Shh.
We're not even going down
that road, okay?
The next four years
are all about your future...
and that's the most
important thing to me, okay?
Things have changed around here.
We have talking sessions throughout the day.
We even have a talking room
where students are encouraged...
to go in and talk
to their heart's content.
- Sounds like fun.
- First thing he's said all day.
The point is I'm not my father.
I do think it's best
for the Milford School...
to distance itself
from the Bluth name.
It's... nothing personal.
Are you talking about the fact
that my father is in jail?
Because I don't like to be
compared to my father either.
- I don't mind being compared to my father.
- Save it for the talk room.
- Sorry.
- I can assure you that my family
is back on track...
- and no longer in any trouble.
- Not according to today's paper.
Oh, God.
What have we done this time?
- Don't ever mention Klimpy's to me again.
- What did you do?
If I still had money, I'd buy a Klimpy's
just to burn it to the ground.
I know, Mom. You hate Klimpy's.
Tell me what happened.
Your sister and I tried to get into
that new restaurant, Rud...
and they wouldn't let us in.
Mrs. Bluth, there's absolutely no room.
Come on. I've suddenly lost my appetite.
Oh, who's going to believe that?
With her blood sugar at a perilous low...
Lucille made Lindsay pull into
the nearest restaurant.
Welcome to Klimpy's!
Anywhere you like!
This does not bode well.
- I'll have the Ike and Tina Tuna.
- Plate or platter?
- I don't understand the question,
and I won't respond to it.
- And what would you like?
- I'd like my old life back.
So there really was no fight?
Well, one tiny thing at the end.
- How can you treat me this way?
- Oh, please! Everything I've said about you...
can be covered with makeup
and a lie about a thyroid problem.
Good grief almighty!
You think I'm enjoying my slide into poverty?
Sorry, Lindsay.
There goes your dessert.
Why don't you eat it, Mother?
Why don't you just take this cake
and shove it...
Hey, who called the cops?
It was all just a big misunderstanding.
Totally blown out of proportion.
Well, listen, I think it cost George Michael
a chance to go to the Milford School.
Oh, big deal.
Buster's the only one who ever liked it.
Buster so excelled at being
neither seen nor heard...
that he remained at the school
undetected for a full two semesters...
after he was supposed to graduate.
Nonetheless, this bad press
is starting to taint my son's future...
and we've got to put an end to it.
Michael, if this is a lecture on how we're all
supposed to whatever and blah, blah, blah...
well, you can save it
'cause we all know it by heart.
- Good-bye, Missus.
- Lindsay, you'll be happy to know
that I have a new idea.
I met a publicist today.
I'm gonna hire her.
- We need somebody to make us look good.
- I say it's a waste of money.
We're plenty sympathetic as we are.
- Is this your onion?
- Yes.
- What's in the foil?
- Nothing. It's a ball of foil for my son.
Have a great day, sweetie.
I don't know how she can't.
So this publicist, Michael, is she cute?
I never really noticed.
- In fact, Michael
had noticed her at the gym...
but only recently gotten up
the nerve to talk to her...
giving him a chance to work
on his flirting skills...
- Race you to the top of the hill.
- which had gotten rusty over the years.
- I'll race you to the top of the hill.
- I brought a picnic lunch.
- Hey, that hill was really...
- Jessie Bowers.
If you ever have any
public relations needs...
My relations are already a little too public.
I'm Michael Bluth.
- From the Bluth Company?
- That's right.
I'm giving you my direct line.
Okay, sure. She's...
She's cute, I suppose.
I mean, now that you're making me
think about it, uh, she's cute.
She's a cutie. She's a little cutie pie.
But I never really noticed.
- Why don't you just ask her out?
- That's not an option.
- 'Cause you're scared?
- No, because of George Michael.
He still hasn't gotten over
losing his mother.
I just want to get him through high school;
then we'll deal with me.
So you didn't get any
while you were in high school...
and now you're not gonna get any
while George Michael's in high school.
And so the family gathered
at the model home...
eager to hear
their new publicist's plan.
- Get jobs and behave?
- Instead of us getting jobs...
why don't you do your job and
tell everyone we've got jobs?
- I have a job.
- Kiss ass.
Well, we were all thinking it.
Uh, I'm unclear about
what it is exactly you do.
Excellent question.
A publicist...
No, no. I was talking
to George Michael.
When did you get a job?
- At the banana stand.
- Oh! Duh.
I thought you meant like
a plumber or something.
And I was like, "When did that happen?"
Jessie, why don't you just
go ahead andjump in here.
It's a tough group
to keep focused.
I'm going on the offensive.
I want to get an article in the paper...
to show that this is a functional family
and a relatable family.
Are we on? Hello!
Hello from prison!
Thanks toJessie
for setting up this telelink.
I've started a Torah study group.
I'm very excited about it.
Looks like... I don't know... looks like
I have some possible converts.
Your father's religious now?
We'll play that up.
- It's very sympathetic.
- Yeah. Who doesn't love theJews?
And it allows me to put
Michael front and center.
He needs to be
the new face of this family.
He's the only likable one
in the bunch. No offense.
- None taken.
- I'm sorry.
Isn't Michael the least likable one
in the family?
No. There are very few intelligent...
attractive and straight men
in this town.
Well, that certainly leaves me out.
She... She said single.
You did say "single," correct?
I thought l...
I didn't quite hear that.
The reception is bad.
But as the Talmud tells us...
...to the jackal as to an oxen.
Did it get a laugh?
Sorry. I'm still on the whole
Michael being likable thing.
You know that he's only had sex
with, like, four women, right?
Let's focus on your likability.
You're going to start doing
some charity work with your magic.
Actually, I'm kind of
the charitable one of the family.
- I think it's best if you got a job.
- Oh, come on!
I'm a parent. I care about my daughter every
bit as much as Michael cares about his son.
What grade am I in?
- What kind of job?
- Something where you'll be seen.
I represent Cloudmir Vodka...
and they want someone to promote it
by ordering it at a hot bar.
- A place like Rud.
- Okay. I'll do it.
And, Tobias,
you're a medical doctor...
and you're living an absurd fantasy
as an actor.
- It's time to get real.
- Wow.
It's tough talk, but I like it.
You're saying land a major film.
I'm saying get your medical license back.
I've set up a hearing
for tomorrow in Boston.
- Michael has generously donated $1,100
for your trip.
- I'm sorry.
I truly believe that the universe wants me
to be an actor and not a doctor.
- I'm just waiting for a sign.
- Here's your cash.
- Universal Shuttle picks you up at 8:00.
- Any sign, really.
Sorry. Some of my students
are arguing the significance...
of the shank bone
on the seder plate.
But that... Not... not wag our genitals
at one another to make a point.
- Thought provoking.
- And, Lucille, people think you're cold.
Hanukkah can be spelled so many ways. Oh, God!
- Buster.
- Right here. Ready to go.
At your service.
Get me out there.
I want you to stay in.
People find you
odd and alienating.
You make them uneasy.
Stay out of the spotlight.
I shall be neither seen nor heard.
Watch me.
You can always tell a Milford man.
Each with their new charge...
the Bluths set about
redefining their image.
Tobias was off to Los Angeles
International Airport...
determined to return
to his family with a career.
Well, this is great.
Why would anybody take a limo?
What is this, like, $12?
Why would anybody pay more than $12
to go to the airport?
Next stop, LAX.
Come on! We're stopping again?
How many more stops are we gonna make?
Honestly, I haven't even seen
this part of Los Ang... Is that snow?
Really, now. This is ridiculous.
I paid 12 American...
Oh, my God.
You are Carl Weathers, the actor.
I went to San Francisco to attend
your stage fighting workshop.
- But you never showed up.
- I got bumped from that flight.
Hell, they'll give you $300
if you get bumped.
It's this crazy loophole in the system
that the wrong guy discovered.
Guess where I won't be going.
Yeah. So...
I am an actor too.
- Oh. Good.
- Well, I want to be.
Without the proper training,
I'm afraid I'm doomed to be a doctor.
Well, hell, I can train you.
Oh, well, I'm afraid
all I have is $1,100...
and that's for this plane ticket, so...
Check this out. $1,100 is exactly
what I charge for acting classes.
- No, it isn't!
- Yeah.
What are the chance...
Universe, you've done it again.
Meanwhile, Gob was beginning
his charity work at a local nursing home.
I'm gonna need a volunteer
for my next illusion, the Aztec Tomb!
- A tomb?
- Or box. Box is... fine.
Oh, yes! Well, excellent.
Let's get you in the box.
There's a panel.
just flip it around, curl up behind it,
don't make any noise.
Ancient lore has it the Aztec gods
put a curse on any man who dare...
- What?
- He's gone.
Buster was also
doing his share for the family.
And Michael, atJessie's insistence,
was out on the town.
I haven't been out to dinner in so long,
I feel a little guilty.
You have nothing
to be guilty about.
You're the only one in your family
who's ever been responsible.
Well, I'm certainly the only one
that's ever held a real job.
Oh, really, Michael? Watch this.
Wow! This Cloudmir's
making me think fuzzy.
I have almost no judgment at all.
- Two more Cloudmirs, please.
- "Only one with a real job."
jessie, you've really been doing
a great job with my family.
- Oh, good. Get one of Michael and me on a date.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
A date? This is a date now?
I thought this was just business.
Can't it be a little bit of both?
How will I know
which part of it is business?
Uh-oh.
Can't wait to see
which part of it is a date.
Show me business again.
What you doing?
just trying to get the TVworking.
Oh, yeah, I tried that earlier.
I think it's still hooked up to the prison.
So when those guys kept saying,
"Hey, you, boy," that was me?
- I was the boy?
- Sounds like it.
Have you told your dad
you don't want to go to that school?
I'm thinking of just going. I mean,
the graduates go on to do great things.
I suppose, but that means we won't
be going to the same high school.
Man, it just keeps getting worse.
- But he's my Dad.
I don't want to disappoint him.
- Man.
You and I are so different.
It's like we're not even related.
That'd be amazing.
Oh, my God.
- Hey, buddy.
- Hey, Dad.
I'm sorry that I'm so late,
but I was with Jessie.
This girl's making some serious progress
in getting you into that school.
She just booked Gob a gig
at Earl Milford's nursing home.
- You're gonna be a shoo-in.
- Oh.
She's kinda something, isn't she?
Yeah, I guess.
I mean, you know, hey,
she is no replacement for your mom.
- Oh, no. No way.
- Not at all.
- She's just working for us.
You're not dating her.
- No, I am not dating her.
Absolutely not dating her.
just you and me.
The Bluth boys.
Bluth boys.
- Good night, buddy.
- Good night.
- Hey.
- Is he in bed?
- He's on his way.
Hey, listen, listen,
listen, listen.
This might be moving
a little bit too fast for him.
I mean for... for us.
Me. Uh, for me.
Maybe we should
take a step back...
and just keep
this relationship professional.
- Oh, I think that would take all the fun out of it.
- No. Seriously, seriously.
You're amazing...
- but I just think we should slow down.
- Uh-huh.
So the two months on the bike,
that was, what, for my health?
We had great conversations.
- Seriously, this is hard for me.
- This is hard for me too.
I've got a life to get on track,
and I don't like wasting time, so let's do this.
Let's take two steps back...
and why don't you find yourself
a new publicist.
jessie.
No. I was just saying your name
as you walked away. I didn't...
I have no follow-up.
Jessie.
Michael felt bad...
- but he felt even worse
when he got a call from his brother.
- Hello.
It's Gob. I'm looking forJessie.
- She just left. What's wrong?
- I need her to spin something for me.
Well, that's too bad
because I think she quit.
- What do you need her to spin?
- Murder.
Michael was summoned to help his brother.
- Murder, huh? Who died?
- My career.
- I'm going to go home now.
- I lost a guy.
I put him in the Aztec Tomb,
and he disappeared.
- Isn't that the point?
- This will ruin me.
- He's probably fine. He just escaped.
- No! I need Jessie!
Well, she quit when I told her
that I couldn't go out with her.
You know, I have to do
the right thing for my son.
Then you better get her back
because the guy I lost was Earl Milford.
- What?
- I didn't know it was him.
Although he was
spectacularly quiet in there.
You can always tell a Milford man.
Gob, have you destroyed my chance
at getting my son in that school?
Not with the right spin.
jessie. Get her back.
Charged with the task
of renewing his medical license...
Tobias was enjoying his first acting class
with Carl Weathers.
I don't know what your police captain
told you about me...
but I'm a different breed of cop.
I'm from the streets,
and I'm the last cop...
you're ever gonna wanna
mess with in a darkened alley.
Dark alley. And l...
Listen, Mr. Weathers,
I don't know.
Perhaps my wife was right.
I don't know if I'm cut out to be a...
a De Niro...
or a Regis or a Pinkett-Smith
or what have you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Tobias.
Dreams are worth fighting for.
Now, are you gonna be a fighter,
or are you gonna be a doctor?
You're right, Carl Weathers.
I should just march into that restaurant
where my wife works and tell her...
Your wife works in a restaurant?
Do they get a shift meal...
or do they just pay half-price
on select menu items?
- I don't know.
- Well, let's find out, man.
And the press got hold of Gob's story.
- Where is Earl Milford?
- l... I don't know, all right?
I put him in a box.
I didn't kill him, all right?
And don't edit this for your broadcast
so it looks like I'm screaming...
"I killed Earl Milford."
Startling confession,
tonight at 11:00.
Minutes later, Gob unloaded his equipment...
and made a surprising discovery.
Don't send me back.
They abuse us. It's not pleasant.
Earl, I have to take you back.
- It's the only way to clear my name.
- You'll have a new name:
- Hero.
That could work for me.
Meanwhile, Jessie decided
to pay George Michael a visit.
Hi, George Michael.
Proud of yourself?
Yeah. I got a bum away from the stand
without hurting his feelings.
- That was pretty sweet.
- No. I mean about your father.
About denying him
his chance to be happy.
You're into that too?
I'm rubbing off on you, huh?
No. I want my dad to be happy.
It's too late now.
I've seen to that.
Daddy lost his shot at happy,
and it's all your fault, Opie.
Jessie had gone too far,
and she had best watch her mouth.
Michael's about to become
the most unlikable man in town.
Check the papers.
She kind of reminds me of my mother.
And later that night,
Lindsay was working at Rud.
You seem like a man of taste and class.
I'll give you $2,000 to touch me.
Oh, my God. My husband.
You're married to Carl Weathers?
What's going on? Why are you here?
Why aren't you in Boston?
- Who's he?
- His name is Carl Weathers,
and he's my new acting teacher.
And, Lindsay, he's teaching me
all these valuable life lessons.
- I buy all my cars at police auction.
- He's full of stuff like that.
And, Lindsay, he's teaching me
to follow my dreams.
Give me a bourbon.
Any room on that tab
for me to jump on?
And Michael caught up with Jessie.
Listen, thanks for coming.
I was just...
I was doing some thinking.
You know, I pulled away,
and that was wrong.
- I really want to make this work.
- Get away from my son!
Hey, Mom.
Kind of on a date here.
You'll change your mind after this.
And Michael saw the story
thatJessie had planted.
Let me tell you something, sweetie.
We may pick on each other,
get into little scrapes...
call each other names and
occasionally steal from each other...
but that's because we're a family.
You have no right.
You don't get to do that.
"Lindsay's a combative,
entitled princess"?
I should hire somebody
to kick your ass for that.
- Save your money.
- Yeah, you're right. I'll do it myself.
Hey, whoa! We are not settling things
like that anymore, all right?
- I don't need my son reading about us
in the paper.
- Oh, you and your son.
Stop using him as an excuse
for everything you do.
- I saw him today. He's fine with us.
- What? You saw him today?
Yeah. I told him he was getting
in the way of your happiness.
You did?
You said that to my son?
Yeah.
You're on your own.
Ladies?
Food fight!
What are you doing?
Oh, my face!
I'm gonna get you guys!
Stop!
The press is having a love affair...
with hating the Bluth family...
and they were the center
of another brawl this evening.
I'm looking at $50,000 worth
of medical bills here.
It looks like you won't be getting into
this school. Are you disappointed?
Well, are you disappointed?
Look, George Michael, I want you
to tell me how you feel, okay?
I don't want you to worry so much
about hurting my feelings.
I didn't want to go to that school,
and Jessie's a psycho.
That could've saved us
a little bit of time.
But, Dad, if you ever want to date
anyone else, that's fine with me.
Yeah? Thanks, buddy.
- 'Cause you know, I mean,
four women, that is kind of sad.
- All right. Thank you.
I know you got married in college,
but that was your sophomore year.
- You had your whole freshman year to...
- That's enough honesty for now.
- Thank you. Good night.
- There must have been girls at parties.
On the next
Arrested Development.
Gob holds a press conference
ofhis own.
And, now, prepare
to call me "hero."
He's resting, so...
Oh.
Pick a card.
Oh, boy.
And Buster moves
to the kitchen.