Can you believe
that they found them?
They had caught the robbers to find out
that there were so many people involved,
makes me feel like I can't trust anyone.
[Kim] I have to go to New York
to go meet with, like, the French judge.
[Khloe] Mom, a reoccurring theme
is that you seem to, like,
not do anything with us.
Like, we want to bond with you.
[Kim] Scott brought a girl out here.
Yeah.
This makes me really anxious.
[Khloe] Oh, my God.
[Kourtney] I just don't want Khloe
to cause a big scene.
[Kris] I think what we're wondering
is if you have a girl here and why.
[theme music playing]
[Kris] I think what we're wondering
is if you have a girl here and why.
Um, obviously we're both trying
to move on.
-That's what we've all been saying.
-Mm-hmm.
So I'm trying to do
everything I can [bleep] do
to not think about her.
[Khloe] But on a family trip, don't you--
Listen, you can do whatever you want.
On a family vacation, don't you think
it's inappropriate, disrespectful?
Disrespectful to who?
To me.
-Really?
-And your kids.
And to all my family.
[Scott] All right, we obviously
never discussed boundaries ever.
Well, there's just something.
There's a level of respect
and appropriateness
that should just be known.
But apparently it's not.
[Scott] All right, so obviously, like,
I did something wrong,
as always, like…
Well, this,
you flew someone out of the country.
[Kourtney] That is so disrespectful.
[Kris] Someone with any kind of integrity
would never do something like that.
Dude.
All she wants to do,
she says she's moving on. "I'm moving on."
-"I'm trying to get over you."
-[Kourtney] It's nothing about me.
But every night
you [bleep] go to bed with our kids
and I have to sleep alone,
sad and miserable. That's my life.
[Kris] You should be with us
at the house, that we have organized…
I'm not strong enough to do that.
This all just reminds me of a life
that we used to have.
[Kourtney] Stop playing the victim.
You had your chance.
I thought we were spending
our whole lives together
and I've done everything I can.
[Scott] That's fine.
I had to go back to a different lifestyle.
Then you shouldn't come
on our family vacations,
if you can't do four days
without bringing some random girl in.
It's just not cool.
[Scott] So let me [bleep] you,
then I won't have to do [bleep] like this.
You can't go four days?
No, I'm a sex addict.
I'm a [bleep] up, horrible sex addict.
So, how did you go in Aspen?
[Scott] I was [bleep] like crazy.
You know, saying I'm a sex addict
is honestly the first thing
that popped into my head,
and I don't really think
it's my actual problem.
But, you know, it's definitely not easy
hearing everybody attack me
and tell me how disrespectful I am
or I'm being.
And I don't know, literally,
what else to say.
[Khloe] If you need
to get your [bleep] wet that badly,
then get your [bleep] wet.
[Corey] I had a baby blue shirt on.
Get your [bleep] [bleep] wet
and there you go.
[Kris] Oh, boy.
[Scott] Oh, no. Hey!
[Kourtney laughing]
-[Kim] That was for Dubai.
-[Kris] You know what?
I'm not mad at that.
You kind of deserved that.
Oh, no!
And think about it.
-Should we go?
-I guess.
All right, should we head home together?
No.
You and me?
[Khloe] I'm sorry.
I'm just, like, he's such a [bleep] liar,
I can't handle it.
[Kim] I threw one in his face.
-Why?
-[Kim] Water. I don't know,
just 'cause you did.
[both laugh]
[Khloe] You're walking with him?
You're walking with him?
-I think we're good.
-Yeah.
[Khloe] You've got
some new gel in your hair?
[Khloe] Listen, Scott,
don't [bleep] with us.
[Scott] That should be
the story of my life.
-[Khloe] We're un-[bleep]-able with.
-We're un-[bleep]-able.
But we really are [bleep]-able.
Have a good [bleep].
[Khloe] Shut up.
Wear a condom!
That actually made me feel better.
I definitely feel relieved
that we had that conversation at dinner,
and now I can move forward.
It's been, like, nonsense for ten years,
like, up and down.
So, this is, like, the final,
you know, door closed, we're done.
[phone chimes]
He said, "So, can I stay in your room?"
"I don't want to stay at this hotel."
"Now, you're right."
"I mean, I'm [bleep] gross."
"Like, what animal does this?"
"I just got to get over Kourtney somehow,
and I feel like the sicker I am,
the more she will never be with me,
and I can move on."
Oh, good excuse.
Say that.
[upbeat music playing]
[Mason] Hi, Dad.
[Scott] I missed you.
[Mason speaks gibberish]
[Scott repeats gibberish]
I definitely think
things got a little crazy last night
and the truth is I have no idea, really,
how the girls are gonna react today.
So, of course, I mean, I'm anxious.
[upbeat music playing]
You okay?
[Scott] Yeah.
Are you?
Did you like
that shower you got yesterday?
[Mason] What shower?
Your daddy got a shower.
I gave your… [laughs]
That sounds weird.
I threw water on your dad last night.
[Mason] Whoa.
Isn't that so crazy of KoKo?
[Mason] I want to do that.
[Khloe and Scott laugh]
Trust me, there will be a time.
It's totally hard to stay mad at Scott,
but also Scott and I were texting
the whole night.
He was so remorseful
and felt like a piece of [bleep].
So, like, what am I gonna do?
Like, kick someone when they're down?
It's like, he already gets what he did.
[Scott] So, we're good?
Okay, we're good.
So you had a nice night?
No.
[Khloe giggles]
We ruined it?
-Yeah.
-We know how to ruin things
from a distance.
[Khloe] Hey!
[Scott] There she is.
So hot.
[Khloe] I cannot wait to go to the beach.
[Mason] I can't wait to go to the beach.
We're going tomorrow.
[Mason whoops]
Chill day!
[Khloe] Want to go to the beach, too?
Yeah, you do. Right?
What's wrong with you today?
Regardless of the fiasco
that happened last night,
I am not gonna let a little drama
get in the way of a beautiful trip
that I have planned.
We are gonna be taking some helicopters
and going to a second location
and we're sleeping there.
So, chip, chop, we're still on track.
Take off, baby!
[helicopter blades whirring]
[upbeat music playing]
-[Scott] Welcome to The Springs.
-[Khloe] There's a volcano.
Look how gorgeous this is.
We're in the jungle.
[Kourtney] Living the dream.
[Corey] It's pretty pretty, huh?
[Khloe] Keeks?
I've played that game, too, before,
-that I-can't-open-the- door game.
-You ready?
[Kim] I don't know if I want to go.
'Cause I didn't know
that you go in an inner tube,
I thought
we were going white-water rafting
in a big boat.
So, I didn't know we were getting wet.
How would you not know?
[Kim] To know that you go in a inner tube.
I didn't know that.
[Khloe] I know that Kim
is one of the biggest scaredy-cats
of all time.
But we came all this way
to do something as a family.
Look, when on earth do we get
to be in Costa Rica, tubing,
through a rainforest?
I just think it sounds so incredible.
-Kim.
-[Scott] Go tubing.
[Kim] I'm just not gonna go.
I'm not gonna be forced to go.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloe] Look at how good my boobs look
when I do this.
Somehow make it go like this,
'cause my boobs look really good.
Hi.
Mom, what are you doing
in your rocking chair?
We get it, you want to think you're old
[Tyga] You wouldn't look right.
You young'uns go have fun.
I feel nice and at home here.
[Khloe] First, Kimberly
doesn't want to go tubing,
and now my mom wants to bail, too.
[stammers] I'm over it.
Whoever wants to come tubing, come tubing.
I'm all down for it.
[Guide] Everybody ready to have fun?
-[Khloe] Yes.
-[Guide] Ready, crew?
Bye, Mart. Wish me luck.
[Scott] Later, Marty.
Wish me luck, Mart.
Oh, my butt's in the water.
[Kris] Oh, there goes my family.
We'll see you later, Mase.
I left everything to you.
You're rich.
[Khloe] Guys, it's so pretty.
[Kourtney] This is gorge.
[whooping]
[screaming]
Oh, my goodness.
[Khloe] Oh, my God.
[Tyga] So cold.
[bleep]
[Kylie] Oh, no.
Oh, no, no.
[screaming]
[Khloe] Oh, [bleep].
[laughing]
Oh, my God.
[Scott] Oh, my God.
[Corey] Remember that [bleep]
you used to ride at White Water
at Six Flags?
This is the real [bleep].
[laughter]
-[Khloe] Kim would have liked this.
-I know.
Mom would have liked it, too.
You want to see me jump
from there into here?
Guys!
[cheering]
[Scott] Cannonball!
Y'all got to admit that was fun.
-Y'all got to admit.
-[Khloe] That was fun.
-[Scott] Let's check that off the list.
-[laughing]
[Kris] How was it, Kourt?
[Kourtney] So good.
You would have loved it.
Really?
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Hey.
[Kris] I would appreciate it
if no one peed
while we were in here, please.
[Kourtney] It's a hot spring.
It's really good for your skin.
It's good for your psoriasis.
[Kris] It is?
Do you think you could get me
some more water?
Thank you so much.
I'm really thirsty.
Thank you.
[mysterious funny music playing]
[Khloe] Mom, what are you doing?
[Kris] Nothing.
[Khloe] Yeah, you are.
She's, like, filling up all these bottles.
[Kris] If it cures your skin,
and I can get rid of psoriasis,
I would do just about anything.
[Kim screams]
Stop!
Stop.
[Kourtney] You want to do the raft thing?
[Scott] Do it.
[Kourtney] Come on, I'm gonna do it, too.
[screams]
[Scott] Oh, my God.
[Kourtney screaming]
[Kourtney] It's not that far!
[Mason screams]
[laughing]
[Kourtney] Mase, how was that?
[Mason] Good.
[Scott] Give me some, Martin.
Come on, Mart.
[Kourtney] Scott's so lucky,
because I'm the coolest baby mama,
like, on the planet.
Like, the stuff that he's done,
and I still allow him to come
on our family trips,
because he's the father of my kids
and I want him to have
these great memories
and experiences with us.
But I just feel like I need to have
a conversation with Scott,
just to finally say, like,
"We will never be back together."
And it's probably better for both of us.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kris] This is so beautiful, you guys.
We're, like, in the middle of the jungle
having dinner.
[Khloe] I thought the inner-tubing
was so fun today.
That was fun.
You would definitely have liked it, Mom.
[Kim] So, I do not want to go to New York.
-[Kourtney] What are you going for?
-[Kim] To testify
against the robbers.
[Kourtney] Are they there now?
No.
I bet they'll just show me photos.
[Khloe] Does that make you uncomfortable?
[Kim] I just would feel uncomfortable
if I put someone in jail for a long time
if-- I couldn't see them.
I mean, they literally had ski masks.
I thought you said
that you saw their eyes.
No, there was one moment
where I said, "If you get out of this,
like, look into his eyes,"
so when he came so close to my face
and he just said, "You okay, shh, shh."
Like, shut the [bleep] up
and you'll be okay.
So, I was, is there anything
I can see, see, see, see,
and then you just don't think about it.
[Kris sighing] I need some stress relief.
[Kim] Wait, so you just took that
from the hot spring?
I figured I'll take it
and spray it on my psoriasis.
I think I need it for my psoriasis.
Here, try it.
It'll make you feel younger.
Should I spray it on my little…?
[Kris] Yes.
Ooh, where are you spraying it?
[Kylie] It hurts.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloe] Should we do same seaties?
[Kris] Hi, Khloe, good morning.
[Khloe] Good morning.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[all cheering]
[Kris] Hi, guys!
Hey!
[Kourtney] Do we walk
or drive to the beach?
[Khloe] I'm so excited.
The beach is all I've been dreaming about.
[Kris] Now, what's this little boat
-out here?
-[Kourtney] What is it?
[Kris] I think we found
a paparazzi boat, Khlo.
-[Khloe] Awesome.
-[Kris] Two of 'em.
When you travel so far to relax
and be with the family and really try
to get away from everything,
the last thing you want to do
is find pictures
on the Internet of our vacation.
So to see them right out there on a boat
with a big-ass lens is unnerving.
It'll be interesting to see
if they follow you guys over to the beach.
[Khloe] So, who's going to the beach?
[Kim] I feel like
it's gonna be paparazzi city,
so, I just, I don't feel like doing that.
[upbeat music playing]
[kids laughing]
[Kim] Okay, so what is going on?
[Khloe] These just aren't
what they used to be.
We don't do group--
everyone is so concerned
about all these other things now,
which I get, it's our new way of life
and it's honestly
a really [bleep] up way to live.
Yeah.
[Khloe] Like, I go on these trips
hoping we're gonna bond, and I thought
these were, like, more memories
and experiences,
and I am learning
that the older we're getting,
it's just not working out that way.
So I want to know why.
I just think
that your personality is negative.
You're like, "Everyone is so negative,
everyone is so this,"
but you're the only one being negative.
You get what you give out from me.
But you're, like, hostile about it.
[Khloe] When Kim flips the script on me,
I feel like she's Scott.
Like, not taking accountability.
Like, look at how much effort
and time and everything
that I've put into this,
because I really wanted all of us
to hang out and build memories.
Like, how the [bleep] is that wrong?
Because I haven't seen Kylie on this trip.
Don't know
what the [bleep] my mom is doing.
Kourtney is [bleep] playing
Play-Doh with the kids.
It's, like, okay.
So what did we come here for?
Look where we're at.
Like, we're in a beautiful place.
Everyone relax and enjoy themselves.
[Kim] I'm relaxing. I am chilling.
[Scott] I just [bleep].
Oh, Scott, no. Hello. You come here.
-She's saying all I do is complain.
-[Scott] That's all of you.
-I feel bad. It sucks.
-I feel like let's enjoy ourselves.
-[Scott] I agree, just…
-But you don't have to be--
You're just snappy about it.
[Khloe] Please tell me how,
-when I never had an issue with you…
-You're just snappy back.
…except for…
Like, there's no other word
besides "snappy."
[dramatic music playing]
If you think I'm sensitive
or know I'm sensitive,
why don't you become sensitive to that
and my feelings?
Actually be kind.
Don't go ahead and then keep egging me on.
'Cause now you're like [bleep] annoying.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Scott] Mase, you like Costa Rica?
-[Mason] Yeah.
My dream is that I want KiKi to be good
so we can go to the… to the ocean.
[Scott] Wait, I thought we were.
No, 'cause Kimberly doesn't want to,
-so we're not going to the beach.
-[Scott] What? I thought
that was the point,
we got back here today.
So I said, "[bleep] it,
I'm gonna lay out."
[Scott] Wow… this is horse manure.
[Kourtney] Khlo, there's a pap boat
down there.
[Khloe] I really don't care.
[Kourtney] Oh, is that the green tea?
[Scott] Yeah, I'll get it for you.
Thank you.
[Khloe] Don't spit.
[Kourtney] You're disgusting.
[Scott] We're still getting married,
though, no?
I think something
I've learned on this trip
is that we need…
[Scott] Yeah?
…to just move on.
[Scott] Perfect.
You've driven me nuts for ten years.
There's not anything bad
you can say about me.
Stop pushing your ass out
and [bleep].
[Kourtney] I'm scratching my back.
[Scott] Okay. You know what you're doing.
What have you done?
For ten years?
[Scott] Bothered you, too.
[Kourtney] Bothered?
Is that what you call it?
I think the moral of the story
is we are never getting back together.
[Scott] Done.
That's all I've ever wanted you to say.
[Kourtney] I think
after everything that's happened
here in Costa Rica,
Scott knows that it's done,
but just saying those words,
just, like, let's both of us move on
and just feel like, okay, it's done.
You know there's one person
you're allowed to shoot in the pool.
-[Penelope] Who?
-[King] What?
[Kourtney] Uncle Scott.
Yeah, King!
[King] I forgot his name.
-You forgot his name?
-Oh, you're coming?
[Kourtney laughing] No.
You forgot his name.
Oh, there's my little girl.
I get you!
-[Kourtney] P, stay…
-[Scott] Let's throw you over!
Say bye to the nice guy.
[Kourtney yells, laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Hello?
[Kris] Hi.
That's a cute top.
-You're all Chaneled out.
-It's a bathing suit.
Oh, that's so cute.
With a…
-[Kris] Oh!
-…Chanel.
You're just like a little Kris
in the '80s, aren't you?
[Kim] Yeah.
[Kris] What's up, guys?
[Kim] Um, I wanted to come up here
and talk to you
because I really feel bad for Khloe.
We just got into, like, a really big fight
-and she, like, stormed off.
-Aw.
[Kim] She said, you know,
we used to always come on these trips
and they were so much fun and now, like,
they're just not that fun anymore
and maybe we shouldn't go anymore,
and that was just, like, super hurtful.
Khloe's always been really sensitive.
Like, it's wild.
Maybe she thinks
we're moving on in life
because we have kids and this and that,
-and what, like…
-And then she acts like a [bleep]
-and then alienates us even more.
-Then no one wants to hang out.
Yeah.
Self-sabotage.
[Kim whispering] Yes.
I think as everybody grows up,
that everybody experiences
something different,
but if she's not having any fun,
then let's change that.
I feel like we should go talk to her.
Okay. Come on, Kourtney.
Khlo-mo!
Where's my little piece of sunshine
in your yellow bathing suit?
[Kourtney] I like yellow on you.
[Kim] That's your color, for sure.
[Kris] So I was just talking to Kim,
and she was telling me
that you weren't feeling like
this trip was going
the way that you would have wanted it
to go.
And we're not spending enough time,
all of us, together.
[Khloe] It's just interesting
how I don't see you guys a lot,
and I take the time to come here
thinking "Oh, great, this is, like, time
where I get to be with my sisters
and, you know, my nieces and nephews,
and do all these things."
This house is absolutely extraordinary,
but, like, going to the beach
and, like, just doing--
when will I ever go
to a Costa Rican beach?
I don't know.
Kylie and Tyga are locked away
in their rooms,
you and Corey are doing
whatever you and Corey do,
you don't like to do any activities.
[Kris] I love to do activities,
-believe me.
-Kim has her things
-where she's…
-[Kim] Just 'cause I was afraid
of the white-water raft? What's the point
of making it not fun for us
to want to hang out with you
-if you're always snappy?
-No one hang out with me,
[Kris] We want to hang out with you.
You're the funniest,
most fun girl we know.
-[Kim] It's not that, just--
You've ruined my mood already today,
so, you guys could all get away from me.
[Kourtney] What can we do to have fun?
-I don't know.
[Kim] It is so annoying
that you're so snappy.
[Khloe] No, I'm over all you people now.
Ungrateful family members that I can't…
[Kim] This is what I can't handle--
you're just so [bleep],
you're so annoying,
but it's like, "Shut the [bleep] up."
You're the negative one
just saying how awful we are
and how this-- You're like a big bully
that bullies all of us.
You people.
You bully us people.
[Khloe] I want us all
to [bleep] spend time together.
How am I at fault for that
and how is that a bad thing?
I still don't understand that.
But at some point
you have to say "[bleep] it"
and just not try anymore.
[Kim] Truly, Khloe is really annoying.
Like, we went out there to say
I'm sorry, you know, Kourtney and Scott
have each other with the kids,
I'm with the kids, like I get it.
And she's just like, "Nothing!
No! I'm-I'm mad 'cause this!" You know.
I feel like you guys
just always are getting on each other
for everything.
But she can't just be like, "Okay, reset…"
[Scott] Reset is the best button ever.
[Kim] Totally, like…
[Scott] I'm super into it.
[Kim] Yeah. Can't do it.
[Scott] Maybe it's time for you
to end this whole Kardashian thing.
Maybe it's becoming a curse
for the girls, too.
Just break up and all do your own thing
for a little bit.
[Kim] Good advice.
[Scott] See, you don't want to.
Everybody's got a little bit of a reason
why everybody's mad at each other,
but I think
everybody wants the same thing.
-Yeah.
-You have your crap,
she has hers.
You want to try to have fun,
but you have fun a different way
than she does,
and you worry about stuff
a little bit more,
maybe that frustrates her.
[Kim] I know Khloe put in so much work
to plan this vacation
and spend time with us
and all of our families,
so I don't want Khloe to feel separated
or just, you know, like, alone.
I don't want to ruin this trip
over a stupid fight.
All I know is,
I don't want to be in the middle.
I don't need this [bleep] in my life.
I already have
one little bully in my life.
-[Kim] All right.
-I'm going to go hang out with Khloe
and make pretend
I didn't have this conversation.
[dance music playing]
[Joe] How are you feeling? Not tired?
[Khloe] A little tired.
[Joe] Okay, let's do this.
-Lift. Two.
-[Khloe groans]
[Khloe] Ever since the fight,
I'm just gonna do what I want to do,
and, like, my happy place is the gym
so, even though we're on this vacation,
I'm going to work out.
[Kylie] Hey.
Hi.
I just wanted to give you
an intermission hug.
[Khloe] I'm all sweaty.
I have Snapchat glasses.
[Kylie] Snapchat glasses?
What?
[Khloe] Wait, come here.
[Kylie] So they Snapchat?
[Khloe] Watch, look.
Is it blinking?
-[Kylie] Yes.
-[Khloe] Hi, Kylie, you're on my Snapchat.
-[Kylie] How?
-[Khloe] 'Cause it's showing,
and then when it starts,
it's only ten seconds.
-[Kylie] And it's live?
-[Khloe] No, I get to approve it later
-and then push it through.
-[Kylie] Hey!
[Khloe] So I'm snapping my workout.
[Kylie] Khloe…
[Khloe laughs]
[Kylie] Always in cleavage.
[laughing] I just want to…
[all talking over each other]
[Joe] …three, one, okay.
[Khloe] This one has never worked out
a day in her life.
[Kim] Wait, I want to do this exercise.
[brass stabs playing]
[Khloe] You want to work out, too, now?
[Kim] I kind of do, but my shoes
are all the way upstairs and stuff.
I don't want to leave this trip
on a bad note with this fight.
I want Khloe to know
that I love that she took the time
and the effort to come on vacation with us
and plan this vacation,
so I'm going to make one last effort
to make up with Khloe.
[Kim] Wait, I want to do this exercise.
[Khloe] You want to work out, too, now?
[Kim] I kinda do, but my shoes
are all the way upstairs and stuff.
[Joe] Feel it. Two, one…
[Khloe] Oh, [bleep].
-[Kim] Wait, I want to try that.
-[Kylie] Want to do it?
You think that's the easy part.
Just wait till he starts pushing it down.
[Joe] Bend on your knee.
Okay, and from here, like, push up.
Okay, feel it.
[Khloe] Keep pushing.
Kylie and Kim in the fitness room with me.
This is honestly the peak of my trip.
-[Kylie] This is the peak of your trip?
-Yes, 'cause you are with me.
I swear to God,
this is the best time of my trip.
Working out and with them.
[Kim] We want to get on Khloe's level.
[Khloe] No, you guys,
this is the best part.
[Kim] I definitely wanted
to join the workout
just to hang out with you.
And I love that.
That's all I want is, like, family time.
I don't have to do something.
Doing nothing together.
-It's like, that's what life is about.
-Totally.
Watch. Now you push this,
and you're going to see,
like, a little light, and it's on.
[Kylie] Ew.
[Khloe] Ew!
[Kim laughing]
I wonder what this looks like.
I pray this [bleep] works.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Kris] Hey, babe.
-[Corey] Hey, what's happening?
[Kris] This is pretty.
[Corey] Yeah, it look like you.
[Kris] Aw. Who's that? Khloe?
[Khloe] It is so pretty.
-[Kris] Isn't this great?
-Oh, it's unbelievable.
But I do kind of feel like
I'm on The Bachelor,
and I'm going to get, like, my rose.
So, does someone have a rose for me?
[Kris] I asked them to set
this dinner up for us out here tonight
because I didn't want
another dinner on the patio.
[Khloe] You look gorgeous
with your hand on your hip, Kris.
[Kris chuckles]
It's so pretty here.
-[Kourtney] Hi.
-[Kris] Hey, Kourt.
[Khloe] Hi, Reigny.
[Kris chuckles]
Hey, T.
Kourtney.
There he goes.
He copied you.
[Mason] Daddy's here!
[Scott] It's a hike getting down here.
[Kris] Here they come
for their first number.
[all cheering]
The longest runway ever.
[Khloe] This food looks so good-- yummy.
[Kris] Babe, will you hand me
-one of those white things?
-[Kourtney] What's that? Potato salad?
[Kris] That looks good.
[Kim] Kylie, do you like or not?
[Kylie] Yeah, I don't mind.
[Kris] Okay, let's go around the table
and do the pit and the peak.
So, Kim…
-Kim?
-Yeah?
[Kris] We're gonna start.
What is your pit,
and what is your peak?
[Kim] My pit is that Kanye is not here.
And my peak
is that I get an amazing vacation
with the kids and my family.
[Kris] Kylie, what's your pit
and your peak?
I don't like being away from home,
that's my pit.
[Kris] You don't like
to be away from home?
[Kylie] My peak, I don't know,
being with you guys.
[Kourtney] What about tubing?
That was so fun.
[Kylie] That was cute.
[Kourtney] My peak was tubing
and doing the water slides,
and spending time with my kids and family.
[Scott] I think my pit was
that Mase didn't come tubing,
but my peak was
the water slides with the kids.
[Mason] Oh, yeah.
[Scott] That was fun.
-That was fun, Mase.
-You were good.
[Kourtney] And my pit was probably
the anxiety going
to the confrontational dinner.
[Kris] The pit of the trip is
that I couldn't do the tubing,
and I think the peak,
I love being all together
on any family vacay,
because it's memories we're gonna make
that are gonna last a lifetime,
so, I love these trips.
The one thing that we have as a family
is each other.
And nothing will ever change
the love and the bond that we all share.
And it's really nice
to come together on these vacations,
no matter how old the kids get,
and just reconnect.
Khloe, what was your pit?
[Khloe] The pit of my trip is
how so many people love to complain.
[Mason] Whoa, good idea.
[Khloe] Good answer, right?
I don't like complainers.
[Mason] Same.
[Khloe] And the peak of my trip
is that I loved inner-tubing together,
I loved seeing the volcano,
I loved our workout.
So I had kind of a lot of peaks.
And all the kids are having
-a slumber party in my room.
-[all cheering]
[Kris] Yay, Khloe!
[Kim] Can Northy do her peak and her pit?
-[Kris] Yes.
-Okay, what's your peak?
That's the best part.
[North] Giving hugs to you.
Aw.
Well, that's your peak.
[Khloe] Ooh, look, dancers.
[Kim] Oh, look at the dancers, bubs.
[Khloe] What are they doing, King?
-[Kris] How good is this?
-[Spanish music playing]
[Kris] Oh…
[all cheering]
-[Kris] Beautiful.
-[Khloe] Ooh.
[Kris] This is pretty.
[all cheering]
[Khloe] Oh, my. Everyone up.
Look, we can go dance.
We can do it together.
-[dance music playing]
-Northy, look at you.
[Khloe] Ooh. Come on, King.
[man laughing]
[Khloe] Whoo!
[Kris] Kourtney, do you want to dance?
[Kourtney] I'm not a good dancer.
[Tyga] You got a disclaimer.
[Khloe] Yay!
[all cheering]
-[Kris] Thank you.
-Say adios.
-[Kourtney] Can I Snapchat Mike?
-[Jen] Cute.
And say when Mr. Mike Rosenthal
is in Costa Rica.
Well, then I need to snap you, too.
Jen and Mike, when Mr. Mike Rosenthal
is in Costa Rica…
[Jen] I'm his assistant.
[Kourtney] We need
a late- night photo shoot.
[Mike] She a hard worker.
[Kourtney laughs]
[Kylie] Kourtney,
are you naked under this?
[Kourtney] Yeah.
[Kylie] So you really are getting naked?
[Kourtney] Yes!
What do you mean?
Kylie, I bet you can't fight.
Let's have, like, a fake fight, okay?
Just to see.
[Kylie] Okay. Fake fight.
[laughs]
[Kourtney] Wait, there's nothing
under my robe.
Ow!
[Kylie] This is not a fake fight.
[Kourtney] I have your vagina!
[Kylie] This is not a fake fight!
You punched me in my tit!
Ow!
-[Kourtney] Okay, what?
-[Khloe] Kourtney…
Do your shoot and focus.
[Kourtney] Oh, sorry.
[Friend] Kourt, take it off.
[Kourtney] Okay.
[Khloe] Kourtney!
[all cheering]
You're naked!
[Kim whoops]
[Jen] Get a bit more naked.
[Kylie] Can you take
your Cartier bracelets off?
[Kourtney laughs]
-[Mike] Beautiful.
-[Khloe] This is so good.
-[Mike] Oh, my God.
-[Khloe] So good.
[Jen] Kourt, you are giving life
right now.
[Kourtney] I'm just doing
what I've always loved to do.
[Khloe] I honestly was worried about you
after Penelope.
I did think, like, she's gone.
Worried for my soul?
Yeah. Now, she's YOLO'ing it up,
[bleep] bomb-ass body, naked in the pool.
And your sisters should be afraid of you.
[Kourtney snaps]
[Friend] Oh, my God! It's so good.
[Kylie] Wait, let me see.
[Mike] So…
[Kylie] What the [bleep].
I want to get in.
[Khloe] Kylie is getting jealous,
you guys.
[Kylie] I'm so jealous!
[Khloe] Yes!
[dance music playing]
[Joe] You ready?
We're gonna do the side. Cool.
One, two, three. Kim.
-[Khloe] Oh, Kim's here?
-Have we started?
Last night was the first night
I had nightmares.
[Khloe] About what?
[Kim] Just, like, about scary stuff.
[Khloe] Well, I'm sorry. That's not good.
[Kim] I started having a nightmare,
and then I was like, "Wake up."
And I, like, woke up…
[Khloe] I do those dreams.
Those are, like, more night terrors.
When, like, you can't wake up,
and you know you…
you know you're dreaming.
-And you're just, like…
-I couldn't, but I got up.
But I was, like, in it for a while.
But is it from your… trauma?
Not that specifically,
but a new one.
Because maybe your court date's coming up?
-Yeah.
-You probably have
anxiety you don't know about.
Yeah.
I have to fly to New York
to meet with the French judge
to give my whole testimony.
But I didn't really realize
how much it would affect me.
I just don't know
if I'll be able to relive
that night of what happened.
So, I'm just super anxious.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloe] Hi, P.
Can I have a hug good morning?
You look so beautiful.
[Penelope] Thank you.
[Khloe] You're welcome.
[Kim] Hey, everyone,
I'm getting in the car and I'm leaving.
[Kourtney] All right,
let's get everyone to pack it up.
[Khloe] Thank you so much. Thank you.
And I'll see you soon hopefully.
I did have a great trip
and I definitely would want to come
back here,
but probably
with a different group of people.
-Good for you.
-Yeah.
I'm happy for you.
[Khloe] I would go with you.
You and I have a good time together.
Yeah.
Good one, "Yeah."
I could literally just sit here
and be you.
-[imitates Kourtney] Yeah.
-[Kourtney chuckles]
-Thank you so much.
-It was a pleasure to have you.
[Khloe] Hello.
[Kris] Hi.
You guys, that was the best.
[Khloe] Yeah.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Northy, do you want to help me?
Which outfit should Saint wear?
Should he wear this one…
or this one?
[North] I like this coat,
and these shoes and this shirt.
Oh, but I was either thinking
this whole outfit here,
or this outfit here.
-I don't like that one.
-[knock on door]
[Kim gasps] Someone's here.
You want to get the door?
-[North] Mm-hmm.
-Okay, you go. You go.
Oh, my goodness.
My black swan.
[Jonathan] Hello.
[Kim] Say, "Hey!"
Oh, my God,
look who's the prettiest girl
in the whole wide world and New York City.
I'm, like, in my sweats.
-I like this jacket.
-Thank you.
I feel like I haven't seen you in a month.
[Jonathan] So, tell me why you're here,
I don't understand.
You're on trial here? I'm so confused.
No, we're here
because the judge needs me to… like,
they're still
in the investigation process,
so basically, they're gonna show me
pictures of everyone.
But you never saw their faces.
-Just voices?
-Yeah.
But I don't know what it'll trigger
when I, like, look at them.
Just knowing that they caught them
and that they will possibly bring photos,
I think, um,
that's just what gives me
the most anxiety,
is just to put faces
with the terror
that I, you know… went through
and just have to, like, put
all the pieces together now.
They're gonna have, like, weapons charges,
attempted murder…
-[Jonathan] Kidnapping.
-[Kim] Robbery and kidnapping.
[Jonathan] Is there gonna be,
like, one trial for them?
[Kim] There'll be a trial.
The judge is going to ask me to go,
but in the trial, they'll get an actress
that will be-- play me,
and actors to play the robbers,
and they have to act it all out
and have us watch it.
[Stephanie] Is that a normal thing?
-[Kim] I have no idea.
-[Stephanie] This sounds wild.
-[Kim] Right?
-[Stephanie] I've never heard
of something like this.
[Kim] And then we have to tell them
if that's what happened.
They want to feel the trauma of, like,
what's really gone on.
Oh, my God.
I think that they'll get bigger sentences
if you're at the sentencing.
I just don't feel safe,
I don't feel-- you know what I mean?
Like, why would I go
put myself through that?
[Jonathan] I think
you should [bleep] them.
Put those ass[bleep] in jail
for a long time,
which they deserve.
[Kim] I'm just nervous
if I have to, like, look at them
in their face…
-[Jonathan] You could do it.
-…In court.
I definitely respect their system
and they were so great
at finding everyone.
And I'm so willing to help
in any way that I can,
but having to reenact that night of what
happened,
I just don't know
if I would feel comfortable doing that.
[piano theme playing]
[car horns honking]
[dramatic music playing]
[car horn honks]
[cameras shutter clicking]
[line ringing]
[Kris over phone] Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
Just, uh, getting online
'cause Kylie has a launch
in a couple minutes.
Oh, fun.
Yeah.
Um, so I just finished
with my court date.
What happened?
I was there
until, like, literally from 10:00 a.m.
until 6:00 p.m.
Oh, geez, honey, I'm so sorry
you have to go through that.
It was just a really long thing
because, like, you have to explain it
to a translator, then the translator
has to explain it to the judge.
Then she writes it with the clerk,
then they have to read what you wrote.
You have to do it sentence by sentence.
Going in there, I was so worked up
wanting to, like, explain it so quickly
and you just can't do that.
You just have to, like, be really slow
and walk through the entire night,
like, second by second.
And that was just really hard.
So they showed me pictures of all of them.
[Kris] Oh, wow.
But, like, one guy
admitted to driving them,
and then, one inside admitted it.
I think it was really interesting
to see the faces of everyone.
Just by their height and weight,
I could tell who, from this lineup,
was in the room with me.
I was able to see who confessed.
One of them was the guy
that was in the room with me,
and it was very interesting
to hear his story.
And it was pretty similar to my story.
Of course, there was, like, a few things
that they're not saying
to get lesser charges.
But they were pretty honest
and did tell most of the story
exactly like how it happened.
So, um… you know, it's just--
it's really interesting to see
what their side of the story is,
and to hear the background information
about how they had been following me
and how they attempted to rob me
the last time I was in Paris.
But my husband was with me,
and there was too many people around me.
So, to hear that come out of their mouths,
you know, I had an idea
like, "Oh my God, my, you know, husband
just gave me a new ring,
and so they saw it,
and I posted it on social media."
Like, they had been following me
from the year before.
And so, what I had in my mind
of how the whole thing happened
was really different,
and it just is so scary to know
that this would have happened to me
at some point.
So I'm just, like, I'm really happy
that I got it over with
and it's, like, done.
Because, no matter what,
it would have happened to me. It just--
my awareness now of my surroundings
is so different and so heightened,
and, you know,
I'm honestly, like, thankful
for this experience
and that I have all the insider info
and background information now
on how they plotted and planned this,
so that I can prepare and protect myself
even more in the future.
[Kris] I'm sorry
you had to go through that, honey,
I really am.
It's all right,
one step closer to it being over.
Yep.
All right, I love you.
Okay, love you. Bye.
Coming up next week…
When's the last time
you've gone to Palm Springs?
[tires screeching]
Kourtney, you might be
the worst driver I've ever met.
Kourtney is a horrible driver.
Oh, [bleep].
The car broke down.
What are you doing?
I'm pushing, I'm really strong.
[car horn honks]
Oh, shut up, [bleep]!
Wait, what is this?
I got a letter from a royal family,
requesting to purchase my eggs.
Okay, now, that's weird.
Don't count me out yet.
[both laugh]