[Kris] Robert is being honored
on behalf of cancer research.
[Kim] We should do, like,
a tribute video for him.
-[Kourtney] For the Ball?
-[Kim] Yeah.
I just want everyone to see
what a great person my dad was.
21 shows canceled.
[Khloe] Seems like he needs a break.
I know how much he works. It's crazy.
[Kim] Hey.
What?
What's wrong? Don't scare me, please.
I-I can't.
[crying]
[Kim] Why? What's going on? What's wrong?
Don't scare me, please. What's going on?
I-I can't.
[crying]
I get a call from one of Kanye's friends,
and my heart drops.
But what is he, like...
This is, like, serious.
They're not telling me anything,
and I am so scared
and I don't know what to do.
Oh, my God, I just got to New York.
[exhales] I'm just, like...
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
He's crying on the phone to me,
and he just, like, wouldn't say
what's wrong and I'm like,
"Tell me what's wrong."
I just, like, don't know what to do.
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
[Kim] Hey. It's, like, so sad.
I just feel so bad, 'cause it's
gonna be, like, so public and,
like, I don't know if...
I can't be going to this Angel Ball.
I'm, like, here in New York.
You know what I mean?
I don't even know
what's going on right now.
It's getting pretty hectic at home,
and everyone's just getting,
you know, really worried.
[Kris] Do you want to go home tonight?
[Kim] I just like, don't know what to do.
But I think he really needs me,
and I have to get home.
-[Kris] Yeah.
-[Kim] That's the right thing to do.
[Kris] It is the right thing to do.
[Kim] I know this
was really nice to honor my dad
for the Angel Ball, but I know
that everyone involved will
totally understand my position.
I don't even think it's an option.
I have to get home.
-[Kris] I'm sorry, Kim.
-[Kim] It's okay.
[Kris] I really am.
Just can hardly believe it.
Are you gonna be okay flying by yourself?
-[Kim] Yeah, I'm fine.
I just need to get home.
[Kris] Yeah. I'm so sorry that you came
all this way. I feel bad now.
-[Kim] It's okay.
-[Kris] It was just...
[Kim] I thought it was
the right thing at the time.
-[Kris] I'd go with you if I didn't...
-[Kim] No, you stay.
[Kris] Because Kourtney
and Khloe can do this,
and I could go home with you.
If you want.
[Kim] No, it's fine.
[Kris] All right.
-Okay, I'm gonna go get dressed, then.
-[Kim] Okay.
[Kris] And text me
when you're about to leave
and I'll come give you a hug, okay?
Love you, Kimmy.
[Kim] Love you, too.
♪ ♪
[Kris] What time does Kim take off?
[Corey] Call her, she's probably...
Waiting on the runway about to...
-[Kris] Yeah.
-[Corey] If they haven't already.
[Kris] No, it's okay.
[reporters clamoring]
[reporters] Kris! Kris!
Khloe, one more time!
[indistinct chatter]
[Kris] We're here for Denise Rich
and the Angel Ball.
So we're very excited and
honored they're honoring Robert.
[reporter] And how is Kim doing,
will we see her tonight?
[Kris] Um, she's-- one step at a time,
you know? It's a process.
Um, I'm gonna run, but thank you so much.
As much as I wish Kim was here,
I'm glad the rest of us could stay
here to honor her father.
♪ ♪
[announcer] Every one of us knows somebody
extremely close to us
who has been affected by cancer.
-[Tommy] Gorgeous.
-[Corey laughing] All right.
[announcer] Every one of us
is deeply affected by this illness.
-[Tommy] No Kim?
-[Corey] She just had to get on a plane
and go back for a family emergency.
She just had to go deal
with a situation, so, she had...
she just took off to go back.
[audience whooping]
[Heliose] Wow. A huge heartfelt thanks.
As the late, great Michael Jackson said,
if you want to make this world
a better place,
then make the change.
Celebrity philanthropy, like tonight,
is an incredibly powerful force
to do good in this world.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's an absolute privilege
to recognize the late Robert Kardashian.
[whooping, applause]
[Robert] After 34 years,
I have finally realized
what true love is to me.
Caring about you, enjoying your laughter,
your tears and our joy.
Oh, Kourtney. Do you want to walk?
-[Kourtney] Hi, Papa.
-[Robert] Hi.
-[Kourtney] Watch me go around.
-[Robert] Okay.
Kourtney. Aw, Khloe.
Three.
[Khloe] Being at the Angel Ball
is an incredible honor.
It's a blessing to be here.
-[Robert] What a cute picture.
-[Kourtney] Cheese!
[Khloe] I know that Kim's overwhelmed,
but I know my dad is with her in spirit.
My dad has her back,
and she will be surrounded by strength.
[announcer] Please welcome
Kris, Kourtney and Khloe,
accepting in honor of Robert Kardashian.
[whooping, applause]
[Kris] Good evening, everybody.
When I met Robert Kardashian,
I was 17 years old.
One of the things he used to teach me,
and then passed down to our children,
was about philanthropy,
and what you make, you give back.
And I'm thrilled and honored--
my girls are honored--
that you honored Robert tonight.
So thank you so much. Thank you.
[applause]
♪ ♪
[Khloe] Hi.
[Kris] I'm gonna sleep
as long as I can,
since I got, I think,
40 minutes of sleep last night.
[Khloe] I mean I feel
super bad that, like, Kim...
has so much going on and then,
like, this is happening to her.
I just feel like, in our family,
it's, for some reason,
when it rains, it pours.
I'm sure that's with other people,
and I know it could always get worse,
but it seems like when someone's
having a hard time,
like, they have a really hard time.
I don't know why.
[Kourtney] I'm glad
that we're just on our way home.
No matter what,
we're just trying to be supportive,
and I just want to be here for my sister.
[Khloe] What did Kim say?
[Kourtney] She said
she just needed to sleep.
I mean, my heart's definitely
breaking for Kim.
I know that her and Kanye
have both been through so much this year.
With everything that just
happened in Paris and now this,
I just feel, like, heartbroken for her.
It just, like, never ends.
I'm just anxious.
♪ ♪
[Khloe] Tristan and J.R.'s turkey drive.
[Tristan] Damn right. How y'all doing?
-[JR] How are you?
-[man 2] Good, man.
-You haven't been to church.
-[Tristan] How y'all doing?
-[boy] I'm straight.
-[woman] Hi.
[Khloe] I stopped in Cleveland
from New York
for a turkey drive with Tristan.
He's so passionate about giving back
to the city of Cleveland.
[crowd cheering]
I really wanted to go back
to L.A. with Kim,
but she encouraged me to go to Cleveland
and stick with my commitment.
I really appreciate that,
but still I can't get out of my head
that I feel like my sister needs me.
-[Larry] Good evening.
-[crowd] Good evening.
[Larry] We want to thank a few people
before we get started.
We want to thank,
um, what's your name again?
[crowd laughs]
[Larry] We want to thank
our friend, Tristan.
[crowd cheers]
[JR] Give it up for your boy!
[Larry] We want to thank
my newfound friend, Khloe.
[crowd cheers]
[Tristan] I want to thank
the church community.
First of all, we love y'all.
Thank you so much.
You know, it's the holiday season.
Smile, I see you got your phones out.
Make sure you get a good picture of me.
[crowd cheers and applauds]
♪ ♪
-[Khloe] Happy Thanksgiving.
-[woman] Thank you so much.
[Khloe] It's incredibly hard being away
from my family,
especially at a time like this,
but to be able to experience something
that he's so passionate about
is an honor for me and I'm thrilled
to be able to do something like this.
[woman] I just want you to know
that we all appreciate this so much.
[Khloe] Of course, this is a blessing
and an honor.
[inaudible speech]
-[woman] Thank you again.
-[Khloe] Thank you.
♪ ♪
-[Mason] Look at me.
-[Khloe] How do you know to do that?
-[Mason] I can do it.
-[Khloe laughs]
-[Mason] It's easy.
-[Khloe] I like that.
Are you a one-woman man
or you like a few girls?
-[Mason] A few.
-[Scott] No.
[Khloe] I heard that you like a few girls.
-[Scott] That's not cool. One.
-[Mason] Yeah, one, one, yeah.
[Khloe] One. What does she look like?
-[Mason] Mm, blonde hair.
-[Khloe] Oh, good.
The last one looked exactly like Kourtney.
[Scott] What? With like a bob?
[Khloe] Just like long black hair,
dark skin...
-[Mason] No.
-[Khloe] She looked just like your mom.
-[Khloe laughs]
[Khloe] Oh, my God.
Anyway, how was Thanksgiving here, Scott?
[Scott] Yeah, I mean I feel
like Thanksgiving... it was cool.
The only thing that was a bit weird
was there wasn't a lot of people,
like that you weren't there,
Kanye wasn't there.
Kim came, but obviously
she was like, you know, pretty tired,
down and out
and it was, like, definitely awkward.
And I feel like everybody, like,
didn't want to say certain things and...
I don't know, it just felt
a little bit uncomfortable.
[Khloe] It's been a few days
since I've been back in L.A.
and I still don't know much
about Kanye's situation.
Kim just said, you know, give her
her space right now
and when she knows what's going on,
she'll let us know
and we can come and be by her side,
but she needs her space right now.
[Scott] Um, I feel like Kim's taking
everything as good as she can, right?
-[Khloe] Yeah.
-[Scott] My heart goes out to them.
You know, that's just really scary.
♪ ♪
[cell phone ringing]
[Kris] Hi, babe. Okay.
No, I was just wondering
when you're on your way back,
if you could, um...
[Kris recording] I was just wondering...
I was just, I was just wondering.
[Kris] ...if you could go to
the liquor store?
I need some of that tequila
that Cindy Crawford drinks.
Okay, bye. Hi, Kendall.
-[Kendall] Hi, Mom.
-[Kris] Are you starving?
[Kendall] Yeah.
[Kris] I just got a call
from the offices over at Vogue.
They're coming to review
the Kendall+Kylie collection in New York.
-[Kylie] I love it.
-[Kendall] Really?
-[Kendall] That's really cool.
-[Kris] This is such a big deal.
[Kris] This year, Kendall
and Kylie launched their new clothing line
called the "Kendall + Kylie" collection.
[Kendall] So exciting.
[Kris] Getting a review from 0
and having it be positive
would mean everything to the girls.
[Kylie] I'm excited, that's really cool.
[Kris] You should be proud.
The fact that they're giving you
this attention in year one...
Vogue usually does this after
a designer has established themselves,
even for years, before they go in
and Nicole Phelps is actually the one
coming to review the line.
[Kendall] That's terrifying.
[Kris] Nicole Phelps is the director
of Vogue Runway
and is a very important person to impress.
Is there anything you guys need
to do to prepare?
[Kendall] Kill myself.
It's a little nerve-racking.
Don't get me wrong, it is really exciting,
but this line is just
something very personal to Kylie and I
and if they don't like it,
I don't know how I'm gonna feel about it.
I'm nervous.
[Kris] You should be very flattered
that they want to see what you're up to.
-[Kylie] Well, no pressure.
-[Kris] Fingers crossed, ladies.
[Kylie] I should be your hairstylist.
[Kendall] Remember when Mom was spiky?
I love spiky mom. This mom.
[Kylie and Kendall laugh]
-[Kylie] You're talking about this mom.
-[Kendall laughing] Yeah.
[Kylie laughing] This was a cool mom.
[Kendall] But you know
what spiky I'm talking about, right?
I'm looking it up.
-[Kylie] Let me see.
-[Kylie gasps]
It's season one Mom.
[Kris laughs]
♪ ♪
[Khloe] I need a little candy.
When I was little, my grandma
used to give these to me all the time. Oh.
[Penelope chuckles]
Where'd it go?
-[Kim] Hi, P.
-[Penelope] Hi.
-[Khloe] Hi, Keeks, how are you?
-[Kim] Hi, guys. I'm good.
[Khloe] Give me a hug.
[Kim] I'm tired.
-[Khloe] I bet.
Are you okay?
-[Kim] Yeah, I'm just, like, exhausted.
-[Khloe] We've been trying to call you.
[Kim] I know, I just,
honestly, I haven't even, like,
had my phone for days.
[Khloe] Do we know anything?
Like, is everything gonna be okay?
[Kim] I'm not in the mood
to get into it right now.
I'm just, like, emotionally
just, like, drained and exhausted,
but it will be okay.
Everything'll be okay.
This is, like, forcing him just
to take much-needed time off,
which I think he just really needs.
-[Kris] Hey, guys.
-[Khloe] Hey, Mom.
[Kris] Hi.
[Kim] And, um, you know,
I think that that will be...
just really good for him.
But I feel like a sense of responsibility
just with the pressure
of taking care of everything
and even after, just,
like, the robbery and everything.
It's just I've been staying home
and I've been, you know, looking to him
just to take care of everything
while I stay home and...
[Kris] Yeah.
He's got so much incredible energy.
-He just gets so excited about everything.
-[Kim] He just can never take time off.
[Kris] Yeah. And he doesn't like
to take time off.
[Kim] Yeah. I think sometimes
in life you just need some time off.
[Kris] Yeah. Yeah.
-[Kim] I'm just, like, so drained.
-[Kris] Of course you are, honey.
[Kim] There was definitely
one moment where I just was, like,
"I need a minute."
I went outside in the hallway,
and I literally sat there
and was, like... [sighs heavily].
Like, deep breaths.
♪ ♪
[Malika] Hi.
-[Khloe] Your watch is stunning.
-0[Malika] Thank you.
-[Khloe] You look cute.
-[Malika] She's shining.
-How's Kimmy doing?
-[Khloe] Um, she's okay.
I've just been giving her space, though.
Who knows, though, but what's going on?
What'd you do?
[Malika] You want to know
the juicy details about it.
[Khloe] It'll be about time I've been
literally begging you for (bleep) details.
[Malika] So, he's really cute,
and he's really sweet,
and you would be really, really
happy about that.
[Khloe] Malika and I are
genuinely like sisters, but the
but the last time I saw her,
she was on her way to film a show
called Famously Single.
[Malika] Hello.
[Khloe] Malika goes
into this house single,
and she comes out of the house
in love with a man.
[Malika] He's that cute little
(bleep) from Jersey Shore.
[Khloe] Give me all the juicy gossip.
Like, how the (bleep) did this happen?
Obviously, you went to, like,
all those relationship therapy stuff.
[Malika] It was like a boot camp.
[Khloe] You've got to know
about his past. Like, everything.
[Malika] For sure-- the good,
the bad, like, all of that stuff
and, still, we're just, like,
sticking to each other.
-[Khloe] That's good.
-[Malika] Yeah, it's a good feeling.
[Khloe] And now that you guys
have been out of the house, is it...
like, weird?
[Malika] It's not weird, but you have
to put forth a different kind of effort.
[Khloe] Yeah. 'Cause you're not...
[Malika] It's different
when you're forced to stay there. Like...
[Khloe] Got it. Got it.
[Malika] Yeah, so that's what we're doing.
So, when do you want to meet him?
[Khloe] I mean, I'll meet him
whenever you want.
-[Malika] Plan.
-[Khloe] Yeah, we could like...
[Malika] We'll make a plan. Poor guy.
Ugh, he has no idea what he's in for.
-[Khloe] Mm-mm.
-[Malika] We shall see.
[Khloe] Ooh! Okrrr.
♪ ♪
[Kendall] Kylie.
[Kylie] Why do you have
the line out-- what are you doing?
[Kendall] A little bit of everything.
I just wanted to , like, look over it,
make sure we like every little thing,
if there's something
we wanted to take out.
Oh, (bleep), I don't know why
I'm so nervous.
I'm really proud of the line,
but I've worked really hard
to be taken seriously
and recognized in Vogue
and in the fashion world.
If this doesn't go as well as we hope,
it might, you know, tarnish
some things in the modeling world.
So it's even more frightening.
[Kylie] I mean, are you having
second thoughts?
[Kendall] It just freaks me out.
Everyone wants an excuse to,
like, talk (bleep).
And I don't want this to be that.
[Kylie] I think it's cute.
I feel confident about it.
We worked so hard on this.
There's so many pieces, like,
no way they're not gonna love it.
-[Kendall] If you say so.
-[Kylie] We've got this.
We've got this, man.
-[Kendall] Are you crying?
-[Kylie] Yes.
-[Kendall] Kylie, stop it.
-[Kylie] I'm crying.
-I'm so proud of us.
-[Kendall] Oh, Kylie, stop.
[Kylie] I'm proud of us.
[Kendall] Stop the fake crying.
You're good at that.
[Kylie] I know.
[Kendall] Does anyone ever
tell you you look like a Bratz doll?
♪ ♪
[hammering]
[Khloe] When is she gonna be done
with this house?
[Kim] It is so (bleep) annoying.
I can't even stand it.
[Khloe] Why do we come to this place?
[Kim] I don't know.
This house is so goddamn annoying.
-I'm freezing.
-[Khloe] At all times, though.
[Kim] I couldn't live here.
[Khloe] Well, you're just like
her, so I don't know.
[Kim] Yeah, I can't comment on it.
[Khloe] When are you moving
into your palace?
[Kim] Well, it's pretty much done.
[Khloe] Okay.
[Kim] But I just stopped the project.
I just told everyone, "stop."
I'm just so tired.
I can't even, like, function.
[Khloe] Last year at this time, kid.
[Kim] We traded places.
[Khloe] Traded places.
I can't imagine having kids
and doing all that.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Khloe] Must be crazy.
[Kim] And that's what's hard.
'Cause, like, they don't know anything,
you know?
So I'm just trying to be, like,
normal at home for them.
[Khloe] Mm-hmm. And they're used
to him being gone.
[Kim] Yeah. To the studio and stuff.
Kanye was really cute, he's like,
"So this is what
for better or for worse means?"
And I'm like, "Yeah."
And all of his friends are texting me,
like, "thank you, you're so amazing."
And I'm like, no this is, like,
being a wife.
This is what you got to do.
He's gonna be fine.
[Khloe] Okay, good.
My heart breaks for Kim.
This year's been, just,
not a great year for her,
but what I know about this family
is that we (bleep) fight, and we get
and we get through things,
and we don't know how to do
half the things
that have been thrown our way,
but somehow we do it.
[Kim] It's just, like, a lot on his plate.
[Khloe] A lot on your plate, too.
♪ ♪
[Scott] Khlo, I stopped
and picked you up dinner.
-Poskinova.
-[Khloe] I don't want food in my room.
-[Scott] You don't want to eat in bed?
-[Khloe] No.
[Scott] To let you know it's here.
-[Khloe] Oh, thank you.
-[Scott] It's all yours.
[Khloe] Thanks.
[Scott] You want to come downstairs
and eat your dinner quick?
[Khloe] No. I was gonna eat later,
I'm not that hungry right now.
[Scott] All right.
I realize it's only 5:30.
-[Khloe] Yeah, is it?
-[Scott] Like, 5:45.
-[Khloe] I'm like...
-[Scott] This darkness is insane.
[Khloe] Why are you trying
to feed me so early?
-[Scott] Got any big plans tonight?
-[Khloe] No, I'm, like...
[Scott] Oh, is it a don't tattle Tuesdays?
[Khloe] No, it is tattle-free Tuesday.
-[Scott] But Malika's, uh--
-[Khloe] Malika's gone.
I swear I call her, like, every day,
and she just has not answered my call
one time.
-[Scott] Ugh, can we call her?
-[Khloe] She won't answer.
[line ringing]
Not working.
I totally get it, when you're
in a new relationship,
you want to be around your man 24/7.
I get it.
Still, I think she could,
you know, call a girl back.
Text me, just say you're busy.
But she doesn't have to, like,
ignore me the whole time.
-[Scott] Has she sent you pictures? Oh.
-[Khloe] They post pictures all the time.
[Scott] This is ridiculous. This is them?
What, do they really think
they're in love over here?
[Khloe] Mm-hmm, with the sunset.
[Scott] You've got to be sucking
on my brazhoul.
[Khloe] You know, I think
this is like the La Brea Tar Pits, right?
[Scott] Could be a tar pit.
So, like, are you gonna
accept him into the fam?
[Khloe] Yeah. I'm gonna accept...
she accepts everything I do.
Gotta accept her...
[Scott] You have to.
[Khloe] Yeah, I mean,
it's just funny, it's Malika.
Mark my words, let's just see
how long this lasts.
[both laugh]
♪ ♪
-[man] Got to be Kylie!
-[man 2] Yes, Kylie.
[man 3] Oh, my God, queen,
you are slaying my life, mami.
-I missed you.
-[Kylie] I miss you!
[man 3] Slay, Kendall.
Hit that walk, honey.
Yes. Yes, Kendall, party slay, honey.
[Kylie] Are you nervous, Kenny?
[Kendall] I feel like,
I obviously work with Vogue a lot,
but in a different way.
And it's kind of nerve-racking.
[bodyguards] Guys, get out of the way.
Get out of the way, please. Thank you.
-[Nicole] Kylie.
-[man] Hello.
[Nicole] Hi, I'm Nicole.
[Kendall] We are here with Nicole Phelps.
[Nicole] Hi, how are you? Hi, hi.
[Kylie] Nicole Phelps has reviewed lines
like Louis Vuitton, Giovanni,
and all the top designers.
[Nicole] Yeah, so we were paging
through a bit.
[Kendall] It's terrifying
knowing that such a big name
is gonna review our line,
and I'm freaking out.
-[Kylie] We show you our favorites?
-[Nicole] Yes, please.
[Kendall] I'm really
into the very simple stuff.
A bunch of, just the one pieces
and the little tops.
We have them in, like, every single color,
and off-the-shoulder, little slip dresses
and stuff like that.
This is Kylie's dog.
[Kylie] They're my inspiration.
[Kendall] I'm literally obsessed
with this.
I brought this from my trip.
I can't read her face at all,
and I have no idea what she's thinking.
I'm nervous.
[Kylie] We really wanted
to represent our everyday style.
[Nicole] How do you guys describe that?
I mean, obviously,
you're California girls,
but are there other ways you describe
your everyday style?
[Kendall] I think super cool
and comfortable.
-[Kylie] Simple.
-[Kendall] Simple, yeah.
You could throw everything together.
Everything could go with each other.
[Nicole] So, you're not afraid
of repeating outfits? Yeah.
[Kendall] Well, repeating
an outfit may be a little iffy,
but repeating a piece,
I love re-wearing things that are cool.
[Kylie] And our age demographic is, like,
a lot younger, but also goes...
I feel like everyone can wear the line.
[Nicole] Who do you think of
as the Kendall + Kylie girl,
like the shopper?
[Kylie] We used to say
the California girl, beachy.
[Kendall] We've evolved, very much.
[Kylie] We've definitely evolved.
[Kendall] This is so nerve-racking.
[Nicole] Would you send me
the previous season, too,
just so I can see
what they're talking about? The evolution.
[Kendall] If they love it,
it'll be amazing,
but if they don't,
it could potentially make or break us.
Kylie, I think I'm gonna puke.
♪ ♪
[Mike] All right, slow it down.
Now speed, and roll camera.
Set, and action.
[Khloe] For me, weight loss
has always been about looking great
and feeling great from the inside out.
And that is what I absolutely love
about Protein World.
[Mike] Good, that's great.
♪ ♪
-[Mike] Nice, beautiful.
-[Khloe] These are so cute.
Thank God I got a spray tan this morning.
Malika, where the hell have you been?
And I thought you couldn't come today
because you were with your boyfriend.
[Malika] I told you I would
if I could, and I'm here.
[Khloe] Hmm...
[Malika] I just wasn't sure,
because he planned a spa day for us,
and then both of our days just flipped.
We're still gonna do that today,
I was, like,
if I could only see you for 30 minutes...
[Khloe] I don't care.
[Malika] ...it's what's to become...
[Khloe] Just letting you know
that I do call you.
[Savas] I just heard
you value certain people
-over others...
-[Malika] That's (bleep).
-[Simon] You have a boyfriend?
-[Malika] (bleep). I do.
-[Simon] Wow.
-[Malika] Shocking, right?
I'm still in shock myself.
[Khloe] I just don't like stuff like that.
[Malika] Look, you know,
sometimes priorities,
-some things change. Sorry.
-[Savas] You got replaced.
[Malika] Khloe understands.
She got a man
and her priorities changed, too.
[Savas] Wow.
[Malika] I took a backseat,
the same way she's taking a backseat now.
-[Khloe] Actually...
-[Savas] You got called out.
[Khloe] Did you not come to Cabo with us?
Have you not hung out down in Maryland?
-Did you not come with us?
-[Malika] It's different.
[Khloe] I don't like, like,
the fabrications of it all.
How many times did I call you
and you never answered my calls?
[Malika] You moved,
so it makes things harder.
[Khloe] You're trying to say
how I've changed,
when I do try to make an effort,
so let's not play that game.
She starts coming at me about
how I've been neglecting her?
I have no idea where her
accusations are coming from,
but I'm not gonna put up with it.
[Malika] Shut up.
♪ ♪
[Khloe] You're not allowed
to comment in this room.
You don't have opinions in here.
You can come in here;
you're only allowed to sit over here.
Sit. Sit right here.
Only allowed to sit.
Sit down.
Sit.
You already know how I feel
about letting you into my closet.
[Kim] Okay. You don't need that one.
[Khloe laughs]
[Khloe] You're not allowed to speak.
These are like, my streetwear.
-[Kim] Okay.
-[Khloe] Ugh, (bleep) 0Malika, man.
Like, she's (bleep) fighting
with me over some bull(bleep).
She's like, "You're not making quality
time for me," and all.
I'm like what the (bleep)?
But you don't have time,
either, right now.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Khloe] So if we both don't have time,
-we're adults about it.
-[Kim] It's life.
[Khloe] Just 'cause things
aren't at your beck and call
in the way you want them to happen,
that's not my problem.
[Kim] I get it.
[Khloe] I already feel bad
always, like, leaving you guys
and not being here for certain things
or, like, just even the holiday--
whatever, like, I already feel,
like, (bleep) I'm not here as much.
I already feel guilty about that,
you don't add more to my plate,
make me feel even worse.
[Kim] Like, you can't even feel bad.
You've got to tell her, like,
"Dude, this is my one time. Let me live."
[Khloe] Ugh, I just feel
so bad even complaining to you about this,
'cause it's, like, so stupid
in the grand scheme of life,
and you're obviously
dealing with, like, real (bleep).
[Kim] No, it's fine.
It, like, actually gets my mind
off of everything.
♪ ♪
[Kris] Kendall?
[Kendall moans]
Wow, this place is huge.
Do you feel like Eloise? At the Plaza?
-[Kendall] I'm so tired.
-[Kris] Cheer up, little lady.
You look like a little black swan.
-[Kendall] Thanks.
-[Kris] How was the walkthrough?
[Kendall] It's so nerve-racking.
Nicole was just really hard to read.
She, I thought she hated me.
[Kris] You know, nobody has
adapted to this business faster
and more professionally than you.
I'm so proud of you.
You're so blessed to be able
to even have the opportunity
to have the people from Vogue...
Vogue magazine came to review
and check out your new line.
That's a big deal.
So you have to just say,
"Wow, I did the best I could."
Take a deep breath
and let it go for a minute.
You know what I mean?
[Kendall] I'm just nervous.
I'm not usually on the other side of it.
[Kris] But at the same time,
I think that the modeling business
has given you a sense of thick skin,
so that no matter what they say
you're gonna be able to take it
as constructive criticism...
[Kendall] Mm-hmm.
[Kris] ...and not take it personally
because business is business.
[Kendall] Okay. I hope so.
♪ ♪
-[Malika] Hello, Khloe.
-[Khloe laughs]
Why are you laughing?
[Khloe] I mean, I've been calling you
and I haven't heard from you.
What are you doing?
[Malika] You look so uncomfortable.
It's funny.
[Khloe] No, I'm not uncon...
it's just you are a funny broad.
[Malika] Do you want to just
talk and get it over with?
[Khloe] Is that what will make you
feel better?
-'Cause I've been trying to call you.
-[Malika] I'm here.
[Khloe] Okay. Do you want to sit down?
-Is that what this is?
-[Malika] I would love that.
[Khloe] Malika is acting
so weird right now.
I don't get it.
You're the one that's been MIA.
You ignored me.
Look in the (bleep) mirror.
[Malika] It's become very difficult
for me because I don't feel
like you're really around.
[Khloe] Even if I'm out of town,
like, I still try to call you
and I still try to have our talk time
and if that is bothering you,
like, you also need to explain that to me
so I could try a little harder.
And if I'm not here,
that doesn't mean I'm not here for you.
It doesn't mean... if anything
I have more time where I could talk to you
on the phone and, like,
gossip and do whatever.
[Malika] But you're happy
and that's another thing.
Sometimes I understand what you're saying,
but sometimes you don't...
[Khloe] You're mad that I'm happy?
[Malika] You're, like, happy
and that's another thing.
Like, sometimes... I understand
what you're saying,
-but sometimes you don't...
-[Khloe] You're mad that I'm happy?
[Malika] I'm so happy that you're happy
that I don't want to put my (bleep)
on you.
So, like, even when I'm going
through stuff, like,
in my relationship that has taken
a complete turn for the worse...
[Khloe] But how am I supposed
to know any of these things?
That's complete news to me.
[Malika] Yeah.
[Khloe] I had no idea.
If you're sad, like, I want to get you
out of being sad.
But you shouldn't do that by yourself.
That's absolutely ridiculous
and it makes me feel like,
okay, so are we not as close
as I thought we were?
[Malika] I think we are,
but our relationship has become
a little bit more estranged
and obviously, I miss you, that's all.
-[Khloe] Why are you crying?
-[Malika] Because I do.
[Khloe] Oh. Don't cry.
Malika confessing that her and Ronnie,
they've been having a lot of problems.
I feel horrible for her,
but for her to feel like
she can't tell me these things,
it makes me feel really sad.
It's you and me.
When I am here, let's try to spend
as much time together as we can,
even if it's doing nothing,
going to the grocery store.
It's still quality time.
-[Malika] I agree.
-[Khloe] I get it.
She doesn't want to, like, rain
on my parade,
but I don't care what I'm going through,
I'm never gonna not be Malika's friend.
That's what we're there for.
And maybe she's embarrassed
that she's dating Ronnie
from the Jersey Shore...
'cause I would be.
I'll need to take you out
for a glass of wine
and hear all the details.
[Malika] Oh, it's pretty funny.
[Khloe] If he's not treating you right,
send him back to Jersey.
[Malika laughs]
♪ ♪
-[woman] Hi, Kendall.
-[Kendall] Hey.
-[Will.I.am] Miss you.
-[Kendall] Me too.
I am shooting with will.i.am today
for Buttons, will.i.am's
will.i.am's headphones,
and I'm really excited,
but I'm also trying not to stress
about everything else that's going on.
But it'll be good, it'll be fun.
[photographer] Let's get them on set.
♪ ♪
[photographer] Ready?
You look great. Great.
Beautiful girl.
[Kendall] After talking to my mom,
she made me realize that,
yeah, it did take me some time
to get comfortable in the
in the modeling world,
so I just have to use
that same patience in the design world.
[photographer] Gorgeous. Look there.
[Kendall] In any form,
any criticism that you get,
you should always just take that
and use it to grow and learn.
[photographer] Forward to the one.
[photographer] Thank you, everybody.
Great job. Great job. Great job.
-[Kris] That was a long day.
-[Kendall] Yeah.
[Kris] So, hey, couple things.
I know how nervous you were
about the Vogue reviews,
let me show you.
[Kris] And I heard they don't
really give...
-[Kendall] Shh.
-[Kris] ...them this early.
[Kendall] Oh, my God.
[Kris] You okay?
♪ ♪
[Kris] I know how nervous you were
about the Vogue review.
[Kendall] Shh, Mom, I can't read.
Oh, my God.
[Kris] You okay?
They loved every single piece.
[Kris] They just don't pass
those out on a whim.
[Kris] I'm so proud of you.
You should be so proud, really.
You did it, yeah.
[Kendall] I was really bracing myself
for a bad review,
but instead, we got a really good one.
And it was a really nice surprise.
I'm so relieved, though,
because I was so nervous about it.
-[Kris] You should be proud of yourself.
-[Kendall] Yay.
♪ ♪
-[Malika] Hi, Kimberly.
-[Kim] Malika, Malika, Malika.
[Malika] You look amazing, by the way.
-[Kim] I've had it with you.
-[Malika] Have you? What did I do now?
[Kim] I hear you are ho'ing it up
around town and not telling me.
[Malika laughs]
[Khloe] She's not ho'ing it.
She's actually, for once, not.
[Malika] I wish, that would be fun.
This (bleep) not.
[Kim] How cute is that pic?
Did I send that to you?
-[Khloe] No.
-[Kim] From yesterday.
[Khloe] Oh, my God.
[Kim] Like, is that not, like, classic
Saint's birthday? We did a snow thing.
[Khloe] Oh, he was so thrilled,
but look at his face.
-[Malika] So cute.
-[Khloe] Aw.
[Kim] It was so cute.
[Malika] Kourtney showed me videos
of you and, um, North.
[Kim] It was really cute.
There was just, like, Kourtney and us.
It was just easy 'cause I didn't want
to overwhelm, like, you know.
[Malika] Yeah.
It's probably better that way.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Malika] Give it time.
[Kim] Yeah.
-[Malika] And it's important.
-[Kim] Yeah.
[Malika] And you've got other little lives
to pay attention to right now, anyway.
[Malika] Are you done having kids?
[Kim] Uh, me, personally, yes.
I, we had a...
[Malika] So you would opt
for someone else to carry it for you?
[Kim] I just feel like I need
some time to see.
[Malika] Okay.
-[Kim] All right, should we eat?
-[Malika] Let's eat.
[Khloe] God, it's been so long
since I've had chow mein.
This makes me so happy.
[Kim] I love fortune cookies.
Wait, you have to hand it to me
-and I hand you yours.
-[Malika] Really? Didn't know that.
[Kim] And if you want it
to come true, you have to eat it.
[Malika] Oh (bleep). Okay, fine.
Was my cookie supposed to break like that?
[Kim] "Your troubles will soon cease
and good fortune will smile upon you."
-[Malika] Yes.
-[Kim] Thank you, Lord.
Should I eat the paper?
[Malika] That is amazing.
I'd eat the whole damn thing.
"Your investments of time now
will lead to success later."
[Kim] Have you been investing your time?
[Malika laughs]
[Kim] Coming up next week...
[Caitlyn] The book is... finished.
[Kris] I've never been so angry.
I just can't sit back anymore. I'm done.
[Caitlyn] Don't even go down this road
'cause I'm not talking about it.
-[Rob] Chyna took everything.
-[Kim] They aren't healthy together.
[Khloe] She texted your sisters
and said she'll leave you
because you can't
get your (bleep) together.
-[Rob] You are speaking out of your ass.
-[Kourtney] What's wrong with him?
[Kim] Everyone wants to protect Rob,
but there's only so much we can do.