[Kim] This season on
Keeping Up with the Kardashians…
-["FML" by Kanye West playing]
-♪ I been ♪
♪ Livin' ♪
♪ Without ♪
♪ Limits… ♪
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[Khloé] My career is about
being vulnerable
and sharing my life with people.
-[reporters clamoring]
-[reporter 1] Kim! Kim!
[Kendall]
Being in the public eye is pretty crazy.
-[reporter 2] Kim, how are you?
-[reporter 3] Kris! Kris, over here!
[Khloé] It's a lot of pressure
to put your life out there.
-[siren blaring]
-[reporter 4] In Paris,
Kim Kardashian has been robbed.
-[Kim] I have a family.
-[shrieks]
-I have my kids.
-[blabbering]
♪ I will die for those I love… ♪
If the elevator does not open in time,
I'm [bleep].
♪ Revealing the layers to my soul… ♪
[Caitlyn] We certainly have grown apart.
[Khloé]
You're not the step-dad I once had.
[Kendall]
I had someone break into my house.
Until we go to trial, he stays in jail.
[Kim]
He walked offstage after three songs.
What's wrong?
[Kris] As a mom,
you wanna keep your kids safe.
She's the love of my life.
♪ Don't stop your loving ♪
♪ No, not for nothing… ♪
[Kim] Scott brought a girl out here.
You're just like a [bleep] whore.
I'm a sex addict!
It's never gonna work out.
[Rob] I wanna be with her.
We're figuring it out.
♪ They don't want to see me love you… ♪
[Khloé] She took the baby away?
[Khloé]
She wants nothing to do with you anymore.
[Rob] Khloé's a hater and a liar.
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[Kim] Everything has changed,
-but we can't be afraid.
-[screaming]
We can't let people scare us
into not living our lives.
[Kris] At the end of the day,
we have each other.
That means everything.
[upbeat music]
[Jonathan] P? P?
Oh, no, I'm getting a hug hello.
-I don't care.
-[Kourtney laughs]
[Kourtney] Mase, this is my store.
This is our store of clothes.
-[Jonathan] Checking in, checking in.
-Hi.
-[Kourtney] Hi.
-All the money there? Everything good?
[Kourtney] How are you?
How's it going?
Is it usually, like, it's more crowded
-on the weekends?
-Definitely.
Remember when we had lines, like,
every day, around the block?
-Yeah.
-Barricades.
Crazy.
My sisters and I own three DASH stores.
One in L.A., one in Miami,
and one in New York.
-[crowd screaming, cheering]
-[camera shutters clicking]
Our DASH stores were
the first business venture that we did,
like, together as sisters.
But now, with our busy schedules,
it's really hard for us to be
as involved in the stores
as we would like to be.
-[Kourtney] Cheese city.
-[Jonathan] Come on.
Everyone wants streetwear now.
-[Kourtney] Totally.
-[Jonathan] Like those DASH shirts,
why aren't they made, like,
rock and roll shirts?
-Chopped up, ripped up, DASH.
-Yeah.
You know what, this is like, looks like
a shirt for security at a concert, like,
"Keep it going, keep it going."
[laughs]
And that bag up at the top
with the lips? Please.
[Kourtney] Like, we need to evolve.
[Jonathan] I feel like we need
to major re-brand to keep up with, like…
Totally. Life.
Like, what we're into.
You know, we want DASH
to represent us and represent our style
which is constantly changing as we change.
[Jonathan] Now, does Kim understand at all
how cheesy her store is?
-'Cause you know how crazy she is.
-[Kourtney] No.
-[Kourtney] Should we call her?
-[Jonathan] This is gonna be fun.
-[line ringing]
-[Kim over phone] Hello?
-Hi.
-[Kim] Hey.
Our stores definitely have times
when they're doing better than others,
but I think that when me, Kim, and Khloé
put all of our energy into them,
is when they really thrive.
[Kourtney] It's so 2009.
Like, I don't even have
the words to explain.
[Kim] Shut up.
[Kourtney] All right, well,
when we're in Miami for the concerts,
I think we need to check out
the Miami store.
-[Kim] I feel you.
-All right,
I'm gonna call you when I get out of here,
but call me if you need me before then.
-[Kim] Buh-bye.
-Okay, love you, bye.
-[Jonathan] This could be really sick.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
What do you think about my store?
Not good.
-Not good?
-[Mason] No.
-You want to leave?
I want… yeah.
-[Jonathan] Oh, my god.
-[Kourtney] All right, guys,
should we rock and roll?
-[Mason] There's nobody here.
-[Kourtney] Okay. Thanks, guys.
I appreciate you guys. Thank you.
[crowd cheering]
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[cheering continues]
[upbeat electronic music]
-[Larsa] Ooh, this feels so good.
-[Kourtney] This heat.
I prefer this to, like,
an air-conditioned…
Me too.
-…situation any day.
-There's nothing better than Miami.
[Jonathan]
People used to hang out on beaches.
-This is just so pretty.
-Everything's so peaceful.
I'm really excited to be in Miami,
and a lot of our friends are in town also.
We're here to check on DASH,
but we're also here to just have fun
and go to Kanye's concert.
Like, it just kind of all worked out as,
like, a perfect excuse to go to Miami.
[Jonathan] Guys, there's people, like,
literally swimming.
[Kourtney] Wait, who wants
-to go swimming?
-[Simon] Oh, my god.
-[Larsa] Kourtney, go, get in.
-[Simon] No. We're going to dinner.
[Jonathan] Let's go take that clothes.
-[Jonathan and Kourtney chuckle]
-[Jonathan] Kourtney, you do it.
[Kourtney] Grab their clothes?
They're gonna see us.
-[Jonathan] Just do it.
-[Larsa] Get some balls.
-Let's go.
-[Jonathan] Ain't that crazy?
[Larsa] Come on, Kourt.
Come on, guys!
Grab this. And go!
-Go, guys!
-[Kourtney] Ew, ew!
I have someone's underwear.
[all screaming and laughing]
[Larsa] Oh, my god.
[panting]
[Kourtney]
Are we throwing it in this bush?
-[Larsa] No, don't throw it in the bush.
-[Kourtney] I have no idea.
-[Jonathan] You're such a troublemaker.
-Oh, my god.
[laughs]
[Jonathan] I think we made it.
I think we got away.
I feel like we need to do
something else now.
[Simon] Let's go for a skinny dip.
Kourt, show those…
Show your tits.
-[all] Show your tits!
-I'm not showing those too…
[laughter]
-Go.
-We're gonna go! We're gonna go!
-[indistinct shouting and laughing]
-[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] Here, go this way.
[Jonathan] There's a ghost in here!
[Larsa] The hotel's haunted!
Hurry up, get out!
Get out! Get out!
[man] Can you keep it down?
-[Jonathan] Sorry.
-[Kourtney and Larsa] There was a ghost.
[Larsa] We're trying to warn you people.
[upbeat electronic music]
[Khloé] Who is this?
Who is all these kids?
Who's this? Another kid.
-[Penelope] It's not a kid!
-[Khloé] It's not
-a little boy?
-[Kourtney] Khlo!
[chuckles]
I haven't seen you in forever.
You look so good!
I'm super excited to be in Miami
to meet up with everybody.
You know, we lived here for a little bit,
Kourtney and I.
[Kourtney]
Should we go out on the balcony?
-Did you check out the view?
-No, I literally just got here.
We have such great memories of Miami
and when we come back here,
I feel like we get that same vibe again,
where we just want to, like, have fun,
be carefree and, like, be out on the town.
[Kourtney] Should we go do
our old school workouts,
where we would run on the beach?
[Khloé] [bleep] no.
Now if we run on the beach,
paparazzi would run with us.
-That's not as enjoyable as it used to be.
-No.
All right, well,
should we get this show on the road?
Yeah, let's go to dinner.
Excited to talk…
-Hear about your trip to Disney World…
-[Kourtney] A little "Hi, how are you?"
I just haven't heard
about your trip or anything.
I know.
Scott and I are, you know, doing our best
to be good parents together
and remain a family,
even though we're not together.
We even stopped in Orlando
and took our kids to Disney World.
-[Scott] All right, let's go.
-[Penelope] Yahoo!
[Kourtney] We've been going
to the beach every day, and, like,
I love just, like, being able to get
to spend time with the kids
and Scott together as a family.
[Scott] Okay. Let's go eat, guys.
[Kourtney] Are you bringing the backpack?
Yeah, it's my bag.
[Kourtney] It's so big.
Just put your phone in your pocket,
what else do you need?
I mean, makeup, charger,
deodorant, money, I.D…
[Khloé] What do you mean what's in it?
What's in your purse?
[upbeat electronic music]
-[Khloé] Grutman.
-[Dave] I missed you.
[Khloé] How are you?
-[Kourtney] Long time!
-How are you?
Kourtney, this gonna piss you off?
[Kourtney] Yeah.
What's in there, like, a diaphragm?
What the [bleep] backpack is it?
You guys, it's just my travel backpack.
I came from the airport.
I don't know what you guys want from me.
I'm so excited to eat here.
I've only heard fantastic things.
-The rice, just you wait…
-The rice?
[Kourtney] The forbidden rice.
-Does that…
-[Dave] Oh, the black, no, black rice.
Yeah, black rice.
-I love black things.
-Oh, okay.
[Dave laughs]
Kourt, I saw the Disney pics. was it fun?
[Kourtney] We did 13 hours.
-13 hours?
-[Kourtney] Nonstop, yeah.
With Scott?
And the kids.
And Nor… I brought North and Saint.
-Did they like it?
-[Kourtney] Loved it.
-[man] Okay, what's up.
-Yo!
I got you! Yo, how you feeling tonight?
-[man] Good…
-[Scott] Right, right, right.
Yo, you look good.
-What up, girl?
-[Kourtney] What?
[Simon] Wait, Kourt, it's done, right?
Disney World is done?
[Scott and Kourtney] Yes.
[Simon] 13 hours sounds intense.
[Kourtney] He took breaks.
I took, like, two minutes off.
Bro, she's very, very thorough,
like CIA-style.
Like, she [bleep] runs,
and she's high-fiving people.
It's [bleep] nuts, man.
[Simon] Were the kids not tired?
[Scott] P was in some mood
at the end of the day.
Very similar to somebody.
[laughs]
[Scott] I wanted to kill myself.
-[Khloé] Not awkward at all.
-[Scott] But that was a great time!
You should probably have a kid too.
[Simon] Well, you're trying, aren't you?
You expedited things so much.
-Why? What'd you do?
-She spent time with my kids.
I'm sure you helped a lot.
This is the perfect situation.
This is exactly what you want, honey.
Get knocked up and leave your husband.
[laughs]
[Khloé] This is turning
into a really weird dinner, you guys.
-Like, I feel like…
-[Scott] No, it's not at all.
-Are you tired?
-[Kourtney] So tired.
Yeah, you look really shut down.
I really do enjoy hanging out with Scott
with the kids,
because we know what we're doing.
But, like, if we're doing things socially,
I just don't really know how to act.
For so many years,
I've been used to playing a certain role
and having to be responsible
and watching out for his behavior.
He can be
a little bit obnoxious, and, like,
when I'm in Miami,
just trying to have fun with my friends,
I just don't want him to bring me down.
-[Khloé] Kourt, would you ever try duck?
-[Scott] She's tried it a million times.
-[Kourtney] I have tried it.
-[Raul] I brought King here, my son.
And I ordered the duck.
-Yo, bro, he was so mad.
-[Khloé] He hate it?
"Ducks are your friends!"
-[Kourtney and Scott] Aw!
-[all laughing]
-[Scott] That's funny.
-[Kourtney] You should learn from him.
Kids are the future, I swear.
What the [bleep] does that mean?
[Scott] What else could they be?
The past?
[upbeat electronic music]
[Khloé] Hello.
That's a cute robe.
[Khloé] I've had this.
The [bleep] do you want?
What the [bleep] is your problem?
Oh, my god. Nothing.
How's Tristan?
[laughs]
-[Khloé] He's good.
-[Kourtney] How was Mexico?
[Khloé] It was so much fun.
When the family was in New York
for Fashion Week,
I was in Cabo with a bunch of my friends
and my boyfriend.
His name is Tristan Thompson.
He's a Pisces,
he's Jamaican, from Toronto.
And he plays for the Cleveland Cavaliers.
We just had, like, the best time.
But all those paparazzi shots of us,
not one pap I never, ever, ever saw.
Ever.
So you didn't know until they came out?
Right. It's horrible.
-Yeah.
-[Khloé] Horrible.
I literally thought, "The coast is clear."
Yeah.
Right now, my relationship is really new,
and I kind of want to keep it close
to my heart
and not, like, really shout everything
from the rooftops,
'cause I think I've learned from the past.
It's just a lot of pressure
to put your relationship out there.
I don't need someone
dissecting Tristan and I.
So I'm very choosy
as to who I share my dating life with.
We're all so opinionated,
and we're also, like, an intense family.
And I just feel like I like to, like,
keep things as confined as possible.
No, I think that's a great thing.
It's like, what's the rush?
[upbeat electronic music]
Hello!
-OMG!
-I see you!
[Jonathan] Hi!
[Khloé] I haven't seen you in forever.
[Kim] I literally haven't seen you
in 20 years.
You look like Miley Cyrus with that hair.
Not a bad thing.
-[Khloé] I don't want to be Miley. Oh…
-Well, you are Miley Cyrus today.
[Khloé] Okay.
-What's going on?
-Your hair's so short.
I feel like I don't even know you.
My hair? My hair is always short.
[Khloé] Well, unless I put extensions in.
[Kim] So what's been going on?
I saw you went to Mexico.
-Mm-hm.
-Where in Mexico did you go?
I went to Cabo.
-[Jonathan] Ha.
-[Kim] Cabo is like…
-What?
-And you were just so comfortable
roaming around town?
I never saw one paparazzi.
There wasn't one person near us.
-They're all the fisherman in the boats.
-We… I had no idea there was paparazzi.
Like, who knew that you fully had,
like, a whole new crew.
-[Jonathan] A whole new crew.
-[Kim] Who is this crew?
Like, I don't get it.
Just friends.
So I see pictures of Khloé
with some NBA player,
and even though I know
not to believe everything on the Internet,
Khloé and an NBA player
do go hand in hand.
So, I mean it's my sister.
Of course I want to know
who she's hooking up with.
What is going on?
You've never revealed information.
Like, it's wild
that I have to see pictures,
like, of you online,
and you don't say one thing.
[Kim] Is this, like, Malika?
-Like, is… Why was Khadijah there?
-Malika was there.
-Like, where was Bobby?
-[Khloé] 'Cause we're on vacation.
Kourtney and I tell each other
literally everything.
'Cause we don't pry too much,
until the person decides to reveal
their own personal information.
With Kim, this is what, like,
makes Kim horny in life, is, like,
finding out all these details
and just salivating at the mouth,
asking me all these questions.
So, we all know to not tell Kim anything,
unless we want to tell her
every last detail.
You're making me crazy.
[Jonathan laughs]
It's the hair, the whole thing.
-[Kim] I know.
-What?
I gotta change my hair?
[upbeat electronic music]
[Kim and Khloé speak in English accent]
Hello!
[in normal accent]
Everyone's into really short these days.
No. I've never bought
a XXL that's this short.
It's the type of the shirt.
-[Khloé] 'Cause my army one is way longer.
-Yeah.
Why does his fit different
than the last ones?
[Kim] I don't know.
We will tell Mr. West.
Good thing we know the designer.
Don't tell him I said that.
Um, so you said DASH was just, like,
the New York one is just so not like L.A.
I just want it to look different.
I think it needs to update.
It doesn't need to be, like, glam.
-Yeah.
-[Kourtney] Like, I cannot wait
to go to DASH here.
Let's step it up. Let's do streetwear.
But so, I've been talking to Mom,
and this major department store
wants to buy DASH
and put a DASH store in each one
of their huge department stores.
That would be so cool.
It's such a smart idea,
because it will give us a chance
to finally evolve and move on.
We've had this store for a decade.
And I've already been, like,
I'm vetoing my sisters,
and I'm saying yes,
and Mom's flying in to New York.
-I'm on the same page.
-[Kim] I know you will. That's why I knew.
It wasn't, like, a big thing.
I'm, like, let's just…
Like, who cares about the stores?
[Kourtney] I do. I care about them.
[Khloé] I don't give a [bleep].
-We're overriding you, honey.
-[Kourtney] No.
I was ready to get the buying stuffed up.
[Kim] I don't get it.
Kourtney was ranting to me
about how New York was such a hot mess.
And this is the best opportunity
for the store, for us, for everything.
Does she have time to go in every day?
I don't think so.
-This is such a huge opportunity.
-No, but all the things we kept saying,
"Let's wait, let's wait, let's wait,"
finally just got to the point…
[Kim] I know,
but let's just see the store first
and what the deal is,
and we'll go from there.
[upbeat electronic music]
[Kourtney] Look at this neighborhood…
-Yep, this was home.
-…that we lived in.
[Kourtney] Once, I stayed here,
it was New Year's Eve,
and Courtenay Semel was like,
"You've got to come with me."
Like, all I had was, like, money
for, like, the flight.
I was like, "Courtenay, I have,
like, 60 dollars or something."
And we're like, "A bagel's 60 cents.
-We'll just eat bagels the whole time."
-[laughs]
We just, like,
had the craziest week, like,
so out of our minds.
[Simon] Slob Kabob days.
[Kourtney] Yeah.
-[Jonathan] So what are we doing tonight?
-[Simon] Steph's dinner.
-[Jonathan] Is Scott coming?
-No, Steph's birthday dinner.
-So he's not invited.
-So he doesn't care?
Oh, he's not invited. It's like that?
Well, it's, like, her birthday dinner.
-I know, but it's, like, all of us.
-They don't even know each other.
Why does he have to go
everywhere that we go?
-[Simon] Yeah.
-I was just curious.
And that's why
people get confused with stuff.
-I'm, like, we're not together.
-Right.
It's just frustrating sometimes.
I just need a break from Scott.
I just think I need to prioritize myself
and be able to go
to my friend's birthday dinner
and enjoy the night
without him being there
when he's not even friends with her.
It's, like, already, any fun event,
he always seems to be invited.
-So, I don't think he needs to be invited.
-Right.
[upbeat electronic music]
-[Khloé] This is a gel?
-[Kim] It's a gel, yeah.
It works a little bit.
-[Khloé] It's definitely…
-[Kim] Better.
…helping.
[Kim] What is all of this?
Why are you buying lingerie in Miami?
[Khloé] Why are you so up my ass?
'Cause I'm just, like, curious.
Who are all these shirts for?
[Khloé] Oh, my god,
you ask a million questions.
You've got all these men's shirts.
Uh, does Pablo make women's shirts?
-[Kim] Actually, he does not.
-Exactly.
So there you go,
but you got doubles and triples.
Who are these for?
Kim, just mind your own business.
[Kim] Khloé says there's nothing going on.
Like, I'm not stupid.
I mean, the clues are all adding up.
Just why, like, why hide it?
Just makes no sense.
Like, I'll just snoop and spy
and figure it out on my own.
Just, like, asking questions.
I'm not, like…
You're not what?
-Being nosy as [bleep]?
-I'm just a curious cat.
[Khloé] Curious cat.
You literally have, like,
bruises on your legs.
[Khloé] Oh, now, what?
That's a problem too?
No, but that hickey on your neck is.
[chuckles]
Who do… who, like, gives hickeys?
Who doesn't mind their own business?
Oh, my god.
This is exactly
why I didn't want to tell Kim.
Look how [bleep] nosy she is.
She's not gonna crack me. She's like…
This makes me want to withhold
my information even more.
I'm dating. I'm figuring it out,
and when I'm ready, I'll tell you,
and until then,
mind your [bleep] business.
Are you ready to get out of my room?
-I am.
-[Khloé] 'Cause I think you've asked me
one too many questions.
I'm getting home to my kids.
You know what?
Ask your kids some questions.
-[smacking lips]
-[chuckles]
-[Kim] Bye.
-That's why I have bruises.
[upbeat electronic music]
[squeals]
Hold on, baby.
-There's Khloé. What's up?
-Hi, Snappers.
Make sure we didn't see
anything on your phone.
[Khloé] My phone's facing me.
Look how many people
are packed in this car.
I wanted to go in my own car,
and they thought I was being
too bougie and antisocial.
-Are you gonna introduce your friends?
-[woman over phone] Yeah…
-What? Why are you all in my phone call?
-Are you gonna introduce your friends?
[Khloé]
Are you getting jealous or something?
-Yeah.
-No, I'm just like, trying to,
just trying to, like, figure out
why you're not talking to us.
-[Jonathan] Doesn't your hand hurt at all?
-No, I'm very comfortable over here.
If anything, it hurts
that you're literally riding
my [bleep] right now.
-That's right.
-That's what [bleep] hurts.
-Get off my D.
-Wow.
[laughs]
[upbeat electronic music]
[Kourtney]
What kind of ceviche is the fish ceviche?
Like, white fish?
Can I get an order of that, please?
I've never been this hungry in my life.
[Simon] I am starving.
Wait, so, once a week,
I go to church at home,
but I feel like now I've missed it.
It's been three weeks
'cause I've been on a nonstop world tour.
[Jonathan]
You have a lot of repenting to do
-after three weeks.
-I have a lot of catching up.
[Jonathan] Is that what you do,
repent in church?
No, repenting is Catholic, isn't it?
Oh, is it different?
-I don't know. I'm Jewish.
-[Kourtney] I'm Christian.
Khloé, do you want to come
when we're back?
I'm sorry, to what?
-[Kourtney] To church.
-Yes.
She's so distracted.
You got a lot of repenting to do.
Yeah, she's in love. He's hot, by the way.
-[Khloé] He's so hot.
-[Simon] It's crazy.
You're in love already?
You're not in love.
I feel like you guys,
you're gonna tell Kim,
-and I don't want to tell Kim anything.
-I don't tell Kim [bleep].
-Yeah, right.
-Really?
You know, if you tell Kim something,
she's texting people as you're telling it.
[Simon] As she's… as she's telling it.
Everyone just do me a favor
and swear they won't tell Kim?
-Swear on my life.
-[Jonathan] On my life.
Kim is my sister.
I'm gonna obviously tell her, eventually.
But it's fun to torture her.
She's tortured me my entire life.
So, I feel like this is, like,
the perfect time to just, like,
drag this out as long as we possibly can.
Doesn't she ask? She's such a nosy…
Yeah, she'll ask.
And then I'm like, "Oh, my god,
that Balmain outfit you wore."
And she's like, "Okay."
-It's fab, it's fab.
-Right. She's like a little puppy.
[Simon] Yeah, but this one sounds like
a good one.
It's like you don't want
anyone to mess it up.
It's too good.
Does he have any idea
what he's getting into?
-Probably not.
-[laughs]
[upbeat electronic music]
[camera shutters clicking]
-Yo, this is a much better look…
-[Khloé] Hi. How are you?
-How's thing?
-[Khloé] So good.
What the [bleep] is that gold
[bleep] up there?
Kourtney.
-It's actually really cute.
-[Khloé] Stop.
[Kim] We're looking at our Miami store.
It's probably gonna be the same problems
as DASH New York.
And even though
there's an offer on the table,
we'll, like, appease Kourtney
for a little bit.
The hats are fine, right? Or no?
They're not good hats.
[Kourtney] And then are we over these bags
or are they cute?
[Khloé] "Juicy." I can't.
I love the floors.
The DASH beanie just needs to be redone,
don't you think?
[Khloé] Obviously.
[Kim] There's no way to salvage
any of this. Horrible.
[Jonathan]
You know that font makes me sick.
[Khloé] Kourt, we would literally
have to update every single thing.
[Kim] Kourtney is delusional.
I think that the store is really past
putting more money into it
to make all these changes
for us to still not be able
to be there all the time.
So, I just don't really get
what she's thinking.
This just really confirms
that we need to close these stores,
and Kourtney just has to get on board
with this.
[Kourtney] Khloé, what do you think?
Should we just give these away
every purchase, just put them in the bag?
-[Khloé] Yeah, why not?
-They actually sell very good.
-[Jonathan] Are you kidding?
-[Kim] Really?
Everything at the cash wrap
sells very quickly.
So, let's not order any more of these.
She just said they sell.
[Kourtney] I'm trying to figure out
how to make everything better for DASH,
and my sisters are so checked out
that it seems like they've already
just made up their minds
about wanting to close the store.
[upbeat electronic music]
[camera shutters clicking]
[Kim] Kourt, there's a size 24 jeans here.
Oh, this could be cute.
This is dope.
Do I want to wear off-white sweats?
I love them, and I love this.
-[Khloé] Hello.
-[Alexa over phone] Hi.
Hi. Um, will you do me a favor?
Will you please call my hotel and see
if they have, like, four extra rooms
until Monday?
[Kim] What are you ordering
all these extra rooms for?
[Alexa]
Do you need tickets to the concert?
[Khloé] I did that. We have an extra car.
I think we have security.
I'm so excited because Tristan
and some of his friends
are coming to the Kanye show.
I think it's, like, a really fun way
just to, "Surprise, Kim!
Here's the guy
you've been asking me about."
-Why wouldn't you ask me?
-I just didn't want to bother you
so I was having the assistants
deal with one another.
[Khloé] But I'll have to admit
that messing with Kim,
it's a fun game for me.
It's actually been the most rewarding part
of this entire Miami trip.
Okay. Thanks, Alexa.
[Kourtney] I'm gonna have Mason with me.
-He's coming to the show.
-[Khloé gasps]
Stop.
Just… you never know who's gonna show up.
Hmm.
[upbeat electronic music]
This is beyond glam.
-I got it in Nantucket at that store.
-Okay, I knew I've seen it
-and I was like, I was with you.
-You were with me. Duh.
I'm so excited.
[Simon] I haven't seen you
this excited in a long time.
[Khloé] I know.
It is so hard to find
someone you have a crush on, though.
-We always talk about, crushes are…
-There is no one.
-[Kourtney] You're a constant crusher.
-No, I never get, like…
Like a real crush,
-like the thing that, like…
-Yes, like butterflies,
-it's so fun. It's exciting.
-Right. Nervousness.
-[Simon] Everything.
-Yes.
You never get that way?
-No.
-[Simon] No, do you?
-Yeah.
-I thought after Lamar,
you just don't get that way.
Really, I thought after Lamar…
There's a crazy person
to the right of the car.
-[Khloé screams]
-[dramatic music]
All right, there's a real lunatic
by the side of the car.
My god, that scared the [bleep] out of me!
I was literally looking like this,
but the words couldn't come out.
[Khloé] That was terrifying.
[Simon] I'll block you from behind.
[camera shutters clicking]
[Khloé] Hey, guys.
I'm so excited for tomorrow.
[Simon] Birthday girl.
[people whooping]
Cheers to Stephanie!
-[all] Cheers!
-[Larsa] And to Miami.
You shared your toast with a city.
[Stephanie laughs]
[Kanye] For your birthday.
Your birthday toast was shared
with a city that's here all year.
We are at
one of our favorite Miami hot spots,
Prime One Twelve. It's the best food.
We're celebrating
my assistant Stephanie's birthday.
We wanted the whole crew just to make her
feel special on her birthday.
Can you impersonate any person?
-[Kim] No.
-You can do it.
-I don't think I can.
-[Khloé] Don't be shy now.
It's just us. Okay, be British.
I can't, I can't.
[Kourtney] I can impersonate someone.
[in Spanish accent]
My name is Inigo Montoya.
You killed my father.
[Jonathan speaks in normal accent]
Uh-oh, never mind.
With those kind of accents, don't do it.
[all laughing]
[Kim] Scott is texting me.
[Kourtney]
Just don't tell him what we're doing.
[Khloé] Wait, he just texted me too.
[Kourtney] Like, why?
Isn't that so annoying?
[Jonathan] I can't.
[Khloé] You know, I totally get it.
Kourt and Scott aren't together,
but it has to be hard.
They have all the same friends.
It just blurs a lot of lines.
We don't know
what we're allowed to invite him to,
what we're not allowed to invite him to.
And it's like,
I don't want to be lying to Scott.
It's a weird, [bleep] up situation.
Not just for me,
for everyone at the table.
[Jonathan] Oh, boy.
Oh, my god, I'm dying.
[upbeat electronic music]
[Kim] What is this water jug?
Water hydrates your body.
[Kim] I know, but, like, how crazy for you
to carry around a big jug.
So I suffer the curse of camel toe.
Like, don't you know by now
that camel toe is not a curse?
[Khloé] So, you are being a bump on a log.
Do you want to take over DASH on your own?
Why? Why wouldn't you
just want to all do it?
We're about to be making moves.
How? Tell me when.
We're building an app
so people can shop online.
I'm doing a full revamp.
How long is this gonna take, four years?
Yeah, you move like a [bleep] slug.
I don't think we should close DASH Miami.
[Khloé scoffing]
Then you're an idiot.
I think it is a blessing from God
that a huge department store
wants to buy DASH.
That was our end goal,
and Kourtney just can't [bleep] go
with the [bleep] flow.
I don't get it.
Like she wants to be at DASH every day.
It's laughable 'cause she's the last one
to do any sort of hard labor.
She wants to live in Nantucket
with her kids and a horse and carriage.
What are we doing now?
What profit do we make?
What this or that? Nothing.
It's not always about money.
But I'm saying just wait, let's figure out
what it is without you being, like,
"I don't know.
I don't know if I want to do it."
For real, what the [bleep]
we're doing now is what?
-Getting started.
-What you just said…
Getting started?
We've had the [bleep] store
for four million years, literally!
[Khloé] Are you [bleep] on drugs?
You're complaining
about tile on the floor.
You can't even do
the [bleep] buying on time!
It's ridiculous.
-[Khloé] We're getting rid of the store.
-We've worked so hard
to get to this place.
I don't like that my sisters feel like
they're just ready to let go of DASH
so easily.
I just really think that our stores are
more than just a business.
How dare you really try to argue us
on getting rid of the [bleep] stores.
We're getting rid of the stores, Kourtney!
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Smell this out of the bottle.
I want a gardenia scent.
Smells like pure throw-up.
[laughing]
Like, legit.
Wait, it really does. That's so weird.
Um, I just wanted to talk to you
about this whole DASH situation.
I know that, like, you don't care as much
about the stores anymore.
But I just, I don't know,
I feel like it's, like, sentimental.
[Kourtney] After Dad passed away,
having DASH really gave us something
to do together as sisters
and kept us together.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-And so, I just feel like
as long as we get our merchandising down,
we should definitely keep our stores,
100 percent.
I mean, I haven't really been,
like, thinking about
why you've been fighting so hard
to keep it and, like, now I kind of get it
and it makes sense.
From a business standpoint,
sometimes it's easy to forget
that, like, you know,
the DASH stores are really sentimental.
You know, it's been a long road for us.
I do wish Kourtney would look at it
a little bit differently,
but I'll try really hard to look at it
from her point of view
and really understand how she feels.
I think you should just be,
like, open to other options.
Yeah, I am.
Um, Scott texted me that he didn't want
to come to the concert tonight,
just because he wanted
to give you your space.
I feel like he's, like,
shutting himself off
because he doesn't want to feel
like he's stepping on your toes.
And I feel bad.
No, you can't feel bad for him.
He's invited to everything.
Like, I can't breathe.
I get it, but you can't change what you do
when he's there, so you just just have to,
like, live your life.
He lived his life.
I mean, I definitely don't want to have,
like, a Mean Girls situation
and feel like
I'm trying to not include Scott
and hurt his feelings.
I feel like you should call him
and be like,
"Look, we're all going to the concert.
Don't be ridiculous.
Of course you're invited."
Maybe I can try to not let him
affect my mood and see how it goes.
[line ringing]
-[Scott over phone] Hi.
-Hi. We're all in Miami together.
So, I feel like you should come
to the concert tonight.
[Scott]
I definitely want to go to the concert,
but I feel like it's a few nights,
and I thought,
like, tonight was your big night out
with all your friends,
and everybody was, like,
excited to go out after, so,
I don't know, I was gonna maybe
just go to the show a different night
and let you do your thing tonight.
If you want to go to the concert,
-you should just go.
-[Scott] Listen, I just didn't want
to rain on your parade.
If you're down and you're comfortable,
of course I'd like to go with everybody.
Okay.
[Scott] All right, fun.
Sounds fun.
[Scott] Are you getting all dressed up?
-[Kourtney] Um, probably.
-[Scott] Look at you.
-[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Scott] All right, bye.
-Another good deed.
-[Kim] Put it in the deed book.
Write it down.
[upbeat electronic music]
[crowd cheering]
-[Kourtney] How are you?
-[Fat Joe] Hello.
[Kourtney] I randomly saw you
on Wendy Williams today.
-[Fat Joe] You did?
-[Jonathan] Did you?
[Kourtney] I was getting hair and makeup,
and they had it on.
[Jonathan] That was a good episode.
[Fat Joe]
Scott's, like, an honorary Terror Squad.
Totally.
[Jonathan] He's a real terror though.
[Fat Joe laughs]
Maurice. Respect, the god.
[Kourtney] Hi.
[indistinct chatter]
[Khloé] Yeezy, this is Tristan.
[Kim] Hey, how are you?
I knew it. Khloé shows up with a new guy…
All right, he's going on stage.
Let's go.
I knew she was messing with me,
but I'm just happy
that she's having a good time
and starting a new relationship.
He's a little young,
but I'm so excited to tell Jonathan
and, like, a couple of my friends.
[Kim] Steph, I need my phone.
I just need my phone to Snapchat.
I'm going on the stage.
-[upbeat music]
-[crowd cheering]
[Kim] He's getting his harness on.
We're backstage.
Look at these muscles, you guys.
He's about to go on stage.
[Kim] Look at these muscles!
Must work out.
Oh, he's running from me.
[Scott] Get ready, Marty.
[man laughs]
He's about to go up.
[crowd chanting]
Kanye! Kanye! Kanye!
[crowd cheering]
[crowd screaming, cheering]
[Kanye] I know y'all don't understand
what I went through to make this song.
That's what art is though, right?
That's what hip-hop is though, right?
I need y'all to sing it.
at the top of your lungs.
Let's go.
["Famous" by Kanye West
ft. Rihanna &amp; Swizz Beatz playing]
-[Rihanna] ♪ How it might be ♪
-[music stops]
[crowd singing]
♪ Kinda hard to love a girl like me ♪
-[music continues]
-♪ I don't blame you much ♪
♪ For wanting to be free ♪
♪ I just wanted you to… ♪
["Famous" by Kanye West ft. Rihanna
&amp; Swizz Beatz continues playing]
[Kanye shouts indistinctly]
[Kim] Kanye has thought
of this floating stage idea
for a few years now.
The venues were finding it hard to,
like, price the ticket sales
because Kanye wanted it moving around
and having everyone have
a really good seat.
They didn't get it at first.
And so they finally took
a chance on it, and it's, like,
the dopest stage ever.
I mean, the Saint Pablo Tour is like
one big house party.
[Kanye] ♪ For all my Southside [bleep] ♪
♪ That know me best ♪
♪ I feel like me and Taylor ♪
♪ Might still have sex, why? ♪
[crowd singing]
♪ I made that bitch famous ♪
[Kanye] ♪ Goddamn ♪
♪ I just wanted you to know ♪
♪ Bam bam 'ey 'ey 'ey ♪
♪ Bam bam bam, bam bam dilla ♪
[Kanye] ♪ How you feelin' out there? ♪
♪ Bam, bam bam ♪
♪ Bam bam dilla ♪
♪ Bam bam, bam… ♪
I'm having so much fun at the concert.
I'm glad that Scott and I can both be here
as individuals,
and I can be having a good time
and not affected by him.
♪ Bam bam ♪
♪ Bam bam bam bam ♪
-[song ends]
-[crowd cheering]
[upbeat electronic music]
[Kourtney] The remote?
No.
Thanks, man. Okay. Bye
-Hi, Daddy.
-Hi, buddy.
What did you think
about the quote for the drapes?
[Kourtney] I didn't really look at it,
I'm so…
telling you, I'm really behind.
-What do you do?
-[Reign blabbering]
-[Kourtney] Oh, here, Dory.
-[Reign] Dory.
-Oh, Storks is out.
-Just so I understand, so, like,
when I send you information,
do you just literally, like, skip over it?
-Like…
-Sometimes.
So maybe I should, like, spend time
doing other things maybe? Not…
-[Kourtney] Oh.
-…trying to help?
Is this Dory? Dory.
So I feel like, overall, Miami was good,
but…
I feel like
it's kind of awkward sometimes,
me and you.
I think it's more awkward
in social environments.
Like, in our day-to-day…
[Scott] Right, but that's the problem.
You and I are, like, somewhat
best friends every day, all day,
but then when it goes
into, like, a social place,
neither of us really know how to act,
and it just becomes uncomfortable.
-Is there a solution to this?
-[tense music]
Uh…
[sighs]
[Scott] Is there a solution to this?
Uh…
[sighs]
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, I do feel like I worry
about my actions setting you off
since you have been doing well.
It's not really fair for me
to feel that way.
I don't want you to have to feel
anxious or guilty.
There was a time in our life
when your actions would affect me.
Now, I've gotten older and realize
all the responsibility I have to take on.
Like, no offense to you,
but no matter what you do,
I can't change my life over it
for the worst.
Okay. I just feel like if I need to, like…
you know, I don't think
we need to do stuff 24/7.
I was trying to give you your space
to, like, have your own fun
-on your own terms, too, like…
-Yeah.
And you don't really communicate that well
and you're like,
it's always like,
"Oh, it's fine, it's whatever."
But then sometimes I feel like, you know,
I guess we both do need to do our thing
without us being together.
I don't know, I feel like maybe
there's times you want to run around
with all your girlfriends, like,
probably don't want your ex-boyfriend
to be there, I get it.
-Yeah.
-[Scott] You know what I'm saying?
-If I'm hitting the strip,
-I probably don't want you rolling.
-[Kourtney] No.
-Well, that's good to hear.
-[Scott] Yeah.
-So knock yourself out, kid.
-[Kourtney] Oh, yeah.
-[blabbering]
-Buckle your seat belt.
I'm happy that Scott is bringing this up.
Communicating is something
that we're clearly
not the best at together.
I just think it's gonna be
a constant process
of figuring out how to live life,
like, parenting our kids
and still being a family,
but not being together.
[remote clatters]
[Scott] I hear you, buddy.
I know the feeling.
[Scott] He's a Disick, I get it.
[upbeat electronic music]
[Khloé] Hi, Mom!
[Kris]
Guess what I'm making this afternoon.
-Cinnamon rolls.
-From whose recipe?
-[Kris] Khloé Kardashian.
-I actually have--
-[Kourtney] These are the cars
that I was maybe gonna get.
-Is this too crazy?
-I like it.
You know what, when I sent Mom
a recipe, I even sent her visuals.
I'm a really good…
It's like, why do I try
with all of you guys?
[Khloé]
You won't ever get one 'cause of that.
[Kim] So, I've really been thinking
about what you said
about how DASH is just,
like, super sentimental.
Mm-hm.
You know, it's, like, more to us
than just our store.
It's, like, something
that we've all built together
-as, like, sisters.
-Mm-hm.
So are we doing the deal?
[Kourtney] Yeah, what's happening?
[Khloé] So, are we doing the deal?
We're waiting for the offer,
as far as an upfront payment.
[Kim] So, we can figure out
the deal later,
about, like, what we do online
and other stuff later,
but I think, for now,
that we should get rid of New York.
Since we opened up the online store,
I think that that really cancels it out,
and it's just,
like, a better business decision.
Agreed.
[Kris]
Miami is such a great tourist location.
People go there from all over the country.
[Kim] Yeah, I mean, I think
we want to keep Miami open.
[Kourtney] Yes.
[Kim] Just get a whole new buying team,
we're gonna order so much more merchandise
that's all the current stuff
that we're wearing,
and we're just gonna focus back on DASH.
'Kay.
I decided to, kind of, reevaluate
what DASH means to us.
We put so much, like, blood, sweat,
and tears into this business.
-[Khloé] Hello. DASH.
-[laughter]
[Kim groans]
Hey, don't, Khlo!
[screams]
[Kim] I guess at the end of the day,
it just makes so much sense
to close the New York store
'cause rent is so expensive.
But with Miami, I think we're gonna find
a really good team
that we feel comfortable with,
and pay attention more
and put more effort and time into it,
which I think we're all willing to do.
[Kris] I'm really glad
you guys are gonna keep DASH.
Makes me really happy.
It's really your roots
and how you guys got started
in fashion in 2004…
Oh, I remember it.
Let's reminisce.
[Kris] That was some of the best years
of our lives, you guys.
[Kourtney]
I used to give everyone Zipfizz.
Do you remember that stuff?
You pour it in your water
and I would shake it
and I would make them for everyone
and I would go,
"Let's start vacuuming."
We would be going nuts.
Kourtney and I cleaned both stores.
[Khloé] We never ate one time.
And we did inventory, cleaned the stores,
did the whole back rooms,
and we had, like, the best day.
And I was like,
"Y'all, I don't know what you gave me,
that was literally the craziest thing."
[chuckles softly]
[slurps]
It's really hard to drink with a lip ring.
[scoffs]
[Kim] Coming up next week…
Bonjour!
Oh, my god, I cannot believe
we're at Paris Fashion Week.
Givenchy, here we come.
I can't believe this is the first time
Kourtney's seen me walk.
[applause]
[dispatcher speaks in French over phone]
2-1-1 speaking, good evening.
What is your emergency?
I just said, "Please, I have a family.
Like, let me live."
Either they're gonna shoot me in the back
or if the elevator does not open in time,
I'm [bleep]. There's no way out.