[Kim] After Paris,
one of my first things is going to Dubai
and doing this master class.
If I don't make it out alive,
just tell my family I love them.
My anxiety is so high, and I feel like,
"Is this really what I should be doing?"
[cheering]
[Man1] Make some noise!
Scott Disick!
[Scott] I'm in Dubai and I found out
that Kourtney was with somebody.
This is the worst thing
I could ever hear.
[Kim] I know it bothers him.
Scott starts texting me about Kourtney,
and I feel so bad for him.
It just really sucks,
'cause he's been doing amazing.
-Whose purse is that?
-[Chris] I don't know.
[Kim] Girls are here?
Should we go in
and scare the [bleep] out of her?
[theme music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Or do you think we should go
bang down the bathroom door
and see what [bleep] whore is in there?
Should we go in there?
What the [bleep] are you doing here?
Seriously?
You're just like a [bleep] whore.
Such a tramp.
Get your [bleep]
and get the [bleep] out of here.
[bleep] groupie.
Get your [bleep],
and security will escort you
the [bleep] out of here!
[door shuts]
Hey, we're gonna go.
And I just think it's better
that we go by ourselves.
-What?
-We'll talk about it later.
But I'm gonna go
and enjoy the rest of my time
in the desert.
I don't think we need to talk
in front of everyone.
What are you even talking about?
What am I talking about?
The [bleep] girl in your room.
I don't want to feel sympathy for you
after you feel bad about Kourt.
[Scott] She's made it clear
that we're not together.
[Kim] But you made me feel
really bad about it and you're--
Feel bad about what?
[Kim] I don't want
to feel sympathy for you
'cause you felt bad that my sister,
there was a rumor of her
hanging out with a guy.
It was not a rumor.
Why do you care what Kourtney does
or why are you even getting mad at her
if you're doing the same thing?
[Security] I'll get your stuff.
Go out the door.
[Carla] You're so disgusting.
[Security] Let me grab her purse.
[chuckling] This is bad.
[Kim] Whatever.
I just don't want to be involved.
It's just not my style.
The last thing I want to do
is be in the middle of this right now.
And I just… I feel so duped.
Like, he made me feel so bad
about their situation.
But he's, like, living life
doing whatever he wants to do.
[Jen] How did you get the bathroom open?
[Kim] It was open.
She was about to come out,
'cause she heard the elevator.
[Simon] My heart is pounding
from all that excitement.
Okay, let me call Kanye back.
[line ringing]
Hey, babe, are you awake?
I just caught a girl in Scott's room
and went so [bleep] ghetto on her.
All of my friends…
like, literally, jaws dropped.
Like, who is this ghetto girl?
Like, Stephanie and I are, like, shaking.
I'll tell you all when you're awake.
Go back to bed.
Okay, love you. Bye.
I did see her shaking.
-[Kim] No, trembling.
-Yeah.
Wait, I'm calling Kourtney.
-Just wait till 7:00.
-Till 7:00, yeah.
-[Jen] It's 4:00 in the morning.
-'Kay.
Ooh, that girl does not know
what just hit her, man.
[Kim sniffing] Ugh, I felt…
I need deodorant.
I forgot to put on deodorant.
That's what it is.
After I showered this morning.
[Simon chuckles] How bad?
Bad.
Like a man?
[Carla] This is
because you were being so you?
Smell it. It's so gross.
[Simon] Oh, my God, Steph!
[Stephanie] You don't smell!
[groaning]
[Oriental upbeat music playing]
[Simon] Oh, my goodness. Yes.
Yes.
[Oriental upbeat music continues]
[Kim] Can I take a picture?
[Carla] Kim, you want to hold it?
Should I? I'm afraid.
[Stephanie] You got it, you got it. Yes.
[Kim] Even though I am so pissed at Scott,
I'm just gonna not think about it--
not think about this girl,
not think about Scott being wasted,
not think about
what I'm gonna say to Kourt
and have fun with my friends.
[Stephanie] All right.
[chuckling] Ooh, my God!
Ooh.
[engines revving]
-[Kim] Which one am I going in?
-[Carla] Yeah. I don't go fast.
[Simon] This is beyond, by the way.
[engines revving]
-[Stephanie laughing]
-Yes!
[whooping]
Yes!
Yeah!
[overlapping chatter, squealing]
[Carla] So dope. [sighs]
[Simon] Guys, how was it?
-[Carla] So fun.
-[Jen] Scary.
[Simon] This angle's nice
'cause you see the sand.
[Man3] Three, two…
[camera shutter clicks]
[Simon] Oh, my God,
-this is literally wild.
-[Jen] You guys,
-it's the cover of our album.
-[Simon] Cover.
-Yes.
-[Stephanie] Oh, my God, I love it.
[Kim] I'm glad we did it.
[engines revving]
[Jen] It smells like a camel in here.
[Simon] Oh, I reek.
[Carla] Kim's armpits.
[Kim] No, my armpits don't smell anymore.
[Oriental upbeat music playing]
[phone rings]
[Kim] Kourt's calling.
Hey.
I feel bad.
Like, I do feel bad
for yelling at the girl
and scaring her
and pulling her out of the bathroom.
You know, like, that part,
she's definitely traumatized.
[Kourtney] I would have done that
if Kanye had a girl,
even if you guys weren't together.
-You know?
-[Kim] Yeah.
It's just, like, what you do.
It's just, like, your reaction.
I think it's just also
because he was talking to you
and trying to say things,
like, as if I'm doing something wrong.
Like, I try to be as low-key as possible,
you know?
[Kim] Yeah.
When does he get back here?
-[Stephanie] 8:35.
-8:35.
P.m.?
-Yeah.
-Okay, good.
I have a full nother day without him.
[Kim] I think that Kourtney always had
this thought in her mind
that she wanted him to be sober
and then she would consider
getting back with him.
I know she wanted him to do that
for himself first.
And it's really not fair for Scott
to hang this guilt over Kourtney.
This has nothing to do with her.
[Kourtney] I feel like we just need
to figure out a better way
to, like, separate our stuff.
Like, I don't need to deal with
this nonsense any longer.
Yeah, you don't.
[upbeat music playing]
[Mariam] Hi. How are you?
How are you doing?
Mariam. I'm the director.
-Sheikh Mohammed bin Maktoum.
-Kim. Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Announcer] Please give a warm welcome
to Kim Kardashian.
[applause]
[Kim] While I'm in Dubai,
I had this trip planned
to a children's hospital
and care center for the disabled.
I really want to explore the culture.
And I love
that there's, you know, really good people
in this world
that do really positive things.
It's such an amazing program.
[Mariam] Oh, my God, who's she?
[Student1] It's Kim Kardashian!
I made it with a sandwich wrapper.
[Student2] We made cookies in the workshop
and cakes.
[Mariam] Making cookies
in the workshop, yes.
[Kim] Oh, my gosh, amazing. Thank you.
You made this? Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
Hi. That was amazing.
[camera shutters clicking]
[Man4] Thank you.
[Announcer] The lovely Kim Kardashian.
[applause]
[Kim] I was really nervous
coming on this trip,
but I'm glad that I'm taking the steps
and making the moves to, you know,
slowly get my life back on track
and feel comfortable and safe.
[cheering]
Seeing these children
and the amazing people
that are working there
and taking care of them,
it's so heartwarming.
This is, like, what life's about.
[Announcer] Thank you
for coming here in Dubai.
[cheering and applause]
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Hello?
-[Scott] Hey.
-[Kim] Hey.
Scott just texted me
that he wants to talk about what happened.
And I'm just, like, angry and annoyed.
It's gonna be so awkward.
Ugh, I hate confrontation.
[Scott] Forget about our confrontation.
You got into, like, a full fight
with somebody for no reason.
[Kim] But, like, I didn't know what to do.
Like, I just… It was my first reaction,
you know what I mean?
-I don't know…
-Yeah. I spoke to Kourtney about it.
Kourtney was like, "I have no intentions
of us working things out, really."
"I want to live my life, you live yours."
And I'm like, "I would've loved
to have just been with you and that's it.
But that's not what you want,
and that's fine.
But you just weren't honest and told me."
And I'm not even trying to play games.
But, yeah, I'm not gonna lie,
it's hard to [bleep] sleep at night.
You know what I'm saying?
So I'm like, "[bleep]."
Puts me in a weird position.
I don't want
to be doing half this [bleep],
but I don't know
what else to [bleep] do with my time
to take my mind off of it.
I don't want to be in the middle,
and I don't want to be
like, "I have to tell Kourtney,"
'cause I have to tell Kourtney.
You know what I mean?
I don't want things to be awkward,
but I don't want to feel bad.
She never, ever gives me
any kind of pat on the back for anything.
Yeah.
The only time I hear from her,
if it's something negative.
The second she hears
that she's got something
to be mad at me for,
she then calls me
and then actually talks to me.
[dance music playing]
[Kourtney] Hi, guys.
I didn't know I had the pleasure
to eat with both of you guys.
Yeah.
[Kim] How are you?
[Kourtney] Good. Tired?
-[Kanye] Is that the chai tea?
-[Kim] Yeah. I'm gonna sweeten it up.
[Kourtney] You guys ever had Matcha?
No. What's Matcha?
It's, like, green tea,
but more caffeine.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, I don't want
to start anything, but…
What?
[Kim] Scott was so out of it in Dubai.
He was sitting up there.
-Didn't try to save this girl to--
-But did he say anything?
Did he say, "Don't go down…?"
No, not a thing. Didn't even flinch.
-Didn't even care.
-Yeah.
But then, Scott and I had
a really good talk.
He was like, "I don't plan on drinking
when I get home."
Think it was just a quick, little thing.
I don't know. I guess we'll see.
But I can tell when he's a little off.
But I did call him, and I said,
"Hey, I heard what happened,
and I don't care,
so just, you need to stop trying
to make me feel bad for anything I'm doing
and make everyone else try to feel bad."
But I do think where you go wrong…
[Kourtney] Mm-hmm.
…is you go to Cabo with him,
you go to Aspen with him,
and he thinks he's trying to impress you.
-Mm-hmm. Right.
-He gets the check,
he gets the this, he has the security.
I mean, he tells me like,
"Oh, we had such a nice time."
-You'll watch a movie with him.
-But I said,
"You have the best of both worlds.
I could do my thing,
and you could do your thing."
"What a great scenario."
To be honest, if Scott
got his [bleep] together,
I feel like you would be with him.
Yeah, it is your baby daddy of three.
[Kourtney] Yeah. But, you know,
it's his fault we're not together.
[Kim] Yeah.
What do you think of this guy?
[Kourtney] But aren't those
the kind of dogs that die right away?
They're literally that big.
-They only get up to three pounds.
-[Kanye] Are they called "Pomeranians"
-'cause they fit in your palm?
-[chuckling] No.
[upbeat music playing]
[door opens, closes]
Hello.
Hello?
Um, squad goals.
What the [bleep] is this?
[Simone] Isn't that…?
No, it's a… It goes up.
It's literally like a cool jockey strap.
[Simone] Yeah, that… It's like… it's like…
[Khloe] You don't want me
in your fittings, I know, Simone.
-[Simone] No. I…
-[Khloe] I know.
The fact that Simone
still hangs out with you,
and you basically got her killed is wild.
-My God! Khloe.
-[Kim] You know what?
But had help come sooner,
they would have been killed.
[Khloe] I know.
-[Kim] So…
-[Khloe] Yeezy balls.
-I like that jacket.
-Oh, me, too, darling.
Thanks for designing it.
So, this isn't, like,
your trip-packing, right?
-[Kim] No.
-Oh.
Every year, we go on a family trip,
and we always try to do
something new and different.
This year, I'm super excited
to be going to Costa Rica.
Kylie, T's coming on the trip, right?
[Kylie] Mm-hmm.
-That's fun.
-[Kylie] King's coming, too.
[Khloe] That's cool.
Super excited
to go to Costa Rica with my family
and just spend some QT time…
-[Kim] And you're planning it all.
-Good choice.
[Khloe whoops]
Planning it all. I'm excited.
The Kardashians in Costa Rica.
[laughter]
[Khloe] He's not coming, right-- Ye?
-[Kim] No.
-[Kylie] I'm gonna go home.
-[Khloe] Okay.
-I have lots of things to do tonight.
[Kim] At least my bags are packed.
Bye, guys. I know
I just walked out really abruptly, but…
[Khloe] Bye, Kylie.
I love our trips.
There's so many things
that I want to do,
-and I--
-What do you want to do?
Adventurous, fun things.
If there's a bunch of monkeys,
I want to be with the monkeys,
and not have Mom like,
"Do they have fleas?"
"I can't be around animals with fleas."
"Rah, rah, rah!"
The point is
to, like, be one with the people,
the culture, the animales.
Everyone has
their own lives and families now,
and a part of my life is in Cleveland,
so I'm in Cleveland a lot of my time.
And I just feel like this family trip
is needed for all of us,
especially me,
'cause I miss everybody.
[Kim] Get over here, boo-boo.
[Saint babbles]
What's this stank face
you've been making lately?
[birds squawking]
[birds chirping]
[Kim] I want, like, a warm hot chocolate
with marshmallows is really what I want,
because it's freezing,
-and that'll warm my soul.
-You want that hot tea
that's, like, the apple
-with the honey and all that?
-I'll have anything.
I mean, I feel bad
that I woke you guys all up
so early this morning.
I think I woke up
with, like, 150 text messages.
Can you believe that they found them?
I honestly never thought
that they would catch the robbers.
I just thought so much time has gone on,
and I didn't really realize
how diligent the French police were being
and just all the hard work
they were really putting into it.
And to find out
that there were so many people involved,
hearing detail after detail,
really just opened up
a whole different perspective for me
of feeling safe.
They got the fingerprints
of two guys inside,
and then I think they tapped their phones
and went from there.
How would they get their fingerprints?
They weren't wearing gloves?
They were wearing gloves,
but he left the duct tape,
and that already had fingerprints
from when they were at home
putting it in the bag.
[Kourtney] Oh.
Do you feel better?
Like, do you feel relieved or anything?
It definitely opened up my eyes
to a whole different world
that I can't erase.
I can't go backward.
Like, life is always gonna be different.
Now I just have to be, like, super aware
of everything that I do
and who I share it with.
-You know?
-Mm-hmm.
So… I have to go to New York
from Costa Rica, from our family trip
to go meet with, like, the French judge.
-Oh, really?
-Mm-hmm.
So that I don't have to go to Paris.
Knowing that it's a possibility
that people close to me were involved
makes me feel I can't trust anyone,
and that really sucks.
It just opened up my eyes
that this happens,
and that there's, you know,
really bad people
in this world.
I could still live my life,
but just on edge.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kourtney] Daddy's coming, I think.
[Reign] Okay.
[Scott] Ooh! Where's Marty?
-[Kourtney] Look who it is.
-[Reign] Where's Marty?
Oh, hey. Hi! Hi!
-Hi, Daddy.
-Hi.
I'm so excited to go to Costa Rica,
and Scott was invited on the family trip
before his trip to Dubai.
You go on that one?
-I go on that one.
-"On dat one"?
[Kourtney] He seemed really excited
planning different activities
for the kids,
and I think he's fine to come along.
[Kim] Who's excited to see the monkeys?
King, are you excited?
There's gonna be a beach, too.
[Khloe laughs]
We are about to go to Costa Rica.
We have to have two separate planes
because there's so many of us.
For me, the more, the merrier.
I love the family dynamic
and all of us hanging out.
Everyone loves your curly hair.
-[North] Yeah.
-You didn't know that?
Sadly, Kendall and Rob
were not able to make it,
because Kendall
has some work commitments,
and Rob just had a baby,
so he is being a new daddy
with his family.
[Kourtney] You want a pretzel?
Thank you, Mom!
Thank you, Mommy.
Oh, you're welcome, my angel.
[Reign] Thank you.
[King] We're getting higher and higher!
We're in the air.
Kanye was having, like, major FOMO
knowing that all you guys were coming.
[Tyga] Why didn't he come?
[Kim] He wanted to come.
He almost changed his mind last minute.
But I'm going to New York,
and he's been so comfortable
staying at home.
I have to fly from Costa Rica to New York,
when our trip is over,
'cause I have to go in front of the judge
to give my testimony.
I don't want to overwhelm anyone else
with all my robbery stuff.
I can handle it, you know, by myself,
and just get it done.
Are you okay?
No offense, but I'm not feeling well.
[Kim] I'm kind of stressed.
It's overwhelming.
This is overwhelming for me,
in such a big way.
I'm usually 150% in on a vacation,
but it's been so challenging
going through this whole process
with Caitlyn and her book.
I can't seem to stop thinking about it.
So my wish on this trip
is to rejuvenate my mind, body, soul,
and not worry about a thing.
[Latino music playing]
[Penelope] Say, "Welcome
to Costa Rica," Reign.
Rica.
[Penelope laughs]
[Kim] Thank you so much.
Hey. Yeah, we're going to the house now.
You would have probably thought
the flight was brutal,
with all the kids,
like, packed on a plane.
Like Snakes on a Plane?
[Kim chuckles] Okay. Bye.
[Kanye] Love you.
Love you, too. Bye.
Aren't you excited to be here?
I am.
I feel like it'll be fun.
Is Scott staying in our villa?
I forgot he was even coming.
I know.
He hasn't spoken to me
'cause he knows he [bleep] up in Dubai.
But, like, did he [bleep] up in Dubai?
Like, yeah, he was majorly inappropriate,
-but, like, they're not together.
-They're not,
but she leads him on.
Going to, like, Aspen together
for New Year's is strange.
-Yeah, I told her that.
-I said, "You're giving him false hope.
I understand why he thinks
you guys are together.
I think you're together."
You do what you do, who cares?
If Scott were to own it,
no one would give a [bleep].
It's from the-- literally,
the two different personalities.
Yeah.
Why don't you wear your sister necklace?
It's so rude.
You just don't believe in our sisterhood?
You know I do, but I have it at home
-sitting right on my thing.
-Okay.
[Latino music playing]
[Penelope] Come on. Let's go.
[Kourtney] Hey, Mart, what do you think?
[Reign] Yeah.
[Kourtney] Ooh!
-[Host] Welcome to Villa Manzu.
-Yeah, thank you.
Do you guys want a towel?
We're in Costa Rica, girl.
[Penelope] Yeah.
[Khloe] Ooh.
[Kourtney] Hey, guys.
This is so nice. It's amazing.
[Scott] Wow, this place is wild, Mase.
[Hostess] Would you like
some fresh coconut water?
-[Kourtney] It's so good.
-[Khloe] Greetings.
Is this your new house?
-[Kourtney] Hi.
-It's beautiful.
-[Kourtney] Welcome to my house.
-[King] Mason!
[Kourtney] Aw.
[Khloe] This is so pretty.
Look at the pool.
That's nice.
[Khloe] The house that I found
for all of us in Costa Rica
is absolutely gorgeous.
You're submerged in the rain forest.
And because it's our first night,
I have something
a little special for everybody
that I'm super excited
to surprise them with.
[fireworks exploding]
Oh, my God.
Look, you guys.
[kids cheering]
[Kris] That is so cool.
[North] Wow.
[Kourtney] Oh, Khloe, this is so romantic.
[Mason] Real fireworks!
Next to Kylie and Tyga.
[Kris] Look at that one.
[Khloe] Oh, how pretty. Look it, you guys.
[Khloe] It seems like every family member
is oohing and aahing,
so pat on my back.
I mean, I pulled this off,
and I should probably plan
every family trip.
[all cheering]
So you're not gonna stay at the house?
[Scott] No.
Why? Just stay here.
[Scott] I like my own space.
I feel you,
but you should have stayed here.
[laughing]
In Costa Rica I'll be staying
at a hotel down the street,
because I only really get lonely,
and then start to annoy myself more
that the girl I used to be with
is down the hallway
and I'm not sleeping with her.
What has my life come to?
So I don't really feel like
there's any reason for me
to sleep under the same roof.
Kourt, look at P and North.
[Khloe] You guys are so cute.
Doesn't that make you guys happy
-that they're, like, best friends?
-[Kim] Yeah.
[Kourtney] Can I sit next to you?
This is gluten-free bread.
You can dip it in that oil.
[Penelope] Where's my mac and cheese?
[Kourtney] You didn't order
mac and cheese.
This is what you ordered, babe.
[Penelope] No, I don't like my quesadilla.
-Babe, babe.
-[Kourtney] She doesn't like
when I call her "babe."
She likes when I call her "honey."
[Kris] It's interesting
that your genes are so strong,
because Kourtney's genes
were really strong.
She was the most Armenian-looking baby
-that I had.
-Oh. They came out all right.
[Kris] You should have another one
just for the hell of it.
[Khloe] Babe, what are you guys
most excited to do?
[Penelope] Nothing.
-[Kris] I'm with you, P.
-[Scott] Me, too.
I knew Lovey would be with you.
Nothing is so relaxing.
-[Khloe] What about whitewater rafting?
-[Kris] Tubing.
[Khloe] Okay, whatever.
You're not doing any of this, Mom?
Why not?
[Kris] 'Cause that's what
people that are 61 do.
[Khloe] Like, why do you fly
all the way out here to do what?
Like, we want to bond with you.
[Kris laughs] All right.
I get not wanting to do that
and staying here and laying out.
We're going
to the dinosaur park, aren't we?
-[Scott] That was my idea.
-[Kourtney] Yeah, we're going
-and we'll take the kids.
-[ringtone playing]
[Khloe] Hi, Kylie.
Why would you go up to my room, anyway?
Kylie wants to hijack my room.
You guys are ass[bleep].
-[Tyga] Good-bye, room.
-[Kylie] Good-bye.
This is what I'm talking about.
A real couple's sanctuary.
Yeah, it's more romantic up here.
This is romantic.
Drinks?
There's a fridge?
Oh, my God. They played us.
[Khloe] What the [bleep] is going on?
[Kylie] Khloe, we're stealing your room.
Thank you.
Thank you? You didn't ask.
You guys just moved--
I don't know
how you brought that back down here,
but that's the price you pay.
[Tyga laughs]
And by the way, every trip,
I've never gotten the big room.
I'm always wherever. So then you guys--
I'm literally at dinner for 15 minutes,
and you guys take my room.
-[Tyga] Mm-hmm.
-You should have been watching.
[Khloe] Note to self,
get my own house when I come here.
Hmm. Got to.
Got to boss up.
[Khloe over P.A.] ♪ Good morning! ♪
♪ This is our day in Costa Rica. ♪
There's so much to do.
The sun is shining.
Everybody, get up.
Kourtney, Kimberly, Mom.
Everybody!
Good morning, princess.
Good morning, Kingie.
Oh, yeah. Good morning.
[Kris] Hi, honey.
[Khloe] Look how beautiful it is, guys.
Mm-hmm.
You're up kind of late for yourself.
I haven't even woken up yet.
[Khloe] That's fine.
Yeah.
What's your bracelet?
Corey gave me that,
like, two years ago.
[Khloe] It's so pretty.
[Kris] Oh, thank you.
[Khloe] Mase, where are you going?
I'll see you in a little.
[Khloe] Okay. I'll see you in a little.
Mom, how long
have you guys been boning for?
[mystery music plays]
-Khloe.
-Okay, dating.
-Same thing.
-I remember that first night
like it was yesterday.
Ew.
How long have you guys been dating for?
-Two and a half years.
-Wow.
[Corey] It'll be three years this summer,
the day we started,
getting it.
[Khloe] Okay.
Why are you sitting over there?
That's Kris Jenner.
[Kris] I haven't had much rest in a while.
And on this trip I just want to relax.
So, Khloe's gonna have to accept that
at some point,
and stop torturing me.
I'll be fine. I just need to eat.
This is why these vacations
normally just aren't vacations.
[Corey] You have Khloe
screwing a knife to her head.
-I just--
-[Corey] She want
-to spend time with you and bond.
-Because I never see you guys.
Jesus Christ.
-So, what, here?
-[Corey] Yeah.
Tell me about Cleveland.
[Khloe] It's nice.
But it snows there. There's seasons.
I wish Tristan wasn't playing basketball,
-because he could be on this vacation.
-[Khloe] Well, I don't.
I don't. That's his career.
I don't wish he wasn't playing basketball.
I know, but I mean it'd be nice
if he was on vacation.
When are you gonna bring him
on a family vacation?
I mean, we would go
on, like, a private family vacation,
but I don't want him to be on camera
-anytime soon.
-[Kris] Yeah.
[Khloe] Our lives are, like, so great
and it's so good
and, like, I need to keep
some things to myself.
I agree.
[upbeat music playing]
What is that?
You would love those crackers
in the other room.
Have you had 'em?
[Kourtney] Rice cereal, honey rice.
-Hey, what's up, girls?
-[Khloe] Hello.
-[Kourtney] Hey.
-[Corey] What's going down?
[Kourtney] Sorry.
Y'all should, like, do this sometime,
like, have a slumber party,
then gossip and talk all night.
With Kim in one bed
-and Kourtney and I in another.
-We should.
Yeah, the big girls and the little girls.
That would be fun.
[Corey] Well, when it happens,
y'all can't have cell phones.
Y'all just gonna have each other,
like good old days.
Good old conversation.
Does anyone find Scott weird?
[Khloe] Oh, my God.
Playing in the bed, the guy…
[Scott] I'm just trying
to talk to my wife.
She's not your wife.
Oh, I forgot.
Khloe, help me.
Oh.
[Kourtney] I don't know
how many more times I could say,
it ain't happening.
Khloe, help me, help me.
[Khloe] I don't know
if this is, like, what you want.
It's typical Scott behavior, I think.
But do you think he does that
because you don't say no?
I think I probably do say no.
Yeah, you're like, "Stop!
[giggles]
Stop!"
[laughs]
[Kourtney laughing]
[Khloe] You guys, stop kissing!
Whatever we're thinking,
I'm ready to go.
[Khloe] Ew.
[bleep] Awkward.
[Kourtney laughs]
[uplifting music playing]
[Kourtney] I think I'm just gonna make
the tiniest to-go plate.
You ready for your journey?
[Kris] Mm-hmm.
[Kim] I know it's really annoying,
and I'm sorry.
I want to sit in this seat.
-[North] Mom?
-[Kim] Mm-hmm?
Uh, P said this is
where real dinosaurs were,
but they're not.
No, there's no real dinosaurs.
They're all pretend.
-Take a picture for me, okay?
-[North] Okay.
Big hug. I love you so much.
[Scott] Let's try to do this.
Let's do it.
[Pilot] Hi.
[Scott] Every time
that we go on a vacation,
I try to find something that's special
that we can experience as a family.
So I found this dinosaur park
in Costa Rica
that I thought the kids would love.
They're into dinosaurs.
I'm excited.
[Mason] Hello, everybody.
-[Kourtney] Are you the tour guide?
-[Mason] Yeah.
[Scott] Please keep your hands
-and feet inside.
-Is that a dinosaur down there?
[Scott] What! You saw one, where?
-[Kourtney] That white thing?
-Oh, no.
[Kourtney] This is our first time
seeing Costa Rica in the daytime.
It's so green, so beautiful.
It's nothing I've ever seen before.
I'm just excited
for, like, a fun adventurous day.
[Scott] Let's go.
[Mason] Dino park this way.
[Kourtney] Look, Mase,
this is people's houses.
That's how they dry their clothes
after they wash them.
I love seeing this kind of stuff.
No matter what is going on
with me and Scott,
having him there with the kids
so that they can have these memories
is really important to me.
[Tour guide] All right, my friends,
we are in the dino park now.
Follow me, please.
[Scott] What do you think, North?
-[North] I think it's real.
-[Scott] I think it's real, too.
[dinosaur roars over speakers]
What the heck?
[Kourtney] Ooh.
[Reign] Dinosaur.
[Kourtney] Dinosaur.
Look at it, Reigny.
[dinosaur roars]
-What do you think?
-[Reign shrieks]
-[Kourtney laughs]
-[Reign] Uh-oh, dinosaur!
[Kourtney] Look, Northie.
See?
-[Scott] Guys, that's not nice.
-[Kourtney] Don't bother them
'cause they'll eat you
and it's not healthy for them.
[Scott] This is pretty amazing, huh?
[Kourtney] Dad, you want
to hold him for a sec?
[Reign] Daddy.
Those are dinosaurs.
[Scott] There's definitely two ways
of looking at the situation
with myself and Kourtney.
We get to spend
all these amazing moments
together with our kids.
But then, at night, where you'd want
to have the other side of the relationship
we don't have,
just frustrates me and makes me sad and…
[Kourtney] You guys want to get a snack?
[North] Can I have a lollipop?
[Kourtney] Yes.
Can we get uno de este?
Gracias.
[Kourtney] Oh, si.
Oh, she wants one with Mase.
[Scott] Stop.
[Kourtney] Get it, Mase.
Get it, Mase, yeah.
I'll take it.
[Scott] Oh, my God.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloe] Let's go.
[grunts]
[King] Swimming?
[Khloe] Pull it down.
[King] Okay.
[Khloe] Ay-ay-ay.
[King giggles]
[Khloe] Hey, King, King.
[King] Daddy!
[Tyga] What's up, man? You out the pool?
[Khloe] I think what I planned for
was all of us to spend
at least, like, day one together.
Scott and the kids go into the dino park--
totally get it.
And then, like, Kim just wanting
to lay out, I get that, too.
But being divided,
it just isn't what I… planned.
[Scott] Whew.
I'm gonna go shower.
[Kourtney] Are we eating at your hotel?
[Scott] Yeah, at 6:00.
Love you.
Mmm, mmm.
[Kourtney] Stop.
-[Scott] Love you.
-[Mason] I love you.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloe] Wow, what a nice room you have.
What are you wearing?
[Kim] Just, like, a dress.
What's happened?
I'm not wearing this to dinner.
Is that what you're wearing to dinner?
Yeah.
-It's cute.
-Sorry to disappoint you.
[Kim] I have some news to share with you.
Oh, my God, you're pregnant.
[Kim] Oh, you think that every time.
I'm just kidding, I'm kidding.
I just wanted to [bleep] with you.
Um… so you're gonna die.
No, I don't like these kind of things.
What's happening?
No, you're gonna [bleep] die.
[Khloe] What?
[Kim] So, Scott flew out a girl.
Yeah.
Stop.
[Kim] Yeah. So that's why he's staying
at the other hotel.
Her name is Chelsea.
On our family trip with the kids?
[Kim] With the kids.
[Khloe] Like, I-I don't believe it.
I'm in shock.
Who the [bleep] does something like this?
You were just downstairs
literally trying to make out with Kourt.
How dare you?
Chelsea... hold on.
[Kim] We need to get Kourt up here now.
We can't be doing this behind her back.
[Khloe] I don't want to do anything
behind her back.
How did you find this out?
[Kim] Security called Stephanie
and was like, "We have such and such
trying to get into Scott's room."
"She just flew in here."
"Is it authorized to get in?"
-So what do we do?
-The balls this guy has.
[Kim] I know. What do we do?
We're going there for dinner tonight.
So, let's go to his room.
I'm gonna go by his room and confront him.
Well, I don't want to do anything
because of the kids.
[Kourtney] This is cute.
-You look gorge, Kourt.
-Thank you.
[Kim] Um…
What is happening?
[Stephanie chuckles]
[Kim] We have something to tell you.
Yeah?
[Khloe] Is your heart racing?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-Don't-don't freak out.
[Kourtney] What?
[Kim] We have something to tell you.
Yeah.
-[Khloe] Is your heart racing?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
[Khloe] Don't freak out.
[Kourtney] What?
Scott brought a girl out here.
For what?
Like, what's the point of even…
-[Kim] On a family vacation?
-No, no, but what…
yeah, like, what's even the desperation?
[Kim] I don't… I have no idea.
It's four days. You can't last four days
without getting your [bleep] sucked?
What a [bleep] loser.
I always had his back.
I always thought, like, "Oh,
they're gonna get back together."
Move on.
[Kourtney] Scott and I are living
our own lives,
but, you know, we're here with our kids.
We're here to just be a family,
and I don't understand
why he would even think
to invite somebody.
It's hurtful and disrespectful.
-Loser.
-[Kris] What's going on?
-I thought we were gonna go to dinner.
-[Khloe] I know. I'm starving.
Do you want to tell?
[Kourtney] Scott has a girl
here on the trip.
-Scott flew a girl out.
-[Kim] Chelsea.
[Kris] No, he didn't.
And is staying in his hotel.
Are you guys serious?
[Kim] Yeah.
[Kourtney] What if he's bringing her
to dinner?
I'm not going if he's bringing her.
[Khloe] He's not bringing her to dinner.
[Kourtney] Why even…
why even take that risk?
It's almost like he wants me to know.
[Kim] Totally. I'll just put my clothes on
-while you finish talking.
-[Kris] Why don't we go there,
and then, when he sits down for dinner,
we'll just go, "How's Chelsea?"
I just don't care for the confrontation.
-What happened to you?
-If I show up somewhere
and everyone starts going…
-You used to be so combative.
-…"Kourtney,
what were you doing?"
I wouldn't want to deal with that.
But this is wild.
-It's disrespectful.
-Should we just tell him
dinner's canceled?
[Kris] No. Don't cancel dinner.
I'm just saying
cancel him from dinner.
-Let's just get in the car.
-Kourtney, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just thinking about
all the guys I'm gonna [bleep]
when I get home.
[laughing]
[Kim] Like, what did he think,
that we weren't gonna find out?
[Khloe] Basically.
I don't think I'm down for, like, drama.
I think we should just have
a couple bites,
tell him we'll see him tomorrow.
[Khloe] That's… I mean, we don't care
if you do your thing.
-It's just we're on a family trip.
-Well, I wasn't gonna have him come,
but then I was like,
"Ugh, just have him come,
because we could all hang out
as a family."
But if it's gonna be like that,
then I don't need
to go on a family trip with him again.
[Khloe] Hola. How are you?
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
Looks delish.
It's beautiful.
We could sit Scott and his girlfriend.
[Khloe] Scott could sit down there.
[Kourtney] Scott's writing me,
"You at dinner yet?"
[Khloe] Just don't answer.
-He'll figure it out.
-[Kourtney] Literally, God is good.
God is [bleep] good.
Like, I really don't think
I could get back together with him.
Yeah.
My kids, like, deserve to have,
somebody with better, like,
moral characteristics.
Yeah.
So this is, like, your epiphany?
No, no, I've already had the epiphany.
I'm just saying, this is confirmation.
Removing that as, like, an option
is just a positive thing to do.
[Kim] I just don't get
why he'd even want to show face.
I think it's good he wants to come.
I want to see what kind of mood he's in.
Thank God I'm the furthest away,
'cause I cannot handle this.
[Kourtney] That's why
I was literally, like, shaking.
[Khloe] Oh, I love it.
I know you do.
That's why I said,
"Don't do this to me, Khloe."
I just don't want Khloe to cause
a big scene.
That's not why I'm here.
And I'd rather just deal with it
in, like, a calm, normal manner,
like, when the trip is done.
I love that he's coming.
Don't do this to me.
I'm not gonna do anything.
Whew.
-He's walking up.
-[Kris] He's walking up.
Maybe you want to trade places with me.
[Khloe] My God.
[Kris] Hey, Scott.
[tense music playing]
[Corey] Ho, ho, ho.
Good luck. That's good luck.
That's good luck?
-The praying mantis?
-Yeah.
[Kris] You might need it.
-The good luck?
-[Kris] The good luck, yeah.
Is everybody excited
about the springs tomorrow?
-[Khloe] I am.
-[Kourtney] I am.
[dramatic music playing]
[Scott] Sure.
[Khloe] So, you're going tomorrow, Scott?
-[Scott] Yeah.
-[Khloe] Hmm?
[Scott] Yeah.
-[Khloe] Oh, you are? Good.
-[Scott] Yeah.
[Scott] Is that all right?
-Yeah.
-[Kris] So what time
are you gonna be at our place
in the morning, Scott?
What time do you want me to be there?
Probably 10:00.
-You got it.
-Hmm.
-[Kim] Thank you.
-[Kourtney] No, I'm finished.
Did you guys hear what Chelsea said?
[Khloe] Oh, yeah, she's such a bitch.
[Kim] No, she was so nice.
-[Khloe] She was a bitch.
-[Kim] Oh, Chelsea Handler. No.
No, no, I'm talking about Chelsea Clinton,
what she said
how she was sticking up for Barron Trump.
[Khloe] That's nice that Chelsea did that.
But I thought you meant Chelsea Handler.
[Kim] No.
[Khloe] Scott, how are you feeling?
-[Kourtney chuckles]
-[Scott] What?
Was that a weird question to ask?
I'm confused.
-[Kim] Let's cut the bull[bleep].
-Right.
[dramatic horn stabs playing]
[Kris] Uh…
[Kourtney] Oh, my God.
[Kris] This is gonna be amazing.
-[Kris] Wow.
-[Kourtney] That looks crazy.
[Scott] It's pretty obvious
that the girls know something's up.
Nobody really wants to say
what's on their mind.
And if this dinner isn't awkward enough,
these fire dancers have to come out
and start doing hula hoops.
I mean, I already felt, like, under fire.
[all cheering]
-[Kourtney] Wow.
-[Corey] Good job.
-[Kris] Great job.
-[Khloe] Thank you, guys!
[Kris] Thank you!
Thank you so much.
What are you doing
the rest of the night, Scott?
[dramatic music playing]
[Scott] What I have to.
What does that mean?
A crock of [bleep].
[Kourtney] There's so much tension.
We're all waiting for Scott
to say something,
and this is just the most awkward dinner.
You said, "I'm doing what I have to."
[Kris] I think what we're wondering
is if you have a girl here and why.
[Kim] Coming up next week…
[all shouting]
-Kourtney!
-[whooping]
[Stephanie] A bit more naked, Kourt.
You are so sensitive.
I'm so over all you people.
-I don't care.
-Shut the [bleep] up.
Do you know that I'm going to New York
to testify against the robbers?
They had been following me for two years.
There's a level of respect
and appropriateness.
If you need
to get your [bleep] wet that badly,
I'm gonna get your [bleep]ing [bleep] wet.