♪ ♪
[clock ticking]
-[Kourtney] Hi.
-[Reign] Gabbana.
[Kourtney] Gabbana's coming.
Do you like Gabbana?
[Kourtney] She's kissing you.
That's how she kisses.
-[Reign] No. Gabbana.
-[Kourtney] No?
[Khloe] This braid? I swear,
I thought it was P from this side.
He looks like a G-I-R-L.
[Kourtney] It's not, like, G'd up?
[Khloe] No, 'cause you're not giving him
a cornrow,
you're giving him, like,
a half up, half down.
[Kourtney] Well, I didn't do it.
Wait, I'm just gonna do a ponytail.
Are you okay?
[Khloe] You're okay. [laughs]
You're okay.
[Khloe laughs]
Are you okay, Reign?
Yay!
Just deal with it, okay?
♪ ♪
[siren whoops]
[Corey] Is Kim here?
[Kris] Kim's in the green room.
[Kim] Hi.
[Kris] I brought Ashley to say hi.
[Kim] Hi, guys.
[Corey] And me.
[indistinct chatter]
[Kris] We're at Kanye's Pablo Tour.
Kim hasn't been out
since the Paris robbery.
Are you wearing a shirt again,
with nothing on under it?
[Kim] I don't have any energy
to, like, put on clothes or makeup.
[Kris] That's all right.
I know she's having a hard time,
so I really want Kim to be
around her family, her friends.
I know it'll be therapeutic for Kim.
[crowd cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Katy] How are you?
-[Kim] Hi!
-[Katy] I'm so glad.
-[Kim] How are you?
[woman] Have you been going
out much or seeing how...?
[Kim] Not really, no. This is actually,
my first time going out,
and I'm so used to staying home.
The plan was always to go
on the entire tour.
So I feel really bad that I just
kinda have been at home,
but the Forum is a place that,
pretty much, my aunt and uncle own,
the Azoffs, so I do feel like
it's a safe place to go to,
and I want to definitely support
my husband.
[Marc] Simone texted me,
she's like, "We were robbed."
And I was like, "Oh, like, someone came up
and, like, stole, like..."
[Kim] That's what Kanye thought,
even when he got off the stage.
They made it sound like,
they were like, "Give me your bag."
[Katy] How are you? How's everyone? Good?
-[Kris] Hanging in there.
-[Katy] Coming together.
-[Kris] I just want Kim to be okay.
-[Katy] She will. Everything is a lesson.
[Kris] Yeah. For sure.
[Katy] Every relationship is a lesson,
experiences, traumas,
-lesson, lesson, lesson.
-[Kris] I agree.
[Kendall] You're here?
-[Kris] She is so strong.
-[Katy] Yeah.
-[Kris] If she can get through this?
-[Katy] 100%. And...
[Kris] She teaches me a lot.
-[Kim] Mom, I want to go out, it started.
-[Kris] Okay. All right. Let's go.
[crowd cheering]
-[Kim] Where is Kourtney and them?
-[Kourtney] What? I'm here.
[Kanye] Welcome to Saint Pablo.
♪ ♪
-[Stephanie] Are you okay?
-[Kim] Yeah.
[Kourtney] This girl's video-ing you.
Just don't video my sister.
I'll have you exited.
[Kim] I can feel the energy
of, like, people pulling out
their camera phones,
and feel like a lot of people
are so, like, curious to see,
"What is she doing?
What is she...?"
You know, "God forbid she's smiling,"
or if I'm, you know, not smiling,
then it's, like, "Oh, she's so depressed."
I don't want that kind of pressure
right now.
[crowd cheering, screaming]
♪ ♪
Feeling the vibe of the crowd,
I'm really nervous.
I now think, like, everyone has
a weapon, or everyone is gonna
do something harmful, like,
I just now have this, like, anxiety.
I just want to go in the back.
Just want to disappear for a little bit.
♪ ♪
[crowd cheering]
[Kourtney] The show was fun.
I've never been in the mosh pit.
Everyone's so sweaty down there,
that they have full sweatshirt hoodies.
[Kim] Yeah.
[Kourtney] So that they don't touch
anyone.
And I'm like, I didn't have my jacket on,
so I'm, like, fully in this.
[Kanye] Did you get sweated on?
[Kourtney] I didn't care. It was so hot.
I was like, "Sweat on me, people."
[laughs]
♪ ♪
[Kris] Oh!
[Corey] Kendall, happy birthday!
[Kris] The birthday girl and her buddies.
[Kendall] MJ! Hi! It is my 21st birthday.
[Corey] Oh, look at this pose.
[Kendall] We're having dinner at Catch.
[Kris] Hi.
-[Scott] You look like the Caped Crusader.
-[Kris] I am.
-[Scott] You see JJ?
-[Kris] Ta-da...!
-[Khloe] Where are you sitting?
-[Kourtney] Wherever.
[Khloe] I don't want
to sit next to Caitlyn.
[Kourtney] Why not?
[Khloe] And do what, be fake
this whole time?
I just don't know what to do.
[Kourtney] Okay. I'll sit here, and then,
Khadijah, sit next to me.
[Khloe] I'm starving.
I am hesitant to sit next to Cait,
because of how Cait handled
her transition.
There's no handbook on this,
there's no right or wrong way, I guess,
but Cait hurt a lot of people.
She hurt her children,
but she also really devastated my mom.
And when push comes to shove,
I'm always gonna be Team Kris Jenner.
-[Caitlyn] Khloe?
-[Khloe] Hmm.
[Caitlyn] I haven't seen you in forever.
[Khloe] I know, I don't know
the last time I saw you.
[Caitlyn] Have you been
hanging out in-- where is it-- Cleveland?
[Khloe] I have.
[Caitlyn] And how's that going?
[Khloe] Good. I like Cleveland. It's nice.
[Caitlyn] Good.
[Khloe] Can I have some
of those fries, MJ?
[Caitlyn] Are you going over?
[Kris] In a minute. I'm gonna go use
the ladies' room.
[Caitlyn] Need any help?
[Kris] Sure. Come on, Jenner.
[Caitlyn] This is a first. Let's go.
Where is it?
[Khloe] Caitlyn and Mom
went to the toilet together.
[MJ] Let's go watch them.
[Khloe] You should go.
I'll sit right here.
♪ ♪
[Jonathan] So how many people
are outside now?
There's always somebody here 24 hours now?
[Kris screams, laughs]
[Kim] What?! What?! [Kim screams]
What?! What?! What is it?
[laughter]
[Kris] It's the phone cord.
Oh, this twisted around my leg somehow.
I thought it was crawling up my...
[Scott] You guys probably
haven't seen anything long
and white go your direction
in a long time.
[laughter]
[Kris] Oh, my God, I have whiplash.
Are you gonna be in New York?
Like, for the whole month of November?
What's your schedule?
-[Jonathan] I'm in New York, November,
and then I move to Miami in December,
always, for the cold.
[Kim] L.A. for Christmas.
-[Kris] You did, once.
-[Jonathan] I did.
-[Kris] Twice.
[Jonathan] Yeah. Last year.
I was so nervous,
I couldn't even talk to--
I saw Caitlyn and almost fainted.
[Kris] Yeah, I know.
-[Jonathan] A shocker.
-[Kris] It's shocking every time.
[Kris] So, on the 21st, though,
Denise Rich has her annual Angel Ball.
[Jonathan] Oh, nice.
[Kris] Our family's being honored
on behalf of Robert.
-They'll raise money for cancer research.
-[Jonathan] Of course.
[Kris] And as he died
of esophageal cancer,
this is a great way to bring attention
to all sorts of cancers.
[Jonathan] Is Kim going?
[Kim] I don't know if I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna see how I feel.
[Jonathan] Kim, you need
to get out of the house.
This is crazy,
she doesn't want to leave the house.
[Scott] The more you, like,
let yourself not be who you are,
it's like you just got to live your life,
I feel like.
[Kim] My dad's being honored,
and I think it would be
really meaningful if I went.
But after Kanye's concert,
and me just, like, feeling so overwhelmed,
I just don't think I'm ready.
[Jonathan] You have to go
to a public event eventually.
One honoring your dad,
with your whole family...
[Kris] If she doesn't show up,
it would be odd.
[Kim] My nerves might seem,
like, irrational to other people,
people, but I have to do what
makes me feel comfortable.
I don't know, I just have
to think about it.
[Scott] I'm excited to go
on a ski trip. Not that it's now, but...
[Kim] Are we going on a ski trip?
[Scott] We always go skiing
and take the kids.
[Jonathan] Where'd we go
when I went with you guys?
-[Scott] Montana? Nice.
-[Jonathan] Montana.
-[Kim] It was so scary.
-[Scott] It was?
[Kim] The almost the car accident?
[Scott] Ridiculous. I didn't want
my family going down by a 16-wheeler.
[Jonathan] That was insane.
[Scott] Other than that, it was great.
♪ ♪
-[ringtone plays]
-[Kris] Hello.
[Caitlyn] Wow, Kris, how are you doing?
[Kris] I'm fine, how are you?
[Caitlyn] I'm on the driving range,
I'm doing good.
[Kris] Oh, that's good.
[Caitlyn] Yeah, I raced a car
with Burt this weekend, that was fun.
-[Kris] Oh, really?
-[Caitlyn chuckles]
Well, I won a trophy,
but I love trophies, you know me.
[Kris] Yeah, you've always loved
a good trophy.
[Caitlyn] I know.
I'm doing great. [chuckles]
I ju-- you know,
I just, you know, worry about Khloe.
Every time I text her,
she's fine if I'm talking
about little trivial stuff.
And I said, "Hey, we got to get together."
And, uh, then she never texted me back
when I say that.
[Kris] Well, Khloe's been in Cleveland
for the last month,
and, like, everybody has some real,
big, major life-changing thing going on.
[Caitlyn] You know it would
mean a lot to me if you would
just, uh, reach out to her
and let her know I want to talk to her.
[Kris] Okay.
My emotions are a roller coaster
when it comes to Cait.
[over phone] That you would
have the nerve to go to help Caitlyn
to pick a gown. Like, what is going on?
[Kim] I'm just gonna try to stay neutral
and not get involved.
[Kris crying] I want loyalty.
I don't want (bleep) neutral.
I do feel bad when I get angry
at one of my kids
for having a relationship with Cait.
That's not fair.
[Caitlyn] You have to realize
that I'm a little on the sensitive side
when it comes to all the children.
♪ ♪
You know? 'Cause I-I could spend
a month out at my house
and really never hear from anybody.
You know?
[Kris] Sometimes everyone
gets sort of distracted
and life takes over, you know?
[Caitlyn] I get it, I just miss her,
that's all.
[Kris] Bruce entered Khloe's life
when she was five years old,
and I never want to be the one
that influences Khloe,
one way or the other,
how to behave with Cait.
♪ ♪
[Khloe] Wow, don't you look
pretty, Michael Jackson.
[Kris] This is my French outfit.
Louis "Wuitton."
-[Khloe] Vuitton?
-[Kris] W-Wuitton.
-[Kris] Wui-tton.
-[Khloe] No, still a "V."
-[Kris] Vuit-ton. Vuit-ton.
[Khloe] No.
-[Kris] So, Caitlyn called me.
-[Khloe] Okay.
-[Kris] And gave me an earful.
-[Khloe] About what?
[Kris] About how there's no relationship,
and you never call, and...
[Khloe] Cait hasn't called me one time.
[Kris] So are you ever gonna
have the energy to sit down
and talk to her about what the issue is,
for once and for all, and maybe just...?
[Khloe] I'm not opposed to it,
I'm just like there's really not an issue.
Like, I'm cordial, I'm nice,
it's not that I'm mean.
Like, if I don't just vibe with you,
I don't vibe with you.
-[Kris] Yeah.
-[Khloe] I won't fake the funk.
As a human being, I don't like
how I've seen you treat my mother, or me.
And I don't care if you've
transitioned or not.
She's not the stepdad I once had.
[Kris] I don't ever want you
to feel guilty
about having a relationship with Cait
because of what happened to me,
or the way I was treated, or my feelings;
it should be two separate relationships.
[Khloe] I mean, after your
reaction to Kim,
and how hysterical you got at the ESPYs,
I don't know if you really mean that.
[Kris] I don't either, but I'm trying.
[Khloe] I appreciate that.
I really am impressed by my
mom's maturity in all of this.
If my mom is asking me to talk to Cait,
then I feel like I owe that to my mom.
But sitting down
and having a conversation with Cait,
I don't really feel like goes
much of anywhere.
So, I do have mixed feelings
about the entire situation.
But it's also, like, I'm not complaining,
I'm not holding onto some anger and--
like, I genuinely don't care.
-[Kris] Yeah.
-[Khloe] Why bring up stupid drama?
[Kris] Yeah.
[Khloe] But I'll see how it goes.
♪ ♪
[Khloe] Oh, my goodness,
happy birthday, Kris.
[Kris] It's my birthday.
And one of the sweetest things
that my kids did was rent out
the Cinepolis theater.
-[waitress] A Bloody Mary?
-[Kris] Yes.
A movie, and dinner at The Grill.
Great Saturday, everybody.
-[phone rings]
-Oh, here we go.
Hi, Kim.
-[Kim] Hey, Mom, happy birthday.
-[Kris] Thank you.
Well, we missed you today.
[Kim] Sorry I couldn't be there.
[Kris] Don't worry about it.
It breaks my heart
that she still feels uncomfortable
about being out and about.
[Kim] I want to give you your present,
so I'll give it to you back at home.
-[Kris] Alright.
-[Kim] Love you.
[Kris] Love you.
It's just gonna be a process,
and we're just gonna have
to take baby steps.
[all] ♪ Happy birthday... ♪
[Kris laughs, all cheer]
-[Khloe] Yay. Mom?
-[Kris] Yes.
[Khloe] I wanted you to know
that I think you are
one of the best people that I know
and the reason why we are able
to be very well-rounded entrepreneurs
that could go from the White House
to the trap house, and that's all
because of our mother,
so, Mom, God bless you.
[Kris] Thank you.
[Kourtney] To the trap house.
[Khloe] To the trap house.
[laughter, phone rings]
[Kris] Hello. Mm, thank you, honey.
Where are you?
Why?
-Her water broke?!
-[Khadijah] What?
[Kris] Are you serious?
-[Rob] I'm on my way,
I just got out the shower,
I'll go grab her
and go right to the hospital.
-[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Kris] Okay, we'll come to the hospital.
[Rob] No (bleep) you will.
But I'll go there right now.
[Khloe] Rob, are you lying? Say "Bible."
[Rob] Khloe, I don't know who you are,
you delusional...
[Khloe] See? He's lying,
he won't say "Bible," Mom, he's lying.
[Rob] It's your birthday,
this is amazing. I'm on my way.
[Khloe] See, Mom?
He's just a (bleep) liar.
[Kris] Wait, am I going
to the hospital or not?
If I get to that (bleep)
hospital and you're not there,
I will (bleep) strangle you by your balls.
[Rob] Come over here.
-[Kris] What?
-[phone beeps]
He hung up on me.
[Khloe] He didn't say "Bible,"
he's obviously a pathological liar.
[Kris] No, let's just (bleep) with him,
I'm gonna say,
"FaceTime me, I'm driving."
[laughter]
She isn't going into labor.
"I'm just messing with you."
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
♪ ♪
[Kim] "Kim, have a great
birthday. I love you. Daddy."
[Kourtney] What is that?
[Kim] This is a box that
Grandma Lou gave me.
Do you think Khloe would mind
if I posted this?
[both laugh]
Says she's got five home runs,
she's cutest on the team.
[Kourtney] "Cutest on the team"?
[both laugh]
-[Kim] That is so funny.
-[Kourtney] Would she just die?
[Kim laughs]
[Kim] I'm gonna send it to her.
Looking at all of this,
just all these memories,
I bet we'd have so much footage of Dad,
-on all the VHS stuff that he would do.
-[Kourtney] Mm-hmm.
[Kim] We should do, like, a
tribute video for him.
-[Kourtney] For the Angel Ball?
-[Kim] Yeah.
[Kourtney] Will you go?
-[Kim] I don't know.
"Kimbo the bimbo."
This is a card you made me on my birthday.
That video that Kanye made me
for my birthday, did you see it?
It literally made me cry.
[Kourtney] So many times.
How much longer is Kanye on tour for?
[Kim] I think he just added,
like, 20 more shows.
I mean, I just feel bad 'cause,
like, he lost his voice the other night.
[Kourtney] So, do you say that?
[Kim] Um... I mean...
he wants to do the show.
He should do the show. You know?
I-I don't want to, like,
tell him what to do.
I think he knows, like, his own
limits, you know?
[Kourtney] Yeah. He'll be fine.
I'm sure everyone, like, who's
on tour loses their voice at some point.
[Kim] Yeah, I mean, it wasn't that.
It was just like one song.
Kanye is, like, beyond an overachiever
and has to do everything
to the highest level.
I love that drive in him.
Like, that's just who he is.
You know, it's just, like, a lot.
♪ ♪
[Kim] Ah, so cute.
[Khloe] He's very calm.
How are you so calm?
-[Penelope] He doesn't even talk.
-[Khloe gasps]
[Kim] He doesn't talk.
But you know what he does say?
He says "go."
[Penelope] And he says "Daddy."
[Kim] He says "Dada" and "go."
Still no "Mama."
[Khloe] Why not "Mama"?
[Kim] I've gotten a "Mama" out
of him maybe twice.
-[Khloe] What is that face?
-[Khloe trills]
Do you guys want to go look at the videos?
[Kim] Yeah.
Even though I'm not ready to go
to the Angel Ball,
I just want everyone to see
what a great person my dad was
and just make a really sweet video.
[Khloe] So, that box right
there is all from Mom's house
and it has the most significant stuff
with Dad in front of the camera.
[Kourtney] Okay.
[Robert] Here you go.
Here's our little baby.
-[Kris] Hey, Kourtney.
-[Robert] Our three-day-old baby.
-[Helen] Everybody's in red and white.
-[Robert] There she is!
[Robert] There's Kourtney.
[Khloe] Aw. He's so happy to be a dad.
[Robert] Isn't that cute?
[Khloe] Dad looks like Pablo Escobar.
-[Kim] I've never seen this. Have you?
-[Kourtney] No.
[Robert] Kourtney went for a little walk.
It's the first day of school,
and what grade are you going into,
Kimberly?
-[Kim] First grade.
-[Robert] Okay.
[indistinct chatter on video]
-[Kim] Uh, is that Mom?
-[Khloe] Yeah.
[Kourtney] I feel like our parents were
always, like, having the best time.
[Robert] Kourtney will remember this party
the rest of her life.
[Kim] Kourtney, like, reminds me of North.
It's so funny.
[Khloe] She reminds me of North, too.
[Robert] All my... I have all
movies of Kimberly then.
-[Kim] And Khloe.
-[Robert] And Khloe.
[Khloe cries]
[Kim] I don't know.
I feel like I should go to this.
-[Kourtney] Go to what?
-[Kim] The Angel Ball. I feel guilty,
like, not being there to honor Dad,
but, I don't know if I'm ready yet.
My dad shapes the person that I am today,
and so, to miss out
on seeing him being honored
would really be unfortunate.
Maybe it's a good thing.
Maybe I should put my fears aside.
[Khloe and Kim laugh]
-[Kourtney] That doesn't look like Dad.
-[Khloe] It doesn't look like Dad.
[Robert] Hey. Okay.
[Khloe laughs]
[Khloe] Dad legit looks like a Colombian.
♪ ♪
[Scott] Can't believe
your brother has a baby.
What's the baby's name?
-[Kourtney] Dream.
-[Scott] Dream?
[Kourtney] Dream Kardashian.
[Scott] It's weird going to the hospital
when it's not our own kid
getting delivered.
Kourtney and I have been separated
for a pretty long time.
And it is a little weird because
any time I've ever gone to the hospital
like this in a rush,
she's usually pregnant and having a baby.
So, it brings back memories,
and, you know,
it would be nice
to have that family unit back.
[navigator] In 800
feet, turn right onto Beverly Glen.
[Kourtney] Come on, biatch.
Make a right on Beverly Glen.
♪ ♪
[Kourtney] Hi.
-[Scott] What a surprise.
-[Rob] Me, neither.
[Kourtney] Congratulations.
Oh, my gosh. She is Rob's twin.
[Khloe] Aw. She's such a cutie.
[Kim] Oh, my gosh, she's so cute.
[Chyna] Thank you.
[Kim] Oh, my gosh, she looks
just like Rob, don't you think?
-[Chyna] Exactly like Rob.
-[Kanye] So cute. Congratulations.
[Kris] One of the greatest honors
of my life has been
being in the room
when my grandchildren are born,
and nothing is a bigger blessing.
I'm so proud of my son.
He's gonna make such a good daddy.
[Scott] This time next year,
we'll be back here with our fourth.
-[Scott] We're all excited about it.
-[Kourtney] That's not true, guys.
-[Kourtney laughs]
-[Scott laughs]
[Scott] As long as this is there,
she's not gonna get pregnant.
[Kourtney] We've got to catch our flight
to Mexico.
[Khloe] Wait, you're going to Mexico?
I have no idea what is going on with them.
They say they're gonna go to Mexico.
I have so many questions
that I want to ask,
but Dream was just born
and I'm not gonna push it today.
-[Scott] Congratulations.
-[Rob] Have fun.
-[Kourtney] Love you.
-[Rob] Yes.
[Kourtney] Um, I'll call you.
[laughter]
I'll call you when we get there.
-[Scott] All right, bye, guys.
-[Rob] Love you. Have fun. Be safe.
♪ ♪
-[Kim] Can I check out your guest house?
-[Khloe] I'm missing lampshades.
-[Kim] I'm not judgmental anymore.
-[Khloe] Since yesterday? Voilà.
[Kim] Hmm, how gorgeous.
[Khloe] Literally, like,
I want to hide in here
when everyone's annoying me in that house.
[Kim] Mm-hmm.
-[Khloe] I'll be like, "Don't (bleep) me."
-[Kim] Yeah, I love it.
[Khloe] Dream looks just like Rob.
It's so crazy.
-[Kim] Like his twin.
-[Khloe] Yeah.
[Kim] She's so cute.
[Khloe] Wait, so, did you even
know that Kourt and Scott were in Mexico?
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Khloe] You did?
-[Khloe] Together?
-[Kim] Yeah, he was asking me advice.
Planning the trip and trying
to figure it all out and...
-[Khloe] Just them and the babies.
-[Kim] Yeah. Yeah.
[Khloe] Is this a they're-trying-
to-figure-it-out type of trip?
[Kim] I just don't even question it.
I'm, like, pro-them. Team him.
Like, oh, I hope they get back together,
I hope they get back together,
and just so into it.
[Khloe] It's so weird.
Who goes to Mexico with their ex
with just your kids?
[Kim] Unless there was any
chance of getting back together,
I would never go on vacay.
[Khloe] Exactly.
So, I saw something online
and I, like, hit up Scott.
I was like, "Hey, what you doing?"
[Kim] I didn't see.
-[Khloe] Of, like, her ass.
-[Kim] That is wild.
[Khloe] They're alone. He said
he's having, like, the best time ever.
He labeled it, "Views."
I don't know what the (bleep) is going on.
Cabo is, like, romantic.
This seems like an intimate
vacation, which is great.
I would love for them to have
their family back
and be together,
as long as Scott acts right.
I'm totally down with that.
And Scott's been doing great.
He's been on a great path lately.
They're literally inseparable.
Honestly, I'm saying they're (bleep).
[Kim] It fully seems like
they're back together.
-[Khloe] Totally. Hundred percent.
-[Kim] I wonder what she says to him.
[Khloe] I would literally give money
to be a fly on the wall.
Like, "Baby..."
I don't know if she says "baby."
I don't think she's a "baby" kind of girl.
[Kim] I don't, either.
-[Khloe] She'll say "babe"
'cause babe's more like you're
at a distance.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Khloe] She won't say, "Baby. Hi, baby."
She goes, "Hey, babe."
[Khloe] That sums up who Kourtney is--
she's a babe girl, not a baby girl.
-[Khloe] I'm a baby girl.
-[Kim] Yeah, I'm, like, a babe.
-[Khloe] No, you're a mix.
-[Kim] I'm a mix.
[Khloe] You're a mix.
♪ ♪
-[Caitlyn] Khloe? I'm here.
-[Khloe] Coming.
-[Caitlyn] Where are you?
-[Khloe] I'm coming. Hi.
[Caitlyn] Hello, baby.
[Khloe] Hi. How are you?
[Caitlyn] Good to see you.
[Khloe] Did you see Gabbana?
[Caitlyn] I know. Gabbana heard my voice
as soon as I came in.
Do you want to get a drink?
-[Khloe] Yeah, do you? Perfect.
[Caitlyn] We might need one. Perfect.
-[Khloe] That makes me super excited.
-[Caitlyn] I know.
[Khloe] I have a ton of opinions
and feelings about Cait,
but before Caitlyn, there was Bruce.
And Bruce was in my life for,
like, 24 years.
So, I'm gonna have the sit-down.
[Caitlyn] We haven't talked in a while.
And I'm so happy to be here.
[Khloe] Thank you,
I'm happy to have you here.
[Caitlyn] Um, I just really
feel like over the last year and a half,
it-- we certainly have grown apart.
Day after day, after month after month,
nobody calls,
nobody checks in-- just, "Hey,
how are you doing?"
You can't help but sit there and thinking,
"Okay, is it because I transitioned?
They don't like me anymore?"
And I want to know what I did wrong,
what I didn't do wrong, what I did right.
And, uh, move forward.
[Khloe] I don't necessarily
want to say you did anything wrong,
'cause I don't know
if, just 'cause you didn't do
something the way maybe I would
have preferred, that makes it wrong.
We deal with things quickly.
We don't have time to really process
a lot of things,
'cause we're always on to the next.
And, for me, at the time,
I just wasn't at a place in my life
where I really could invest
in new relationships.
It was very hard for me to experience
a lot of new things
so quickly and still feeling like
I have to protect my mom
in certain things that were
happening, where I felt like
they might not have been
the most positive.
But then I was also like,
"This isn't my fight to fight anymore.
Like, I have my own (bleep) to deal with,
so why don't you guys figure that out?"
But I don't think
Caitlyn is a bad person at all.
[Caitlyn] You've been through a lot.
I get that.
But that's, you know, 23 years
of my life invested in the family and you.
You know, being there when
you have good days and bad days,
and all the things that you go through
when you're growing up,
and sneaking out of the house
and I found you and stuff like that.
[Khloe] For me, you're all I remember--
Bruce was.
So, not having you in my life,
it's a huge blow.
'Cause I'm like, "Okay, my second dad,
this guy that I've grown up with,
that raised me,
was taken away from me,
but no one really let me have that."
[Khloe] Okay, my second dad,
this guy that I've grown up with,
that raised me, was taken away from me,
but no one really let me have that.
I still need to, like,
how you need to transition,
I need to transition into,
like, accepting.
'Cause to me,
you are two different people,
to me, and I don't know
if that's politically correct to say,
I'm not sure.
[Caitlyn] Your feelings are important,
that's how you feel, so... yeah.
[Khloe] I appreciate.
I'm getting to re-know you again.
I know you still have the same interests
and you like to race cars and all.
But your personality,
you got to admit, is different. To me.
-[Caitlyn] To you. Yeah.
-[Khloe] To me, like, you...
[Khloe] The fact that you go to a club,
like at Kendall's,
I was like, "Bruce would never be here."
Bruce was always, "Let's go home."
[Khloe] "I got to be home."
But Caitlyn is, like, you said yourself,
likes to go out and be social and...
[Caitlyn] Yeah.
[Khloe] You said Caitlyn's different
than Bruce. Not in a bad way.
I've never said Caitlyn was bad.
I never said Bruce was bad.
[Caitlyn] True.
[Khloe] So I'm getting accustomed to that,
but it's like-- it has to be authentic.
You can't just, like,
push someone onto somebody.
It, like, has to happen in time.
[Caitlyn] Mm-hmm. I just want
you to know, from my perspective,
how important our relationship is.
[Khloe] To me, too.
-[Caitlyn] In this case,
how can we move forward from here?
[Khloe] What's done is done.
And, like, that's why I don't
want to bring up the (bleep) that, like,
-bothered me.
-[Caitlyn] I don't, either.
[Khloe] If it's as simple as,
"Okay, yeah, I didn't try hard enough."
And like, we both didn't try hard enough
to meet each other or hang.
Like, it's a two-way street.
So, yeah, I'm sure we could both
try harder.
-[Caitlyn] You know I love you.
-[Khloe] And I love you, too,
and I never want you to think
that I don't love you.
[Caitlyn] Yeah. Um, although
it may be tough,
I would like for you to experience
some of my life and what I do now.
[Khloe] Good. Like, I'm just about,
like, life and family and love
and, like, p-- like, whatever's, like,
makes everyone happy.
That's all I'm about.
[Caitlyn] Yeah.
So, do you feel better
about this conversation we've had?
-[Khloe] Yeah. Do you?
-[Caitlyn] Of course, I do.
[Khloe laughing] Okay, good.
From this meeting that we've had,
I think, you know,
we're making the right steps,
and with any friendship, you know,
there's ups and downs,
but I really hope that this will turn
into a relationship that I really want
to invest energy and time into.
I'm excited to see where Caitlyn
and I take things.
[clicks tongue]
[Caitlyn] Oh... You know, it's amazing,
even going through all of this--
transitioning and this and that--
she still knows who I am.
[Khloe] Of course she knows.
[Caitlyn] See, Gabbana knows
more than you. I'm still the same person.
♪ ♪
[Scott] Pool day.
[Khloe] Hey-ya, Scott.
[Scott] How are you, Khloverfield?
-[Khloe] Good, you?
-[Scott] Looking good.
[Khloe chuckling] Thank you.
Since you just came back from Mexico,
I wanted to still be outside,
enjoy the weather.
[Scott] Nothing's changed.
Different sister, but same vibe.
[Khloe] I'm sure we'll get further
than you and Kourtney did.
[Scott] 100%, we already did, just now.
[Khloe] How was Mexico?
[Scott] It was perfect, just
to, like, get away. We hung out, swam.
-[Khloe] You guys were getting along well.
-[Scott] Yeah.
-[Khloe] Reconnecting?
-[Scott] Yeah, I think so.
I mean, we've, like, made future plans
to do things together, so that's good.
-[Khloe] That's cute.
-[Scott] Yeah.
-[Khloe] Did you guys kiss on the lips?
-[Scott chuckles sheepishly]
You did! I could tell.
[Scott] No, I-I don't think--
I probably did, she didn't.
She doesn't want anything to do with me.
You know, it's a one-way street, but...
[Khloe] It's cute that you're covering up
for her. I'll ask her, too.
She'll tell me, [imitating Kourtney] "No."
-[Scott] No.
-[Khloe] "Oh, my God, no."
[Scott] Kourtney and I have had a lot
of issues over the past... lot of years.
But some of these times
that we get to spend with our kids,
really, is, like, the best moments
in my life.
So, the trip to Mexico
was very successful.
It felt like old times.
It was great to see the kids,
swim and have fun.
And truthfully, I'm not really
sure why we're not together.
I mean, it seems like it's all the same.
A little confusing.
-[Khloe] Uh-oh.
[Kourtney] Hey, guys. What are you doing?
[Khloe] Hey-ya, Kourt! You look so pretty.
That ass shot of yours.
Now you're really one of us.
-[Scott] I took that.
-[Khloe] That was a good one.
[Kourtney] Then, today,
when I was changing in the closet,
Patrick and Andrew were like,
"Your ass looks so good."
[Scott] Makeup people are gonna
tell you your ass doesn't look good.
-[Khloe] Right.
-[Kourtney] No, but, what a hater!
-Always. What a hater.
-[Scott] Hater?
[Scott] Okay, 'cause I'm telling you
you look bad.
[Kourtney] In Mexico, at dinner, I said,
"I notice that when people are older,
they look better, with long hair."
-[Khloe] Mm-hmm.
[Kourtney] He's like, "You're really
obsessed with age. Well, guess what.
I'll love you no matter how old you are.
In my opinion, I think you're already,
like, over-the-hill.
Like, it's all downhill from here."
[Khloe] Scott!
[Scott] I didn't say that.
[Kourtney] I said, "I think
I have another ten years,
so I think you're just trying
to get back with me
so that you'll waste up my ten years,
then you'll ditch me.
Like, trade me in for a younger model."
[Scott] That's absolutely not the case.
It wasn't like you portrayed it.
[Kourtney] No, and he was saying,
-like, "I could trade you in now."
-[Scott] Right.
[Khloe] Like, he could find
someone that's 18.
-[Kourtney] I didn't mean it. So could I.
-[Khloe] I know!
[Scott] I'm gettin' out of here.
This (bleep) trip was (bleep) worthless.
-[Khloe] Why are you so mad?
-[Kourtney] I don't know.
[Khloe] Everyone, chill.
♪ ♪
[Khloe] Ooh, yeah!
[Scott] Oh, God.
[Khloe] You're steezing it up.
That's a tricky pair of pants.
[Scott] Why is that?
[Khloe] Why do you have
metallic by your (bleep)? Don't you see?
It's just right there.
-[Scott] Looks like I was at a strippy.
-[Khloe] Body makeup on your brasule?
Get any tickling down there?
Like, when you and Kourt, like, kiss,
'cause you know you want it to work...
-[Scott] We didn't.
-[Khloe] You told me.
-[Scott] I said I kissed her good night.
-[Khloe] And she didn't kiss you back.
[Scott] She didn't when we were together.
[Khloe] But, so, did your "sau-seege,"
move in your pants a little,
'cause it got excited?
[Scott] I'm still turned on by her.
[Khloe] Do you see other
people at the moment?
-[Scott] No. Uh-uh.
-[Khloe] You don't?
-[Scott] I technically could, I guess.
-[Khloe] Yeah, totally.
[Scott] I don't feel comfortable.
-[Khloe] No?
-[Scott] No.
-[Kim] Are you getting over it, though?
-[Khloe] You're getting over Kourtney.
-[Kim] 'Cause she's, like, lagging.
[Scott] No, I mean, you know,
she's a tough girl.
I mean, it's tough sometimes.
[Khloe] You're not getting over her,
right?
[Scott] No, I mean, I feel like
I would never be over her.
She's the love of my life.
But, you know, I try to do everything
to be there for her,
and it's just... There's literally no
appreciation for anything ever.
You know, I definitely realize
that a lot of things truly are my fault,
and I'm happy taking ownership
for all that.
I just hope that, you know,
one day she understands
that I would never want to be
with anybody but her.
♪ ♪
[notes played on piano]
[Khloe] You know what the
problem with the piano is?
It tells you "A," "B," "C," "D,"
like, on there,
and then randomly it starts giving you
these weird shapes.
If you want me to take piano lessons,
keep up the alphabet
and stop switching over to numbers.
'Cause these shapes are not
cutting it for me.
[Kim] Hi.
[Khloe] I was just getting
warmed up, and you ruined it.
I was about to play the best song.
But you take precedence.
-[Kim] I am, like, exhausted.
-[Khloe] Why?
[Kim] I just, like,
have not had any sleep.
[Khloe] Is everything okay?
[Kim] Kanye just, like, walked
offstage last night.
Kanye had a show in Sacramento,
and he performed a few songs and
left early, and I feel really bad
for the people that missed out
on that show and I know
he cares about his fans so much.
[Khloe] I know how much he works
and how much all you guys work.
I think it's crazy.
[Kim] Yeah.
[typing]
[text alert chimes]
[text alerts chiming]
[Khloe] You guys! Get off your phones.
I'm not kidding, give me
both your phones. Give it to me.
-[Kourtney] I'll hide it.
-[Khloe] No.
-[Kourtney] I'm not using it.
-[Khloe] Shut up. Give me your phone.
[Kourtney] You're grabbing my crotch.
[Khloe] You two are the most
annoying human beings I've ever met.
♪ ♪
[Penelope] Northie wants
a new baby sister.
-[Khloe] Yeah, she does. Do you?
-[Penelope] No.
[Khloe] Yeah, I don't blame you.
Do you want a brother, or you're
fine with the two you have?
-[Penelope] The two.
-[Khloe] Mm-hmm.
[Khloe] Kourt, do you want
to have another kid?
-[Kourtney] I don't know.
-[Khloe] What?
[Kourtney] I don't know. What's so crazy
about saying "I don't know"?
-[Khloe] It's not a definitive yes or no?
-[Kourtney] Uh-uh.
-[Khloe] I was sure you'd have said "no."
-[Kourtney] No.
-[Khloe] What'd you do with it?
-[Kourtney] Love it.
-[Penelope] Here, I'm done.
-[Kourtney] All done?
[Khloe] So I spoke to Scott,
and he told me that you guys
had, literally, the best trip.
Good for your guys' relationship,
and you guys were, like...
[Kourtney] We literally got into fights,
and I'm just, like, ugh,
we've got so many issues.
[Khloe] My thing is,
from an outsider looking in,
it seems like you guys are trying to work
things out, which is absolutely awesome.
-You've been together for ten years.
-[Kourtney] Right, but we're not.
[Khloe] I don't think
Scott thinks you're not.
I think, for Scott, like,
every trip it's like, "Oh,
I'm that much closer,
I'm that much closer."
In a way, it's leading him on.
[Kourtney] It's nice for the kids and us
to be able to go on trips together...
[Khloe] Every relationship is different,
and can do things in their own way.
I'm saying I think you have to
spell it out for Scott.
[Kourtney] But he said, "Do
you want to go to therapy together
so we can, like, work on things?"
And I'm, like, "No,
because we're not working on things
right now."
It seems like Scott is just
reading into these trips so much
and, like, analyzing, like,
our every move.
And, like, I love going
on these family trips together,
but maybe it's just too much
for him to handle.
I've told him,
"I'm not just sitting around.
I'm living my life,
and you're working on you.
And, like, you've never been better,
but you're so inconsistent that,
like, I need to see
if, like, you can be consistent."
♪ ♪
[Kris] Look how pretty the city looks.
Good morning, New York.
[phone rings]
[Kim] Hi.
[Publicist] Hey, how are you?
[Kim] I'm good, how are you?
[publicist speaks indistinctly]
Yeah, um, you know,
he just needs some time off,
so we just made that happen.
As I'm traveling, everyone's
trying to make this decision
to cancel the rest of Kanye's tour,
and, you know, he would never want
to give, like, a half-assed show.
He definitely wants to give his all,
and he knows that he needs
a little bit of time off in
order to do that.
So it'll be okay.
He just needs to take some time
for himself and just...
get back focused,
and I think it's for the better.
Okay, bye. Thank you.
21 shows canceled.
[Kris] Were they add-ons anyway?
[Kim] They were, like, another leg.
[Kris] So, tonight,
who's gonna get up and speak?
[Kourtney] I won't,
and I'm not even capable of doing that.
We all said that you were, Mom.
[Kris] I... He wasn't my daddy.
He was my baby daddy.
♪ ♪
-[Kourtney] Cute.
-[Kim] A homemade breakfast is here.
-[Kourtney] Ooh, flowers?
-[Kim] This is nice.
-[Kourtney] Have you ever stayed here?
-[Kim] No.
[Kourtney] Oh, my God,
I love it, it's my favorite.
Well, that was nice.
[Kim] Oh, from Scott?
-[Kourtney] I thought it was the hotel.
-[Kim] Me, too,
-but why would the hotel say "Kourt"?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
[Kim] Do you think Scott's gonna,
like, end up being normal?
[Kourtney] What do you think?
-[Kim] Do you care?
-[Kourtney] Yeah, I care.
[Kim] Not for your kids, but for you?
[Kourtney] I feel like it's
in God's hands, you know?
[Kim] That's what I'm putting
on your tombstone.
-[Kourtney chuckles]
-"In God's hands now."
[Kourtney] I mean, it would be nice.
-[Kris] Hey.
-[Kim] Hey.
-[Kris] What are you drinking?
-[Kourtney] Orange juice.
[phone rings]
[Kim] Hey.
What? Why, what's going on?
What's wrong?
Don't scare me, please. What's going on?
I-I can't.
[Khloe] Coming up next week...
Is everything okay?
[Kim] I'm not in the mood to
get into it right now.
[Khloe] Kim's been through so much.
[Kim] There's just a lot on his plate.
[Khloe] A lot on your plate, too.
[Kris] Vogue wants to review
the Kendall and Kylie collection.
[Kendall] No idea what she's thinking.
It could make or break us.
[Khloe] Okay, so are we not as
close as I thought we were?
[Malika] Our relationship has
become more estranged.
Obviously, I just miss you, that's all.
-[Khloe] Why are you crying?
-[Malika] Because I do.