[Kim] What's going on with you and Chyna?
I've been pretty...
I've been pretty, like, upset.
Right now, we're just each
pushing each other away.
You built your foundation
on attraction and sex.
And then you was like,
"Oh, crap, what do we do now?"
-[car horn honking]
-[Rob] What the [bleep]?
[Scott] I don't even understand.
[Rob] I do that all the time
to lame-ass [bleep] bum bitches like him.
-Are you kidding?! I hate...
-What did he do?
He just tried to come up next to me
and try and look in and be a weirdo.
A [bleep] Calabasas sticker boy.
What the [bleep]?!
Well, I should... Should I flash?
Nah. This feels crazy.
I hate people like him.
[Scott laughs]
-[Rob honks horn]
-Yo, yo.
[both laugh]
-What a [bleep].
-[Scott] He faced up on you.
[Rob] He's such a loser.
I hate [bleep]... Argh!
[both laugh]
-Go ahead.
-[Scott] Yeah, ramp it.
Oh! Did you not...? If nobody goes,
I wait until somebody goes.
-Like, I'm gonna wait again.
-[Scott laughs] Just for fun?
-[Rob] Watch.
-[Scott] What?
[Scott laughs]
[Rob] Let's just let all of them go by.
[horn honking]
I think you got to go eventually.
[upbeat dance music plays]
[Kourtney] What's
New York weather? Is it that cold?
[Dani] It's snowing.
[Kim] Hey. Look at my shoes from...
-[Man] Hi.
-[Kim] Hi. How are you?
-...100 years ago.
-[Kim] I love those.
We just made an outfit with them.
[Kim] That's cute. Really cute.
This is warmer things.
We haven't done this rack.
-[Kourtney] That's for the trip.
-[Kim] NYC?
-Or... yeah.
-[Kim] Or what?
[Kourtney] 'Cause I can't decide.
She's the most annoying,
indecisive person on the planet.
I asked Kourtney months ago
if she would come
to New York for Fashion Week.
She hasn't given me a solid answer.
-Do you need a decision?
-I'd have other people fly on the plane.
Right now, I'm flying, like, my Glam
and everyone else commercial
so that there's room for you.
I'm just not gonna know
until the last minute.
How can you live your life like that?
Kourtney is truly the most indecisive
person I've ever met in my entire life.
I haven't even decided
if I'm 100 percent going.
-Kim said she liked these drapes.
-You live here.
I can't decide.
You can't have people
book something and then change it.
Everything is all set, ready to go.
At this point,
it's just beyond frustrating.
I think I want to be home with the kids.
But then I feel like I want
to be there for Kanye.
I mean, if you can't decide,
then don't come.
[Kourtney] Mm...
-All right, so I think I'm gonna come.
[Kim] Okay.
Okay. Oh, yeah.
-[Kim chuckles]
-[Reign giggles]
[Mason] Reign. Crazy!
[dance music plays]
[Jamel] Don't show up late.
Don't try to slide out early, Rob.
Focus, man.
-[Rob] Hey.
-[Gunnar] How's it going?
-[Rob] Good to see you.
-[Jamel] You ready for this?
-[Gunnar] Are you good?
-[Rob] Yeah.
-[Rob grunts]
-[Gunnar] Are you on the market now?
Just got to know.
I'll put some feelers out there for you.
-Always put feelers out there.
-[Gunnar] No.
If you're spoken for,
I won't have you spoken to.
No, I'm not spoken for.
You're intentionally making me stare
at my sister's ass while I'm working out?
It could be interpreted that way,
but that's not how I intended it. [laughs]
-Walk it out.
-[Rob panting]
-[Gunnar] Having a baby changed your life?
-[Rob] It's cool.
When the baby's with me,
I, like, won't leave my house.
Everything's just on lockdown mode,
which is a good thing.
-That's how you're meant to raise a kid.
-[Rob] Yeah.
[Rob] In the past, when I was depressed,
I disconnected from literally everyone.
But I'm not gonna go back
to that, like, dark place.
I'm just gonna focus on trying
to be healthy. I'm in the gym.
And I'm working every day
and getting better lately.
I'm gonna change my shirt real quick.
He killed it. I mean, I'm not surprised.
I'm happily surprised, and...
There's something in there.
Whoever that guy was from
the Dancing with the Stars,
we're looking for that guy.
it's in there.
-[Gunnar] It's in there. See you Friday.
-All right.
-Wear something sexy.
-G, it was a pleasure. Have a great day.
[upbeat electronic music plays]
-Hey.
-Hi.
-It's really nice.
[Kim] We're right next to each other.
-No, like, arm rest.
-[Stephanie] Feels like...
We're so excited. We're going
to New York for Fashion Week.
It'll be this fun sister trip. Kendall
will be there, Kylie will be there.
It'll just be so much fun.
We're still waiting on Kourt.
She's not here. Should I call her?
Yeah.
-[phone rings]
-Is she calling you?
-[Kim] Mm-hmm. Hey.
-[Kourtney] Hi.
What's up? We're here.
How far are you?
[Kourtney] I'm not coming.
I'm not coming to New York anymore.
What? Why?
[Kourtney] I don't know. I felt God
just, like, telling me not to come.
God was telling you not to come. Okay.
[Kourtney] I've gone in circles, and the
final answer came to me this morning.
You need, like, serious therapy.
Who would do a full fitting
and pack a whole bag and then not come?
[Kourtney] I can wear the outfits in L.A.
Yeah, but it's just so annoying
that you're this indecisive.
Are you gonna still pay
for half of this plane,
or are you now stiffing me with the whole
bill, since you decided to be indecisive?
[Kourtney] I will pay
whatever you'd like me to pay.
As annoying as it is for you,
it's twice as annoying for me.
-[Kim] All right. Bye. I'm taking off.
-[Kourtney] Um... Okay. Fly safe.
Have fun.
[Kim] I should make her
pay for half the plane.
Everything was sold out
'cause it's Fashion Week.
We got a room for her that
it's, like, now stuck on my credit card.
How annoying. Ugh!
[crowd cheering and screaming]
[cameras clicking]
So fancy.
This is gonna murder us,
this whole situation.
-I'm kind of into this caviar.
-I didn't think you would be. I love it.
-[Kim] Mmm.
-[Simon] How is New York?
-Good. Mm-hm.
-[Simon] Good?
Everything's really thought out,
you know.
[Simon] Your new security team
is incredible.
-New security's great. On top of it.
-[Simon] That's so nice.
Yeah. So Rob called me last night.
Oh, God.
Him and Chyna don't talk or get along.
Like, he's not going to fight
with her on social media.
I think she'll be chill.
He'll be chill. I'm hopeful.
Is the weight still on him?
-He's dropped, like, 13 pounds.
-Okay.
-Even through all the turmoil with her?
-[Kim] Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
I know that Rob really wants
to keep his family together,
but I do think
that this is a good path for them,
so that they're both happy.
Everything's a life lesson.
I just hope that they can be great parents
and just have a good relationship.
-He needs to move on from all that drama.
-[Kim] Mm-hm.
-[Simon] There's no...
-I hate it's olives.
-[Simon] Really?
-[Kim] Mm-hm.
-Oh, I do. I... I hate olives.
-Like, everyone loves them.
Uh-uh. It overtakes the entire salad.
It becomes an olive salad.
Mm-hm.
[Jamel] You've got a big birthday soon.
If you could create something for yourself
for your birthday, what would it be?
Mm, something that's,
like, very important to me
would be to have, like,
that friendship with Chyna.
[Jamel] Yeah.
Like, it kills me to not be able
to at least speak and be friends.
-Yeah.
-[Rob] You know what I mean?
At least we should be able
to have that relationship
for the sake of our baby and each other.
I love her as a friend, so that's
important to me have that relationship.
I'll never accept the fact that we can't
at least be friends and have peace.
In order for you to effectively
communicate with her,
it's learning how to love
and communicate with yourself first.
Being good to yourself,
being a positive influence for yourself
and inspiring yourself.
When you do that, you create space
where you are comfortable being around,
then other people can be
comfortable being around you.
[mid-tempo dance music plays]
-[Khloe] Hi, Mom.
-Hi.
-I have those same sunglasses.
-You do?
-Yeah.
-Oh.
-Want to sit over there or here?
-Right here is great.
Yeah. [Kris sighs] You look so good.
-I thank you. So do you.
-How was Cleveland?
-Great. Yeah.
-Yeah? How's my little Tristan?
-He's so good.
-He has a game today.
-[Kris] He does?
-Yeah.
You know what I've been finding
that's been escalating
and escalating and escalating
is how [bleep] annoying Kourtney is
with, like, just doing anything.
This is what I go through
on a daily basis with her.
"Should I go to New York, or not?"
I've watched her spend three days
picking a paint color
as if it's her full-time job.
After hearing how Kourt bailed
on Kim for the whole New York thing,
it's, like, Kourt doesn't get
that her lack of decision-making
does affect other people.
I know she's meeting us here,
so I'm gonna pretend
that you and I are, like, driving
and we're not here yet.
I'll say: "We changed our mind.
We're going somewhere else."
-You're gonna [bleep] with her?
-She [bleep] with me on a daily basis.
-Oh, this is giving me life.
-She literally [bleep] with me.
-[Kris] This is amazing.
-[ringing tone]
-[Kourtney] Howdy.
-[Khloe] Hey.
[Kourtney] What's up? I'm close.
-We're not going there anymore.
Go to Casa Vega. I know it's far,
but just take your ass over there.
[bleep] I'm going the wrong way now.
See you soon, beautiful.
I'm turning around now,
so I'll see you guys there in 15 minutes.
My bad, Suzanne.
Will you pull over for a second?
We changed to go to a different
restauran. Mom's on the phone.
I don't know exactly where we're going.
[Kourtney shrieks] [bleep]
I'm so hungry. I don't have time.
We can go to any restaurant.
What's better
than pulling a prank on Kourt
and making her feel what it feels like
when someone is that indecisive?
-Just let me know, and I'll be waiting.
-Okay, bye.
[Kris laughs] Mom's got a craving.
Do you think she'll be pissed
we're eating before her?
-I don't care.
-[Khloe] Well, damn.
[horn blares]
Thank you.
Yes.
[horn honking]
[Kris and Khloe] Bruschetta!
I'm hungry.
[phone ringing]
[Kourtney] What's going on?
I'm sitting at the gas station car wash.
-Where am I going?
-Sorry. Mom is on the phone.
-So you can't be that mad.
-[Kourtney] I don't care!
I'm hungry. It's 2:30 p.m.
We decided to actually stick
with Grissini's.
-We should have gone with our guts.
-[Kourtney] Is that a joke?
-We're here.
-[Kourtney] What's wrong with you?
She sounds pissed, and so I don't
really know if she's gonna think
this experiment is
as funny as I find it to be.
She's not exactly
the practical joke type, though.
She might kill you.
-[Kris] Hey!
-[Khloe] Oh, Kourtney's here!
-Look who's here.
-Gluten-free.
You guys ate without me?
-We've been here for a while.
-You had me on a wild goose chase.
-I think it will teach you a lesson.
-[Kris laughs]
You had me driving in circles
because you thought it was funny?
How was that gonna teach me anything?
Why are you so indecisive
about single move in your life?
When I ask Kourtney,
"Let's work out tomorrow."
She goes, "Basketball court or
your garage?" I go, "What do you think?"
"Let me just Google the weather."
-You are indecisive.
-[Khloe] So indecisive.
I know I'm indecisive. It's debilitating.
-Think about New York.
-[Kourtney] Exactly. It's debilitating.
You're debilitating me.
Either way, I'm not
gonna be happy with the answer.
The indecisiveness is debilitating.
-Did you learn that word today?
-Mm-hm.
It's like, every time you say
"debilitating," we should all have a shot.
-Debilitating.
-Debilitating. Drink up.
[upbeat dance music plays]
[crowd cheering]
[crowd screams]
[crowd chants] Kylie! Kylie! Kylie! Kylie!
[chanting continues]
I'm in New York during Fashion Week,
and I am doing my second pop-up.
[Kylie] I never imagined that
Kylie Cosmetics would grow to what it has.
[crowd cheering]
I love makeup, I love creating looks,
so when things like this happen,
I get really excited.
We are making records today.
This is insane.
So thank you all for everything,
making this happen. [whoops]
[Kylie] It's really important
to me to be hands-on
and always working on elevating my line.
[crowd cheering]
[crowd chants] Kylie! Kylie! Kylie! Kylie!
[chanting continues]
-[Rob] Do I look crazy?
-[woman] No. If you want a mask.
-[Rob] Thank you.
-[woman] You're welcome. Have a good day.
I'm wearing this,
'cause my lip looks crazy.
[Jamel] Are you still in pain? Really?
Like, throbbing pain?
Well, this side is the throbbing side.
-I'll have to get this looked at.
-Why don't you have them do it now?
'Cause they need to call
the root canal specialist.
-That sounds like a lot of fun.
-They'll put me to sleep.
[Jamel] Chyna's having
a photo shoot today.
How'd you feel if we show her
some support?
[Rob] I have no problem
going and seeing her.
Us not communicating could lead
into us never talking again.
[Jamel] When's the last time you saw her?
-[Rob] Um...
-Like, in actual person?
I can't even remember
the last time I seen her.
[Jamel] You got
some anxiety, bro. I can see it.
Even though
it's very important to be there
and have a great friendship
with Chyna, I'm really nervous.
I don't know what to expect.
[Jamel] All peace,
love and harmony today, right?
No crazy questions,
no sarcasm, dags.
Don't bring anything up.
-Alfreda!
-[Chyna] I don't have any clothes on.
Oh. Sorry. My bad. She's not decent.
[Rob] I feel like we've already
overstayed our welcome.
-[door opens]
-[Chyna] Hi.
Hey, buddy. How are you?
We good to come in now?
-[Chyna] Hey, Rob.
-Sorry we shocked you.
-[Chyna] Hmm?
-[Chyna] Mm-hmm.
-Can we come in?
[Chyna] Yeah. Come on.
[Rob] So I was at that dentist.
-My whole mouth is...
-[Chyna] Let me see.
-[Rob] My whole mouth is very numb.
[Rob] Nah. My lip's, like, all...
They just had to replace
one tooth. That was all.
-[Chyna] When'd you do it?
-[Rob] Just now.
-[Chyna] Really?
-[Rob] Mm-hmm. I just came from there.
[Chyna] That's cool.
-[Rob] How's your shoot?
-[Chyna] Good.
[Jamel] How much longer to go?
-[Chyna] Um, this is the last look.
-[Jamel] Nice.
[Rob] Yeah. Well, good stuff.
[Rob voiceover]
Chyna's acting super weird to me.
There's so much awkward tension
between Chyna and I.
I have no idea how to be around her.
-[Chyna] It's so hot outside.
-[Rob] It's perfect. It's hotter in here.
[Chyna] Yeah, no. Yeah,
I was freezing earlier. That's why.
-[Jamel] It's hotter than...
-[Rob] It's too hot. I got this mask on.
[Jamel] Yeah, it's... Wow.
Wanted to come to support you.
Show you some love.
-Rob] Yeah.
-Chyna] Thank you.
We weren't in he neighborhood,
so this is a special drop-off,
just so you know.
-[Rob] Just wanted to stop by.
-[Chyna] Thank you.
Well, we'll let you go finish.
Have a good rest of your shoot.
-[Chyna] Thanks for stopping by.
-[Rob] Yeah.
-[Jamel] That was perfect.
-[Rob] No.
[Jamel] Why?
She could have said, "Don't come."
[Rob] I just don't feel welcome, honestly.
[Jamel] I don't think it was
the most exciting part of her day,
but she could have said no.
I know there's a problem.
We don't even have to talk about...
-We should talk about it.
-[Rob] I could heard it in her voice.
I could see it.
It really did not make me happy.
It did not make me want to stay there.
-I didn't even really want to go.
-[Jamel] Well, I'm glad you did.
'Cause that's a positive interaction, bro.
It was a bit awkward,
but if you say that you support her
you're not judgmental
about what she does...
[Rob] I don't know if I said
that to her where she heard it.
Did you not support her? You're
crazy. Of course she knows.
Some things don't have to be said.
Just your presence alone says it all.
[Rob] I just find it all very interesting.
Interesting or strange?
[Rob] Well, just off.
Everything's just off.
That [bleep] just bugs me.
It's just frustrating.
[rhythmic electronic music plays]
[crowd cheering and screaming]
[crowd chants] Kylie! Kylie! Kylie!
Okay, guys, so we are gonna
go to Kylie's pop-up shop.
We're gonna check it out.
Maybe see if I can get in.
[crowd cheering and screaming]
[Kim] It's so cute in here.
Okay, so we're here
at the Kylie pop-up.
It's so cute. Look at the Kylie sign.
-[woman] Kylie everywhere!
-[Kim] What should we steal? That?
-[woman] These are kind of dope.
-[Kim] Ooh!
-[woman] Oh, my God!
-[Kim] I am so proud of my Kylie!
[Simon] We've arrived at the
Kylie pop-up. There's a lot going on.
Would Kylie
would kill us if we told everyone
they could have free lip kits on Kylie?
I was thinking, how would you feel
if I took 30 from the back
and was, like, "You get a lip kit!
You get a lip kit!"
And just throw them everywhere?
-Do you think that...?
-[Kylie] You can. I don't care.
[Kim] Will I have to pay
for them is the question. [laughs]
-[Kylie] That's fine.
-[Kim] Cool.
-[Simon] This is amazing.
-[Kim] Where are lip kits?
-Hi, guys. Want a free lip kit?
-[woman] Thank you!
[Kim] I'm giving out
free lip kits from Kylie.
[Kim voiceover]
I am really proud of Kylie.
The store looks really great.
It's fun for me to, like,
see what her passion is
and to be a part of that,
and I want to be there to support her.
[crowd screams]
[woman] Kim! Kim! We love you!
Hello. Hello. Hello. Is it working?
-It's working.
-[Khloe] It's not as loud as I would like.
-But you just have to yell.
-[yells] Hello?
-[Malika] There you go.
-But I'm yelling.
Why would I yell
if I have this thing?
-[Malika] 'Cause you get louder with that.
-Okay.
So, doing anything
with Kourtney is the best,
but also some of the worst times of
my life 'cause she can't make a decision.
It's, like, crippling,
and it literally alters her life.
It is, like, a horrible thing
that she can't... She's so indecisive.
-Does she realize that, though?
-[Khloe] She knows. It's not a secret.
I need her to learn how to make
decisions in a timely fashion,
so I don't have a week
to wait for something that...
-[Malika laughs] Got it.
-Then we could also...
But, like, we could be distracting her.
-We got a pincher. A pincher.
-I don't...
Is that to wake her up?
No, just her kids
are probably like, "Mom! Mom! Mom!"
-You still have to decide things.
-Got you.
-[Khloe] You're a mother of three.
-[imitates siren]
-[squeaky siren blasts]
-[Kourtney] That is annoying.
[Khloe] Kourtney is here!
-What is happening?
-[siren blares]
Are you ready to learn how
to make a decision on a dime?
-[Malika] Are you?
-Can you decide that?
-[Kourtney laughs] Yes.
-[Khloe] Okay.
That's a good start.
I am really trying to help Kourt
with her indecisiveness,
so this is a little experiment
to make you think fast, be decisive,
get your [bleep] together and stop being
the most indecisive human being ever.
We're gonna play
some little fun games,
and it's about
making decisions in a timely fashion.
I just don't know
how Khloe comes up with this stuff.
Malika's will act
as if your three children...
I am your distraction.
[Khloe] One side has our family
members' names. This side has gifts.
-I would like you to take the red pen.
-Uh-huh.
We're gonna time you.
And I would like you to draw a line
from each gift to each person.
-Really identify what they would want.
-[Kourtney] 'Kay.
You have a total of ten seconds,
starting now.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
-Mommy! Mommy!
-...six, five...
-Mommy! I'm hungry! I need to pee.
-...four, three, two, one.
-[Kourtney] Hold on.
-[Khloe] You're done!
[Kourtney] I made a mistake.
Kendall and Kylie's is switched.
I thought you meant
who did the thing go with...
[siren blasts]
[laughs]
-[Kourtney] Awful game.
-Now we're onto round two!
So in this situation,
I'm gonna hold up two cards.
You pick between the two cards
of what you like more.
-Okay.
-[Khloe] Ready? Go.
Dairy-free or gluten-free?
-That is awful.
-[squeaky horn blows]
New York or Miami?
[Kourtney] Some days I'd wanna
go to Miami, some days, New York.
[squeaky horn blares]
Hugo's or Health Nut?
This is not the stuff
I have problems with, you idiots!
This is just such a joke.
Like, none of this is helpful.
I'm getting a headache.
This isn't teaching me how to be decisive.
To get pregnant, or not to get pregnant?
[Malika] That's a good one.
-[squeaky horn blows]
-You're done.
Who am I getting pregnant with?
That's not the an... the question!
Well, now I can't hear
and this was pointless. Thanks, guys.
Kourtney, don't leave the premises.
This probably wasn't the best exercise
when it comes to making
Kourtney get over her indecisiveness.
I don't know what the solution is here,
but I still have something up my sleeve.
You could benefit
from this whole experience.
She hates us.
[bouncy dance music plays]
[cameras clicking]
[indistinct yelling]
Better late than never.
-[Kim] Can we go backstage?
-[stagehand] We're going through the back.
[Kim] Okay, cool. I just want
to see Kanye before it starts.
Today, is Kanye's fashion show.
I even haven't seen any of the prototypes
that they've been designing
and putting together,
so I'm just excited to see it
for the first time myself.
-[Kanye] Yeah.
-[Kim] I said a prayer.
-This is gonna be so good.
-Yeah.
Everyone's just, like, so excited.
The line of press that was
just outside is so crazy
just to get people's arrivals.
-For real?
-So much.
-Nah, it's exciting.
-It's gonna be good.
[indistinct chatter]
["Bed" by Ye plays]
♪ Girl, change into
that Victoria Secret thing that I like
♪ Alright, okay
tonight you're havin' me your way
♪ Perfume, spray it there
put our love in the air
♪ Now pull me right next to you
finna raise the temp' in the room... ♪
[Kim voiceover]
Kanye had this amazing idea
where the models
are seen inside this giant cube.
It's just been so much fun,
seeing everyone's reactions to it.
And then for the finale,
they all walk around.
♪ Wanna put my fingers through your hair
Wrap me up in your legs
♪ Then love you 'til your eyes roll back
♪ I'm tryna put you to bed, to bed, to bed
♪ I wanna put you to bed
to bed, to bed... ♪
Kanye has worked so hard
at this fashion show,
and the show's great
and so visually exciting to see.
So it just makes me so proud.
[audience applauds and cheers]
[audience cheers and whoops]
You get to see the clothes.
And then they walk out. It's awesome.
Yeah. I thought it was
a really cool way to do it.
-I agree with you.
-Yeah.
[Kim] Get in the photo.
[man] Something tells me Kim's phone
takes really good photos.
There's something on her phone
where we all gonna look like models.
[Rob] Mom, what are you doing?
Are you done yet,
or... you still need another hour or two?
-Mom?
-[phone alert]
I got it.
'Cause I have to leave
to go to Gunnar's at 50 minutes,
so if you need another
40 something minutes that's cool.
No, I'm good.
What's going on with you right now?
Everything's fine. I'm trying to,
like, just be peaceful and...
What's going on with Chyna?
I don't know.
We really just have stupid...
Well, like, we just communicate
very poorly, and that's...
-It's all dumb. Fights.
-Yeah.
I was just thinking
on how good of a relationship
you and my dad had
when you guys weren't together
and it wasn't awkward.
-There was no tension or anything.
-Right.
It was very, like, healthy.
I want to have the type of elationship
that you and my dad had,
'cause we all remember only positive.
-There's never anything negative, so...
-[Kris] Yeah.
Here's the thing.
-You were two years old.
-[Rob] Yeah.
It didn't happen right out the gate.
We were better best friends
than we were being married.
It took us 18 years to realize that.
He was mad. I was mad.
But after everybody settled down,
it was a conscious decision to be adults
and be inclusive.
It would just kill me if I didn't have
that friendship and have that peace
between us for Dream and just in general.
You can get there,
especially with your attitude.
I think the fact you're thinking like this
is amazing. You're a good man.
For Rob to understand it does take
perseverance and determination
to get to the place
that Robert and I were,
and still is willing to work things out
with Chyna is truly remarkable.
Most people don't think
like you think, Rob.
They don't stop and go, "I need
to consciously make sure
that we put Dream first."
-[Rob] Mm-hmm.
-That means you and Chyna decide:
We'll be great parents.
Then once she gets to say,
"I want to go to Daddy's tonight,"
and you guys can be flexible like that...
-Yeah.
-...you'll raise an amazing daughter.
I hope that Rob and Chyna
really, truly find a way to get there.
[Khloe] Hello!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Are you guys ready?
[Kris] What is getting you
worked up and hot and bothered?
-I have a surprise for you!
-A surprise?
-I thought we were going to work out.
-It's a form of working out. Come on.
I'm down to do things that are new,
so I have something
a little special for Kourt
and me I get to burn a few calories,
so we all go home happy.
[sings fanfare]
-[Kourtney] What?
-[Khloe] We're going on an adventure!
-[Damien] How you doing?
-[Khloe] Hi, guys! I'm so excited!
-[Damien] Ready to fight fires with us?
-[Khloe] Yeah!
Fight fires?
Are we going on a drive-along?
[Khloe] I've been to fire stations before.
They have a ton of quick-thinking drills.
Yeah, shotgun!
[Khloe] So I called the fire station
and they're down with us coming by.
Oh, my God,
there's axes in here! You guys!
An ax to, like, knock down
the door when there's a fire!
It's just gonna be an exciting adventure.
I don't really think this
is gonna really help Kourtney
in the grand scheme of things,
but I think it'll be hysterical to watch.
-Kourtney, turn on the siren.
-[Kourtney] Okay, I'm gonna do this.
-[siren wailing]
-[Khloe laughs]
[Kris] Good little girl.
Oh, my God. You would think
we're 12, but this is what excites us.
[Kris] My God, here's a fire, Kourtney.
Oh, no, this is, like, real. Oh, my God.
[Khloe] What?
[Khloe] There we go.
[Kourtney] We've got a fire to fight.
-This whole thing is really for you.
-Okay.
Because you are one of
the worst decision-makers of all time
so you're gonna lead
this whole excursion to save you,
like, the damsel in distress.
Okay. I want to be the damsel in distress!
-[Damien] Put your jacket on.
-[Kourtney] This is heavy.
-So, are these fire-proof?
-Yeah.
-Obviously, Kourtney.
-[Damien] So what we're gonna do:
We need to get through that door.
It's called forcible entry. Okay?
You ready? Come on.
[Kris] I can't see anything! [coughs]
-Which tool you want to use for that door?
-The ax.
-Good choice.
-Yeah!
-[Kris] Help me!
-[Damien] Hurry up, there's a fire.
-[Khloe] Run, Kourt.
-[Damien] Sister'll hit it.
Hold on. I need
to hold it first, you freak.
[Damien] Now hit it.
Now pull. There you go. Good job.
-[both] Yeah!
-[Damien] We need visibility.
We'll throw a ladder up.
Which ladder you think we need?
-[Kourtney] The extra tall one.
-The extra tall one?
We got a roof ladder, an attic ladder.
-[Kourtney] Eh...
-[Kris] Help me!
[Khloe] Kourt, hurry up!
Someone's dying inside!
-[Kris] You guys, help me!
-[Kourtney] Khloe, I don't know!
[Kris coughs]
[Khloe] Come on, Kourt.
Mom could be in there dying!
[Kris] Oh. [coughing]
Dead. Someone died with that...
Like, how indecisive you are.
-Someone just died.
-No.
-[Kris] Phew.
-[Khloe] Kourt!
-[Kourtney] A roof ladder.
-[Damien] Let's grab one.
-[Kourtney] Do I put my tool down?
-[Khloe] Come on, Kourt! [bleep] Hurry up!
-[Kourtney] Thank you.
-[Damien] Tell them what you want, Cap.
-[Khloe] Kourt!
-[Kourtney] Let's put it on this side.
-[Khloe] It's not gonna fit.
-[Kris] You need a bigger ladder.
I'm inside dying!
-We need the bigger ladder.
-[Kris] Come on.
-Hurry up, Kourtney!
-[Kourtney] What am I doing?
-[Khloe] Tell them what the [bleep] to do!
-[Kourtney] Let's put it up against the...
against the building
and we'll get up there.
Do I have to go down the same way?
-Holy [bleep].
-[Damien chuckles] You'll be good.
[Kris] Hurry up, Kourtney.
We don't have all day.
-[Khloe] Oh...
-[Kourtney] Can't see. Goggles down.
[Kris] Save yourself, people,
'cause Kourtney's a snail.
[Khloe] Hurry up, Kourtney. Holy [bleep].
Someone's gonna have
to rescue me from up here.
'Cause I'm not coming back down.
[Kris] Kourtney, help me!
Holy [bleep].
-I'm not going back down.
-[Kourtney] My goggles are fully down.
[Damien] You didn't bring that ax?
[Kourtney] Oh, shoot. forgot.
Kourtney, you [bleep] didn't bring the ax?
-[Kourtney] No.
-[Damien] We need that ax.
-Captain forgot it.
-[Kourtney] Khloe, shut the [bleep] up!
[Kris] Save me, Kourtney!
[Kourtney] Wait, but what is this?
-[Khloe] You gotta let the smoke come out.
-[Kourtney] Do a real rooves have a box?
-[Damien laughs] No.
-[Kourtney] Okay. No, I didn't know.
-[Kourtney grunts weakly]
-Try to dig a hole in it.
Hit it like you're mad. Hit it harder.
-[Khloe] Think about Scott, Kourtney!
-[Damien] Little harder.
[Kris] We got people trapped down here
We need rescue!
Let's get down.
There's not a spiral staircase somewhere?
Khloe, you can do it.
[Khloe exhales]
[Kris coughs] I'm dying!
Listen, God, you're not
gonna let me die this way.
-Yes!
-[bleep] a duck.
Argh! [Khloe laughs]
Oh, my God, I hate heights. Ooh!
-Oh, my God.
-[Kris] Come on, you got to go faster.
-[Kourtney] Yeah, Khloe!
-I did it!
-[Kris] It's burning up in here!
-Ready to go rescue someone?
[Khloe] Yes.
-[Kris] Kourtney!
-[Kourtney] I can't see!
-[Damien] Stay low.
-[Kourtney coughs]
-[Kris] It's really hot in here.
-[Kourtney] Stop complaining.
-[Khloe] Mom, come here.
-[Kris] I can't see anything.
Oh, Khloe saved me! Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Whoo!
Where's Kourtney?
I got to go in for my colleague.
-I found you.
-[Kourtney] Whoo!
-[Kris laughs]
-[Kourtney] That's what it's like?
-[Kris] Wow.
-[Kourtney] You can't see?
-Don't you get claustrophobic?
-That wasn't even hot.
-It's intense.
-Watch Backdraft.
You'll respect everybody so much more.
Don't you have a newfound
respect for our firefighters?
I do.
Like, it's way, way, way crazier
than I would've ever thought.
I think, like, just the cool--
You didn't rescue your mom.
I was claustrophobic.
Did you take pictures of me
and Khloe in our gear?
'Cause that's what you're worried about.
[Kris] Kourt, turn around.
[Khloe] Do you have
any petite firefighters?
There's a lot of girls
that are petite that are on the job.
[Khloe] Like, I don't know
what this one would do.
-[Dream cooing]
-[Chyna] Ooh.
-[Chyna] Hey, Rob.
-[Rob] What's good, what's good?
Hey, what's good, what's good?
[Chyna makes whooshing noise]
[Rob] She's comfortable right there.
-[nurse] Four months already?
-[Chyna] Mm-hm.
[nurse] Let's go weigh in
those cute cheeks you have, huh?
Right down here.
We can come on down.
Let's see how big you're getting.
How much everybody's carrying around.
Ooh. 16, two and a half. Okay, perfect.
Leave her just like that
and Dr. Peter will be in.
[Rob] Okay, thank you.
[blows raspberry]
-[Dr. Peter] Hi, Rob.
-[Rob] Dr. Peter.
-[Dr. Peter] How are you, sir?
-[Rob] How are you?
-[Dr. Peter] Nice to see you.
-You, too.
-[Dr. Peter] Dream.
-[Rob and Chyna] Dream.
[Dr. Peter] We've come
full circle with Rob.
[Rob] Yeah.
Just gonna listen to your heart.
Give me a little tummy time.
Who's that?
She's a ten.
So she's gonna get
a Prevnar vaccine and a polio vaccine.
-But she looks great.
-[Rob] Thank you.
[Rob whispers] Kiss her stomach.
[Rob] Kiss her stomach.
[Rob] Ooh, yeah.
[Chyna] She's a baby. Kick, kick.
-[Rob] Kick 'em, kick.
-[Chyna] Kick me. Kick, kick.
-Dream, kick, kick.
-[Rob] Yeah. Good job.
I'm sorry.
[nurse] Only a little pinch. I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry, baby.
-[Chyna] Ooh.
-[Rob] Sorry.
-[nurse] That's it. Look how good you did.
-[Rob] I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-[Chyna] She didn't even cry.
-[nurse] You're awesome.
-[Rob] I'm sorry, baby.
-[Chyna] Dream, look at me!
-[Rob] I'm sorry.
-[Dream cries]
-I'm sorry.
[nurse] That one
stings a little. All done.
-[Rob] I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-[Chyna] It's okay.
-[nurse] All right, you're all set.
-[Rob] Yeah.
I hate that our relationship
is a little uncomfortable,
but I'm very committed to building
the friendship between Chyna and I
because the type
of relationship I had with my dad,
I want to have that with my daughter.
I'm just trying to do the best
for my baby, uh, Dream,
'cause everything I'm doing is for her.
-[Dream squeals]
-[Rob] That's so cute.
-I'm sorry.
-[Chyna] It's okay.
Easy-peezy.
-[door closes]
-[Kourtney] Greetings, earthling.
-Ooh, "earthling."
-Do I see a protein smoothie?
-Keeks, there's a protein smoothie I made.
-Is there extra?
-[Khloe] Right there.
-Good. Where are your cups?
-Where they've always been.
-[Kim] I've never used a cup.
[Kourtney] So, couple things.
Clearly, my indecisiveness
is affecting everyone,
and talking about it
with you and you and Mom
and doing all these exercises
made me realize
that I want to do
something to be more decisive.
So, last night, I watched
the Tony Robbins documentary,
and I feel like it helped me
get to the root of it.
I feel like Scott and I were
very codependent,
and I just would
always bounce every idea off of him.
Also, I'm just, like,
living a different life now,
where doing more
for myself is, like, an option.
And now that I am able
to make my own decisions,
I want to make the best decisions.
Tony Robbins taught me
to make decisions from the heart
and not from your head.
And, like I said, I had
a million reasons to justify
going to New York, but in my heart,
it was telling me to stay home,
so I want to start, you know, listening.
[Khloe] I am really proud
of you for, like, addressing this head-on
and taking control over something
that was debilitating to you.
It's, like, that shows that
you're good at making decisions.
We did have, I think, a lot
of fun trying to figure out
why she's so indecisive,
but I'm really proud of Kourt for making
the steps in the right direction.
I hope eventually she won't have this
debilitating indecisiveness about her.
Thank you, Tony.
[Kourtney] Thank you, Tony.
[Kim] Coming up next week...
[Caitlyn] Jay Leno, in the house.
Should I be concerned?
My daughter leaving with an older man?
-Nice thing is they don't get much older.
-[Caitlyn laughs]
[Kendall] I met this guy.
He's the first gay prince
to come out in India.
There are similarities between
Prince Manvendra's stories
and my parents' stories.
-I read Caitlyn's book.
-Stop.
-Yeah.
-And?
Everything is always your fault.