[Khloe] So did you even know that Kourt
and Scott were in Mexico?
[Kim] Yeah. I'm, like, pro-them.
Like, oh, I hope they get back together
and just so into it.
-[Khloe] Do you see other people?
-[Scott] No.
-[Khloe] You don't?
[Scott] I technically could, I guess.
[Khloe] Yeah, totally.
[Scott] I realize that a lot
of things truly are my fault
and I'm happy taking ownership
for all of that.
I just hope that, you know,
one day she understands
that I would never want
to be with anybody but her.
[Kanye] Welcome to Saint Pablo.
[crowd cheering]
[Kim] Holy (bleep).
Feeling the vibe of the crowd,
it's just a lot, all at once.
I'm going to chill in the back, okay?
I want to, like, disappear
for a little bit.
♪ ♪
-[Scott] Hi.
-[Kris] Hey. How are you?
-[Scott] Good.
-[Kris] I'm looking for my shoes.
-[Scott] Oh, very European.
-[Kris] Ooh. You have a scratchy beard.
-[Scott] Yeah.
-[Kris] What's going on?
Speaking of scratchy beards,
I was thinking about you
because you're starting to remind me
of the guy
on the new Fifty Shades of Grey.
[Scott] Isn't that a good but weird thing?
[Kris] Melanie's daughter
is in the movie, Dakota,
and somehow I ended up
with the Fifty Shades of Grey
-official pleasure collection.
-[Scott] What's that?
[Kris] What I'll do with this?
[Scott] What am I gonna do with it?
[Kris] Gosh, I hope this isn't a vibrator,
I'll feel stupid.
-I'd have wished I'd have kept it.
-[Scott] I've seen the first movie.
He, like, ties her hands up.
[Kris] So, like, put your hands
above your head.
-[Scott] I'm innocent.
-[Kris] I'm not arresting you.
[Scott] Oh, disco.
[Kris] So you just kind of do this,
you know, and just get it.
[Scott] It's uncomfortable
that you know how to do this so well.
-This is great?
-[Kris] Yeah.
Ooh, this is cute. What is this bracelet?
-[Scott] You want it?
-[Kris] Who gave you that?
Yes. Take it off. Okay, thank you.
-My work here is done. I love you.
-[Scott] All right, good trade.
You get a gold bracelet,
I get to tie myself up.
[Kris] I'll buy you a razor.
Merry Christmas.
[Scott] Hap... uh, happy Hanukkah.
♪ ♪
-[Khloe chuckles]
-[Kim] Hey, guys.
-[Khloe] You're relaxed.
-[Kim] Just hanging out here.
Oh, yeah.
[Khloe] I like those sweats.
I might need a pair.
Kim doesn't get me (bleep).
-[Scott] Mason kept me up last night.
-[Khloe] You've got to put him to bed.
[Scott] No, I put him to sleep,
he wakes up, comes in,
he, like, throws his arm on me. He's like,
"Hey," and then he goes back
to bed, but I'm up then.
So it's, like, last night
I literally slept zero.
[Khloe] Life of kids.
[Kim] Yeah, well, how was Aspen?
You guys were, like, posting cute videos
on the airplane.
[Scott] Aspen was, like, really good.
Like, she usually doesn't want
to ever go to dinner with me
without the kids, so that seemed
like a huge step in the right direction.
Kourtney and I have been spending
a lot more time together.
So I decided to take her
and the kids to Aspen
and she agreed to go,
so, for me, that's a big thing.
At the end of the day,
it was our first trip
we've had in, like, a long time,
where we, like, actually were a family
and got to feel like it was
like the old days.
-I'm happy.
-[Khloe] Good.
[Scott] I feel like all
Kourtney really ever wanted from me
was for me to be sober and healthy
and be there to take care of my family.
I've been really present
and haven't been drinking.
You know, a year or so ago,
I feel like there was a point
where we didn't even speak
or see each other, so this feels good.
I mean, I guess everything is going
in the right direction, then. I mean...
[Kim] Wait, I have a question.
Does Kourtney know that you got her
a ring to propose?
[Scott] Yeah.
-[Khloe] We found it in the townhouse.
-[Scott] The whole thing is weird.
-[Khloe] Is it what you mean?
-[Kim] No.
This was a nice Lorraine Schwartz ring,
and then he returned it.
[Scott] No, and I like,
asked her to marry me...
-[Kim] Not with the ring, but she... Oh!
-[Scott] No, with it.
[Kim] Oh, you didn't tell me this.
[Scott] It was weird;
We didn't tell anybody.
[Kim] I'm really happy to see Kourtney
and Scott in a good place.
I mean, at the end of the day
if Scott got his (bleep) together,
do I believe him and Kourtney
would be together? Yes.
He's been so good;
I think Scott just has to keep it up.
[Scott] It was somewhat cute,
and then we just got scared about, like,
media and this and that and we were like,
"Let's just put the ring aside and
we'll talk about it another day."
Never spoke about it again.
-[Khloe] That's strange.
-[Scott] Yeah.
That is strange, come to think about it.
♪ ♪
-[Caitlyn] Kendall!
-[Kendall] Hi.
[Caitlyn] There you are,
just the way I left you, eating.
-[Kendall] Yeah.
-[Caitlyn] How you doing?
-[Kendall] Good.
-[Caitlyn] Oh, it actually smells good.
[goat screaming on computer]
-[Caitlyn] What are you looking at?
-[Kendall] Goats screaming like humans.
[goat screaming]
-[Caitlyn] They sound like that?
-[Kendall] 16 million views.
-People have no lives.
-[goat screaming]
-[Caitlyn] You wanna talk about the barn?
-[Kendall] Sure.
[Caitlyn] It's been done for three months.
[Kendall] My dad is really cute,
and built Kylie and I a barn in Malibu
at her house.
-[Caitlyn] What do you think?
-[Kendall] I love it.
[Caitlyn] It's absolute bribery.
To get you out here more.
-[Kendall] Is that it?
-[Caitlyn] Yes.
[Kendall] I have always had a passion
for horses.
So, since this is happening,
I think that it will help us to hang out
a little bit more.
I want to bring my horse out there,
but I don't want her to be alone out there
with, like, no other horse.
[Caitlyn] Well, I understand.
If we get a horse,
-are you gonna come out and ride it?
-[Kendall] Yes.
-[Caitlyn] I hope so.
What we need is one for Kylie
and one for me.
-Let me call Kylie.
-[line ringing]
-[Kylie] Hey.
-[Caitlyn] Hey, how are you doing?
[Kylie] I'm pretty good. What's up?
[Caitlyn] We are sitting here
looking at horses online.
[Kylie] Nice.
[Caitlyn] Would you be willing,
if we get two or three horses,
spending a day running around
and looking at these horses?
[Kylie] Yeah, I'll go.
[Caitlyn] I'll let you know when,
but as long as I know you're in.
'Cause I got this barn that's been sitting
out there for three months, done.
[Kylie] I know, we got to do it.
[Caitlyn] Love you. Bye.
-[Kylie] Love you.
-Bye, guys.
-[Caitlyn] Bye.
-Yeah, I'd say we go check out horses.
-[Kendall] Can we get a mini horse?
[Caitlyn] We buy a little mini horse
and then what the hell do we do with it
-we do with it when we get the next?
-[Kendall] It hangs out. It's company.
Mini horses for sale.
I used to search this, like, all the time?
No, I want little babies.
-Look it, it's $1,000.
[Caitlyn] All this mini horse does
-is just eats and poops and hang out.
-[Kendall] Yep.
Oh!
Sold, sold, sold. They're all sold.
[Caitlyn] You mean mini horses
are in demand?
-[Kendall] Yeah, of course they are.
-[Caitlyn] Shocking.
♪ ♪
[Kourtney] Hey, girl.
Get on it.
-I feel like this can't carry me.
-[Kim] And then, squeeze your butt.
I'm heavier than you.
You just squeeze your butt up.
[both laughing]
P, it's so cute.
[Kourtney] It's just so exciting
that you have this whole room.
P, you got to try this,
it's a really good workout.
-Do you want to go or no?
-[Penelope] No.
[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Scott] Is it the baby?
-[Penelope] Yeah.
[Kourtney] Hi.
[Scott] Hi, Poosh.
Whoa, it does look real.
[Kourtney] Wait, so were people excited
that you tweeted?
[Kim] Yeah, they were like,
"Oh, my God, she's back."
-[Scott] What did you Instagram?
-[Kim] Just, like, a photo.
[Kourtney] And tweeted.
[Kim] I've slowly started
to get back to my normal life
and I really did take so much time
away from that.
I decided to post a family photo
and share with the world
what we've been up to.
You know, it was such a warm welcome.
I'm slowly coming back.
[Kourtney] So when are you guys going
to Dubai?
[Kim] On the 11th for, like, four days.
After Paris, I canceled all my work
and I had to reschedule everything,
so one of my first things back
that I'm doing is going to Dubai
and doing this Masterclass with Mario.
You better suck it in.
Masterclass is this big makeup seminar
where we show people how to do makeup.
The last few times I've been to Dubai,
it's always been, like, pandemonium.
-Mahaba!
-[crowd cheering]
I truly have never felt more love
than I felt here in Dubai.
[crowd cheering]
I, basically, just am the-the model
for it and Mario does my makeup.
[Kourtney] Are you excited to, like,
get back out and start work?
[Kim] I'm starting to just, like, get
excited to work, but I'm just more nervous
of freakish things happening.
[Scott] Now you take all the precaution
that you should have been taking.
[Kim] I mean, totally.
We're bringing, like,
a whole security team.
The Masterclass is on a stage
with, like, thousands of people.
It's not like I'm doing baby steps
and stepping out at home
and doing work stuff at home
or in the States.
Like, it is an international trip.
To say that I'm not nervous
or scared is an understatement,
but I'm going to try to get back
to normal.
♪ ♪
-[Andrea] Hello. I'm Andrea.
-[Kim] Nice to meet you.
-[man] Ms. Kardashian, welcome.
-[Kim] How are you? Thank you.
We're staying at the Atlantis
at the Palm Hotel.
I stay here every time I come.
They have the most amazing suite.
-[Stephanie] Hi.
-[Kim] Hi.
-[woman] Welcome back.
-[Stephanie] Thank you so much.
-Oh, yeah, you've never been here before.
-[Scott] No.
-[Stephanie] You're lying.
-[Scott] I swear.
[Stephanie] Oh, my God, this is, like,
for the queen.
[Scott] It's like the Taj Mahal.
[Stephanie] This is for the Queen
of Calabasas here.
[Kim] Scott's here, Stephanie came,
one of my good friends, Carla,
and Simon is meeting us.
I love having my circle,
and just feeling as, like,
comfortable as I can be.
[Stephanie] Ooh-la-la.
[Scott] This isn't over-the-top at all.
-[Stephanie] How nice, right?
-[Scott] Wow.
[Stephanie] Yeah. Are you hungry or...?
[Scott] What is this for, 900 people?
[Stephanie] Scott, you need just a picture
at the end of this table, like...
-[Scott] Yeah, having a quick dinner.
-[Stephanie] Yeah.
I can't even see you.
[Scott] This is like in Richie Rich
when they talk to each other.
[camera clicking]
[Stephanie gasps] Yeah! Simon!
[Simon] This is insane!
-[Stephanie] You've never been here?
-[Simon] No.
-I've been doing, like...
-[Kim] Oh, it was Scotty and Joyce.
-[Scott] Hello, Simone.
-[Simon] Hi!
[Scott] Welcome to Dubai.
We got some food for ya.
-[Simon] Are you staying in here?
-[Scott] No.
-I'm staying in the aquarium room.
-[Simon] Oh. This is so good.
-[Scott] How you doing?
-[Simon] You look nice.
[Kim] Let's go see the aquarium.
[Simon] This... is... crazy.
-[Scott] Uh-huh.
-[phone ringing]
[Kim] Guys, look at.
P and Northie, look at.
-[Simon] Oh... my... God, insane.
-[Kim] Look at, in this hotel room,
you guys, look what's behind me!
It's a big aquarium!
[Simon] Oh, he got a sign. He has a sign.
[Kim] Northie, P, look. Aah!
Scott, it says "Welcome Scott."
[laughter]
-[Scott] Oh, that's fantastic.
-[Kim] Oh, my gosh.
I'll call you guys back. Wait, wait.
I need to Snapchat this.
Look at Scott's welcome. How amazing.
[Scott] So, if I'm in this bathtub,
vibing, this dude's just gonna peep me?
[Kim] Okay, I totally hung up
on the girls on FaceTime.
[Stephanie] This is so cool.
♪ ♪
[Caitlyn] We're out in the middle
of nowhere.
[Kendall] I know. It's crazy.
[car horn toots]
-[Caitlyn] Talking horses.
-[Kendall] Yeah.
-[Caitlyn] Where's Kylie?
-[Kendall] I thought she was with you.
[Caitlyn] Well, she's supposed to be here.
This is more for her than it is for us.
You've already got a horse.
Kind of ticks me off.
[Kendall] I don't know what to tell you,
man. Hi!
-[Jessica] Hi.
-[Caitlyn] How you doing?
[Kendall] This is awesome.
I don't even feel like I'm in L.A.
[Jessica] You're not really.
This is paradise.
-[Kendall] But you're 20 minutes.
-[Jessica] Heaven on Earth.
-[Kendall] How are you?
-[Jessica] Hi.
-[Caitlyn] How are you?
-[Jessica] I'm blessed.
-[Kendall] Kendall. How are you?
-[man] Welcome. Awesome.
[Kendall] Hi, buddy.
-[Caitlyn] Who's this guy? I like you.
-Is that one up for sale, too?
-[Jessica] Yeah.
-[woman] Diamond? Yes.
-[Jessica] Go, girl!
Look at this girl! Okay.
[Kendall] Hi.
[Jessica] So this is a really nice
broke quarter horse gelding.
This is a nice horse.
-Just get up and go.
-[Caitlyn] Get up and go.
[Jessica] You are a good little rider.
Wow.
-[Caitlyn] Good job, Kendall!
-[Jessica] Nice job.
[Kendall] I'm excited
that the ball's rolling,
and we can spend more time together
and start riding again.
How am I doing?
-Post. Post. Post.
-Come on.
-[Jessica] How does she feel?
-[Kendall] Good. I like her.
[Kendall] Dad, will you take a picture?
[line ringing]
-[Kylie over the phone] Hello, Father.
-[Caitlyn] Hello, daughter.
We're up here.
I'll send you pictures of the horses.
We may wind up buying one for you,
even though you've never ridden it
'cause you didn't show up today.
[Kylie] Yeah, I didn't.
I've been working every single day.
[Caitlyn] Say hi to the one I like.
This is Ruger.
[Kendall] I get my dad missing
hanging out with Kylie,
but I do make an effort to come out
and hang out with her.
[Caitlyn] Oh, they-- wait a second.
Okay, now you're FaceTiming. Hold it.
-Wait, wait, wait.
-[Kendall] Give me!
[Caitlyn] We're FaceTiming now.
-[Kendall] Oh, my God.
-[Caitlyn] Wait a second.
[Kendall] She's just obsessing over Kylie
and ruining out time together.
[Kylie] She looks really pretty.
[Caitlyn] Yeah, we'll send you pictures.
Love you.
-[Kylie] Love you. Bye.
-[Caitlyn] Wish you were here.
Do you think she would shoot us
if she didn't ride it first?
She's not here, so we'll make
that decision, right?
Kendall?
Kendall?!
♪ ♪
-[woman] Hi, Kim!
-[woman 2] Hi!
[woman 3] Hi, Kim!
[Scott] We could probably
order a couple of things.
Maybe get, like, some yellowtail jalapeno,
like, super thin?
Maybe some new-style salmon,
spicy tuna, crispy rice.
Yeah, and then some black cod wraps
for everybody.
-[Carla] How's Charley?
-[Chris] She's good.
Her and Mason were like two peas
in a pod the whole time in Aspen.
They wouldn't do anything
without each other.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Scott] Mason was so sad after.
[Kim] What's so funny is that North,
she has such pride when she talks
about Mason.
If he's nice to her,
she'll come home and be like,
"Mama, Mason was so nice to me today,
Mom."
Like, it'll, like, make her whole day
when Mason's nice to her.
I've just, honestly...
I've been to maybe one restaurant
in three months.
[Scott] How does it feel?
[Kim] Like, a bit of anxiety
with, like, a lot of people.
[Stephanie] We literally haven't been
in a setting like this in, like...
[Kim] I haven't... yeah.
In months and literally everywhere I look,
everyone was videotaping everything.
[Scott] Anybody who went through
what you went through
would have probably more anxiety
than this.
[Kim] I think that my sense
of, like, what's going on around me is,
like, times a hundred that it used to be.
I can just feel people around,
like, taking pictures,
or, you know, talking and calling my name.
[Scott] Yo. I think we need to, like,
step up the security guys.
[Scott] This girl's taking pictures
of Kim eating.
Like, it's, like, have one guy over here.
One guy needs to be here and one here.
I don't know where they keep going.
[Kim] I don't want to be this
crazy person that's like,
"This person can't take a photo of me."
I'm in a public restaurant. Why not?
I get it seems ridiculous,
so I'm trying to ease into it,
but it's just how I feel.
♪ ♪
[Carla] I came here with your mom
and Corey.
-[Kim] You did?
-[Carla] Mm-hmm.
[Kim] Thank you.
I think I'm gonna have pasta, you guys.
Don't judge.
[Jen] Does anybody want salmon sashimi?
[Simon] You know that salmon
has the Japanese tapeworm.
-[Kim] Wait, what does?
-[Simon] Salmon on the...
-especially on the Pacific coast.
-[Kim] Does that make you skinnier?
[Simon] Yes. Well, a parasite,
so it would make you very skinny,
but very sick.
-[Carla] Very skinny.
-[Kim] Oh, very sick.
[Carla] I'll have the veal piccatine.
[Simon] Tuna tartare and the branzino.
[Jen] I'll do the salmon sashimi.
[Kim] What?!
[laughter]
You're gonna die.
[Jen] Stop. Really?
[Kim] I have to Google it.
[Jen] So, have you not seen Scott
at all since you've been here?
[Kim] I feel bad because, you know,
he mentioned to me.
I know it kind of bothers him.
Like, if he hears a story
about Kourtney, he's kind of like,
"Hmm, is that true?"
And he'll, like, ask me about it.
Last night, after dinner at Nobu,
Scott heard the rumor from a friend of his
that Kourtney's hooking up with someone,
and he starts texting me
and asking me about it.
Like, Kourtney's so secretive
that I honestly have no idea what it is,
so I don't know what to say to him.
[Simon] And they're not together.
[Carla] They're not,
but I'm sure he's hurt.
[Kim] Yeah, but the thing is,
he's trying to win her back.
I mean, it must not be easy for him
to take news like this,
'cause, you know,
they just had the best time in Aspen.
I definitely was like, "Okay,
they're back together."
I feel so bad for him.
It just really sucks,
'cause he's been doing amazing
for four months.
[Jen] What do you mean
amazing four months?
Like, he's not drinking?
-[Kim] He's been sober.
-[Simon] He's not going to clubs.
[Jen] He's probably doing that
for her and not for himself.
-[Simon] Right.
-[Kim] But he said,
"I'm not even doing this for her.
Like, I'm doing this for me,
and I'm gonna stay the course."
He fully has said that to me three times.
[Jen] I feel like a lot
of broken families...
[Simon] Broken families.
[Jen] Is that what it's called?
What do you call divorced people?
Broken home?
[Stephanie] It's dramatic, but, yeah.
-[Simon] Like, a modern family.
-[Jen] Okay, sorry. Modern family.
Anyways, people in a modern family,
it's probably really complicated.
Somebody always has to move on
before somebody else.
When I get my second husband,
it's gonna be awkward, you know,
for Mike for a while.
[laughter]
♪ ♪
[women screaming]
[man over microphone] Five, four,
three, two, one.
Dubai, make some noise!
Scott Disick!
[crowd cheering]
[Scott] Thank you, Dubai, for having me.
I'm pretty excited to be here.
[women screaming]
[man] I saw your Snapchat.
It was, uh, you and Kim
at a very long table.
[Scott] Yeah.
[man] And it was so long,
you had to actually have your phones out.
-Is that true?
-[Scott] Yes, that is true.
[man] Uh-huh,
and that was a little awkward, I imagine.
[Scott] It was a bit awkward. So is this.
[woman screaming]
I'm here across the world in Dubai,
and I found out that Kourtney
was with somebody else.
[man] Dubai, make some noise!
Up in the rafters, too.
Scott Disick!
[crowd cheering]
[Scott] I'm trying to be friendly
to all these people
that came out to see me at this
appearance, but little do they know,
I'm dealing with something
much bigger than anything now.
This is, like, probably the worst thing
I could ever hear, ever.
-Is there any direction here?
-[man] You're just taking pictures.
-[Scott] Hold both of 'em?
-[woman] One of them.
[man] The blue one, the blue.
[cameras clicking]
[Scott] I don't think
she realized a friend of mine saw her.
Of course, I call and ask what's going
on, and she blatantly lied to me.
It was somewhat heartbreaking.
I didn't see things going this direction.
[Scott] You know, I feel like everything
I've been working so hard for is done now.
-Yo.
-[Mansoor] Oh, really? Go party, man.
Whoa, man, we're gonna turn
the (bleep) up tonight.
-[Scott laughs]
-I'm-a tell you, bro!
Let's go party the (bleep) up, bro.
I know you need a drink.
♪ ♪
[Jen] Shopping with Kim Kardashian.
Nothing to see here, kids.
[Kim] This is cute.
Honestly, I haven't been shopping
in months.
And, not that I even need anything,
but I always like to see
what stores have in different countries,
or if there's special pieces.
Oh, my God, and it matches my outfit!
It's just so much fun.
[Carla] This is enough to put in your bag.
-[Kim] Oh, my God.
-[Carla] Your little one.
[Kim] Should I get one for North,
so it's like me and her?
[Kim] Gosh, we'll have our matching bags.
It's, like, perfect, right?
Perfect.
[cameras clicking]
[Simon] You good?
[Kim] Yeah.
[Jen] Are you not nervous
about that crowd?
[Kim] Yeah.
This is just like what I was afraid of,
is just this feeling of panic.
I just don't know who--
I'm, like, afraid of everything.
-I just get scared.
-[cameras clicking]
With so many people gathering,
and then, they start social media.
She's here."
And other people will know
exactly where I'm at.
It gives me such anxiety.
[Jen] This is going to be a scene.
[Kim] Can we go out the back?
[sales associate] There is an elevator,
yeah.
[Kim] Thank you so much.
[Caitlyn] Kendall!
Daddy's here!
Ooh, you got cookies, huh?
-[Kendall] Yeah, go ahead and eat 'em.
-[Caitlyn] Have they been here for weeks?
-[Kendall] No.
-[Caitlyn] No? Fresh?
-[Kendall] Today.
-[Caitlyn] Cool.
Have you heard from, uh, Kylie?
'Cause she's driving me kind of crazy.
Does she want this horse?
-[Kendall] I don't know.
-[Caitlyn] Maybe it'd be good for her.
Like, get out, go riding. You know?
She's... she still hasn't been out.
Driving me nuts.
Canceling on stuff all the time.
Why is she canceling?
[Kendall] You talk about it a lot,
don't you?
[Caitlyn] I do talk about it a lot, yeah.
[Kendall] I'm here. I'm not good enough?
It's really starting to hurt my feelings
that my dad only really talks
about Kylie when we hang out.
You keep complaining
and it's making me
not even want to be around you.
I've been bottling up
how this has all been making me feel,
but I just decided
I have to say something.
[Caitlyn] We're talking about,
you know, Kylie.
Um...
Actually, I'm sorry.
You know, honestly, I thought
you would be able to help a lot with it.
And I'm sorry I put you kind
of in the middle of all of this.
[Kendall] Mm-hmm.
[Caitlyn] You know, I get pretty insecure
at times with all the kids
and everything that I've been through,
and, um, you know,
even with all my insecurities,
you've always been there for me,
and I appreciate that.
-You know?
-[Kendall] Yeah.
[Caitlyn] You've been great
with the horse stuff,
so I appreciate you coming out,
helping out.
[Kendall] Of course.
[Caitlyn] You know?
[Kendall] I'm glad that my dad
acknowledged what she was doing.
And I do realize that she has had
a little bit of a struggle bonding
with all the kids, and I appreciate
that she's opening up.
I hope that now, we can just hang out
and enjoy our time together.
[Caitlyn] I would have to put you
as my number one child.
[Kendall] [hiccups]
Oh, every time I drink something hot,
I get the hiccups.
[Caitlyn] You get the hiccups?
-[Kendall hiccups]
-[Caitlyn laughs]
But I thought I made you perfect.
[Kendall] [hiccups] Nope.
Apparently not. [hiccups]
[Caitlyn laughs]
♪ ♪
[Simon] Morning, Kim.
[Kim] Good morning. How are you?
Did you get some sleep?
[Simon] Yeah.
You slept okay?
[Mario] The-the two obligations for today.
He'll say, "Kim Kardashian West,"
you'll come out.
The lights will still be on. We'll hug.
We'll go sit down.
When you sit down, um, is when
they'll dim the lights and we'll start.
Like last time,
they'll be asking questions.
[Kim] Okay, what am I gonna say,
if someone asks about the robbery?
[Mario] I'll tell 'em, to ask questions
beauty-related about what we're doing,
um, but no personal questions, obviously."
[phone chiming]
[Kim] What is this?
Security just texts me
that Scott is drunk at the hotel.
Did they stay downstairs
when we went upstairs last night?
[Simon] I couldn't even tell you.
[Stephanie] Damn, why did he do that?
She's gonna be so sad.
It's his (bleep) up.
[Kim] I have to text Kourt about this.
I think this has a lot to do
with what he thinks Kourt's up to.
And that just, like, really sucks.
[line ringing]
-[Kourtney] Hello?
-[Kim] Hey, I don't know what to say.
[Kourtney] I mean, not my problem anymore.
But you can't control people,
nor do I want to.
[Kim] I do think
it's because he heard about you
and he's like, "I took Kourtney to Aspen
and I gave her the royal treatment
and we took a jet
and we had a this and we had a this,"
and he's...
[Kourtney] It's not the point.
The trip is, like, a family trip to, like,
be able to do things with our kids.
He's, like, going, thinking
it's like he's trying to woo me back.
And I'm just like, "The timing is just
not happening right now."
[Kim] Well, he needs to know that.
[Kourtney] Like, I'm not into him
unless he proves... maybe,
I don't know, maybe I will be.
I said it's in God's hands.
[Kim] I think Kourtney can look like
she is giving mixed messages, for sure.
Usually when people are broken up,
they don't do family vacations together.
Kourtney should have been
a little bit more honest
and just say, "Look, we're not together."
Because, you know, he genuinely cares
so much and he genuinely--
like, I just feel so bad for him.
[Kourtney] Whatever. I don't care.
He doesn't need to answer to me.
I'm not, like, the sober police anymore.
But it is good for me to know,
like, what he's up to.
[Kim] Yeah.
-[Mario] You want to walk out?
-[Kim] Okay, I got to go.
-[Kourtney] Good luck.
-[Kim] Thank you. Okay, bye.
[Simon] I get it--
his drinking is all anxiety-related.
[Stephanie] That makes me so sad.
♪ ♪
[gulls calling]
[Mario] So that's for the staff,
this is for you.
-[Simon] Is this your first comeback?
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Simon] With all these people?
[Simon] How do you feel about it?
[Kim] I'm gonna be a little bit nervous
when there's the group photos.
I think of more violent things that
could happen all the time out in public.
I, like, have chills.
Like, I get nervous
about things like that.
Like, I don't know how I would ever do
a book signing again.
But then, now, this trip, it's like,
"Reality check, I have to get to work."
[Simon] The only silver lining
I see in this is the fact
that you've become so prepared.
You have a great team, you have secur...
like, it's not like it was in Paris.
[Kim] All of that's great and amazing,
but it doesn't...
it doesn't change the way
that I feel about the world now.
I live my life so publicly.
But after Paris, I just feel like,
"Is this really what I should be doing?"
[Mario] You ready?
-[Kim] Do I come out with or do I wait?
-[Mario] No, you're gonna wait here.
Then you'll hear me introduce you--
Kim Kardashian West-- and you come out.
Like, is it worth it for me to have
all this anxiety?
I mean, I just don't know
if I even want to do this anymore.
[crowd cheering]
[Kim] Do I come out with you?
[Mario] No, you're gonna wait here.
Then you'll hear me introduce you--
Kim Kardashian West-- and you come out.
[crowd cheering]
Will you tell me when he calls my name?
'Cause I can't hear.
[Mario] So, the look
that we're gonna do today--
I know you are makeup artists--
we'll incorporate all of the techniques
that I've been doing on Kim
for the past ten years.
[Kim] I'm nervous.
[Mario] ...also gonna be a makeup
that lasts really, really long.
[Kim] Whatever's meant to be will be.
If I don't make it out alive,
just tell my kids, my husband,
my family I love them.
I can never do appearances again.
It's, like, not worth it.
[inhales]
I know in my heart
that I don't want to have anxiety.
I don't want to freak out.
I don't want to be nervous
and scared and not wanting to be,
you know, out in public.
So I just got to get through this.
[Mario] So welcome Kim Kardashian West.
[crowd cheering]
[Kim] Hi, guys.
[woman] We love you, Kim!
[crowd cheering]
[Mario] Um, I'm guessing you guys want
to see something a little more dramatic.
-Am I right?
-[audience] Yes.
[Mario] Yeah, I'm gonna get started.
If you have a question, raise your hand
and we will give you the microphone.
[woman 2] Hi, Mario.
Would you recommend the round
foundation brush or the flat one?
[Mario] Whatever you're comfortable with.
Sometimes I use flat and sometimes round.
[woman 2] Thank you. And, Kim, I love you.
[Kim] Love you.
[woman 3] This is a question for Kim.
Um, what are the key areas
that you focus on,
just on a day-to-day basis?
[Kim] I would just do a little bit
of contour around my cheekbones
and my jawline and my forehead
and just a dab of concealer under my eyes.
That's, like, my go-to.
[woman 4] What's your favorite brand
of skin care?
[Kim] My favorite eye cream is,
uh, Dr. Ourian's eye cream.
[woman 5] How are you, Kim?
I love Sainty and North very much,
and I love your mama.
She's so gorgeous.
[Kim] Thank you.
I know that a lot of this fear is
in my head and I have to work through it.
I'm just like, "It's gonna be okay."
[man] Uh, my mom, she has kind of,
like, old skin, and it's kind of rubbery.
-[Mario] Rubbery skin?
-[man] No, it's kind of bouncy.
It's not rubbery but...
[Mario] It's bouncy?
[man laughs] No, like...
[Mario] So, for older ladies,
I like to use less product.
You know, for example, you'll see on Kim,
I'll use a few different layers
of concealer.
-[Kim] Older ladies?
-[Mario] Yeah.
[Kim] Wait, what you're using on Kim?
-[Mario] No, I'm saying... I'm saying...
-[Kim] Thanks.
[Mario] I would do not
what I'm doing on Kim.
[Kim] He tells me I'm so old
all the time, you guys,
-when he does my makeup.
-[woman 6] Come on.
[Mario] Because, guys,
she was a baby when I met her.
So we-we kind of grew up together.
-[Kim] I thought you were referencing me.
-[Mario] No, no.
[Kim] After a minute,
I definitely warm up,
and it's just not as tough to be out here
as I thought it would be.
I love Dubai.
We're having so much fun.
Everyone here is so nice.
I love spending time here.
It does feel like just
when I would do them before.
So I feel comfortable.
I mean, not, like, all the way safe,
but I feel comfortable.
[crowd cheering]
[Kim] Thank you, guys, so much
for coming out.
I hope you learned a lot from me.
[laughter]
No, Mario really is the best
teacher and he's, you know,
taught me everything I know
when it comes to makeup
and I'm so grateful that he's in my life.
So thank you for coming out
and experiencing this with us.
[Mario] Thank you, guys, so much!
[crowd cheering]
♪ ♪
-[Kim] Hi!
-[woman] Hi!
[Kim] I'm really glad
that I pushed myself to be here,
'cause I think the only way you could
overcome anxiety is if you face it.
Of course, I'll live my life differently
and do whatever I have to do
to make me feel safe,
but I still want to be this fun person
that I used to be.
[photographer] One, two, three.
Thank you.
[fan] Thank you. I really love you.
This is from my friends and I.
[Kim] Oh, thank you, how sweet.
♪ ♪
[Kourtney] Felicia.
Felicia. Bye, Felicia!
[Khloe] You're obsessed
with my outfit today.
I mean, seriously.
[Kourtney recorded] Felicia.
Bye, Felicia! Is my voice annoying?
[Khloe] Our voices are always annoying.
[Kourtney recorded] Bye, Felicia!
Oh, Felicia.
Can I say something to you?
I called you at midnight
because Kim texted me and was like,
"Scott is still drunk, and it's noon."
-[Khloe] Scott relapsed?
-[Kourtney] Yeah, so he drank.
Steph was writing me.
Simon was writing me, "Oh, God,
this is so sad. I can't believe it."
[Khloe] I'm so mad at him.
[Kourtney] So I called him,
and he's like, "Hello?"
And I could tell that
high-pitched voice...
-[Khloe] "Hello?"
-[Kourtney] So I go, "Oh, you relapsed?"
And he was like, "No, I'm just waking up"
or something,
-and I go, "Don't (bleep) lie to me."
-[Khloe] He's such a bad liar, too.
[Kourtney] I was like, "I've known you
for ten years. Don't lie."
And then he was like,
"Oh, I'm lying to you?
You're lying to me."
He keeps bringing up, like, my behavior...
-[Khloe] Right.
-[Kourtney] ..."your new way of life."
And I'm like, "You're not blaming me
for any of this."
[Khloe] Never accountable
for their actions.
Everything is someone else's problem.
[Kourtney] For ten years,
I was trying to be supportive
but letting him know, like,
in the meantime,
while he's showing his consistency,
like, I have to live my life
and make myself happy.
I mean, ultimately, he has to take
responsibility for his own actions.
[Khloe] Wait till I talk to Scott.
Let's go down and see our friends.
[Kourtney] P, your friends are here.
-[Penelope] I know.
-[Khloe] Hi, guys. Did you walk around?
[Travis] No, I just saw this.
[Kourtney] Our neighbor and friend,
Travis Barker, decided
to come over to Khloe's house
because his kids and mine
are good friends.
[Khloe] Did you have dance today? No?
-[Kourtney] Did you guys have school?
-[Landon] Mm, not today.
-[Khloe] Is it homeschool?
-[Landon] Yeah.
[Khloe] I did homeschool, too.
[Travis] Yeah, they have to do P.E.
three times a week, so...
[Khloe] At homeschool?
[Travis] Yeah, one of our homies
just teaches them,
-like, dance or boxing. It's pretty cool.
-[Khloe] No way, that's so cool.
[Travis] We try to wake him up
sometimes and see if he'll train with us,
but he doesn't want to.
[Kourtney] Mason loves to do the ab thing,
like, that one,
-and he loves to do, um...
-[Khloe] The push-ups.
[Kourtney] Push-ups. Yeah.
[Khloe] It's good to teach him at six
to do that.
[Kourtney] Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
[birds squawking]
[Simon] Hola.
[Stephanie] Who's ready?
[Simon] The camels are waiting.
-Hello.
-[Kim] Hey.
[Simon] How you doing?
[Scott] Hey.
[Simon] The jetlag is real.
[Kim] I have this desert adventure set up
for me and all of our friends and Scott.
And I know he's upset about Kourtney,
so I just figured we can do something fun.
[Carla] Hi, Scott.
-[Scott] Hi.
-[Carla] How are you?
[Scott] You know.
-[Stephanie] Let's hurry...
-[Simon] So we don't lose the light.
[Stephanie] We got to get the light.
Whose purse is that?
[Chris] I don't know.
[Stephanie quietly] Hey, um,
I think there's a girl here.
There's a girl's purse here.
[Kim] Girls are here? What the (bleep)?
Like, this cannot be. Something is up.
Scott is, like, pacing, and just
something came over me
that I was like, "He has a (bleep) girl
hiding somewhere, and we'll find her."
[Scott] All right, let's go!
Let's disco.
[Kim] I forgot, we forgot
to take aquarium pics.
These are the best.
Can I go down and pick a--
take a pic in the aquarium?
How do you get down?
-[Chris] It's messy down there.
-[Kim] Huh?
[Chris] A mess down there.
[Kim] I want to take a pic
in the aquarium.
♪ ♪
-We should do a Boomerang.
-[Simon] Are we doing Boomerang?
[Kim] We should do a Boomerang.
Should we take a pic in here?
Oh, look at the big stingray!
[Chris] That stingray says hi
all the time.
[Kim] Should we do, like, a cool one,
like, sitting?
[Stephanie] Yeah.
[Chris] I wouldn't go in there.
[Kim] Don't go in here? Why?
[Chris] Just don't.
[Scott whispering] There's a girl
downstairs.
-[producer] What?
-[Scott] There's a girl there.
[producer] Oh, my God.
[Scott] I'm gonna have a heart attack.
Yeah. This is gonna be really awkward.
-[Stephanie] Yeah, that's dope.
-[Simon] So dope, Kim.
[Kim] Look in the bathroom.
Go wash... go to the bathroom.
Go in the toilet.
[Simon] Oh. I have to pee badly.
[Stephanie] Go now so we don't, like,
have to wait.
[Simon] I don't know
where the bathroom is.
[Chris] There's one upstairs.
Use the one upstairs, Simon.
[Simon] This is locked.
[Stephanie] Is there another bathroom
down here?
Make sure we go because
it's a 45-minute drive, so...
[Kim] Is it cheesy that I'm taking pics
all by myself?
-[Stephanie] No.
-[Simon] No. They're Polaroids.
-[Kim] Okay.
-[Carla] Shall we?
[Kim] Should we go up this way?
[Stephanie whispers]
Scott's door's locked.
-[Carla] Kim.
-[Jen] Bathroom's locked.
[Simon] Yeah, I couldn't get in.
[Chris] She's taking the elevator.
[Kim] Yeah?
[Chris] No, Carla's halfway up the stairs.
[Kim] Or should we go
bang down the bathroom door
and see what (bleep) whore is in there?!
♪ ♪
[Kim] Or do you think we should go
bang down the bathroom door
and see what (bleep) whore is in there?!
Should we go in and scare
the (bleep) out of her?!
'Cause the bathroom's locked.
I'm not (bleep) stupid.
Should we go in there?
What the (bleep) are you doing here?
Seriously?
You're just like a (bleep) whore.
Such a tramp.
Get your (bleep)
and get the (bleep) out of here.
(bleep) groupie.
Get your (bleep), and security
will escort you the (bleep) out of here!
♪ ♪
Coming up next week...
I have to go to New York to go meet
with, like, the French judge.
Whether they catch them or not,
it just opened up my eyes.
There's bad people in this world
that do really bad things.
[Khloe] We're in Costa Rica, girl!
This is so pretty!
Yeah!
[Kim] Scott flew out a girl.
Yeah.
-[Kris] Let's cut the bull(bleep).
-[Scott] Right.
[Kris] I think what we're wondering is
if you have a girl here and why.