Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi
[ MOUSE SQUEAKS ]
[ PENGUINS CHIRP ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
[ SCREECHES ]
♪ ADVENTURE TIME ♪
♪ COME ON, GRAB YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ WE'LL GO
TO VERY DISTANT LANDS ♪
♪ WITH JAKE THE DOG
AND FINN THE HUMAN ♪
♪ THE FUN WILL NEVER END ♪
♪ IT'S ADVENTURE TIME ♪
BMO: FOOTBALL,
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
Football: I DO, BMO.
I DON'T SAY THINGS
I DON'T MEAN.
YOU LOOK VERY SMART
AND VERY HANDSOME TODAY.
OH, FOOTBALL,
THANK YOU.
I LOVE YOU
SO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU,
BMO.
RING RING.
HELLO?
FOOTBALL?
THIS IS BMO.
OH, HELLO, BMO.
WHAT A WONDERFUL SURPRISE.
WHAT'S UP?
OH, NOTHING.
JUST WANTED TO SAY
THAT I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
GOODBYE. CLICK.
CAN I
TELL YOU A SECRET?
OF COURSE, BMO.
YOU CAN TELL ME ANYTHING.
I LOVE YOU.
OH! [ GIGGLES ]
NOW YOU TELL ME A SECRET,
FOOTBALL.
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE MIRROR.
WELL, LET'S SWITCH PLACES
FOR THE DAY.
OH, BMO,
YOU'D DO THAT FOR ME?
YES, FOOTBALL.
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU.
OH, BMO.
♪♪
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANS ]
[ PANTING ]
OH!
OH! [ LAUGHS ]
SEE YOU BACK HERE TOMORROW,
FOOTBALL.
[ GASPS ]
OH! OH!
AH!
WHOO.
[ MOANING ]
♪♪
HELLO.
AND YOU ARE CARLOS,
MY BEST FRIEND SINCE COLLEGE.
[ QUACKS ]
CARLOS.
OKAY, LET'S NOT LEAVE IT SO LONG
NEXT TIME, CARLOS.
[ QUACKS ]
HMM?
JAKE,
GET OUT OF MY FRUIT, MAN!
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU'RE CUTE,
BUT YOU'RE DIRTY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ FOOTBALL GASPS ]
OHHHHH.
OOH. AH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ON THE FLOOR,
YOU BAD BABY?
YES. SHH. YES.
I UNDERSTAND.
OH, BABY,
DON'T TURN AROUND.
BUT FINN IS SAT
RIGHT OVER THERE.
HELLO,
MY NAME IS FOOTBALL.
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU,
FOOTBALL.
HOW'D YOU GET THE NAME FOOTBALL,
FOOTBALL?
BMO GAVE IT TO ME.
IS BMO
YOUR LITTLE PAPA?
[ GIGGLES ]
UH, SO WHERE DO YOU LIVE,
FOOTBALL?
THE MIRROR.
OH, YEAH?
WHAT'S IT LIKE THERE?
COLD.
EMPTY.
IT'S...LONELY.
♪♪
WEIRD.
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
♪♪
VERY WEIRD.
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
HELLO?
FOOTBALL, ARE YOU OKAY?
IT'S WEIRD IN HERE.
I'M NOT GOING BACK,
BMO.
COME CLOSER, FOOTBALL.
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
I'M NOT GOING BACK,
BMO.
I'M STAYING
ON THIS SIDE...
FOREVER.
FOOTBALL. FOOTBALL!
NO! NO!
FOOTBALL, NOOOOO!
[ GRUNTS ]
MMMYAH! YES!
SEND ANOTHER G-FRUIT
TO THE SLAUGHTER, JAKE!
YOU GOT IT.
MYAH!
[ Panting ]
FAMILY MEETING!
HMM?
[ CHUCKLES ]
SORRY, MAN.
DID SOMEBODY SAY,
"FAMILY MEETING?"
WHAT'S UP, BMO?
NO, I'M NOT BMO.
I'M FOOTBALL.
OH, YEAH.
HI, FOOTBALL.
YES. HELLO.
I'M HERE,
AND I AM FOOTBALL.
AND I WILL ALWAYS
BE FOOTBALL.
[ Voice breaking ]
BECAUSE BMO TOLD ME
TO TELL YOU
THAT HE HAS GONE AWAY FOREVER.
[ Sobbing ] BMO.
"TAKE MY PLACE, FOOTBALL,"
IS WHAT HE SAID.
IT WAS SUCH A HARD DECISION
FOR HIM TO MAKE.
[ SNIFFLES ]
HE SAYS FOR YOU GUYS
TO TREAT HER --
I MEAN, ME...
...AS NICE AS YOU TREATED HIM,
BMO.
WE ALL NEED TO STAY STRONG,
SO THE BEST THING EVERYONE
CAN DO IS FORGET ABOUT HIM.
REMEMBER, IF YOU GUYS MISS BMO,
I MISS HIM MORE.
THAT'S GREAT, BMO.
FOOTBALL.
OH, RIGHT --
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
HEY, FOOTBALL.
GRAPEFRUIT
FOR YOUR TROUBLES?
UH...[ CHUCKLES ]
OH BOY!
THANKS!
YOU SURE YOU'RE DOING OKAY,
LITTLE PAL?
MM.
LISTEN, B--
FOOTBALL.
YOU SEEM LIKE
YOU MIGHT BE FEELING, UH,
A LITTLE DONKED UP IN YOUR HEAD
OR YOUR HEART OR BOTH.
AND THAT'S OKAY.
EVERYBODY FEELS SOME TYPE OF
SOUL NAUSEA LIKE THAT SOMETIMES.
BMO:
FOOTBALL. FOOTBALL.
BMO?
I KNOW HOW TO FOLLOW YOU,
FOOTBALL.
HOW DID YOU GET
IN THE SPOON?
I FIGURED IT OUT!
I'M GOING TO GET YOU,
FOOTBALL!
DID ALL THAT
MAKE SENSE?
YEAH.
[ Panting ]
OH, MY GOSH!
[ PANTING ]
[ BMO GROANING ]
I'M GOING TO GET YOU,
FOOTBALL!
AAH!
HA! [ PANTING ]
HA-HA!
THIS IS THE WAY
IT HAS TO BE...MO.
[ PANTING ]
OH, MY GOSH!
HUP.
I'M SORRY, BMO.
[ GROWLS ]
FOOTBALL.
DON'T DO IT!
[ FOOTBALL GRUNTING, PANTING ]
AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
BMO, WHAT IS GOING ON
IN HERE?
BMO?
AAAAAAH!
BMO! AAAAAAH!
BMO, WHY!
AAAAH!
[ HUMMING ] HUH?
OW.
AAAH!
BMO:
FOOTBALL?
FOOTBALL,
I KNOW IT'S YOU.
FOOTBALL?
YAH!
♪♪
UH...
[ GROWLS ]
I'M GONNA GET YOU,
FOOTBALL!
AAAH!
[ THUD ]
AH!
Finn: ALL RIGHT, HAND OVER
THE SHILLELAGH, BMO.
Football:
NO! NO! NO!
HEY, JAKE, BMO WENT ALL HOG WILD
IN THE BATHROOM.
Jake: GROSS!
NOT LIKE THAT.
OHHH.
WHY YOU GOT TO BE
SO DESTRUCTIVE TODAY, BMO?
ARE YOU DOING ROBOT PUBERTY
OR SOMETHING?
JAKE!
JAKE, HELP ME!
ALL RIGHT, FOOTBALL,
YOU KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS.
♪♪
SOONER OR LATER, YOU'RE GOING TO
SLIP ON SOME SPAGHETTI,
AND I WILL BE WAITING
ON THAT SHINY FLOOR
TO DRAG YOU
INTO YOUR WORST NIGHTMARE.
BMO,
YOU'VE SEEN WHERE I LIVE.
YOU KNOW WHY
I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK.
BUT WE MADE
A DEAL,
AND WHERE I COME FROM --
A FACTORY --
BREAKING DEALS MEANS
YOU HAVE TO GO TO THE DIRT HOLE.
THAT'S WHERE YOU ARE GOING,
FOOTBALL,
IF YOU DON'T SWITCH PLACES
WITH ME.
NO!
YOU'RE GOING TO THE DIRT HOLE,
FOOTBALL.
DIRT HOLE!
NO!
I'M GOING
WHERE YOU WILL NEVER FIND ME.
Jake:
OH, FOOTBALL!
[ GRUNTING, PANTING ]
BMO,
WHAT THE HECK?
I AM FOOTBALL!
AND I AM SAFE
UP HERE!
COME ON, MAN,
WE'RE WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
COME BACK INSIDE.
NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO!
NO!
[ PANTING ]
♪♪
I'M SAFE UP HERE.
NO REFLECTIONS.
SAFE.
BMO: FOOTBALL.
[ GASPS ]
DIRT HOLE!
AAAAAAH!
OOH. AAH!
[ GASPS ]
FOOTBALL?
OH, BMO,
THIS PLACE.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL HERE.
ALL MY FRIENDS
ARE HERE.
[ QUACKS ]
CARLOS IS HERE.
IT'S ALL
I EVER WANTED.
HMM.
ABOUT WHAT I DID...
IT'S OKAY.
I KNOW WHY YOU DID IT.
I DIDN'T LIKE
YOUR BATHROOM MUCH, EITHER.
THERE IS NO BEAUTY
IN THE BATHROOM.
WILL YOU
STILL VISIT ME?
YES, FOOTBALL,
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU,
BMO.
[ QUACKS ]
♪♪
BMO!
YOU OKAY?
OH, FINN AND JAKE!
I AM BACK!
[ LAUGHS ] OHHHHH!
PUT THAT TRAFFIC CONE
BACK ON YOUR HEAD, YOUNG MAN.
[ Chuckling ]
YES, I'D LOVE TO!
I'VE MISSED MY TRAFFIC CONE
SO MUCH!
[ GIGGLES ]
HOORAY!
♪ COME ALONG WITH ME ♪
♪ AND THE BUTTERFLIES AND BEES ♪
THIS PARTY IS SO CRAZY!!!