Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi
[ Mouse squeaks ]
[ Penguins chirp ]
[ All cheering ]
[ Screeches ]
Adventure Time
come on, grab your friends
we'll go
to very distant lands
with Jake the dog
and Finn the human
the fun will never end
it's Adventure Time
Finn: Yee-ow!
Whoops.
And I dub thee
sir Jake the dog.
[ Ting! ]
You two now comprise
the royal guard
of the one true princess
of ooo --
that's me!
As such,
you may no longer
own property
or operate children
and must render
all treasure and wives
unto your sworn princess
within a hangman's fortnight.
[ Scoffs ]
Joke's on you, man.
We spent all our treasure
the other day --
plus,
don't even have any wives.
Wait, what?
What about lady?
Lady's my girlfriend.
Wait, but...
That was tree trunks.
Oh, yeah!
We,
the inhabitants of ooo,
owe you heroes
our very lives.
As the once powerful
and dignified Princess Bubblegum
sulked off into exile,
it fell upon you two
to save us from
the impending comet of doom
and/or from
the hideous orgalorg,
who aimed to eat
the powerful comet
and grow invincible!
And for that,
we are eternally grateful.
I know I am.
But now your bravery
is essential
to a new heroic task!
Can you guess
what it is?
Uh...
Come on. Guess!
Um...
Fight a --
fight a dragon?
Wrong!
Follow me.
[ Sighs ]
Man, this is stupid as heck.
I miss p.B.
[ Panting ]
Yeah, I guess.
Phew!
[ Sighs ]
I mean, except for
this sweet armor, though.
This armor's hot
like fire.
Nah.
The armor's stupid, too.
Dang king of ooo,
going around
like d.J. Snappy.
This is it, fellas --
the only spot in the kingdom
left unscoured
during my treasure census.
I'm afraid it'll explode
or something if I open it.
But I really think
there could --
nay, there might --
be precious treasures in there,
so I want you two
to do it.
Man, this seems like
a really bad idea.
Yeah, well, it's an order
from your princess.
Git, git, git!
Both: Hey!
[ Grunting ]
[ Thudding ]
Come on!
All right, all right!
[ Door creaks ]
All: Hello.
Old guard #1:
We are the sworn protectors
of the forbidden
inner sanctum, heh.
Uh, to proceed, you must answer
this ancient riddle.
I forgot the riddle.
That's okay.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Hey,
there's stairs back here.
I love you guys.
[ Purring ]
Old guard #2: Oh.
[ Liquid bubbling ]
Whoa!
Jake:
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sighs ]
Wait up.
It's a dragon --
a candy dragon.
Look.
He sucks the vitamins
from the roots
and transforms it
into candy juice.
And then -- and then the juice
goes in all those drains.
This -- this is the lifeblood
of the whole kingdom!
Power, defense, recreation --
this is everything!
King of ooo:
mo-mo-mo-money
it cleans, it nourishes,
and, and...
Mo-mo-money, money, money
mo-mo-mo-money, money
go on.
What are you talking about
with all this money talk?
Yeah, why are you singing
the money song?
What, you don't see it?
[ Chuckles ]
They don't see it.
Look, everyone needs juice
to live, right?
And I control
the source of the juice.
So by me charging a mere
pittance for every single drop,
I can easily quadruple
my treasure pile!
Man, if you think we're just
gonna stand here and --
although...
If this dragon thing
could pick up the pace a bit,
we could have enough
of a surplus left over
to export worldwide!
Hey! You there!
What do you think
about picking up the --
[ screeching ]
[ Crash ]
Looks like the candy kingdom
empire is finished.
But the four of us
will live like kings
till the juice runs out.
What do ya say, boys,
let's -- oh.
I wonder
where they ran off to.
Princess, princess,
princess!
Princess!
Both: Princess, princess,
princess, princess!
Oh, hey, boys!
Finn: Princess!
Skliz is really blizzed up
with the king of ooo!
He really blizzed up
all the skliz!
He blizzed it all up, man.
Yeah, well, maybe he should
unblizz it, then.
Why do I always
got to unblizz everything?
But, princess,
under the tree, there's --
there's a dragon,
and he took the juice.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, no.
This is all my fault!
Neddy.
Finn: Princess?
Princess, what is it?
[ Sighs ]
That dragon you saw,
he's my brother, neddy.
[ Both gasp ]
Wha-a-a-a-a?!
We spawned together
from the mothergum.
And now I'm all he has.
[ Squawks ]
Neddy's very sensitive.
It's not safe for him
out there.
He needs my help,
and I'll need yours.
Wuh-oh.
Aaah!
[ Clicking ]
[ Screeching ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Popping and clicking ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Screams ]
Ah!
[ Chuckles ]
Hmm?
[ Screeches ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Popping and clicking
rhythmically ]
It's pretty quiet, huh?!
[ Sobbing ]
[ Screeching ]
[ Caws ]
[ Screeches ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Sobbing continues ]
Okay, guys,
neddy's in this cave.
I know because
my bod-rod here
is calibrated
to our sister/brother bond.
Now, people frighten him,
so I'm going in alone.
If he tries to run, stop him.
I don't think we can,
he's a giant --
yup!
Thanks, guys!
[ Sighs ]
This armor...
Is driving me...Nuts!
No way!
I changed my mind.
I feel like
a fancy shield.
Or if I was like
a dangerous candlestick.
Like,
a Knight's candlestick.
You don't stretch, man.
This thing's
crampin' my crimps!
[ Grunting ]
Whoo!
Dude, I don't like that.
[ Squeals ]
Aah!
[ Whimpering ]
Neddy, you sweet weirdo.
[ Popping and clicking
rhythmically ]
[ Yawns ]
[ Snoring ]
Ooh!
Oh, no!
I just want consistency!
If the king of ooo
tries to come here again,
you have my secret permission
to stop him.
No holds barred --
moosewood stadium freestyle.
So what are you two up to now?
Eh, guarding stuff,
I guess.
Um...Hey, Bonnie?
You always act like a-a loner,
right?
But next to your brother,
you're the light of the party.
Sorry, the light of the party.
I mean, yeah.
One of the first things
I did
after making sure
neddy was safe
was to start making
the candy people.
I was formed
in the mothergum.
My mind and my gum
were in touch
with dozens of others
like a crowded womb.
I guess I miss that.
But neddy's from the same place
you're from,
and he's a wet hot dog
around everyone!
People get built different.
We don't need to figure it out,
we just need to respect it.
Maybe he likes his own company
better than I like mine.
Well, do you miss
the candy people?
Hey, babaloos.
Good thing that juice
is back on.
I was making a mint,
but -- hoo, doggy --
my candles
were starting to turn.
[ Laughs ]
Thanks, Jake.
[ Sighs ]
That's the stuff.
Hey, do you know
if I can drink this?
Like, is it like well water --
good for bathing,
but not so good for drinking?
You know what?
I'm going for it.
[ Slurps, wheezes ]
Yep. It tastes
just like you'd think.
Come along with me
and the butterflies and bees