Ice King:
[ Snoring ] Una-- [Snorts]
Unacceptable.
Mm...Un-unacceptable.
Unaccepta--
aaah! Lemons!
Whew!
[ Sighs ]
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Gunter?
Y-you having a bad dream?
Oh, my glob.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hello, Simon.
Aaaaaah-- oh, lady!
Hi.
Wait,
you don't remember me?
Oh, man. I'm so sorry.
I stalk a lot of ladies.
Were you at
shelby's barbecue?
Huh. Looks like you've
lost it all the way.
You've crossed
the valley of tears
and come out the other side
but a shadow.
Oh, thanks.
Well, all the better
for you to submit.
I like where this is going.
Don't resist.
[ Hisses ]
[ Smooches ]
Sell your spirit to the skies.
Surrender to the empress eyes.
[ Magic warbles ]
Empress, my darling!
My great eternal love!
How can I serve you?
[ Slap! ]
Bring me blood.
At once!
[ Penguins muttering ]
Alley-oop!
Weh-weenk!
[ Splat! ]
[ Laughing ] Oh, oh,
this is so sad.
Here you go, my love.
What's this?
Don't you have any human?
Humans? Well, Finn's
the only human around here.
Try a penguin.
Wenk!
Ugh.
You know, empress is
a kind of penguin,
and your name is empress.
That's kind of cool, right?
Bleh.
Tastes like cheese water.
Where's
the top-drawer stuff?
Oh, uh, don't be like that,
honey-poo.
I'll fix it.
I'll do anything for you.
Bring me the blood
of Finn!
Okay.
[ Whooshing ]
[ Laughs ] Oh, look.
I've gotten to my bit.
"Today I met a super-pretty
cyclops lady with fangs.
She told me to eat
a fat boulder, and I did it."
Ha!
I'd forgotten that one.
[ Laughs ]
[ Groans ]
The empress!
[ Pat! Pat! ]
Vampiyah,
I'm gonna kick yah
I'm gonna lick yah
Vampiyah --
[ snap! ]
[ Gasps ] Aah!
[ Creak! ]
[ Shatter! ]
Uh-oh.
It's pb's outside clock!
[ Footsteps approach ]
[ Creak! ]
[ Yawns ] Ahh.
You did a tremendous job
guarding the cabin, Jake.
But it looks like
you need to be relieved.
Yeah, I need relief.
Pb still working on
new vampire-busting gear?
Yeah,
but she's almost done.
No sign of Marceline,
though.
I think she ditched us to
fight the vampires by herself.
Solo-style.
We'll go look for her after
pb's device is up and running.
So, how did you
pass the time?
Patted my laps
and made some rhymes.
Stoop, stoop,
sittin' on the stoop
stoop, stoop,
is that pb's outside clock?
Stoop, stoop,
sittin' on the stoop
looks like
it's been staked.
Stoop, stoop,
sittin' on the stoop
what did you do?
stoop awww.
I heard a loud snap,
and my vampire-hunting
reflexes kicked in!
Dude, that was her
Uncle gumbald's outside clock.
Yeeegh! She doesn't have
to know I broke the clock.
Let's blame it on
the vampires!
Or we can hide it!
Whoo!
Problem solved?
Yeah?
WhOoop!
[ Door closes ]
Echoed voice: Snap!
Aaah! What was that?!
Vampiyah!
Aah! Aah! Hyah! Hah!
Snap, snap,
snapping branches for fun
oh, ho, ho,
this is riveting.
"The empress is so nice.
Today she let me Polish
her boots with my tongue.
That's almost like
kissing, right?"
Hey!
Who's my hunny bunny?!
Simon!
Marceline!
What has she done to you?
[ Rustle! Rustle! ]
Did she bite you?!
Hey, calm down.
You're destroying the mood.
I'm trying to get her
to bite me later.
Minion!
Honestly, I'm standing
right here
as you collude against me
with my sworn enemy.
It's a bit rude.
Sorry.
Eh!
Stake!
[ Yoink! ]
Yeah!
Finn?
I got your back,
Marceline!
Hwah!
Huh? Ow.
How dare you stake
my back?
I was aiming for
your heart!
Ice King,
bind the interlopers in ice.
Heh.
[ Magic warbles ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Finn and Marceline screaming ]
Let's keep it down, huh?
My baby's resting.
Aaaaaah! No way!
Waaaaaaah!
Shush!
[ Magic warbles ]
Simon, you have to resist
the empress!
But she's a woman.
Aha! Ohh.
She's a vampire!
I hunt vampires
because of you!
Because of me?
how my life was without you
[ echoing ] I thought my life
was through
I could barely
stay on my feet
and I couldn't find much
to eat
every so often,
I'd make a sad tone
because I felt so, so alone
I missed you by my side
I was so lost
without you as my guide
then one day, I thought
I saw you from far away
but it wasn't you when
he turned around to say
hello to the little girl
running up to him
also to his wife
the day was getting dim
I wanted to get close,
and to talk to the couple
then I saw a vampire
about to cause them trouble
I destroyed the vampire enemy,
but I'd scared away the family
[ both screaming ]
Mem-mem-memories
mem-mem-mem memories
mem-mem-mem-mem memories
mem-memories
staking vampires,
protecting
the last remaining humans,
it felt like I was
protecting you.
It was the only thing
that brought me happiness
during those years.
Oh, Marceline!
[ Crying ]
Simon?
A-are you remembering?
[ Sobbing ]
[ Cackles ]
Pa-chazz!
[ Clunk! ]
Shmowzow.
Please, Simon!
Remember our history!
Our what now?
[ Cries ]
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, Marceline.
I heard everything.
I was invisible.
All your tiresome
mortal emotions,
they'll all be over soon.
Minion, I order you
to kill Marceline.
Whaaa? No way.
She's my pal!
Are you disobeying me?
Hey, it's called
real talking.
1,000 years later
and you still can't get
anything right, can you?
Here's our chance!
[ Smash! ]
Ice King: Please, baby,
don't say that.
[ Smash! ]
Yes!
You're my thrall.
I am enthralled by you!
You distract
the empress.
[ Whooping ]
Squeeze!
Yaaaah!
[ Magic warbles ]
Ha!
No!
Heuk!
[ Ice crackling ]
Drat.
Aaaaaaaah!
You got this comin'.
No!
Simon,
what are you doing?
Let me go!
If you want to hurt my lady,
you'll have to go through me!
Uuuuuugh!
Now, oaf! Kill her!
Sweetie, there's no need
to raise your voice.
What?!
Okay, that's it.
Turn and look at me.
Oh!
Are we gonna gaze into
each other's eyes again?
[ Slithers ]
You must fall deeper
under my spell.
Sell your spirit to the skies.
I can see myself
in your pupils.
Hee-hee.
You're not even hypnotized.
At all.
Them gigantic
sparkly orbs of yours
could hypnotize
an earclops.
[ Ting! ]
So, you're not.
Eh-heh, no.
You stupid donkey.
[ Hiss! ]
B-but honey, wh-why you
being so mean to me?
Because you're too thick
to even fall under my spell.
And you got no class.
Oh, so you're doing that?
You're gonna start
name-calling?
You want to play
the blame game?!
Okay!
Well, if you weren't
so perfect
and -- and pretty...
And statuesque and...And --
come on, Simon.
It's over.
[ Whimpers ]
It's gonna be okay, man.
Nope, nope.
This way. This way.
Come on. Let's get you
some ice cream.
That's the last time you're
gonna toy with his heart.
Psht!
If you really cared about him,
why'd you let him degenerate
into this pathetic
clown character?
He used to have more of
a silver-fox thing going on,
with his hair
and those cute glasses.
He was happier then,
you know.
When he was serving me.
Aaaaaaah!
[ Shatter! ]
Dang, girl.
Aaah!
Aah! [ Hisses ]
Gah!
Open those peepers!
Eat a stake!
[ Hisses ]
Huhn...No!
[ Laughs ]
[ Magic warbles ]
Ugh!
I don't understand this.
Marceline!
Yeah, you're welcome!
[ Stab! ]
Hunh...
[ Poof! ]
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Echoed laugh ]
Um...Marceline?
[ Sighs ] All right.
I shouldn't have tried to
go it alone with the vamps.
From now on,
we'll do this team-up style.
Okay, team.
You're still invisible.
Oh! Heh...Whoops.
Oh!
Hm.
[ Splat! ]
this party is so crazy!
Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi