Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi
[ Mouse squeaks ]
[ Penguins chirp ]
[ All cheering ]
[ Screeches ]
Adventure Time
come on, grab your friends
we'll go
to very distant lands
with Jake the dog
and Finn the human
the fun will never end
it's Adventure Time
Root Beer Guy: Fearlessly,
Captain Root Beer Guy
charges across the battlefield.
The ancient sleeper raises
his power staff to attack.
With one lever pull, captain
Root Beer Guy saves the --
Root Beer Guy!
[ Exhales sharply ]
One day at a time.
[ Purring ]
Okay, loafy,
just a second.
[ Water running ]
Hmm?
Hello?
[ Gasps ]
Root Beer Guy?
Nope. Starchy.
You do this
every morning.
I know.
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm trying, but I can't stop
thinking about him.
Look, we've been married
two months already.
I love you,
baby,
but isn't there an expiration
date to this grieving thing?
I don't think
it works that way.
Starchy, dear,
could you feed the cat later?
I've got to
prep a witness tonight.
Anything for
my cherry cream soda
and her sweet,
little kitty cat.
[ Hisses ]
Oh!
I'll win your heart someday,
loafy.
We can't all be
a cute, little character
with a cute,
little straw
sticking out of our cute,
little head.
But take some advice
from an old grave digger, huh?
Maybe it's time to do something
with that.
Here's a thought --
I could bury this for you.
An unmarked grave
kind of thing.
Just -- sswt! --
Toss him in there with whoever.
Well, that's --
that seems macabre.
But sweet.
I'll think about it.
Okay, okay.
[ Smooches ]
See you tonight.
Looks like
it's gonna rain.
Don't forget your umbrella,
Starchy.
Ooh, thanks.
Maybe I'll take my hoe
in case things get sloppy.
Well,
bye again.
Bye.
[ Wind whistling ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Humming ]
You two are married.
[ Wind whistling ]
Goodbye, Root Beer Guy.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
[ Pop! ]
Good morning,
husband.
wife.
Shaving your 'stache?
Uh-huh.
Aaaaahhhh!
Starchy!
What? What?
[ Both screaming ]
Blazes mazes!
What is going on?
I saw him.
He was right outside.
Who?
Finn? Jake?
Candy person number 22?
Maybe I can still
catch him...
Hi, sweetie.
I was dead,
but I came back to life.
That was
really something.
Hmm.
It's okay, baby.
Starchy's here.
Oh,
thank heavens.
It was just
another hallucina-a-tion.
Honey, I'm fairly upset
that you remarried.
But how
is this possible?
You were zapped by Darren
the ancient sleeper.
Your dome
was cracked.
Your root beer
soaked into the ground.
I buried your remains in a Mason
jar, which is now your head.
And...And --
and now I'm with Starchy.
I mean,
we're -- we're legally married.
You're legally dead.
Not that I want to sound
obsessed with legalities,
but I am
a lawyer.
Hey, where's that little statue
I got you?
It said, "I wuv you,"
on the base of it.
It was a little bear
with his arms out like this.
[ Clatter ]
He was all, "I wuv you,
I wuv you, I wuv you."
[ Crash ]
No sudden moves, baby.
He's got freaky zombie strength.
Maybe it's up here.
[ Grunts ]
Did you hire a maid service
or something while I was gone?
I sure hope they didn't
throw out the "I wuv you" bear.
Enough!
I should have put you
in the ground a long time ago!
Hey,
I came back for her.
[ Popping ]
Root Beer Guy, if that is you
in there, I'm so proud of you.
But this
isn't fair.
You ended our life together
when you pulled that lever.
You made the choice,
and you saved the kingdom.
But you lost me.
Heh. Burn.
Cherry cream soda,
I still wuv you -- whoa!
[ Popping ]
You always wanted this wall
knocked down anyway, right?
[ Chuckles ] Ooh.
Oooh! Wah!
You come back
with no explanation,
wreck up the place,
and you expect to just
pick up where we left off?
Get out
of my house!
I'm sorry.
Starchy wins!
[ Laughter ]
Jake:
That's funny.
I can't believe you used to
be married to such a freak.
He isn't a freak.
Or he didn't used to be.
[ Sighs ]
Shh, shh,
shh, shh.
Don't worry,
honey.
Don't touch me now,
please.
I need time
to think.
Look, baby.
Starchy knows
all the fresh widows in town,
and Starchy chose you.
Starchy wuvs you.
It's time to dig a hole.
I thought she'd be happy to
see me, but it was disaster.
I didn't know
where to pick up with her,
so of course
I just acted like a goof.
Oh, and now
I'm one of the undead, I guess.
Hey, man, there's absolutely
nothing wrong with you.
[ Speaking Korean ]
[ Sighs ]
She's got a point, though.
I was the one who wanted
to be the big hero,
and I got
my wish.
But I didn't think
about her enough.
I'm not even
thinking about her right now.
Yes, you are.
I am?
Run back
and tell her
all the stuff
you've been telling us.
Maybe you could pick up from
a place you haven't been yet.
I don't know what that means,
but it sounds very encouraging!
See you guys later.
He didn't bite you,
did he?
Cherry cream soda!
I've had a revelation
of some kind.
No dirt-heads allowed.
Uh, but I have to talk
to cherry cream soda.
Oh, no you don't.
Nuh-uh.
I'm trying
to be polite.
[ Clang! ]
Oh, dear.
Hmm.
Pardon me!
It's on, zombie.
What the heck?
You have met your match,
freaky dirt guy!
Woo-woo-woo-woo!
Look, will you
give me a break?
Too chicken, huh?
Look, I'll put the shovels down.
See? Hah!
This is childish.
[ Knock on door ]
Ha!
Get away
from my head!
Ho-ho!
We have
some unfinished business.
Wait for me,
little dirt beer!
Ooh, is somebody afraid
of old Starchy?
I'm afraid
of killing you.
Oh, boo-hoo.
Don't hurt me!
Ugh. Is it not possible
to get away from you?
I'm escorting you
to your new home --
far away
from my house.
It's not even
your house.
Ha!
It's practically mine.
Tonight,
you'll sleep in a hole --
the same dirty grave hole
from whence you sprang!
I'm not usually violent,
but you pushed me.
Nah.
What's this?
Okay,
now we're talking.
Poke me with a shovel now,
you mustache face.
Aw.
Stop it,
both of you.
Neither of you thought
to ask me what i want.
I've made a decision
who I want to be with.
[ Wind whistling ]
I don't want to be with
either of you.
What?!
You're a maniac.
I can't believe
I ever got that low.
Hmm!
Starchy doesn't need this.
And you.
I don't know you anymore.
Okay.
Take care of yourself.
I said "I don't know you,"
but I'd like to.
Would you like
to go on a date?
Yee!
[ Clears throat ]
I mean, yes.
This is weird, right?
Well, we've never
actually dated before.
We got married
so fast.
Let's take it slow
this time around.
One date
at a time.
Come along with me
and the butterflies and bees