Hey, Cinnamon Bun.
Hi. I'm here
on diplomatic business.
Yeah, the princess
is expecting you.
Cinnamon Bun, welcome!
On behalf of the Fire Kingdom,
here's the get-well card
for Hot Dog Princess.
Please pass it along
to the next princess
after you've signed.
Understood.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
I'm here!
Hey, Finn!
What's up,
my main cinna-man!
Please deliver this card
to the Slime Kingdom.
Will do, PB.
CB, keep up that smile.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Sit down, CB.
Let's catch up.
Uh...
I guess I can chat
for a few seconds.
It seems like living
in the Fire Kingdom
is doing you a lot of good.
Oh, I like it there a lot.
I have an important job.
I have a wolf.
There's no other candy people,
so that's weird.
Hmm.
Well, it was nice catching up.
Okay. Bye.
Oh, CB!
You forgot your keys!
Hey, look who we have here!
Hey, guys.
Chet, you still make
those awesome nachos?
You know it.
Crunchy, still chewing
that same piece of gum?
Yep!
You still acting like
a big goofball all the time?
Ha! I was a different guy
back then.
Heh...
Very different.
Everyone watch!
I'm gonna do a flip!
Whoa-oh-oh!
Oh! Oh, no!
Yi-yi-yi!
But now life is great.
It can't be easy for him,
living alone somewhere
so different than home.
Princess?
Where are you?
Oh, hold on.
Almost done.
I want to show you
my newest creation.
I call her Bun Bun.
Hi! I'm Bun Bun!
Hey!
Is she like
a little Cinnamon Bun clone?
I grew her
from old CB experiments,
so... maybe more like
a third cousin?
Your mission is to take Bun Bun
to the Fire Kingdom.
Yay!
I made you a new fire suit.
Bun Bun doesn't need one
since I engineered her
to be fireproof.
So, how does it feel
to be alive?
Um, it feels good, I think.
What's the opposite of good?
Bad. That's funny
that you don't know that word
but you know
the word "opposite."
What was that?
Hm. I must be hungry.
Hun-gry?
Trail mix
will fix this grumbling.
Here.
Have some.
Like this?
You're funny, Bun Bun.
Huh?
Bun Bun, chipmunks
are eating your trail mix.
What are chipmunks?!
Look!
I made friends!
Bun Bun, you're all right.
I'm all right!
Hey, Finn.
Make way for the princess!
Finn?
What brings you here?
Special delivery
for Cinnamon Bun.
Who's this?
I'm Bun Bun.
Are you a chipmunk?
No.
Bubblegum made her
from your spare parts.
She's supposed to be your squire
or whatever.
My... squire?
Hmm.
Bun Bun, we'll have to run you
through some security checks.
Okee!
Turn around.
Jump back.
Jump forward.
Reach for the sky.
Reach!
She's clean.
Go have fun
with your new friend, CB.
Come, squire!
I'll show you
our beautiful palace.
All right, then.
See ya.
Finn, wait. You don't have to
just run off like that.
We can hang out
if you've got time.
Really?
I have a light schedule today.
Hi! I'm Bun Bun!
Hiya! I'm Bun Bun!
This is the statue
of the third Flame king.
Ooh, but that statue
over there is bigger!
Yah! Yah! Yah!
Careful, Bun Bun!
Whoops.
Bun Bun!
Look!
I'm king of the fireplace!
Behave yourself, Bun Bun!
Okay! I'm-a run this way now!
I love you!
Um...
She's new.
Is something wrong
with your coals?
No, they're fine.
It's just...
When we broke up, I said sorry,
but I didn't fully understand
exactly what I did wrong.
I get it now.
I shouldn't
have manipulated you.
That was a really, really
messed-up thing to do,
and I'm truly sorry.
You've grown up a lot, man.
I forgive you.
Awesome.
Bun Bun.
Bun... Bun Bun.
Ooh, what's in there?
That's where we keep
the evil former king.
Yeah, we're not supposed
to go in.
Bun Bun!
Hi, fire man.
You look sad.
I don't get sad.
I'm evil!
I'm just bored
of this intense loneliness.
You want some mush?
Um...
Who are you?
Bun Bun.
Do you like dogs?
Sure, I like dogs.
Not those stupid tiny ones,
though.
I like them medium-sized.
Oh! I like dogs!
We're friends!
But I just met you.
First I'll need to know
exactly how evil you are.
I'm 100% evil.
What's evil?
Now, what you're doing
is really good.
Trying to make friends
with the old king and all.
But there's one
very, very important thing
that you need to promise me.
Yes.
You see that button over there?
Whatever you do...
Button!
Well done, Bun Bun!
Now to the hills
to regroup my forces!
Ha ha!
I'm free!
Oh, my Glob.
Free!
Free is good, right?
No, this is bad!
We have to catch him.
Catch!
Oh!
The Ice King!
Shelby.
Princess Bubblegum!
Okay.
Who am I?
Pbht!
I practiced that one.
So, what else you been up to?
I started freestyle rapping.
What?!
Everyone says I'm good,
but I can't tell
if they're just flattering me
'cause I'm king.
Right.
Fire man!
Shh!
This is serious!
Want to see me do a flip?
Wow.
Ohh-aaaah!
Bun Bun!
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
On to plotting
our diabolical scheme.
Bun Bun, I hear the Flame King!
So, wearing your fire costumes,
you'll pose
as a basket of orphans
left on the castle doorstep.
They'll take you in.
And when they bring you
to the king,
you bust out the water guns
and seize control!
Any questions?
Are these your kids?
They're my army.
Your plan's not gonna work.
I know.
I'm rusty at this war stuff.
You should do chipmunk stuff.
Is that what I am now?
The chipmunk king?!
Uh... I don't know.
Perhaps you're right.
I have no allies left
in the Fire Kingdom.
And even if I did manage
to steal it back,
I'd probably have to redecorate
the whole castle.
Maybe I could stay here
and rule.
Figurehead-style.
And I'll be
the royal dog petter!
Would you really stay here
with me
and my kingdom
of adorable vermin?
Okay.
You're all right, Bun Bun.
All hail the chipmunk king!
Bun Bun,
you're gonna do great here.
'Cause you're brilliant.
Thanks for helping me out.
Finn the human,
he wears a bear hat
Someday he'll be old and fat
Unless he is immortal
or a turtle
'Cause turtles always look old
- Ohh!
Turtles got told by me, Phoebe
Pure gold
Guess who's back,
it's Cinnamon Bun
Bun Bun told me
how to have fun again
Also, she let out the old king
What?!
It's okay.
He's a in a chipmunk cave.
It's nice.
See?
Aww.
Did Bun Bun draw that?
No.
We can't just let him
run around though, right?
How do we know he won't moidle
all those chipmunks?
No, he always did like animals.
I wonder if a new environment
might help bring out
that softer side of him.
Being stuck in a lamp
sure won't do it.
Let's leave him be.
"Dear Cinnamon Bun,
I have a dog now."
His name is Cinnamon Bun.
"Love, Bun Bun."
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!