Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi
[ marceline humming ]
Knock, knock.
Yo, peebs, you want to make
a midnight squeez-e-mart run?
I'm gonna drink
the red
from out the customers'
bloodshot eyes.
[ Chuckles ] Psych.
I'll probably
just get a slushie.
Bubblegum?
Bonnibel!
Wha...?
[ Screams ]
Aaaaaaah
ugh!
What are you doing here!?
Be not afraid, child.
It is I --
the one true princess of ooo!
Where's bubblegum?!
[ Chuckles ]
Whoa! Relax!
Bubblegum is fine --
just fine.
And deposed --
and powerless!
So crushed by defeat
was she
that the tyrant exiled herself
to a sad cabin
on the shores
of lake butterscotch --
technically, still
candy kingdom territory.
But in my mercy,
I've allowed her to remain.
You're the princess?!
Since when?
Well, by the reckoning of
my "new torontian calendar" --
ooo's
official calendar --
uh, two glorious months.
Two months?
But -- but, then,
why didn't she t--
[ growls ]
Bubblegum!
Tell bubblegum
I wear her nightgown!
Tell everyone!
[ whistling ]
Huh?
Bonnie!
Marceline.
What up?
Ugh. Why didn't you tell me
you got throne-jacked?!
I gotta hear it
from that wax fraud!
[ Shotgun cocks ]
Peppermint Butler:
Be cool, marceline.
Let's all be real cool.
Give us a minute,
peppermint Butler.
Hmm!
Hup, hup, hup, hup...
Well?
I didn't get jacked.
I quit.
But yeah, all right,
I should've told you.
I was just [Sighs]
embarrassed.
And it all happened
so fast.
I'm still trying
to sort things out,
see things rationally.
Huh.
Well, you could have
talked to me about it.
[ Scoffs ] Yeah, 'cause
you're so dang rational.
Ha ha.
I'm sorry.
That's mean.
I'm trying
to be less mean.
That's why
I'm starting fresh
with a new kingdom
out here --
just me, pep but,
some pretty stars.
Ugh. And, of course,
some varmints.
Varmints?
Varmints!
Raiding my pumpkin patch
every dang night!
After all my sweet
bio-engineering?
The nerve
of these varmints.
Not tonight!
[ Whistles ]
So, how long
you gonna sit out here for?
Long as it takes.
[ Shotgun cocks ]
Uh, all right, yeah.
Let's get
these varmints.
Um...Yeah.
Pbbbb,
pbht-pbht-pbht-pbht,
pbht, pbht, pbht,
pbht-pbht-pbht.
These must be
pretty good pumpkins, huh?
They're citizens
of my garden kingdom --
100% loyal
garden citizens.
[ Chuckles ]
That reminds me --
so I was in the grocery kingdom
last Sunday,
'cause free samples,
you know.
They had these, like,
shrimp cocktail dealies.
So good!
I was sucking
the sauce off them
and hucking the shrimp
at the ceiling.
I kept going back
for more and more samples.
I could not
stop myself.
I don't know, man.
The shrimp must have
gone bad or something,
'cause all that red
came right back up.
Still invisible and yakking red
all down the produce aisle.
It was awesome.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, you remember
that one time --
[ rustling ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Shotgun cocks ]
Hey!
[ Growls ]
[ Snarls ]
Varmints!
After them!
Varmint hole!
Aw, nuh-unh!
A ding dang
varmint hole.
I can't believe
my sweeps didn't find it.
Well,
you found it now.
So, what next?
[ Muffled ]
Next? We dig.
Hmm.
This looks like
a delivery tunnel
from the old
rock-candy mines.
Huh! We haven't been down here
in hundreds of years.
Remember
when I'd get you out
of those stinky cheese kingdom
trade meetings
and we'd sneak down here
and spray-paint the walls?
Um, I am pretty sure
it was me who found you
vandalizing my property.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, but I got you
to tag something, didn't I?
I bet
I could find it.
Here. Come on.
We used to follow
the mine car rails,
cracking jokes,
telling stories.
Whoa!
The broken bridge!
Remember?
You jumped across this!
[ Chuckling ]
You were so scared.
Mm, I think I was just trying
to prove something.
Bonnibel bubblegum --
always so prepared.
Yeah, I have to be
"always so prepared."
We can't all
just "wing it."
I didn't have to
always worry
about so many things,
you know?
The candy kingdom used to be
so small, so manageable.
But then it kept growing
and growing,
and there was
always some new disaster
to prepare against.
Is...That why
you stopped talking to me?
No, I...
[ Creature growling ]
[ Growls ]
[ Hisses ]
Bring it,
ya dern pumpkin munchers!
[ Snarling ]
It's a freakin'
mother varmint!
Ugh!
[ All screech ]
Marcy, cover me!
No problem.
Yaaaaaaaah!
[ Guns click ]
Psh!
Uaaaaaaaaaagh!
[ Rumbling ]
Gah!
[ Gurgling ]
Yah!
Ew!
Marceline! Look out!
Huh? Unh!
Ugh!
Marcy!
[ Gasping ]
[ Growls ]
Ugh!
She's going to bring
the whole tunnel down!
[ Hissing ]
Yeesh!
My snap-back!
Marceline: In there!
[ Click ]
[ Screams ]
You got
any more gadgets?
Um...
Some bandages, a pen,
unpaid Internet bill,
and...
A strawberry lip balm.
[ Slurps ]
Ahh.
Maybe we can find
something useful around --
ohhhh!
Your tag!
We actually found it.
Man, your handwriting
hasn't changed at all.
[ Chuckles ]
Still as prissy
and prim as --
what?
[ Sobs ]
Hey, hey!
Whoa. Wait.
I didn't mean...
I like your handwriting.
I think it's...
Really pretty.
It's -- it's not that.
I lost my hat.
We can...
Get you another hat.
I lost my hat,
lost my home, lost my people.
I can't even keep dern varmints
out of my pumpkin patch!
Oh, Bonnie, you're...
I tried.
I really, really tried.
I just -- I thought
that if I shut everything out
and just focused on work,
it would all be okay.
[ Rumbling ]
But look
where that landed me.
All I managed to do
was push everyone away.
I pushed you away.
I'm sorry, marceline.
I've been a real dinger
to you.
Come on.
What are you
even apologizing for?
[ Rumbling ]
Unh!
Oof!
Uh...How about
we not get buried
under a metric ton
of rock-candy rubble?
[ Gasps ]
The field generator!
[ Varmints snarling ]
Aw, geez!
Okay, uh, maybe I can rig up
a graffiti bomb
or a rudimentary
rock-candy Cannon or -- or...
What?
This time,
I'm prepared.
[ Hisses ]
I've been watching these dudes
pretty close.
I think I can varmint-style
dig us through the wall.
It's just a shame
about your tag.
I don't want
to mess it up.
Naw.
It's good, I think.
Mess it up.
Dig, dig, dig, dig!
[ All hissing ]
Yo! Varmints!
Ya hungry?!
I'll eat you!
I'll eat your mom!
I'll eat your eggs!
I'll --
whoop!
[ Roars ]
Thanks.
[ Slurps ]
Boing!
I'm crazy-tired,
marceline.
I think I have been
for a long time.
[ Sighs ]
But those varmints
are still out there, waiting.
Eh, worry about it
tomorrow.
I'll keep a lookout
tonight.
I will watch the heck
out of this pumpkin patch.
Come on.
[ Yawning ]
Well, okay.
Maybe for a bit.
Don't let me sleep
too long.
Promise to wake me up
in 15 minutes.
I promise.
[ Snoring ]
Peppermint Butler:
Uh...Can I come back now?
Come along with me
and the butterflies and bees