Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi
[ panting ]
Marceline, nOoooo!
Don't let anyone
read my diaries!
Burn them, Finn!
They're embarrassi--
[ screaming ]
And then he said,
"fine."
That's the story
of how I met your dad.
Can I play now?
No, Marceline,
sweetie.
It's nap time.
But I don't want
to sleep.
My dreams are weird.
All dreams are weird.
But, mom,
my dreams we-e-e-ird.
[ Chuckles ]
Honey, something weird might
just be something familiar
viewed
from a different angle.
And that's not scary,
right?
Let's go in the garden
you'll find something
waiting
both:  right there
where you left it
flying upside down
when you finally find it
you'll see how it's faded
the underside is lighter
when you turn it around
everything stays
right where you left it
Simon: Hello, Marci.
I don't know if you'll ever
hear this message.
I fear my thoughts
are no longer my own.
Just watch over me
until I can find my way out
of this labyrinth in my brain
and regain my sanity.
And then maybe,
Betty, my princess --
maybe you will love me again.
[ Sighs ]
Please love me again, Betty!
[ Sobbing ]
Okay, bye.
[ Camera shatters ]
[ Sighs ]
Hey, Simon.
I, uh, finished
packing your gear.
So, can I have
my tape now?
What? No.
This is private,
silly.
There you go.
Snug as a bug.
Seriously, Simon.
Please don't go.
I-I have to
protect you.
How can you protect me
if you're not even here?
I'll arrange for someone
to come take care of you.
I'll make sure
he doesn't leave.
Please, Simon,
I could help you with this.
Yeah.
Maybe one day you will.
But until then, you have to stay
brave, my fearless Marceline.
Ouch!
You see?
I have to go now.
Goodbye, Marci.
Wait! No! Wait!
Ohh!
Simon!
[ Wind howling ]
[ Growls ]
[ Panting ]
Gah, ew.
[ Laughing maniacally ]
Okay,
I know you're here.
[ Laughing continues ]
Peek-a-pop!
[ Laughs ]
The fool!
You found me,
Marceline!
Now you're it.
We're not playing, fool.
You're an evil,
blood-sucking fiend.
I'm trying
to kill you.
Hey, you want to see
something funny?
[ Inhales deeply ]
I look like a butt.
Pbht!
Ohh!
[ Laughs ]
[ Coughing ]
Huh?
[ Sniffs ]
[ Laughing maniacally ]
Oh. Cool.
Sweet music to my ears.
[ Bass plays ]
Come on, little bun.
Just turn around.
Ugh, stupid animal.
Wha?!
Oh!
I'm sorry!
All right,
hold still.
There you go.
See? It's okay.
[ Screaming ]
No, kid!
You don't have to
be afraid of me!
I'm a really good...
Person.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys,
guys, guys, guys,
guys, guys, guys!
Huh? Huh?
There's...Ohh, hoo...
A vampire!
No! No!
Yes way.
I saw it real close.
It looked like a girl,
but it had fangs like...
[ Grumbling ]
Everybody,
ready your weapons.
Don't worry.
We'll be ready for it.
[ Bird squawking ]
Ohh!
[ Gasps ]
Hey.
[ All gasp ]
No, no, I-it's cool.
I'm on your side.
[ Whimpers ]
Go away, vampire.
I'm in the sunlight.
I'm not a flipping vampire!
[ All screaming ]
[ Sighs ]
Mm? Mm?
What's that?
Oh, you want old two bread tom
to play the song.
Please do not
play the song.
No,
the child is right.
As humans, it's our duty
to tell the tales,
to sing the songs.
Art must survive.
Streaks on the China
never mattered before
who cares?
When you drop-kicked
your jacket
as you came through the door
no one glared
but sometimes
things get turned around
and no one's spared
all hands, look out below
there's a change
in the status quo-o-o
gonna need all the help
that we can get
[ coughs ]
[ Growls ]
[ Imitates guitar ]
You want me
to play more?
Two bread tom:
Yes, please.
The consensus is that
your cover's better.
According to our new arrival
life is more
than mere survival
and we just might
live the good life yet
[ bass playing ]
Hmm?
Oh, man, schwabl,
I sure hope there ain't
a little vampire kid
sneaking up behind me.
Vampire attack!
Oh, no!
Ugh! I'm dead.
[ Spits ]
This is serious,
Marceline.
What if I was a vampire?
You need
an animal hat.
Looks like the project's
coming along, huh?
[ Foghorn blares ]
Waaaah!
[ Marceline whistles ]
Hey, Marceline!
Marceline!
Two bread tom,
how's it going, man?
Oh, so good.
I had a hoagie for lunch.
And even better, the ship's
repairs are almost done.
We should be ready to sail
in another day or two.
Oh, that's really great.
But listen,
I've cleared out
almost all the vampires
that are left.
In another week or two,
you won't even have to leave.
Yeah, Marceline!
Oh, Marci,
you're such a sweet weird kid.
But it's not just the vampires
or the oozers
or them hungry-looking
rainbows.
The latest atmospheric readings
are going bananas.
Something big is coming.
And it's gonna change
all of this.
No, we'd do best to clear out
of this continent altogether.
Hey,
you should come, too.
After all,
you're one of us.
[ Bell clanking ]
They're here!
Aah!
He's biting my hat!
Get to the boat!
[ Vampires grumbling ]
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, geez.
That's not schwabl, man.
[ Laughs evilly ]
Well, you got me.
What gave it away?
The boots?
Aah!
Marceline!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hi, there, hierophant!
Why can't you just let us
eat humans?
You're, like, messing up
the natural order.
This is our time.
It's my time.
And once I stake and gank
your shape-shifting power,
I'll be unstoppable.
Ha!
[ Gasps ]
What?!
[ Laughs ]
I picked up self-healing power
last month,
off some vamp with a head
like a garden trowel.
So, you've slain
sister moon.
Look at you.
You're just
a hapa demon punk,
blind to the price you must pay
for such powers.
[ As Dracula ]
Blah! I don't care!
Fine.
Ah! Show yourself!
Okay.
Wah-wah.
[ Gulps ]
[ Laughs evilly ]
Ka-ching!
[ Gasps ]
Oh, geez.
Hey, Marceline,
let me "ax" you something.
[ Laughs ]
You get it?
You have to leave, tom.
Oh, I didn't think
it was that bad.
You have to leave now!
Aah.
He's here.
He's the worst of them all --
the vampire king.
[ Screaming ]
What?
Marceline, you're not dead!
Whoo!
P.B.'S cure.
It must have worked!
No soy vampire.
Also, untie me, please.
I'm not a murderer!
Okay, but wait,
if she's not a vampire,
then what's been draining
our cows?
[ Groans ]
Aah!
Finn?
Geez.
I hope Finn
didn't get blood-sucked
after I stress-fainted.
Who the heck is this?
[ Mellow music plays ]
[ Hisses ]
this party's so crazy!