Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi
there! Right there.
Do you see?
Uh, yeah.
It's a small...Thing?
Hey, do you have
any bigger chairs?
-Stools.
-Huh?
They're stools,
not chairs.
Well, can I have
a bigger stool?
Jake!
Stop interrupting!
Sorry.
Enhance!
-Huh? Hey!
-Whoa, whoa, hey!
-Whoa.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Looks like a mushroom.
Is someone throwing mushrooms?
Yes, very good!
It is a mushroom,
or a toadstool.
That's why
you're sitting on stools.
-Oh.
See? You guys
got to trust me, okay?
I picked those stools
for a reason.
Trust my process.
You can get up now.
[ Back cracks ]
My legs.
No.
Nobody's throwing mushrooms.
I believe they're flying
on their own.
That's where you two come in.
Okay, the flying mushroom
came from that direction,
so I want you two to head
that way until you find one --
a big one.
And I want you to capture it
and bring it back.
-Why?
-Huh?
-Trust my process.
Okay, but why, though?
Yeah, we're curious.
I want to ride it around
instead of walking.
I think people
will respect me more.
Hey! Hey, you,
what's your name?
I'm dirt beer guy.
What would you think
if you saw me
on a giant,
flying mushroom?
Boy, that'd really be somethin'.
See? Don't fail
on this one, boys.
Don't you dare fail me.
Actually, I'm kind of glad
we're walking
in this direction.
We never walk
Hey, how long do you think
capturing
a flying mushroom takes?
Well, we got
to find one first.
Yeah, that too.
How long?
Hmm.
An hour to capture, and
if we don't find one by dinner,
we'll tell koo to send out
a banana guard patrol.
Tell who?
Koo.
-King of Ooo?
-Yeah.
-[ Laughs ]
Did you notice
he was wearing
Princess Bubblegum's clothes?
Yeah, that was sort of cool,
but, you know,
pb just left her kingdom
to him and all her stuff,
so what's that about?
Hmm.
[ Sniffing ]
I smell mushrooms.
yeah, good job, Jake!
Check it out -- big enough
for koo's tiny heinie.
Yeah. The only thing, though,
is it's not flying.
Hmm. Yeah.
I guess we can just sit here
and wait for it to fly?
Canyon:  I know
you are looking for a sea
-you hear that?
-Yeah.
That lies beyond your reach
it's pretty.
But I'm hoping my heart
can stop you
you want to go check it out?
Mm, yeah.
I know you have places to go,
I know that you want the sea
but I'm hoping my heart
will grow
and that you'll come back
to me
oh, geez.
Looks like some sort of
old glob ritual.
We should sneak away.
We don't want to disturb.
-Finn?
-Canyon?
-Jake!
Finn?
I mean, canyon?
Billy's ex!
How are ya?
Sorry we interrupted
your sacred ritual.
Oh, no, I was just
procrastinating.
What are you guys doing?
We're on an official mission
for the princess.
Nothing!
Cool!
That's really cool.
What are you doing, canyon?
Oh, I'm using
this dowsing rod
to find my family's
lost sacred spring.
-Cool!
-Whoa!
You guys want to help?
-Uh...
-Yeah!
Wait, Jake, what about --
dude, have you ever taken a sip
from a sacred spring?
It's the boo boo best.
Plus, you know
I've always wanted to learn
how to use a dowsing rod.
Mm, okay.
All right!
Canyon: There you go.
Just hold it
like you would a butterfly.
You got it?
-Yeah.
Whoa.
It's going nuts!
It works!
[ Ping! Ping! ]
King of Ooo: Finn? Jake?
You boys there?
Uh, hey, what's up, koo?
-What?
-I mean, king of Ooo.
What's up?
-Princess king of Ooo.
Just checking in
on your progress.
Have you found a flying mushroom
big enough to sit on?
Have you captured it?
-Uh...
Psst! Jake!
King of Ooo:
What's going on?
Who's that saying "psst"?
Oh, look at that!
Yes. That's right.
Finn!
Tame that wild beast.
I don't want it
bucking me off now. Yes.
See you soon, boys.
[ Laughter ]
-That was dope!
That's who's running
the candy kingdom now?
What a tool.
-Mm.
-What's the matter, dude?
I don't know, man.
We're disobeying royal orders.
Is that bad, maybe?
Koo probs will forget about
this whole mushroom thing
in a day or two.
And if you don't
like your job,
it might be time
to find a new one.
Hmm.
Huh?
Whoa! What the --
it's some kind
of mega-mush.
Ha! Cool!
Mega-mush!
Mega-mush! Mega-mush!
Whoa.
Calm down, buddy.
This is a fake mush.
See?
Whoop!
Whoa!
In here!
What the donk, man?
Hmm. Those looked like
spore-dispersing blasts.
I'd say
a bunch of mushrooms
joined into a next-level
flying super-organism.
They're gonna rule
the school.
I'm just guessing, though,
but it sounds plausible,
right?
What you think
it tastes like?
[ Blows raspberry ]
Tra-a-a-apped.
Maybe we can wait
him out.
Hey, yeah!
Maybe it's already gone!
Boop!
Looks like the co--
yeah, no,
he's still out there.
[ Sighs ]
I'm gonna go out there
and talk to it.
Maybe it can be reasoned with.
This could just be
a big mush-understanding.
[ Laughs ]
Hey, buddy.
Whoa, whoa.
Times! I call times!
We're sorry about earlier.
We goofed up.
There's no way
our fake mushroom
could come close
to your level of...Beauty.
It's true.
You're stunning.
Oh, glob, no!
U-uh...
I mean --
I am an excellent source
of vitamin b,
copper, and zinc!
Uh, congrats?
Yeek!
Hey, now!
That was poor sportsmans--
whoa!
Mid-joke?
You monster.
If you combine me with yeast
and ferment me,
I'll form a healthy tea
called kombucha.
The health benefi--
aah!
[ Battle cries ]
Yah!
[ Panting ]
-Shing!
-Hyup!
Finn: Mushroom chop!
Whoa! Ugh!
The health benefits
of kombucha
have not been confirmed
by scientific research.
We're learning a lot
about mushrooms today.
Ugh.
They're in my sinuses.
Yoink.
In fact, drinking kombucha
has been linked in rare cases
to serious side effects.
[ Gasps ] Ugh.
[ Coughing ]
That was dumb.
[ All coughing ]
Canyon, your dowsing rod!
Dude.
The sacred spring.
Mushrooms are gentle.
To clean me, wipe me
with a damp paper towel.
-[ Grunts ]
-Whoa!
Hyaaaahhh!
Yahhhhh!
Canyon, you're so cool.
My chromophores
can be used
to dye wool
and other natural --
[ kaboom! ]
Farewell, mega-mush.
May we meet again
in your next incarnation.
[ Laughs ] Cute.
This was fun, canyon.
[ Laughs ] Yep.
I found the sacred spring,
and we exterminated
the flying mushroom infestation.
Mission complete.
[ Laughs ] Yeah.
Oh. Hmm.
That wasn't actually
our mission.
King of Ooo: All right,
boys, let's see it.
Fair princess of Ooo,
we were unable to procure
a flying mushroom,
so instead, may we present
an advanced mushroom pizza!
[ Gasps ]
It's not as you ordered,
my liege...
But this pizza can probably fly
if you believe hard enough.
Ooh!
A delightful pizza-ah!
Well, then,
you two are...Fired!
-What??
-Whaaaaat?
You have defied the order
of your princess.
Henceforth, you are banished
from my royal guard.
We don't even like you --
hup-hup-hup.
Spare me your groveling.
You're fired.
Shoo, shoo.
Ooh!
Hmm.
Hmmmm.
Yeeees!
I can feel it working!
Banana guards!
Hup, hup, hup, hup.
Give me a push!
-Yahhhh!
I'm flyyyy--
[ thud ]
Eeeh. Wha--
[ gasps ]
Uh.
Uh, uh...?
Mama?
[ Coughs ]
Mama said
there'd be days like this
there'd be days like this,
mama said
mama said, mama said
there'd be days like this
there'd be days like this,
my mama said
mama said, mama said
come along with me
and the butterflies and bees