[ Chattering ]
[ Owls hoot ]
[ Blink! ]
[ Swords scrape ]
[ Screeches ]
Adventure Time
come on, grab your friends
we're going
to a very distant land
with Finn and Jake
and Marceline
and Princess Bubblegum
it's Adventure Time
hey this is nuts, right?
Look, I've got
both my teeth!
Look!
I lost one in
a box turtle once.
Also, I used to be dead.
Ah!
Mmf! Mm mm!
Mmm!!
Mmwah!!
Pwah!
[ Poink! ]
Fool, this is life.
Get a hot dog if you
can't take the bun.
Pah! It tastes
different here!
Where are we?
It's like we fell asleep
on a raft
and woke up in strange seas.
Humph!
Fell asleep?
We died.
The demon Marceline
staked us all.
Why are we back?
How did it happen?
Listen -- I dunno know
and I don't care.
We're alive
and I'm going to get eating!
Ugh.
Aaah...
Does anyone have any milk
for this?
Do you, like, carry milk?
Moo!
Moo?
This is well and good
for you, hierophant.
All you ever needed was a forest
and something hot to chew on.
[ Gnawing and snorting ]
Where are the comforts
of the old hive?
The minions...
The blood...
The good blood, with
the gold leaf flaked into it.
The gold leaf was stupid.
It didn't taste like
anything.
We had standards!
It doesn't matter
when we are
or where we are because --
we are.
We must start rebuilding
our realm.
There's life here
and I bet it's pathetic.
[ Humming ]
We march in, we take control,
and we rebuild the hive!
My king,
are you listening?
The fool: I dunno.
Like...
[ Yawns ]
What if we just got
a loft downtown?
[ Warble! ]
Whoops, I'm hypnotized.
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh!
[ Splat! ]
[ Pop! ]
[ Laughs ]
Good old "backwards egg!"
[ Vampire king humming ]
Ugh. Ugh!
I don't like to dance.
I'm a wallflower.
Oh! Ugh!
Hierophant: My king...
Surely you agree
that this is our chance
to go back to our old ways.
Surely diverging from
the old ways
is what made us vulnerable
the first time!
Surely -- whoaaaa!
Surely?!
[ Grunting ]
Surely?
Surely j. Temple!
Oh!
[ Gasp! ]
I am your king,
and say it's a new era!
Old-fashioned ideas
have no place here.
[ Growls ]
Do what you like!
I knowwhat's right!
[ Rumble! ]
If you are going to caterwaul
like this,
then I may as well
start building my army.
Hasta luego, turds.
[ Zip! ]
[ Bubble! Bubble! Bubble! ]
[ Humming ]
Oh, getting' dizzy...
[ Gasping for breath ]
You sure the sun's
not hurting you at all?
No, this is great.
I can even feel
my skin aging.
[ Gasping and panting ]
Huff! Cow...
Teeth and...
Shirley temple...
Aaaaaaah!
I ran into some vampires!
They were being weird as crabs!
Do you know these oily doilies,
Marceline?
What?! No!
I'm cured!
[ Sighs ]
It is weird though that
it's happening at about
the same time I got
un-gunked.
I gotta go see Bonnie.
[ Grunts ] Ow!
Oh yeah,
guess I'm walkin'.
No mo' powers.
Didn't your daddy
give you demon powers?
My dad never gave me squat!
Well, just some
soul-sucking skills.
Remember this?
[ Hissing ]
Aah! My soul!
[ Chuckles ]
Ugh,
even though I got
my soul sucked,
I'll still give you a ride
to Bonnie's...
[ Creak! ]
...because I'm good.
Bonnie, I don't get it.
Jake's talking about vamps
at the same time you fixed me,
and there can't be any
still around!
Well, clearly something's
creeping around.
Okay, what about the paste
you took out of me?
That should be all that's left
that's vampiric
in the modern world.
It's all over there,
safely in the safety bucket.
What?!
Pep but, what'd you do
with the gunk?!
Hold on, I'm working.
Okay. There was one
that looked like
if a baby-snake
was a baby-baby.
[ Scribble! ]
Nah, that's not right.
There was another one
that looked like
if an ant hill
were a girl.
[ Scribble! ]
Nah, that's not right.
There's one of them that
looked like a wet Uncle.
[ Scribble! ]
Nah, that's not right.
There was a lady who looked like
black drapes on a cake pop.
[ Scribble! ]
Nah, that's not right.
There was also one that
looked like an angry stop sign
coming out of
a loaf of bread.
[ Scribble! ]
Nah, that's not -- oh, actually
that one's pretty close.
What?!
[ Gasps ]
Vampire king: You can stop this
now, Marceline,
it's not too late.
You've got power now.
I see it.
But you haven't paid a price.
It's making you crazy.
Marceline,
there's no one left but me.
Would you wipe out
an entire species?
For the last time, yes!
That is literally
my entire plan!
So be it then.
Uh...Duh.
[ Grunts ]
I gave you a chance, Marcel--
blah, blah, blah, blah!
[ Thud! ]
[ Both grunting ]
[ Both growling ]
[ Slam! ]
[ All gasp ]
You know, Marceline,
there's still another way.
Give it a rest already!
No another 'nother way...
To save my people.
[ Shing! ]
Wait!
[ Grunting ]
[ Slurping ]
NOooo!
[ Gasps, screams ]
This is really bad.
These guys...
They're heavy hitters.
If they get back
to full strength,
they'll tear this world
apart.
What's the plan, Marceline?
How do we fight them?
Peppermint Butler:
[ Exaggeratedly clears throat ]
If I may...
[ Thud! ]
Strong enough for
an ultravampire...
But made for a vampire.
All: Wow.
Look, Jake,
a two-pronged stake...
And a stake boomerang.
Yes, and what's this
behind your ear?
[ Gasp ]
A super garlic bomb!
Bubblegum:
What the heck, peps?
Why do you have all this
vampire junk lying around?
I have these high-tech weapons
painstakingly stockpiled
in case a certain
frenemy of yours
decides to turn on us someday.
Peps!
No no, he's right.
I could've snapped
and done you all in at any time.
[ Shudder! ]
Ugh!
The cave is totally empty.
No sign of anyone.
Phew!
Nothing going on
out here either.
Maybe we should all fan out --
look for tracks.
Or clues.
All right,
but everyone be careful.
Even in their mushy state, these
guys'll crack up ya sacrum.
Jake: Gross.
Don't worry about
us, Marceline.
Yeah, we're ready
for anything.
[ Squeak! Squeak! ]
[ Laughs nervously ]
[ Sniffs ]
Can't smell nuthin' no more.
[ Thwack! ]
Ugh! Ahh.
[ Ping! ]
Crud.
[ Shatter! ]
Whoops.
[ Jake and Finn coughing ]
Oh no, my bomb!
[ Slip! Splash! ]
[ Dry heaving ]
Hey guys, why don't y'all
head back to the cabin?
I'm gonna try to put together
a profile, you know...
Forensically.
Okay, Marceline,
sounds good.
Come on, boys,
let's get you cleaned up.
I know you're in there,
you skunk.
You butt. You stain.
You --
[ creak! ]
Hey.
Long time no see.
[ Creak! ]
Indeed.
Hey! Marceline!
Look at me!
I'm all grown up now!
I ate a chicken,
Marceline.
I see you're getting
your strength back.
Yes, not long now.
Well don't get
your hopes up.
Pbht! Pbht!
Things are different now.
The humans are long gone.
[ Sniffs ]
Someone's smelling a bit human
herself these days.
Anyway, you don't need to worry,
I've changed, as well.
I only eat animals now,
just like everyone else.
Ugh. Huh?
Does that mean we can be
friends now, Marceline?
It doesn't matter how
you pretend to change.
[ Gasps ]
You've done enough already
to get staked
a thousand times over.
You're monsters.
You'll always be --
smell my feet, Marceline.
I promise you won't
regret it.
[ Poink! ]
Oooh!
Ohhhh...
Your loss.
[ Poof! ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Echoed laugh ]
You know, the others
won't be so easy, Marceline.
Well how 'bout you?
It doesn't have to be
like this.
Those are some pretty
frou-frou last words.
[ Zip! ]
[ Grunts ]
You've lost a step!
I'm not even gonna
need my powers.
I'm surprised, Marceline.
[ Sighs ] What now?
Surprised you have the time
to play around
while the empress makes her way
to the land of ice and snow.
[ Zoom! ]
Simon. Crud!
[ Grunts ]
[ Door opens, closes ]
[ Growls ]
[ Sproing! ]
[ Whoosh! ]
[ Splat! ]
Fixed & Synced by MoUsTaFa ZaKi