January, 2021.
On the year of their tenth anniversary,
this group made a new start.
Hello everyone.
Hello!
Seriously?
Oh, hello.
Sexy Zone.
We all said, "We'll do it"
and gave the okay.
Each one of us wanted to find
a new side to ourselves
that we haven't seen before.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
In 2011,
with an average age of 14,4,
they became the youngest group
to debut from Johnny's.
They appeared on Kohaku
six years in a row from 2013.
In 2018, they were chosen
as the main personality
for 24HOUR TELEVISION.
After that, their mood maker,
Matsushima, went on medical hiatus.
Okay, this time it's for keeps!
Roll it!
Since then,
the remaining four continued working,
wishing for Matsushima's return.
This is when it was made.
The song that seemed
to show their hearts.
NOTHING CAN START WITHOUT YOU
RAISE OUR JOINED HANDS HIGH
DON'T STOP, DON'T STOP
WE'VE ONLY JUST BEGUN
You know,
this song also includes
our feelings for So, right?
"Nothing can start without you."
It's a song with a message
to connect to his hope.
This could be that bridge-building song.
2020 AUGUST
The one who returned was...
Matsushima, after a year and nine months.
And then...
Let's just have fun.
-Okay!
-Yeah! Let's go!
Yeah!
-Woo!
-Thirty seconds.
Their concert was postponed
due to the pandemic,
but after eight months,
it became an online concert,
with no audience present.
However...
Is this position alright?
Should I stand here?
Crouch a bit.
In December of last year,
Marius Yo, due to poor health,
announced he would take
a temporary leave from show business.
Okay!
-Okay!
-Thank you!
Then in 2021,
the four bandmates made a new start.
SEXY ZONE
FUMA KIKUCHI (25)
We are in a rough shape.
But...
So came back after his break.
It sort of starts now.
This is where the hard work begins.
How can I put it? I feel like...
there was more I could have done.
I do feel responsible.
But...
even in this state,
I can't just be negative.
So is back after all.
It's our tenth anniversary as well.
On behalf of Marius who is on a break,
we should probably try to
have as much fun as we can.
In this moment,
how much can we enjoy this work?
I think that's what's important.
January 8.
Each with their own feelings,
they took a new step forward.
The choreography for the lead song
from their new album, "SZ10TH."
Hand in front.
And your face...
Face to the side.
It's the same as at the start?
It's the same.
Yes, that's it.
The choreography was made by
a team with global recognition.
With this song, they look to the future.
You need to be aware of stopping
for 0,02 seconds or it doesn't work.
Right now, you're like this.
You need to stop here.
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
Okay, sorry.
Stop just for a moment.
One, two, three, four.
Try it with the music.
Tyrant!
I'm so tired.
Some parts are tricky,
so go over them on your own.
The parts where you're like,
"Oh, that wasn't good."
Go over those and do your best.
-Okay.
-Great.
It's about mental state.
Above all, those who are supporting us,
like all our fans...
When I think about how they feel,
I don't have time to stop right now.
There were times
when the group seemed like
it would stop over the past ten years.
But my motto has always been
"Never stop moving forward."
The bandmates are
working hard with me.
The one who is on a little break is too.
Everyone has their own life to live.
So we're all just trying to do our best.
Then came the filming of the music video.
There's not a single word of Japanese
in this whole song.
In fact, when we chose this song,
they were like,
"This'll be quite a challenge."
"Do you really want to do it?"
But we all said, "We'll do it"
and gave the okay.
Each one of us wanted to find
a new side to ourselves
that we haven't seen before.
That was pretty deep, right?
That was pretty deep.
Like any group, we have to
always be changing.
We have to always be doing something new.
Making our dance that precise
is also something new.
As a beginning for Sexy Zone's challenge,
I think it's a really good start.
It's their first time making
a dance number with all English lyrics.
Bam, bam.
I can't tell the difference.
Oh, here.
-You can tell when they leave.
-The white is a little clearer.
The colors aren't too clear.
It's hard to tell the difference
between us and the four dancers.
We should change it a bit more.
Will this work?
They change their outfits,
and shoot it again.
Okay, that's good.
Did we do it?
Let's use this.
We did it.
Above all, it's just fun.
That's the best part.
They're having fun too.
They're lively.
Well, Marius is the one
who's good at English.
I can't beat Marius.
Even though I'm trying so hard.
I can't win.
I'm defeated.
Defeated by Marius.
Leading up to their tenth anniversary,
this song shows a new side of them.
2021 JANUARY 23
Then on this day,
they did something for the fans
during the pandemic.
Hello. One and a half minutes left.
One minute thirty seconds.
Okay.
Five seconds. Four, three, two...
Here we are. Good evening, everyone.
We're Sexy Zone! Yay!
Welcome to the first
Sexy Zone Online Meeting.
Today, we are online,
reading your comments.
We see them.
Here on these pads.
-Wow.
-Pads...
On these pads.
-We'll see them there.
-Wow, there are so many.
"Shori is the only winner."
"Shori is a genius."
They're all about you.
-They're all you.
-Sorry, I'm so self-centered.
During the livestream,
comments from fans flooded in.
This project was made from
the ideas of the members.
Last year, in September,
a meeting was held
for the tenth-anniversary album.
We should use the five-member "RUN."
Just for "RUN," I see.
These four were the ones
that presented the song
and it also really signifies
how they protected Sexy Zone.
So I think it's better
if we don't put it on the album.
Oh.
It could be...
I thought it could be like
a record of that time.
I understand.
For the fans, collection-wise,
I think we should
start from the beginning.
I think it's important to reflect back
on all the songs.
It might be like creating a concert.
I think...
We could have fans vote for everything.
Yeah, an album made by the fans.
It seems right for the tenth anniversary.
There are a lot of good tracks
from the Sexy Zone B-sides.
That's ten years' worth
of songs to choose from.
Social distance.
As much as possible.
Definitely, right?
So we don't make trouble.
Each with their own ideas,
they planned the anniversary album.
Announcing the results after
fans voted on the songs
was the purpose of this fan meeting.
FOURTH PLACE
"WITH YOU"
That was a good one.
I was surprised this was fourth.
I thought it might be first.
After all, it was before
we performed "Sexy Zone"...
Yeah, I remember Shori
like this at the start.
Stop!
-Let me explain. It was choreographed.
-Like you were forced.
If I stood like this,
I looked even thinner.
I think Sanche said,
"You, stand like this."
-Oh, that's why.
-"Be more powerful."
It wasn't just me. So too.
Yeah, So was like this.
I did! How do you remember?
Sanche's grip was so strong though.
-Like this. Weren't they strong?
-I remember.
-"Like this?"
-"No."
"You go like this!"
"And Shori, you do this!"
"Yes, sir!"
Rather than ten years of nothing,
we have so much to talk about
from the past ten years.
I think that's a wonderful thing.
I feel like the last ten years
have been very rich.
They began running towards their dream
for their tenth anniversary.
Happy New Year.
January.
Their tenth-anniversary challenge.
The rules will change
depending on the city.
I think we'll try for 50%.
Their wish was...
a concert tour with a live audience.
It's our tenth anniversary.
We want to be able to say thank you.
Right?
So we're all thinking about
how we can do this.
We're all in it together.
They can't see what lies ahead,
but they do it for their patient fans.
In a Sexy Zone concert,
we always have lasers, right?
We could do it a new way.
If we're showing each of us off...
If we prepare too much
and can't use it all,
we should give the lasers
their own place to shine.
Which is better?
Like a monument or...
And the question of where.
MAGAZINE "TV STATION" PHOTO SHOOT
Sexy Zone.
The future they look forward to.
Sexy Zone...
is a group that can turn
a crisis into an opportunity.
Those words really fit the five of us.
Despite the pandemic,
our motivation hasn't changed.
We're always thinking about what we can do
to give the fans a good time at concerts.
But it's really thanks to
the strength of our fans
that we've also been able to stay strong.
We really do support each other.
For the amount of support
they've given us these ten years,
we need to thank them properly.
By returning it in some way,
and continue to support them too.
I always say it, but
"Our hearts are close."
We want excitement as well.
We were about 14 years old
when we debuted.
Even though ten years have passed,
we're still in our twenties.
So compared to
other groups and our seniors,
I feel like our ten years
have been different.
Everyone has an incredible desire.
Of course we do. We're in our twenties.
We should be just getting started.
I want to make it a special anniversary...
I want to make a tenth anniversary
that suits us, and I think we can.
Yeah.
Sexy Zone has to get more popular.
We still have so much strong competition.
We have to beat them.
If we don't, there's no point.
Can we keep on being Japan's
Sexy Zone for another ten years?
I want to work on being Japan's Sexy Zone.
On our 30th anniversary,
we'll still be in our forties.
Everyone.
Alright, then let's say 25 years.
On our 25th anniversary,
me and Nakajima will be just over forty.
Some will be in their thirties.
That's it.
I'll accept world fame
on our 25th anniversary.
The world's Sexy Zone
-It's perfect.
-Okay.
Okay.
That's it for the dance.
Sexy Zone.
They're off to capture
a yet-unseen future.
Yay!
On the next RIDE ON TIME...
V6 embraces their 25th anniversary
since their debut.
Idol? Am I still considered an idol?
What do we do from now?
Who are we living for?
Each with their own beliefs,
they take on a new challenge.
We've started, so now we have to do it.
I don't know if I was crazy
or just sucked-in.
Could I have been alone?
What do they see as they look ahead?
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka