Anything interesting so far?
How long is the show?
Four 30-minute episodes.
-Four episodes?
-That long?
Two hours?!
-Nothing'll happen.
-Yeah.
There won't be any incidents.
It's so peaceful.
-Should we fight?
-Okay.
Hey, you!
-Not young enough to fight.
-Boring, right?
Nothing.
There must be something.
No, we've already done all that
in the last 25 years.
How long are you gonna stay?
Until November 1.
Oh, nothing will happen.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
1995 NOVEMBER 1 DEBUT
"WA NI NATTE ODOROU"
"AI NANDA"
"IT'S MY LIFE" MUSIC VIDEO FILMING
V6 celebrated their 25th anniversary
last year.
Normally,
the six of them work independently.
These three have been
bringing the group together.
The older three are known
by the nickname of Tonisen.
You mean that I'm ordinary?
The oldest member of the group,
Masayuki Sakamoto.
He's nine years older
than the youngest member.
He is highly acclaimed
as a musical actor, too.
V6 HIROSHI NAGANO (48)
While being active as a stage actor,
Hiroshi Nagano is a licensed cook.
He always watches over
the other members quietly.
Oh, this one!
Yoshihiko Inohara is known
as an actor and a TV show host.
V6 YOSHIHIKO INOHARA (44)
I'll teach you a lesson. Hey, you!
Not him! It's him!
Oh, him! You...!
Ouch!
Ow, ow! Somebody! Please help!
In October...
V6 decided to have a livestream show
at the same venue as their debut concert
for their 25th anniversary,
and started rehearsing.
I feel like I just went swimming.
Your hands are getting a bit slow.
Slow? Okay.
INOHARA ASSEMBLED THE MEMBERS
Let's talk in private, just the six of us.
It's about a new song which is
exclusively for their fan club.
For the project for our fan club,
we're asking KREVA to write us a song now.
I worked with him in a movie last year,
and I'm personally really close to him,
but I didn't ask him.
We wanted someone from our generation
to write it, so Avex and Okada talked
and KREVA was the only candidate.
I talked to KREVA.
He said he wanted our ideas and keywords,
so I said we'd give him that.
This is the first time the six of us
are communicating with a songwriter.
I wanted to do something new.
I thought we'd better do it,
just the six of us.
Inohara met the members
who'd share the same fate with him
and debuted when he was 19.
His age was right in the middle.
He brought the group together
by serving as a bridge
between the old and the young.
What... What are you rubbing?
I don't know. Something round.
-He's not watching. He won't join us.
-Jeez, he won't join us.
Nice. I like this group.
You sometimes see someone
creating a good atmosphere.
I think I have to be like that.
Because many others
are taking serious roles.
Okay. Thank you.
Inohara had something he wasn't good at
for a while after he debuted.
Hi, everyone!
Um, I'm Inocchi.
Today's the last day...
So make good memories.
Mr. Johnny told us that
our banter was boring many times.
It was just the worst.
I really didn't want to do it.
I didn't want to do it
and he would talk about other groups.
Like, "KinKi is so entertaining!"
I said, "Well, that's because
they're a duo."
"Being a duo is hard, too."
"There are six of you
and you're that boring?"
I was frustrated.
When it wasn't successful,
it was really bad.
I could tell, "Oh, it wasn't fun."
-They don't even wear a fake smile?
-Yeah.
FILMING
He now hosts a long-running TV program.
Well, the program...
I know it's going to be edited...
But there's nothing special...
-Are you worried about RIDE ON TIME?
-Yes.
Thank you.
But it's a nice location to film at.
That drawing on the wall of
that Toyoko Inn changes periodically.
Goro always says
long-established stores and restaurants
keep changing themselves
little by little but quite boldly.
And Adomachi,
you'll see it when you're the host.
Like, "Shouldn't we do that thing?"
"No, not anymore."
They get rid of things just like that.
-Like things they've been doing?
-Yeah, sometimes they just stop.
They'd do something new or
go back to the old thing, they're quite...
They're quite flexible.
The show has been running
for 25 years. Just like us.
Both us and the show have been dealing
with problems that occur on the spot.
When I film three episodes in a row,
I've got to eat something.
I'll eat!
Fifteen minutes to go.
Hello.
-I'm Inohara. Hello.
-Oh, hello.
For the livestream concert,
the challenge of mastering a dance
they'd never done before began.
Performing their song
without vocals. Just by dance.
Awesome. So cool.
-Thank you.
The problem is if I can memorize it.
-Yoshie.
-Yes?
Do you think we can do it?
Definitely.
-Let's try our best.
-Yes, let's go.
It's a rare opportunity
to show off your skills.
Yes, thank you.
One, two, three, four!
Seven, eight!
Move! Five, six, seven, eight!
Nice!
Let's do the fast arm movement.
One and three. Four, five, and six...
So fast!
Nice!
Yeah, that's it. Yes.
Okay, let's do it one more time.
Nagano was working on it quietly.
Is your back okay?
-It's fine.
-Healed?
I'm not sure, but I can move normally now.
The arm movement at the end looked hard.
-That's hard, right?
-It is.
-It's super fast.
-It's hard.
If you think, you'll be left behind.
Like, if I do this,
you'll dodge it this way.
Just like that, I have to train it
like muscle memory. Yeah.
"Wait for You" from the top.
Nagano joined the agency when he was 13,
and even before V6 debuted, he was active
in TV drama series and so on.
He became the first to play a hero
in a tokusatsu series in the agency
and became popular among children.
1996 ULTRAMAN TIGA
He got a cooking license,
and qualifications
to be a vegetable sommelier.
He published three books about food.
The ingredients in his recipes are
detailed down to their nutritional value,
which shows his personality.
What made you get qualified
to be a vegetable sommelier?
Well, I've always had an interest in food
for quite a long time,
and I didn't have much work to do.
I wasn't busy at all.
I was thinking,
"Is there anything I can do?"
So I went, "Okay, let's just get them"
and that's it.
I know I'm greedy,
but I want to do various things.
Acting, too, of course.
V6 is basically my foundation.
Because of V6, I got work
and I think it's the same even now.
My attitude towards work
is always the same.
I want to value every work that I get.
Even on this day...
You'll see how amino acids work
and why you need them.
You'll go, "This is what'll happen.
That's why I need them."
Hmm... So it's better take them?
Yeah, you should take amino acids.
They can't be produced in your body.
Okay. You can get them from food, right?
Yeah, getting them from food
is the easiest.
Can I still call myself an idol?
I'm not sure.
What? You're an idol.
Idol? Am I still considered an idol?
Am I still an idol?
The one who kept on practicing
the dance performance
was the oldest member, Sakamoto.
I may look young on the outside,
but what's inside is
definitely 49 years old.
-You can't hide it?
-Not anymore.
Let's do it with music. Play "TL."
The rehearsal for
the dance performance was nearing its end.
It was the most out of sync today.
The most out of sync today?
One more time.
Okay, you're now quite in sync.
All right. Let's do it one last time.
Good. I couldn't take my eyes off of you.
Oh, it's tough today.
Sakamoto had a knee surgery two years ago
and hasn't fully recovered yet,
but he was engaged in
their 25th-anniversary activities.
Since the beginning of the rehearsals...
And go...
That's it.
One, two!
-Damn.
-Are you okay?
My knee hurts.
-Does it hurt?
-Please don't push yourself.
I'm not young anymore!
I'm an old man.
Sakamoto joined the agency when he was 16.
But he felt anxious about his future,
and became a corporate employee
before he turned 20.
But he ran into someone by accident.
So I'm commuting to work, and by chance,
I run into KinKi Kids on the train,
both of them.
They asked me,
"What are you doing now, Sakamoto?"
and I couldn't answer.
Maybe I felt embarrassed
and frustrated and miserable.
-You couldn't say it proudly?
-No, I couldn't. No.
Then, whenever I turned on the TV,
everyone was on it.
More than feeling frustrated,
I wanted to go back.
Then, when he was 24,
he debuted as a member of V6.
He had to lead the younger members,
but there was one thing he wasn't good at.
They were cute.
Yeah, they were.
-I watched them like a parent.
-I know.
That was TV-show filming.
It's been 25 years, so you may say,
"What are you talking about?"
but I still can't get used to TV cameras,
and I get nervous.
So like I said, I still get nervous.
But when I'm onstage...
I don't get nervous.
PLAY "OSLO" REHEARSAL
He has focused mainly on musicals
and has had many experiences.
I don't know.
Stop pretending and tell me.
No, really, I don't even have a clue.
What are you saying...
Before I knew it, I was like...
I felt so free and relaxed.
I couldn't afford to miss that.
And I was heading toward it
without thinking.
I don't ever wanna stop doing musicals.
-Ever?
-Yeah.
Hey.
Every day after work,
he goes straight home
to his dog who is waiting for him.
I sound lonely, right?
I talk to my dog all the time.
-They listen to you.
-Yeah, they really do.
She goes like "Hm?"
So I go, "You know..."
Hello.
Yes.
Do I wear the coat for this one?
Last year, Inohara teamed up with someone
much younger than him from his agency.
In the movie, he played a father
who makes bento lunches every day.
His son was played by...
Shunsuke Michieda
from Naniwa Danshi, 18 years old.
Hello.
Could you two share
bittersweet childhood memories?
Oh, do you have something?
What? Yes, I do.
When I was in the fifth grade,
I got a chance to sit next to my crush.
And while I was sitting there...
During the filming, they made a rule.
When we exchanged contact information,
he told me to talk to him like a friend.
One day, I messaged him
in honorific language,
he took the trouble
to fix it into casual language,
and even added a smiling face,
and sent it back to me.
Then he wrote, "I won't get mad,
so don't worry."
I thought, "Who would say that
to someone who's 26 years younger?
He's so awesome."
If I get to meet someone younger
from my agency and work together,
I want to do the same for them.
-Paying it forward.
-Yeah.
-Just the two of us first, right?
Mr. Yoshihiko Inohara
and Mr. Shunsuke Michieda!
The next episode...
How about wearing
the jacket at some point?
Or just do without it.
Without changing.
-No change?
-No change.
It'll work if the quality is high.
They talk over and over about the show.
This isn't enough.
To be blunt, I've seen this before.
What they have on their mind
will be revealed.
Subtitle translation by: Tsuyoshi Koide