Sexy Zone is here! Thank you for coming!
SEPTEMBER 10
MAKUHARI MESSE
September 10,
after one year and nine months,
Sexy Zone performed with all five members.
I can't.
-You can.
-I'm nervous.
We look backstage. Also...
There was a time when
there were just three of us.
If that hadn't happened,
I don't think I could be here now.
I wouldn't be able to be here now.
The bonds between the bandmates.
Their history is about to be revealed.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Of all the Johnny's groups
they debuted at the youngest age,
Sexy Zone.
This August...
Yay!
Woo!
It's So!
So Matsushima, who was on medical hiatus,
returned after one year and nine months.
Two weeks after that...
AUGUST 26
Please don't stop
Don't stop
Yes.
They began rehearsals to prepare
for the five-man show.
-Can I try once more?
-Of course.
Step forward...
This was in fact,
two hours before the others arrived.
-I want to stop this anxiety.
-I get it.
If I can stop it...
Look to the side and put my hand out.
ONE YEAR AND NINE MONTHS
Fighting to catch up.
Even so...
Wait. I still have an hour, right?
-Yes.
-Then they'll come.
Two hours of extra practice fly by.
This part is important.
-Your arm went out.
-Sorry!
I put it out.
The last pose starts here. Keep it here.
I will. Sorry!
That's not right either.
-It's to the side.
-Oops.
It's like this.
-He's here.
-I'm getting excited.
Take it slow.
Yes.
-One step at a time.
-Good morning.
And then...
For the first time in one year
and nine months, the five danced.
We haven't danced with So in ages.
Yeah.
Two years?
About two years.
But he can really, you know,
dance well, so I was surprised.
I feel like I've learned it a little.
I'll go home and practice some more.
While I am impressed,
he tends to push himself too hard.
So we have to somehow try to set the pace.
I believe that's our responsibility.
Sexy!
He's teasing me!
Sorry! Bye everyone!
Goodbye!
As for Matsushima,
what was he feeling about
returning to this place?
Uh...
This is my first time
talking about it, but...
I had never really, in elementary school,
or in my childhood...
I never really had things I liked doing,
or things I wanted to do.
Everyone was in soccer clubs and...
the tennis club or something.
Everyone was doing what they wanted,
but I didn't have that.
I was wondering what my future held
and I happened to see
Hey! Say! JUMP's debut concert DVD.
I was like, "Wow, who's that?"
And that started it.
He entered Johnny's at age 13.
His debut was about six months later.
Thinking back,
he says he was missing something.
The other four bandmates,
they had a certain determination
for doing the job,
but I didn't have that determination yet.
Especially Fuma and Kento, they'd been
in Johnny's Jr. for a long time,
so they were determined to debut.
And they had goals for after that.
They were prepared for how it would be.
But in my case,
I wanted to join Johnny's
and change my life.
I just fearlessly jumped in
and I suddenly debuted.
I didn't have time to prepare, mentally.
And I didn't even know what work was.
A lot of things happened
and I just couldn't keep up.
We asked the others about Matsushima.
With him, with all things,
we wanted him to experience them
in a positive way.
We always thought about that.
No matter what So decided to do,
I told him I'd support him.
I also told him that
the love I feel for So hasn't changed.
They each kept a certain distance
in their own ways.
I had a feeling this song would
get So to come back.
And with this song,
we'd make a comfortable place
for So to return to.
It's a can of juice for Matsushima.
Matsushima's here
and we're all taking a break together.
We wanted to make that sort of atmosphere.
It's not the answer, but
that's how I see it, anyway.
To keep the pressure off me,
they tried to keep a good balance
and I could see that.
That sort of thing made me really happy.
It helped me realize,
"I do want to work with those four."
I spoke to the people at the agency
and I said, "Let me start talking
to the bandmates again."
So I'm grateful to Mr. Johnny
and I'm grateful to my bandmates.
And to all the fans
who kept supporting me,
of course, I feel gratitude toward them.
That's why I wanted to
give this another try.
September 10, Makuhari Messe.
Today's our first time with five.
I'll do my best.
The day finally came.
FIRST PERFORMANCE WITH 5 MEMBERS
Two, three, four.
Before the show, they made final
adjustments in a corner of the venue.
Are you okay, So?
I'll practice alone.
Practice alone?
-Want to go again?
-No.
You're okay?
We don't need to do it together.
I can do it alone.
However...
Don't overthink.
-Yes.
-Do it with us.
-Okay.
-If we're here, you'll get it.
The others came back right away.
He was concerned about this sequence.
...Look!
Don't push so hard.
You're like, "I gotta do this!"
That's why it looks weird.
Okay. I'll try to relax.
I'll do it one more time. I'm worried.
Look!
Don't think about doing that.
You all look nice doing this.
Don't do it with the sound.
Hear the sound and then do it.
...Like that?
Not quite. It's not that kind of song.
Yeah, but that's it.
I can't.
-You can.
-I'm nervous.
Before the performance.
We're going to give this to Sakurai.
In fact, the day before...
Welcome to Sekai Kindan no Hakobiya.
Kikuchi finished his first
prime-time show as host.
Afterward, he spoke about
his senior, Sakurai.
Tomorrow, we're on The Music Day.
We'll be, you know...
We'll have the honor
of recording a segment.
Sho Sakurai is the MC
and he said that tomorrow...
he's going to come see us.
He told me that himself.
Originally, it was just the five of us
going there to record it alone.
And then that would be used
during the live broadcast.
But he said, "Since it's all five of you,
it's important for me to be there."
It was...
It was really moving.
-Hi.
-Good to see you.
Thank you for today.
Thank you for coming.
This is the second one.
The one from the other day was A.
-So this is B?
-It's the regular one.
It's not B?
There's a reason.
-This has all English lyrics.
-Really?
Since you're working with Bruno Mars,
we also wanted to show you what we can do.
I see. Sorry, I didn't realize.
Thanks. You even signed it.
Thank you very much.
I can't wait.
Thank you for your time.
-Thank you.
Excuse us.
-Why the smirk?
-Hits the spot!
Don't lie.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Sexy thank you!
Thank you sexy too!
Then, the shoot.
-Hey, So.
-Yes!
Welcome back.
Thanks! Sorry for the wait.
How are you feeling?
I'm very happy to be
able to perform as five.
And these four gave me
such a warm welcome. I'm really happy.
Seeing the five of you together
makes me happy too.
Everyone, places please.
Thank you!
Here's that part of the performance.
This is how Sexy Zone
launched their new beginning
in the best possible way.
Thank you very much!
That was great.
Wow, I was so nervous.
Performing with all five of us,
I feel, is really great.
With So there,
the atmosphere is warmer,
our laughs are friendlier.
He's like the connector between bandmates.
It's part of So's character.
That's how he does it.
Appearing as a five-man group
makes a difference
when he's with us. We're stronger.
5 MEMBERS
The insistence on having five members.
This is a part of Sexy Zone's history.
There was a time when
there were just three of us.
We've been through a lot.
But the fact that we are five,
that was one core element for me.
From 2014, Sexy Zone did in fact
operate as a three-man group
with Sato, Nakajima, and Kikuchi.
Marius and Matsushima
each had formed their own subunits.
MARIUS YO
SEXY BOYZ
SO MATSUSHIMA
SEXY SHO
The fans really got the wrong impression.
They kept saying, "Marius and So
were kicked out of Sexy Zone."
It's true that it looked that way,
but I thought of it positively.
"Now's my chance to improve myself."
That's how I felt.
I am glad we went back to
five members now though.
Back then, it was simply a matter of age.
I didn't understand how anything worked.
"Why am I working apart from those three?"
That was all I thought about.
But now I don't feel negatively about it.
I don't think it's bad at all.
That's not just for the camera.
I really don't feel that way.
In fact, if that hadn't happened,
I don't think I could be here now.
I wouldn't be able to be here now.
I think Mr. Johnny knew...
that I was missing something.
He had me form a side unit like that
in order to find it.
I think he gave me the time to do that.
If I hadn't had that time,
I wouldn't have grown.
I needed to grow
as a person and as an artist,
so that unit, Sexy Sho,
was totally necessary.
Their positive outlook on past experiences
helped bring the bandmates closer.
Late August.
They began learning new choreography.
It's the theme song for a drama
starring Fuma Kikuchi.
"NOT FOUND."
Three and four.
AUGUST 26
This was the first day.
I got it.
This song has a lot of choreography.
I'm really using my brain.
I just have to get used to it.
Repeat it until I remember.
They continue rehearsing.
Meanwhile, where was Fuma Kikuchi?
Rolling. Ready, go!
Follow the path you believe in.
Every day,
he was busy filming
as the lead in that drama.
Yes, okay. Cut, okay.
Because of this...
rehearsals were done
with the remaining four.
Then, the time came
to shoot the music video.
Okay, I think we're done.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
-Was that the lip-sync?
-Yes.
This next one is the hardest part.
From start to finish,
we dance the whole time,
for nearly four minutes.
Yeah, so if you make one mistake,
you have to start over.
I can't make any mistakes.
I'm really nervous.
Is that right?
I do get nervous.
What if I make a mistake?
Then, it began.
The shoot they can't mess up.
The one who made a mistake was...
Okay, let's restart now.
Take two.
This time, they made it to
the final section without a mistake.
But then...
I'm so frustrated!
Is your hand alright?
-Can we do it again?
-Okay!
Kikuchi got stuck in a rut.
Then...
Let's take a break!
I need to rehearse.
And then...
-Okay!
-Yay!
Hey!
I'm so sorry about that. Thank you.
Good job.
Yay!
Then on October 27...
they had their first variety show
since they became five again.
OCTOBER 19
SEXY ZONE'S ALL NIGHT NIPPON PREMIUM
I'm so nervous my throat is dry.
The time is now 6 p.m.
Good evening to all our listeners.
I'm Shori Sato.
I'm Kento Nakajima.
I'm Fuma Kikuchi.
I'm Marius Yo.
I'm So Matsushima.
We're Sexy Zone.
-Thank you for coming.
-Thank you.
"I'm so nervous."
That went on air, didn't it?
It did.
Please keep an eye on the clock.
Sorry!
With one silly outburst,
these five began
their live radio broadcast.
It's been a while for all of us.
For one thing, I'm really glad
that it's the show with ARASHI.
"VS ARASHI" FILMING
A program hosted by their seniors, ARASHI.
-Good morning!
Before the show.
ARASHI
It's Sexy Zone!
They're real!
Thank you for today.
The camera's on!
They're real!
Our kind seniors.
They then headed to the show.
Next time, they go
where their fans await them.
We can finally do it.
It's all love. Nothing but love.
So's on here.
We're the only ones with this.
With Matsushima's return,
Sexy Zone was whole again.
They went with all their strength.
An online concert with
no audience present.
They're doing something they've never
done before on the center stage.
I like this group.
I like this group and everyone in it.
So that's it, I guess.
They searched for their own answers.
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka