NOVEMBER 2020
ENOSHIMA
-We made it to Enoshima.
-We did.
Matsuku? Where are you?
At the train station?
I'm at the ticket gate.
No, I'm walking.
There you are.
He looks so shady.
Like he's up to no good.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
How was Shime's driving?
-It was fine.
-Really?
Yes, it was smooth.
-I messed up the highway exit though.
-Yeah?
-Was it around February?
-Yeah.
They are Travis Japan's
Ryuya Shimekake and Kaito Matsukura.
OCTOBER 2020
Until a few days ago, they were standing
on the Shinbashi Enbujo Theatre stage
in a stage play starring
the seven members of Travis Japan.
I'll give you a signal
if it looks like you'll hit Noel.
Okay, thanks.
-Seriously, thanks.
-Don't mention it.
-It's about helping each other.
-So cool.
I didn't make my quick change.
The costume has a zipper,
and it got jammed.
I had to go out without fixing it.
FINAL REHEARSAL
Then Shime was like, "Just look forward!"
-He was actually cool.
-Screw you!
You jerk.
This was their brief moment of respite
after finishing their run of 28 shows.
It's cold.
It's seriously cold.
-What is nishoku-don?
-Let's see.
It's whitebait prepared
two ways over rice.
What is sanshoku-don then?
It's a nishoku-don
with minced tuna and green onion.
For real?
We'll take two nishoku-don and...
-And two boiled whitebait rice bowls?
-Yes.
Sorry, also...
Could I have the sashimi platter?
The platter? Thank you.
You're having fun at least.
-Thank you for this meal.
-Time to dig in.
It's really good.
The whitebait is so springy and tender.
Inside my mouth it's like...
It's like shu, shu, shu, shu.
-Why are you stuttering?
-I'm cold.
Shu, shu, shu, shu...
Can whitebait be springy?
-Isn't that for soba noodles?
-Right.
Food reviews are hard.
Yes, they are.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
SEPTEMBER 2020
Rehearsals for Travis Japan's
stage play have begun.
-That's so high.
-Be careful.
The trampoline acrobatic stunts
can send them over four meters in the air.
It's crazy scary.
For real?
Because that's so high.
It's scarier with high ceilings.
The stage play Torajya Ninjapan
is an entertainment show
that was created for Travis Japan in 2019.
FIRST STARRING PERFORMANCE
While they instantly sold out every show,
the trampoline, tap dancing, and action
led to a physically-demanding performance
that was more rigorous than anticipated.
I tend to turn.
Okay, okay.
They play the roles of ninja
with superhuman abilities.
In the climax,
they were asked to try out
some astounding moves.
We want to get on the world stage.
While we're not the best in Japan,
we want our play to reach that status.
We don't just want the play to blow up.
We want to make sure that we grow as well,
so we can ultimately
perform overseas together.
So they stand on this legendary stage
to realize their dream.
SHINBASHI ENBUJO THEATRE
Naturally, they are asked to make it
an even better show than before.
Five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten.
-Shizuya, did you do one extra?
-Sorry.
One more time.
Yeah, that's tiring. You guys okay?
We're doing stuff that even the best
trampolinists in Japan can't do.
So try to focus.
It's going to take a lot of stamina.
Ready? Go.
Sorry!
We just have to practice.
Jump on two. One, two, three.
The leader Kaito Miyachika ardently
gives them advice during practice.
You two can go like one, two, three.
Okay, good.
You can do a flip from there.
Make the left twist sharper...
Then there is Noel Kawashima, the oldest.
He pushes the group
with his detailed, constructive feedback.
One of Travis' best qualities is that
when they come up against a problem,
they talk things over together
and give suggestions as a group.
You get a wonderful sense of teamwork
that you'd be hard-pressed to find,
even in team sports.
That is a big help to me.
They are the oldest group
within Johnny's Jr.
FORMED 2012
Five of the initial
nine members still remain.
I've been with Noel since
before we became a group.
-We didn't get along at first.
-Really?
I didn't talk to him at all,
even backstage.
Really?
I don't think he was a fan of me either.
It didn't help that I realized
I had a problem with him.
I don't know, Shizuya and I
didn't get along,
and Shime and I didn't hit it off at all.
I hated him.
I didn't like Noel or Shime much either.
I see.
At the start.
Noel was really prickly, too.
He wasn't the nice
and friendly guy he is today.
I'd be like, "What's his problem?"
I was really touchy back then.
I was like, if I can do it,
everyone should.
It was really messed up
the way I judged everyone.
Kawashima was working
while still attending school,
so there was a time when he was as hard
on others as he was on himself.
-This is so nostalgic.
-Yeah?
It's super nostalgic.
This is it.
I started here in junior high,
and attended for ten years.
This right here.
That building over there with four floors...
That's my university's research facility
for the political science department.
Back then, he frequented the office
of his professor who was mentoring him.
I think this was it.
This brings back memories.
It's the only one with curtain rails.
It's something my professor left behind.
While everyone searched for jobs,
he had doubts regarding
his future as an idol.
It's okay to have
different values and personalities.
You can talk differently
and speak different languages.
University was bringing
all sorts of things into one place.
When you meet all kinds of people,
you start thinking about
how interesting other jobs can be.
I have friends who are pharmacists...
They have all sorts of professions.
I actually want to do it all.
I want to experience them all.
From the piano to linguistics,
acrobatics to intensive studies,
he took on anything that interested him.
Good morning,
good afternoon, good evening.
Thinking about what he could do
during the quarantine,
he uploaded sign language
tutorial videos every day for 50 days.
He is relied upon to emcee
and handle the press.
Its fun meter is just so, so, so high.
Last year, we went from zero to one.
This was a piece in which we worked hard
to turn that one into a ten or a hundred.
We're sure that you're going to love it.
Could you give me a smile?
However, all the weapons he mastered
sometimes make it hard to see
Kawashima's human-side.
Okay, please turn your gaze back this way.
Nice and soft.
I heard you can't force a smile.
Yeah, I'm so bad at it.
I'm terrible at it.
It's so hard for me to smile for pictures.
Sometimes we wonder
when we'll be able to see the real Noel.
Yeah.
I probably have all these weapons
because I'm scared to show the real me.
So, you're afraid.
It's because I'm weak.
Part of me feels that I can't be an idol
if I'm too natural.
What will happen?
Well...
Part of me feels that I can't be an idol
if I'm too natural.
What will happen?
Well...
-People will think I'm just crazy.
-Yeah?
-You mean like dangerous?
-No.
People don't understand me.
I feel like people like idols because
they feel a sense of closeness,
or there's a part of them
that grabs their interest.
And I probably don't have
a single thing like that.
I'm just not confident in myself.
Seriously.
I wasn't great at anything.
With work, with my studies.
I worked hard to try to be the best,
but I couldn't pick one thing.
I was too scared to face failure if I did.
That's why I want people to look
at the facade I've crafted,
but it gets peeled away.
-It gets peeled back?
-Yeah.
It's those guys who peeled it back.
So I'm incredibly grateful.
I see.
There were nine initial members.
One by one they would quit,
until one day they were down to five.
Some believed the group would dissolve
before they even had a chance to debut.
Then what happened was...
my dad stopped me.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-From quitting?
When we got down to five of us,
my dad invited me to dinner, so I went.
I wasn't really giving off vibes that
I was going to quit or anything.
Anyway, my dad was like...
going down this path wasn't a mistake,
and that I should keep going because there
were definitely good things in my future.
Yeah.
Part of it for me was...
KAITO NAKAMURA
...there weren't many fans.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But the ones we did have still
cheered me on so enthusiastically.
My first fan letter made me so happy.
-You remember it?
-Yeah.
It said, "You caught my interest
so I've started watching."
I still think I have it at home.
I think it was someone
from Fukui prefecture.
During this time
of uncertainty for the five,
2017 offered a turning point.
It was the addition of Kaito Matsukura
and Genta Matsuda.
Much was expected of their dance skills.
However, their dance skills weren't
the only thing they brought to the group.
Okay, ready?
Let's see.
No! Why are you cheating?
You're so cheap.
He's a cheater.
Okay, ready?
Chàng gē.
I know that one...
"Sing a song"!
-That was awesome.
-Okay.
Rèn shi.
Got it!
Bāng zhù.
-Wow.
-Don't be so hesitant.
Pǎo bù!
Wait, I know this one.
What's the definition?
Go at the same time.
Ready?
-"To run."
-"Running."
They're both correct.
We'll split it 50-50.
No!
After MatsuMatsu joined,
we all started
communicating with each other.
Also, the two of them take the initiative.
They goof off and set the tone.
It's like...
Like...
Light entered the group.
For real.
It was pretty dark
when it was the five of us.
Really?
Genta was the one.
He was the one who really
broke me out of my shell.
When I was trying
to look all cool and manly,
he'd share an embarrassing story about me.
At first I was like, "Stop it!"
"Stop it, I worked hard to craft this!"
Is what I thought...
but it was so freeing to take it off.
I was so grateful when I realized that.
It's all thanks to him.
Were you scared?
Not at all.
GENTA MATSUDA (21)
Even if he got mad,
I thought I'd just tease him more.
I think he wanted to loosen up,
but his position demanded maturity,
which is why Noel felt so liberated
after peeling that back.
Then everyone could ease up
and expand their horizons.
After I took Noel's shell
and broke him out,
I realized everyone would change.
Ow.
It hurts.
This doesn't ease the pain.
I mean, it does but...
-It slows inflammation.
-Yeah?
You still need to take care of it yourself
by stretching and soaking in a bath.
This will just help you heal faster.
Thanks, you're a lifesaver.
It won't hurt for a while,
but the injury hasn't healed,
so try not to move too much.
Be careful.
Thanks.
There was a chance it may not
have been this current lineup.
Yeah.
I probably would've quit.
-Really?
-Probably.
I wonder.
Before we became seven,
I thought about quitting.
I thought about quitting even after.
I don't know.
Although, when they joined,
I thought I'd really try
because this could be it.
I thought if this lineup didn't work out,
we'd be finished.
They would be taking on
another new challenge this time.
They would try to run up both sides
of a rotating wall from a trampoline.
It would be a performance that would
require all their stamina and skill
to draw people into a fantasy world.
Crap.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
You five are jumping.
-Go!
Ready?
Get ready.
Okay, now!
Hold on. Crap!
This is insane!
It's so hard!
-Kaito.
-Oh my gosh.
You have to jump the longest.
I'm going to die.
"If you're not going to try,
it doesn't matter which path you take."
Those are the words
my professor shared with me.
Whatever path I choose to take,
if I don't find or try to find
something that excites me
or something that really drives me...
If I'm just doing it
for the sake of doing something...
then it doesn't matter if it's
in entertainment or another job.
Regardless of whatever I choose,
I won't be able to enjoy my life.
So why not try and see what happens?
Next time, they attempt a new dance.
The man they all admire
handles the choreography.
TOMOYUKI YARA
Like, "Wow, it's this different."
Learning and doing aren't the same.
People say my expression is scary.
I wonder whether I'm improving at all.
They search for a deeper expression.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto