Their tour was postponed
due to the pandemic.
As the group was becoming less active,
Sexy Zone's 18th single,
"RUN" was released.
It's a song that asks us questions.
It also says,
"It's our tenth year, let's keep going."
Nine years since their debut,
the four stood on a new starting line.
There's someone
they're always keeping in mind.
An important person.
He might not come back.
If So is happy that way, then that's okay.
I can't say, "I want to perform
as five. Please come back."
SEXY ZONE
FUMA KIKUCHI (25)
Yeah.
And then that day came.
This is Marius, I'm Matsushima.
We're SoMari!
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
The youngest Johnny's group to debut.
They appeared on Kohaku
just two years later.
Everyone thought that
they were on an elite path.
But in their hearts...
I'm under pressure.
I've never not been under pressure.
But we haven't done anything
memorable in the ten years.
I was always anxious.
There was a lot of conflict too, yeah.
I guess it's just...
We didn't have time to prepare
before we debuted as Sexy Zone.
There was a sense of crisis as a group.
What's more, So Matsushima
went on medical hiatus.
And then...
the national tour scheduled
from March was postponed.
Each member worked to do what they could
in a struggle to break out
of their own shells.
On this day,
Fuma Kikuchi was recording
a variety program.
-Could I get a comment?
-Yeah.
For that long?
-It does say 16 minutes.
-That's amazing.
I couldn't last 16 even if I shed blood.
In 2008,
when he was a second year in junior high,
Kikuchi contacted the agency himself.
He talks about his attractive image
which is the opposite of his personality.
I might be the most negative one.
I think there is some frustration
with that, in the group.
"Why is he so pessimistic?"
I think there's a bit of that.
That's why he's the one
who sees situations most calmly.
Five seconds. Four, three...
For him, the place where
he broke out of his shell was variety TV.
I do want to be recognized as cool though.
When I walk around town,
people call me "That Naked Guy."
I get people saying stuff like,
"I saw you on Endless Pranks Grand Prix."
Things like that
have never happened before,
so it was a bit surprising.
I'm grateful for the opportunity.
Expanding his activities to variety TV
has had a synergistic effect.
"SHIMAUMA PRINT" COMMERCIAL
The same vibe, but could you
do your pose a bit lower?
He landed his first
solo commercial appearance.
His comical appeal
became a part of his strength.
It's a sort of surreal comical touch.
I think I exude a strangeness,
so I want to try and do more of that.
Repeatedly challenging yourself
is something Shori Sato is doing as well.
On this day, he acted in a short drama
for a variety program.
It's different from usual in that
I have to represent the group.
I really enjoy doing variety programs.
Trying new things
is really important to me.
Especially these days.
Aah.
He plays a loser with an Oedipus complex.
When Mommy feeds me, it tastes so good!
Rolling! Ready...
In the end, he gets slapped.
He's taken a role that's different
from his usual image.
Things other people aren't doing
or that nobody has done before.
I try it, and I think about it a lot.
His even features
have earned him the name,
"Living National Treasure Face."
He began a new series
in a women's fashion magazine.
There was yet another member
trying new things.
The youngest of the group, Marius,
was searching for his own position.
Homework.
Homework? For university?
University, yes.
This is about Brexit.
It's about Britain leaving the EU.
We have discussions.
It's a kind of seminar course.
Marius debuted as
an elementary school student,
but now he's a third year in university.
It's "How do democracies die?"
It's interesting, really. I like it.
I want to use my position
as an idol to inspire people
to learn about government
and the world and get more interested.
On this day, he had
a recording for a quiz show.
KONYA WA NAZOTORE FILMING
There are sides to me
I can't really show with Sexy Zone.
I'm a little more...
I can speak different languages.
I do use that as a sort of weapon.
Born in Germany,
he speaks German, Japanese
and English. He's trilingual.
There's something called Invader Game.
Have you heard of Invader Game?
"Invader."
Oh!
Not that?
-Let me see...
-In English.
Is this the first time Fuwa's with Taka?
If I'm invaded, I'm done for.
Say that again.
Invade... Invader.
-Good work today.
-Thank you.
Like I said earlier, I think I got to
use my language skills a bit today.
Invader.
I'm finished for today.
I'll go home and get back to my homework.
Catch you later!
Bye everyone!
Good bye!
"PERFECT ONE" COMMERCIAL SHOOT
Perfect.
Even Nakajima, the eldest,
was energetically pursuing his own work.
SHIOSAI BRIDGE
What do you have today?
Today is...
I have a series in anan,
so it's a shoot for that.
On this day, Nakajima had
photo shoots with five magazines.
On to the next one.
Alright!
Next, we go up I think?
We'll go up, and I have
a shoot with Ribon.
Like you're sleepy.
Rub your eyes a bit.
Where are we now?
This is, uh, The TV.
MAGAZINE "THE TV" PHOTO SHOOT
Thank you.
All of the shoots have ended.
-Good work today.
-Thanks.
Since you're alone right now...
Yes.
Can we talk a bit?
Yes, of course.
As the eldest,
Nakajima has always led the group.
My group is especially sensitive.
A lot of them can be touchy.
I just accept everything
without judgment.
I think that's...
a good quality and a bad one,
at least, in my opinion.
In 2008, Nakajima
auditioned at the agency on his own.
There, he met Kikuchi,
who joined at the same time.
Ever since their Johnny's Jr. years,
they were popularly known as
the handsome duo "Fumaken."
"FUMAKEN"
But as a result of their closeness...
We've been together for 12 years.
There were times I hated him
and times I liked him too.
And also times I didn't care at all.
But he's always been by my side.
I guess we both have that awareness,
that it's a friendly competition.
I think we both felt that strongly.
So at one point...
there was a time when it was all thorns.
Yeah.
Now that we're almost at
the tenth anniversary of our debut,
we talked on the phone yesterday...
Uh...
We had a meeting about a video
we're going to put online,
so we talked about a lot of things.
He has this human side
that I want to show people.
I think he should promote it more.
In that sense, Kikuchi going on
those prank shows,
variety shows and all that...
I feel like he's on a good path right now.
I really like how he isn't
trying to act all cool anymore.
According to Kikuchi...
I think Nakajima and I
are both a little odd.
I do look at things from a step back.
Or at least, I try to take a step back.
So I think that might...
sometimes look emotionally distant.
Well, Nakajima is the eldest after all.
I think he has his pride.
He sometimes says so himself.
But above all, Nakajima is more like...
the point-getter.
He's really the shooter after all.
So I have to give the assist.
I feel like it's my job
to make those passes work.
That's what I think.
It really feels like that.
Overcoming many barriers,
the two grew to respect one another.
Their readiness
to fight together is the same.
And the member who acts
as the group's mediator.
So Matsushima.
He's an adhesive,
but really more of a glue.
As a member of Sexy Zone,
he's really like the sun.
Just by being there,
the mood gets lighter.
There's footage that shows
Matsushima's character.
It's right there.
We're getting hungry.
SEXY ZONE 5-MAN TRIP
This was the bonus content
from their 2018 album.
-Oh!
-Whoa!
Did it take it?
It ate it!
You were robbed? So.
That's not fair!
Give it back!
Matsushima was
the mood maker for the group.
As they hoped for his return from hiatus,
the bandmates felt conflicted.
I really like So as a person,
and I respect him.
I just want him to get better.
And for example, if that means
he might not come back,
If that's the case...
If So is happy that way, then that's okay.
I can't just say it.
Of course it's better with five.
I can't say, "Please, I want to perform
as five. Please come back."
Yeah.
I wish he could...
somehow find a way to be happy.
That's how I feel now I guess.
"RUN" was released on August 5.
It holds special meaning for the group.
Ready? Hi, everyone! We're Sexy Zone!
Yay!
To all our supportive fans,
we have some news.
Thanks to all of you,
our new single, "RUN"
was number one
on the weekly singles charts! Yay!
And then, the day arrived.
This day was a shoot for the fan club.
Sitting there was...
SEXY ZONE
SO MATSUSHIMA (23)
I'm happy. I am happy.
Before, we were always the youngest
so we came to work first.
-We'd do our makeup together.
-Yeah, that's right.
Good morning.
Thanks.
For what?
What "thanks"?
You did that for me.
Of course I did!
Wouldn't you say, "Long time no see?"
We'd always message each other
so it doesn't feel like
it's been a long time.
In the sense of distance.
It's scary while sleeping.
The same atmosphere as always.
That's how they chose to respond.
You nervous?
I'm super nervous.
-I might pee my pants.
-Nothing's stopping you.
Ah, the camera was on.
Okay, rolling!
Five seconds, four, three, two...
Hello everyone.
We are Sexy Zone!
Today, we have some happy news.
We wanted to tell you right away,
so we're making this video.
-Yes.
-Everyone, well...
-I know you already know.
-That's right.
You've been waiting.
-Yes, truly.
-Yes, I've been waiting.
What shall we do? Should we call him?
Or should we...
What should we do?
Wanna get him? Shori, go.
-Okay, I'll go.
-You go.
Hey, let's go.
Yay!
Woo!
It's So!
Yes. Sorry for being away for so long.
I'm So Matsushima from Sexy Zone.
It's public. You're coming back.
Yes, thank you very much.
Please support us!
Please do!
Do the honors.
This has been...
Sexy Zone!
Yay!
And on this day,
the shoot to announce
Matsushima's return ended.
It's been so long, I'm still sort of...
Yeah, but it's still so...
I feel like it's all coming back to me.
Uh...
Later, on the radio program he hosts,
Sato told the fans.
We have announced So Matsushima's return.
We've caused everyone to worry
for nearly two years.
We've always considered So
to naturally be a bandmate.
So it's only natural.
It's really just natural. Yeah.
That's how much... Hmm.
How can I put it?
So that's why we say, "Welcome home."
Yeah.
Sexy Zone will go on to be
Sexy Zone in its true form.
We'll show you
what Sexy Zone is all about.
This was Shori wo Kimi ni
with Sexy Zone's Shori Sato.
Good work.
Sato chose his words carefully
and shared his thoughts.
Soon after his return was the shoot
for the cover of their new song.
A photo shoot with the five of us is...
Right? It's been a while.
But it feels the same as always.
Just as it was before.
I love how nothing has changed.
We already discussed this!
Why are you so excited?
He's not excited.
He's trying to make a good shot.
We're setting up all these lights.
Don't get in the way!
-Shooting!
-Okay.
They're shooting me.
This feels so extravagant.
This is Marius, I'm Matsushima.
We're SoMari!
Well done today.
Thank you.
This was the first photo shoot
since I returned.
I feel like it'll become
a special memory for me.
A different kind of memory than usual.
I hadn't worked with the four for a while
and each of them had become
a little more mature.
Their faces, too.
It was just refreshing to see.
They really did keep Sexy Zone going,
that same environment.
It's still there.
And here I am, trying to
fit back into that, in the right way.
At times like that, I listen to "RUN"
as I work towards
the goals I set for myself...
As I'm doing that,
I can choose to see
negative things as positive.
That's how this song speaks to me.
And the four members
of Sexy Zone are singing it.
That's the most important part.
We're all doing our best
in the same circumstances.
The fact that people I know are singing...
That makes me really happy.
Though that's probably something
other people can't feel.
Next, the five appear on a music program.
FIVE ONSTAGE AFTER 650 DAYS
Fighting to catch up.
I haven't been in front of cameras
in ages.
When I dance,
I get butterflies in my stomach.
The bonds between the five...
I wish So wouldn't worry.
He can tease, and criticize too.
I believe in him.
You don't need to be perfect.
You can just have fun.
I just want everyone
to look forward to it.
I'm sure Matsushima feels the same way.
-So this is B?
-It's the regular one.
It's not B?
Thank you everyone.
They've only just begun.
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka