Let's just have fun.
-Okay!
-Yeah! Let's go!
Yeah!
-Woo!
-Thirty seconds.
Sexy Zone's concert had been
postponed since March due to the pandemic.
I'm so happy.
We can finally do it.
It's all love. Nothing but love.
After eight months, the answer they found
was an online concert
with no audience present.
Stand by!
Time to go where their fans await them.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
We talked together about this.
August.
A meeting to discuss the online concert.
SEXY ZONE
SO MATSUSHIMA (23)
Actually, if it wasn't a livestream...
Between the four of us,
doing a live concert with Matsushima
wasn't even on the table.
Since it's a livestream,
it's something we can try.
MATSUSHIMA RETURNS
He hasn't been onstage for a concert
for about two and a half years.
Before the MC?
I could come out on the daily special.
Sounds good.
That could work.
You could appear in two spots.
Song-wise, it would be three songs.
You'd be appearing here and there.
That makes it special
and I think it works for a stream.
Matsushima will appear for two songs
in the middle and the final song.
I haven't seen rehearsals
in such a long time.
It really feels like a concert is coming.
I'm thrilled. I'm excited.
To see the four perform is so cool.
It's a work in itself.
But performing as five
is another work.
I hope we can bring that to everyone.
The final number of the concert is
"RUN" with all five members.
During the last hook,
all five run in five directions.
-Okay.
-And then... Three people here.
Above all else,
they want their fans to see
a performance only Sexy Zone can give.
Their homes will be the concert venue,
so I feel more motivated than ever.
If the dancing is half-hearted...
Since our faces won't be easy to see,
the things we convey will be different.
OCTOBER 18
Compared to their previous concerts,
this will be done
in a different environment.
We had a few things to remake and relearn.
People will watch us closely.
It's kind of like folding picture toys.
We're making it our focus
to show a lot of different things.
If they're with us, we can see the fans,
so we can visually check
if they're having fun.
But with a screen,
we don't know if they're having fun.
So my confidence...
It makes me easily discouraged, I think.
A stage without an audience.
How will the five face it?
OCTOBER 28
CONCERT REHEARSAL
It was time for the on-site rehearsals.
Kikuchi stood before 15,000 empty seats.
The situation won't be much different
from a rehearsal.
If I let myself get too carried away
by my excitement while performing,
I might feel sad
when we see the empty seats.
So I have to keep my excitement in check
by not having too much fun.
They prepared
something special for the show.
So's on here.
We're the only ones with this.
Only five were made.
The merchandise is like this.
It was everyone's idea.
Finally, the three-day-long concert's
curtains are drawn.
October 29. It's showtime.
Good morning.
Good morning. Let's do this!
-Good morning.
Good morning. See you today.
Morning.
Good morning.
Where will you be watching from,
besides your three songs?
I'll be in the PA seats, with the staff.
Upstairs on the B stage side.
I'll be able to see from above.
I'll be there this time.
I won't be able to see them directly...
I wish we could meet the people
who love our music most.
We're going!
-Let's go!
-Shall we go?
We're going!
Here we go.
My hands are so sweaty.
It's finally time.
Let's just have fun.
-Okay.
-Yeah! Let's go!
Yeah!
-Woo!
-Thirty seconds!
Wow, I'm happy.
We can finally do it.
They can finally see us and see this.
It's all love. Nothing but love.
Irrepressible elation.
Stand by!
Time to go where their fans await them.
"KYOKUTO DANCE"
Hey, Sexy Lovers on
phones, tablets, and computers!
Is your Wi-Fi network pumped?
Backstage, it's a battle against time
as they change quickly for a solo song.
The one who always
leads in performances.
The eldest, Nakajima.
The one who has grown
to take a more prominent role, Marius.
The always cool-headed Kikuchi. And...
Shori Sato,
who sings a solo about his mentor.
The Johnny's classics are all in there.
What Mr. Johnny did...
What Mr. Johnny was trying...
His ideal image of Johnny's.
I've always strived to be that,
and that was expected of me.
He wrote the lyrics to
"Show must go on" himself.
In order for Sexy Zone
to move on to the next stage,
I have to put all of my past into this
and mark the end of this stage.
I think I need to do that.
Yeah.
Kind of like a fresh start.
The song that shows Sexy Zone's
readiness to go into the future.
"GYUTTO"
"Gyutto!"
Then, Matsushima joined them onstage.
Matsushima's here!
Matsushima?
-I'm Matsushima.
-So!
-Is it really you?
-Matsushima.
The five mark their
new start with "NOT FOUND."
The four continue,
and Matsushima wants to watch.
This part is really good.
They're doing something they've never
done before on the center stage.
I think you should see.
"HOSHI NO AME"
By the middle of the concert,
#SZ_POPSTEP2020 was
the number one trending topic.
Then, at the end of
three days of online concerts.
More than anything,
I'm glad he made this decision.
During his hiatus,
to make a single decision,
I'm sure we can't even imagine
the amount of pressure he was under.
His choice could have been
to leave Sexy Zone.
But among those many choices,
he chose to stand with us onstage,
together as five.
I'm very happy about that.
I want to use all my power
to continue protecting this group of five.
I feel that strongly.
I have these words for everyone.
We're enough.
"SORE DE IIYO"
I think it was really hard
for the four of them.
And as the credits rolled...
the five of them stood by for "RUN,"
wearing those t-shirts.
Then...
Are you okay?
You got overwhelmed?
Now you get overwhelmed?
Finally, the final song
that has a special meaning to them.
In 2011,
they became the youngest group
to debut in Johnny's history.
They searched for their own place.
-Oh!
-Whoa!
Did it take it?
Hold on!
Hi, everyone! We're Sexy Zone!
That's good. It's really good.
Yay!
Woo!
-It's So!
-Yes.
We're SoMari!
-Okay!
-Yay!
Hey!
SEXY ZONE IN 10 YEARS...
Well...
To be a boys group whose music is played
not just in Japan, but the world...
I think I want to aim for that as a goal.
It will depend on how well
we can adapt to change.
An idol needs to have
the power of music and words
to deliver happiness to people.
It's like a mission, like our fate.
If that could naturally
come about in twenty years...
First, I hope we can become
nationally-renowned idols.
Well, of course, I think everyone has
dreams of their own for the group.
But ultimately,
I hope each one of us can be
happy and content.
That's all I need to be happy. Truly.
You can't force...
all five of us to stay together.
I don't think that's right.
All we can do is pray.
"Please."
"Please let everyone's dreams
be united until our 20th anniversary."
All I can do is pray.
Yes, please pray for us.
That Sexy Zone can reach its
20th anniversary as a five-man group.
Picture that and pray hard.
I'd like to see it.
If I could be singing, I'd be happy.
I'd be really happy.
Yeah.
I like this group.
Looking at it objectively,
as long as the other bandmates...
are smiling and having fun, I'd be happy.
Rather than what I want for myself.
That's all I want, I guess.
More than our 20th anniversary.
If we can have fun,
or seem like we're having fun.
I like this group and everyone in it.
So that's it, I guess.
On December 2, Marius Yo went on
temporary hiatus due to ill health.
Shori Sato, Kento Nakajima, Fuma Kikuchi,
and So Matsushima continue with the group.
Sexy Zone will continue
running into the future.
On the next RIDE ON TIME is Snow Man.
Using dance as their weapon.
A look inside as they climb to success.
I wonder how I look.
After many years in Johnny's Jr,
they finally debuted.
It's like we can finally start running.
Dancing in the center at 17,
his true feelings.
For the first time,
I felt like I wanted us to succeed.
CONCERT CANCELED
It should have been their year to shine.
It's unfortunate, or more of a shock.
The view they saw
after overcoming so many walls...
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka