It's been two years.
How far have they come along?
NANIWA DANSHI
Takahashi.
There's a camera.
-Good morning.
-What is the camera for?
KYOHEI TAKAHASHI
RIDE ON TIME.
Correct!
I want to show how much
we've improved since last time.
With the quarantine,
we have a lot we want to let out.
That's what I'd like for people to see.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
2020.
People disappeared from the city.
2020 TOKYO
From Tokyo...
and from Osaka.
2020 OSAKA
The cities grew quiet
as if a fire went out.
They wanted to do something to give back
and lift the spirits of the city
where they grew up.
KANJANI8 / JOHNNYS' WEST
AE! GROUP / NANIWA DANSHI / LIL KANSAI
July 28th.
Naniwa Day.
Singing and dancing on the stage
are idols and young performers
who hail from Kansai.
There's a total of over 70 people.
OVER 70 KANSAI JOHNNY'S GATHER
This concert was also meant
to get people excited for
the 2025 World Expo that will be in Osaka.
There was a reason behind
their level of energy.
"OSAKA ROMANESQUE"
This year, they endured
a year filled with anguish.
That is because the cancellation of
concerts meant they lost their stage.
I was pretty bummed out.
I'm 27 right now,
so canceling those concerts made me
miss out on a one-time experience.
Each day was like fumbling
through the darkness,
trying to make our way forward.
It was frustrating.
It's frustrating when you
think it was COVID's fault.
But for them, they wanted to
lift the spirits of one more place.
LIFTING THE SPIRITS OF ONE MORE PLACE
The Osaka Shochikuza Theatre
that raised them.
It remained closed even as summer came.
OSAKA SHOCHIKUZA THEATRE
Cheers from the audience disappeared,
and the staff members faced
a difficult situation.
And so, this summer,
five groups are putting on
a live concert to empty seats.
AUGUST - JOHNNYS' WEST, KANJANI8
AE! GROUP, LIL KANSAI,
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR., NANIWA DANSHI
How do we showcase
something that only we can do?
It's really difficult without an audience.
This will be a really tough fight.
This is rough.
This was also a time for the seniors
to pass down a tradition to their juniors.
OSAKA
Johnny's activity in Kansai
began in the late 1990s.
KanJani8 debuted their CD in 2004,
and Johnnys' WEST
debuted their CD in 2014.
2018 FOOTAGE
However, two years ago,
Kansai's Johnny's Jr. program
didn't include any units,
and the young men striving to become idols
lost sight of their dream.
Unable to stand by and do nothing,
two men stepped up.
KanJani8's
Tadayoshi Ohkura and You Yokoyama.
TADAYOSHI OHKURA
Ohkura produced the songs
and dance choreography...
YOU YOKOYAMA
...while Yokoyama took charge
of the comedic performances.
There really are a lot of amazing kids.
I consider it our current job
to figure out
how to make each one of these kids shine.
I'm sure everything
they do will be
a learning experience for them.
As a result, a unit with a sweet
and charming image emerged,
Naniwa Danshi.
FORMED OCTOBER 2018
A unit of all high schoolers,
Lil Kansai.
FORMED JANUARY 2019
A unit excelling in comedy and music,
Ae! group.
FORMED FEBRUARY 2019
These three units were born.
JULY 27
This night would be a big
learning experience for them.
The night before their concert
at Expo'70 Park,
they hold a rehearsal in Osaka-jo Hall.
JOHNNYS' WEST
They will only get one opportunity
where all five groups
can rehearse together.
KANJANI8
This time, Ohkura was also deeply
involved in constructing the set list.
KANJANI8
TADAYOSHI OHKURA (35)
SHOTA YASUDA (36)
KanJani8
is the oldest group.
KANJANI8
YOU YOKOYAMA (39) & SHINGO MURAKAMI (38)
Their juniors looked upon them.
JOHNNYS' WEST LOOK UPON
THEIR SENIORS, KANJANI8
When I see them check their choreography
and dance seriously,
it's like they're showing me what to do
and I can't let up.
Even for the rehearsal,
they could almost charge you money for it.
RUKU TOMA (16)
Okay, pencils down!
Even with the variety show rehearsal...
-How about, "Did you decide?"
-Okay.
-When they're ready let's start.
They may need time.
...they were the ones leading the others.
There he is!
KANJANI8
RYUHEI MARUYAMA (36)
They also know how to lighten the mood.
Our seniors foster such a good atmosphere.
Like, once they go into work mode...
They shift gear.
SEIYA SUEZAWA (26)
Ohkura intently checks
the choreography over and over again.
This is for the Tower of the Sun stage.
Once this song finishes the next comes up.
Okay, everyone in this number listen up.
This is for the Tower of the Sun stage...
Ohkura was also busy filming
a television drama at this time,
and was pushing his schedule to the limit.
The show runs a little into September.
So you go to Osaka
when you have time off from the show?
I either go to Osaka,
or they come to Tokyo.
You must be very busy.
It's crazy.
-Have you lost weight?
-I have, yeah.
I thought so.
Naturally?
Yes, because I'm so busy.
Still...
they were always mindful
of a certain presence.
How do you feel being back on site?
-Hm?
-How's it feel being back on site?
So many folks are involved.
I'm really moved.
Our ability to stand on the stage
and see our fans...
Having an audience watch us
is something that's indescribable.
I have to stand on that stage
and try not to disappoint them.
That's how I feel.
On this day,
there were 357 staff members
supporting them.
The big day finally arrives.
Ohkura continues going over
the choreography
while the Jr. kids watch.
At this point...
LYRICS: TADAYOSHI OHKURA
MUSIC: SHOTA YASUDA
Ohkura showed no signs of his exhaustion
as he delivered
his performance to the fans.
However...
KANJANI'S OHKURA TO MISS
TOMORROW'S LIVESTREAM
He pushed himself to the limit.
He was forced to miss
the Shochikuza livestream.
2020 AUGUST 7 SPONICHI
AUGUST 8
SHOCHIKUZA
However, this incident taught
his juniors an important lesson.
DAY OF THE EMPTY-VENUE LIVESTREAM
The four members seemed calm.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Should I get closer? Maybe 1,5?
They make practical changes
to the dance formation and singing parts.
Being professionals, they will entertain
their fans regardless of the circumstance.
There were talks
that it might be canceled,
but the members came together
and we decided to do it.
As a group,
we managed to overcome
a lot of mishaps at Shochikuza.
But the reason why we chose
to do it is for Ohkura,
and all the people who have been
looking forward to it.
I'm sure Ohkura is the most frustrated.
We wanted to stand up there
as the five of us,
but I'm sure he wanted it the most.
How can we take Ohkura's frustration,
and transform it into positive energy
that we can deliver to our fans?
One, two, three, four...
They quickly add one of Ohkura's
solo numbers to the set list.
"BUTTERFLY I LOVED"
OHKURA'S SOLO SONG
The seats are illuminated green,
Ohkura's color.
They also made T-shirts with his photo.
Say cheese.
You guys don't need to worry about us.
If the camera's on you, just go crazy.
Okay.
If you start going crazy...
Ohkura had been the one
mostly looking after the kids,
so the rest of the group
takes over in his absence.
Okay.
Just do that a lot.
The curtains are drawn
as Ohkura watches over them from afar.
Osaka!
"SUKIYANEN, OSAKA."
"ZOU"
These five men have overcome
numerous challenges as a group.
KanJani...
8!
No matter the crisis,
they've transformed it into strength.
Mr. Johnny said
that you have to learn to enjoy it.
Don't panic during mishaps.
He said how you deal
with a crisis is important.
Well, we managed
to make it through the day
without any huge incidents
so I'm relieved.
Meanwhile, Yokoyama felt
a huge obstacle during this concert.
Yes, please.
Of course I think there is merit to
a livestream concert with no audience.
But you know,
I think we're used to playing in front of
an actual audience.
We already know that atmosphere.
So after experiencing that,
I have to admit that it's irreplaceable.
What made him keenly aware of that
was the skit segment he performed in.
Hey!
What?
-What the heck are you guys doing?!
-Hm?
I came here to tell you
that I'm taking center stage today,
but Green's not here!
So there can't
be a center with four people!
There was no response from the audience,
an essential part of comedy.
I can't say it!
Woohoo!
Furthermore, the next groups
to take on the empty venue
are the Jr. units
Ae! group and Lil Kansai.
Most of their performance
would be awkward skits.
I already talked to Ae! group
and the Kansai Jr. kids.
I told them this is going to be
a really tough fight.
Not having an audience...
How do I put it?
They're doing a skit,
so it's really difficult
without an audience.
JULY 11
Preparation for
the skit show began back in July.
LIL KANSAI
The livestream show performed by
Lil Kansai and Ae! group
would center around skits.
What about the radio calisthenics?
What do you mean?
AE! GROUP
How will they overcome
the obstacle of having no audience?
Ae! group has six members
who also play their own instruments.
They all have distinct personalities.
Yokoyama decided to make use
of that in the skit premise.
How about we take off the sunglasses?
-No, it's too bright.
-Seriously?
Their role is to play idols who get
big heads after growing in popularity.
That's just as irritating.
-The staff must hate you.
-Make up your mind.
Playing the director and second director
who get involved with Ae! group
are two Jr. members picked by Yokoyama
who have yet to be in the limelight.
I'm Okumura.
Please accept my apology
for my delayed introduction.
Once he's like, "Woo,"
you should stand up slowly.
What's your next line?
I look forward to working with you today.
He's starting his line here,
but you do this the whole time.
I look forward to today.
As fledgling idols,
their drive to rise to higher heights
is what motivates them.
Don't look at me and smile.
Okay!
To introduce myself,
I'm the director-assisting
assistant director, or AD,
Yuri Oka.
Your character feels
a bit busy with the lisp.
-Thank you.
-It's not a compliment.
Look, like that!
The two who Yokoyama selected
are working hard.
That's it.
That's hilarious.
It has created an air of competition.
AE! GROUP
SANO MASAYA (18)
What makes me most happy with rehearsal?
I'm happiest when Yokoyama laughs.
So right now I'm a little vexed.
Yokoyama is laughing the most with Oka.
After rehearsal,
when everyone was saying their goodbyes,
he gave Oka a thumbs up.
We really wanted that.
But you know, we came up together.
We're all contemporaries.
Okumura hasn't changed.
Kojima from Ae! group
comments on his contemporaries' hard work.
Yuri was given more lines.
I'm happy he got more funny parts,
but it's like I can't lose to him.
And Okumura has tons of lines, too.
Like the narration.
I guess the director's role
is to keep things moving forward.
So he has a lot of lines,
but he had them all
memorized the next day.
I'd think I would need to read
the lines from the script.
So they make me want to work harder.
Their presence is motivating.
-Good work today.
-You too.
This friendly rivalry
is a tradition that is passed down.
AUGUST 11
It's the day of the livestream skit show.
SHOCHIKUZA
FINAL REHEARSAL
Yokoyama had work in Tokyo,
so they run the final rehearsal
in his absence.
Yokoyama selected Oka
for the assistant director role.
Good work.
And Okumura for the director role.
The members of Lil Kansai
are here today to audition.
Hello!
We're Lil Kansai!
It's nice to be here!
The two of them had just come off stage.
Okumura, Yoko's on the phone.
Hello? This is Okumura.
Good morning. Yes.
Yes.
It was a phone call from Yokoyama
who was watching their rehearsal remotely.
"That was wonderful, everyone."
What happened?
Next time, it's the day of
the empty-venue skit show.
Is this supposed to be fun?
What is Yokoyama's secret plan?
They receive messages from their seniors.
Enjoy yourselves.
Lil Kansai endures their own trial.
How do we showcase
something that only we can do?
We need to work together right now.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto