-The chair dance is for the concert?
-That's right. Yes.
They tend to play around like that.
We're working.
If you talk too seriously,
you'll waste your time.
Look at that.
This isn't the right atmosphere
for a meeting.
Oh, jeez.
Morita!
They were the most
mischievous in the group.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
The Yoyogi First Gymnasium.
1995 NOVEMBER 1 DEBUT
In 1995,
this is where V6 debuted.
Since then, they've always held
their milestone concerts here.
2005 10TH ANNIVERSARY OF DEBUT
2010 15TH ANNIVERSARY OF DEBUT
2015 20TH ANNIVERSARY OF DEBUT
And for the 25th-anniversary
livestream concert,
V6 took the stage here again.
YOYOGI FIRST GYMNASIUM
In the first song,
they intentionally appeared
on an empty stage in different styles.
They used the strengths of streaming well.
"HANE"
The six did their best to
bring their current selves to the fans.
-Good morning.
STAGE DIRECTION MEETING
To be honest, I don't want
people to see the chairs...
A lift will be here
and you'll come down on it.
On this day, they first talked about
how to take advantage of a livestream
combined with prerecorded footage.
I like the dance at the chorus.
How the six of you walk...
V6 KEN MIYAKE (41)
What do you think?
I thought they'd hold microphones.
-But I thought it was nice without them.
-Oh, yeah?
It's better to show
that it's pre-recorded...
Cooler without them.
-Then, no mics for "Right Now."
-Okay, I got it.
And about which song they should perform
in the exclusive ending
for their fan club members.
YOSHIHIKO INOHARA
Yes, after the last song...
-"Full Circle"?
-Right.
"Full Circle"? Well, I'm happy with that.
Ken said, "That'd be a good ending."
In "Full Circle,"
maybe we could walk to the center...
I want something we can only do online...
A slightly mature and sexy ending.
An ending, yeah.
"Full Circle" contains
the ideas of the six members.
OCTOBER
REHEARSALS CONTINUE EVERY DAY
IN PARALLEL WITH MEETINGS
This time, a special visual effect
was to be added to this song as well.
This was to show that the members
were taking the fans' thoughts to heart.
Getting the stars on my side now
Maybe a single star can shine.
It'd be nice if the star doesn't just pass
but gets involved with people.
When the six of us put out our hands,
words will come down,
and they turn out to be fans' wishes.
Their wishes come down onto our hands
and it suggests that we'll make them true.
-I see. Yeah.
-That's the message.
A SAMPLE OF THE EFFECTS WAS MADE
Also, the heart blasts like boom
and that's it, right?
It's sad to see the heart just fade away.
And the font.
The font isn't right.
This is too formal.
Something like handwriting...
Right. Handwriting is better.
Like in letters.
It's the same as the difference between
a typed letter and a handwritten letter.
Even if they both say the same thing.
That's right.
It ended up like this.
"ARU HI NEGAI GA KANATTANDA"
-Good morning.
Can I hear the song?
Sure.
Play it.
THE NEW SONG THAT THE MEMBERS
ASKED KREVA TO WRITE, "CLEAR"
I CAN'T SEE MYSELF, BUT IN YOUR EYES
REFLECTS BRILLIANCE AND THAT'S A MIRROR
HOW THE UNEXPRESSED FEELINGS ARE GIVEN
MY MIND BECOMES CLEAR NOW
I SEE MY PAST SELF
UNMISTAKABLY MY OLD SELF
SEEMS LIKE A STRANGER
FELT LIKE SPACETIME DISTORTED
ARE THERE TWO ME'S?
I STAND STILL
THE WORLD IS COLORFUL TODAY AS ALWAYS
I MUST START MOVING AGAIN SOON
BUT I'M STILL A LITTLE BLUE
I THOUGHT I WAS HOLDING THE WHEEL
THAT EXPERIENCE IS NON-RETURNABLE
I CAN'T EVEN MOVE ON LIKE THIS
SO I'LL START ALL OVER AGAIN
I CAN CHANGE MYSELF
IF I CONNECT WITH YOU AND SEIZE THE DAY
The lyrics turned out so cool.
Oh, these, right? Aren't they awesome?
-What did you think?
-How can anyone think of these words?
I'm so impressed.
This part right here. We really like it.
It's exactly like how we are now.
I WON'T HAVE A DEFIANT ATTITUDE
I'LL OPEN THE DOOR TO NEW POSSIBILITIES
EVEN IF WE CHANGE OUR FORMS
OUR PRIDE WILL NEVER BE LOST
And on the same day,
Morita checked stage settings.
Starting halfway through...
If we make it like this...
If we do that, it's pointless.
-Can you sit closer again?
-One more time.
Take a seat.
I like this better.
Okay. I see.
MORITA MADE THE MEMBERS CLOSER
MIYAKE POSTS "I CONSTANTLY ASK MYSELF"
We asked Miyake what he meant.
In this day and age, people say
it's never too late to start something
no matter how old you are.
But...
For men, their thirties and forties
are sort of a turning point, so if I...
If I want to move on to the next stage,
I can't help but feel that
my forties is my last chance.
I think we all feel that.
What do we do from now?
Who are we living for?
Do we live for someone else?
Or for our own selves?
I've been thinking about it
since I was 30.
I think about it as
a separate thing from the six of us.
I bet the others
individually think about it, too
about how they want to
live their own lives.
That's what I meant when I wrote,
"I constantly ask myself."
What do I want to do?
2020 SEPTEMBER 29
"VS ARASHI" DRESSING ROOM
V6 MEMBERS
Good morning.
Let's do our best.
Oh, jeez.
In September,
Okada started to point
his own camera to the members.
I thought,
"Let's capture things only I can."
I'm the only one who's allowed to do that.
I can only take terrible expressions.
-Only you can take them.
-It's hard.
The six have spent 25 years together.
What was that?
Is it blurry?
No, it's not blurry at all.
Okay, let's do it with the music.
Please play "TL."
For this livestream show,
they dared to take on a great challenge.
Performing their song "TL"
without vocals, just by dancing.
Okay...
In the structure,
I want to show V6's dance
as a work of art.
So maybe like a water burst
or the water goes back, I don't know.
I want something to make people feel
it's moved up another gear
just when they think
it peaked at the dance.
The water should be put in
at the right time or it'll be slippery.
-That could ruin it.
-It'll be very slippery.
When you know it'll be slippery,
you can't dance as hard as you can.
Another thing that I'm wondering about
is whether you should wear shoes
or go barefoot.
Barefoot.
-Are you sure?
-I think it's better.
You mean we'll be barefoot before that?
No, that's why...
-We'll take them off.
-Remove and align them?
-We don't need that bit.
-No?
No, we don't need it.
That's what my father taught me.
Good manners.
Like full of energy...
During the meeting, another thing that
the members were very particular about
was the structure of their visual book.
Whether or not to include
the members' interviews.
Do you really want to include them?
Because it's not a pamphlet, right?
It's a visual book.
I thought people can feel "25 years"
more without words.
I'm sorry, but I think
what we have in mind for this one is not
an image of us that's been fabricated.
We want something more raw,
something that's more revealing.
I want to choose photos that show
how a group of real people made it happen.
Like pictures of us sweating.
In other words, we want to shoot photos
that prove what we've done.
What does it take
to be an idol for 25 years?
There must be something to it.
Okada started taking pictures,
but I think what we need are
photos taken from that kind of distance.
He's at a distance that no one else
can be at because he's a member.
So those photos are special.
Why not use those photos?
These photos when you're taken...
It's like, "Please make me look nice."
So the atmosphere's not the same.
Too close.
Just the way they are now.
COSTUME MEETING
MUSIC STATION DRESSING ROOM
The members were also particular
about their costumes.
It's dark and
because it'd look great with the lights,
metallic colors would be nice,
although it's flashy.
I want you to get rid of the notion
that stage costumes equals sequins.
What kind of image do you have
of idols in sparkly clothes?
-Yeah. What kind of image do you have?
-I see.
You're right. It's hard to answer that.
Nice! That's a nice point.
I know you've worn so many costumes,
but I thought this kind of fabric
would look great.
I think you've never worn this kind.
This fabric has just been made.
They found a fabric
that is both gorgeous and mature.
For example, if we come out in that coat,
and then take it off
to show those gold outfits,
it'll be very dynamic.
How long is it gonna be? Like 10 songs?
It's quite long.
That part is the longest.
It'll be better if we can have
three different styles...
How about putting on a jacket
at some point?
You can do that.
That'll be dynamic like Ken said,
and if we put it back on at some point,
we'll look different again.
That's true.
Or just do without it.
Without changing.
-No change?
-No change.
It'll work if the quality is high.
You're right. That's true.
I think it'll work, too.
But in case it doesn't,
let's make a jacket.
As emergency insurance.
If you think that'll work, let's do it.
Then, let's spend our budget on it.
Budget?
Talking about money?
But it's important.
If we can spend money on it...
-That's it from me. Thank you.
-Thank you.
FITTING SESSION
Their stage costumes are being completed.
I'm picky about my silhouette. Sorry.
Then, they'll change into
pure white costumes.
Getting wet... You'll definitely get wet.
In contrast, "TL" which they'll perform
just by dancing is in all black.
Okada...
was struggling with the costume
on the empty stage at the beginning.
What they want to show people
is the way they are now.
I kind of want...
something that is not fake.
If we're gonna stand there.
I want to make it look like
we're just our normal selves
gathering there to perform
and I want that feeling a little bit more,
which means it's not a matter of pattern
or anything like that.
Is it too much?
With those thoughts...
they gathered here.
Inocchi, could you stand in the center?
25 years ago,
this is where they debuted.
You're perfect now. Wait...
Ken.
Stand in the center.
Your hair's... We need the stylist.
Are you shooting now?
We don't need pictures of me.
Hiroshi!
In the middle.
Okada kept taking pictures of the members,
just the way they were.
Director Okada.
Could you do that later, Director?
Could you do this later?
Next time, I'll give you
as much time as you need.
Sorry.
OCTOBER 19
FILMING THE LIVESTREAM SHOW
Finally, they were about to start filming.
It looks cold!
It's a bit cold.
Okay, remove the steps on the side.
Okay, start rolling.
From the beginning.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
-Cut!
-Okay, cut.
It was just me, sorry.
Oh, it's cold!
It's like a hangout for old men.
The next episode will be
the final episode.
The six kept running towards
their 25th-anniversary show.
We can only do a show like this
this year because of the pandemic.
And the special day came.
Subtitle translation by: Tsuyoshi Koide