This year, October 29.
Yokohama Arena.
On this day,
in a venue shrouded in silence,
there was a group preparing for
a concert to create a new era.
Sexy Zone.
Livestreaming has its own benefits.
All five of us will be there
with that in mind.
So I think it will be
a good concert in its own way.
The tour scheduled to start in March
was canceled due to the pandemic.
After eight months,
an online concert without an audience
was the answer they found.
Nine years since their debut.
I'm under pressure.
I've never not been under pressure.
I've always felt anxiety with this group.
FUMA KIKUCHI (25)
"The next place will be
found by you and no one else."
KENTO NAKAJIMA (26)
And the feelings about
the one year and nine months
that they spent apart from
their teammate on hiatus.
TO THEIR SPECIAL TEAMMATE
The four of us and Matsushima
agreed to give each other some space.
He's like Sexy Zone's...
adhesive, but really
more like a sort of glue.
For the fans who kept waiting,
the five become one.
Here we go.
SO MATSUSHIMA (22)
My hands are so sweaty.
Here, nine years after their debut
as the youngest group ever,
is their real conflict.
Eight tumultuous months until the concert.
Alright, let's pump this up!
Yeah!
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
November, 2011.
Their first song "Sexy Zone"
fueled their debut.
I'm Kento Nakajima!
At their debut,
the eldest, Kento Nakajima, was 17.
Ready to love each other?!
FUMA KIKUCHI
Fuma Kikuchi was 16.
Can I hear your voice?!
I'm Shori Sato!
Shori Sato was 15.
Have you been waiting for us?!
In this venue...
So Matsushima was 13.
...can you make some noise?!
Hello, I'm Marius Yo.
The youngest, Marius Yo was 11.
More!
MARIUS YO
I love you all!
Their average age was just 14,4 years old.
In the history of Johnny's,
they are the youngest group ever to debut.
From 2013, two years after their debut,
they continuously performed on Kohaku.
They were seen as an elite group.
Normally, they'd work for several years
in Johnny's Jr. before debuting
by dancing behind their seniors,
gaining experience.
Sexy Rose.
According to Shori Sato...
Because we started at a very young age,
I was always under pressure.
That was the only way for me.
I couldn't do anything.
"Marius, do it right!"
That was what it was like.
"You mustn't make dance mistakes."
I got that a lot.
I wondered if I was
dragging everyone else down.
That caused a lot of anxiety.
For Matsushima and Marius,
it was less than a year
until they debuted.
Then, in 2018,
something unexpected happened.
FACE OF 24HOUR TELEVISION
Three months after they were the main
personality for 24HOUR TELEVISION...
On November 2018,
Matsushima went on medical hiatus.
Since then, they have been
hoping for Matsushima's return
and continued as a four-man group.
The documentary coverage began March 4.
MARCH 4
The four had ten days before the concert
and were at the height of rehearsals.
It's not your first fitting, is it?
This one is the first.
The design, the materials,
we look at it all.
I think the length...
Maybe make it a bit longer?
With a layered effect,
we can increase the volume and the length.
Yeah, like more volume in the front?
Like make it more similar to Shori's?
Long on half.
Yeah, like this but on the left.
A little longer, with more volume.
For the amount of volume,
it would be better
if it was about the same.
Five, six, seven.
They weren't just busy with constumes.
They also had rehearsals.
The eldest leads the group.
Kento Nakajima.
Bang! And back.
...kind of thing.
Use those movements a bit more.
This movement isn't
the focus of this song.
It's just a base to make everything crisp.
Okay.
During his solo song,
the highlight is this
impeccable dance with Johnny's Jr.
Nakajima is busy appearing
in dramas and variety shows.
At this time, he was shooting
a drama scheduled to air in April.
I was balancing the filming
and rehearsals at the same time.
So I am a little behind the others.
I have to get good results anyway.
I feel pressure and responsibility.
And the youngest, Marius, who is twenty,
is trying a stage routine
he thought of for his solo song.
It's magic.
Marius said he wanted to do it.
How can I put it?
It's a magic trick where
a doll inside a box turns into me.
Marius, who was only 11 when he debuted,
is now contributing to staging.
I get so nervous that I can't move.
The best way to gain confidence
is to just rehearse over and over.
So these ten days are going to
be very important.
Everyone's trying extra hard,
since we're entering our tenth year.
This is their second time
doing a concert as a four-man group.
The tour starts in Fukui,
and goes to nine locations.
POP×STEP!? TOUR.
The song they prepared for the encore
was their debut song, "Sexy Zone."
But within this song,
for Kikuchi who had always
calmly observed the group,
there was a big conflict.
I'm under pressure.
I've never not been under pressure.
I've always felt anxiety with this group.
We can be proud we've lasted ten years.
But we haven't done anything
memorable in the ten years.
We haven't transcended "Sexy Zone."
Transcended our debut song.
"Have we made any memorable songs?"
If you ask someone who's not our fan,
I wonder how many songs they could name.
The place Mr. Johnny gave us,
and the place we find for ourselves.
We have to...
face it and think about how to do that.
That's the situation.
The place they have to find on their own.
This feeling was also shared by Nakajima.
Now that Mr. Johnny is gone...
"The next place will be
found by you and nobody else."
I feel like he's telling us that.
Debuting as the youngest group ever,
they carried the burden of others'
expectations for these nine years.
What we found was not
their glamorous popstar image,
but their own selves
facing reality head-on.
In this way, Shori Sato
prepared for the concert
by increasing his rehearsal time.
The songs as well, on this album...
The new songs are all really hard to sing.
I installed a wireless system
in my home this year.
At my place.
I can't just blast the speakers at home,
but it's a wireless mic
and a system to provide the sound.
So I want to use that to practice at home.
Breaking out of their shells.
Finding a new place.
Each of them felt a determination
leading up to the concert.
MARCH 6
On March 6th, in order to add
something new to their performance,
they came to this place.
We've got something specially made
for our center stage.
It's constructed in a unique way.
And we're like,
"Let's tread those boards."
We've never done this before.
It has a pretty unique movement.
For several years, Kikuchi has been
compiling ideas for concert direction.
Each time, there's a variety
of performances to thrill fans.
And this time, they chose
this stage equipment.
It reaches over ten meters.
Turning!
It leans at an angle while turning.
The audience can see every bandmate,
no matter where they are seated.
Will it be okay?
About the slipping...
On this unstable stage,
they check to see how well they can dance.
So your right leg...
Okay!
How will this machine be used?
This looks scary even from behind.
It's scary.
This time, we'll use tempo
and flashy visuals
to suggest more and more
exciting things will happen.
This'll be the big highlight.
It's a big challenge. If we mess this up...
I'll panic.
And on this day...
The flames are out...
They're all out.
Happy birthday, dear Fuma
Yay!
...birthday to you!
So, are you ready?
Sure. Unlike you...
No, no, no. This was just...
It was just a joke.
We always joke around like this.
I want to have a fun 25th year, too.
I'll make it
an even better year than my 24th.
-Thank you!
-Thanks.
Congratulations.
But the following day,
something unexpected happened.
Due to the novel coronavirus,
the first concert in Fukui was postponed.
Then the national tour schedule
had to be changed.
CONCERT POSTPONED
And the back...
Four months later...
JULY
-Good morning!
Good morning.
Sorry about the masks.
On this day, they got an
important announcement from their staff.
In July, the four were brought together.
We've considered the situation
and as Johnny's and as Sexy Zone,
we'd like to start our tour.
Currently, we plan to begin
on August 21 at Osaka Castle Hall.
That's the current schedule.
Wow.
August 21. The plan to
restart the concerts.
It was the fans who encouraged them.
We made a refund liaison and
handled it as Johnny's representatives.
But 90% of ticket holders said
they wanted to wait
for a Sexy Zone concert.
-Amazing.
-Wow.
They have tuitions and food expenses.
I think it was really tough for them.
-I want to do the concert.
-We do, too.
-Truly.
-We want to do it.
-I really want to.
-Yes.
But the biggest priority
was keeping the fans safe.
Since it'll be summer
and knowing how hot it'll be,
we made this with an open shape.
For an unprecedented situation,
they made strict preventative measures
and planned to tour
from August to October.
90% of them are waiting.
I want to get to them as soon as possible
and show them what we've created.
That was at the top of my mind.
Once again, they begin
the journey to find their place.
Okay, this time it's for keeps.
Roll it!
In the midst of that,
they filmed a music video.
Their 18th single, "RUN."
It was as though the four had
poured their determination into it.
THERE'S NO MEANING IN BEING RIGHT
JUST FIND YOUR OWN ANSWER
WON'T IT END? CAN'T IT END?
WE STILL HAVEN'T MADE ANYTHING LASTING
"We still haven't made anything lasting."
The four couldn't decide on
the placement for the song.
When I think of it as a tour
during the pandemic,
we could finish with "Yuki 100%"
and then reveal "RUN."
I think that would
resonate the most with our audience.
It would leave the biggest impression
if it's after "Yuki 100%" for sure.
The momentum of the group
has to be prioritized, so I think "RUN"
towards the end would feel good.
Run as hard as you can
and cut the goal tape.
I'm all for putting "RUN."
But if we do, we need
some movement don't you think?
So we'll do choreography
for the first chorus,
but with the second chorus,
we could have movement.
Then Nakajima brought up
the other meaning of this song.
You know,
this song also includes
our feelings for So, right?
"Nothing can start without you."
It's a song with a message
to connect to his hope.
This could be that bridge-building song.
This was about Matsushima,
their dear bandmate who is on hiatus.
According to Sato...
Matsushima's having treatment,
and information from outside,
or the things we do
could mean more pressure for him.
The four of us and Matsushima
agreed to give each other some space.
That's what we've been doing.
And this was the t-shirt
they made for the tour.
Each member is holding a can
colored with the member colors.
In his left hand, Marius has
Matsushima's color, the green can.
If we say, "It's Matsushima,"
people might take it the wrong way.
They can take it however they like.
Matsushima's here,
and we're all taking a break together.
We wanted to make that sort of atmosphere.
That's how I see it, anyway.
AUGUST
And then...
Sitting there was...
Did you meet up often?
We weren't like, meeting all the time.
A few times?
Yeah, a few times.
Visiting when we can, type of thing.
Hey, let's go.
Yay!
Woo!
It's So!
Yes. Sorry for being away for so long.
I'm So Matsushima from Sexy Zone.
When we sing it, the meaning
really is mainly about So.
On the next RIDE ON TIME...
Yay!
It's So!
Yes.
Finally, they were five once more.
Behind that were the unspoken feelings
for their bandmate.
He might not come back.
If So is happy that way, then that's okay.
I can't say, "Please, I want to perform
as five. Please come back."
As long as he's healthy.
That's all that matters.
There are places they can find
only as a five-man group.
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka