Please accept my apology
for my delayed introduction.
It was July.
The idols from Kansai Johnny's
were putting on a skit show.
KanJani8's You Yokoyama is directing.
Don't look at me and smile.
KANJANI8
YOU YOKOYAMA (39)
I said to take a break,
not put on the brakes.
The participating groups are Ae! group
comprised of young men in their 20s,
Lil Kansai whose five members
are all still in high school...
LIL KANSAI
...and the Jr. members who include
kids still in grade school.
It's good with cream and chocolate.
Hold on!
Many different generations have
come together, dreaming of stardom.
That's the bond they share.
What makes me most happy?
I'm happiest when Yokoyama laughs.
MASAYA SANO (18)
They make me want to work harder.
Like, I can't lose to them.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
JULY 28 EXPO'70 COMMEMORATIVE PARK
On this day,
over 70 idols born and raised
in Kansai took the stage.
It was to get people excited for the 2025
World Expo that will be held in Osaka.
OVER 70 KANSAI JOHNNY'S GATHER
The biggest reason
for their energy that night
was that they were starving
to get back on stage.
JAPAN TOUR CANCELED
KanJani8
canceled their nationwide tour
due to COVID-19.
TOKYO & OSAKA CANCELED
Johnnys' WEST
canceled their tour
that included dome venues.
And three of the Jr. units
saw their hard-earned spots
in the limelight taken away.
Each day was like fumbling in the dark,
trying to make our way.
We had no direction,
but took it day by day.
It was frustrating.
OSAKA SHOCHIKUZA
To break out of that situation,
they would use their own
Osaka Shochikuza Theatre,
and each group would put on
a livestream show to an empty audience.
EMPTY-VENUE LIVESTREAM
Taking on this immense challenge
were Ae! group and these boys.
Hello!
We're Lil Kansai!
It's nice to be here!
Initially, these two groups
will be performing a joint skit show.
Additionally...
AUG. 11, 12
JOINT SKIT
Each group will put on
an independent concert.
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR. (AUGUST 11, 12)
AE! GROUP (AUGUST 24, 25)
It's their first experience
with no audience.
How can they reach fans
that they can't see?
You know,
I already talked to Ae! group
and the Kansai Jr. kids.
I told them this is going to be
a really tough fight.
Can we pump things up?!
It's up to us!
Let's go!
AUGUST, OSAKA
August.
AE! GROUP
Ae! group is rehearsing
their singing and dancing
at a studio on the outskirts of town.
At this time, many of the members
had other commitments,
so they only had two hours
with everyone together.
And yet...
I'm sorry.
Where were you?
Sorry. I got lost.
One of the members is late.
-This is unforgivable.
-I'm sorry.
He's done the unforgivable.
Make sure you film him, not us.
As a way of punishment.
There was a big road...
-Hurry up, Taisei!
-I'm sorry!
Sorry.
This livestream will be
a big opportunity for them.
They had only toured in Kansai before,
so this would be their chance
for the whole country to see them.
With this livestream,
we're discussing how we can work together
and get as many viewers
as excited as we can.
FORMED 2019
Each member is unique.
Seiya Suezawa is the oldest.
Yoshinori Masakado is a boy of candor.
Ready?
Keita Richard Kusama
has an American father.
Masaya Sano
is a former theater troupe member.
KEN KOJIMA (21)
KEYBOARD
Ken Kojima wanted to become a teacher.
And Taisei Fukumoto is a current
student at a public university.
In some ways,
they have all overcome challenges.
Before the unit was formed,
Fukumoto failed to stand out
among the Jr. members.
2018 FOOTAGE
We still remember how he was always
studying in the training room.
There are idols who do news shows, right?
I want to focus on that area.
Hello! I am Mr. Windshield Wipers.
I will wipe your heart.
KanJani8's Yokoyama was the one
who noticed their personalities.
When their band angle was decided
and Ae! group was formed,
it was Fukumoto's
first time touching a bass.
If your timing is off
during the hook, Taisei...
When you miss your note...
Even now, he stays behind
for extra practice.
When I heard Ae! group would be formed,
I was asked if I was ready to work
hard in entertainment.
I said yes and hung on for dear life.
I honestly don't remember much
from that time.
I was just working desperately
the whole time.
You usually don't carry your instrument
around to interviews, but I did.
I kept playing while
I was being interviewed.
It was like I had to.
The formation of the group
was a turning point for
the vocalist Suezawa as well.
SEIYA SUEZAWA
When we visited Shochikuza on this day,
Suezawa was in his own room.
Excuse me.
Yes! You startled me.
You startled me!
You're alone.
It's my first time.
Shochiku has other green rooms
on the other side as well,
but this is my first time on this side
since joining Ae! group.
We all aspire to get over here.
The big room is for everyone
and these are for group members.
It's only for kids who are in a unit.
So it took about 10 years,
I guess 11 years.
It took 11 years to come to this side.
Making it here makes me realize
that I need to do an even better job.
Thank you.
But right when they got their break,
their stage was taken away
by the COVID-19 pandemic.
Their desire to hurry back
to standing on stage grew stronger.
AUGUST 9
Two days before
the livestream skit show...
After you get everything here,
you can synchronize it...
Nervous energy fills the training room.
Good morning.
Good morning, everyone.
Yokoyama experienced performing
without an audience the day before.
He was keenly aware of the difficulty
of performing
without an audience's reaction.
You have to go with a quick tempo,
or I think this is going to be tough.
A streamed skit
feels long if they don't think it's funny.
I think it's better to cut out
as much as possible.
It'll be easier to watch.
You don't really want to
make them think too hard.
Try to push things together.
Me and Masakado will...
It is trial and error.
Okay, so I'll do something,
and you're like, "That's pathetic."
Should Okumura's cue go
after Masakado's line?
-The cop bit?
-Yeah.
Strange wigs are brought out
for Lil Kansai
who'll be sharing the stage.
It's an inner color ponytail.
KOTARO OKAZAKI (16)
They are idols,
but their priority is
to entertain the audience.
That is the tradition they pass down.
You do skits to bring out
their personalities?
Yes, that's right.
You know,
they can showcase their character.
Kansai Jr. kids will be there tomorrow.
I believe we need
to leverage their talents.
AUGUST 11
FINAL REHEARSAL
It's the day of the show.
With Yokoyama away on work in Tokyo,
they run the final rehearsal without him.
The members of Lil Kansai
are here today to audition.
Hello!
We're Lil Kansai!
It's nice to be here!
I'm the director, Okumura.
And I'm the director's...
Hey!
Something happened while
the smooth-talking Okumura
and the inarticulate Oka
were doing their scene on stage.
Okumura, Yoko's on the phone.
Hello? This is Okumura.
Good morning. Yes.
Yes.
It was a phone call from Yokoyama
who was watching their rehearsal remotely.
"That was wonderful, everyone."
Yes, thank you very much. Goodbye.
Thank you.
He said he wanted more energy.
My articulation is good,
so I can be more outgoing.
Yokoyama took the trouble to call.
Meanwhile,
Ae! group received a message
from a different senior.
I'm thinking this is something
only Ae! group can do.
It was from KanJani8's Yasuda.
It can be what makes people realize
how hard you're working.
What's best is to show them
you're having fun.
So have fun out there.
Okay.
Enjoy yourselves.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Thank you very much.
-That's great.
-Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's time for the big show.
AE! GROUP IS ABOUT TO BRAKE?!
They decide to show themselves
in good spirits.
Is this supposed to be fun?
Could you take off the sunglasses?
Ae! group is playing the part
of idols who get big heads
after growing in popularity.
Your outfits keep getting flashier.
I get recognized everywhere I go.
I'm this show's...
Many different characters interact.
Please accept my apology
for my delayed introduction.
It's fine.
That's so weak.
We'll take a strand of hair
for DNA analysis.
Just one? Please just take it all!
A dad can become a mom.
A mom can become a dad.
It's Mom! It's Dad!
-It's Mom!
-Hold on!
The next day.
AUGUST 24
AE! GROUP INDEPENDENT PERFORMANCE
-Thank you!
The curtains finally close
on an emotional stage.
I was reminded how much
I like being on stage.
I had the realization.
I'm glad I didn't give up.
I suddenly remembered my life a year ago.
Like the feeling of frantically searching
within myself for something.
Remembering that brought back something.
Next is Lil Kansai.
Rock, paper, scissors!
JULY, OSAKA
Yeah!
The day of Lil Kansai's empty-venue show
was drawing closer.
FORMED 2019
These five members
are all high school students
who attend the same school.
Toa Shimasaki, their center.
HIGH SCHOOL 2ND YEAR (17)
Takuya Nishimura, the earnest one.
2ND YEAR (17)
Fuga Onishi, the shy one.
2ND YEAR (16)
Kotaro Okazaki, the easy-going one.
It's intense.
Ruku Toma may be the youngest,
but he has big dreams.
Maybe in seven years.
I say seven but I really
want to do it in five years.
AUGUST 14
For them, having no audience
would be a disorientating ordeal.
DAY BEFORE THE LIVESTREAM SHOW
Please take this seriously.
Are you looking out at the audience?
Sorry, can you do it again?
I looked down.
Don't look at it!
Okay.
Without an audience,
they don't know where to look,
and their eyes drift to the monitor.
Okay.
What's more, it was their first
time as the main act,
and it was their job to lead the kids.
Guys, seriously don't be so lazy.
You're done dancing,
now try climbing down.
The five members were worried.
We'll pause at the dance.
I'm scared to be the MC.
Tens of thousands of people
will be watching. That's scary.
I've been underestimating the MC's role.
Actually doing it is crazy hard.
FORMED 2018
NANIWA DANSHI
On this day, Naniwa Danshi
had their rehearsal after Lil Kansai.
Their performance
was playing in the green room.
Kenty got way cooler.
Nagao's costume is amazing.
What's this costume?
Naniwa keeps pushing
further and further ahead of us.
They're always in front of us.
The gap just got bigger again.
TAKUYA NISHIMURA (17)
We want to do something
that only we can do and Naniwa can't.
-But they're so cool.
-It's really hard.
I can clearly see that we're not as good.
I'm learning how to play the piano now.
I want to play other instruments, too.
I want to be someone who can do anything.
They're doing it as a team.
What is it that they need to do now?
-Good morning.
-Hi.
Who did this?
Toma remembered what
his seniors did for him.
That startled me.
LIL KANSAI
RUKU TOMA (16)
Man.
Right when I first joined,
you know...
Even with the songs
to hype up the audience,
when we were just trainees in the back,
Jo would be like, "Get in front."
He'd come to the back
and tell us to go to the front.
I've always felt that
our seniors all want us to stand there.
If everyone gets to shine,
the show will ultimately benefit.
Shimasaki and Nishimura
went to their juniors.
Remember how I told you
to bring the mic closer?
-Apparently it still sounds a bit fuzzy.
-Okay.
So just energetically yell, "Car!"
If it's a car, shout "Car!"
If it's a dog, shout "Dog!"
-For Charades?
-Yeah.
Just be loud.
As loud as you can.
If it's too quiet,
the audience might be like,
"What's he saying?"
You can be wrong,
or even yell, "I don't know!"
Just give a reaction.
Whatever happens, give it a lot of energy.
The Jr. squad began
practicing in the hall.
Around that time,
Onishi was in the green room.
Want to change something?
Yeah, could I try hopping in to MC?
-Yeah, sure.
-You two go for it.
There is meaning in consciously
challenging one's weaknesses.
These high school kids were starting
to face their role of being the main act.
AUG. 15
DAY OF THE KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR. SHOW
The big day arrives.
Lil Kansai was feeling
the enormous pressure.
We've never had
this level of responsibility before.
But we're the oldest ones this time...
And we also need to make sure
the little ones stand out, too.
We're all one group.
We want to get through this together
and become an even better group.
The little idols
take their shot.
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR. PERFORMANCE
"UME GOIN ON!"
Hello, we're Kansai Johnny's Jr.!
Let's all have a great time together!
"BANG BANG!!"
It's our After School Lil Game Tournament!
Yay!
Here is our category!
Charades!
What's next?
That's hard.
Try making a nice circle like this.
-Takoyaki!
-Correct!
"KANSAI ISLAND"
This tradition has been passed down
so that anyone can shine on stage.
Thank you!
This was fun. Thank you very much!
-Good work.
-Thanks.
It was awesome.
It was really great.
I was moved.
-I mean...
-Really?
I went all out.
-So I'm just exhausted.
-Yeah, true.
This summer, they've successfully
overcome another obstacle.
Good work!
On the next RIDE ON TIME,
it's Johnnys' WEST.
This is tough.
Their challenge
is a midsummer livestream concert.
They strive to go further.
Sometimes I just think to myself,
"Man, I'm alive."
What pushed them
was the grief of losing a big opportunity.
It's the first time I cried over work.
Ain't it great?!
They will get their revenge in Osaka.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto