I was told I had no sense of rhythm.
My little sister started
taking dance lessons,
and I was taken along
to the dance studio to try it out as well.
That's where it started.
It was fun.
"SENNEN MEDLEY"
I really love when I'm dancing
without thinking about anything else,
and there are times that listening
to a song makes me want to dance.
So I love it,
but when I have to think about
how to present it,
I don't exactly hate it,
but I do think it's difficult.
However, once I get past that...
I feel that I'm able to continue
doing this work
because I like receiving the praise
and applause from the fans.
I'd say that it drives me
to aim higher even now.
Yeah.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
OCTOBER 10, 2020
It's opening day for Travis Japan's play,
Torajya Ninjapan.
Make sure you share this
with anyone who needs it.
-Master!
-What is it, Master?
-She gave me the best salt.
-Salt?
It really recharges you.
-For real?
-It's crazy.
Try it if you ever twist an ankle.
-Seriously, thanks.
-I twisted my ankle!
30 MINUTES TO CURTAIN
It's been 225 days since
Shinbashi Enbujo last had an audience.
As they took safety measures,
the moment finally arrives.
I guess you don't get nervous.
I really don't get nervous.
That's impressive.
-I'm not nervous.
-What are you then?
I just feel energized.
SHIZUYA YOSHIZAWA (25)
-I might be too pumped.
-I see.
Yara mentioned it before,
but we shouldn't try so hard.
That really is the case.
We should stay composed
to keep our performance relaxed.
Then the audience can relax too.
Right.
This is tough.
It is.
The third floor is such a pain.
I might get more tired from this
than the trampoline.
Ow.
KAITO NAKAMURA (23)
Are you over your exhaustion?
No. It's bad.
Huh?
I'm worried about my legs.
Your legs?
-You might get a cramp?
-Yeah.
I didn't get to take
a cold bath yesterday.
I see.
So I think my legs are still tired.
Crap, this is bad.
5 MINUTES TO SHOWTIME
Okay.
Yeah!
It's opening day.
Let's avoid any injuries
and deliver a good performance.
Yeah!
You guys ready
to make it through another day?
You bet!
-All right!
-Let's go.
-Don't try too hard.
-Okay!
Have fun.
TORAJYA NINJAPAN 2020
ACT ONE
Okay!
The play's first act
is centered around the drama,
while the second act is centered
around the dance numbers.
The first act
is about an hour of
non-stop acrobatics and action.
It is a performance
that pushes them to the limit.
My sons, you must never raise
your hand against the meek.
Understood?
Yes, Father!
We...
This will likely become a familiar sight
by the time the show ends its run.
...please teach us!
Father, we will use these powers
to become the legendary Torajya!
We will all get through any hardships
together as you wish, Father.
My sons...
Yet they will stand on the stage again
and give it everything they have.
Hey!
NOVEMBER 2020
Get Kaito!
Genta's open!
Damn it!
-Kaito!
-Hey!
Corner kick.
Doing this is nice too.
You guys went all out.
I'm beat.
You can't help it.
You just start playing get caught up.
Damn!
They underestimated us!
This is fun.
I spend more time with them
than I do with family.
We're together when we work,
but it's not a problem spending
days off together either.
Time we spend in private
does affect our relationship on the job.
Enjoyment is built
during your time off work.
You only live once.
You never know when you'll lose this time.
You have to enjoy each day
with every fiber of your being.
I know it's cheesy.
Although, I think the obvious
is really important.
The more I blur between
my public and private life,
the longer I can be myself.
You know?
The play enters the second act.
ACT 2
Only three numbers remain.
It seemed things were going smoothly,
but their fears proved true.
Everyone cramped up.
-Cramped up?
-Yeah.
Shime and Kaito Nakamura.
I know how they feel.
KAITO NAKAMURA
Kaito Nakamura shared his concerns
before showtime.
He soldiered on while concealing
his cramped leg.
RYUYA SHIMEKAKE
Ryuya Shimekake
also experienced some trouble.
During the first act on the trampoline...
He hurt his neck after failing a landing.
Let's not do the spinning.
In consideration of their condition,
they hastily cut out
a number of sequences.
Does everyone know this?
-Yes.
Are you okay with jumping?
I'm not sure.
We're a team. It's okay.
However, the next song "Volcano"
is an intense dance number with
a big moment when they jump in unison.
They cannot cut out this jump sequence.
The decisive moment comes
as they stand on stage.
-Bath time.
-Yes.
Go take a bath.
AFTER THE SHOW
-Sorry.
-Oh, whoa!
TOMOYUKI YARA
You're allowed
to laugh in situations like this.
Sorry.
-How did you do it?
-Trampoline.
Right, the trampoline. That rascal, huh?
-Yeah, that's the one.
-Yeah.
-Your robot was really good though.
-That's true.
Man, I look so ridiculous.
Ow.
It hurts.
It was fun though.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I hope this helps people
get through another day.
Even with their masks on,
you could still tell
how happy everyone was.
It really made me aware of
how grateful I am to the others.
Please come in.
Just don't show my lower half.
I had no idea this was here.
I always come here alone.
I see.
Wait...
Whatever, it's just us guys here.
You know...
it was just so frustrating.
But I mean,
they could have said
I didn't need to go out.
However, the guys suggested
changing things or skipping certain parts
to compensate and highlight
our other strengths.
It's really nice how they helped me.
It really made me feel like
I'm not alone with this group.
It made me want to work even harder.
It was fun, and it felt good.
I could really tell
how happy the fans were.
This was only made possible...
because of the efforts everyone put in.
Every little thing does help.
Getting to see an audience for the first
time in a while,
I actually cried during "Together Now."
I was just overwhelmed with happiness.
You know...
I've probably flipped around
30 to 50 times.
I can feel it taking its toll,
but it's not like I can say
that I can't move anymore.
I can't be crying about it.
I almost need to be the one
pushing everyone else.
It may add pressure on me,
but I personally find it fun.
I'm not alone after all.
There are the other members,
so I do it for them and for myself.
-Great work out there.
-Thanks.
It feels like the closing day.
Right?
During "Together Now"...
Yes?
You were crying, weren't you?
You caught me.
Yeah, but you know...
I don't know.
Whenever I accomplish something,
I want to enter that state of mind.
Being able to see the people
you haven't been able to...
there's something
that really builds up inside.
I'll need to give it my all
until the 27th.
You think you can?
Well...
I have the guys.
I'm not in this alone.
Between the seven of us,
we can equally split our responsibilities,
so I feel there's less of a burden.
I feel like I can give it my all.
Until the day they take the stage again,
they have each other.
That alone is what makes
their ability for expression limitless.
The next RIDE ON TIME
is a special edition.
Sexy Zone celebrated
their tenth anniversary this year.
Sexy Zone is a group that can turn
a crisis into an opportunity.
Each one of us wanted to find
a new side to ourselves
that we haven't seen before.
An obstacle they must overcome.
We are in a rough shape...
This is where the hard work begins.
Rather than ten years of nothing,
we have so much to talk about
from the past ten years.
I think that's a wonderful thing.
An anniversary
that brings people together.
Sexy Zone!
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto