Please begin!
On this day, the choreography
for this group's new song was shown.
Sensei, I'm excited!
Been a while since we did your dance.
-I want this exact.
-So it's this way?
That part's fine.
The idol group, Snow Man.
This way.
Do this four times.
Try to keep your left hand wide and loose.
And we want the head going this way.
We want the left hand around here.
-Okay!
-This way.
I think it's tilted. Like this.
This here shifts.
The style is like this.
Then within a matter of minutes...
They've nearly mastered the choreography.
It's cooler when we're in sync.
We are Snow Man!
-Yay!
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Let's get this started!
In January 2020,
Snow Man made their long-awaited debut.
Their greatest weapons
are their acrobatic moves
and outstandingly high dance skills.
Their debut single which
had been awaiting release, "D.D.,"
sold over a million copies.
With those polished skills,
they're now trying to make their way
to the forefront of their generation.
Good evening!
Although rare for a first year group,
their namesake show had begun.
The longest residing member has 15 years
of experience as a Johnny's Jr.
They had finally grasped their debut.
Things have changed a lot.
There are times I find myself thinking,
"Oh, I've made my debut."
Sometimes.
From here on,
I think we have infinite possibilities.
The things people say are impossible
or a bit difficult...
I kind of want to challenge those.
What awesome cherry blossoms!
Everyone had been imagining
a spectacular first year like that.
Good morning!
In March, their introductory debut concert
had been decided,
and their rehearsals had begun.
Oh, there's a camera!
Huh?
However...
Hey, sorry, everyone.
Fujii has been leading until today,
but for various reasons
there's been a personnel change...
...to HiHi Jets.
You're kidding!
-No way! Seriously?
-Stolen by our juniors!
One of their choreography staff had
been reassigned to their juniors' group.
But this is their reaction.
It's the one from YouTube.
Their debut concert
was to consist of 14 performances
at three arenas.
In addition, visits to Bangkok,
Singapore, Jakarta,
and Taipei had been scheduled
for an Asian tour.
HIKARU IWAMOTO (27)
Hikaru Iwamoto is the group's leader,
and also choreographs the dances at times.
TATSUYA FUKAZAWA (28)
Tatsuya Fukazawa is trusted by the others
as the group's organizer
and has a comical personality.
Oh, baby, baby!
DAISUKE SAKUMA (28)
Daisuke Sakuma is the group's mood maker.
You go like this and if you do that...
His acrobatic skills are guaranteed.
Think of it as pulling in the legs.
RYOHEI ABE (27)
Ryohei Abe holds
a meteorologist certification
and is a regular on quiz shows.
Well... I was able to win.
But honestly, playing with
the legends of the quiz show world
and winning quizzes like that
makes me really happy.
Shota Watanabe.
He is such a beauty enthusiast,
women's magazines with his cover...
have sold out.
The highlight of this song
is our lip choreography and leg movements!
Time's up!
Was that 10 seconds?
RYOTA MIYADATE (27)
Ryota Miyadate performs
in historical plays and Kabuki.
He is irreplaceable in Japanese theatrics.
And then there's the three
who just joined last year.
Ren Meguro, who also models
for fashion magazines,
burns with silent passion.
REN MEGURO (23)
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven!
-It's all spirit.
-Backflips are about spirit. 98% spirit.
Then we have...
What happened?!
...the one who always spreads laughter
in the group, Koji Mukai.
Coming from Kansai Johnny's Jr.,
he moved to Tokyo alone.
I feel like there's a lot of meaning
in being able to return to
Osaka as part of Snow Man.
I want to be told, "Koji you're amazing!"
RAUL (AGE 17)
And the current high schooler, Raul.
He joined Snow Man at 15 and was
suddenly entrusted with the center role.
He never shies away from
his seniors or veteran staff either.
Now, immediately change T-shirts
and disinfect with alcohol.
When the idea was raised to create a film
that would show fans their appreciation...
If we wanna show our appreciation,
I think we can express it
through our song.
Like as an approach.
As one way to convey it, yeah.
The debut concert's stage had dynamically
scaled up from their Johnny's Jr. days.
The giant monitor was to be lit up
with the latest video technology.
However, during this time,
the effects of COVID-19
were already creeping up on them.
Earlier this morning,
Mr. Abe said the state of emergency...
-He declared it?
-It could be declared on the 13th...
Oh, he's deciding on the 13th?
Right.
Amid the situation,
was this day's filming of
the music video for their new song.
-Thank you for being here.
-Likewise, thank you.
Okay, please begin.
Please begin!
This is their second single,
"KISSIN' MY LIPS."
They were supposed to introduce this song
at their debut concert.
-Koji.
-Yes?
You may be early in the interlude, Koji.
-Ah, the rap?
-Yeah.
And one, two, three, four!
-Oh, it's this!
-It's probably this.
-It might be a bit stiff.
-Ah.
I see now.
For Snow Man's stage,
dancing is their lifeline.
-This?
-Yeah.
At this moment, the members
had already been notified of the news.
JOHNNY'S MARCH PERFORMANCES CANCELED
SANSPO, MARCH 17, 2020
SNOW MAN'S 14 PERFORMANCES
OF THEIR FIRST ASIAN TOUR
AFTER THEIR CD DEBUT...
Well, it's unfortunate,
or more of a shock.
It was our debut concert...
Well, in that sense,
I really wanted to do it.
Well, I was seriously saddened by it.
My mom was even planning
to come watch too.
Well, more than feeling sorry,
I feel sad about it.
On the other hand, Miyadate...
I feel like this is typical for Snow Man.
Because Snow Man has experienced a lot
and overcome many tough times,
and now we've sort of hit
yet another even bigger wall.
If we can't break through it,
even if we make our debut in many things,
I think... we'll be defeated.
-You see this as a test?
-That's right.
And so, they entered their long,
stay-at-home life.
In their important debut year,
they had to come to a halt.
APRIL 7 - STATE OF EMERGENCY DECLARED
Snow Man was formed in 2012
with six members.
They built extensive experience in Jr.,
diligently polishing their skills,
but repeatedly had their debut
preceded by others,
and were left feeling frustrated.
SHOTA, TATSUYA, HIKARU
RYOHEI, DAISUKE, RYOTA
Later, even voices saying that their debut
would be impossible could be heard.
JANUARY 2019
Fukazawa describes
how he felt at the time.
I've thought about giving up
on many occasions.
I've thought about giving up a lot.
All of my previous groups
broke up in the end,
so I've always wanted
to protect this group.
JANUARY 2019
However, the tide turned
in January last year.
A few years ago, I would really never
have believed a day like this would come.
Takizawa Kabuki ZERO.
"HIRARI TO SAKURA"
On the stage known as the gates
to success for a Jr.,
Snow Man was chosen as the leads.
"KUMIKYOKU"
TAKIZAWA KABUKI
"GOEMON ZERO"
Goemon!
Do not move!
Say what?!
"TAIKO"
The show blends various kinds
of Japanese culture.
My wig!
We're wasting time.
That stage polished them
both physically and mentally...
and Snow Man made their debut
with nine members.
They were looking forward
to that show this year as well.
JANUARY 2020 DEBUT
The performance had been canceled,
but then it was relabeled
as Takizawa Kabuki ZERO 2020 the Movie,
and was decided to be released as a film.
TAKIZAWA KABUKI ZERO 2020 THE MOVIE
BASED OFF THE SAME STAGE PERFORMANCE,
TO BE RELEASED WITHIN THE YEAR
-Morning!
-Good morning!
Good morning!
In July, the members finally gathered
after ending a long stay-at-home period.
He's grown so much!
Just vertically, so I'm doing a bit of...
No, horizontally too!
You need to work out.
I was finally able to meet everyone
and see their faces.
That alone made me happy.
I think that was probably our time
to build up our own strengths.
This day's lesson was for "Kumikyoku"
where they dance for nearly nine minutes.
Opposite of where you're pulled back...
Um, your left shoulder blade
goes the other way.
There's a bit of a mutual pull and...
Due to the stay-at-home break,
their bodies won't move as freely.
Like this... Yeah, that's good!
On top of that,
their face masks obstruct their breathing.
It gets hard to breathe halfway through.
-Can we start?
-Please!
They decide to have a run-through.
-Let's do it for real then.
-Okay.
Okay.
That was dangerous!
I slipped on someone's sweat.
You okay?
Should we do it again?
Man, we have to bust our butt again.
Well, I'm surprised
at how much I can't move.
My body's screaming in pain.
I'm surprised how I was able
to move this much a year ago.
I feel like I have someone else's body.
That's how panicked I felt, yeah.
It's about to be a tough battle.
Don't forget that we decided
the numbers today.
Okay.
Late July.
SHINBASHI ENBUJO THEATRE
The filming had begun
for Takizawa Kabuki ZERO 2020 the Movie.
Everyone good? On standby?
Ready, begin!
This sword battle performed
by all nine of them is "Kyukenshi."
The members' expressions
and moves are captured more dynamically.
Cut!
-Isn't fatigue building?
-Well, lactic acid sure builds up.
-We're going on next.
-Yes.
See you.
And this is the video that was filmed...
"KYUKENSHI"
And this jump...
Ten days before filming,
Sakuma was here rehearsing.
DECEMBER 2018
This is amazing!
Acrobatic moves
are his ultimate specialty.
Try to feel how it goes once.
For Sakuma, there was a contraption
he had to master this time.
-Whoa!
-Like that just now.
Try not to kick it yourself.
If you try to kick it, the timing
will be off and you'll miss the lift.
If the timing isn't correct,
it could lead to serious injuries.
-I'll try it.
-Okay.
All right!
-Here I go!
-Okay.
You'll hurt your knees...
It completely got me.
You mean like this?
Yeah, like that.
Here I go.
I see!
Ugh, I don't understand! What is this?
Here I go.
Hm, I still don't understand.
I can't grasp it at all.
-Try it a few times to get the feel of it.
-True.
As Miyadate watches over...
Okay!
He succeeds on his thirteenth try.
That one was great!
That one was nice!
Yes.
One more time.
-Please, go ahead.
-Here I go.
-Yeah!
-Nice!
Yay.
Is it easier if we lift it?
I think so.
It depends on how it feels for you.
Like, whatever you do in acrobatics
is always scary at first, you know.
And as you get used to doing it,
your fear starts to fade.
To overcome your fear
is probably most important.
Well, in my case, I happen
to be able to dance and do acrobatics,
but I really suck at sports.
I'm a slow runner.
I can't swim freestyle either.
Tomorrow, I'll be walking like this.
Each one of the members has
been polishing their own unique skills.
At last, the day to film
that one performance has come.
JULY
This is the highlight of Takizawa Kabuki,
"Fukkin-daiko."
With only their abs to hold them up,
they have to continuously
beat taiko drums.
Roll camera.
Rolling.
Action!
The torturous moment has begun.
On the next episode,
the filming reaches its climax.
Raul displays a chilling performance.
Can you do the same moves?
No, I can't.
Age is kind of like a title...
And to the climax.
Izo!
I'm climbing up.
I wonder how I look.
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi