Ready, action!
They have overcome countless difficulties.
Takizawa Kabuki ZERO 2020 the Movie.
"HIRARI TO SAKURA"
The leading roles are played by
the nine-person group, Snow Man.
"KUMIKYOKU"
The stage play they had performed
became a movie last year,
giving birth to a never-before-seen
form of entertainment.
"NEZUMI KOZO JIROKICHI"
"FUKKIN-DAIKO"
They have made their way
to the forefront of their generation.
Nine years ago,
Snow Man was originally formed
with six members.
They spent years training,
and there were whispers saying
their debut was impossible.
However, two years ago,
three new members joined
and they made their debut.
But they were put to the test again.
REN MEGURO, KOJI MUKAI, RAUL
PERFORMANCES CANCELED
What was to be their memorable debut
concert and Asia Tour scheduled in March,
was canceled due to the pandemic.
SNOW MAN'S 14 PERFORMANCES OF THEIR
FIRST ASIA TOUR AFTER THEIR CD DEBUT...
The canceling of a debut tour...
is something I don't think
has ever happened.
All our fans were waiting for it.
We were ready to do it any time too.
And after waiting for seven months...
-Wow!
-Excellent!
The time had finally come.
The first day of our debut concert!
Yeah!
-Ready to get pumped up?!
-Yeah!
Here we go!
Alright!
Let's do this!
These days showed
the undefeated spirit of Snow Man.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
MARCH 2020
The debut concert's rehearsals started
in March of last year.
Good morning!
-Give me a hand!
-You kind of changed.
The very first order of business
was a briefing on the stage costumes.
The part they were most concerned
about was...
I think there's a lot going on
in the waist area for many of us.
This is when we're moving a lot.
I think if we have less attached,
our dancing stands out more.
That's true, yes.
Making that the priority may be good.
Having the dancing, the moving...
-As the main focus?
-Yes.
More so that the moves can be seen...
Yes.
Okay.
For Snow Man,
the dancing is their lifeline.
What's essential to their dance
is their acrobatic moves.
You go like this and if you do that...
One of the key people
in those performances is Sakuma.
Think of it as pulling in the legs.
My arms are stopping here, right?
Yeah, so right now, this is...
DAISUKE SAKUMA (28)
You're not jumping backwards,
so your body isn't moving back.
It's probably my arms.
HIKARU IWAMOTO (27)
Iwamoto is also a key person.
You go up to here by yourself,
but Koji will spin you
the rest of the way.
I understand the image
of what you're saying.
The cancellation of their debut concert
was announced just moments later.
RYOTA MIYADATE (27)
Miyadate put into words the emotions
stirring within their hearts.
I feel like this is typical for Snow Man.
Because Snow Man has experienced a lot
and overcome many tough times,
and now we've sort of hit
yet another even bigger wall.
If we can't break through it,
even if we make our debut in many things,
I think... we'll be defeated.
-You see this as a test?
-That's right.
SEPTEMBER 2020
September.
Their debut concert was decided
to be held with no audience,
and their rehearsals resumed.
Recalling it is easy, so let's do it.
No, I don't think we remember it.
One and two! Three and four!
And five and six, seven and eight!
Wasn't it this?
Oh, it's this!
-Go home!
-Once more!
Koji is center and...
I'm this way.
And...
It's the one where you start dancing
from the middle...
The effects of a half-year break
are indeed great.
Even so, there was one mission
Fukazawa wanted to accomplish.
It was regarding a concert program
that included their senior groups' songs.
And from here, there's that kind of...
I want to do a concert
using just our own songs.
I was wondering
how everyone felt about it.
-I see.
-Right.
If we can go this far, let's do it.
If so, we don't have to worry
about the video.
Then I'll go ahead and...
Since the journey to their debut was long,
they have a lot of original songs.
This one is in the beginning, right?
By structuring the program
with just their own songs,
they wanted to share that journey
with their fans.
Yes. So...
-So that's our full set?
-Yes.
Performing only Snow Man's songs
at a debut concert
will also become a hot topic.
Thankfully, we were given many songs.
So I think we can probably give
a very Snow Man-like,
good presentation of ourselves.
The concert was now just a day away.
The stadium was lit up
with each of the members' colors.
OCTOBER 21, 2020
REHEARSAL
Oh, what's all this?
-I'm honestly excited!
-Awesome!
The display alone is insane!
It's super pretty!
Watch your step.
The stage set had dynamically scaled up
from their pre-debut days.
Now, let's see.
Whoa!
-Fire!
-Woo!
-Awesome!
Thank you very much!
It's blazing!
The stadium's center walkway
to the stage are lifts.
Amazing!
They each even get their own.
Everything was moving smoothly
toward the concert.
However...
Sakuma who is the key person
in the acrobatics is acting strange.
Where are our girlfriends?
Which leg was it? The right?
I sprained it.
-You got stuck?
-What?
The gap?
-Yeah, I got in the gap.
-Ah, that.
Ugh, damn it!
We are the nine guys, Snow Man!
He could only watch over the acrobatics...
Yeah!
What is with that dance?! Do it right!
Good work, everyone!
Thank you very much!
See everyone tomorrow!
Please excuse us!
Now I've done it. Everyone, I apologize!
No, it's no problem.
I apologize!
I'll seriously do my best with this!
Is it okay to film?
Yes.
Injuries. I don't like injuries.
I don't want people to know my injuries.
For the fans, it doesn't really matter,
you know?
Um, they're paying to see us...
so me getting hurt may be sort of rude.
Well, I was honestly waiting
very eagerly for it.
Seriously.
But even if you push yourself now,
it'll be no good if it gets worse.
That's true.
So that's where the other members
will seriously help out.
They'll take all sorts of measures
to accommodate me.
I'm grateful for them. Seriously.
It can't be helped. It happens.
I always do this
right before the actual show.
It's typical.
Injuries are bound to happen.
That's how difficult your role is.
"Tomorrow, I'll go as far as I can."
That's what he decided.
OCTOBER 22, 2020
DAY OF THE DEBUT CONCERT
-Smile for this last one.
-Yay!
It's the day of their debut concert.
Okay, thank you.
Alright! Let's do this!
The first day of our debut concert!
Yeah!
-Ready to get pumped up?!
-Yeah!
-Will you all enjoy it?!
Let's all do this with a smile.
Here we go!
Alright!
Let's do this!
Let's do it!
OCTOBER 22, 2020
Let's get this party started!
-Daisuke Sakuma!
-Woo!
Snow Man!
-Snow Man!
Wow!
Thank you!
The nine of them each gave
their whole heart to that stage.
I had the dream of becoming
Japan's best entertainer in the future...
and came to this agency.
And now, I am a member of this Snow Man...
having our debut concert.
Many people said it was impossible.
"You can't do it."
"You'll be a backup dancer forever."
"Snow Man is too timid."
"Even when there's a chance to MC
at their senior groups' concerts,
everyone just steps back."
But... those timid guys are now
proudly standing on stage as the main act.
I... have a habit of keeping
all my problems to myself.
I never discuss them with anyone...
Uh...
But despite that...
The really... insecure parts of me
were supported by my fellow members,
and they've really saved me.
There were really rough times
when I was a Johnny's Jr. for 15 years,
but now I'm extremely happy.
When I see everyone
standing here like this
they look very dependable.
Right now, my throat
and body are worn out...
and the skin on my feet is worn out too.
But still...
we managed to get through these nine
performances that we gave our all to.
It sure was
a once-in-a-lifetime debut concert.
To our dear staff who support us daily
and above all,
to all of you who always support us...
we wanted to show our appreciation
through our performance.
After joining Snow Man...
my way of thinking and my attitude
toward entertainment really changed.
That was, more than anything,
thanks to these eight members
who've shown me a great example.
I've come to realize
that these eight members
are the reason why I am able to
perform here like this now.
Snow Man is just awesome!
Snow Man.
Thank you very much for today!
Thank you very much!
Now, it's showtime! Please go on.
Please go on!
At the end of the year,
Snow Man's schedule was growing busier.
"WA NI NATTE ODOROU"
Thank you very much!
And now, they were about to stand
on the stage of their dreams.
However...
DECEMBER 25, 2020
SPONICHI
They had to withdraw from Kohaku.
Miyadate's infection with
COVID-19 had been identified.
The nine members had hit
yet another big wall.
SNOW MAN BACKS OUT
OF NEW YEAR'S PERFORMANCE
JANUARY 6, 2021
And so, the new year started.
Good morning.
Happy New Year.
After finishing the two weeks
of quarantine,
the members finally got together.
Good morning!
Did you watch Kohaku?
I watched Kohaku.
I made sure to watch all of it.
It should have been difficult
for SixTONES to contact us,
but before they went on air,
they went out of their way
to tell us that they'd work hard
for Snow Man too.
That made me very happy.
And, well, it's true that we actually
couldn't go on Kohaku,
but I'm sure SixTONES was able
to pick up on Snow Man's feelings...
and they expressed them
for us on Kohaku's stage.
That's what I thought watching it.
Yeah, so...
I thought I should watch it and I did.
Hello! We're Snow Man!
Yay!
Snow Man's second year after debuting
began from their sweat-dripped
rehearsal room again.
Let's have another good year.
"NAMIDA NO UMI WO KOETE IKE"
I've always wanted to protect this group.
It's smashing good weather!
That's why my back
is killing me right now.
The things people say are impossible...
I kind of want to challenge those.
Seriously, you only live life once.
The nine who never give up their dreams
sail beyond the sea of tears.
Snow Man!
The next episode features the seven-member
Johnny's Jr. unit, Travis Japan.
It's their second year on the main stage.
What is the new challenge they face
in their dance performance?
"You're with Johnny's, right?"
"You can't dance, right?"
As members of Johnny's, we can't have
people like that underestimating us.
Dance, huh...
That's all I've ever done.
We need to shine brighter,
and confidently stand on stage.
It's not like I can say
that I can't move anymore.
I can't be crying about it.
Pǎo bù!
Wait, I know this one.
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi