That had truly been a debut fit
to be called a great success.
JANUARY 2020 DEBUT
The nine-person idol group, Snow Man.
Their greatest weapon is their outstanding
physical abilities and dance skills.
Following their debut single,
their second hit, "KISSIN' MY LIPS,"
also sold over a million copies.
From here on,
I think we have infinite possibilities.
The things people say are impossible
or a bit difficult...
I want to kind of challenge those.
The group's leader, Hikaru Iwamoto,
also choreographs the dances at times.
The center role is filled
by the high schooler
who just joined last year,
Raul.
RAUL (17)
The group's organizer is Tatsuya Fukazawa.
TATSUYA FUKAZAWA (28)
With his serene voice,
Shota Watanabe is assigned solos.
SHOTA WATANABE (28)
Mr. Handsome's here.
He's a good guy.
KOJI MUKAI (26)
These two also just joined last year.
Koji Mukai from Kansai Johnny's Jr.
and Ren Meguro, who's also
a fashion magazine model.
Later, he goes the comedy route...
REN MEGURO (23)
He's smooth, right?
Ryota Miyadate also performs
in historical plays and Kabuki stages.
RYOTA MIYADATE (27)
As a certified meteorologist,
Ryohei Abe is also in great demand
on quiz shows.
RYOHEI ABE (27)
Yes.
I hope it comes out well.
Thank you very much.
Smashing weather!
And the group's mood maker is...
It's smashing good weather!
Daisuke Sakuma.
Oh, awesome!
I just wanna sunbathe!
What awesome cherry blossoms!
These nine have begun to face the wall
they've hit during the COVID-19 crisis.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Takizawa Kabuki ZERO 2020 the Movie.
It blends various kinds of Japanese
culture into the ultimate entertainment.
On last year's stage,
Snow Man played the lead roles
and were scheduled to again this year,
but it was canceled due to the pandemic.
For all the anticipating fans,
the stage play would be made into a movie.
The nine members
each faced the filming with
their own feelings in their hearts.
July.
Good morning! Thanks for coming.
Rehearsals started after
their long stay-at-home life ended.
The most concerning problem
was that their stamina had declined.
-Can we start?
-Please!
Should we do it again?
Man, we have to bust our butt again.
Don't forget that we decided
the numbers today.
Okay.
While many members
are in their late twenties,
there is one who is only 17 years old.
The current high schooler
who joined Snow Man last year, Raul.
-Everyone ready?
-Yes.
Five, six, seven...
During the stay-at-home period,
did you train on your own?
Well for Kabuki...
It was right during that period
that Kabuki was decided.
I did whatever workouts I could at home.
I see.
I would run outside while
wearing a mask pretty often.
You ran?
I ran. I just kept running.
Raul has been on stage since he was young.
MAITO RAUL MURAKAMI
When he was in the sixth grade,
he won second place
in a global dance competition.
BORN JUNE 27, 2003
Afterwards, he entered the agency
and performed in a different unit,
but his expressive dance style
was acknowledged
and he was chosen to be Snow Man's center.
MARCH 2019
This is Raul when he had
just joined Snow Man last year.
He was made the center
at only 15 years old.
-Here we go, next.
-Okay.
But the speed of his growth was fast.
And at the filming
that took place this day...
Okay, let's begin filming
if everyone's ready.
...Raul displayed a chilling performance
unbelievable for a 17 year old.
Will Fukka and the others
go into Number 3?
Abe, Fukazawa, and Raul's original dance.
Raul's solo part is all freestyle.
Rolling. Music in three, two...
Cut!
And cut! Remember those poses, everyone.
Um, Raul, in the last cut,
your right hand...
Your right hand was raised
when you finished.
-So you'll start from when it's raised.
-Okay.
Okay, then.
Please start with the hand raised.
RECREATING THE MOVES FOR EDITING
-Okay, looks very good. Once more please.
-Okay.
Once again...
This is the part of the hook
where it gets the most emotional.
And cut!
Um, let me make sure,
but can you do the same moves?
No, I can't.
-You can't, huh?
-No.
Right.
The director was forced
to rethink the filming plan.
You can whatever you want now.
Cuts don't matter,
so do it in one shot please.
Okay.
Music in three, two...
Age is seriously, in a sense,
just a title and that's it.
"You can't bring out certain elements
at this age."
I've never really thought of things
like that before.
Like, yeah,
I express what I want to express,
and I just work hard,
so that people can enjoy it.
Cut! Okay!
And cut!
You danced as you felt it,
so you can't recreate it.
I said I couldn't do it, because I can't.
Yeah.
Well, but I think this song
is where a woman...
I don't have a woman.
Um, so I think of an imaginary woman.
I imagine my favorite woman.
Oh?
I want to be in love with her,
but I can't.
Like I think, "How come?"
-But that's the same with me.
-Right?
Yeah.
Why are you chiming in?
Same with me.
When I sing, that's how I feel.
But Fukka has a woman.
He just needs to imagine her.
Ah, a woman? I have one.
She's called a fan.
You...
He gave it away.
You sure know me!
And at last, one of the biggest highlights
of Takizawa Kabuki ZERO...
"Fukkin-daiko."
Holding their bodies up with their abs,
they beat the taiko drums.
-Okay, once we reset we'll start.
-Okay.
All right.
Now, let's go into the actual take.
Okay.
Rolling. Ready, action!
"FUKKIN-DAIKO"
And cut!
My hand's peeled.
It hurts so bad.
Nice.
It's the same on my right.
Um, we're going to do
the same thing once more.
From a different angle.
-Okay.
Unlike a stage performance,
it won't end after one run.
That is the tough part about a movie.
...we'll run it three times
so get some rest now.
Okay.
Okay, good!
However, the filming isn't over yet.
Meguro is on the stage set device
along with Mukai...
and Sakuma.
These three have an even tougher pose.
-Ready?
-Yes.
Okay, let's do it.
Rolling. Ready, action!
The device continues to spin.
And it continues to recline further down.
And cut!
Please pull them back up.
Watch your heads.
Koji, you need a trash bag?
I'm okay!
Are you okay?
Yes!
The actual recording is finished,
but right now...
Iwamoto had a bitter experience
on this stage as well.
January of last year.
It happened during
the first Takizawa Kabuki ZERO.
This is super scary.
-Dropping you down now.
-Okay.
During the Nezumi Kozo rehearsal...
That was close!
You've taken quite a chunk out.
-This is a test of endurance.
-Yeah.
His shins got scraped.
-Here it comes.
-Right.
Now I've gone and done it.
Come on, man.
Things have been hectic...
The pain doesn't bother me.
I just wonder what the hell I'm doing.
I still have a proper scar from my injury
during the previous RIDE ON TIME.
That?
It's still there.
-Oh, wow.
-This.
Ah, it's quite a scar.
I think it's an incident
I'll remember all my life.
If RIDE ON TIME wasn't there,
I'd probably have cried.
-No way.
-Seriously. It seriously hurt.
During this time's coverage,
one of my goals is
to not incur any injuries.
Yeah.
Meanwhile, the movie's filming
was about to reach its climax.
EDO WONDERLAND, TOCHIGI PREFECTURE
Filming was progressing for
Takizawa Kabuki ZERO 2020 the Movie.
Rolling! Ready, action!
The name of this play
is Nezumi Kozo Jirokichi.
It's not that easy to become
the next Nezumi Kozo!
That's right! You'll never find anyone
that can replace Mr. Nezumi!
Remember Mr. Nezumi wished for Edo
to be filled with smiles and no tears.
Chief Shinkichi, please work hard
and become the next Mr. Nezumi!
Iwamoto is a detective who people want
to become the next Nezumi Kozo.
With his comical personality,
Fukazawa is a young townswoman.
Follow me, Shinnosuke Tokudawara!
The austere and manly Miyadate is
a constable who protects the city of Edo.
RYOTA MIYADATE
Sakuma and Watanabe humorously play
a kooky pair of brothers.
SHOTA WATANABE, DAISUKE SAKUMA
The serious Abe was purposely
assigned the role of the cat.
I wonder how I look.
And the thieves who raid Edo
are Raul, Mukai, and Meguro.
The Edo that Nezumi dreamed of...
The three show off their acting
as the villains.
Now, go.
Find the whereabouts of Shinkichi.
KOJI MUKAI
Izo!
If you are to get in our way,
I will...
kill you.
This performance is a chance
for each to gain great experience.
Clear up!
Ready, action!
The mix of different elements on this day
made for a very Snow Man-like scene.
And cut!
What is Takizawa Kabuki ZERO to them?
I almost laughed so many times.
School. It feels like a school.
I think Takizawa Kabuki is all about
growing from a performance standpoint,
but there's also personal growth.
It's a place where you can learn
all of those things at once.
Like show business school.
September.
Raul was starting another new challenge.
Cut!
Okay! Good.
HONEY LEMON SODA FILMING
He was chosen as the lead role in a movie
that's planned to be released next summer.
I'm very thankful for this opportunity.
If I could bring the results
of this solo gig back to the group,
that would be really nice.
Look sharp now.
Next episode,
each member of Snow Man
shines with their own light.
The things they etch in their hearts
as they polish themselves...
Okay!
Within that tense atmosphere,
I was challenging myself the entire time.
...and the true feelings revealed
by the 17-year-old center.
That's why I didn't quit.
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi