SUMMER 2020
This year was a turning point.
What kind of summer did they have?
It felt like my first summer.
I was able to reaffirm...
RYUSEI ONISHI
...how glad I am to be an idol.
It all began here.
The idol unit
Naniwa Danshi.
They lost their chance
to perform due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
On this night,
they were able to reaffirm that
the stage is where they feel alive.
That was fun. I felt like
I got to be an idol again.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
As Naniwa Danshi
started to garner attention...
they were undergoing a new challenge
at Shochikuza, their second home.
CLOSED
Shochikuza had canceled many shows,
so they were putting on a livestream show
to give back to the theater.
EMPTY-VENUE LIVESTREAM SHOW
KANJANI8 / JOHNNYS' WEST / NANIWA DANSHI
AE! GROUP / LIL KANSAI
Takahashi.
There's a camera.
-Good morning.
-What is the camera for?
RIDE ON TIME.
Correct!
-It's for our future selves.
-To remember.
Right.
I hope to be at the top.
Though the effects of isolation linger,
they seem cheerful after
their first good workout in a while.
This is intense.
There'll be no audience,
but they want to use this stage
to present a new side of themselves.
I'm scared.
I want to show how much
we've improved since last time.
With the quarantine,
we have a lot we want to let out.
That's what I'd like
you to capture on camera.
Hey.
Could you two not make all that noise?
They can edit it.
Yes, their lives have changed
drastically these last two years.
They had a rich experience
beyond their imaginations.
Naniwa Danshi was formed
in October 2018.
Since then, they have continued
to light up the scene.
JANUARY 2019
OSAKA-JO HALL
Two months after their formation,
they played four shows to a sold-out crowd
in Osaka-Jo Hall with Kansai Johnny's Jr.
JANUARY 2020
KYOCERA DOME OSAKA
One year later...
they advanced to Kyocera Dome Osaka.
They attracted
130,000 people over three shows.
However, the looming COVID-19 pandemic
would cast a shadow on their momentum.
To draw interest from fans overseas,
they planned a show
that would embrace Japanese culture.
It was to be held at the sumo arena,
but was cancelled.
MARCH 29, 30
RYOGOKU KOKUGIKAN SHOWS CANCELED
Since then,
they haven't had
another chance to stand on stage.
The other gigs we had scheduled
were postponed.
That includes TV work.
They'd be postponed.
We couldn't anticipate anything.
We can't even do that now.
It was worse, though. Each day was
like fumbling through the darkness,
trying to make our way forward.
We had nowhere to direct it.
This feeling, these emotions.
It was frustrating.
It's frustrating when you
think it was COVID's fault.
And there was one more obstacle
that they had to overcome.
2018 FOOTAGE
KanJani8's Tadayoshi Ohkura
was their senior who supported them,
whenever Naniwa Danshi
took on a big challenge.
KANJANI8
TADAYOSHI OHKURA
He gave them advice on everything
from production to costume design,
but they couldn't rely on him forever.
JULY, TOKYO
July.
They found time between work in Tokyo
to rehearse a new song
they would debut at Shochikuza.
Good morning.
SHUNSUKE MICHIEDA (18)
Michieda was busy with constant
offers for TV acting roles,
and he joins them after wrapping.
Two years ago, he was constantly scolded
by the older members
for taking things too easy,
but that is not the case anymore.
-Michi has something to say!
-"7stars."
-Okay.
-Let's rehearse that.
Okay.
What's this?
We attached a hoodie to a shirt.
The youngest member, Nagao, has started
to take part in the costume designs.
KENTO NAGAO (18)
I don't like it baggy.
A belt would be nice.
Like a belt that's attached on the inside.
Do you think you could make this?
Okay, understood.
Thank you very much.
OSAKA SHOCHIKUZA
And on this night...
Fujiwara was the one
attending meetings in Osaka.
LIL KANSAI
He will help produce the variety segment
performed by his juniors
Lil Kansai and the other young trainees.
Have a good night.
Did you learn something
by being in charge?
Yes, of course.
You can be more objective.
I've always been one of the players,
but now I can step back and
see the audience's perspective.
And look.
"VS Skit produced by Joichiro Fujiwara."
They tease me about it.
I guess they do it out of love though.
Only two years after forming,
each member has been expanding
their own field of expertise.
That is why the time they spent
this summer was so valuable.
Ready and action!
The seven members were filming
a teen drama series together
about a group of high school boys
with unique personalities
who attend a boarding school.
We ask Nagao what his role is.
I'm really feminine.
Someone who likes cute things.
I've never worn something so frilly.
I'm doing my best.
When did you wake up?
Today? Some of the guys woke up at 3:30.
Right?
They spent every day being together
from the early morning
for nearly a month and a half.
Ready?
As each finds individual success,
they will gradually lose the time
they can spend together as a group.
It's special that the seven
of us are starring in this.
We don't know what the future holds.
Is there a big difference between
shooting a show solo and as a group?
It's completely different.
It's reassuring.
When someone isn't quite
up to par that day,
we can support each other.
That's a really big deal.
FOUR DAYS UNTIL THE SHOW
The day of their big livestream
in Shochikuza was drawing near.
Hey.
The doll part.
Unlike the times before,
they had to come up with their own ideas
for the presentation of each song.
...and you follow it up.
I'll think of something later.
What if everyone comes out
from behind when we shout?
I want something with lots of energy.
They were thinking of ways
to showcase their own unique style.
It's not about who's better,
we need to show how we're different.
KAZUYA OHASHI
But that's pretty difficult.
-Let's set up for "Firebird."
-Okay.
You're not quite getting that part.
No.
-Let me explain it again.
-Okay.
Do you see the line?
So like this then this?
They began rehearsing
one of the big numbers for the show.
The show's theme is "Zero Distance."
It's meant to give fans
a close and intimate watching experience.
Something like this?
That's too far.
-Then this much?
-Yes.
I think the cord...
This is the number that they
were going to perform in Ryogoku.
Ryusei, can you line up next to Nagao
so you're shoulder to shoulder?
Can you give it another try
from there together?
Ohashi's part is the same.
What will the final result look like?
Also on the same day...
Charades!
Lil Kansai was rehearsing
their variety segment
with the Jr. trainees.
-Charades!
-You all know the rules.
After School Lil!
Fujiwara was in charge of direction.
NANIWA DANSHI
JOICHIRO FUJIWARA
The ceiling camera is awesome.
They draw out the kids'
natural energy and cuteness.
Here we go. Ready?
One!
Hey now, this teacher
has no patience for your pain.
Hurry, let's go!
But something seems to be on his mind.
Fuga!
He heads to the member
in charge of the MC role.
-Hey, Fuga.
-What's up?
Don't "What's up?" me.
What's up?
When you introduce the next song,
you use the same tone as
when you call out a song title.
Like, "Check out this next song."
Instead say, "Let's go to our next song!"
Then cue the song.
-And you're turning too much.
-Okay.
If you're in front and we're behind,
you end up facing the wrong way.
Instead, step backwards.
-Back to your spot.
-Okay.
Then start talking...
He gives specific direction.
Okay, jump. Ready?
-Ow!
Exactly.
And he makes the stage
a fun place for the kids.
You're trying to convey
the pain to the camera.
Okay.
From KanJani8 to Johnnys' WEST,
from WEST to Kansai Jr.
You have to show the Jr. trainees
that there's this system,
even though they're young.
But seeing them in the green room,
I'm glad they're still the same.
AUGUST 18
DAY OF THE LIVESTREAM SHOW
The big day finally arrives.
They rehearse right until showtime.
What can idols deliver
during the COVID-19 pandemic?
We'll go with these members.
Okay.
Then, 30 minutes before curtain...
Now? Costume designer!
It's a crisis!
Michieda's pants are torn.
-Michi has a tear.
-I do.
I actually tore them.
-Okay.
-I tore them.
He needs them now.
Sorry, I forgot to mention it.
You have to tell us sooner, Michi!
Want to change?
I'm sorry.
We still have 30.
We can make it. Go!
This will be a summer memory.
I'm going to give it my all.
NANIWA DANSHI
EMPTY-VENUE LIVESTREAM CONCERT
Naniwa Danshi's livestream began.
"DIAMOND SMILE"
"AOHARU -WITH U WITH ME-"
(NEW SONG)
Good work today!
I think it went well.
I'm smiling like this guy.
I need to get better.
I'll keep working hard
to entertain everyone.
Yes!
Everything we had bottled inside,
we were able to release
today with this show.
Right now, I'm feeling really rejuvenated.
I'd like us to become big enough stars
to do a dome tour.
Hopefully within five years.
At the end of August,
the members of Kansai Johnny's Jr.
were taking on a new challenge again.
I'm freaking out.
LIL KANSAI
Many shows were canceled
because of the pandemic.
This would be Lil Kansai's
first show with an audience,
as well as their first solo show.
CONGRATS ON YOUR FIRST SOLO SHOW!
Oh man, I'm about to cry here.
Thank you.
Four days later, Ae! group...
There's an audience.
I can't believe it.
I'm so moved.
It was a special summer where
each member spent time thinking
about what being an idol means.
What would you say your job is?
My job?
-If I'm trying to be cool...
-What?
My job is to sell dreams.
Do you think being an idol
is a necessary job?
If you're asking if everyone needs it,
then the answer is no.
But if there are people who need us,
then I feel like we need to
work hard for their sake.
We're on this journey now
to discover that.
Yes, this will be a long journey.
They have a song dedicated
to that journey.
They sang it here, where
the World Expo will be held in five years.
In five years?
I hope we'll have all made our debut.
If we can bring in 2025 as one team,
that would make me happy.
I hope to be at the top of Kansai Jr.
I bet I'll have blue hair by then.
I have no idea about mine.
I hope the five of us are still together.
Surprise!
You ruined our joke!
I want to look back
at how we wanted to be famous
and say we've surpassed it.
I hope we're even bigger by then.
There will always be a challenge.
Their journey will continue.
On the next RIDE ON TIME,
it's Sexy Zone.
What are their true thoughts
entering their ninth year?
I've always had anxiety with this group.
I felt like we fell short...
I was really frustrated.
We take a closer look
at the youngest group to debut.
The four of us and Matsushima
agreed to give each other some space.
He's really like the sun.
For the fans who waited for them.
It's So!
I'm back.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto