OCTOBER 10, 2020
There's one thing that's never happened.
Having the warmth of an audience
in front of you.
It's a feeling I've never had before.
My back is killing me.
"You're with Johnny's, right?"
"You can't dance, right?"
As members of Johnny's, we can't have
people like that underestimating us.
We need to shine brighter,
and confidently stand on stage.
-Good!
-Yeah! Here I go!
Go for it.
It's not like we know
the names of each individual.
Or how each one cheers us on.
None of us know.
However, the fact that we can
definitely meet each other...
...is something that really touched me.
SHINBASHI ENBUJO THEATRE
FIRST PERFORMANCE IN 225 DAYS
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Good morning.
Thanks for being here.
JULY 2020
There's something going on.
It's RIDE ON TIME.
Oh! Starting today?
Yes.
-It's been a while.
-Yes, it has.
Hey, guys!
-Hi.
-We have friends.
Oh, nice to see you again.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-From today?
-Yes.
Good to have you.
Nice to see you again.
-Looking forward to working with you.
-Long time no see.
Good to have you here!
It's been a long time.
They are the Johnny's Jr. idol group
Travis Japan.
Good morning.
I'm here too.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
This group of seven
has skyrocketed in popularity.
How many months will you be with us?
As of right now, we want to
film up to the Torajya show again.
Right.
We don't even know what'll happen.
I hope we can do it.
NOEL KAWASHIMA (26)
-Creating the narrative must be hard.
-True.
There's the trampoline too.
We've lost a lot of
rehearsal time because of COVID.
-Is he too hidden?
-Yes, maybe...
Kawashima, can you come forward a bit?
Like there?
Not right in front of me!
Their greatest weapon
is their high-precision dancing.
Their coordinated dance videos
marked the arrival of
a new type of Johnny's group.
That's why they care
so much about their dancing.
They made sweeping choreography changes
to other Johnny's songs
and recreated them as their own.
Many of the numbers were choreographed
by the members themselves.
Seeing a need to make a performance
group fit for the world stage,
Michael Jackson choreographer Travis Payne
handpicked the Travis Japan members
with Johnny Kitagawa.
In other words, perfecting their dancing
has been their mission
ever since their formation.
It's crazy fun.
I did the choreography and structuring
for the "Entertainment" number.
RYUYA SHIMEKAKE (25)
What made you want to do that?
Well, you know...
I wondered what it would be like
to create something from my imagination.
I wanted to challenge myself.
The other members involved in choreography
are Shizuya Yoshizawa
and the leader Kaito Miyachika.
KAITO MIYACHIKA (23)
Just go ahead and pick
another song or two.
-Okay.
-Then put them in.
We can do "VOLCANO" now,
and two new songs.
Okay.
-How about putting it in a formation?
-Okay.
During rehearsal, they fine-tune
their choreography and positioning.
They all have strong convictions
towards dancing,
and strive to become a group
that specializes in performing.
Five, six, seven.
One and two and three and four.
One, two, three.
I run across this a lot too.
There are times when it's actually cooler
when you loosen up a bit.
Instead of this,
try something like this.
Just emphasize the key points.
The rest can be more loose.
It's about how relaxed you can be
with high tempo songs.
It's reassuring to dance in a group.
You're not alone.
So it's like you're enjoying that.
However, none of you
are who you were a year ago.
You're completely different.
-You've all really grown.
-Thank you.
It's so fun!
A performance that stands on its own.
You don't know who to look at,
but when they're all together,
it's really cool and in-sync.
You just wish you had more eyes!
I consider that the mark of
a good performance.
They're really great, like real dancers.
-Really?
-Yes.
KAITO NAKAMURA (23)
You were really into it.
Not at all.
I still have a long way to go.
It's not ready to show people yet.
Really?
Have you learned the moves?
It's like that's all I've done.
I couldn't charge people to watch this.
You really love dancing.
Yeah well, that's all I've ever done.
We're seriously not good at all.
We might be a little confident,
but we don't think we're good.
I mean, in the end, we're artists.
We're Johnny's idols.
We have to be able to sing, dance,
and be expressive.
We have to be able to do it all.
I've recently realized that
we can't make it with just dancing alone.
Of the 200 members of Johnny's Jr.,
Travis Japan currently has
the most senior status.
Hey, flex your muscles for me.
Thanks.
That was really awesome.
-Are you friends?
-No.
He's your senior.
Yeah, he is.
Do you think of him as your senior?
I mean, he is.
Really?
A really cool senior.
-Really?
-Seems pretty casual.
It does seem casual.
How could you say that?
Are we having fun?
AUGUST 26, 2020
Eight years since their formation,
they've paid their dues.
They're now waiting patiently
for their CD debut.
What is it that they truly need as idols?
They are still searching.
Our performance is one of our weapons.
Mr. Johnny told us that,
so I'd like to ensure that it always is.
KAITO MIYACHIKA
However, that's hard to do.
Has that conversely been something
that's tied you down?
That's not how it feels to us,
but it could be the case.
You can easily say you want to be good,
but it's difficult to achieve.
There is definitely a part of me
that gets distressed by dancing.
However, there are good dancers
who exist in the world.
Which means,
there's no reason we can't become
good dancers as well.
That's something that I think
we need to work on even more.
SEPTEMBER 2020
It's September, and the seven members
were planning their livestream show.
It was meant to be performed five
months ago in front of a live audience.
Shizuya Yoshizawa is one of the members
in charge of choreography.
SHIZUYA YOSHIZAWA
He had previously revealed his
complicated feelings toward dancing.
You didn't join because you loved dancing?
Not at all, if anything I hated dancing,
I mean, it's tiring.
I don't really like working up a sweat.
I never thought idols
did that kind of stuff.
However, he was selected to join a group
striving to be the best at dancing.
I mean, seriously.
What can I do to actually enjoy dancing?
I don't know.
Despite this, he continued to practice,
even getting involved in choreography.
Now he's an integral part
of the group's performance.
You know.
Unlike everyone else,
I'm not really good at dancing.
I can think about it, though.
I can think about it and come up with
my own choreography,
but I never did
much dancing to begin with.
I never took lessons,
so doing it my way is all I know.
I see.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Then step back, step back. Bam, bam.
Yoshizawa choreographed this number
to perform at their next show.
You want to angle...
In addition to choreography,
he has to convey to the other members
the vision he has
for moving around the large space.
Then we come together...
and go to the front.
A little slower.
Like be at the front on six.
That startled me.
If we get to Stage B by the second measure
once the interlude starts,
we should be able to make it.
I want Shizuya to be here
for the rap break.
I think it could be
even more towards the front.
-Here?
-Around there.
That's far.
Maybe while one is rapping,
the others can move.
If it's here, the next part is far.
Oh is it?
I mean, this is number 11.
-What if I ran from here?
-Should work.
Then I'll do that.
If you run from "Get your hands up!"
You might make it.
I think that's just enough if you run.
So try to time it to that.
We'll have to wait a bit
if you do it from here.
This is crazy.
Everyone's so good,
it's harder to teach them.
It's hard work.
I mean, I could be more demanding,
but all seven us have our opinions.
There are a lot of ideas.
You know how it is.
Shizu weirdly lacks confidence.
I don't know why.
I mean, he has the support
of the fans and all of us too.
He should be confident.
Although, I get that's just who Shizu is.
Shizu is the type of person
who loses confidence
if he tries and doesn't see results.
Even though he's had a lot of results.
NOVEMBER 2020
Nice, it went in.
Playing basketball
is one of his favorite hobbies.
This day, he's joined
by a junior he's close with.
I keep missing.
You'll have a better chance of making it
if you know how far you can throw it.
Shoot, I hit it.
-Do you admire Shizuya?
-Yes, he's the best.
I respect him.
He also loves Torajya.
There's a lot I can learn.
Basketball is about how cool
you can make it look.
I see.
I hate showing off.
With basketball, you just naturally
look cool dribbling or making shots.
Maybe that's why I like it.
You don't have to worry
as long as you make it.
-As long as you make it.
-Yeah.
That would've been cool if I made it.
It happens.
I wish I had made it.
I talked with Miyachika, and he said that
you're the type of person who loses
confidence if he doesn't see results.
Yeah.
That's true.
It's like, if I don't get praised
for something I won't improve.
I don't know...
Also, for example,
if someone in the group is being
asked to do the choreography,
my name's not the first to come up.
Shime is the one usually picked.
-Really?
-Yeah.
That's another reason why
I don't have confidence.
It's like, it doesn't have to be me.
I'm just the last resort.
-I see.
-Yeah.
-You want the guys to acknowledge you.
-Yeah, I'd change if they did.
They don't acknowledge me. Those jerks!
Yeah.
Although, the guys and the fans
tell me that I'm needed.
Yeah.
So I think,
"Well, what is it they need then?"
I don't have anything.
I don't have any weapons.
So then I think, "What could I
possibly have that no one else does?"
SEPTEMBER 26, 2020
DAY OF THE LIVESTREAM SHOW
Something only he has.
What could that be?
The show will go on whether
he's found the answer or not.
SEPTEMBER 26, 2020
LIVESTREAM SHOW
It's our first show together in a while.
Our audience
is watching over us from afar.
Let's make sure
we live up to their expectations.
Yeah!
Let's see which of us
can have the most fun!
You're on!
Let's get this started!
Yeah, come on.
I hate being in the front.
However, I've finally gotten comfortable
being at the front of the stage.
I've finally reached that place.
That's good.
Everyone's a good dancer
and a hard worker.
I don't think we would've made it
if we had someone who didn't try.
Everyone works hard.
I mean, if they didn't
I don't think I'd be able to.
I need to get better at dancing.
-You're not good enough?
-Not at all.
I'm probably still at the bottom
of the dance world.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know if that's true,
but I think there's more I can do.
I'm not good enough.
I think I need to put in more work.
What do you think of him?
I think he's cool the way
he can talk about this.
Oh, man!
None of my juniors think of me that way.
I usually get disrespected by my juniors.
They tease me.
Next time, they begin rehearsing
for their stage play.
We didn't get along.
I hated him.
We didn't hit it off at all.
What are their thoughts on teamwork?
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto