There's an echo.
-Wow.
-Right?
These men are visiting
Osaka's Kyocera Dome
after losing something important to them.
Can you indulge me?
I'm home!
I want to say that in front
of an audience.
Seeing it again, it's so huge.
-It is huge.
-Was it always this big?
This is idol group
Johnnys' WEST.
Their summer performances
scheduled for the dome stadiums
in Tokyo and Osaka were canceled...
due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
I've been doing this for ten years,
and it's the first time I cried over work.
I was pretty bummed out.
I'm 27 right now,
so canceling those concerts made me
miss out on a one-time experience.
When I sit and think about everything,
it's a little painful.
In order to vent such frustrations,
they took to the stage this summer.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
JULY 28 - EXPO'70 COMMEMORATIVE PARK
In July,
Johnnys' WEST shared the stage
with over 70 of their juniors and seniors
who all hail from Kansai.
It was a way to send a message of joy
to all of Japan from Kansai.
Johnnys' WEST's greatest weapon
is their enthusiasm.
This man is the embodiment of that.
Akito Kiriyama who is
also an actor and MC.
AKITO KIRIYAMA (31)
Tomohiro Kamiyama, who's responsible
for the group's songs and lyrics.
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA (27)
Nozomu Kotaki is stylish like a model,
and has a strong sense of responsibility
despite being the youngest.
NOZOMU KOTAKI (24)
Takahiro Hamada is
the funny mood maker of the group.
TAKAHIRO HAMADA (31)
Working with KanJani8
to direct the production of this concert,
was the oldest and dependable
Junta Nakama and...
How was it?
It's not bad.
They've allowed us to make it together.
It feels like a festival.
...Ryusei Fujii, who is in charge
of the show's staging.
RYUSEI FUJII (27)
Finally, the group's center,
Daiki Shigeoka.
He's recently garnered acclaim
for his acting skills.
DAIKI SHIGEOKA (28)
This summer,
another important stage
was waiting for them.
This is Osaka Shochikuza Theatre
which has trained countless Kansai idols.
CLOSED
In order to give back to the theater
which was struggling due to the pandemic,
five groups would hold a livestream show
to an empty audience in August.
The first group up would be Johnnys' WEST.
Preparations began over a month earlier.
It's really hard.
There's so much stopping and starting.
Until now,
many of Johnnys' WEST's songs
and dance numbers have been fast-paced.
However for this show, they were trying
a more mature and sensual dance
with smaller movements
that were actually harder.
I see.
Furthermore, the masks would torment them.
I spun around too much. I'm going to puke.
-I'm out of breath.
-How about we...
We want to show that
we're growing one step at a time.
It would be great
if our voices can reach people.
No idea if it'll work though.
For this show in Shochikuza,
members who can play instruments
like the guitarist Hamada
were given solo parts.
That night,
Shigeoka practiced alone
into the early hours of the morning.
-Here?
-Yes.
Right.
I need to make it sharp.
Sorry.
IT'S NOT WRONG
MEETING YOU, BELIEVING IN OUR DREAMS
BARING OUR FANGS AT THE ANSWER
GOODBYE TO INATTENTION
I'M ME AND MYSELF
There was a time when Shigeoka became
overly fixated on what he wanted to do.
Alone and isolated, these are the words
his bandmates shared with him...
IT'S NOT WRONG
We're idols,
but we don't really have much of
the sweet, picture-perfect idol image.
So even if we mess up...
I mean, we mess up a lot.
I might be getting stupider.
So does that mean
you're okay with showing flaws?
That's totally fine.
I think we're all okay
with being embarrassed.
We're all pretty strong mentally.
They paid their dues
back in their Jr. days.
While each of them were in a unit,
they had no seniors to teach them.
So at every show,
the seven boys would share ideas
to make the best show they could.
CD DEBUT PRESS CONFERENCE
They were finally able to debut
ten years after KanJani8
in 2014.
The seven of them asked
and somehow won the chance to debut.
Ain't it great?!
Coming back to Osaka for this show,
the first place they went was where
they held their debut press conference.
It's really one step at a time.
That was also true before we debuted.
It's a big deal how we've made it this far
without losing anyone.
It's important to remember why we started.
I'm glad I got
this opportunity to do that.
The dome concerts were meant to prove
that the path the seven
of them walked together
was not wrong.
DECEMBER 24, 2016
FIRST CONCERT IN KYOCERA DOME OSAKA
They first proved themselves
two years after their debut.
But they haven't had
another opportunity since.
They were meant to play the domes
again this year after a four-year hiatus,
but that was canceled.
The seven members were at Kyocera Dome
this day to shoot a video.
They sang their new song
that they were going to perform here.
"SHOKO"
It's really frustrating that
we couldn't do it this year.
But we can leverage this feeling...
We'll make it back here one day.
JULY 17
It's two weeks
until their Shochikuza show,
and one member was
taking on a new challenge.
A year-long gap is scary.
That's true.
-This is 1,500 millimeters?
-Give or take.
This will be our first time
doing it from this height.
A backflip from this platform,
nicknamed a "platflip."
They made it 30 centimeters taller
than the show they did a year ago.
Yes, thank you.
With his amazing athleticism
and experience at the move,
Kiriyama succeeded on his first try.
Meanwhile,
this was Kamiyama's first attempt ever.
That was scary!
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA
Jumping backwards is scary.
Here I go.
Yes!
You can do anything you set your mind to.
I want to send that message to everyone
by doing this.
Next is Kotaki.
NOZOMU KOTAKI
You okay?
How can he brace for the landing?
How many more can I do?
Good luck.
His legs must endure a force
three times his weight,
which is roughly 180 kilograms.
Okay.
All right.
This is rough.
JULY 29 OSAKA SHOCHIKUZA
THREE DAYS BEFORE THE LIVESTREAM
There's three days left
before the big show.
This show would be performed
to an empty venue,
with the video streamed live.
Any mishaps will be broadcast unedited.
-Want to get close?
-Let's try it.
Maybe we should have just one back row.
-Want to try side-by-side?
-Okay.
The hardest challenge they are
undertaking for this show is this...
A performance with mirrors.
With their backs to the seats,
they perform to their own reflections.
Additionally, the Jr. members
have to move the mirrors.
The seven members sing while
completely surrounded by the mirrors.
Okay.
Singing inwards has more impact,
so for this song don't look back.
Understood.
It doesn't have to be a costly production,
but they all come together
to create their stage.
This is how they started out.
Using mirrors or other common objects
in a creative fashion is something
we've done a lot in Shochikuza.
We've done a lot of creative productions.
So incorporating some new technology
isn't something we've really done.
I would like to put on a show
that can inspire others to persevere.
Nice.
These handheld fans instilled with love
have given them strength
from their supporters.
It only took ten days for fans
to send nearly 10,000 of them.
WEST + YOUR FANS = 1
They're cute.
I bet they were hard to make.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
They're so impressive.
GIVE US YOUR LOVE!
I want people to see this.
How should they respond
to their fans' love and their crew's
hard work and dedication?
HUMAN MIRACLE
TAKAHIRO HAMADA
I'm so grateful for our crew.
I need to let it show every chance I get.
"Hold on, I'm not doing enough."
That's how I feel.
I need to set a good example.
You know? For our juniors.
I need to be a good role model.
Around this time,
they were rehearsing that special move.
Nice!
That looked painful.
Want more pads?
Kotaki was giving it his all.
Absorb the landing.
Ow!
Absorb it.
Ow.
All he needed was to absorb the impact.
That is what everyone thought...
AUGUST 1
Johnnys' WEST's final rehearsal.
It was time for the platflip.
Kotaki is on the left.
Something was off after his landing.
ONE HOUR BEFORE GOING LIVE
Excuse me.
That hurts there.
Here?
Something on the inside of my heel...
That hurts?
It might be bad.
It's probably just a bone contusion,
but there's a possibility that you
may have slightly fractured something.
What will happen to the performance?
I'm so frustrated.
They cut the platflip from the show.
I hate this.
Can you still dance?
I'm honestly not sure given this pain.
We're about one hour out.
I'm ashamed.
Just then, Shigeoka plays
that song from the green room.
"It's not wrong."
For their younger selves who strived here
when nobody knew their names...
This is where
the seven of us first played.
We were in different groups,
but this is where we spent our youth.
We grew up here.
This is our home.
TEN MINUTES TO GO
It's because this is their home...
That looks painful.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You've got a little limp.
Kotaki
decided he would take the stage.
Let's deliver happiness
to all of Japan from our home of Osaka!
Let's go!
Let's put on a good show with our crew!
Yeah!
The curtains were drawn.
JOHNNYS' WEST
LIVESTREAM
Shochikuza is the place of our youth!
It's been a while. Let's go!
"EEJANAIKA"
DEBUT SINGLE
"SAYONARA NANKAJA OWARASENAIKARA"
"MACHIGAECCHAINAI."
MUSIC AND LYRICS BY DAIKI SHIGEOKA
Thank you very much.
Thank you, cameramen!
Thank you to the lighting technicians!
And to Kotaki...
This is Non's birthday cake.
I drew his face here.
I think it came out pretty nice.
The artistry was indeed good.
-It's almost a waste.
-Nice.
Is it good?
Maybe I'll have some too.
I'll have Non's leg.
My leg?
What do you think an idol's role is?
I guess it's to really do anything.
Entertain the audience while having fun.
They just need to continue
doing that one simple thing
for as long as they can.
Simply go one step at a time.
Ready?
On the next RIDE ON TIME,
it's Naniwa Danshi.
Their special summer...
It's frustrating when you
think it was COVID's fault.
The stage suddenly taken from them...
Ow!
But they continued to search
for what they could do as idols.
I don't think that we're special.
We have to do what we can.
They take the stage with resolve.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto