Can we do it with so many people around?
Can we?
-This...
-Wait a minute.
People are coming. Hey.
-Should we line up?
-Yes, please.
-Hurry. Just include them.
-It's kind of macho.
No, we don't need to include them.
I don't want that.
Sorry, but you're in it a little bit.
Can you... I guess not.
Could you press the button?
Press it.
All right. Ready? I'll take it.
V6. Their 25th-anniversary photo.
-Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
Thank you for the time.
Sorry for the wait!
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
1995 NOVEMBER 1 DEBUT
In 1995, the idol group V6 debuted.
Starting with this debut song,
they have been releasing songs
that are still being sung today.
"WA NI NATTE ODOROU"
"AI NANDA"
Hello.
Let's do it.
RIDE ON TIME? Is this RIDE ON TIME?
-So you'll follow me?
-Yes, sorry.
Not at all.
They have a unique way of operating.
The six members are
usually active in their own fields.
But for their 25th anniversary,
they're going to have
their first concert in three years.
Be careful, he has a high sense of beauty.
I've always wanted to lower it,
but I can't.
The older three are known
by the nickname Tonisen.
-Five more?
-Yes.
V6 MASAYUKI SAKAMOTO (49)
He is highly acclaimed
as a musical actor, too.
The oldest member of the group,
Masayuki Sakamoto.
V6 HIROSHI NAGANO (48)
Hiroshi Nagano is thriving
as an actor and an entertainer.
He is a licensed cook
and has even published cookbooks.
V6 YOSHIHIKO INOHARA (44)
Yoshihiko Inohara is known
as an actor and a TV show host.
-I have 150 larvae at home now.
-Do you really?
-Seriously?!
-Yeah.
Does anybody want some?
The younger three are known
by the nickname Kamisen.
V6 JUNICHI OKADA (40)
He has now established his reputation
as an actor who excels at action scenes.
The youngest member, Junichi Okada.
Film stars don't laugh.
V6 GO MORITA (42)
Go Morita is a great actor who played many
difficult roles on stages and in movies.
It's RIDE ON TIME.
Ride on time
-Ride on time, ride on time
-That's not it.
Ken Miyake has a successful career
on stages and in TV shows.
V6 KEN MIYAKE (41)
He serves as a navigator for a TV show
in sign language which he learned himself.
Right, right. I remember that.
The 25 years they've spent together
and now...
Okay, let's do it!
"PINEAPPLE" CHOREOGRAPHING
Their new song is a mature love song.
It requires soft movements.
Like this?
That's it.
That's hard!
Do it slowly.
I don't think we're used to this move.
One more time. One, two.
Good work today.
Can I take this salad home?
-Good work!
They basically rehearse
intensively for a short time.
Today's filming is all done!
I have work from 5:50 tomorrow.
They always book me for something
early in the day after a V6 job.
Well, we're the same age...
The same age...
We're always tired.
We're old men.
AGE 14, PASSED AUDITION
When Okada was 14,
he participated in an audition held as
part of a TV show from his hometown Osaka.
After passing, he stayed in Tokyo.
The only thing he had
in his bag was a hair dryer.
I debuted when I was 14.
I didn't have money.
Soba noodles were the cheapest...
They were the cheapest, so that was good.
I had to eat something,
so I just ate soba noodles.
I ate the same thing for three years.
Nothing else.
I didn't have extra clothes
and didn't buy them.
So I think everyone remembers
that I always wore overalls.
It was white,
but I wore it until it turned black.
Everyone talks about it.
But the truth is I didn't have money,
so I couldn't buy anything else.
That's why he looked for his own weapon
to work in the industry for a long time.
He chose to be an action star himself.
He appeared in a number of movies
and historical dramas.
In Japan, actors prefer
to be in subculture movies.
No one wants to be mainstream.
You're cooler in subculture stuff.
Movies that make you go,
"Bam! Now this is entertainment"...
There weren't that many of them back then.
But I'm part of Johnny's
which is all about entertainment.
So I went that route,
and I became a geeky actor
who only gets offers
to play military men and samurai.
That's what I wanted though.
Let's go aggressive.
Let's film something crazy.
-Go aggressive.
-Yeah.
In the film that was shot last year...
he put his body on the line.
That's why he has one thing
on his mind right now.
Considering the impact of
the pandemic and also my age...
I'm trying my best to keep up with
the changes brought on by the pandemic.
But at age 39, I feel a gap
regular people wouldn't understand.
I feel like I could challenge myself
to do something more.
I feel like I've always been
struggling like that.
I don't know if I was crazy
or just sucked-in enough.
Could I have been alone?
When you want something great,
you really want to be lonely.
I mean, you'll become lonely.
That kind of conflict within me about
making things grows bigger and bigger.
I wonder if I push myself hard enough.
I have a lot of concerns like that.
What's the aspect ratio?
It's 16:9.
Oh, okay.
You can even shoot a music video with it.
TOCHIGI, MIBU TOWN
MINAMIINUKAI JUNIOR HIGH
Okay, let's do it!
"V6 NO AI NANDA 2020" FILMING
This day, they're filming
V6's popular TV show.
Wow.
Introduce yourself.
Year 1 Class 2, Riki Kuroda.
Kuroda...
-It's Riki.
-Riki. Oh.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
-You're just a first year.
-You're cute.
Am I?
-I'm so nervous.
-Oh, yeah?
-Nice.
-Go!
Year 1 Class 2! Riki Kuroda!
My mom...
loves V6's Go Morita!
What?!
-No honorifics.
No honorifics.
The real Go Morita is more...
tanned than I thought!
-Good job.
-You did great.
Nice job!
Tanned?
Tanned.
KANTO DAIICHI HIGH SCHOOL
This day, in the same program,
they collaborated
with high school students.
What was your name?
Rin.
Rin. Go ahead.
You've got a little more now.
Many kinds of...
I was hoping to see happy faces
and beautiful eyes.
-So it's good.
-Expressions of teens?
You can only be like that
for this period of time.
So when I see it and feel it,
I feel really glad that
I'm been doing this program.
It's nice.
Oh, Teacher. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Say hi to everyone for me.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Morita joined the agency when he was 13.
He was mischievous even after he debuted
and often gave the older team a hard time.
The way we thought was different
from the older three.
We didn't think about anything
and we just wanted to have fun.
So there was a huge gap there.
STAGEPLAY "ARAJINN" REHEARSAL
But when he was in his late twenties,
Morita realized the fun of acting onstage.
By building experience
in the rehearsal room,
he improved himself.
This day, he was choreographing
all by himself.
A choreographer who knew him
before his debut said this.
The first time I worked with V6,
he was the most accurate
with moves and positions.
It was Go.
He may not look it,
he does things the most properly.
-That's why he's interesting.
-True.
He always watches rehearsal videos.
-He does, right?
-Yes, always.
This is the kind of work
that Morita is not good at.
Enough!
That's too many!
-It's taking so long today.
-It's the same for everyone.
It's so long.
Just five more.
You're taking pictures endlessly.
I want a little more.
I can't.
You seem to save your energy
during photo shoots.
That's rude.
You're saving your energy
the most in the group.
You don't understand at all.
Yeah?
That's not good for
the production of the show.
Really.
I look like I'm saving my energy, huh?
Yeah, no surprise there.
I don't actually know
how other members are,
but I guess we care about
different things.
I like acting onstage...
So I do it.
It's not like I save
my energy for everything.
It's about balance.
The balance of myself
and the overall balance.
Members like Nagano
wouldn't say anything, but I assume
he's got stuff on his mind.
But sometimes there's a lot of
meaning in things that aren't said.
That's something that I think
other people should be aware of.
During a rehearsal...
A lot of people are here for hours
so we have to ventilate.
We're focused,
so we can't give you orders.
So you guys should take the lead
and watch the clock
and ventilate every 10 or 15 minutes.
Let's have a meeting
and open the doors every hour.
Since the state of emergency last year,
Miyake has been writing this
at the end of his every blog post.
TO HEALTHCARE WORKERS...
For the people at the frontline
in this pandemic every day.
THANK YOU ALL, WHO TAKE RISKS
TO SUPPORT OUR DAILY LIVES.
Not just the healthcare workers...
It's not just healthcare workers.
There are so many people
who are supporting our daily lives.
There really are so many people.
Like those who are working
at grocery stores,
and nursing homes and banks.
I want everyone...
to think of them.
But I don't want to be pushy about it.
So I simply write it
to express my appreciation.
Readers can take it as they like.
That's all.
I forgot how "PINEAPPLE" went.
This is how the oldest member,
Sakamoto, sees Miyake.
Of the six of us, Ken is the one
who thinks about a lot of things. Really.
-About the group.
-Oh, yeah?
About each member... Surprisingly.
He'll be embarrassed
and won't admit it though.
He joined the agency when he was 13,
And even before his debut,
his looks drew attention.
GoKen Combi with Morita
held their own concert, which was
unusual for Johnny's Jr. at the time
and they became popular.
10 years after his debut, Miyake began to
learn sign language on his own,
and became a navigator
in a show about sign language.
SIGN LANGUAGE FOR EVERYONE
It all started...
when he met a certain fan
at a handshake event
during their 10th anniversary tour.
I shook hands with fans one at a time...
It was really like in a day or in an hour...
Like 8,000 fans a day.
And the security in the back
was like "Go, go."
So it was really like a flash
with each fan.
And that's when I saw...
this Deaf girl.
And she talked to me a lot
in sign language,
but I didn't know what to say back.
I couldn't even say anything.
And she was gone.
How should I say... The fact that
I couldn't say anything to the fan
at all is very regrettable for me,
and that had always stuck with me.
So I decided to learn it,
and I attended a workshop that
the ward was hosting for three years.
From that point,
everyone including Deaf people...
I began to want to make the things
we offer to be enjoyable for everyone.
Our DVDs basically have...
For all on-stage banter and everything,
we have subtitles that you can turn on.
I think that really made them...
enjoyable for everyone.
Oh, hi!
Cute! What is the dog's name?
-Vinnie.
-Vinnie?
Vinnie.
So cute!
Vinnie, sit.
Oh, good doggie!
Let me smell your paw pads.
Do they smell?
Well, when they get tired...
Oh, stinks! A burnt smell.
Yeah, as they get tired,
that smell gets stronger.
What are you doing?
It's true!
What are you two doing?
For 25 years,
they have been together.
In the next episode, they start preparing
for their 25th-anniversary online show.
The older three who have been
supporting the group.
I'm able to work, in large part
because of V6.
I can't wait to see
how it's going to change.
"There are six of you
and you're that boring?"
Subtitle translation by: Tsuyoshi Koide