JANUARY 19, 2021
January of this year.
TOKYO COVID-19 OUTBREAK
I've started collecting cards.
Hey, me too.
-What card games do you play?
-Yu-Gi-Oh! and Pokemon.
You play Pokemon?
-Yes, I do.
-Let's play sometime.
Travis Japan member Kaito Nakamura...
JANUARY 17, 2021
...has recovered from
his novel coronavirus infection.
I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-Thanks.
Sorry.
It's okay.
-Good to see you again.
-Good to see you.
Your hair grew.
I think it's been about
a month since I cut it.
At New Year's, our group danced
behind ARASHI at their final concert.
I watched it.
When we found out I couldn't go on,
everyone else had
to re-rehearse everything,
so I feel really bad about that.
You know...
After that happened,
I dwelled on it for about a week.
What do you most want to do now?
-Right now?
-Yes.
I want to dance with everyone.
Really?
I'm really looking forward to that.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
To anyone who is a part of Johnny's,
there is a legendary dance number.
TORAJYA 2020
"Sennen Medley."
Incorporating contemporary elements,
the intense choreography
expresses a unique world.
NORIYUKI HIGASHIYAMA
It started in 1990,
born as Noriyuki Higashiyama's
solo number.
Ever since then,
many juniors have aspired to perform it,
but the high difficulty meant that only
a select few have been able to cover it.
Entrusted to carry on its legacy
is the seven-member Johnny's Jr. unit,
Travis Japan.
In order to perform it
at their Torajya Ninjapan stage play,
they adjust the formation
for the seven of them.
In charge of that was...
the greatest Johnny's performer
of all time, Tomoyuki Yara.
TOMOYUKI YARA
For example, this section here.
If you go one, two, three.
It changes the way it looks if you just
focus the movement within yourself.
You guys will synchronize
even if you don't want to.
So rather than focus on that, try to be
more conscious of the groove and rhythm.
Okay.
You know...
KAITO MIYACHIKA (23)
You need to study in order
to achieve something greater.
Since we have someone who studied it
by our side supporting us,
part of me wants to depend on him.
The much-respected Yara would
be coming up with new choreography
for the jazz version of Travis Japan's
original song "Happy Groovy."
That was a good sound there
with the foot tap.
One, two, three, four, five.
I would hate for Travis Japan
to lose this opportunity.
I want them to be...
better than last year.
They show nothing but promise.
That's what I see in them.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Then bring it close and take this,
and one, two, three, four, yeah.
Side slide, slide.
Drop.
It's so hard.
I can't do it. What am I going to do?
It's crazy difficult.
This might be
my favorite song in the world.
-This version?
-Yeah.
For real?
It's a great song.
It's fun. It's crazy.
GENTA MATSUDA (21)
My adre... adre... My something-line.
Adrenaline.
My levels would break
the Guinness world record.
They only had half a day
to choreograph the number.
They go over one move after another.
If you bob your head like this,
it'll slow you down.
Then you incorporate this.
We'll break it down a little later.
NOEL KAWASHIMA (26)
It's tough.
I'm exhausted.
Everyone's good at learning,
but learning and doing aren't the same.
Like, "Wow, it's this different."
It feels like the real deal.
I don't feel like I'm doing well at all.
It's the first day.
It's fine.
I was kinda sleepy myself.
If anything...
I'd rather them not try too hard.
Yeah.
I've been telling them not to try so hard.
They don't have to give it their all.
This was the homework Yara gave them
during the previous session.
I thought you were really flat
throughout the whole thing.
"They're working really hard."
"They're going for it with the dancing."
It didn't get past that.
To be honest, it hurts.
He's right.
If it looks like they're trying hard,
then that's where it'll end.
As a viewer, you want to be able to see
another story or something.
Still, I think they've
really improved since last year.
-Really?
-Yeah.
With everything
they've done over the year,
I think they've gotten past that.
Until now, they've dedicated their time
to improving their precision,
in order to perfect dancing in unison.
However,
that also meant stifling the expression
of each individual performer.
People say my expression is scary.
I just get into the song.
I'm just giving over my entire soul.
But I guess it comes off as scary.
I see.
So in an effort to seem less scary...
I hold a part of me back.
Sometimes I think that
the way I did it last year felt better.
I don't know which is right,
but then sometimes I think
it looks better this year.
I'm still figuring it out.
I see.
I guess dancing in unison is something
we need to try harder to do,
but to us, that goes without saying.
For example, we often do this song
"It's BAD,"
and the choreography doesn't
really call for idiosyncrasy.
So when we started talking about what we
want to do for our next coordinated dance,
Yara told us
the same thing last year, but...
"If you synchronize the feel of a dance,
it will look unified even if you have
slightly different interpretations."
That's what he told us.
So in regard to synchronizing our vision...
A song like the one we made this year,
"Happy Groovy,"
with that jazz arrangement,
makes it seem we're synchronized
even when the choreography
looks a bit different.
That's another strategy we're trying.
-It might work if we hit that part.
-Yes.
Shime's too far.
Maybe we let him through first.
Shime.
He goes, then it's Kaito, Shime, Kaito.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Yeah, there.
Kaito goes through
the middle at the start.
You mean like this?
Like this and stop.
Then you can go this way.
So we don't hit each other.
Okay.
-So you're first.
-Okay.
Ready?
Good, like that.
Then I come in.
Awesome!
That was really cool.
You just barely slid by each other.
-That'll be our base.
-Okay.
-Thank you all.
-Thank you!
The choreographing finished in five hours.
However, the wonderful dance
gave the members mixed feelings.
I feel like if we try harder,
we can seriously make something
that gives you goosebumps.
Especially with this song.
But we don't have the time.
The play's first act features a variety of
performances like action and tap numbers,
while the second act
focuses on dance numbers.
There was a lot to learn
in a limited amount of time.
Moreover, most of the program's difficulty
had been raised from the last show.
Are you okay?
You're not pushing too hard?
I don't know.
-So it's not something you're measuring?
-Right.
About once every two or three days,
I wonder whether I'm improving at all.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Why?
-Well...
I'm turning 25.
I often get told that I'm pretty childish.
I wonder if it's okay to be such a kid.
This is more like a personal issue
than a work issue.
You're unsure if you're mature enough?
Yeah.
Like, am I even aware of my surroundings?
Sometimes that pops into my head
while I'm working.
Not trying too hard is proving
to be harder than they imagined.
MEETING ROOM (2)
This is my usual green room.
RYUYA SHIMEKAKE
-Every week?
-Yes.
Thank you.
-Your usual tuna mayo onigiri.
-Okay.
Once a week, Shimekake appears on a local
program in Tochigi, his home prefecture.
Four, three.
TOCHIGI TELEVISION
EVENING 6 PLUS
Message Theme Talk!
"Dochide SHOW"!
He enjoys this part of his job,
sharing news about himself
and the group with his hometown.
Really?
Let's take a closer look.
Within the homey ambiance,
he learned about work
he's never experienced before.
I'm writing a letter on my computer.
-It has a "t".
-Right.
-Do you remember this, Shime?
-Yes, I do.
-It was a bit muddy.
-Yes.
This one wasn't muddy.
It's British English.
American English gets a bit muddy.
It sounds more like a "d."
That's all.
Shimekake left his hometown
when he was around 18.
He came to Tokyo filled with hope.
I just kind of left without thinking.
I just wanted to get
far away from the nest.
Then I suddenly lost work
at the same time.
I was like,
"It wasn't supposed to be like this."
So because I kept losing work,
I was losing money.
I started worrying about rent.
I was trying to make do,
barely scraping by.
I mean, I got through it and now
I'm making a living just fine,
but it was tough at the time.
Success isn't guaranteed.
Okay, let's end on a message from Shime!
Please go ahead.
Next month, Travis Japan has a play,
and we would love your support.
I'll do my best.
Good luck!
Thank you very much! Good work.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
-We finished on time.
-Yes.
We fit it all in.
I actually wanted to say,
"I'll be waiting for your gyoza, Daiji."
That's too bad.
Sorry, if I was two seconds faster...
I saw I only had three seconds left
when I started to say it.
You figured it wouldn't fit.
You've been mindful of time lately.
I should've given you a countdown.
I should've spoken two seconds faster.
Okay, let's say that next week.
This has been the only job
I felt was worth doing.
You had other options, didn't you?
No, not really.
I mean, not at all.
Really?
Yeah.
There are some difficult times,
but most of it is good.
Yeah.
There's something I'm picky about.
Even if it's a minute detail.
That's just how much Travis...
KAITO MATSUKURA
...cares about our synchronized dance.
So in that regard...
we should be showcasing our
personality as Travis Japan.
Not each of our individual personalities.
Sometimes my own personality
gets in the way of that.
However, I feel like...
I should hold onto my convictions,
because if that falters,
well, I won't be myself anymore.
I strongly believe that,
so I want to hold onto them forever.
They don't want to
give up their expression.
They use their hard training, joy,
and even their personal struggles
to expand their sense of expression.
Then they will demonstrate to the world...
the power of entertainment.
TORAJYA NINJAPAN 2020
Next time,
what is their determination as they stand
before the audience on the main stage?
I like receiving the praise
and applause from the fans.
I'd say that it drives me
to aim higher even now.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto