A moment during the 17 year old's
after-school time.
NOVEMBER 2020
I love to go on walks.
I love to walk around
places I don't know in the city.
Really, that's a surprise.
The aromas drifting
from regular households,
like the smell of baths
or the smell of curry is what I love.
The center position of idol group Snow Man
is filled by the high schooler, Raul.
RAUL (17)
Right now, my...
The view that I think is amazing
in this moment
was completely unimaginable a year ago.
It kind of makes me hope that next year
I can have an unimaginable view too.
Seriously, you only live life once.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
"HIRARI TO SAKURA"
Both Japanese and Western,
they are an idol group
that can express two different worlds.
In January 2020,
this nine-member group made
their long-awaited debut as Snow Man.
"KIMI NO KARESHI NI NARITAI."
With their remarkably high dance skills,
they released another
best seller last year.
Where is your end goal?
Someplace no one's ever been.
We could do this and even this,
but probably a position beyond that.
That's probably the place I'm aiming for.
That is Hikaru Iwamoto,
the leader of Snow Man, which originally
formed nine years ago with six members.
While working their way up,
each of them polished their character
over the long years.
HIKARU IWAMOTO (27)
The one who leads Snow Man
with an iron body, Iwamoto.
Who would fit the yokai role?
The excellent talker who livens the scene,
Tatsuya Fukazawa.
TATSUYA FUKAZAWA (28)
Right. In other words, who's the monster?
The key person in acrobatics,
Daisuke Sakuma.
DAISUKE SAKUMA (28)
The one who illuminates the stage
with his serene voice, Shota Watanabe.
SHOTA WATANABE (28)
Follow me, Shinnosuke Tokudawara!
The one who is essential
in Japanese theatrics, Ryota Miyadate.
RYOTA MIYADATE (27)
I'm Ryohei Abe. This time's...
The one who is very popular
on quiz shows, Ryohei Abe.
RYOHEI ABE (27)
As a result the character
I created is the only one of its kind.
I want to keep arming myself
with lots of different skills.
And then there's the three new
personalities who added fresh color
to that Snow Man group.
October.
-You brought them all?
-Yes, as props.
Then I'll use them all.
One member was facing a photo shoot.
-Nice!
-Yes.
Three, two, one!
Nice sound!
Koji Mukai first joined
Snow Man two years ago.
On this day,
he was not the one being photographed,
but the one taking photos.
Making use of
his long-time photography hobby,
he began a series last year
in a weekly magazine.
In each volume he receives
guidance from popular photographers.
The instructor this time
is Mr. Masashi Asada,
who takes photos in humorous settings.
PHOTOGRAPHER
MASASHI ASADA
The setting Mukai attempted was...
Right, so...
the crime scene
is certainly expressed now.
So if this person's presence
was a bit more...
Ah, I see!
-More expressed...
-I see.
-Here.
Three, two, one!
All right!
-It's good?
-Yeah.
Then let's have you look
at the depth of field.
I'm not really confident on the focusing.
He entered Kansai Johnny's Jr.
at twelve years old
and always kept his work base in Kansai.
His specialty was comedy.
However, despite reaching
his mid-twenties,
his chance to debut never seemed to come.
Then in January 2019,
he moved to Tokyo and joined Snow Man.
At first, he was barely able to keep up
with the other members.
JANUARY 2019
It's so fast.
...two, three, four!
Jet Pistol!
Mukai had soon begun to point his camera
at his fellow members who supported him.
Isn't this awesome? Cool, huh?
It's a 135 millimeter, a superzoom lens.
I always carry this with me
to capture our members' portraits.
I capture...
Well, their smiles,
but I guess their natural selves?
When I publish their natural selves,
all the members are pleased,
so that's why I do it.
You know, I'm very shy.
It's like I can learn about everyone
through a picture and a camera,
so I'm always grateful that
they let me photograph them.
That's how I feel.
And all our fans enjoy it as well,
so it encourages me
and it leads to my motivation, yeah.
You're good! I knew it.
A little this way...
There's a car coming.
One's coming from that way too. Careful.
For Mukai right now,
Snow Man is a valuable place
where he belongs.
Isn't this good?
Oh, nice! Looks really good!
It's good, huh?
Okay, roll the camera.
There was one other personality
that was added to the group as well.
The one who joined
at the same time as Mukai...
Ren Meguro.
REN MEGURO (23)
"Mr. Handsome's coming"? I'm here.
But, you know, the great part about him
is that he's a good guy.
He's found his special weapon
and is wielding it.
Like how he says he's working
on his comedy.
So he really knows how to manage himself.
He compliments a lot.
He's smooth, right?
A smooth talker.
But I wanna say what's good about people.
You know how it's harder to compliment
a person if you become too close to them?
Most people are like that,
but I wanna say it.
It makes for a better relationship.
If something's good, I say it.
If anyone else said that, it'd sound fake,
but when you say that,
it feels very natural.
Well, I could say that too.
Something like that...
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven!
He also diligently worked
on acrobatic training.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven!
-It's all spirit.
-Backflips are about spirit. 98% spirit.
OCTOBER 2020
PHOTO SHOOT
That attitude never changes
even in his personal work.
And put one hand in the pants pocket.
Okay.
He has been modeling for a men's
fashion magazine for three years.
You make him change here?
-Can I have an onigiri?
-Go ahead.
You skipped breakfast?
I didn't eat.
He is always dedicated
to any work he's given.
Behind his work ethic lies
his feelings toward the peers of his past.
Meguro entered the agency
at thirteen years old.
Once he had trained for about six years,
a unit called Uchu Six was formed
and they worked toward their debut.
However, in January 2019,
Meguro had joined Snow Man alongside
of the unit and a busy life ensued.
I went on tour with ARASHI to Osaka.
I got back at around 11:30 last night,
and I heard we were doing this today,
so I asked for a video of the routine.
I practiced it right until morning
before I came in today.
What time was it?
Maybe about 5:00 in the morning.
Thank you.
In the end,
Meguro decided to narrow down
his work to just Snow Man.
The time when he broke the news
to his Uchu Six members
is still carved into his heart.
When I narrowed down to Snow Man only,
of course I had mixed feelings.
But how do I put this?
My Uchu Six members at the time
all understood me.
They really cheered me on saying,
"Do your best. You can do it."
Or, "You have talent,
so I always knew you could do it."
Like, they gave me some
unbelievably kind comments.
How do I say this?
You know how nothing is definite
with Johnny's Jr., right?
I mean, we each have our own life,
and we're each taking a gamble
with that life, you know?
So everyone understands that too.
The Uchu Six members all understood that.
That's why, maybe they thought,
"You have your own life too."
They may have thought
like that for my sake.
So for the people
who have encouraged me and my life,
I want to make it one I can truly enjoy.
-I see.
-Yes.
How embarrassing.
Thank you very much. Thanks.
OCTOBER 2020
And in October,
a large opportunity approached Meguro.
This is the filming of the monumental show
that aired during New Year's, Kyojo 2.
Okay!
The setting is based in a police academy.
PROPER HAND SALUTE
How do I put it?
He says, "Then I'll go," with concern.
It's written right there.
Meguro plays the student who causes
the incident that is key to the story.
Playing the instructor role beside him
is one of his seniors who he looks up to.
TAKUYA KIMURA
Ready, action!
REHEARSAL
Good work, sir.
It says, "I should quit the police,"
and, "I shouldn't quit," here.
Write each reason under them.
-And cut!
-Cut!
Even after the cut,
he remains in character.
DIRECTOR ISAMU NAKAE
REHEARSAL
Okay.
And cut!
Okay, quiet please!
FILMING
Ready, action!
During the filming, Meguro sustained
that posture the entire time.
END OF FILMING
Once his senior speaks to him,
he finally eases up.
To be able... to work with Mr. Kimura
I think is probably
a once-in-a-lifetime event.
So, when the camera's rolling
as well as when it's not,
I just want to keep watching him.
Like, the way he is on-site
or what do you call it...
how he carries himself?
Within that tense atmosphere,
I was challenging myself the entire time
to see how much I was capable of doing.
Even after the cut,
you kept your back straightened.
That's right.
Once I got on-site, I thought of staying
a police academy student the entire time.
That's why my back
is killing me right now.
This was the last scene
filmed on this day.
Each of your steps
are different lengths, so...
They decided to practice
with all of the student roles.
Then...
Meguro's senior who wasn't being filmed...
Forward!
...stood by in character,
watching over his acting.
One... One...
"To be acknowledged as an actor
like his senior."
One, one, one, two...
He hopes to fulfill this dream one day.
Last year, one of Japan's biggest
fashion shows was held without spectators,
the Tokyo Girls Collection.
The other irreplaceable personality
from Snow Man appeared on that stage.
The 17-year-old center, Raul.
His dance is all freestyle.
I feel super good!
There's nothing more to say.
Currently, even brands overseas
are focusing on Raul for modeling.
Another two or three shots
and we'll finish.
Okay.
Ready, action!
Furthermore, he had been assigned the lead
in a movie due to release this summer.
Cut!
NOVEMBER 2020
How does Raul see
his current 17-year-old self?
Now...
I've always said it up until now,
but I think I've been extremely lucky.
That's probably what I'll think
right before I die too,
"Wow, I was extremely lucky."
I'm not trying to be modest by saying,
"I was just lucky."
Well, I'm sure there are
many different opinions,
but I was able to join Johnny's,
and I was able to join Snow Man.
There must have been a reason for it,
so I feel that I myself
shouldn't ever forget that.
I wished for something to happen twice
and something did happen twice.
There are better groups than us,
amazing singers or artists
who can dance more.
If you look around the globe,
there's plenty of them.
Well, so this is the interesting part
about entertainment.
I just wish for something to happen
with all my heart.
That's why I'm really spoiled.
And while I think that I'm spoiled...
If someone asked what I'll do
to compensate for being spoiled,
I'd just say,
"I'll work desperately hard."
We'll desperately work hard
in the environment given to us,
and I'll wish for something to happen.
Anyone who talks like that is obnoxious,
so I'm gonna work hard.
-Thank you very much.
-Thank you.
-Wow!
-Excellent!
At last, Snow Man was approaching
the moment to fulfill one of their dreams.
Oh, what's all this?
-I'm honestly excited!
-Awesome!
The display alone is insane!
After being canceled due to COVID-19,
their long-awaited debut was here.
It's made the fire
within me burn stronger.
The next episode is their debut concert,
and Snow Man dashes through to a new year.
I want to do a concert
using just our own songs.
However, an unexpected situation occurs.
Ugh, damn it!
Which leg?
I sprained it.
Happy...
New Year!
Hi.
We're Snow Man!
Snow Man is just awesome!
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi