Let's do our best!
DAY OF THE SHOW
The day of their 25th-anniversary show.
As the six held hands,
they welcomed the moment.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Okay, this way.
2020 OCTOBER 19
FILMING FOR THE EVE OF THE SHOW
A video shooting for the livestream show.
They arrived at the place
where they debuted 25 years ago.
The Yoyogi First Gymnasium.
YOYOGI NATIONAL STADIUM FIRST GYMNASIUM
When they see the venue,
I bet they'll get excited.
Yeah, they will.
They initially planned
to tour the country,
but gave up due to the pandemic.
They decided to do
a no-audience, livestream concert.
We've been rehearsing
and we've finally come this far.
We were feeling how everyone felt
as we walked all this way.
That's right.
Let's do our best until the end.
"TL" DANCE FILMING
On this day, they filmed the most
demanding dance performance.
All right, members. It's time to rehearse.
They began to walk through it
one last time.
Come out and stop.
Okay, that's it. We'll stop right there.
Okay. Stop right there. Yes.
That's good. Yes.
Members, when you're ready,
please get into the water.
I see.
It looks cold.
It's kind of cold.
It's quite deep.
It's deep and cold.
I have to get used to it.
All right, let's do it. Start rolling.
From the beginning.
-Okay. cut.
-Cut.
A towel. Give me a towel.
I slipped.
I couldn't go back after this.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
-Cut!
-Okay, cut.
It was just me, sorry.
The filming lasted three hours.
The six decided on the staging
and dared to challenge themselves.
-Bring the steps, please.
-My teeth were chattering.
Oh, it's cold!
It's like a hangout for old men.
Oh, it's really tough, isn't it?
-Looks like a group of stuntmen.
-A group of stuntmen?
Even on this day, Okada continued to
take pictures of the members.
Start rolling.
-Play the song.
-Three, two, one!
Okay, perfect!
Oh, this is great!
Amazing.
Wow, this is so cool. Who is this?
This is Ken.
-Looks like a religious painting.
-It does.
I shot a religious painting.
Let's do it.
Miyake shoots Okada.
Let's start.
Three, two, one!
-I like it.
-Here comes the water burst.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, one!
Here's the preview.
That's a wrap.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Good work!
So I don't want them to feel too much.
-I see.
-That's what I feel.
-After we did it?
-Yeah.
I think it's about time to decide.
-Decide now?
-Right.
If we can sing "WALK" and "Hane"
wholeheartedly, that's good.
If we can really sing them properly,
those songs before them will be...
Or should we try not to make
that section over the top.
Well, the full version
of that is pretty long.
I don't want us to look like
we're trying too hard with it.
I'm starting to think
"SPARK" is just right.
I think "SPARK" would be about right.
Which do you want to prioritize,
the songs or the audience's excitement?
Which one?
If we can sing "WALK"
and "Hane" wholeheartedly...
All right. I tell you what.
-Let's postpone the decision.
-Okay, got it.
He postponed it.
-Thank you very much.
Good work.
2020 OCTOBER 30
2 DAYS BEFORE THE LIVESTREAM SHOW
The stage that they put their
special thoughts into had been set up.
It's amazing. Apparently, there are as
many crew here as a dome stadium concert.
Usually, we'd have an audience down there.
So I'd like to turn it into
something positive.
There's a lot of "We can't do it" and
"We have no choice" in this world.
But I'd rather not show it to my audience...
when we make things.
THE DAY BEFORE THE SHOW
Even on this day, they filmed
videos for the show.
You'll be in the rain and
we'll film it with a high-speed camera.
The last song for
the general audience is "Hane."
This staging is
related to a special memory.
In a concert in 2003,
at the same Yoyogi Gymnasium,
they let it rain.
"HANE"
Playing the video in reverse.
Along with the rain,
time flowed in reverse.
-The floor...
-Staff members, please step back a moment.
Is everyone in?
Okay, the stage...
Ready? I'm gonna take it. One, two.
2020 NOVEMBER 1
THREE HOURS LEFT
The day had come.
Revisions continued
until the very last minute.
I feel like it's hard to see
the bond between members.
I see.
-There aren't many scenes like that.
-Yeah.
It depends on the vibe in between songs.
Everything else is perfectly staged,
but that's an emotional aspect.
Just taking a glance at the others
when you move would be fine.
AN HOUR BEFORE THE SHOW
Any thoughts, Go?
I think just the beginning is fine
if we're gonna do it.
There's still an hour,
they can prepare it.
They've got lots of other things to do.
30 MINUTES BEFORE THE SHOW
15 MINUTES BEFORE THE SHOW
Two minutes to go
until the livestream starts.
Okay, less than 30 seconds to go.
At that moment, the six held
each other's hands without being noticed.
The special time had begun.
"THUNDERBIRD"
We'll sing two songs that represent
who we are now before we say goodbye.
THE FANS SENT THEM A MESSAGE
CONGRATS ON YOUR 25TH ANNIVERSARY!
TO YOU, WHO HAVE STRIVED FOR 25 YEARS
WE'RE MISSING YOU ESPECIALLY TODAY
YOU'VE NEVER STOPPED FOR 25 YEARS
WE WANTED TO SEE YOU
None of the members changed
and we didn't lose any either
and we've been running for 25 years.
The fact that we've always kept
this group alive
really means a lot in our lives, I think.
Being idols for 25 years means that
we had to continue to be loved
by many people for 25 years.
And I thought no one
could understand how that felt.
But now, I really feel like
people understand that.
I've always hoped that
by singing, dancing,
and providing entertainment,
even if it is just a little,
we would be able to help you
and cheer you up,
so we've continued to do that.
But I fully realized
that because our fans supported us,
we were able to keep providing something.
I once again felt that we are connected.
I'm really grateful.
I realize that we've been able to
do this for 25 years because of our fans
every time we do a concert like this.
We've been doing this for 25 years
and of course, it wasn't all roses.
But we've been doing this
for a long time and today...
we get to celebrate this anniversary.
I really feel that our fans are giving us...
courage and energy.
Well, but really,
it would've been nice to see
everyone in person, right?
I really wanted to see them.
-Thank you very much.
Yay!
Okada.
-Okada, you started this.
-It's your project.
Nice smile.
Thank you very much.
What's this?
What? That's awesome.
Oh, wow.
It was from the crew who supported them.
Thank you very much!
-I'm thrilled.
-This is amazing.
Masayuki Sakamoto.
Hiroshi Nagano.
Yoshihiko Inohara.
Go Morita.
Ken Miyake.
Junichi Okada.
And now the six of them,
with 25 years of pride in their hearts,
begin a new story.
Subtitle translation by: Tsuyoshi Koide