I'm Tom Swift, inventor, billionaire,
shoe collector extraordinaire.
But none of that was
good enough for my dad.
I thought if I built him
a spaceship to Saturn,
I could earn his love,
but his mission ended tragically.
Or so I thought.
Turns out, he was sabotaged.
My father survived the attack
and sent me a message capsule
with the data I need to
rescue him from space,
but it exploded when it
entered the atmosphere.
Now I have to find the
pieces of that capsule
and reassemble my dad's message.
A global conspiracy called The Road Back
is standing in my way, so
I can only trust my squad:
my best friend Zenzi,
my bodyguard Isaac,
my adopted brother
Lino, and my AI Barclay.
Together, we're going to find my father
and bring him home.
Tom, we're 100 yards from
the capsule piece I found.
We'll have to go on foot.
Zenzi, you didn't wear heels, did you?
No, but you did.
- Jodhpur boots have a natural lift, okay?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
How much of your father's message
is in each capsule piece?
We won't know until we reassemble it.
Wait, that's a capsule piece?
No, it's just wreckage.
Putting this capsule
back together is gonna be
more difficult than I thought.
The capsule piece we're
tracking is the "brain," right?
Yeah, and it unlocks the other pieces.
Without it, we're screwed.
I don't understand what happened.
I-I don't think Barclay messed up,
but I did build him when I was eight.
I'm running a defrag
and a source code analysis just in case.
Oh, could you translate
that out of nerd?
Okay, think day spa but for an AI.
A software mani-pedi,
then recalculating the
landing vectors by hand.
I'd translate, but you'd only understand
if you hadn't gotten a four on AP calc.
Oh, did I get a four, or
did I tell you I got a four
to make you feel cool?
Don't come for me. I'll
hack your test scores.
And I'll post your
eighth grade school photo.
Ooh, remember when you
tried the one-brow look?
O-okay, okay, you cannot
let Isaac see that.
- I have a reputation to protect.
- Oh, ooh.
Speaking of Isaac, he
mentioned an ex-girlfriend.
Mm-hmm.
I thought he was gay.
He watches your shirt
move when you yawn.
I can't help it if
he enjoys the ab show.
Many people do.
Yeah, I know. I've seen the IG comments.
Okay, a lot of those
people need to pray.
Yes. So he's trans and bi...?
No, he's not bi. He's pansexual.
He's open to falling in love with people
across the gender spectrum.
Hmm, well, judging from
how he brings you coffee,
he's Tomsexual.
And I don't date men who
are interested in Tom Swift.
Operating level:
Beyoncé Formation Tour.
What did I miss?
Thank God you're back.
I used the satellite
data I got from Justin
to model the size of each capsule piece.
Yeah, to show how all the missing pieces
will eventually fit back together.
Now, Barclay, remind
us what it looked like
when the capsule broke apart.
The heat of the reentry
threw off my ability to lock on.
Okay, I did some vectoring
to recalculate a landing point
for the actual capsule.
Ooh, Zenzi, shame about that four.
Sorry, we're gonna have a
couple more math words here.
Stream to map.
If you hadn't been so busy
flirting with the proctors
that got you that two on AP geography,
you'd know that's the Darby estate.
- Chris Darby?
- Mm.
I hate that family.
They are pretentious and rude and...
Kind to us all the time.
- Isaac, they're lovely people.
- I'll reserve judgment.
The Darby estate was built in 1937
when the family discovered oil.
They are literally oil barons.
How cliché. Look, who even uses gas?
Your private jet.
The resources are protected
by a state-of-the-art security barrier.
30 feet tall, steel and concrete,
countermeasures unknown.
Why would your father send it there?
Couldn't it just land here?
He needed to protect it.
If he sent it here, it could
end up in the neighbor's pool
or smash through a coffee shop.
Yeah, the Darbys have over
200 acres for it to roam.
Should I DM Chris?
No. Look, we can't tell anyone.
We don't know who's been
compromised by The Road Back,
or what they'll do to us if
they know my dad is still alive.
What are the angles, Isaac?
It looks impenetrable.
How about explosives?
Can we try asking nicely?
A dinner? An expensive bottle of wine?
Are we saving your dad or not?
I am out of shape.
- Are you kidding?
- I'm serious.
Hey, Mom. Hi, interloper.
I need to talk to my mom.
Can you go sweat through
a shirt somewhere else?
Thomas Alexander Winston Swift,
apologize to Claire at once.
You're full-government-name mad?
I'm sorry, Claire.
Can I get you a glass of water?
You know, as always,
you look parched, girl.
Tom, I am only here to help.
I'd be a great mentor
if you would let me.
Thanks, Claire.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye. See you, dear.
Mm. I do not understand
your distaste for her.
You know, she's my friend.
She plays tennis in track
pants and a headband.
Is she 12?
You are incorrigible.
I try. So, I need a favor.
Plan a dinner with the Darbys.
There's a mineral on
their property that I think
could be a powerful fuel source.
But you know them.
They won't let me explore
without kissing their asses first.
Well, they did tell us
they'd love to see us
after the funeral, but people
never mean those things.
Well, pretend they did.
We'll have a casual,
somewhat boring meal,
you'll help me out, and...
What's wrong?
It's my first social
event since your father.
You know, he was always...
he always made these things so easy.
Well, I guess I can plan
a menu and wear black,
and try not to slap someone
if I hear "everything
happens for a reason."
No, I don't want you to go through that.
I'll take care of it.
No, no, no, no. If you need me
to arrange this dinner, I'll do it.
Thank you.
And after the dinner,
there are some things
that we need to discuss
about the Tubman Social Group.
I will be your attentive student.
Right after we charm the Darbys.
And I expect you to be
on your best behavior.
And wear something respectable.
Like your father's cuff links.
August 30, 1983.
The day Guion Bluford,
the first Black man to
go to space, took off.
Remember how we cracked
this open when we were 15?
Uh-huh.
I got in and out so
easily, my dad never noticed
that his watches went missing on Friday
and didn't come back until Sunday night.
This would make Jay-Z feel broke.
Actually, I heard he came
to a fundraiser here once,
stopped rapping, started buying stocks.
Mm-hmm.
It's in my memory cache,
but I can't find the creation metadata.
I've been trying to figure out
why this photo is here at all.
It's the congressman's bodyguard Rowan.
Wait. Wait, this is from last week,
when you spoke to the congressman.
Watch your tone
when you're talking to the congressman.
Rowan put his hand on your shoulder
during that meeting, as I recall.
Tom didn't seem to mind.
What if Barclay
held onto his image because
Rowan used that moment
in the office to compromise him?
We need to shut down your...
I fixed him. It's fine.
A-and Barclay is not a
device. He's my friend.
We need him to locate that capsule.
And his internal audio and camera
are on a closed loop anyway,
so nobody can eavesdrop on us.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I tracked the location
of the capsule piece.
It's in their drill mines.
Oh, that...
is supposed to be dangerous.
Something about acid and vines.
Did you ever go in them?
Portions of the property were
corrupted by drilling runoff...
Okay, we don't need to hear any more.
I'm not going in those mines.
Uh... you're not going into the mines?
We'll find another way.
And if we can't?
Wow.
You look wonderful.
Your father would be proud.
So excited to see you.
Oh.
- Zenzi.
- Hmm?
What text has you smiling like that?
Oh, it's from Chris Darby.
I wonder if he's still
with that Delta from UPenn.
Barclay, when was the last time
Chris posted a simple-looking
girl with a flea market purse?
Ten weeks ago.
And it looks like she's
deleted him from hers.
Oh, he's single.
- That's interesting.
- Yeah, Chris is smart.
He's Black. We grew up together.
It could be, as Aunt
Lorraine says, interesting.
Chris "trifling and
also bucktoothed" Darby
- is interesting?
- He is not bucktoothed anymore.
He's pretentious. He's rude.
And he thinks he's the
smartest person in the room.
Oh, so you don't like
him because he's you?
Now, now, Zenzi, Tom,
the Darbys are just a little extra.
You know, it's the constant
one-upsmanship I can't stand.
- Mm.
- And they are obsessed
with keeping up with the Joneses.
Or the Swifts.
Remember when Dad special-ordered
- that blue Maybach?
- Oh.
And Mr. Darby hired a private detective
to find him one in the same color.
- People buy blue cars.
- Mm.
Maybe he just liked it.
Or maybe they're tacky,
thirsty and pressed.
Ooh.
Okay.
I got that out. Yeah.
Let's go kiss some Darby ass.
A toast to our most gracious friends
Mr. and Mrs. Darby...
and Chris. We are so moved
that you'd join us for
dinner on such short notice.
We're happy to be here, Tom.
I thought you invited us here
instead of coming to dinner
at our house because you still
thought our ancestral home
was a tacky tract house
that smelled like feet.
Did I say that?
- Oh, yeah.
- Uh, you know what?
I just needed to mature
before I could appreciate
sophisticated design.
Oh, uh-huh.
Zenzi, are you back permanently?
Mm. Yes.
- All done with Atlanta.
- Mm.
And done with that Marcus, I hope.
See, I never understood you two.
It never seemed like a, a good fit.
So this is, uh...
this is good news for me.
How are you holding up?
You know, everything
happens for a reason.
Mm-hmm.
And with friends like you all
to support us through
this difficult time,
I'm sure we'll be able
to manage this weight.
Zenzi, I thought that
your speech at the memorial
- was absolutely beautiful.
- Mm-hmm.
It was touching. It was moving.
It was everything a eulogy should be.
Yes, yes, it was.
Yes.
Well, words sometimes fail us.
But Tom's actions to build the
company speak for themselves.
Mm-hmm.
I used to love your
pool parties so much.
- The giant, giant ice cream trucks.
- Oh, yeah. Yes.
- Ice cream sandwiches. Yes.
- Yeah.
You loved those, Tom.
Yeah. Yeah, I sure did.
My favorite.
Thank God for cardio, right?
Look at your boy now.
Remember you used to
follow the lifeguard around?
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah, he was about 20.
He went to Sarah Lawrence.
Oh, you were obsessed with him.
Zenzi, uh, didn't Tom
steal one of his, um...
his Speedos?
Wait, uh, you... you did what?
- A lifeguard? I... I did not do anything.
- Yes.
He had to drive home in a towel.
Your dad found it in your backpack.
Yeah, no,
I-I think I remember this.
Well, I certainly remember.
Remember we had to pay him double.
A little boy-crush fee.
Hey, guys, he-he left it
in the bathroom and I
just brought it back.
It was... No towel involved.
It's okay, Tom.
I looked at a few bras myself.
Mm. I never,
uh, took any home with me,
but, you know...
Oh. Wait, your dad was so upset.
He was yelling his son had, um...
sugar in his tank.
Yes.
You see, I'm just so glad you
guys got to a place of acceptance.
That...
never... happened.
Oh.
You know, we're having
such a lovely time
laughing at my expense.
But you know what I think is funny?
My parents and I have
always had big laughs
over how every time we
buy something... mm-hmm...
the exact same thing
ends up at your place after you see it.
Hmm?
Hmm? It-it's almost like...
you guys are so desperately insecure
that you have no choice
but to copy and paste...
yourself a life based on ours.
And I think that's...
hilarious.
It's just, it's Tom. Tom.
You know,
Tom, you-you've got all of my humor...
and-and none of my tact.
Barclay,
thanks for doing this drone flyby
to scope out the Darby wall.
My pleasure. I love secret recon.
The security fence seems to be
modeled on classified technology.
I wasn't able to access blueprints,
but it has motion
sensors, heat tracking...
And sound, right?
Exactly. How did you know?
I've seen one of these before.
Hello, old friend.
Thank you.
You need to go deal with that.
I...
am so sorry, Mr. Darby.
The wine got the better
of me, and I just...
We are aware of your limitations, Tom.
And I am grateful for your patience.
Swift Enterprises is looking
for a special mineral,
which only occurs in your area,
for some conductivity experiments.
Since they're no longer in use,
could Zenzi and I perhaps
explore the drill mines?
Absolutely not.
You have got to learn to
think before you speak, Tom.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help it.
You never can.
You wanted to talk to me about
my Tubman responsibilities?
I'm tired. Not tonight.
You don't belong here, Rowan.
- Wait, what... what's going on?
- Mrs. Swift,
I've been trying to reach you all day,
and your staff told me to come back.
I work for Congressman Eskol,
and he asked me to
bring you an invitation
to his spring fundraising dinner.
Mm. He makes you be a human e-vite?
Well, you thank the congressman for us
and tell him that we will be happy
to continue to support his campaign.
He saved my life, Isaac.
He's harmless.
Of course he is.
Can I talk to you about
business for a second?
I worked with Barton for ten years.
And... and now I'm spearheading
a new consumer-facing model
that will bring Swift Enterprises
into its next 50 years of dominance.
And Tom is leading the engineering.
Tom is doing wonderful
things with the company.
But as you said,
he needs guidance.
Swift Enterprises needs a
leader who is ready on day one.
So when my term as interim CEO is up,
I'd appreciate your support
in becoming permanent CEO
of Swift Enterprises.
Lorraine, I didn't mean to...
It's okay.
It's all right. It's just...
You're right.
You're right. Tom isn't ready.
He behaved so poorly
last night at dinner.
He insulted our guests.
But I can't take this away from him.
He's wanted this since
he was a child, and...
I'd break his heart.
Just like he's breaking mine.
I understand.
I'm sorry I get emotional.
Um, it's just I've
barely slept in weeks.
I think we can help you with that.
I'm sure there's something in our
pharmaceutical department that...
can help you get the rest you need.
Thank you, Claire.
Of course.
♪ Work, let's work, work, work... ♪
Want to go for a round?
Wouldn't be a fair fight.
Question...
- what's going on with Zenzi?
- She's just her usual
high-strung, rule-following,
fabulous self.
Why?
She's been going on about
that Chris guy since dinner.
- Mm.
- But she's smart.
She's beautiful. She's well-connected.
I don't see what she'd see in him.
Zenzi's weakness is Black
Harvard alums with bad lineups.
She sees a guy like Chris
and... she can't help herself.
They fulfill her Black
love TikTok dreams.
Meet me at Swift Enterprises, please.
Marked urgent.
Don't keep her waiting.
Got it.
What is this reanimated
sweater doing here?
I thought that maybe if the
two of you had a chance to talk
without your parents,
you could work something out.
I'm open to hearing what you
have to say if you're going
to be... reasonable.
See?
- He's open.
- Mm.
And I think he'd be particularly
open if you apologized...
For insulting his entire life.
Yes, Tom.
Apologize.
Humbly.
From the heart.
Nah.
I'm good.
Same old Tom. Emotional, as always.
Same old Chris. About to
get slapped, as always.
I mean, it's not my fault
you insulted my family
- when you needed a favor.
- But it is your fault
- your breath smells like ass and hot chips.
- You know what?
You're just mad I dared you
in the mines ten years ago
and you came back crying
like a little bitch.
You were a coward then,
and you're a coward now.
I'm calling my security
and letting them know
if you come anywhere near my family's
property again, it's your ass.
Zenzi, you're always welcome.
I'll text you.
I was at the Darby estate one summer,
bored out of my mind.
Chris was always a dick to me.
But that day, he was nice.
He told me that we were going to do...
a "man test."
Don't touch it. The
mine runoff is acidic.
It'll burn you up.
He told me, if I closed my eyes
and-and waited in there
for five minutes...
I'll come back and get you,
and then we can play video games.
And don't be a bitch about it.
Actually wait.
I waited for what felt like hours.
And Chris never came back to get me.
So I ran out and got lost.
I got these cuts everywhere and, uh...
burned off my right eyebrow.
Don't you remember how crazy
I looked in eighth grade?
Yeah.
You said you overshot a brow slit.
What did he say about it after?
He told me he did it
because I was acting too gay.
So, yeah,
I'm not exactly excited
about apologizing to Chris
or going back into those mines again.
Yeah, Tom, why didn't you tell me?
- I have been friends with these people...
- I am done
talking about this.
We need to get that capsule portion.
But how do you solve a
problem like a drill mine?
Barclay, have the roof rack and
the lights put on the G-Wagen.
We'll need four-wheel
drive and the winch.
The farthest mine entrance
is one mile from the Darby residence
and will put you within
100 yards of the location
of the capsule piece.
What about the giant fence?
I did a little recon on the Darby estate
while y'all were having dinner.
It's handled.
We'll go in stealth.
That's a pretty steep fence.
This opening can only
be accessed from above.
It opens to a 50-foot vertical drop
and has the highest concentration
of acidic fumes and runoff.
May I suggest gloves?
So, I'll rappel out of the truck.
But what about that runoff?
I feel like you're gonna
need sunscreen or a wet suit.
I wish I still had mine, but
this is a no-heat natural.
It does not get wet.
Wait, do you still have
that leave-in conditioner
I made for our St. Bart's trip?
Ah, this leave-in is like shea butter
that did some pushups.
The synthetic bonds to
your hair and seals it.
If I could up the concentration...
Then it could seal you.
Barclay, run a polymer
sequence at a concentration
of four moles instead of .63.
At one concentration, this
polymer protects a 4B natural.
But at a higher concentration,
it's an impenetrable barrier.
How will you see through that mask?
Let's cut some eye
holes. Uh, non-starter.
Beyoncé wore this on...
Fine.
May the Hive forgive me.
Which shoe, Tom?
Dior.
Nature, but make it fashion.
Let's go for a hike.
You might want to put these earplugs in.
Okay, Olivia Pope.
You said it's handled.
So, do you need a white
coat and some red wine,
or just a ladder?
Not exactly.
This isn't a fence, it's a system.
Cameras. Sound. Motion detectors.
I had to go through one of these
when I was in the Special Forces.
So, let me guess.
You're going to cover yourself in mud
to hide your body temp
from the motion sensors.
Oh, take out the cameras
with an infrared array
and find the kill switch?
Nah.
Did you put in your earplugs?
Of course I did.
Targeted the localized EMP.
Killed the fence's power
source in this section.
A lot easier than
covering yourself in mud.
- You shouldn't go alone.
- It's a tight fit already.
It's the only way we're
gonna make it down.
I've got this.
Call us if you need any help.
The suit is protecting
you from the acid.
Chris, where are you?!
Chris! Chris! Chris?
Oof. Ah!
Seems the acid is eating
away at that rip in your suit.
And don't be a bitch
about it. Actually wait.
Ah! Ah!
Fix your wig, Tom.
Oh, crap, I'm stuck.
How's it going down there?
Uh, fine! Totally fine.
How are you?
You never knew about Tom in the mines?
Nope. My best friend let
me think everything was fine
so he could save face.
It's how we were raised.
All people care about it is
what will our friends say?
Everyone's just lying, and I hate it.
What about you?
Are you a liar?
I used to be.
Tom and I grew up the same,
but in 2008, my dad went broke
when the market crashed.
And unlike normal people,
my parents lied their
way through everything.
They maxed out their credit cards
on $10,000 tables at
the Tubman cotillion
and couldn't pay my tuition.
And they never let me or my
sister say a word about it
because they were afraid
of what people would think.
Uncle Barton paid for me
to stay in private school.
And Tom... has no idea.
So he's not the only one telling
a redacted version of the truth.
Is that why you go for guys like Chris?
Because they let you keep up the lie
your parents wanted you to tell.
No.
They make me feel like I belong.
Chris wants you to
think that he's the prize
and you're lucky to have
him, but someone like you
should never be waiting to get chosen.
Then why is someone
as cool as you waiting
to be chosen by Tom?
I'm-I'm stuck.
I need you to cut through
a steel beam down here.
There's another suit in
the back of the truck.
Zenzi, you'll have to do it.
I brought a spare just in
case intermittent fasting
had got me too snatched.
And you guys?
Hurry.
Give me the word and I'm down there.
I won't let you fall.
I got this.
My line is stuck and I
can't cut it to free myself.
Wait, did you put on
hair to come down here?
Oh, you're not the only one
that keeps a backup in the car.
This is Camille.
Oh, hey, Camille.
Camille, could you tell
Zenzi to cut this beam
and skip the attitude?
- Oh, are we skipping attitude?
- Yeah.
Will we also be skipping quips
for the remainder of the day?
And now you say...
Thank you, Zenzi.
My nanobots will latch into the
mining lanterns and give us...
The capsule piece.
Okay, let's grab this and get out.
Okay.
He added a security layer in
case someone else found it.
We need to disarm this or
it's going to self-destruct.
Okay, a raised fist and the sun.
Maybe the power of sunrise.
Okay, um...
Oh, oh, try "From the rising of the sun"
to the place where it sets,
"the name of the Lord is to be praised."
Uh...
Uh, your mom's birthday?
Oh, one attempt remaining.
Of course he couldn't make this easy.
- It had to be one of his stupid lessons.
- Look, I'm sure he thought
- that you would be able to...
- Would you stop?
I can be right about
my own father and Chris
without you poking holes
in everything that I say.
Yeah, well, if I had been
given all the information
I needed, I wouldn't
need to question you.
And you can't get mad at
me for asking questions
when you're the one
who's been keeping secrets
- for ten damn years.
- Oh!
So I'm supposed to humiliate myself
so you can ask me if it's true.
Secrets aren't always bad.
I know that my dad paid your tuition.
I never said anything because, Zenzi,
I didn't want you to be embarrassed.
Tom Swift doesn't get
bullied or called too gay.
And I didn't want to
be embarrassed either.
Well, I can't have your back
if you keep things from me.
Even if they are embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Okay, look, let's just
get this capsule piece,
and then never speak
to the Darbys again.
Okay, a Black Power fist and the sun.
To be kept safe, um...
Wait. To be kept safe,
like the watch safe.
Whoo!
- First Black astronaut in space.
- Yes!
I guess my dad knew
about the missing watches.
I thought I told you two to
stay off my family's property.
Is there some jackass quota
you have to meet every day?
You broke in. You're stealing.
I could literally be
doing anything, Chris,
and you would still come for me.
I-I was... I was nice to you,
and you were a dick.
And now I'm not nice, and surprise,
you are still a dick.
You know, in the cliché
version of this story,
this is where the bully
reveals that he's gay.
So let's get to you on your knees
so I can get something good out of this.
That's what I thought.
Do you have any idea what it's like
to be compared to Tom Swift?
My family owns rocks.
You build rocket ships!
I've spent my entire life
hearing my parents say,
"Why can't you be more like Tom?"
You're... jealous.
Not... not no.
Your father was so proud of you.
And he left you this... this legacy.
I don't have that.
My dad said that he's proud of Tom?
Aloud?
This is our parents' mess,
not ours, Chris.
They pit us against each other,
and now we're just
playing out their fight.
We don't even know each other for real.
I am sorry for adding to that.
But we can stop it.
Look, I'll make Darby Minerals
an official Swift vendor.
That way we share a legacy.
I'm sorry about that.
All right, let's have dinner.
Next week? Soho House?
I can... I can sponsor you to get in.
I would rather trim my eyelashes
with a weed whacker than to
ever go to dinner with you again.
This is the capsule's brain.
The other pieces split
off, but we can find them
using this copper alloy signature.
Barclay, export.
Chris said that my dad was proud of me.
That's insane, right?
You are the only one who
could have solved that puzzle.
He chose you for this
because he knew that...
knows that you can bring him home.
And now we know exactly
where we're going.
I'll ask Claire for some PTO.
Oh, and before I forget,
- here is the sleep gel we talked about.
- Oh, yes.
I sourced a prototype from
the chem division archives.
It's a nitrous oxide substitute.
I tried it on myself after work.
It resulted in the
most blissful power nap.
You apply it in places with
sensitive nerve endings.
- May I?
- Mm.
Mm.
Pass me your wine glass.
You can just put it down.
I'll put it down.
Lorraine?
Are you okay?
I did what you asked me to.
Set the thermostat to 65.
What's your ATM pin?
Uh, it's, uh, six-seven...
Stop.
No wonder the trial stalled.
The gel makes the wearer...
suggestable.
What will it take for you
to make me permanent CEO?
You will never be CEO
of Swift Enterprises.
I'm Barton's number two.
I've given my life to this company.
You're a caretaker.
Barton would never leave
our Black family's legacy
to someone who isn't Black.
What are you up to, Rowan?
Congressman Eskol requests
the pleasure of your company
for a private dinner on Friday.
I've never received a hand-delivered
dinner invitation before.
It's better than a 2:00 a.m. text.
Thank you.
Yes!
You did it.
You don't sound right.
Show me your source code.
Isaac, I just figured out
what's wrong with Barclay.
It's a tracking algorithm.
It's sending all of our data
to an unknown destination.
So far it can only access incomplete
blips of video and text exchanges.
But if the spyware
breaches Barclay's firewall,
it can start to relay
full video and audio, too.
All right, quick, use Barclay to send me
your protein shake recipe.
20 grams powder,
two grams sexy.
Tom, Barclay was compromised
by Eskol's body man Rowan.
I'm close, man. I can
handle this right now.
No. Stand down.
I'm gonna handle this a different way.
Hey, Rowan.
You up?
Synced and corrected by chamallow
(www.addic7ed.com)