The city's called Duke
The state's called New Mexico
Among the gangsters
The gringos' fame is inflated
'Cause of the new drug they created
They say the colour is blue
And the quality pure
This potent drug's runnin'
Through the city
And no one could stop it
If they wanted to
The cartel's runnin' hot because
They weren't getting respect
Talkin' 'bout some "Heisenberg"
Who owns the market now
No one knows the man since
They've never seen his face
The cartel's 'bout respect
And they ain't forgiving
But that homey's dead
He just doesn't know it yet
Heisenberg's fame has got
Down to Michoacan
From way far away
They want to taste that meth
That blue stuff has crossed the border
Now New Mexico's livin' up to its name
Looks just like Mexico
In all the drugs it's hiding
Except there's a gringo boss
And he's known as "Heisenberg"
The cartel's runnin' hot because
They weren't getting respect
Talkin' 'bout some "Heisenberg"
Who owns the market now
No one knows the man since
They've never seen his face
The fury of the cartel
Ain't no one escaped it yet
But that homey's dead
He just doesn't know it yet
What the hell are they thinking?
Sending us some loudmouth
who doesn't speak the language?
Politics, man. Politics.
Supposed to be some hotshot hero.
I say it's a bunch of crap.
Hero for Albuquerque, maybe.
Maybe it don't take much up there.