Geez.
- This place is a mess.
- Mm.
You ever hear of a trash can?
And I know you know how to fold.
Uh-uh. Get up.
You know good and well I did
not raise a son this lazy.
Get on up now. It's close to noon.
Yeah?
Hey, it's Earn.
Um, just checking in.
You-you doing okay today?
Al?
Yeah, man. I'm-I'm-I'm...
yeah, I'm okay.
All right. Good, um,
did you get a chance
to look over those forms yet?
They need them to be
signed by Wednesday.
Nope. I, um... I ain't get a chance yet.
- Okay. Just...
- Yeah.
What's up, bro?
Hey.
You all right?
Yeah.
Hungry?
Nah, bruh. I'm good.
You sure? I just learned
how to make pasta.
Nigga, when'd you learn to make pasta?
In a dream.
Yeah, Mayor McCheese was there,
the girl from Dharma and Greg...
Oh, that's, um...
that's my ride, man. I'll see you later.
Is that Sierra?
Yeah.
- Mm.
- What, man?
Nothing, man. I just, you know,
I thought you were
allergic to girlfriends.
- Man, Sierra ain't my girlfriend.
- Okay.
Well, make sure you ask her
if she wants some of
this fire pasta. Yeah?
I will, um, keep that in mind, bruh.
- I'll see you later.
- Mm-hmm.
All right, I'm serious, man.
I'm-a put my foot up in this.
♪ I need some drop,
I need some drop ♪
- ♪ I need a bird.
- ♪ Brr, brr ♪
♪ Color like Durk... ♪
What's up, girl?
♪ 4:00 a.m. I'm just
gettin' started ♪
♪ For my birthday, I
threw me a surprise party ♪
♪ Reminiscin' 'bout the trap ♪
♪ Playin' the first Carter ♪
♪ My life changed when
I had my first daughter ♪
♪ Got my first quarter
flippin' $50 slabs ♪
♪ Your nigga lookin'
at the bills... ♪
You know I used to
dance around here, right?
In that strip club right there.
♪ So you kind of the boss ♪
♪ You keep playin' with me... ♪
Yeah. Yeah, you told me.
You ever go in there?
Shit. Sometimes.
Well, maybe you seen me there before,
like, before we was anything special.
Shit, I could've been
grinding on your junk
thinking you was just
another dumb, broke nigga.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
And I could've thought you
was just another stuck-up ho
with too many damn stretch marks.
♪ Drop a pin, send a location... ♪
You crazy, girl.
God, I'm so glad you
could kick it today.
Yeah.
I swear, I don't see nobody no more.
It's just photo shoots and appearances.
Shit is crazy.
Yeah, I hear that.
Yeah. You get it, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
It's nice to be around
someone who gets it.
106.5 The Jam.
Nothing but the hits.
♪ Uh, uh... ♪
Oh, shit.
Aah!
Yeah!
♪ Hey, yeah, Paper... ♪
How's it going? Go over here?
Yo, Alfred.
Yo.
You should get these shoes.
I ain't got no interest
in looking like no damn black Aladdin.
Ugh. Whatever.
That dope boy from the
hood act won't last long.
Really? Since when can
you tell the future?
Uh, since I'm about that money.
Y-You keep being
smart, but I'm serious.
People gonna get tired
of seeing a sweaty nigga
in a polo and cargo shorts.
Nobody wants somebody famous
to look just like them.
Yo, how much are they?
Man, who cares? If you like them,
have your manager get
them for you for free.
Yeah, that ain't happening.
Yeah, why?
'Cause Earn, man, he don't...
he don't know how to do all that.
He don't get you free shit?
I mean, he get me liquor
sent to the house sometimes,
but other than that...
Oh, my God! Baby.
Baby, you got to level up.
Get you a manager with a big dick.
You know, girl, I don't
know nothing about all that.
Look, enough with the kiddie shit.
You need someone who's working for you.
- Whatever, girl.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, hello?
Can we get some assistance?
He needs to see a couple
sizes in this shoe.
Yeah.
You bossing white people around, huh?
Hey, somebody got to do it.
I got you.
Aw.
Huh?
Ah, that girl just posted that picture.
So sweet.
I love fans.
Huh. Ooh!
I'm sorry.
It tickled. I-I-I'm sorry.
I ain't never felt
nothing like that before.
Oh, you know, most guys would
not be caught dead in here.
Is that right?
Hell yeah. Niggas be acting
like grooming theirself is gay.
That shit's fucked up.
Ain't nothing wrong with
caring about your hair,
your nails, your skin.
Most niggas need makeup more than I do.
You don't need makeup.
Aw, you're so sweet.
No, I'm serious.
It's my brand.
I'm Instagram famous, boo.
I can't be selling my wigs,
and out here looking janky.
I got to compete with
white girls with lip fillers
and butt injections, selling
lip gloss and spray tan.
Shit.
Everybody want to be a black girl,
but the black girls ain't
making no money from it.
Hey!
Watch it.
Um, you need to post on Instagram more.
No, no.
I hope your manager's figured that out.
He...
He's a...
It don't even matter.
Hey, look, no offense, but, um...
I ain't into all that fake shit.
I'm just trying to stay real.
Oh, that's funny?
Huh? That shit funny to you?
Kinda.
Shit, you on the radio,
and you making money.
You been not real.
Uh-uh. Uh-uh, uh-uh.
Y'all got to speak English
if you working on me.
Don't play with me.
I will call Marco over here,
and he will bounce both
of your asses out the door.
See? See, when they start
speaking in another language,
that's when you know they talking shit.
Especially her.
She got a attitude every
time I come up in here,
talking to me up out her nose.
Man, why you bring me here?
Hmm?
We hanging, Paper Boi.
Sh...
Look. I just think we
could be good together.
Okay, so you want a boyfriend?
We can get that money.
We already getting money.
We can attach our brands.
Boost each other... Look, we don't even
have to fuck all the time.
We just got to give them
something to talk about.
Something like... this.
Hey... hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Delete that picture, Sierra.
Why?
'Cause I told you, I ain't
into that weird-ass fake shit.
Uh, why are you so moody today?
Because you ain't ask my
permission to take that,
- that's why.
- Permission? Nigga, you famous.
Look, just delete the
damn photo, Sierra!
Why? What was I supposed
to say, "please"?
- I just told you, I ain't about that...
- What, nigga,
'cause you real?
Fuck this.
You sitting over there, whining,
acting like you better than me
'cause I'm trying to get paid.
Wake the fuck up.
That shit ain't real.
Look, I ain't got to
stop being me, all right?
That's something boring-ass
people like yo ass got to do.
Well, where are you going?
I'm leaving.
I drove.
I can walk, ho.
I told you, like, 50 times, man.
There are no zero gravity
scenes in Star Wars.
- You sure?
- Nigga, you ain't even seen those movies.
Why the fuck do you care?
Whoa!
You Paper Boi.
What's up, man?
Yo, this is so crazy.
We've been listening
to you from the start.
Man, we love that new song, bruh.
I've been driving my
momma crazy with it.
I appreciate that, man.
When I tell my brother
about this, he gonna trip.
- Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah. So what are you doing here?
- I'm just living, man.
- You alone?
You ain't got no car?
I ain't allowed to walk?
Aw, you keeping it real.
That's what's up. That's what's up.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
Well, shit.
I got his watch!
Oh, shit!
Paper Boi!
- Hey, Paper Boi!
- Fuck!
Where the fuck do you
think you're going?
Fuck!
Shit.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Who's that?!
"Who's that?" That, that, that.
What the fuck, man?
- "What the fuck?"
- Shit.
Hey, look, man, I don't-I don't
want no trouble, all right?
I'm just passing through.
You looking for them
boys? Them bad boys?
Yeah. Yeah, you seen
which way they went?
Yeah, I seen. Th-They went that way.
Then they went that way.
Then they went there.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
I'm just high.
- You want some money?
- Nah, man.
Come on. Let me give you some money.
You can't go to the dance
without no money, boy.
Let old Wally help you out.
Wait. Wait!
Please!
I lost my baby.
What?
Take some ChapStick.
I don't like sharing lip
to lip. You got germs?
Don't follow me, man.
Man, will you shut the hell up, man?
Stop following me! Take your ass home.
You in bad shape, boy.
Oh, shit.
Oh, come on, man.
That's you.
Deer guts.
That's what I'll call you.
Big ol' black-boy deer guts.
You're stubborn.
You're stubborn, and you're black.
I'm serious, man.
Leave me the fuck alone!
Boy, you is just like your mama.
What?
What's the matter?
You looking all crazy.
Don't think you can out-slip me.
Why you sitting?
I'm tired, man.
I'm tired. I had a very bad day.
Shit.
Ahh.
I-I just need to think, man.
Boy, ain't nobody could do that.
Nigga, you so damn useless.
You better watch how you
talk to people, deer guts.
You sit around in people's
houses insulting 'em.
You better stand up and make a decision
about how you getting out of here.
Nigga, just leave me alone. Goddamn.
Make the decision.
Nigga...
Keep standing still,
you're gone, boy.
You're wasting time.
And the only people
who got time are dead.
And if you're dead, I'm
gonna take them shoes
and your wallet
and that shirt.
All right.
I...
Okay.
Just...
Shit.
I'm-a count to 30,
and if you ain't walked
out of here by then,
I'm gonna hurt you,
'cause ain't nobody out
here but you and me, boy.
One... two... three...
12... 11... 13...
14... 15... 17...
Shit!
Hey, excuse me.
A-Are you Paper Boi?
Uh, yeah, man.
Yeah, I'm Paper Boi.
You want a picture?
Come on.
All right. There you go.
- Yeah, yeah. I got it.
- All right.
Ready?
Got to give, like, a mob face, man.
Yeah. Do it again.
You got it? Take another one.
All right.
All right, man.
- Thank you.
- Yep.
Be safe out here.
Synced and corrected by Octavia
- www.addic7ed.com -