Yo, we should probably get moving.
You know, the 75 about to be crazy.
Oh, and your fit's on the table.
Yeah.
Hey, man, if you want this money,
we need this college fan base.
And, you know,
first it's this, then it's Spring Fling,
and that's $60K guaranteed.
You heard me, right?
Nigga, I heard you.
$60K.
You do realize I'm trying
to make you more money?
- That's how I make money.
- Look, no shade,
but we both got different
standards of living, a'ight?
- Yeah, that's true, but obviously...
- Where y'all going?
- Oh!
- Oh, fuck, man!
Tracy, man, what'd I tell you
about breaking in my
goddamn apartment, man?
This .38 almost sliced your ass.
But, nigga, you know I'm staying here.
Yeah, but what happened to
"one week," Tracy, man, huh?
One week was months ago.
Man.
You know what? Whatever, man. Whatever.
Where y'all going?
We're going somewhere not fun.
We're leaving right now.
It's-it's... We got to leave.
- That's funny.
- Right now.
'Cause I ain't asked
when. I asked where.
Man, we doing a show.
At Statesboro. For free.
Yo, let me roll, man.
You need security, right?
Look, all I need is a hotel floor, bruh.
We're not staying in a hotel.
Plus, don't you have to
tell your P.O. if you leave?
Damn, yo, you Fulton
County Police or something?
Yo, hold on, hold on.
Bring it back, man.
What you mean, no hotel?
Hey, Earn.
You're not allergic to
jicama, are you? By chance?
I don't... No. I don't know. Listen...
- Cool.
- It's not a hotel, per se,
but-but I think
it might be better. Huh?
- The fuck I'm looking at, Earn?
- Oh, wait.
Th-That's the girl when
both our phones died.
Exactly. And I found her on Instagram.
And guess what? She love you.
And she runs the Pajama Jam.
Okay, we can just stay
with her and pocket the
money from the hotel.
Ooh. She cute as hell, too, boy.
You stay trying to be slick.
Man, I am slick.
Her roommate? Treasurer.
That means Spring Fling next year.
That's, like...
probably more than $60K
if I can, you know, sweet-talk her.
All right, man. We'll see.
You know, any bad bitch
with over 3K followers,
it could be tough.
You know, she got an
unrealistic worldview
on how the world works.
She only got, like, 300 followers.
That's even weirder.
See.
Oh, found my fork.
- Yo, I'm ready.
- Hey, hey, hey, man.
- Oh, I'm ready, too. All right.
- Yeah.
Let's do this, baby.
Oh.
We're...
we're not gonna have enough room.
And we're leaving right now.
Nigga, I'm ready right now.
Yeah, man. $200 for security right here.
- Bring all black, boy.
- Say no more.
Come on, man, we're leaving.
Oh, shit, let me get my jacket, bro.
♪ Sniper Gang ♪
♪ Yeah, I like this
lil' beat right here ♪
♪ Yeah, this a nice little beat ♪
♪ I'm sippin' on Belaire ♪
♪ My chick from Bel-Air ♪
♪ My whip from Germany ♪
♪ I'm cooler than LL ♪
♪ I'm sippin' on Belaire ♪
♪ My chick from Bel-Air ♪
♪ My whip from Germany ♪
♪ I'm cooler than LL ♪
♪ I clap a nigga ♪
♪ Like patty cake ♪
♪ I clap a nigga like patty cake ♪
♪ I'm swaggin', I got flavor ♪
♪ I got sauce, call me Ragù ♪
♪ I love my baby girl ♪
♪ Pussy bald, call her Caillou ♪
♪ I clap a nigga like patty cake ♪
♪ Yeah, that way ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to grab the Wraith ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to grab the key ♪
I think somebody tailing us.
♪ Snatch your baby girl
and skeet all on her face ♪
Oh, no, we good, we good.
They turning, they turned.
It's all good. My bad.
♪ It's either I win or you
lose 'cause I won't accept... ♪
This it?
Yeah. We made it.
- This place kind of stinks.
- Damn.
The fuck?
- You good, bruh?
- Yeah, man. Shit.
A1. That's a good sign.
Hi. Uh...
does Violet live here?
- Hey, guys.
- Oh.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey, how's it going?
Hi. I'm Violet.
'Sup.
Oh!
- I see you brought one extra.
- Yeah.
That's Tracy. Uh, he won't
be staying here, though.
I think he's staying with family.
Nah, nah. I'm staying here.
- We can find space.
- Oh, word? Cool.
- Great.
- Okay, come in.
"Find space."
Okay, guys, just make
yourselves at home.
Uh, so, you guys remember Erika, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah. And, uh, you met Honey.
Mm-hmm.
So, you two can sleep in Erika's room,
and Tracy, you can sleep here.
All right, cool.
You got cameras around the perimeter?
- Uh...
- I'm Paper Boi's security.
He's not really security,
but he'll be fine.
Hey, uh, let me show you
where you're sleeping.
All right.
Hey, you need a hand, big dog?
- I'm good, bruh.
- You sure?
Okay.
Nigga, are you eating chocolate chips?
Yeah, bruh.
Mmm.
You can sleep on the bed with me.
No, no, that's cool.
I can sleep over here.
Don't be stupid.
Come here.
Come on.
All right.
Yeah.
See?
This is nice.
Mm-hmm.
Can I tell you something?
I had a dream about you.
We were holding each other,
naked by this river,
and you were this beautiful white crane.
And I was this magnificent crocodile.
And we were just laying there.
- Hmm.
- Holding each other for warmth.
And then I ate you.
There was blood everywhere.
And then this, like, intense light
just shot through my belly.
And I knew that meant
that we were connected.
I knew this would happen.
Eventually.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, what's up, team
Paper Boi? How we living?
Don't be rolling up on
my mans like that, bruh.
- All right, man.
- Hey.
We know them. They just performed.
What was that all about?
Oh, my God. I'm such a fan.
- I loved your mixtape.
- You're crushing this shit tonight, man.
- Thanks, man.
- That's good shit.
Earn, what's good?
You want to get, like,
a picture or something?
Like those pajamas.
Yeah, you know.
- Yo, that was a great show.
- Good for a college set.
This kid's killing it. Clark,
you killed that tonight.
Oh, thanks, man. Yo,
y'all were dope, too.
I like the outfits, man. Y'all
trying to get lit with us?
- No, man, we gonna hang back tonight.
- Come on.
Look, I could use some weed
though, like, bad. Come on.
- Uh, I don't think we...
- Dang, bro.
I'm sorry about that. We do got bottles
in the greenroom, though.
Carson Flex gonna pull up.
- Y'all trying to hang, anybody?
- Oh, yeah, we'll hang.
- Oh, yeah.
- She would be great.
- They're coming?
- You can go with her.
- Thanks, man.
- Yep, all right.
- I'm-a find you later, right?
- Yeah, I'm-a find you, man.
Generous, man. Thank you.
Catch you guys later.
Don't have too much fun without me.
Hey.
- I'm about to hit the field, all right?
- Yeah.
You need me, just give me the signal.
Hit it from here to there.
- Know what I'm talking about?
- You already know.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- Hey, man.
- Appreciate you.
- For sure, baby.
This nigga really think he a bodyguard.
Yeah.
He's just trying to earn his
money. I can understand that.
You really showed up.
I'm sorry. We have a lot
of artists bail on us,
so thank you so much for coming out.
Oh, no. It's all good. Thank you.
Well, uh, this is my girl, Elise.
- Hey. How are you doing?
- Hi.
She's majoring in modern literature,
and she's actually
writing a paper on you.
What, like, a Paper Boi paper?
- Yeah, yeah.
- All right.
- I can feel that.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- You're very aware of your words.
- Oh, yeah?
You're the only rapper
doing that right now.
I appreciate that.
Yo. Should we save Alfred?
Nah. No, that's good for him.
I haven't seen him smile in a while.
He needed that.
If I'm worried about anybody,
I'm worried about that nigga.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
You know that Clark County dude?
- Yeah.
- Industry plant.
- Yes, I've been saying that.
- For sure, for sure.
Yeah. No, I mean, it's obvious.
What the fuck?!
Are you fucking kidding me, man?
I saw that shit, bro!
No. Okay, just stay.
- Hey, what?
- Hey, chill, all right?
- Yeah, I'm good, man.
- Just, I'm-a check this.
- I'm-a check this out.
- He was looking at
- those skimpy-ass whores.
- Who gives a fuck?
I wasn't asking you.
What the fuck you think
he's supposed to do?! You
think you're the only one?
Oh, after I bring all
of y'all into my house.
Listen, bitch, keep your
hands off of me for real.
- Why not?
- Do it again, see what the fuck happens.
- I'm not scared of you.
- Bitch...
You fucking broke-ass security guard.
Whoa!
You all right? You all right?
Yo, you okay?
Oh, damn. Shit.
I knew her ass was crazy, man.
I told you, man. What
happened, yo? What happened?
Nothing, nothing. Oh, my eye.
Hey, she slapping the shit
out of you ain't nothing, man.
You good?
I told you her fucking ass
was crazy, man. What happened?
- Yo, we should...
- Those fucking niggas
- was trying to get me!
- We got to... we got to go now.
- Yes!
- We need to leave right now.
Hey, Paper Boi. What's up,
man? What the fuck, man?
What's the issue? What, man?
- Just chill, you guys.
- Where the fuck y'all going?
- Man, we standing right here, nigga.
- What y'all do
- to my little sister, man?
- Stop it. Go, go,
- It wasn't us. It was, um...
- Come on, man.
What we running from? I
don't even know why we running
- from these niggas, man.
- Yo, where the fuck is Tracy?
Why are we running from them, man?
Dude, you can't do
shows in a hospital, man.
- They ain't gonna do shit.
- Hey! I'm talking to you.
- Man, we listening nigga. What?
- Watch your tone. Relax. Relax.
- No, fuck this dude, man.
- I-I'm gonna take care of this.
- You want to square up?
- Hell no.
Relax. It's cool. Okay, listen.
We're all here to have a
good time. Black people.
Just non-violent. We're trying to...
- Bitch!
- Oh!
Run, nigga, run!
Run! Run! Run!
Thank you, man.
What the fuck?!
Oh!
What the fuck are we running from?
Let's go.
Oh, shit.
That shit was crazy!
Me and Paper Boi!
- You good?
- Yeah, man.
I can't believe y'all got
me out here like this, man.
Sweating through silk. Shit.
I'm looking like a goddamn peasant, man.
All I know is that girl Violet
better not touch my weed.
That's all I know.
- Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Fuck, bruh. Yo, yo. Come on.
Oh, shit, come on.
Come on. What the fuck?
All right, man. Goddamn.
Come on.
All this fucking running. Shit.
- Fuck, man.
- We got to get off campus.
Violet knows everybody.
Look, all I know is I
need to find some weed,
or I'm gonna lose my shit, man.
Wait a minute. Y'all smell that?
- What? What is it?
- Sniff. I mean, use your...
Certain hats, weed.
Yeah.
Citronella. This way.
Fuck, man.
Holy shit. You're fucking Paper Boi.
- Yeah.
- That explains the citronella.
What are you doing here,
man? Are those silk pajamas?
Yeah, man, I was... I was
performing at Pajama Jam.
The what?
Forget it, man. Hey, y'all got weed?
Yeah, yeah, fuck yeah, we got weed.
We got fuckin', fuckin'
smoking with Paper Boi.
Hell yeah, man. Y'all on them Backwoods?
We got some other shit in the
house, too. We'll smoke you out.
Thank you. Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Hell yeah.
Oh, what the fuck was that?
It's all good. It's just
some pledges, you know?
Newbies got to pay the price, right?
Hey, uh, here, come on.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Yeah.
Hey. Paper Boi's here. Come on.
Man, this shit is bugged
the fuck out, bruh.
Man. But I like what
y'all doing here, bruh.
You don't give no fucks.
Hey, yo, I just... I
got to tell you, man.
You're like... one-one of
my two favorite rappers.
You know, you and Post Malone?
Yo, that Postal mixtape...
That changed my shit up, man.
Hey, man, is that... is
that an elephant rifle?
Uh... yeah.
Yeah, a bunch of the alumni
send guns to the frats.
A lot of them are in the NRA.
Oh, okay.
I was... word. I was thinking
about joining the NRA.
Y'all are crazy.
We have a whole gun room.
- A gun room?
- Yeah. Want to see?
Wait.
We got a few of these, too.
Oh, shit.
Hell yeah. Y-You want
to see the gun room?
- I'm trying to see that shit.
- No, go ahead.
- Yeah.
- Come on with it.
Whoa.
Excuse me.
Oh, yeah, man, like I
was saying, though, yo.
Yeah, a lot of us are from the South.
I'm, like, a really big UGK fan.
Pimp C, like, one of the
last real prophets, man.
That was like the-the
Crime Mob, D4L, Maceo days.
Yeah, those were classic.
So you into snap music?
Man.
You remember that song, um...
♪ The bubble gum. ♪
Yeah, that was my shit.
♪ Laffy Taffy. ♪
Yeah, my cousin used to
always play that shit.
Hmm.
Matter of fact, hold on.
All right, pledges, get the fuck up!
Gonna do this dance for our new friends!
♪ Girl, shake that laffy taffy ♪
♪ That laffy taffy,
shake that laffy taffy ♪
Snap, y'all!
♪ Girl, shake that laffy taffy
♪ That laffy taffy,
that laffy taffy ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm lookin' for Mrs. Bubble Gum ♪
♪ I'm Mr. Chik-O-Stick ♪
- ♪ I wanna ♪
- ♪ Dun dun dunt, oh ♪
♪ 'Cause you so thick... ♪
♪ 'Cause I stay so hard ♪
♪ You can suck me
for a long time... ♪
All right, uh, stop, y'all!
♪ This a candy store ♪
Uh, I got to go give
these pledges a mud bath.
Uh, y'all need anything from the fridge?
- We good, man.
- Yeah, we're good. Thank you.
All right. Yeah, cool, man.
Move out!
Oh...
Tonight, man...
Tonight was some bullshit.
Yeah.
I know. Uh...
I think we need to talk
about the real problem.
Yes.
Thank you.
Tracy's got to go, man.
Oh, shit, nigga, I'm
talking about your ass.
What? What are you talking about?
- How am I the problem?
- Man, you gonna
act like tonight wasn't a
bunch of your bad decisions?
Did you not see Tracy throw a girl down
- a flight of steps?
- I saw it.
And it happened after
she threw a cup at me
for talking to another broad, man.
And speaking of which, that bitch...
Man, that bitch was
crazy from the start, man.
And you knew that.
And you still put me in
the same room with her ass
so you could save the same
amount of money I would
have made in an hour
or less off the block.
Tracy escalated a harmless situation.
- Bro.
- You saw that, bruh.
Nothing was about to happen
until something happened.
I've been talking to Clark
County's manager, man.
About what?
The fuck you think, Earn?
Managing me. Actually managing me, man.
Shit I could be getting,
shit I should be getting out here.
Look, you family, man, and
I'm trying to ride with you,
but sometimes that
shit ain't enough, bro.
'Cause money is important.
I see exactly what's happening out here.
It's getting colder, it's
getting harder to eat.
I need shit, Lottie
needs shit. You need shit.
I gotta make my next moves
my best moves, man, so...
Something gotta shake.
I don't think you're cut out for it.
- Oh... shit, boy.
- The fuck.
Fuck, no, man.
What the fuck is all this shit?
- That's fucked up, bruh.
- Fuck, bro.
That's fucked up, bruh. For real.
No, goddamn it. God, man!
Al, just chill.
Damn it, man.
My car and shit, man.
Fucking college bitches.
Who the fuck are we dealing with, man?
Look at all our shit on
the fucking lawn, man!
- Oh, God, bro.
- What the fuck?
Oh, fuck no, man!
Look at this shit.
They cut up all my shit!
Goddamn!
And of course my fucking weed gone.
Oh.
- Goddamn, let me see that, bruh.
- Oh, shit.
Not the kicks, bruh.
Damn, I couldn't even be mad at that.
That's kind of... It's impressive.
Huh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God, these fucking hos, man.
Fucking hate these
fucking college hos. Shit!
Where's my laptop?
Violet.
Violet!
Ah, shit. This nigga losing it, man.
- Violet, open this fucking door!
- Hey, Earn.
Violet! Violet!
- Open this door.
- Earn, it's not really that serious.
Don't fucking touch me, man.
Yo! Violet!
That's your cousin, bro.
Earn, look, man. Ain't
nobody in there, bro.
Nobody's there; they gone.
- Nah, somebody's in there.
- Look, we'll just go back home.
They're gonna open this fucking door.
We'll just figure this out.
- What is you doing, man?
- Oh!
Yo, Earn. Earn, man.
Earn! Earn, Earn, Earn, man.
- Hey, man, I got you.
- Hey, man, let's go, man.
- You'll get your stuff back.
- Let's go, man. Earn!
- Man, you don't hear that shit?
- It's cool.
- Man, don't do this to me, nigga.
- I'm on probation!
Open this fucking door!
I'm leaving with or
without your ass, man.
- Come on, man.
- Get your ass home.
Earn. Come on, man.
Fuck that nigga. I'm out, man.
That shit was crazy, huh?
Earn?
Bruh, you pulling
that fire alarm on 'em?
Now, that shit was fucked up, my nigga.
- You ain't have to do 'em like that, man.
- For real.
Yo, this nigga was kicking the...
kicking the door
and shit...
Oh, fuck, man.
What made you go like
that, bro? Kickin' the door?
What, you think a woman
gonna open the door
for you, kickin' the
door like that, bro?
Tracy, could you do me
a favor and stop talking?
I'm not in the mood.
"I'm not in the mood."
Yo, man. Your little
cuz got a temper, man.
You need to watch out for that one.
You got to watch out for me?
Nigga, this is your fault.
Yeah. It was me that
made them girls crazy.
Nigga, it was. Were you there?
Hey, both of y'all, chill.
Did you steal that?
Goddamn!
Yo, is you the campus police?
Let me see your badge.
Let me see it.
Bang!
Nigga, it's old as fuck, bruh.
You can't even put a
bullet in this thing.
Look at his face, man.
He's scared as hell, boy.
Yo, pull this car over,
so I can fight this nigga.
Fight this nigga?
- Earn.
- Yeah.
Who are you...? Oh, he playin', right?
Pull the car over.
- Earn, relax, man.
- Al, pull the fucking car over.
- You better get your cousin out.
- So I can beat this nigga's ass.
- Beat my ass?
- Yeah, beat your dumb ass.
- Your fucking dumb country ass.
- Ooh, I want to see
- that shit, man.
- Pull the fucking car over.
Bruh, if this car stop, I'm-a give you
- these fucking hands, bruh.
- Nigga, I wish it would stop.
- I don't give a fuck.
- Earn, man.
- I'm-a turn your ass...
- I'll knock you the fuck...
I'm so sick and tired of
your fat fucking mouth!
Open... open this...
- Oh, hey, man. No, no, Earn.
- Pull the fucking car over, man!
- Yeah, you want me to pull over?
- Pull... yeah, pull the fucking
car over, so I can
beat this nigga's ass!
- All right, all right, let's go.
- Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Come on, man up.
Come on, dawg.
All right. What's up?
Nigga.
Come on, man. Stop playing, dawg.
Get in the car.
Come on, man. I don't
want to do all this, bruh.
Come on. Stop playing with me, man.
Yo! Stop fucking playing with me, man!
Yeah.
- For real? For real?
- Yeah, yeah, nigga.
I told you to stop fucking with me, man!
- Tracy, man.
- It's your fucking cousin, man.
- It's not my fault, bruh.
- Come on, man. Come on.
- This nigga, man.
- Come on, man.
That's your fucking cousin, man.
You want to fuck with me, nigga?
- What? What?
- Come on, nigga.
What's up? What's up, pussy?
Oh! Shit.
Goddamn.
Synced and corrected by Octavia
- www.addic7ed.com -