Previously on Velma...
I'm sorry I didn't believe you
about your hallucinations.
But, Velma, I told you this.
Your mother didn't go missing
because you solved a mystery.
She left us.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la!
Be in my office Monday morning.
I'll tell you everything I know
about my mom, Dr. Edna Perdue.
That book you gave me
opened my eyes
to your inner beauty.
Wait. Really?
Brenda?
I'm your mother, Carroll.
And I'm your father, Darren.
If there's one thing
teen dramas get right,
it's that nothing is ever
actually a teenager's fault.
We're all really just paying
for the sins of our parents.
They're either lying to us...
Oh, yeah, you discover
that polonium, Marie Curie.
...or trying
to change us...
...or hiding
some dark family secret.
Mom!
If Velma hallucinates
while learning the truth
about Grandma, she could die.
Let the adults handle this,
son. Blythe?
But when it comes
to truly crappy parents,
no one beats my dad.
Dad, I need to get
to school early
to talk to Principal Rogers.
She might have clues
about Mom's kidnapping.
That's great.
Really? But you hate
that I think she's missing.
Are you kidding?
That's even better, Sophie.
Uh, what's happening?
People only wear fleece
when they're looking
for startup money,
or...
Oh, no. Going hiking.
What's happening is
I'm taking paternity leave.
Paternity leave?
When I was born,
you doubled your work hours.
We know, but Amanda's birth
has made your father realize
he needs to find
a work-life balance,
or risk messing her up
the way he messed up--
Well, you know.
Hey, Velma,
want a ride to school?
We got champagne,
AC, and the driver
has a funny story
about how he survived
the Khmer Rouge.
Uh, sure, thanks.
Absolutely not, Frederick.
Unless this is your selection
for our hunt?
No, Father. I like her now.
Have you heard of inner beauty?
That's a myth, you fool!
Well, at least my relationship
with my father isn't that bad.
Principal Rogers, I just want
to say thank you for--
Hey, do you mind?
Oh, yeah, mmm.
All right. Go help Velma
not hallucinate
while she talks to your mom.
But don't let her
push you around.
You're your own man.
Damn straight.
And just real quick,
when do you need me
to have your pants mended by?
Ugh. Now.
But lunch will be fine,
I guess.
As I was saying, thank you
for agreeing to talk to me
about your
mad scientist mother.
Now spill it!
Okay. Well, buckle up,
because things are
about to get weird.
See, in the 1970s,
my mother, Dr. Edna Perdue,
was a brilliant neurosurgeon,
who had discovered a way
to keep the human brain alive
outside of the body.
I never should have
been an organ donor.
A woman scientist?
Her work
caught the attention
of Army General
Harry Meeting, who felt
he could use it to spy
on what he believed
to be the biggest threat
to the American way of life.
Oh, let me guess. Communists?
Meat made from plants?
-Women's sports?
-No!
Meddling kids.
It was the 1970s, and
according to General Meeting,
meddling kids
were ruining everything.
War's not, like, cool, man.
General Meeting had tried
to infiltrate these groups.
But what if war is,
like, cool, man?
But the meddling kids
always foiled him
with a technique
called mask pulling.
So, General Meeting
tried to infiltrate them
through hypnosis.
But this only worked
so long as no one ever...
...snapped their fingers.
So, when General Meeting
saw my mother's work,
he wondered,
what if she could
put a soldier's brain
into the head
of a meddling kid?
He called the program
the Special Covert Operations
Brain Initiative,
or SCOOBI.
SCOOBI? And wait,
what did SCOOBI do?
It attempted to create
the perfect spy,
by swapping people's brains.
Oh. Did it work?
No.
And as the years dragged on,
and the pressure
to produce a result grew,
she slowly went insane.
Until one day, my mom
bricked up her secret lab
in our basement,
hid her journals
so no one could
recreate her work,
and was committed
to the Crystal Cove
Insane Asylum.
Wow, I can't believe
that's your mom. I mean,
playing God, removing brains.
That's some white people shit.
She was always a trailblazer.
But wait, my mom disappeared
after finding
Dr. Perdue's journals,
and the dead girls
all had their brains removed.
Could they be connected?
Wow. For all
your personality flaws,
you're actually
a pretty good detective.
If there is a connection
between your mom
and the dead girls,
the key to finding it
is in this box.
You're late, Daphne.
Are you rebelling already?
As a criminal, I like it.
As your dad, knock it off.
Sorry, to get past my moms,
I had to put on
their wedding DVD.
They'll spend all day arguing
about who let Uncle Lou dance
when they knew
he had a heart condition.
What's all this?
- Uh, that...
- Remember,
not a word about
why we really need her
until we know we can trust her.
What happened?
Why is there a needle
in my good boob?
It's an adrenaline shot.
Your heart stopped
from a hallucination.
Norville, why didn't
you make me laugh?
I tried. I did three minutes
of hilarious new stuff.
You just didn't
get the references
because you haven't
taken calculus yet.
Velma, I'm sorry,
but I'm not telling you
anything more about your mom
until you stop
your hallucinations.
The nurse only has
one adrenaline shot left,
and I want shrimp for lunch.
Allergies be damned!
But if you think
my mom is connected to
the serial killer in any way,
I have to know.
Please.
Fine. Velma, your mom--
Norville, what am I gonna do?
I hallucinate
because I feel guilty
about having caused my mom
to disappear.
The only cure
is to find my mom.
Though, I have heard
some good things
about alcoholism.
Okay, well, uh,
when was the first time
you hallucinated?
Hmm. It was a few days
after my mom went missing.
This is all your fault, Velma.
Why'd you have to go
and solve your own mystery?
Okay, but you'd been
trying to find your mom
before that, right?
Why didn't the hallucinations
start until then?
As a man analyzing a woman,
-can we assume menses?
-No.
But wait, something else
did happen that day.
My dad took me out to breakfast
for the first time ever.
Hey, Dad. Great news.
I've been looking for Mom,
and I think I have
some new leads--
Velma, stop! For the last time,
your mother wasn't taken.
She left us.
Now, see if you can
solve the case
of how to entertain yourself
while I make work calls.
Wait, I've always wanted
my dad to love me more.
Maybe the hallucinations
are my subconscious
keeping me
from looking for my mom.
Because you saying
your mom was kidnapped
upsets your dad
and just makes it harder
for him to love you.
Exactly! Wait!
Oh, no, I hallucinate
because I have daddy issues.
Gross.
Okay, so, don't search for
"Daddy issues
and teenage girls."
And bookmark.
But if your
hallucinations started
because your dad
doesn't believe
your mom was kidnapped,
maybe they'd stop
if you make him believe
she was kidnapped.
I tried,
but whenever I mention it,
he shuts me down.
Then I have to eat a whole pie
to feel better,
and I will die
before I give that up.
What's another way
to cure daddy issues?
Eh, I wouldn't know.
The thought
of having any issues
with my own sweet, sweet daddy
is foreign to me.
Really? Even though
he's the one
who basically taught you
to be a beta.
Excuse me?
My father is not a beta.
He drives the speed limit,
no matter how many people
are honking at him.
Knock, knock.
Norville, can I grab you
for a second? I need a hand
-with some heavy lifting.
-Of course, Dad.
Because heavy lifting is
exactly what alphas like us do.
Thanks. We're helping
your mom's old boyfriend move.
Ah, that doesn't help.
Ah, come on.
Don't even think
about it, Aman.
I haven't slept in 48 hours,
so if you're serious
about paternity leave,
then you have to realize
your family is more important
than your phone. Oh!
I am so posting that.
Hey, Dad, can we talk?
You can be drunk,
if that's easier.
What? No!
Paternity leave applies
to all my children.
Let's go to lunch. Run!
Aman!
Okay. Quick lesson
in the power of crystals.
This is angelite.
It treats anxiety
by transmuting
aberrant thoughts
into productive cathexis.
Whoa, cool!
So, do you rub it?
Or grind it up
and snort it at a party,
like regular anxiety meds?
You take it
and bang it on your head,
real hard.
Wait, really?
No.
Crystals are a hoax, Daphne.
Like vitamins, or internships.
That's why we loved
working here so much.
Charging idiots 30 bucks
for a mystical rock
feels like a crime,
but it's totally legal.
So, that's why
you turned to real crime
when the crystal market
collapsed, to chase that high.
Yes. But the party ended
when your moms raided us.
Sure, we got away,
but they stole you.
And now they're gonna pay.
Everyone's gonna pay.
Whoa, wait. What?
For crystals. Everyone's
gonna pay for crystals.
See, thanks to
underemployed millennials,
ex-reality stars,
and zero sense
of global security,
believing in crystals
is back, baby!
We can sell this hall
and retire
to the non-extradition country
of our choice.
Hello, Angola.
Wait. You're leaving already?
But there's still so much
I don't know about you.
Daphne, I'm on the run.
A few more days of mining,
and we're gone.
But we can get to know
each other until then.
Say yes, and we'll tell you
why you have orange hair.
Oh, my God, yes!
I smoked during pregnancy.
Like, a lot.
Like, I should be dead.
Oh. Well, I'm glad
you're alive.
Let's get to know each other.
So, what do you wanna
talk about? The Miller case?
Oh, right. This is lunch
with my daughter.
Uh, a couple of things.
First, I think this place
has changed
since the last time
we were here.
Oh, my God,
I totally didn't notice.
Sophie's boobs are out
so much these days,
this seems normal.
Oh, speak of the devil.
"Buy diapers."
Oh, you think that's bad?
Sophie told me I can't
pee in the shower anymore,
because that's where
she bathes Amanda.
Now I have to pee in the shower
at school, like a weirdo.
Pro tip, aim for the drain.
She'll never know.
Oh, I'll try that.
Wait. Did you just
teach me a life lesson?
Yeah. You want another one?
Don't date anyone who owns
more throw pillows than books.
Yes! Oh, my God. I had no idea
you at least realize
Sophie kind of sucks.
It will make it so much easier
to kick her ass out
when I find Mom.
Wait. "Find Mom"?
Not this again.
But that's what I need
to talk to you about.
To stop my hallucinations,
I need you to believe me
that Mom was kidnapped.
Velma, please.
Can't a father and daughter
just enjoy a nice meal
at a strip club,
-without it being awkward?
-Uh, no?
But we were having fun
for the first time ever.
Yeah, we were. Look at us.
Can we at least talk later?
I have to stop
my hallucinations.
Hold that thought.
I have to make some work calls.
Oh, so you're going
to work, are you?
Well, then call me
Ernest Shackleton,
'cause I'm headed to a pole.
Fred? What are you doing
at Nana's Nipples?
I thought rich guys went
to the Tits Carlton.
That's our next stop.
Yeah, my dad found out
I like you
and is now trying
to "normalize" my brain
back into thinking
girls like Chestiny here
are hot.
You!
Get away from my son!
He just asked the manager
if there's a stripper
gender pay gap!
There is. Guys make way less.
But thanks to you,
Fred won't call it
reverse sexism.
He-He-He's ruined!
Oh, yeah. Keep it all on.
Show me nothing, baby.
Velma, what are you
doing up there?
I'm doing what every girl
is doing up here.
I'm just trying to get
my dad's attention.
And one day, it will work.
Velma, stop!
You have my attention.
That's why I was on the phone.
I was calling Sophie
to tell her
I need to spend the rest of
my paternity leave with you.
Wait, what? Are you nuts?
She'll kill us both.
I don't care. Like you said,
we were just starting
to have fun together.
And let's be honest,
the last couple of years
haven't been very fun.
What with my hair turning
-gray--
-Mom being kidnapped.
Sure, right. All that.
So, what do you say
we go have some fun?
Just us.
Ahh! I said, "Wait!"
Eh, by the time
I say something,
I could have already paid
$5 for another coffee.
Oh, from now on,
I'm wearing 'em.
Amanda, where are you?
Oh, God!
To the best day ever.
And yes, I know I still need
to talk to my dad
to end my hallucinations,
but I don't want
the fun to stop.
Yesterday, for the first time
ever, he said,
"Your birthday's
in March, right?"
Hey, can you answer that?
I'm, like, substitute
teacher-level hungover.
No, it's Gigi.
And you were right.
My dad has taught me
to be a beta.
So I'm working on power moves.
This morning, I left my bowl
-in the sink.
-Damn.
Hey, Velma.
When you see your pops next,
tell him thanks for me.
Homie changed my life.
Fred, I've told you.
My dad isn't
the Bhagwan Shree Rajneesh.
No, he helped my dad
buy Chestiny's contract
from the strip club,
so we could date
and get my head sorted out.
Isn't that right, babe?
Anything but kiss.
Uh, that's impossible, Fred.
My dad's on paternity leave.
The only love he's buying
right now is mine.
Yeah, I don't know.
Your dad figured out
all the legal junk yesterday.
Wait, what?
Oh, my God!
You only told Sophie
you wanted to spend
your paternity leave with me
so you could work
while I was at school.
What? No!
I'm only here because--
'Cause I'm having an affair
with this woman!
An affair? How dare you?
Also, here's that extra work
you requested.
Where's that box?
I'm ready to learn
how my mom is connected
to those dead girls.
So you finally got your father
to believe you?
Freaking awesome.
That's right, I swear now.
And you're wearing
a leather jacket?
I stole it, baby.
Off a teddy bear in the mall.
We don't know
what's gotten into him.
I'm out of here.
And I might be late for dinner.
Don't pour my milk.
Okay, now give me that box.
Velma, wait. Are you sure
you won't hallucinate?
Yes. My hallucinations
were caused
by my desire
to make my dad love me.
But after today,
he's dead to me,
and if I don't care
what he thinks,
then I won't hallucinate.
Oh, my God. Honestly,
I was, like, zero percent sure
that would work.
But I'm cured.
I can find my mom.
How is she connected
to the dead girls?
Okay, so after my mom died,
her house was put up for sale,
and Fred's family bought it.
And that's what first got
your mom interested in her.
In her effort to learn more
about Dr. Perdue,
Diya uncovered the one thing
my mother never intended
anyone to find, her journals.
That's how she learned
Edna was my mom,
and that her secret lab
was still buried
underneath the house.
So,
that's what my mom
was doing at Fred's house
on Christmas Eve.
Looking for
Dr. Perdue's secret lab,
before Fred's family
- moved in.
- Yes.
Hmm. Okay, but how does
this connect my mom
to the dead girls?
There's only one explanation.
Your mom opened the lab, and...
The ghost
of Dr. Edna Perdue
has returned
to finish her work!
Wait, wait, wait.
You're saying my mom
was taken by the ghost
of your mom?
Really? I thought only idiots
and B-list actresses
believed in ghosts.
Uh, have you seen
our school bathrooms?
No living human could do that.
Ugh, I don't have
time for this.
I have to go find my mom
and her not-a-ghost
serial killer kidnapper.
Damn it, Norville.
Where is everyone?
And the crystals
are all gone.
Wait. Are you leaving already?
But I'm not ready.
I need to know so much more.
Daphne, the only thing
left for you to know
is you deserve better than us.
A gun?
Hold on. Is that
a goodbye gift?
Oh, I didn't get you anything.
Sure you did. You are
our insurance policy
in case your moms
try and stop us
on our way out of town.
Wait, what?
Is that why
you let me find you?
Just so you could use me?
That's so manipulative!
Which explains
why I'm so manipulative.
But still, I'm your daughter.
And your parents
are criminals, Daph.
I'm sorry--
Yeah, you are sorry, Darren.
We've been on to you
since you busted out of jail
and put a geode
through our daughter's window.
You have?
We're maybe not the best cops,
but we're great moms.
We always know
what you're up to, sweetie.
What's this?
"Brenda"? Huh! Why does
that name ring a bell?
She's one of the dead girls,
and that's her tank top.
You can see stains
from her boob contour.
What? Carroll found
that shirt down here,
and I upcycled it as a rag.
We only have
one planet, people.
Velma!
Where are you? I'm sorry!
Also, please be cool for once
and don't tell Sophie.
Velma? You can't be here.
I told you, Father forbids it.
Fred, there's a secret lab
under your basement
and I have to find it.
Now, you can help me,
or you can keep
telling yourself
that if you jump
through all of Daddy's hoops,
maybe one day, he'll love you.
Please. As if my father
has the time
to make me jump
through hoops. Hey!
Hairy girl not wrong.
Only way to earn
father's respect
is take a stand.
You want I help kill him?
Yeah, let's do it. Hmm?
Whoo-hoo! I'm rich!
Now Daddy will love me.
Norville, what's going on?
You're ignoring my calls
like I just took you
on a first date.
That's because a man
answers his phone
when he damn well
feels like answering
his phone, Lamont.
Okay, well, Gigi almost died.
She was stung by a bee
digging her pants
out of the garbage at school,
and the nurse was
out of adrenaline shots.
Oh, no!
I'm making her
a "Get Well" lemon cake.
-Wanna help?
-I'll get my zester.
Wow. I never knew
how big it was
down here in the bad boy room.
I just hang by the door
ever since the rats
ate that butler.
The lab entrance!
But it's still closed.
If my mom didn't open it,
where'd she go?
Oh. Maybe it's one of those
doors where you push in a brick
-and it opens.
-Fred, wait!
No!
So you really knew I was
with them the whole time?
Or was that just another lie?
Another lie?
The only thing we've ever lied
to you about is the dog.
Truth is, he went to a farm.
No, I know you stole me
from them.
Stole you?
We didn't steal you.
We took you.
We gotta go.
And there's not gonna be
enough room for all the goods
and Daphne.
Oh, okay. Well, as parents,
there's only one right
decision to make here.
Damn it! They got away!
Oh, my God,
I feel like such an idiot.
They abandoned me twice.
That's why we never
told you the truth.
We loved you
from the moment we saw you,
and didn't want you
to ever feel
like you were unwanted
for even a second.
I love you, too, Moms.
Ooh, angelite.
That cures anxiety.
Velma? Sweetie?
-Can you hear me?
-Mom? Is that you?
I found you.
But did you, like,
get a weird haircut?
No, Velma, it's me.
The parent who only
abandoned you emotionally.
Dad? Wait. Did I die
and go to hell?
Damn it! I always knew
atheism was a gamble.
How did you find me?
I can locate your phone,
like any good parent.
Okay. Sophie installed it
so you never catch us in bed
talking smack about you.
No, no. I don't have
time to sit here
and listen to some
too-little-too-late excuse.
Yes, you do.
Because your legs
are still buried.
Now look.
I'm sorry for how much I worked
when you were little,
but I figured you were fine
because you had your mother.
But then she walked out on us,
and I wanted
to be there for you,
but it's too hard
because I feel so guilty.
So, I hide at work.
But you wouldn't feel guilty
if you just believed
she was kidnapped.
Who would kidnap your mother?
No one wants to talk about 9/11
that much anymore.
Fine, don't believe me.
I'll just find her on my own.
I'm fine.
Footprints?
People were just here.
And what's this?
Jinkies!
"Jinkies"?
Why are you saying "jinkies"?
Is this like when you tried
to make "Keep it frosty"
a thing?
No!
Someone wrote "jinkies"
on this paper.
But why?
You'll never know, Velma.
Oh, no, Dad!
I need you to believe me
that Mom was kidnapped,
or I'm gonna die!
Okay, okay, I believe you,
I swear!
-I believe you.
-Oh, my God!
That... That did it.
-She's gone.
-Psych!
Oh, no, she's back. But how?
Hold on. Were you lying
about believing me?
Velma, I want
to believe, but...
Wait.
Oh, my God, you're right.
She was kidnapped!
I actually believe you,
for real this time.
-He does?
-You do?
He does!
No!
My hallucinations
are finally over.
Are you sure? 'Cause I feel
like you've said that before.
Like a few times.
No, it's over.
I know my dad believes me.
I'm so sorry
-I doubted you, Velma.
-It's okay.
Because when you saw
I was willing to die
for my truth,
you finally came around.
-Because you do love me.
-Yes.
But also, "jinkies" is written
in your mother's handwriting.
She was just here.
Jinkies!
Okay, now you're totally
trying to make it a thing.
So, if this was all about
your dad believing you,
how did making you laugh
also stop your hallucinations?
Right? Or kissing Daphne?
"Kissing Daphne"?
Uh, the point is, I don't know,
but I'm sure
I'll figure it out.
It would be pretty lazy not to.
Now, come on!
Whoever has my mom,
and removed those
girls' brains,
was just here.
So the question is,
where'd they go?