Previously on Velma...
I had to find you because I still
didn't know if you'd listened to my VMs,
voice mails, let alone
responded. Did you?
The police
found my mom's car
abandoned and empty,
except for her glasses,
and a single wrapped gift.
It's like what I said.
Someone is trying to
recreate Dr. Perdue's work.
Which means... Brains,
where's my mom?
Best of luck in all your
future endeavors, Wilhelmina.
Would you ever consider interning for
me at Jones Gentlemen's Accessories?
Really?
Oh, my God, yes.
What the actual hell?
Oh, my God, I do remember
who the serial killer is.
It's...
It's me.
So, uh, yeah.
After all that, it turned out my mom
wasn't kidnapped by the serial killer.
Apparently, she was
the serial killer.
And yet, it got worse.
Because it made no sense.
Reading Dr. Perdue's journals,
I couldn't understand why my mom
would recreate the work
of a mad scientist.
I have to talk to her.
Nothing added up. And yet,
no one seemed to care.
Okay, the next item on the block
is this 1969 van,
recently used by Diya Dinkley,
one of America's only
female serial killers.
You can own a
piece of her-story.
And yet,
it still got worse.
Velma. There you are.
Any comment on today's
front page story?
Because I'd also
lost my best friends.
Norville, I'm sorry I accused your
dad of being the serial killer.
Norville, that's enough.
Velma needs us.
The only thing I need is to
kick your ass for kissing Fred.
And yet, it somehow
got even worse.
Okay, the swelling from your
daughter's beating has gone down.
Can I go do your job for you and
question my obviously innocent mom now?
No. We need you
to watch something.
So, why did you do
it, Doo-dad? Huh?
Your choices on the
lady confession form are
"revenge, jealousy,"
or "You know how we get!"
Okay, I'll tell you.
I did it because I wanted to
put the brain of a popular girl
into the head of
my daughter, Velma.
What?
But that makes even less sense.
If she's now saying
she's guilty,
why did she pretend
to have amnesia?
Or try to frame me with
Brenda and Krista's bodies.
Velma, we're
struggling too,
but Diya insists she did it.
Meaning this afternoon, she'll
be sentenced to death row,
and, worse, brutally hounded
by true crime podcasters.
Death row?
Then please, just give me
five minutes down there
to figure out what's
really going on.
What's that?
Look, you didn't
hear it from us,
but the only way Cogburn's letting
you anywhere near your mom's cell
and potentially
messing up his case
is if you get arrested yourself.
Arrested? I see.
Well, then call me
a medieval minstrel
'cause I'm about to loot.
Yeah. Unfortunately,
he's so worried about
you talking to your mom,
the only thing he'd arrest
you for right now is murder.
Murder?
Now, Daphne.
Though I married
into this company,
I'm the one who built it
from a small ascot shop
into the multi-billion dollar
target of child labor
lawsuits it is today.
- And I did it all by...
- Moxie!
Aggressively supporting
politicians who look the other way.
And I have impeccable taste.
Like this. Our
newest fragrance.
Oh, I love that.
What's it called?
"Smells Like Mommy."
Yes, it's terrible.
Freddie named it.
Which brings us to the
point of your internship.
You mean I'm not
just a diversity hire
- for the company photo shoot?
- No.
See, Freddie doesn't
listen to me.
But yesterday you were able to coax
him back to being popular like...
- A modern-day Anne Sullivan.
- A celebrity dog trainer.
Regardless, if Fred has any hope
of running this company
one day, I need your help
teaching him that same kind of
strategic thinking and drive.
So, I'd have to spend
more time with Fred?
I have to sort out some
personal stuff with Velma first.
Oh, hey, this is a good
business lesson to learn.
Nobody cares.
Fred, open up.
I need your help to get
arrested and save my mom's life.
Ugh, not now.
Fred?
Fred, why are you raging
out? Can I assume sports?
No, Velma.
I'm raging out because my
mom doesn't think I'm capable
of running the family business.
But she's wrong.
Look how good I paint
the company logo.
Your company logo
is an asterisk?
Oh, to indicate a troubling
footnote about child labor.
It's not an asterisk.
It's a flower.
I painted those ones better.
Wait, Fred. You
bought this van? Why?
Because all cool fashion
advertising for teens
is just trashy,
pedo-tinged sex stuff.
So, maybe if I drive
this thing around,
I can make Gentlemen's
Accessories cool
and prove to my
mom I'm not a joke.
Because nothing's trashier
or more pedo-tinged
than teens in an old van.
That's actually not a bad idea.
Wrong! It is a good idea! I
can run the family business.
Oh, wait. You just agreed
with me. Sorry, I'm...
I'm just sensitive from
always being wrong about everything.
Well, then I have good
news, 'cause I'm taking you
to the one place no one
will ever doubt you.
Officers, arrest me.
I've committed the only crime worse
than eating ethnic food on an airplane.
Don't care. Until your mom
is removed from our custody
and goes to death row,
your presence here is
like a condom in a porno.
Not wanted!
But would you arrest
her if someone like me
said someone like her
was bothering him?
Well, yeah, that would do it.
Norville, have you seen Velma?
She wasn't at the pep rally.
And you know how much she loves
knocking over cheerleader pyramids.
Sorry, Daph. But I'm just
too tired of Velma's bullshit
to care where she is.
Norville never swears.
Oh, my God.
Huh? A geode?
"My dearest daughter..."
I almost died
while finding this.
I think it has something
to do with the murders.
"And while I know it can never make
up for having abandoned you twice,
please consider us even
for the $10 I took from your
locker!"
Be quick. Your mom doesn't have
much time before her sentencing.
And the creature that lives
in the toilet feeds at 2:00.
Mom?
- Velma?
- Mom!
I know you didn't really
wanna change my brain, right?
I assume you misspoke and meant
change my bra? 'Cause I get that.
Velma, I did it because
I wanted to put the brain
of a popular girl into the
head of my daughter, Velma.
- But why?
- No, Velma, listen to me.
I did it because I
wanted to put the brain
of a popular girl into the
head of my daughter, Velma.
Yeah, Mom. I get it. Wait.
You keep saying the
exact same thing.
Yes! When I try to say
what actually happened,
that's what comes out.
I don't think I had amnesia,
I think I was hypnotized.
Hypnotized? I thought that
only worked in '70s cartoons
and '80s comedy clubs.
Wait. But the cure
is always snapping.
Sorry. Time to go to death
row. You failed, Velma.
You're not ruining this for me.
Let me out of here.
My mom was hypnotized,
and the serial killer
is still out there.
Yes, he is, Velma.
Oh, no, he's here!
Daphne?
Sorry. I just had
to clear my throat.
My moms told me you were here.
Ugh, I'd rather you
were the serial killer.
Well, then, good news.
Because I have something
that might help us find him.
A pocket watch?
Wait, I remember
that from somewhere.
And
do you remember me?
How am I on a dirt road?
Oh, no! I died, and
hell is a cross country race.
Wait. This is a memory
of the night I started
hallucinating, two years ago.
I'll never find my mom.
My mystery solving caused this.
No one will ever believe me...
because I'm a weirdo.
Oh, my God. I remember!
That pocket watch belongs
to the serial killer.
I recognize it because he
didn't just hypnotize my mom,
he hypnotized me two
years ago as well,
to cause my hallucinations
and keep me from finding her.
Now, did you check the watch
- for fingerprints or semen?
- No need.
There's an inscription.
Okay, but Daphne, it
belonged to a serial killer.
It's 100% caked in semen, and you're
just, like, holding it in your hand.
"Harry Meeting?"
Of course!
General Harry Meeting
hired Dr. Edna Perdue
to run his Project SCOOBI
brain-swapping program.
And he was a master of hypnosis.
But, wait, he's dead.
- Man!
- Exactly.
Which can only mean one thing.
It's
General Meeting's ghost,
back to finish
Dr. Perdue's work!
For the last time,
ghosts do not exist.
So, if you'd like to
join me back in reality,
I'm gonna see if this watch jogs
any memories for the Brains.
I'll come with. But first...
I'm sorry about
kissing Fred. Forgive me?
And I promise nothing will
ever come between us again.
Hold up. I have to
take this. Victoria.
What? Fred was caught
trying to lure teens into
a van for trashy sex stuff?
I'll be right there.
I am so sorry. I have to
go. But here.
Perfume?
Is that to remember
you while we're apart?
Yes. But Victoria
also wants to know
if you like it and or
get a terrible rash.
Text me your
thoughts and be safe.
Fred, tell your mom I'm getting
in the car you sent right now.
What do you mean you
didn't send a car? Oh, God!
Ugh, fine. You sent a limo.
Yes, I know the
difference, you asshole.
Okay.
Clap, clap. Group shower
discussion of the day.
Aren't you so over characters making
dramatic entrances on TV shows?
- For sure.
- Totally.
I like the quiet characters
who don't get much to do.
I actually love
dramatic entrances.
-  Velma?
- Yeah.
And before you say anything, my mom
didn't kill you and put you in those jars.
She was hypnotized
by whoever took you.
So please, tell me
you recognize this.
- Where was that?
- I do...
not know.
-  Sorry.
- I don't either.
Well, great! Now I have nothing
and my mom's going to the chair.
Which is exactly what
you deserve, Velma.
Well, not your mom
going to the chair.
But you were given the
best thing in the world,
and every day you treated
it like worthless garbage.
Hair that's full of
bounce and easy to style?
No! Norville!
And now, he's
transferring schools
because it's too hard for him to be
around the person who betrayed him.
What? That's impossible.
I know I messed up
by accusing Lamont,
but Norville would've told
me if he was leaving school.
He did.
He left you a voice mail.
Just one of the 1,000
you never listened to.
I don't...
I don't have time for this.
I have to save my mom.
And where did her
phone come from?
We're naked!
What's wrong, baby?
Three Chaka Khan
songs have come on
and you haven't even
bobbed your head.
Ugh, nothing.
I'm just wondering if I made
the right decision to leave...
Oh, my God! I'm home!
So Brenda and Krista's
bodies were used to frame me.
But, wait. Lola's was
found by someone else.
Norville, where
are you when I need you?
Fine.
Velma,
it's Norville. I'm switching
schools. See you in hell.
If I ever visit from
the Halls of Mandos.
That's a Tolkien reference,
which I know you hate.
Damn it, Velma. Why didn't
you ever listen to these?
Hey, Velma,
it's Norville, and
I have huge news.
It's banana pudding
day in the cafeteria.
Call me back!
Hey, Velma, it's Norville.
Who's got two thumbs and
wants to say good morning?
This guy!
Yeah, that's maybe more of
a visual joke. Call me back.
Hey, Velma, it's Arnold,
the Actornator.  JK, JK, it's Norville.
Call me back.
Wow. This is the first
voice mail he ever left me.
Uh, hey, hey, Velma.
It's Norville Rogers
from... From math.
I know we don't really
know each other,
but I... I just wanted to say
I'm sorry your mom got taken,
and I think it's cool that
you're wearing glasses now.
Wow. He even noticed these.
Mom's frames are made by
Jones Gentlemen's Accessories?
A pocket watch!
Oh, my God! Harry Meeting used
Jones Gentlemen's
Accessories pocket watches
for his hypnosis. That's it!
Dad! Dad! I figured it out!
How to wash that sweater?
You've literally
never smelled better.
No, that's just some dumb
perfume Daphne sprayed on me.
Mom's innocent.
What? How?
My glasses! It was my glasses!
Mom didn't drop them in her
car the night she was taken.
She left them as a
clue for me to find.
But how are glasses a clue?
Unless they solve the mystery of
why a girl can't get a date, right?
Sorry, I'm
drunk. Please continue.
I'll explain everything on
the way to the Jones estate.
If I'm right, Daphne
and Fred are in trouble.
So, if the serial killer caused
your hallucinations with hypnosis,
how did me believing that your mom
was kidnapped stop them?
Because my hallucinations
preyed on my insecurity
that I'm a weirdo no
one would believe.
So, you believing me
counteracted that.
Same with Norville saying
he liked me.
I thought it was because
he made me laugh.
But it was because he
made me feel cared for,
the way a cool-ass boss bitch
like myself deserves to be.
And I'm falling off the wall.
Velma!
Are you okay? 'Cause if
not, we can definitely sue.
I'm fine. Just go get the cops.
On it. But could you
maybe fake an injury?
- The Joneses are a cash cow.
- Get the cops!
Okay. How do I sneak
into this lab again?
Hey, Angela Lansbury, or whoever
is in charge up there now,
please don't let me die today.
There are so many things I
haven't done yet in life.
Like, make a bucket
list. Or this.
Hello.
You've reached Norville Rogers.
And, if this is
Velma, don't forget
you're a piece of...
Norville, look, I know you hate
me, but in case I die tonight,
I just wanted to say you'll
always be my best friend.
That's it. Bye. Love you.
Love you? Oh, no!
Ah! What's happening?
Don't donate my body to science!
Ugh, great.
My phone's dead. Now I
can't call back Norville,
or order Thai food.
"To find the lab
entrance, walk 32 steps.
The jersey number of
the great O.J. Simpson"?
Ugh, God. Dr. Perdue, could
this journal be more dated?
"Now, look for the
stone that is as perfect
as Woody Allen and Mia
Farrow's marriage"?
Wait, there it is.
My glasses.
I hope this doesn't
keep happening.
Daphne, wake up.
Velma! Get
me out of here.
Oh, and Fred, if there's time.
I will. I just have
to figure out how.
Oh, that's it.
Excuse me!
Wait. Do you think
seeing us fool around
will give the serial
killer a heart attack?
Worth a
shot. Oh, God!
And now you die, Velma.
Then I guess I better smell
good for Angela Lansbury.
Oh, my God, you're a genius.
How did you know the
perfume would do that?
My shrill voice
usually repels bats.
So when they attacked
me in the well,
I knew it had to be the
perfume driving them crazy.
Ahhh! Get, them
off! Get them off!
Wait, no. Keep them on.
Velma, how did you
know we were down here?
Was Fred right about the government
putting trackers in those vaccines?
No. After connecting General Meeting
to Jones Gentlemen's Accessories,
it was obvious.
So, it is the ghost of
Dr. Edna Perdue. I knew it!
Don't be an idiot,
Fred. It's the ghost
of General Harry Meeting.
Stop before I think less of
you. Just let me explain.
This all began when the serial
killer tried to frame me
for the murders of
Brenda and Krista
by putting them in my
locker and recycling bin.
But then Fred raged out in court
and went to prison for
those murders instead.
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
Wow, crazy couple of weeks.
But the third body, Lola's,
wasn't used to frame me. Why?
Because the serial
killer needed a body fast
to exonerate Fred and
get him out of prison.
But why would the serial
killer want Fred out of prison,
only to then take
him at Fog Fest?
Because the serial killer is...
- Mother?
- Victoria Jones?
Formerly known as
Victoria Meeting,
the daughter of
General Harry Meeting.
Once I learned of her
past, it all made sense.
I mean, first off,
only a real monster
has a destination
wedding in Bali.
What? Mother, how could you?
Because she wanted
to replace your brain
with that of
someone more capable
of one day running Jones
Gentlemen's Accessories.
Replace my brain? Hold up.
Am I not your special
number-one little guy?
I tried to encourage you,
Freddie, but in the end,
I couldn't let your incompetence
ruin my life's work.
The way my father's incompetence
ruined Project SCOOBI.
Huh? I thought
Project SCOOBI failed
because Dr. Perdue went insane
trying to swap people's brains.
That's the public
story. The truth is
Dr. Perdue succeeded in her
brain-swapping procedure.
But then my father tried to take
all the credit for her work.
When Dr. Perdue found out,
she undid the experiment,
bricked up her lab
and hid her journal,
so her work couldn't
be recreated.
But hoping to make her talk,
my father had her
institutionalized.
But Dr. Perdue didn't crack,
and without the journals, my father
couldn't reproduce her results.
Project SCOOBI was shut down.
- No!
- And we lost everything.
Wait. Our family was also poor?
Can this
day get any worse?
To save us
from financial ruin,
I married William Jones, the
man whose family business
supplied the pocket watches
my father used for hypnosis.
- You love me, right?
- Shh.
And after building
Jones Gentlemen's Accessories
into a global brand,
you couldn't stand to see
it undone by your own son.
So you decided to give
him a better brain
by buying this house
and finding
Dr. Perdue's journals.
But your mom
had already found them.
So, when my mom
showed up here two years ago,
you hypnotized her
and made her rebuild
the lab, while you found
the perfect brain to
put in Fred's head.
Case closed.
Okay, but why pick the brain
of a hot, popular girl?
We're literally the only
murders people care about.
Because I wanted
someone like me.
An ambitious,
status-conscious young woman
who could appreciate
what she might achieve
as the male president
of a global corporation.
But now I see the
perfect brain for Fred
is the one I tried
hardest to keep away.
William.
Oh, God. Look at his
eyes. He's hypnotized.
I had no choice.
The poor fool figured
out what I was up to.
Victoria!
Think this through. Once
my brain is in Fred,
I'll just go to the police.
Right after I've
looked at myself naked.
No, you won't, Velma,
because not only
are you brilliant,
who more than you
would truly appreciate
the advantages of being a
handsome, rich white man?
Oh, advantages?
You think we like
being president of the United
States 97% of the time?
The job sucks!
Having spent time
with the Brains,
I was reminded that hot,
popular girls your age
don't yet realize just how much
the deck is stacked against them.
But a stumpy know-it-all
with bad eyes
and a worse haircut,
such as myself, would.
You know what, Victoria?
You're right. I am so in.
- What?
- Velma!
- Fred will die.
- And worse, be embarrassed!
Exactly. I am so sick
of rich guys like you
not only not realizing how
much is handed to them,
but still thinking
they're the victims
when they mess everything up
because of their lazy
entitlement and fragile egos.
My ego is not fragile.
Yes!
Rage, Fred. Rage with the anger
of a dad who just bumped his
head and break your restraints.
No! What are you doing? Stop!
Fred, your mom is getting away!
You did this!
No, Fred. I only said those
things to rile you up.
I mean, yes, I feel
that way, but...
No. I'm glad you
said it, Velma.
Only friends tell
each other the truth.
And I'm proud to
call you a friend,
no matter how annoying
I find your voice.
Wow. I'm already loving
our new truth dynamic.
Now get out of here.
I'll stop my mom.
Hello, Mother.
Freddie, I'm sorry.
But I, um... I have an excuse.
- A good one.
- Really?
Quick, find the button that
makes the bucket go up.
It doesn't work like
that. We have to climb.
I see.
So, I guess I just
live down here now?
- Victoria? How?
- It's not Victoria.
Mother never could have
wanted to swap my brain.
She told me she's been possessed
by the ghost of Dr. Edna Perdue.
It made so much sense
when she told me,
I accidentally dropped the
gun and, well...
Here we are.
So, say your goodbyes, girls,
as I'm about to transfer your
brains to these cave walls.
Velma, if this is the end,
I need you to know
that I love you.
- I love you too, Norville.
- What?
- Norville?
- Daphne!
I mean, I love you, Daphne.
Velma, I got your
VM. Voice mail.
And I love you too!
Norville, watch out!
Well, it appears I've
gotten away with it,
you meddling ki...
Mother? Ghost of
Dr. Perdue? Hello?
Oh, my God. She's dead.
Like, really dead.
It's over.
It's finally over.
This feels amazing!
Like, best day ever! I
solved the case! Happy dance!
It's true.
I'd solved the case for good.
But like all
prestige detectives,
had I actually lost
more than I found?
Vermin Dorkley Day!
And we also have keys
for your friends.
We're not friends.
Norville killed my mother.
She tried to kill me first.
Only because she was possessed
by the ghost of your grandma.
Fred. Ghosts are not real.
Oh, what a surprise.
Velma's standing up for
Norville, the love of her life.
No, that's stupid.
Sure, my personal life was in
shambles, but I got my mom back!
Okay, so it's a dark mystery
origin story of Boo Boo Bear.
TV got even better while
you were kidnapped.
All right, sounds
great. Turn it up.
And maybe shut the curtains.
Velma, did you change
the locks again?
Let us in. We still
live here. Hello?
Still, all our lives were
changed forever by what had happened.
I can't sleep, Dad.
It's either my
Spanish test tomorrow,
or the fact that I
killed Fred's mom.
Have you tried marijuana?
What?
And events
had been set in motion
that could not be reversed.
Because
little did we know
the real mystery
was just starting.
Well, Cogburn, here's everything
I used to catch the serial killer,
bring home my mom, and basically
embarrass your entire force.
Oh, it takes more than
that to embarrass us.
But you ever feel like becoming a
real detective, we could use you.
You've got a sharp brain.
Thank you.
That actually means a lot.
yeah, almost like a man.
Another thing Velma
was right about.
No such thing as ghosts.
Hello? Hello, hello?