Previously on Velma...
No!
My hallucinations
are finally over.
"Jinkies" is written in
your mother's handwriting.
She was just here.
He is the future CEO of Jones
Gentlemen's Accessories!
Is he, though?
But I had to find you
because I still didn't know
if you'd listened to my VMs,
voice mails, let
alone responded.
Gigi almost died.
She was stung by a bee
and the nurse was out
of adrenaline shots.
Your
mom opened the lab and...
The
ghost of Dr. Edna Perdue
has returned to finish her work!
So, at long last, my
hallucinations were cured.
Damn it!
I was able to completely
focus on finding my mom
and the serial
killer who took her.
Oh, come on.
But first I had to figure out why she'd left
behind the word "jinkies" for me to find.
Since my mom wrote mysteries,
I started by reading
all her old manuscripts
looking for the answer.
But the only thing I found in
them was a cure for my insomnia.
So, then I thought it might be the
serial killer's license plate number,
But it wasn't his license plate,
nor was it JiNKiES,
the party clown,
who'd fallen off the
radar awhile back.
Jinkies! The clown!
Velma, I have to talk to you.
Not now, sorry.
But wherever I looked,
it was just dead end after
dead end after dead end.
Oh, God! Sophie! No!
There's a message written
on the wall, in her blood.
Oh, God, if she's dead,
who's gonna clean that up?
"Aman, will you
go to the Crystal Cove
Fog Festival with me?"
Demon! Back to hell with you!
Velma! Stop! This
was a fogposal.
A fogposal?
You know, like a promposal,
but for Fog Fest.
Fog Fest?
You know, the one night a year
all of Crystal Cove comes out
to celebrate its world
famous spooky fog.
And pick a Fog King and Queen.
Celebrates?
It's a word meaning...
Are you having a stroke?
No. I know what fogposals
and Fog Fest are.
What I don't understand is
how it can still be happening
with a serial
killer on the loose.
What happened to
curfew? It was working.
Curfew is over! Because
it's not a serial killer...
it's the
ghost of Dr. Edna Perdue.
And curfew can't
stop a ghost, Velma.
That's just basic physics.
Blythe went to the
press? But this is crazy.
People would rather
believe in a ghost,
than stay inside
for a few nights
just so they can party?
What's that?
Look, you're not the only one
worried about curfew ending, Velma.
Which is why no girl will be admitted to
Fog Fest without a date to protect them.
Smart, right?
Wait, girls have to
have a date? Great.
So Fog Fest is not only
dangerous, it's sexist, too.
Okay, well, at least I know the
police aren't buying this ghost crap.
Attention!
All of you wondering why the police
have not yet caught the serial killer,
it's because it's a ghost and
not because we're incompetent.
Now let's get ready to party!
But most of all,
I owe the honor of winning
Fog King to my Fog Queen...
...Velma Dinkley.
Velma?
Is that a joke, Fred?
Or are you being serious?
Or is it that cable comedy
thing where it's both?
No, I'm serious.
A girl-killing ghost is
living in our basement.
In the grand scheme of things, who
cares if I'm attracted to a nerd?
Fred, we have no issue with you
liking an intelligent woman.
Our problem is you're
going to take over
Jones Gentlemen's
Accessories someday,
and yet you seem to barely
grasp what it is we sell.
Not true. We sell ascots,
cufflinks, and for the ladies,
bags that make other
ladies feel poor.
No, Fred, we sell the best.
And Jones Gentlemen's Accessories
is sponsoring Fog Fest.
So, if you can't
prove you're the best
by being named Fog King,
how does that make us look?
Like assholes, Fred.
Like assholes.
You can't win with Velma.
So, either you find a way to come
home with that Fog King crown,
or do not come home at all!
Gigi, come on.
Norville was a bad boyfriend.
He ignored you when you
almost died from a bee sting.
And his grandmother
is 100% a ghost
who's killing our friends.
I know, but I still wanted
him to ask me to Fog Fest.
Guys, it's a serial
killer, not a ghost.
- Norville?
- Gigi, ghosts are scary,
but nothing's scarier than a
world where we're not together.
Will you go to Fog Fest with me?
- What?
- Mmm.
I'll have to think about it.
But if I say yes and the ghost
of your grandma steals my brain,
that's it, we are through.
I understand...
boo. Get it?
No.
But that's what
I love about you.
who am I kidding?
Of course I'll go to
Fog Fest with you.
- Norville!
- Oh, my...
You're going to Fog Fest?
You can't actually believe this
ghost BS about your grandma, too.
You're a man of reason.
You talked me out of
my flat earth phase.
Of course, I don't
believe in ghosts, Velma.
But I really hurt Gigi's
feelings by ignoring her calls,
and I will do anything
to make it right.
So, I need Fog Fest to happen.
And honestly, I think
you need Fog Fest, too.
What? No, I don't.
My anger is rooted solely in this
town's selfish desire to party
instead of stay inside
and stop a serial killer.
Velma, come on.
No one loves celebrating all the
crazy stuff that happens in our fog
more than you.
From entering the
fog in one place
and coming out another...
...to thinking
you see a monster in the fog...
...only to realize it's just
someone you know, holding something weird.
You even like
how things can somehow
farcically switch
places in the fog.
You've been working
on that "jinkies" clue for days.
The best thing you can
do is let off some steam.
And what is steam,
if not hot fog?
I don't know.
Maybe you're right.
But girls have to
have a date to go.
And my bottom of the barrel kill
myself desperation date is taken.
Oh, I'm honored
you'd think of me,
but why not just ask who
you always used to go with?
Hey, Daphne, can you believe
all this dumb ghost stuff?
Oh, God,
it's another ghost!
The ghost of Velma.
Someone make it disappear
by trying to talk to it.
Yeah, yeah, I know I've
been MIA, but what...
- What the hell, Fred?
- Go to Fog Fest with me.
Please.
Stop throwing money at my face.
You're supposed to
scare me, not hurt me.
No, Daphne. Fred's
really asking me,
and I'm supposed to be scared
he's back into basic hot girls who
work out and wear non candy jewelry.
Oh, if only that were true,
my buttery little beach ball.
- But I am asking Daphne.
- Huh?
I have to be Fog King.
Excuse me?
Wait, you said
Fog King, not f...
In that case, I will
happily go with you, Fred.
- Yes!
- But, Daphne!
Are Fred and Daphne
are back together?
What does "jinkies" mean?
Well,
- we're off to Fog Fest.
- Have fun.
I'll just be here, alone,
catching the serial killer.
It's a ghost.
You know what? I'm not
gonna let you ruin my fun.
Daphne. Daphne!
I see you ignoring me.
Yeah, what's that like?
Wait, and now you're drinking?
That's uncharacteristic.
What's going on?
Wait.
I forgot I also used my mom's
terrible manuscripts to kill spiders.
Detective
Diya Jinkies held the note
in front of a candle flame,
and a secret message appeared.
"I ache for you,
Detective Jinkies.
Love, Santa Claus."
Mom, gross!
Wait, that's it.
A phone number.
Hello?
Is this
the serial killer?
You better not make a
skin suit out of my mom
just because brown don't crack.
Damn it, he hung up.
Okay, Velma, what did you hear?
There was a crowd,
a roller coaster,
and a foghorn.
Oh, my God, the serial
killer is at Fog Fest.
My queen.
Okay, girls can't go to
Fog Fest without a date,
so our only hope of
getting in, is makeup.
Like a lot. Like, I'm talking
40-year-old actress
had an audition.
Single guy, you can enter. Woman
with a date, you can enter.
Next!
Evening, officers.
My name is Manny.
And as you can tell by my
mustache, I am a male human,
and not at all related
to Velma Dinkley.
Okay, sir, I don't need you
mansplaining who you are to me.
There's something
funny about you.
Not LOL funny,
but more thoughtful
and well observed,
like a female driven comedy.
Uh, are you suggesting I am
a woman dressed as a man?
Because if you are...
- Nut tap!
- Ahhh!
Very good.
Only a true man would know
the joy and camaraderie
found in the surprise tapping...
...of another
man's testicles. Ahhh!
And now, to find
the serial killer.
- Nut tap!
- Ahhh!
That is assault.
Where is
he? Where is he?
Where is the serial killer?
Ring. Ring.
There he is!
Wait. Why aren't we
dropping and puking?
I see the serial killer!
It's
a ghost, you idiot!
Also, sorry, my guy.
But I paid the carny to
keep us up here for a bit.
No, I have to get down
now. He's getting away.
Norville, what's going on?
Gigi, I have something
very important to ask you.
I told you no, I'm not wearing
elf ears when we make out.
Uh, no. Look, I am so sorry
I ignored your calls, when you
almost died from a bee sting.
I know how belittling it feels to be
sent to voicemail by someone you like.
I'm talking about Velma.
- I used to really like her.
- I know.
Well, you deserve
better than that.
So, I am here tonight to ask...
Gigi, will you be my Fog Queen?
No, I can't die! Sophie's gonna
put a treadmill in my room!
Hey, guys, I'm Fred Jones.
Vote for me for Fog King,
or I will make it my
life's work to destroy you.
What?
Norville?
Where'd the serial killer go?
Who is that tasty snack?
Well, at
least I seem to have
scared the serial killer
away from Fog Fest.
Stop staring.
I know I'm eating like a caveman
in a natural history diorama,
but I'm having a bad night.
We're not disgusted.
We're impressed.
Can you teach me how to
unhinge my jaw like that?
I wanna join a sorority.
Impressed? But that's
such a double standard.
Every day at lunch, you're like,
"Hey, mayonnaise isn't soup."
We've never met
before, but I'm Olive.
As in O-live-to party.
Cool.
Well, I gotta squirt.
Oh, my God, and
you're hilarious.
Norville, what the hell is this?
You really think you can
beat me for Fog King?
Yes, I do.
You're gonna be a
big Fog King loser.
Guys, guys.
Since we're already
on the dance floor,
how about we settle this
the old-fashioned way?
Dance-off!
Ugh, those feel played out.
I was thinking a fight-off.
It's like a dance-off,
but with fists.
Oh, uh, I don't think that...
Norville, please!
Being Fog Queen isn't
that important to me.
Gigi, stop!
You're only saying that
because you're so damaged
by being sent to voicemail
by Velma, I mean me,
that you don't think
you deserve a crown.
But I... I mean you
do deserve a crown.
Oh, my God, that was amazing.
Guys put zero pressure on
you to wash your hands.
Even though I didn't
catch the serial killer,
at least tonight's
not a total loss.
Who are you?
Uh, Manny, the man, Jonas.
You remind me of
my friend, Velma.
Wait, so we are still friends?
- What?
- Uh, nothing.
Well, I like this song,
and my date is rolling around
on the ground with another guy.
Care to dance, mysterious Manny?
Oh, I'm a terrible dancer.
My body is really only
built to ram things.
Don't
care, we're dancing.
Oh, my God, Manny.
It's so cute
when guys pretend dancing
is lame and half-ass it.
You don't find it annoying?
You've clearly studied
dance for years,
and yet any bozo can take over a
dance floor just by doing the worm.
What's that? You're
gonna do the worm?
Hell, yes, you are!
No, I'm not doing the worm.
I'm not even allowed to do it
without a note from my doctor.
Worm!
Worm! Worm! Worm!
Worm! Worm!
Yes, finally!
Wait a second. As a
guy, everyone thinks
my worst qualities as
a girl are awesome.
- Nut tap!
- Ahhh!
We're impressed.
Ah! Yeah!
That's it! I know how
to convince everyone
there's still a serial
killer on the loose.
Everyone.
I have something to say.
And as a man speaking
authoritatively,
you're going to listen to me
and you're going to believe me.
Ghosts are not real.
Look, I know that as
Americans, we wanna party.
But curfew cannot end because the
serial killer is still on the loose.
That's what my
daughter's been saying.
But for some reason I
believe it more from you.
We all do.
Okay, well, we're
safe for tonight
because I scared the
serial killer off.
But tomorrow, curfew's back
on, okay? What do you say?
What do we say?
We say, Manny for Fog King!
Manny for Fog King!
Wait, really?
What?
Okay, this is bad,
but we can still win.
Gigi, do you trust me?
- No, not at all.
- And why would you?
I wrapped your self-worth up in
a crown and failed to deliver it.
Fortunately, I have a plan.
If you fall off the
pier and I rescue you...
Holy crap!
No wonder men are so desperate
to hold onto their power.
This is the easiest shit ever.
As a guy, I can do anything.
So I say, "Lady, I'll give you the
parking spot when you stop being a bitch."
Manny! Manny!
- Oh, yeah!
- Manny! Manny!
No crown, no home!
What? Can I at least
get my jade roller
and $10,000 for emergencies?
- Manny!
- Manny for King of the world!
I bet you'd be
great at Fog King.
Hey, so I should probably go
before this goes too farce...
Uh, far, I mean.
Whoa, hey. You're, like,
drunker than a cool
babysitter. You okay?
Honestly? No, Manny.
I'm drinking because I've had
a terrible couple of weeks.
I know we just met. But
can you keep a secret?
Uh, am I a woman just
pretending to be a man?
I mean, yes.
Okay, so I'm adopted.
And I located my birth parents.
But they turned out
to be criminals!
Criminals! Oh, my God.
Why wouldn't you tell Velma?
That, uh, super cool and
attentive bestie you mentioned?
I've tried.
But unless you're helping
her find her dumb mom,
she has no time for you.
Okay, well, a missing
mom is pretty big.
My criminal parents
also abandoned me!
Like I was a puppy
after quarantine.
Oh, that's awful.
I'm sorry.
But is that bigger than...
No, no, you're right.
A good friend would
have been there for you,
even if your thing wasn't
worse than her thing.
Still, this Velma kind of sucks.
Thank you, Manny.
I can't believe I told you,
but I feel like we have
this crazy connection.
Do you feel it, too?
I, uh, do.
But look, I really need
to tell you something.
I'd be super psyched
to kiss you right now.
I bet you would, Velma.
That's my actual mustache,
Fred. I just didn't shave it.
- Velma?
- Uh, no?
Uh, yes!
I've dreamt of those calloused longshoremen's
hands touching my face for weeks.
So as soon as she
slapped me, I knew.
I'm so sorry, Daphne.
Ugh, I'd punch you, if men
didn't sexualize women fighting.
Baby, come on. You're
acting hysterical.
Damn it!
Okay. And now to officially
announce this year's Fog
King. You all know who it is.
Wait! Mother! Everyone.
I just learned that Manny
is actually Velma Dinkley
in disguise, and... to be Fog King.
- Oh, my God!
- What?
Hold on. Hold on a second.
If Manny's a female interloper,
is or is not the
serial killer a ghost?
Look, if we're being honest, just
like everything else these days,
the serial killer is whatever you
need it to be to feel your best.
And speaking of your best,
who wants to make me Fog King?
We all would, Fred!
Yes!
If we hadn't just
given it to Norville.
He rescued a girl who
fell off the pier.
I was pushed!
Thank you.
First and foremost, I need
to say, "You're welcome"
to my deserving Fog Queen, Gigi.
I knew this crown would
restore your self-worth.
Gigi, are you out there?
Gigi?
Daphne, I'm sorry. I wanted
to tell you I was Manny,
but as a guy, there's so little
consequence for your actions.
I was, like, "I'd be an idiot not
to at least try and go for it."
Ba-ba-booey!
You know, the sad thing is,
I'm not even mad at you.
I'm mad at myself
for letting you find
yet another way
to disappoint me.
I know, and I'm mad at myself
for being selfish
and a bad friend,
who only makes time for people
who can help me find my mom.
Maybe we should both be guys
and just stop caring
about feeling so much.
If you were a guy, you'd die
of gonorrhea within the year.
Yeah, but what a year.
Anyway, I didn't
mean to blow you off.
I just feel guilty ever doing anything
other than looking for my mom.
Can you forgive me?
Watch out!
Gigi! Where are you?
The king and queen are supposed to
tastefully grind on the dance floor now.
That belongs to me.
It belongs to the people.
We are a constitutional
fog-archy, damn it!
A churro? Ha!
Norville, stop!
Going through doors like this
isn't physically possible.
Oh, God, you're right!
My entire perception of
reality is crumbling.
Wait, no, it's just a ride.
Now come back here!
Velma, look. An
old-timey photo booth.
We can disguise ourselves.
Daphne, that's stupid.
It will take at least
five minutes to change.
Who would ever stop to put on a
costume in the middle of a chase?
Shoot. The serial killer
disappeared in the fog.
Yeah, but by fog rules,
he still has to be nearby.
Wait, Fred has his phone?
Okay? For the last time. Are you,
or are you not, the serial killer?
I'm not. This dumb thing
must have gotten swapped with
my crown in the fog. So, like,
I know it's bad he
killed a bunch of girls,
but if I don't find
the crown right now,
I'm gonna have to spend
the night in my limo.
Also, come to think of
it, has anyone seen Gigi?
I'm worried the
serial killer got her.
Oh, no!
Wait, no. There she
is, by the exit.
Gigi? Wait.
Are you a man who's been disguised
as a woman this whole time?
A Gi-Joe?
No. I switched clothes
with a dumb carriage
driver in the dumb fog.
Not that you care.
Not that I care?
Are you upset? How?
You won Fog Queen.
You showed the world you don't deserve
to be ignored by people you like.
You ignored me all night trying
to win those Fog King crowns.
Oh, my God, you're right.
I'm a monster.
No, you're not.
You're weird, sure, but
you're also sweet and amazing,
and deserve to be treated well.
Anyone who makes you feel like
you need a crown to prove that,
is the monster, Norville.
Wait, me? Why are
we talking about me?
This whole thing was only ever
about you and your emotions.
Yeah, okay, my King.
A crown! Oh, I can go home.
Who's pathetic now, Father?
Well, I wasn't able
to convince the town
to keep a curfew to protect
them from the serial killer.
But it won't matter.
Now that you have the
serial killer's cellphone,
I know you're gonna catch
him and find your mom.
And after that, I will focus on
only things that you wanna do.
Like complaining about girls I
thought you were friends with.
I'd like that, thanks.
Oh! Damn, girl.
How'd you get all that ass
in those little slacks?