You might, Dan,
want to learn
how to indicate interest in a girl
other than murdering
another person.
I apologize
for the disruption
and the free drinks
you had to give out restoring order.
Jesus Christ,
it's false dawn, Al.
False dawn already.
If we're gonna act,
we should do it in darkness.
Where's the fucking whore?
Wherever Trixie is,
we know what we need to.
Bullock's four square
behind the New York woman.
The question's
do we act?
And to me,
the course is clear.
Well, what's the course?
Murder them
where they sleep!
The New York woman
and Bullock both.
Dan, loan E.B. Your knife.
Nah, I won't
brandish the knife,
but I'll wield a passkey
at the widow's door.
As for Bullock, he sleeps
on his store's second floor,
and I'll steady a ladder,
Dan, at that wall,
while you climb up
and bushwhack him.
Then, with them dead
and disposed of,
we forge a predated bill of sale,
take possession of the claim
with the allocated
percentages of ownership
previously agreed to in
our internal discussions,
and don't spend a fucking
dollar in the process.
Bold?
I suppose.
But when boldness
is called for,
bold men
do not shrink.
That's what the B in E.B. Farnum
stands for.
- Bold.
- You're goddamn right.
Say it, Al.
Say the fucking words
my bones already know.
You're gonna back off
on that fucking claim.
We brung it, sir. Vaccine
for the smallpox, secured in Cheyenne.
Well done, fellas, and congratulations
on the entire fucking settlement.
E.B., get downstairs
and give these heroes what they're owed.
- Yes, sir. $50 a man.
- If you don't spend it in my joint,
I'll turn the mourning
over to weeping.
You won't shed nary a tear
on our account, Mr. Swearengen.
Vaccine to Doc Cochran
in the pest tent.
We'll be toasting the treaty, too,
with the fucking heathens.
- Explain yourself.
- They've all been
called back to the agency.
We heard that in Cheyenne.
- Are they going's the fucking question.
- Fuck yeah, they are.
That's the word
in Cheyenne.
Red Cloud and Spotted Tail
are leading their people in.
Dan, $10 in bonus credits
across the board for these heroes.
10 in pussy, 10 in faro,
10 in booze.
God bless you,
Mr. Swearengen!
Well, not likely,
but my short-term prospects
just improved.
Say the words, so I can
let the dream die.
E.B., did you not hear
the fucking news?
Did you not listen
to the fucking news?
That plague's end's
in prospect.
And so's peace with the fucking
dirt worshippers.
Come here,
come here.
Sit down.
The dam...
has broken,
young man,
and only ourselves
can fuck up,
for we are about to be
swimming in money.
And how could
we fuck up?
By engaging in open
fucking bloodletting.
And right here at hand
in our very hour of need
is the priggish fucking
douche bag, Bullock,
who only wants
to sell pots and pans,
fan his pretty face
and hold his nose
from the stench of our sordid
carryings on over here,
all the time thinking he can protect
the meek and innocent.
The perfect
fucking front man.
And you want
to kill him?
Much as we might want
the widow's claim,
it's a luxury
now to forego.
E.B., find yourself
somewhere to lie down
till the feeling
passes, huh?
First, I'll go give
the hoople heads their money.
Thank you.
You go find
that fucking whore.
What the fuck
is this, huh?
I lost my voice.
- What happened?
- I seen something bad.
Come in.
Here, sit down.
I seen something at the place
my brother works.
A man was stabbed and killed
right in front of me.
One man said he didn't like
the way the other man
was looking at me, and he
stabbed and killed him.
Drink this.
Where's your brother now?
We got a room.
I'll go in a minute.
It's all right, Flora.
I've just come to say
I don't know if I can do this.
It's horrible.
It's one thing
leads to another
and you never know
when it's gonna happen.
Mostly you can steer it,
sweetheart,
and when it's gonna get
to where you can't,
you get just a little notice,
just a couple of seconds
before the one thing
turns into the other.
It's like a funny smell
comes into the air,
then you know there's
no more steering
and get the hell
out of the way.
I smelled it in the saloon.
And did you get out
of the way in time?
It's all right.
Miles doesn't know nothing.
He didn't smell nothing
and he...
didn't know nothing
about what to do.
All right, I know.
Can I stay?
Can I sleep here with you just this last
little while before we have to get up?
Yeah, you can sleep
here with me.
Can you help?
- Name?
- Boland.
Make your mark.
Saint Andy Cramed.
All that's missing are
the scourges and flays.
Maybe they're
under his shirt.
Kind of you to let us work out
of the horseshit and flies.
Sure.
Jesus Christ!
Have you seen Trixie, Doc?
What?
Trixie.
No, tea and honey.
- For this?
- You are a stupid son of a bitch.
Yeah, the traffic's
a boon, Seth.
We're up $27 already
from yesterday's entire proceeds.
Good.
Pitiful specimen you are.
It wasn't a pinprick.
I ain't ate.
Really? Strange you
never keeled over
when we was hungry
on the fucking trail.
Your boss speak to you about sending
me an assayer this morning?
No, sir, he didn't.
I will remind him
once I finish his errands.
I only got one place
left to look:
Bella Union...
that's our competition.
Well, I'll tell him
what you said.
Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Bullock.
Come to have
the child inoculated?
Yes, and to tell you,
for reasons we needn't explore,
that my plans have changed.
As soon as I can
arrange transportation
I'll return with the child
to New York City.
Why needn't we
explore your reasons?
Because, Mr. Bullock,
I've already
quite sufficiently
imposed upon you
my private reasons
and facts.
As regards to the claim my husband
purchased before his murder,
I'm inclined to accept
the last bid
from Mr. Swearengen's
hand-puppet
and I would be very grateful if you
would tell Mr. Farnum so,
as speaking to him
directly makes me ill.
I'm gonna assay your claim,
Mrs. Garret.
I promised Mr. Hickok,
and I promised you.
I released you from your promise
to me yesterday.
And today I instruct you
not to keep it.
You do tend
to change your mind,
and the first promise,
you weren't a party to.
Why don't you get the child inoculated?
I'll go about my business,
and we'll revisit
the whole mess subsequently.
Don't fucking lead
Ellsworth right to it
so he can hoot and holler
and hail fucking Bullock.
You walk around.
You're discouraged.
It's not even worth it
to make the steep ascent.
I start from below?
You start
at the fucking creek.
What, do you want
to start at the cliff?
The three of you
leap the fuck off holding hands?
Top o' the mornin'.
I'm to lead you
to the Widow Garret's claim.
- You're the assayer?
- Nope.
- I'm to take you to him.
- He's one claim over.
Nice fucking guy
and a dead eye
for the fucking color.
- Ellsworth.
- Ellsworth...
is absolutely right.
Well, come on.
I was inoculated
some time ago,
but I thought she should
be treated before our trip.
I am delighted
you're taking her with you.
It was Trixie
who made me realize
that my reasons
for staying weren't sound.
Glad she succeeded
where I failed.
I intend to write her
a note of profound thanks.
I hope that you'll
deliver it to her
at Mr. Swearengen's
saloon.
Is that where she went
when she left you?
Yes, I certainly
assume so.
Sorry, I'm sorry, honey.
It's all over.
When will you
be leavin'?
As quickly
as is practical.
Mr Utter can see to your
travel arrangements.
Soon as he gets his wits back,
I'll send him to you.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you
for everything.
What did she say
about Trixie?
Nothin'.
How'd you do
with that bloodstain?
I scrubbed it real hard.
Did I ask you how hard
you fuckin' scrubbed?
- No.
I asked
if you got it out.
Get me the fuckin'
scrub brush.
Every fuckin' thing
I gotta do myself, huh?
- Where is she?!
- Trixie?
No, Queen fuckin' Victoria.
Last I saw her was yesterday
when she came to see you.
Just get me
the fuckin' scrub brush.
Gives her word
she'll return.
Where the fuck
is she, huh?
What'd she say to you
when you saw her?
She said her pussy hurt
where you grabbed it.
That has a ring
of fuckin' truth.
She said you
nearly killed her.
She said to me
she'd be right back.
A fool's
fucking errand, anyway.
I found out what
I needed to know
when I looked in that cocksucker
Bullock's eyes
while Dority
was spilling blood
that you have failed
to adequately clean up.
You want me
to do some more?
No, shut the fuck up.
Now, what's she doin'?
She makin' a point?
No grabbing at the cunt?
- Is that what she said to you?
- No.
I mean, y-you... she told you, right,
that I grabbed her?
Did she have
an attitude about it?
She didn't have an attitude.
She just said her pussy hurt.
Agh.
Point's made with
the snatch grabs, okay.
50 other fucking things
I should be paying attention to,
rosiest prospects
of my career,
and here I am on
my fucking hands and knees
discussing snippets
of information with a gimp.
There!
Now that's how you scrub
a fucking bloodstain!
I couldn't find Trixie.
You see her,
you send her
the fuck back to me,
'cause if I
see her outside,
she'll wish I had
killed her before.
That shot didn't hurt
too bad, Al,
but it fuckin' itches.
Yeah? Good.
You had your
shot yet, kid?
Not yet.
The line was too long,
and I did not want
to be late for work.
Open for business
and talk like him
- until further instructed.
- Yes, sir.
Aw, Jesus.
Trixie?
God damn it, Trixie,
wake up.
Wake up, Trixie.
- Trixie, wake up...
- Doc! Doc!
- What?!
- Doc!
- Stay the fuck over there!
- It's A.W., Doc.
Stay the fuck
over there, anyway.
Aw, I don't take your
bad temper personally, Doc.
The hours you're working
would try a saint.
What do you want?
I'm in pain, Doc,
in the small of my back,
which I'm aware is
a precursor symptom.
- When did the pain start?
- Am I warm?
Answer the question.
Well, it's become more
concentrated and severe.
- Why did you strike me?
- To secure your attention.
When did the pain start?
The original pain
I've lived with for quite some time,
but in this last period,
it's become much more
concentrated and severe.
In viewing the context
of this outbreak,
I knew I should
consult you.
- Ow.
- Well, you don't have a fever.
- I don't?
- No.
You put on weight?
May I ask
that query's relevance?
It's harder on your back
as you get fatter.
So, in concert
with the symptoms
I'm already exhibiting,
you'd say be alert
for fever?
And work hard
on your paper.
- And get yourself inoculated.
- Uh-huh.
And try to eat less.
You botched
this job pretty good,
didn't you, young lady?
Now you listen to me,
if you want,
I will do the job
for you right.
But first, I want you
to know that
that rich woman
is leaving town,
and she told me that she would
take you with her.
I know that you thought
enough of that woman
to help her
get off this... stuff
you tried to use
to kill yourself with.
But what I don't know is,
is if you wanted to die, period,
or 'cause you thought
you didn't have a way out of here,
'cause you do
have a way out.
Is that a vote
for New York City?
All right, then.
Morning, Mr. Tolliver.
Good morning, Flora.
I swear I saw you leave
last night after your shift.
I come back.
A man was murdered where my brother
works, at The Gem Saloon,
- and I got scared.
- You saw it, honey?
Yes, sir.
I was there picking my brother up.
You're brave to even be
in a joint like that.
And after,
you sought refuge
with Joanie, did you?
- Yes, sir.
- No better port in a storm.
- Anyways, I'll go change.
- Good girl. Good for you.
- You settle in real good, Flora.
- Thank you, sir.
Mm-mmm,
Joanie Stubbs.
Is that a fresh scalp
I see hangin' from your belt?
She saw a gutting
last night.
She was upset.
I held her.
I was watching for you
at the door, Flora,
but here you are
already inside.
Not working yet,
Terrance.
Poor thing.
Adjusting so smooth
to losing her cherry
and yet that upset
by blood.
She lost her cherry back home.
I told you that.
Gonna put your garters
on now?
I'll give you $2 for that apple
and a piece of cheese.
It's my knife.
You want to buy that?
I've got a fucking knife.
I'll just be a second
and take my brother his lunch.
Sure, honey.
Unless she ain't
upset at all.
What happened now,
Flora?
I thought you was changin'
into your garters.
You geek-looking fuck.
Get away from me before
I cut your fucking heart out.
It's Dr. Cochran.
Doctor.
Trixie tried to commit suicide
with laudanum.
- My God.
- She punctured her vein.
That's the only reason
why she's still alive.
Who's with her?
No one at the goddamn moment
is with her, Mrs. Garret.
Her situation in this camp isn't such
that that would be safe.
Which is why, while
trying to dissuade her
from future efforts
at murdering herself,
I told a fib,
invoking your name
and willingness
to take her with you
on your trip.
Last night, Doctor,
I made that very offer
to Trixie.
She refused.
More precisely,
I offered to send
Trixie to New York
with the child
to make the appropriate
introductions
to my family,
and to pay
to see them established.
Is it possible,
Mrs. Garret,
that leaving this camp
and heading to New York City
in service to you
and the child might,
to a girl like Trixie,
appear a more realistic proposition
than being dispatched
on some cruel masquerade?
Please tell her
she's welcome.
Tell her she's necessary.
If her indisposition
doesn't preclude it,
I'd be happy
to tell her myself.
Thank you, madam.
If I'm to get
my throat cut, Dan,
I'd rather not
exert myself further.
If I have any choice
in the matter,
I'd prefer one
behind the ear.
Keep climbing, Ellsworth.
You're off the hook for seeing
that New York dude's accident.
When Swearengen
was moved to trust,
I know you spoke
for me hard.
Well, I didn't...
didn't speak against you.
You might try takin'
a gander over to your right.
You don't have to tell me
where to fucking look.
If you're
the goddamn assayer,
shouldn't I be
following you?
Head on back down,
Mr. Bullock.
We think we found
a formation worth looking at.
Young lady,
thank Christ.
I'd feared after the murder
you'd shun us.
I come for lunch
with Miles.
Well, bless you then
for being a caring sister.
- Miles!
- Sir?
Miles, you lucky son of a bitch,
your sister's here with your lunch.
She brought you
a fresh apple
and some kind of delicacy
wrapped in swaddling.
I've been scrubbing that bloodstain
all mornin', and the cripple has too.
Situate your sister to spare her
to stand at that fucking stain, huh?
- Let's do it.
- Now?
- Now, and get the fuck outta here.
- What if...
Flora, if we do
it slow and right,
we're 50 miles gone
before anyone knows we blew.
My boss is onto me.
Savvy operator from Chicago
and you could tell he's on to you?
Savvy enough
that he didn't crack,
and I still
could fuckin' tell.
You're full of shit.
You want to do it fast and dirty
so you have to cut
somebody's throat.
- This joint you want to take?
- Where I work.
- Where your boss is onto you?
- I can move the dyke.
Held me in her arms all night
like I was a little fucking kid.
Can I assume
there's a fucking plan?
Mr. Bullock, what ho?
Mrs. Garret's room.
Number two.
Don't sell,
Mrs. Garret.
Darling...
um, I'm going
to be unspeakably rude
and leave you here alone
for just a moment,
while I go downstairs
with Mr. Bullock,
who's just arrived
with the most interesting news,
and whom l... I can't
receive here in my room,
particularly
with you present,
for reasons too boring
and complex to explain.
So I'm going to go downstairs
to speak with Mr. Bullock
in Mr. Farnum's
absurd restaurant,
then I'll come back up
and we will continue to ready
our leaving. All right, darling?
I'll be in the restaurant
for just one moment.
Can I bring you
a glass of milk?
All right.
I'll... I'll be right back.
May I inquire
as to the assay's outcome?
- Ask the owner.
- Mrs. Garret?
Is the technical term
"bonanza"?
That's the look of it.
It's a bonanza,
Mr. Farnum.
I see.
Congratulations.
Does the find change your mind
at all about New York City?
I can't see
why it would.
I can't, either,
but I don't count.
Of course you count.
Why wouldn't you?
'Cause your changes of mind
come so quick and often,
I can't keep up.
I can't understand what changed
your mind from yesterday
when it was made up
to stay.
I was made to understand
last night that my reasons
for wanting to stay
have been completely selfish.
- By who?
- Trixie.
I'd offered to send her
to New York City with the child,
where Trixie,
I've since come to realize,
would be completely unsuited.
And because I wished
to stay here unencumbered
when I should be caring
for the child.
Why can't you
care for her here?
Where the fuck is he?
Said he was gonna go tell
the widow of her find.
How the fuck long
does it take to tell her?
I don't know, Al,
I'm here with you.
- Are you getting smart with me now?
- No.
Cocksucker Bullock.
When you can't stand
the sight of him,
he's nowhere
but underfoot.
Sir, my sister
was told of a man
who resembles our father's photograph
down by Lead,
and I'd be grateful
if this afternoon
I could go look and maybe I could take
a night shift to make up.
If I said no,
I'd hope you'd walk out
and go looking anyway,
then seek a new job
elsewhere after.
That is what I'd do, sir.
All right, kid.
Go look for him.
Tell Arnette
at the livery stable
I'll stand metal
for the horse.
If your sister looks with you,
tell Arnette I'm good for her mount.
So you think
it's a good idea to go?
It's why the fuck
you're here, isn't it?
Right.
I'm gonna go get
the horses then.
Permission to leave
the bar, trooper.
Thanks, to both of you.
Ah, struck rich
for the widow, huh, Bullock?
Free drink!
Big, huh?
Rich and fucking thick,
that vein is?
Not being expert,
I can't guess at the extent.
Dan's a fucking expert.
When he's not shit-faced drunk,
so is Ellsworth.
The immediate result
is she won't be sellin'.
Of course,
she fucking won't.
I should fucking
think not, huh?
Not for any $20,000
at least.
Come here. Come drink
with your vanquished foe.
Very good of you
and Mr. Star, incidentally,
to make your venue available
so the hoople heads can get vaccinated.
I was the second
hoople head stuck.
Them riders
that brought the vaccine,
say the heathens
have been called back to the agency.
In a spasm of good sense,
they're fuckin' going.
I heard.
Before you know it, we'll have laws here
and every other thing.
Yeah, which brings me, Bullock,
to the matter of the widow.
I wanted to show you
my bona fides for cooperation.
If a treaty is signed,
be wise for you and me
to paddle
in the same direction.
Tics or habits of behavior
either finds dislikable in the other
gotta be overlooked
or taken with a grain of salt.
Would your bona fides extend
to Mrs. Garret's future safety?
My oath on this:
Every day that the widow sits
on her ass in New York City,
looks west at sunset
and thinks to herself,
"God bless you ignorant
cocksuckers in Deadwood,
who strive mightily
and at little money
to add to my
ever-increasing fortune,"
she'll be safe
from the wiles of Al Swearengen.
She's stayin'.
The oath stands
as a gesture to you.
- Can I take a shave over here?
- Please.
Barney, be careful in the area
of the throat, huh?
If you authorized an offer
of 20 on the widow's claim...
your agent was looking
to skim a little cream.
- How high did E.B. Go?
- $19,500.
I wouldn't trust a man
that wouldn't try to steal a little.
Where's that fucking whore?
You stay here, sweetheart.
I'm so very sorry...
for any part that I may
have played in this.
I don't remember
you being the one
that made me a whore,
Mrs. Garret.
I'm going to stay in the camp
with the child, Trixie.
Dr. Cochran explained
to me the difficulties
your extraordinary
kindness toward me
has put you in, in relationship
to Mr. Swearengen.
If you wish to stay,
I'd be so grateful
if you'd stay with us.
But perhaps you
want to go, Trixie.
If you do...
take this.
As your earnest claim
on the future.
I'll send you more.
I appear to have
struck it rich.
I'll send you
all that you need.
Trixie?
Hello, sweetheart.
Don't I look tired?
Sophia.
You're so beautiful.
I should've guessed it.
Take her home,
Mrs. Garret.
How do you take
my suggestion?
Are you sure
that gold's real?
Absolutely.
Uh, let me think
things through.
All right.
- What's your name?
- Elizabeth.
- I'm quittin'.
- All right, Flora.
I left a pin up in your room.
I wanna go look for it.
Go ahead and look.
When does the part come
when that little piece of trim
finally gets into
her workin' clothes
and starts makin' us
some fuckin' money?
She's quitting, Cy.
She's quitting?
And that seems to be your room
she's walkin' into yet again.
She lost a pin...
up there.
A pin?
Can you tell the stones
from the paste?
Show me
which is which.
I don't think so.
- Let me take it.
- Get outta here, Flora.
Put down my things and I'll let you
get out without raising hell.
Why don't let me go
with your things
and shut your
fucking mouth?
Because I remind you of whoever
the fuck I remind you of.
No.
Now what are you gonna do,
Flora, kill me?
- Maybe.
- Think you're gonna get out alive?
I'll give it
a goddamn whirl.
You're not gonna
get out alive.
You're gonna die here.
Who am I?
Your little baby?
Your little sister?
You?
I wouldn't move this.
- Did you find your pin?
- I did, sir.
Joanie tells me
you're leaving us.
Can't take it
anymore, sir.
Decided I wasn't
cut out for it.
My brother too.
Decided he wasn't
cut out for what?
Sweeping up
at The Gem Saloon.
I see.
My first take on your meaning
was they were fucking your brother
for money over there
like you was gettin' done to here.
Step aside and let me
do my business.
And what is your
fuckin' business?!
You with your beady
little ferret eyes.
She came to say goodbye, Cy.
She's movin' on.
It don't feel
right to me, babe.
But if I'm mistaken
in my judgment,
may I regret what I just did
for the rest of my life.
Now let her go!
You little cunt!
You're gonna die here!
Come on!
Get outta here.
Get out. Get out front.
Get around!
They're goin' over the top!
Come on.
Don't impede her
progress, Joanie.
Don't do nothin' rash.
- What are you doing?
- That's none of your business!
Them two robbed my joint. That's where
they're gonna be dealt with.
I guess they needn't
get beat anymore out here.
Take 'em the fuck
inside, boys.
And you can help
your delicate sensibilities
by turning the fuck away.
Cy wants you
up there, honey.
I tell you, your face come out
of that in pretty good shape.
Matters took a happy turn,
you could still probably work.
Come on in, honey,
over here on what the dagos
call my sinister side,
although your beady
little rat eyes
don't seem like
they're takin' in the view.
You bust somethin' up
there, sweetheart?!
Does that fuckin' hurt you?!
You fuckin' understand me?!
See, that upsets Joanie now.
"Oh, Cy, do up the boy.
My God, I can't stand
to see the other."
You want me to see
to the boy, Joanie?
'Cause you know
I'm clay in your hands.
- Cy.
- What is it, Eddie?
We could all
be elsewhere?
Nothing but true.
Are you awake, Miles?
Don't be fuckin'
passin' out, youngster.
Next breath you draw,
the smell of sulfur's
liable to be strong
in your nose.
Where is your
fuckin' nose, anyway?
Fuck it, Miles!
You're found fuckin'
guilty of bein' a cunt.
I'm hereby
passin' judgment
for your lettin' this bitch push you
around and tellin' you what to do
when you were supposed to be a man
and showing her rules!
You hear me, Miles?
And for bein' the cunt
you are now,
before you could
have been a man,
done your fuckin' part,
you little piece of shit.
I know you don't want
out of here, Joanie.
- Don't hurt her, Cy.
- Don't hurt her?
You mean
before I kill her?
Yes.
Listen to that, Flora.
That's the person you robbed,
who had those kind
of feelings for you.
But I'm the one
you stabbed.
See?
I think your fuckin'
skull's broken, Flora.
You're trying for the knife.
It's maybe a foot to your left.
This is fuckin' pitiful.
Why don't you put that
out of its misery?
Don't do nothin'.
Whatever you want to do
will be a mistake.
You keep drawin' breath
right here.
You did everything
you could, E.B.,
to preserve our
fuckin' interests.
I mean, you know,
sometimes the cards go cold.
Far as the events
at the Bella Union,
by all accounts,
it was two young thieves,
a boy and a girl.
We all know
who they are.
Who they are now
is late night vittles for Wu's pigs.
That young girl
had me fooled.
Your dick
had you fooled.
And in that state
of addlement,
you mistook her purpose,
her so-called brother's
and their entire
fucking cockeyed story.
You did do everything
you could, didn't you, E. B?
You went to the limit
on our offer.
- Everything humanly possible.
- You did go to the limit?
Well, I went
to the limit's precipice.
Sounds like you didn't go
to the limit.
Al, I held back
a few dollars,
against some final
unforeseen turn.
So we'll never know
if them few dollars
you held back wouldn't have
made us both fucking rich.
I'm goin' up.
Find out how much
Tolliver paid Wu.
Don't want to be suckin'
hind tit on disposal fees.
Don't think I enjoyed
that bullshit, Joanie.
Certain things you...
have to do to impress
upon people
what you're willing to do.
Do you like it? No.
Do you enjoy it? No.
Do you have to look
like you do? Yes.
I got Eddie in there.
Gotta let him know.
Capra's downstairs,
gonna hear about it.
When people come to rob you, Joanie,
you gotta get rough.
If it looks like an act,
it's not gonna work.
And then
I grab your hand...
and I think, "My God,
this poor fuckin' girl."
But I did what I had
to do in that room.
And now I'm out here.
I'm telling you,
your happiness
is important to me,
and whatever
the fuck I gotta do,
if you're too much
in my shadow,
if I make things too tough on you,
then we'll stop it.
- We're gonna do somethin' else.
- Cy.
You bring warmth
into my life.
I can't bear to see you
unhappy like this.
I want...
to set you up
in your own business here.
Independent fuckin' operator.
I'll put up the money.
Any kind of interest
in return, that's fine,
but that ain't what this is about.
It'll be your place.
I want you to feel
when I walk in there
that you can say, "I'm busy, Cy.
Come back later."
I want you to watch me
turn around when you say that
like I'm some rube trick
with my chin down on the floor,
"When should I try
you again, Joanie?"
"I'll let you know, Cy."
That's how I want
you to feel.
I used to make you warm,
didn't I, Cy?
And I could make you feel
like something's funny.
You still do, honey.
When you're happy,
you still do.
Kill me too, Cy,
or let me go.
I understood myself
to be sayin', Joanie,
I want to find a way to give you
a looser rein.
You've gotta figure out
a way to mean it.
If you don't kill me
or let me go,
I'm gonna kill you.
Has he got you at your hands and knees
at 2:00 in the fucking morning?
I got myself
at my hands and knees,
wondering what
became of you.
Wake up, David.
I'm up.
? Row, row, row,
row your boat ?
? Gently down
the stream ?
? Merrily, merrily,
merrily, merrily ?
? Life is
but a dream. ?
? I was a-standin' ?
? By my window ?
? Oh one cold ?
? And cloudy day ?
? When I saw that ?
? Hearse come rollin' ?
? For to carry ?
? My mother away ?
? Will a circle ?
? Be unbroken? ?
? By and by, Lord ?
? By and by ?
? There's better ?
? Home away ?
? In the sky, Lord ?
? In the sky. ?