Her Majesty
awakes, huh?
Cocksucker's
gonna grace me
with his fucking
presence this morning.
Fucking
Magistrate Clagett
will impart to me the attitude towards
the settlement
of him and his fellow
lying fucking thieves
at the territorial
legislature of Yankton.
How fucking much
it's gonna cost us to get annexed
when they sign a treaty
with the fucking dirt worshipers, huh?
How hard is the legislature
gonna squeeze our balls
with regard to our title
and properties, huh?
I don't want to talk
to these cocksuckers, but you have to.
In life,
you have to do a lot
of things you don't fucking want to do.
Many times, that's
what the fuck life is...
one vile fucking task
after another.
But don't
get aggravated.
Then the enemy has you
by the short hair.
It'll be different
after the annexation.
That's all.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Everything changes.
Don't be afraid.
I can hope...
those'll be appearing
on a regular basis.
No.
No?
How's your arm?
It's all right.
Don't fucking try doing away
with yourself again, huh?
Good morning,
gentlemen.
This is Ellsworth,
who found the gold on your claim.
- How do you do, Mr. Ellsworth?
- Pleasure.
- And this is Sophia.
- Pleasure, Sophia.
I'm grateful for your expertise
and keen eyesight.
Luck's what you want
to congratulate me on, Mrs. Garret.
Till you decide how
you want develop it,
Ellsworth can spend time
enough at wages
on your claim to sustain
your ownership.
I nod as if I understand
what you just said.
He'll explain it
all to you.
Might we have a word,
Mr. Bullock?
I'm certain Mr. Ellsworth's
are very capable hands,
but I hope you're not
disassociating yourself from my affairs.
I already got my impression
of this fellow, Mrs. Garret.
This meeting's
how you form yours.
I see.
Then we compare notes
and decide how you proceed.
Fine.
Toward a future point when you tell me
my thinkin's so consistently wrongheaded
it's a waste of your valuable time
having to deal with me.
In any case, I know you have many claims
on your attention.
A couple.
Thank you very much.
I'd lean more on what I felt
about this fellow than what I saw.
Late as usual.
I just comes from the creek, Mr. Farnum.
Washin' my pants.
A habit to cultivate.
And under a rock down there, I found
other pants of mine I thought I'd lost.
But seein' as I gets
drunk and on occasion shits myself,
I figured that must be how I lost 'em
in the first place.
I imagine you making
your way from the creek,
rolling into the lobby
when all others are abed,
bare-ass naked with shit streaming down
the backs of your legs.
Sir, no. It must have been the night
that Mr. Hickok was killed.
Now I recall
that Mr. Hickok...
he gives unto me a letter for me
to put in post,
but what with all the hullabalo
and me gettin' drunk,
I forgot about
the whole thing.
Until I found
my pants.
Do you think
I'm gonna touch that?
No, uh, I didn't get
my pants wet,
nor did I soil the letter
when I soiled myself.
That's the miracle
of it, sir.
So I'm to believe that's a letter
written by Wild Bill Hickok
just before his murder
by the coward McCall?
- Just minutes before, sir.
- Addressed to whom?
His wife, sir.
Well, I only hope
you haven't opened it.
No, sir.
At least that eliminates
tampering from the list.
Of what, sir?
Crimes in which your
inebriation and sloth
as my employee
has implicated my hotel,
which I will attempt
to shield you from
in the course of trying
to extricate myself.
I didn't mean to extricate you, sir.
L... I didn't...
Just give me
the confounded letter!
- And none of this hangdog look.
- Sir.
- Not a word of this to anyone.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Utter. Hearty congratulations
on your new venture.
Take a while to find out if those
are what's in order.
Being this is the first
day of my enterprise,
I wore this frock-coat.
Very flattering.
You don't think
it looks stupid?
Not to me, no.
Mr. Dority all
of a sudden stumbled,
and in... in grabbin'
at scrub to steady him,
I saw a color beneath.
Ain't you a little doll.
She's formed
an instant attachment.
Well, anyways, I'm glad to keep
your title good workin' the surface,
but the quartz
outcrop we found...
you're not gonna know
how rich your strike is
until you sink
some shafts.
Now, I ain't expert
prospectin' that way.
I'm a man who
works in creeks.
Thank you for
telling me so.
Not bein' impertinent,
your people gonna
help you with this?
My brother and my father
are aware of my situation
and my husband's
parents.
I have no idea as to the prospect
of their involvement.
Well, blood don't
always prove loyalty.
But you're gonna need
some people on your side, Mrs. Garret,
'cause I believe you got a big one
on your hands.
I believe Mr. Bullock's
on my side.
No question about that.
And I believe
you are, too.
Excuse me.
I was among them
found that little girl.
I'm glad to see
her doing well.
I'm Alma Garret.
How do you do?
Ellsworth.
Charlie Utter.
Come in.
- Yes, sir.
- You see this?
"Utter Freight and Postal
Delivery Service."
That's what happens when
you drop a fucking stitch.
What stitch
did I drop?
I did.
This freight and delivery service
should've been opened by Persimmon Phil
- as a cover for his other activities.
- He's dead.
I know he's dead now.
Well, if you don't know,
nobody does.
I should have brought in a replacement,
is my fucking point.
Well, you'll know
better next time.
The direction
of my thoughts...
with the sustained fucking stupidity
that you're exhibiting,
I hesitate to voice them...
is that you might want
to train for Phil's former position.
Al.
I have hoped
for this conversation
ever since you give me
that Indian head to hide.
How'd it go with Johnny?
I have just fled
my own office in horror
at his fucking
dimwittedness.
Well, Persimmon Phil
was no genius.
I know.
And Johnny, so eager.
I know. Was it not my fucking
idea to ask him?
There's a minimal standard,
he'll be in the wilderness.
You gotta be able
to sustain a thought.
to remember fucking instructions.
- His Honor.
- Oh, yeah.
Hold fast
your valuables.
Hey, Al. Any reason I can't
share with Dan
the proceedings of the talk me
and you just had about me
taking over
for Persimmon Phil?
Yeah, keep Dan
in the dark.
Have a seat,
Your Honor.
- Hey, Johnny.
- Dan.
What's new?
I want to know how the camp stands
with the legislature.
And don't give me
this, um,
- "On the one hand, on the other hand."
- All right.
Just say, "This is the way
I think it's gonna be,"
'cause this several- hands
fucking shit don't help me.
- I'll boil things down.
- Go ahead.
Let's assume for the sake
of conversation
that there's a new treaty
with the Sioux peoples.
"People," that's what we're calling
those cocksuckers now?
That's the way
things are headed?
Assuming the new treaty,
the hills will be annexed.
The territory respects the statutes
of the Northwest Ordinance,
which state that a citizen
can have title to any land
unclaimed or unincorporated
by simple usage.
Essentially,
if you're on it
and you improve it,
you own it.
But, what complicates
the situation
is that the hills
were deeded to the Sioux
by the 1868
Fort Laramie Treaty.
This could mean
that the land occupied by the camp
doesn't fall under any
statutory definition
of unclaimed
or unincorporated.
So who needs
to get paid?
Signs of conciliation and willingness
would weigh in the camp's favor.
But just as important
is the presence
of a ad hoc
municipal organization
that would enable
the legislature to say
Deadwood exists,
we don't have to create it.
It would be disruptive
if we did.
The community's
already organized,
not legally maybe,
but certainly informally.
Why not let's give this
informal organization
the blessing
of legal standing?
What's the right fucking
number for the legislature?
There's a lot of gold
out here, Al.
To define "right"
in this environment
is very liable to be
an ongoing process.
What I'm prepared to do
is make a list of names
and a preliminary guess
at some numbers.
I should tell you as well
that a warrant's reached Yankton
charging you with murder
in Chicago, Illinois.
As the settlement's status changes,
you want to address that.
I could help
with that too.
How much is that
gonna cost me?
$5,000.
If you don't mind,
I'll continue writing.
Good morning,
Miss Jane.
Yeah, hello.
No one croaked today.
Tommy's still fucking
sick and the doc will be back
I guess whenever
he fucking feels like it.
See your fucking eyes
are still playin' tug o' war.
Well, this is the one
to look at.
Left arm still useful
as an old man's dick?
Do I smell strangely
to you, Miss Jane?
What?
Do I have a strange
odor about me?
What is that, your clever way of saying
you smell whiskey on my breath?
No.
If either of your fucking
eyes takes me for hiding
I'm drinking again occasionally,
it's sadly mistaken,
so desist from any clever
odor references.
I thought the smell might
be coming off the creek
so I went into the hills last night
but it followed me there too,
as if my, uh, as if my flesh
were rotting.
I, uh... do I look like a man
taken from his own grave?
God damn you, don't start talking crazy
to go with everything else.
Also, when I read the...
the scriptures,
I do not feel Christ's
love as I used to.
Oh, is that so?
That is too bad.
Join the fucking club
of most of us.
Let me tell you
something, Preacher.
I see you skulking around
when the doc comes in.
You're trying to hide
your fucking eyes,
trying to hide
your fucking arm.
You're a fucking mess.
And I am in the process of wearing out
my own fucking welcome in this camp.
And I wouldn't expect to be
around here much longer
for people to be
disgusted by
so they don't notice
what the fuck is going on with you!
And you need to think
about some of these things
and raise your nerve
to consult with the doc!
God damn you! Spilling my cleaning
water too, Minister!
Up.
Thank you,
I'm fine.
You're fine.
I am off duty.
You're on duty.
You can go
fuck yourself!
Al, what are you
doing out?
Clearing my head.
And if I blink when I speak,
that's because I just
got fucking fleeced.
- What's going on?
- Be at my joint in two hours.
- We're forming a fucking government.
- Yes, sir.
Merrick!
Jesus Christ.
Hey, Merrick!
Cocksucker.
Shoot.
Thank you, sir.
Good luck out there.
I believe it's time
to send for my wife and boy.
Treaty coming
with the Sioux.
Where the fuck
is Merrick, huh?!
We don't know.
Well anyways,
this is it.
What we spoke about before,
this puts it to the test.
All right.
Informal municipal organization.
Not government.
No, that would
mark us rebellious.
But structure enough to persuade those
territorial cocksuckers in Yankton
that we're worthy enough to pay them
their fucking bribes.
We're to meet to discuss
putting this organization together.
Is that what
you're saying?
Centuries of fucking
inbreeding
attune him to the necessities
of the times.
Two hours, my place!
Did a fucking
good job here.
Your room's
put back together.
That ain't
my room anymore.
Cy needn't have done
for them kids that way.
Not in your room,
not in the way
he did for them.
I'm getting
outta here, Eddie.
Are ya?
I'm going to open
my own place.
Good for you, honey.
Have you saved money?
I got a way
to work it.
I know you'll get
a long way away from here first.
You think I have to?
Cy told me he'd help me
open a place here.
He promised he'd
keep his distance.
Good.
- Is he around?
- Asleep.
There's a meeting
in my place
in a couple of hours
he'll want to be awake for.
All the pillars of the fucking camp.
You mind?
You could use
some rest.
I could use
a clean conscience.
So could we all.
Blah!
Where the fuck
have you been?!
- As you see.
- As I see, what?
At my storage cabinet,
replentishing needed supplies.
Be over in a couple of hours. We gotta
form a government for the settlement.
Who does?
Us! You and me.
Come to me in a vision!
You stupid bastard.
Anyways, I'm going
to look for a place.
Eddie.
Swearengen's called a meeting.
Two hours.
Where's Joanie?
Out looking for a place.
Good.
'Cause I told Joanie I'd back her
in having her own joint.
That's what she said.
Something on
your mind, Eddie?
You fucked me up, Cy.
The shit you did
to those kids,
there's no angle to it.
That shit wasn't just
about those kids, Eddie.
You need to sit there and tough
your way through your problem.
Just keep
shuffling your cards
and let your tie hang down
till you feel better.
I want to come
to that meeting.
Do ya?
Come ahead, Eddie.
Put the cards down,
tighten your cravat
and come on if it'll cheer
you the fuck up.
Mornin'.
Good morning.
I'm opening
this business.
Well, good luck.
Thank you.
I'm Charlie Utter.
I'm Joanie Stubbs.
- How do you do?
- How do you do, Charlie?
Ooh, I was out of breath,
but now I'm better.
Are you off someplace?
Uh, you need an escort
or the like?
No, I'm more or less
just walking around.
What do you think
of this frock-coat?
Very well fitted.
I had it made
up in Cheyenne.
I'm one for a good
appearance and all,
but it's a little
out of my path.
If you would have
made me guess,
I would have said
it's not your usual garb.
And I'm a considerable hand
at the freight business,
but far as leasing
this building
before knowing what
the traffic's gonna bear,
I don't know
what possessed me.
See, l...
I do well in a camp
or a settlement
or a township,
but that don't
make me a camp
or a settlement
or a township type.
This is the attire
for that type of type.
Anyway, you're
wearing it today.
You're right.
I'm sorry for running
on about it.
I'm looking for a piece
of property
to start a business on.
That's what
I'm doing out.
I see.
And what sort of business
you looking to operate?
- Brothel.
- Uh-huh.
Well, uh, I'll tell you what,
this camp here,
it seems like
it's got some legs under it.
I'm just a whore, though.
I mean, I run the whores
for this man,
but far as being
ready to run a place
and stand up to all
you have to stand up to,
l... I don't know
what got into me.
I'll tell you what,
something's ready
for you to do something,
don't seem to matter
if you're ready or not.
Better lift
your skirts and...
jump, huh?
That's what's coming
to me to be true.
I'm surprised you're not
at that big town meeting.
Uh, yeah, well,
I'm, uh...
I'm heading
over there shortly.
Uh, I prefer to appear
late to that type of thing.
Bella Union,
where I work, is bigger
but I guess being that
it's Mr. Swearengen's meeting,
that's why they're
having it at The Gem.
Yeah, that's... that's
why it's located there.
Yeah.
It's awful nice
to meet you, Charlie.
Well it's good
to meet you, too, Joanie.
Take care.
I'm going to The Gem.
I'm heading on.
I'm heading
for The Gem.
Hooray for you.
Reverend is laid down
trying to hide another seizure.
Ain't you clever to see
through the subterfuge.
I been letting it go,
but if the idea is for you to drink more
and more till I say something,
I am hereby
officially saying
I wish you would
stop fucking drinking.
I have no fucking idea
as far as you saying
one fucking thing
about anything
I do or don't,
far as drinking
or where I stand
or nap
- or any other thing concerning me.
- I see.
Or go or leave
or don't or when.
All right, Jane.
So you can go
fuck yourself.
And don't try
and hasten anyone anywhere,
'cause everyone follows
their own fucking pace,
and don't try
and fucking hasten them.
And you happen to be
fucking overlooking
that you think it's just
one day after another
with the same
fucking seizure
as if it happened
the week before.
And that just shows
how much you fucking know
and what you
pay attention to.
God damn you!
What do they pay you
to hold that building up?
Charlie Utter
of "Utter Charlie
and Freight."
It's enough to get you
off with a position.
I'm in a position,
you eternally meddling
cocksucker.
Yeah, leaning forward,
shit-faced drunk.
I am talking about
nursing the plague.
Fucking tent operation.
Caring of the sick
in the fucking tent!
How about bullwhacker
of the fucking freight
between Deadwood
and Cheyenne?
No.
How about supervisor,
mail delivery?
Go away, Charlie.
Or any fucking thing
else you want to do.
Go away!
Congratulations on being
a big fucking deal.
No one's any big
fucking deal, Jane.
And all them
offers stand.
I've seen you in some stupid
fucking outfits in my time,
but that one
takes the prize.
I think that this month
we're gonna try
raspberry leaf.
Thanks, Doc.
Young lady,
anything to report
with your privates?
Nah.
All right.
Meeting outside
when you're done, Doc.
All right.
Thanks, Doc.
In a case like yours
I wouldn't know what else to prescribe.
All right.
Whose idea was them pears
and fucking peaches?
I figured since we had 'em
for the plague meeting...
Shows good thinking
and initiative.
Ladle 'em out at various intervals
on the fucking table, Johnny.
Yes, sir.
I'm declaring myself
conductor of this meeting
as I have the bribe sheet.
If I'm excluded,
say so, Al.
Don't leave me to die
the death of thousand cuts.
Sit down, Tom.
Don't subject me
to death by water torture.
Take a seat, Tom,
and toss whatever book
you've been reading on
the fucking yellow peril, huh?
I just opened
across the way.
Was I supposed to attend?
Well before I can
answer that question,
I better know
who the fuck you are.
Charlie Utter.
Of "Utter's Freight
and Postal Delivery Service."
Nice sign blocking my fucking view.
Take a seat.
Had a lovely advert
in today's "Pioneer."
So, US government's
negotiating peace
with Spotted Elk,
Red Cloud
and other leaders of the heathens.
Thank you, Johnny.
The heathens will get money
to give up the hills,
and the hills'll be annexed
to the territory.
First notice of our cost
to avoid getting
fucked in the ass
by those legislative
cocksuckers
was just handed to me
by Yankton's toll collector,
who suggests also our best case
in keeping title to the claims,
property and businesses
is to start up now
a kind of an informal
governing organization
that'll be recognized
by the territorial cocksuckers
and given legal status
when the territory is annexed.
Since we'll all
have proved ourselves
civilized sorts
that don't only wear
our pants to cover our tails,
hence the fucking
meeting.
Do the bribes come
out of our pockets?
Hmm?
The hell you must have gone
through talking to that leech.
Hereafter, you let me
take my fair share
- of the weight in those conversations.
- Yeah, thanks, Cy.
Well, couldn't our informal
organization levy taxes
on the settlement
to pay the bribes?
Say to license
businesses?
Wouldn't that spread
the burden?
Will women who pay
the license fees
have the same right
to operate brothels as men?
What's that got to do
with the price of fish?
Our proper order
of fucking business
is to make titles
and departments
before the territorial
cocksuckers
send in their cousins
to rob and steal from us.
Well who fills
the various positions?
Pick the names from a fucking hat
as far as I'm concerned.
I'd like to be mayor.
Objections?
Mayor.
Wouldn't a good use
for an informal organization
with temporary appointees
be providing a few
services to the camp?
Mayor?
Well, provide
a few services
and use the lion's share
of revenues to pay the bribes.
More than providing
services to 'em,
taking people's money is what makes
organizations real,
be they formal,
informal or temporary.
There's a piano outside.
Piano?
When Tolliver opened
up across the way,
you said we needed a fancier piano.
You ordered one.
You want me to abandon the fucking
meeting to bring in a new piano?
Well, I'm just telling you
it come in from Montgomery Ward.
Yeah.
"Any big arrival, notify me
immediately." You said that.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Well, um...
Floor's open
for levy suggestions
and nominations
for department heads.
Self-nominations
are permitted.
Sorry.
We lack a gavel.
Doc?
Who's gonna
be comptroller?
Well, um, elections?
Will we have
some elections
somewhere down the road?
This is temporary, right?
- Yeah, ad hoc.
- Ad hoc.
Ad fucking hoc.
Free fucking gratis.
Can we just get on
with the fucking meeting?
Timid, ha.
Hardly, sir.
My own strong personal impulse
was to offer my name for office,
but a fourth estate,
independent
in name and fact
from the operations
of government
is of the essence
of a free society.
I've got to find
early occasion
to put the mayor
off his pedestal.
Don't do it
with no mud.
Did you wait a day before you ordered
that fucking thing?
Boss, you specifically
countermanded my waiting
and asking again when you gave me
the order to get it.
What fucking revenue is being generated
by those hoople-heads
gathering around
that cocksucker
and yodeling about
their fucking points of origin?
The shine'll wear off.
My fucking head.
All that organizing
businesses?
Aw, 25 cups of coffee and too much
circulating in the fresh air.
You chaired piss out of that meeting
this afternoon.
That still don't get you off the hook
about that piano.
Before I'd told a story on myself
like the doc did,
I'd have just said,
"Thank you for the nomination,
but I decline being
health supervisor."
They buy bodies
to do their research.
Doctors, they cut 'em open
and study 'em.
All the less reason for saying
you've been arrested for grave robbing.
Seven times.
Anyways,
good for you
volunteering for the post.
If I had known then
they wasn't gonna have a sheriff,
- I'd have never raised my hand.
- I don't follow.
I only raised my hand
'cause I didn't want to be sheriff.
It's all temporary,
anyhow.
That's right.
And ad hoc.
Did you happen
to notice at The Gem
that one girl we rode back with
from Mr. Garret's funeral?
Trixie, isn't that what
she said her name was?
- Who'd been helping with the child.
- Yeah, I noticed her.
Much as she'd taken
to helping with that little one.
Big pull to that,
going back to what you know.
You think she's pretty?
Very.
- Take some air.
- Yes, sir.
- Evenin'.
- Evening.
Some meeting, huh?
Congratulations
on your new post.
Oh.
And for your
freight business.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Evening, Charlie.
Evening.
How much time
you think that
Fire marshal obligation's
gonna take?
More or less as much as your health
commissioner, huh?
How about that doc?
Grave robber.
Anybody else felled
from them canned peaches?
Not to my knowledge.
Why, you feeling poorly?
Well, um, it's...
it's easing up some.
- Evening.
I've wondered how
things were with you...
and Mrs. Garret
and the child.
I expect they're well.
I know she struck
lucky at her claim.
And how are you, Trixie?
As you see.
Earning the greasy eye
from my boss for idle chatter.
Can I buy
you a drink?
I'd rather
you didn't.
This isn't
the place for you.
So you say.
If you insist on
my embarrassing myself,
have it not where
I'd want you to see me.
Come see me then.
He don't permit
our making calls out.
Come to our store.
Come buy a broom.
I don't want what
I can't have, Mr. Star.
All right.
If I did come,
I'd buy an axe,
a hammer and a saw.
All fully stocked.
And we never ask the purpose
of a customer's purchase.
Our mayor.
Oh, Mayor!
Doctor.
I'm gonna have
a look at you.
All right.
Don't turn your head
away, Reverend.
Being sick ain't nothing
to be ashamed of.
Look at my finger.
I apologize
for the smell.
What is it
that you smell?
As if I've died.
You emit no such odor.
I smell my flesh rotting.
It isn't rotting, Reverend.
Your flesh does not smell.
You've not died.
You're having organic
changes in your mind
that's making you
believe these things.
Do you understand me?
Formerly, Doctor,
when the word took me
as I read scripture,
people felt God's
presence through me
and that was a great gift
that I could give to them.
Now the word does not
take me when I read.
Nor do I feel
Christ's love.
Nor do those who listen
hear it through me.
All right.
This is God's purpose.
The not knowing
the purpose is...
my portion
of suffering.
And is there any pain
competing with
the not knowing?
I'm not in pain.
There are new smells
I smell.
And there parts of my body
I can't feel,
and His...
and His love.
And you want
to continue like this?
As long as He wills,
this must be my part.
To be afraid, as well.
Well if this is His
will, Reverend,
He is a son of a bitch.
Good night.
Good night, Doctor.
Hey, Eddie.
Hey, kid.
How'd it go?
All right.
And I got me a four-bit room.
Play your cards right,
I'll tell you where.
Hi, Cy.
I was afraid I'd lost
you to the heathens.
How was that meeting?
All right.
We were organizing for annexation
until Eddie cracked
his fucking mouth.
What'd it turn to then?
A joint like ours, Joanie,
what are we selling?
Walk through this door,
it's a new start.
Come on in,
try your luck here.
Of course, we know
the percentages being the percentages,
you play long enough,
your luck ain't gonna get
no better here than anywheres else.
Maybe it's 'cause
we're in a brand new camp.
Since we arrived,
certain people
that are near and dear to me
seem to have bought
into our own fucking line
and now they're trying
to get me to go along.
But I can't.
See, Joanie,
'cause I'm a big boy.
Now I'm ready for...
Eddie and me
to have a little chat.
I did look around
for places, Cy.
Good, I wanted you to.
I want to go ahead
and do what we talked about.
Good, honey.
With your eyes
wide open.
Eddie Sawyer.
Can we keep
this short?
Sure, Eddie.
If he finds you a 12-year-old farmboy
to have some fun with,
is that short enough
for you?
I never did that
and you know it.
All this crap about
what is and isn't natural,
whatever does it for a fella
is what does it, ain't that right?
I never did that.
But did you ever want to unbutton
some farmboy's Dentons
and get yourself some relaxation?
That's what I'm asking.
Take that boy you spoke up
for up in Joanie's room the other day.
I spoke up for not
torturing that boy.
Well, what you spoke for and what
you would have wanted to do
if it was just you
and that corn-fed in that room alone
is what I'm inquiring
about the difference between.
- A dry hole, Cy.
- Aw, you could work that out.
You just use some
spit on that or lard.
17 fucking years
and I never saw a look on your face
like I saw up there
in that room the other day.
Including when I had
to smack some girl around.
I was never in a room
with you before
where you was
gonna kill somebody.
I do not make judgments.
I gave that up a long time ago.
All I want is for us
to get along better, Eddie.
So every time you open
your mouth in public,
I don't have to worry
about what the fuck's gonna come out!
So let me get you
some fucking kid
to fuck in the ass or mouth or suck
his prick or let him fuck you!
Fuck you, Cy.
Fuck you.
Now, now.
That's where I draw the line.
Friend or no friend, and us wanting
to get along better or not,
I want you to go up
into Joanie's room, which l...
I gather she don't
want to go into no more.
I want you to go up there and think
this thing through.
Imagine yourself
up there with that boy
like the other day,
only this time it's just him and you.
And I want you to figure out
what it is that you want.
'Cause next time
we see each other,
I want you clearheaded,
and understanding yourself.
The old Eddie that knows the percentages
and how to play 'em,
and whatever a man does away
from the table is his own business.
I want you cheerful
and ready to help me with my work
or I don't want you
coming the fuck out!
Hmm?
You finish your shift
and you go up there
to Joanie's room
and you think
things through.
All right,
Eddie Sawyer?!
Do we understand
each other?
Why didn't you volunteer for something
at that meeting?
Why didn't you
put your hand up?
Might've kept you
from being such an evil cocksucker.
Say hello to the new
fire marshal.
I'm getting out.
Goodbye
and good luck.
Wait on it until
you ain't exhausted, Jane.
Maybe you'll
change your mind.
Direction of this
entire camp
makes me sick,
and it bores
the living shit out of me.
Well working hours
like you've been working
would get anyone
out of sorts.
And you helped
a lot of people.
Sent a dozen men
out with their plague sores healed
to go back to getting
'em on their Johnsons.
I will not be a drunk
where he's buried.
And I cannot
stay fucking sober.
So you...
and every human
being on earth...
past, present
and future
can drink
mare's piss.
Believe I'll just have
well water.
- Shut up, Charlie.
- All right.
If the subject comes up,
explain to Bill.
All right, Jane.
All right.
Tell them over at livery
l... I'm good for the mount.
Do not fucking
worry about me.
And inform Hostetler
at the fucking livery
you saved his
fucking life.
All right.
And do not worry about
getting paid back.
Check the mail,
Charlie,
and you will find
soon proper payment.
All right, Jane.
Check with Utter Mail
and Charlie Freight!
All right.
Since last our eyes
were upon each other, lo,
I hope you've earned
me $5.
No.
L... I gave the lady
your note, sir.
She says to come ahead, but to knock
low as the little one's asleep.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Evening.
Good evening, Mr. Bullock.
Sophia's asleep.
So I was told.
Sorry for calling so late.
I'm to see Ellsworth in the morning
and wondered what I should say.
Ellsworth seemed
very competent and trustworthy.
He suggested
that until the extent
of the quartz deposits
could be proved,
he could prospect the creek
on my claim each week
to keep my title active.
How'd that plan
sound to you?
I feel it's exactly
the way to proceed.
All right then.
- Won't you sit down?
- Thank you.
Would it improve
your opinion of me
if I told you I was Commissioner
of the Board of Health?
How wonderful.
I suppose.
It's to put the camp's
best foot forward
as far as being taken
into the territory.
A number of men
took positions.
- I see.
- Farnum's mayor.
How horrifying.
I wrote
to my wife today.
Did you?
About her and my boy
coming to the camp.
You have a son as well?
They're in Michigan
with her people.
My thinking was
with the treaty coming,
annexation,
the camp would
be settling down, a safer place.
Yes.
- Any other sons or daughters?
- No, that's it.
My brother
was in the cavalry.
He was killed
two years ago.
I'm sorry.
Anyways.
I'm glad you got along
with Ellsworth.
Well, thank you for all
your help, Mr. Bullock.
Sure.
And congratulations
on your new post
and the prospect
of your family rejoining you.
Thank you.
Good night,
Mrs. Garret.
Good night.
May I ask why you spoke
of your brother?
My wife
was his widow.
My boy
is their child.
I see.
- Good night.
? Boy, Buddy Bone,
you can blow a mean horn there. ?