That's what McCall
was ridin'.
All right.
Evening.
Evening back.
Look at that paint,
Charlie.
I seen it.
I had a happy
just like that.
Foundered.
Makes me miserable
reminiscing on it.
Do you know the owner?
If he'd sell the horse
is what he really wants to know.
Well, I don't know
if he'd sell.
But the fuckin' jerk's
in that bunkhouse.
- Thank you.
- Evenin'.
Jack McCall.
I'm done.
I don't wanna
play no more.
Bein' a loudmouth
cunt,
I guess some time
since he's been here,
this fella who don't
wanna play no more
probably spoke of killin'
Wild Bill Hickok.
Well, we're
Bill Hickok's friends.
- I'm Seth Bullock.
- I'm Charlie Utter.
And if you got your head blown off
sittin' here with your back turned,
that'd be as fair a play
as you gave him.
Guess you wanna
soften him up some
before you
make your offer?
My plan is to take him
to Yankton for trial.
If you got a different idea,
you can ride ahead.
Nah.
Let's take the cocksucker
to Yankton.
I don't know of
a Henry Anderson in camp,
but that don't
mean there ain't.
This was took of him
in the Union Army.
He'd be 12 years
older now.
Could you
let her hold it?
With so much showing,
it's pretty near fallin' apart.
Here.
Third from the middle.
Right uh...
right there?
Yeah.
That face don't...
don't look familiar.
Thanks for lookin'.
You definite
he's in these hills?
Wrote from Bismarck,
said he'd send for us
when he got set up.
I just gotta say
it's no guarantee your dad's
anywhere near this area.
And there's no fuckin' joy
in me telling you that,
but it's the goddamned truth
and the way human beings are.
- Said he'd send for our mother and us.
- Is your mama here?
She passed.
Sorry.
Well, good luck.
Do you know of...
of work for me?
- No.
- She can get work right here.
- No, sir.
- No, thank you.
- Can you push a broom?
- And I could start now.
Four bits a day.
I bet you'd like
the first in advance.
If you wouldn't mind.
Same for her,
as regrets for me
being such a ruffian.
Here you go, honey.
If I don't fire him first,
you can pick him up at 10:00.
Thank you, sir.
I'll wait
for you, Miles.
Find a safe place
to wait, you hear?
We teach a special
sweepin' technique here.
Follow her lead.
It's all right, son.
It's all right.
Um... excuse me.
I'm required to be
at the graveyard.
The Widow Garret is
laying her husband to rest.
I'd have bet
a month's wages that burial
would've took place
in New York City,
if I had a fuckin'
payin' job.
The uh... wet cloth
to his lips
seems to give him
some relief.
- All right.
- Thank you.
What do you think
of my patient, Doc?
You might wanna steer clear
of his reflection for a while,
but you're symptom-free.
You ain't contagious no more
and you can't get
re-infected, so...
Them as heals under my care
stay fuckin' healed.
Thanks, Doc.
I got clothes
for you back here.
Hereafter in Calamity,
I'll be sure to call for Jane.
You gonna stick
around the camp?
I believe I will
for a while.
Good, 'cause I wanna
monitor your activities,
find out what you do that weighs
so heavy on your conscience.
When I first come
on you in the woods,
all you could say
was, "I apologize."
Before you exhibit your Johnson,
I'm gonna see to this fella.
So long.
Good luck to you.
- Good luck to you.
- All right.
- You're on your own for alterations.
- Hmm.
Now I'm gonna
lay this cloth on your fuckin' lips.
There's Mr. Star
to collect us.
Mr. Star has been
ever so attentive.
- Very considerate.
- To you.
When we leave the hotel,
my boss will be watchin'.
Shall I reel and stagger?
I...
I know the risk lying
to him has put you to.
I've... I can't imagine why I'd make it
the subject of humor.
You're feeling better.
- Am I early?
- Good morning, Mr. Star.
I'll be ready
in just a moment.
- I can have a cup of coffee downstairs.
- No, not at all.
Wait, wait in here,
with Trixie.
I'll just
be a moment.
That widow ain't high.
Maybe waiting till
after the service.
When she'd wanna get good and fucking
loaded is before the fucking service,
against all
the fucking carrying on.
- What do you think?
- Makes sense.
Meaning all that whore's been telling
me the last 10 fucking days
about seeing the widow taking the dope,
and your own fucking assurances,
you verify that she's loaded
personally... you're both full of shit.
I checked in
on the woman daily.
If I was fooled, perhaps I've chosen
simplemindedness, Al,
over realizing
a certain friend
has used me as an instrument
of purposes he concealed.
Say what
you're gonna say,
or prepare for eternal
fucking silence.
I don't believe
you commissioned me
to make an offer
on the widow's claim
to keep the regulators
off you, Al.
I think someone found something
out there you want.
Assume you ain't
been privy
to the ins and outs
of that matter
for the sake
of fucking conversation, huh?
I mean,
was I asleep, E.B.,
when you and me
declared undying loyalty
and full faith
mutual disclosure
about every fucking detail
of every fucking move
- we were ever gonna make together?
- You used me as a pawn, Al.
And you fucked up the game
is the central fucking present issue.
We agreed on 2,000.
You want a fucking percentage instead?
Is that such
an inconceivable proposition?
- Yeah, you got a percentage, E.B.
- How big?
2% of the first million,
half a percent after.
You wanna feel
a damp palm, Al,
select either
of these hands.
Just get to the funeral, E.B.
Go to 20 if you have to.
Just get that
fucking claim.
20 if I have to.
My word.
What a handsome man.
Wish I could tell you I recognize him.
Thank you anyway.
- Your dad, I expect.
- Yes.
You have reason
to think he's out here?
He wrote us from Bismarck
he'd be prospecting the hills.
- "Us" being?
- My brother.
He just got
work over here.
Good for him.
So it's just
the two of you?
Our mother passed,
why we come from Buffalo.
- You're out here looking for your dad.
- Yes.
- Uh, Henry?
Out here looking
for her father, Eddie.
Her and her
older brother.
Got a photograph, I don't...
I don't recognize the likeness.
No.
- Henry Anderson?
- Yes.
- Yeah, I don't recognize him.
- Mm.
What are you gonna do
while your brother works?
Work too, while we're looking to set
aside, if we have to move on.
Ah, if Dad doesn't
turn up here.
Yeah, what do you do?
Cook, clean,
sew, sweep.
Uh-huh.
- How quick do you learn?
- Guess I learn pretty quick.
Maestro.
We are strangers
and sojourners.
Mr. Garret's
burial place
is a great distance
from New York City.
But his heart...
Ingrid... Marta.
- And on the great day...
- Mama.
- His Father will take him into it.
- Papa.
As He will all who
confess His Son savior
from wherever
we may be put to rest.
Our hymn is
"A Mighty Fortress."
? A mighty fortress
is our God ?
? A bulwark
never failing... ?
- My sympathies, madam,
- ? Our helper... ?
but, my own
requirements force me
to ignore
what's seemly.
I must decide where
to place my capital.
Might raising my offer
to say, $19,500, uh,
prompt you
to an immediate answer?
- No, Mr. Farnum.
- ? Doth seek to work us woe ?
? Lord Sabbath,
His name ?
- ? His craft and power... ?
- I would as soon not see Bill now.
I'll see him
some other time.
Come on.
? On earth is not
His equal... ?
I will require a decision
within 24 hours...
Please, stop speaking
to me, Mr. Farnum.
? Did we in our own
strength confide ?
? Our striving
would be losing ?
? Were not the right man
by our side... ?
? The man of God's
own choosing. ?
I hope you ain't gived up
on that little runt of a girl, Al.
Oh, do you worry
for her, Dan?
Wandering the muck
of our thoroughfare,
her tiny self
all but swallowed up in horseshit?
Hey, kid!
Come here.
- Yes, sir?
- Stand with us here a second.
What are...
what are we doing?
Waiting.
And out the door
he'll go,
and prompt as
a Swiss fucking timepiece
three big-tittied whores will now emerge
from behind that screen.
He lines 'em up
at two-foot intervals,
smock tops down,
and all but
sprints past 'em,
giving their
titties a lick.
And if he misses
a titty,
does not let himself
retrace his steps.
- Don't tell me.
- Yeah, then he goes on his way home,
relieved for the day.
What's your name? It's Miles, huh?
- Miles, yeah.
- Yeah.
Strange, huh, Miles?
But something you gotta
know about specialists.
They pay a premium
and they never
cause fucking trouble.
I sometimes imagine in my declining
years running a small joint
in Manchester, England,
catering to specialists exclusive.
And to let 'em know they're amongst
their own, I'll operate from the corner,
hanging upside down
like a fucking bat, hmm?
- We're not such bad sorts here, huh?
- No, sir.
So do you wanna ask your sister
if she'd like to reconsider, hmm?
- You don't really mean that.
- Of course I don't mean it.
How dare you suggest
I'd mean a thing like that, huh?
I did my part.
Raised our offer to 20
and demanded answer within the day.
But what,
you cocksucker?
Complications have ensued:
Bullock's come back.
I expect she'll wanna
take counsel with him.
Tell the whore
I wanna see her.
And I trust this doesn't
alter our agreement.
I trust you know
2% of nothing's fucking nothing.
That fella from Montana
I knew to trust won't be
able to assay your claim.
I see.
We'll engage someone local,
and I'll keep an eye on him.
As I've decided to stay
in camp, Mr. Bullock,
at least
for the near term,
I hope you'll feel absolved
of those responsibilities
towards my interest that you undertook
at Mr. Hickok's request.
I prefer to see
'em through.
They're properly mine.
I even feel marginally
capable of shouldering them
and I certainly realize
that you and Mr. Star
have responsibilities
of your own.
Are you firing me,
Mrs. Garret?
I'm offering you
absolution.
Otherwise
I'm staying on.
I'm so sorry
you were hurt.
So, how hard are they
coming at you to sell?
I could confide
that in an effort
to blur my judgment,
Mr. Swearengen
engaged intermediaries
to indulge me
with opium.
But that would entail
acknowledging that
I've had a weakness
in that direction.
Uh...
more appropriately,
uh, I could add
at the graveyard
Mr. Farnum raised his offer
$7,500,
presumably also on
Mr. Swearengen's instruction,
and set a 24-hour
limit to my reply.
Under the circumstances,
I'd say that's coming pretty hard.
Please forgive me for
making you uncomfortable, Mr. Bullock.
I had better manners
before I began to abstain.
That's all right.
Anyways, are you at risk
for the smallpox?
I was inoculated
in New York City.
The child whose life you saved
presumably has not been,
but I assume she's
safer under my care
than traveling in a covered wagon
with strangers.
Anyways, I'll
line up the assayer.
Thank you.
You are changed.
You seem to be too.
Our stock's depleted,
but we are offering a 100% discount
on any item that
catches your eye.
I've got money.
Our special get-
acquainted-with-those-
we'd-like-to-get-
acquainted-with sale.
Mr. Utter.
I brought these
pickaxes for you to sell.
There's two sifters on that
black cayuse out there.
Mighty grateful, sir.
You got this place just
about built, don't you?
Saving the last
master-strokes for Seth.
Oh, hello.
I didn't see you.
Hello.
Hey, that's that
little girl, isn't it?
Taking care of her
for Mrs. Garret.
As much as she favors you,
she could be yours.
I lost the receipts
for my costs.
Maybe while you was busy
saving my partner's life.
Let me get these
sifters for you.
See if you can make
those accounts add up.
I don't know if
you heard me inside
thanking you for
helping my friend.
I heard you.
It's all right.
I'm sorry
you lost yours.
All right.
Thank you.
Welcome back,
Mr. Utter.
We've had a mild
increase in rates,
but I do have
a room available.
I'll see.
What do you want,
Mr. Farnum?
I have a message
for Trixie
that's looking
to that orphan child.
- She's to see her longer-term employer.
- I'll tell her.
You know
who that is?
I know she works
at The Gem.
And even so, admit her
to your trade at public hours.
Congratulations, sir,
on your advanced thinking.
Al wants you,
Trixie.
Stickler for
self-delivered messages.
Our dad ain't here.
I know it,
even if my brother don't.
Maybe he never even
tried to get here.
Or maybe he did try
to get here and couldn't,
maybe something
happened to him.
There's so many ways
it could be, Flora,
it's not much point
deciding which it was.
He'd never think that,
though, my brother.
Must be how
he needs to do.
I ain't a virgin...
if you wanna know that.
I had a boyfriend
in Buffalo.
Well, was you upset
to have to leave him?
- What do you think?
- I don't know.
I was upset.
At the same time
he was a stupid son of a bitch.
And rough.
Here.
You can't tell
my brother about him.
He'd make it back to Buffalo
and shoot Lewis in the head.
All that way in defense
of your virtue?
That's more trouble
than I ever took with it.
Cy.
Lazarus risen.
Look at you,
you son of a gun.
Hello, Cy.
Good to see you,
Andy.
Don't be afraid
to shake with me, Eddie.
I ain't contagious
no more.
Highly becoming outfit.
I'm here for
my belongings.
Look...
they're gone, Andy.
Measures to stop
the spread.
Ah hell, the important
thing is you're well.
I'll front you
whatever you need.
Let's get something
going, hmm?
- Andy?
- In the flesh, sweetheart.
- Which ain't much to look at.
- You made it, Andy.
Oh, and we ain't
getting nothing going.
All I come back for,
Cy, was my things,
and you tossed
them too.
Why don't you take this and get yourself
outta that clown outfit?
Once you've cooled off
a little,
think how you'd have done different
when somebody showed up
in the shape you was in
and my responsibilities to meet.
Better than to throw him
in the woods to fucking die?
Then don't think
about nothing, Andy.
Use the money
for a whore
and a toot and go join
the fucking circus.
Did you
turn her out?
Her brother's
gonna be a problem.
Fuck her brother.
We'll handle the brother
if we have to kill
the cocksucker.
That's an interesting
piece of strange.
Ain't you a picture?
- What is it?
- Hmm?
Oh, am I detaining you
in some way?
Am I fucking
imposing?
Mrs. Garret's
to sit down with Bullock.
I thought you'd
want me over there.
Oh yeah, so you can bring me
a full and fair report, huh?
But will the widow have her
wits about her, Trixie, huh?
Or will they be
passing the opium pipe
like heathens between 'em,
her and fucking Bullock, hmm?
- What're you pissed off for?
- I ain't pissed off.
I'm in fucking
wonderment.
I'm waiting to be kept happy
by the next fucking fairy tale.
Do you want me
back at the hotel
or do you wanna
do something to me?
Now why would I want you
to go back there, huh?
Or rely on anything
you said transpired
after you lied
about her taking dope, huh?
Her being high...
wasn't gonna have
nothing to do
with whether or not
she sold you that claim,
and she wanted
to get off the dope.
And that little one needs
someone to care for her...
and maybe get her
the fuck outta here.
And I knew it
wasn't gonna be me.
So you want me
back over there
and to tell you what
they fucking decide?
Or do you wanna rip
my fucking guts out?
You get
back there quick.
Don't kid
yourself, Trixie.
Don't get
a mistaken idea.
Mr. Utter.
This is where Bill
got killed, huh?
Uh...
I'll be sorry about that
for as long as I live.
Can you tell me
about it?
Yeah.
It... it was
about sun-up
over at that
Bella Union joint,
Mr. Hickok plum
gutted McCall at draw.
And now here Mr. Hickok
was at poker again.
Say a couple hours
of daylight left
and in come that
coward McCall.
Walked up on him
and shot him in the head.
Bill never know
when he come in.
Uh, those of us
that did,
we didn't have no inkling
of what he intended.
He just murdered him,
right where he sat.
If I may, sir...
This is here where
Wild Bill was sitting
when McCall entered from the front,
approached the table,
causing no apprehension
'cause he had often
frequented the game.
Of a sudden,
McCall produced a revolver
and shouting "Take that, damn you!"
He fired.
Muzzle couldn't have been three inches
from Wild Bill's head.
Now I'm told that Hickok
fell dead immediately,
but I won't
testify to it,
because the bullet, after it passed
through Wild Bill's brain,
struck me
in my right wrist,
and I lost several seconds
to pain before regaining my senses.
Sir, you have my word
as eyewitness to the rest,
and I suppose this wound
as added proof for the doctors
they feared crippled me
in the hand I use to write.
I will take the murderer's
bullet to my grave.
Thanks.
Aces over eights,
as I just now recall.
That is the hand
that Wild Bill had.
Sure, Captain. Sure.
You like how
that falls?
Sure.
- Do you like it, Flora?
- Why not?
I'd prefer you happy, honey,
but if you can't be,
you need to pretend at it
better than you're doing
or you're gonna be
hungry and cold
and getting done to you
for nothing outside
what you'd have made money
to live on and save up besides
if you acted
the part in here.
I thought I only had to act it with them
that wanna stick it in me.
You never know who
that might be, Flora.
There you go.
I prefer you
happy.
Or at least
pretending better?
I think
he's dead, Doc.
Could you tell the litter bearers
not to make so much of getting
this one outta here?
- Has young Joey gone to dust?
- Yeah.
As flesh must,
to be restored
by the Savior's return.
Oh, Mr. Bullock is
back among us,
and also,
also Mr. Utter.
Does Charlie
know about Bill?
They were together,
Mr. Bullock and he.
They'd captured
Jack McCall.
I hope that's only the beginning
of what they fucking did to him.
- Gave him over to federal authorities.
- Gave him over?
- Rendered unto Caesar.
- Jesus Christ.
Mr... Mr. Bullock was
struck by an Indian's axe.
Marked like the first-born
of Adam and Eve.
- Are you drunk?
- No.
- What the fuck is that?
- He's all right.
All right, Reverend.
All right.
You're all right,
Reverend. All right.
He marks us sinful
and forgiven
by confession.
All right.
He has told us and shown us.
He has told me.
All right.
You listen to me now,
Reverend.
You are goddamn exhausted,
and you give yourself
no respite.
These seizures
may owe something to that,
but it also
wouldn't surprise me
if you had a lesion
in your goddamn head,
and that's what's
giving you the seizures
and generating your chats
with the goddamn divinity.
No goddamn offense intended.
- None taken, sir.
- Now get outta here,
- and get yourself some rest!
- Go on, Reverend.
Doc's tired too,
the only reason he's
talking so fucking harsh.
Could not the lesion be
the instrument of God's
instructive intention, Doctor,
if I am so afflicted?
Well, of course it could,
His ways not being ours
and so forth.
But could He not,
Reverend, just want you
getting out of here and getting yourself
some goddamn rest?
- You have to go now.
- We don't have to do nothing,
I'd pay the same price
just to sit with you.
My brother works in this place up here,
and he keeps a hard watch.
If you wanna stick it
in me tomorrow,
you better let me
go in by myself.
- What time are you gonna start?
- 11:00, I guess.
I'll be receiving
around noon.
All right, Flora.
Here's a dollar anyway.
You're swell.
Evening.
Evening, miss.
- You're early.
- Yes.
- I guess no luck finding your dad.
- No, no luck.
I knew you would've had a cheerier
look on your face if you had.
Let me get you a place to sit away
from these rough sons of bitches.
Hey!
Do your drinking at the bar
or get the fuck out of here!
You have a seat here.
I'll get you a beverage. Do you want
a soft cider or a sarsaparilla?
- Cider if it's not a trouble.
- Soft cider.
Did she find her dad?
Her chances of finding
her dad are greater than yours
of walking out
of this door upright,
unless you shut
your fucking mouth.
You got it?
Swearengen's had his hand
on the tiller
far as getting dealing
with this epidemic.
Is that so?
Yeah, the dead don't
drink or chase women
must be his thinking
on that subject.
That Indian fought
like hell.
I'd guess you did too.
Charlie figured out
how it must have been.
The Indian had to kill me
for coming on the burial place,
and maybe it had been me, too,
that killed his friend,
cut his friend's head off so he wouldn't
have eyes to see the sunset
all those years
he'd be lying there dead.
So he had to kill me
for that too.
And he couldn't
before he'd laid hands on me
or the killing
wouldn't be honorable.
We fought like fucking hell,
I'll tell you that much,
and I never once had
the upper-hand.
It just happened out
the way it happened out.
He was just trying to live,
same as me,
and do honor to his friend, and make
some fucking sense out of things.
And we wind up that way,
and I wind up
after beating him till
I couldn't recognize his face.
For Christ's sake!
That Indian saved
Jack McCall's life,
- I'll tell you that fucking much.
- Not for long.
Brian MacDonald's not coming.
I want his recommendation
who should assay
that widow's claim.
- Whose?
- Swearengen's.
Shit, Seth.
Get his opinion, too, who should guard
that henhouse we're gonna build.
So... are you okay?
- Yes, and you?
- Yes.
They're nice here.
And Mr. Swearengen,
he's funny as all get-out.
So what place would make
a better score?
Where I'm working.
But why not
take 'em both?
- Could we have a private talk?
- Sure we can.
- Should I be armed?
- Where do you wanna talk?
Come here.
What do you
think of that?
I think that son of a bitch better stop
looking evil at that little girl.
So was it McCall improved
your appearance?
No.
Whoever got the job done,
I hope you gave as good as you got.
It's good to have you back,
with me being superstitious
and all hell breaking loose
when you left.
I'm here to talk
about Mrs. Garret.
They planted her husband
this morning?
I wrote a man about
coming to assay her claim,
- but he can't make it.
- Plenty of local alternatives.
I want you
to nominate someone.
Do you?
So if any way
his work was mistaken,
I'd be coming after you.
- You would?
- Yeah.
Since I got nothing to do
with the venture,
what if I decline to make
the recommendation?
Then you better hope
whoever I find does his job right,
'cause I'm still
holding you accountable.
I ain't involved.
E.B. Farnum offered
on her claim.
Farnum's your water-boy and I know
what you've been trying to do to her.
So here you come
in all nobility...
threatening me
with a dire result
if the property
of that widow's husband
thought worthless
from when it sold,
turns out not
to be pinched out.
You and I know how it is,
Mr. Swearengen.
- How what is?
- She gets a square shake,
or I come for you.
What if I come for you?
Are you ready for that?
I guess I'd better be.
Then close your fucking store,
'cause being ready for me
will take care
of your waking hours
and you better have someone to hand the
task off to when you close your eyes.
We understand each other.
Al! Al!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Walk right past me,
Your Holiness,
so I can shut
my fucking office.
Al!
Go on! Stare at her now!
Huh? You like
fucking little girls?
Take a look at
that little girl
'cause she's the last thing
you're ever gonna see.
- Stare at her now, cocksucker.
- Let him down!
Let him fucking down!
Or should I have had him
hold him up?
You heard what I said
about the widow.
Oh yes, Your Holiness.
You heard me too.
So I take it this was
a fair fucking fight, yeah?
Yeah! That's right!
Two free drinks for everybody.
And drinks all night for them
that help with the disposal.
That's me!
I'm sorry that
you had to see that.
Shut the fuck up, Dan, and get her
the fuck away from here... now!
Come on.
I'm sorry,
Mr. Swearengen.
I warned him
not to look at her.
I warned him.
Fucking pussy.
That Joey passed
this afternoon.
Been suffering awful.
But that frog-looking
fellow left the tent
that I found up
in the woods,
left the tent fucking cure pronounced
by the Doc himself.
And in the dumbest looking
outfit a grown man ever wore.
Who's there,
God damn it?!
Who the hell's
it look like?
How the fuck do I know
who it fucking looks like? It's dark!
Jesus Christ, come upon a person
unawares in a fucking graveyard!
I heard you was
back in the camp.
I heard you and that Bullock
got the cocksucker did for Bill.
Was Bill dead
by the time you saw him?
Yeah, he was
already dead.
Why did he let
that son of a bitch get to him?
I don't know,
Charlie.
Anyways, people don't
scare me past speaking,
I come up here nights
tell him the fucking news.
Go ahead.
Charlie avenged
your fucking murder.
And that Bullock fella
was with me that you seemed to like.
Although it occurred to me to wonder
why they didn't do
for the cocksucker
right on the fucking spot.
Is that something we need
to get into in front of him?
You got the biggest mouth
in the territory. You talk to him.
Tell him
whatever you want.
I got that mail route
in Cheyenne that we talked about.
I was bringing back
supplies to them hardware boys
and I run into
that Bullock fella.
He was out there looking
for that McCall
that... that killed you.
And he run into
some heathen boy
and he had one
hell of a fight.
Boy, and he just...
he got...
he got f...
he got f-f...
Fuck.
Can l...
can I tell him
some more tomorrow?
Sure, what the fuck
you asking me for?
I don't make
the rules.
Wanna go back
to the camp?
Please.
And what must Mr. Bullock
have been thinking
as I inflicted my personal confidences
upon him?
- I don't know.
- Nor do I.
At least he kept
a decent privacy.
I have to go
back to The Gem.
He's waiting for me now
to tell him
yours and Mr. Bullock's
thinking about selling the claim,
and I won't be able
to lie anymore.
Next I tell
will be my last.
So I better just
get back there.
Mr. Swearengen
discovered our deception?
- Yeah.
- How?
- Looking at you walk out of the hotel.
- He did not.
I was careful to see he
wasn't watching in the window.
It don't matter,
Mrs. Garret.
The point is,
I gotta go back.
And you need someone
to look to this child,
and with choices
bigger elsewhere
and nothing I can tell
to hold you here,
maybe you better
think about selling and getting out.
Would you wanna
take the girl and go?
Where?
- I have no people anywhere.
- You could go to New York.
L- I could have my relatives
there see you established.
What the fuck?
What would
keep you here?
You wanna fuck
this man?
Fuck him, then think
about the child...
Don't use that language with me,
Trixie, or that tone...
Don't you wanna say
to remember my place?
I do, you rich cunt.
And I'm going
back to it.
She's about to say
her name, you know.
She named her sisters
and her folks.
Think of selling.
If you took her away,
you could hear her say it.
? Old friend ?
? All the stories
to tell ?
? Old friend ?
? Could you
bid me farewell? ?
? Ooh, old friend ?
? It might be easy
for another man to see ?
? Old fool ?
? All the pain
and the scars ?
? Old fool ?
? Could you lay down
your arms? ?
? Old fool ?
? It might be easy
for another man to see ?
? But I think you still
look a lot like me. ?