1
00:01:56,987 --> 00:01:58,929
Is that some sort
of a letter, Marshal?

2
00:02:00,348 --> 00:02:02,420
- Journal.
- Journal.

3
00:02:02,460 --> 00:02:04,282
Good.

4
00:02:04,315 --> 00:02:07,478
You know, I was goin'
to Deadwood, same as you.

5
00:02:07,516 --> 00:02:10,515
- Is that so?
- I had my plans about set.

6
00:02:12,092 --> 00:02:16,118
I only wish to Christ I could get
these past three days back.

7
00:02:17,340 --> 00:02:18,768
I can imagine.

8
00:02:21,947 --> 00:02:24,597
No law at all
in Deadwood,

9
00:02:24,635 --> 00:02:26,161
is that true?

10
00:02:26,203 --> 00:02:27,958
Being on Indian land.

11
00:02:29,308 --> 00:02:31,162
So then you
won't be a marshal?

12
00:02:31,195 --> 00:02:34,740
Taking goods there to open
a hardware business, me and my partner.

13
00:02:34,780 --> 00:02:37,430
If I'd have got there,
I'd have been prospectin'.

14
00:02:37,467 --> 00:02:40,815
Jesus Christ Almighty.
No law at all,

15
00:02:40,859 --> 00:02:44,470
gold you can scoop from the streams
with your bare hands,

16
00:02:44,507 --> 00:02:46,895
and I gotta go
and fuck myself up

17
00:02:46,939 --> 00:02:49,938
by supposedly stealing
Byron Samson's horse.

18
00:02:49,980 --> 00:02:51,954
It's poor damn timing
at the least.

19
00:02:56,539 --> 00:02:58,294
Thank you very much.

20
00:02:59,259 --> 00:03:00,502
You're welcome.

21
00:03:01,819 --> 00:03:03,826
I'm sorry as hell
about your shoulder.

22
00:03:03,867 --> 00:03:07,379
Flesh wound. Don't look like
it wants to infect.

23
00:03:07,420 --> 00:03:11,096
Well, never mind
flesh wounds, sir,

24
00:03:11,131 --> 00:03:14,130
when you are goin'
to meet your maker,

25
00:03:14,171 --> 00:03:17,519
you don't feature telling him that you
shot a marshal in the shoulder

26
00:03:17,563 --> 00:03:20,181
for only doing
his legally ordained job.

27
00:03:20,219 --> 00:03:22,324
He may have heard
worse stories.

28
00:03:22,363 --> 00:03:26,967
God? Well, if he ain't,
I'll tell him six or seven

29
00:03:27,003 --> 00:03:29,785
just on people of my own
personal acquaintance.

30
00:03:31,963 --> 00:03:34,581
I'd like to suggest
an idea to you, sir,

31
00:03:34,619 --> 00:03:36,658
that I pray as
a Christian man

32
00:03:36,699 --> 00:03:38,935
you will entertain
on its own fuckin' merits.

33
00:03:44,219 --> 00:03:46,324
Does it involve
letting you go?

34
00:03:46,363 --> 00:03:49,396
I know two scores,
Mr. Bullock,

35
00:03:49,435 --> 00:03:51,158
that we could
make in transit

36
00:03:51,195 --> 00:03:53,366
without moving
20 feet off our path.

37
00:03:53,402 --> 00:03:55,790
People with cash on hand,

38
00:03:55,835 --> 00:03:57,395
and if once we hit Deadwood

39
00:03:57,435 --> 00:04:00,282
and you didn't want to have
anything to do with me,

40
00:04:00,315 --> 00:04:02,518
we'd never speak again.

41
00:04:02,554 --> 00:04:06,328
We would meet as strangers
the rest of our fuckin' lives.

42
00:04:06,363 --> 00:04:08,250
Now...

43
00:04:08,283 --> 00:04:11,032
you tell me what
you think of that, sir.

44
00:04:14,747 --> 00:04:16,307
It don't appeal to me.

45
00:04:16,346 --> 00:04:18,866
Get the fuck out of here
for a moment, would you, sir?

46
00:04:18,907 --> 00:04:20,662
Byron Samson's
comin' for him.

47
00:04:20,698 --> 00:04:22,356
Sir, would you please
get the fuck out

48
00:04:22,395 --> 00:04:24,467
till we have finished
our previous conversation?

49
00:04:24,507 --> 00:04:26,546
- How many backing his play?
- A dozen, shit-faced.

50
00:04:26,587 --> 00:04:28,310
Samson caved in
Tommy Raymond's head at

51
00:04:28,347 --> 00:04:31,346
- the No-Name Frog. He went against it.
- What are you conversing at?

52
00:04:32,891 --> 00:04:34,167
Jesus Christ!

53
00:04:34,203 --> 00:04:36,145
Come out and talk
to us, Bullock!

54
00:04:36,187 --> 00:04:38,423
Now who is that?
That sounds like Byron Samson.

55
00:04:41,435 --> 00:04:44,817
- Yeah.
- What would he want?

56
00:04:56,922 --> 00:04:59,704
Now tell me what kind
of fuckin' luck I got.

57
00:05:03,034 --> 00:05:06,546
All you're doing stalling,
Bullock, is pissin' me off!

58
00:05:06,586 --> 00:05:10,098
'Cause I guarantee you ain't
making it through in there till sun-up!

59
00:05:10,138 --> 00:05:13,105
So why don't you climb out
from behind your badge,

60
00:05:13,146 --> 00:05:14,869
and your big
brick building,

61
00:05:14,906 --> 00:05:16,945
and you bring
Clell Watson out here

62
00:05:16,986 --> 00:05:19,473
so we can give him
what he fuckin' deserves!

63
00:05:22,074 --> 00:05:23,600
What have we got here?

64
00:05:23,642 --> 00:05:25,300
Whoa!

65
00:05:25,338 --> 00:05:26,930
It's a Jew on a wagon!

66
00:05:26,970 --> 00:05:28,879
Yeah, right out here
in the alley!

67
00:05:30,490 --> 00:05:33,719
I'm executing sentence now
and he's hangin' under color of law.

68
00:05:33,754 --> 00:05:36,120
You and your partner plan on making
Deadwood, Marshal,

69
00:05:36,154 --> 00:05:37,560
do not try for this scaffold.

70
00:05:37,594 --> 00:05:40,889
That's a deal,
you loud-mouthed cocksucker!

71
00:05:40,922 --> 00:05:45,231
You hear this?
Oh! Wait, this ain't right.

72
00:05:45,274 --> 00:05:47,161
My sister was comin'
in the morning.

73
00:05:47,194 --> 00:05:50,674
- What would you have her told?
- That's not enough of a drop.

74
00:05:50,714 --> 00:05:52,623
I'll strangle
for 20 minutes.

75
00:05:52,666 --> 00:05:54,389
I'll help you
with the drop.

76
00:05:54,426 --> 00:05:56,564
Get up and say what you'd
have your sister told.

77
00:05:56,602 --> 00:05:58,707
Do not tether that
rope off of that porch!

78
00:06:06,585 --> 00:06:08,308
Any more gunplay
gets answered.

79
00:06:08,346 --> 00:06:10,168
You called
the law in, Samson.

80
00:06:10,202 --> 00:06:12,089
You don't get to call it off
just 'cause you're liquored up

81
00:06:12,122 --> 00:06:13,583
and popular on payday.

82
00:06:13,626 --> 00:06:15,448
You don't tell us what to do
and what not to do,

83
00:06:15,481 --> 00:06:17,869
'cause you're leaving
Montana anyways!

84
00:06:17,913 --> 00:06:20,334
Now do not jump off
of that stool, you cocksucker!

85
00:06:20,378 --> 00:06:22,549
Or what?
You'll kill me?

86
00:06:24,185 --> 00:06:25,940
You tell my sister

87
00:06:25,978 --> 00:06:29,360
if my boy turns up,
raise him good.

88
00:06:29,402 --> 00:06:31,605
What else?

89
00:06:31,642 --> 00:06:33,878
Tell her
give him my boots.

90
00:06:33,914 --> 00:06:35,474
What else?

91
00:06:35,514 --> 00:06:38,001
Tell him his...

92
00:06:38,042 --> 00:06:39,602
daddy loved him.

93
00:06:39,641 --> 00:06:41,266
Tell him...

94
00:06:43,002 --> 00:06:45,271
he has
God's forgiveness.

95
00:06:46,457 --> 00:06:48,180
Anything else?

96
00:06:49,753 --> 00:06:53,048
You help me
with my fuckin' fall!

97
00:06:53,081 --> 00:06:54,739
Come ahead.

98
00:06:56,442 --> 00:06:58,296
Fuck you!

99
00:07:37,497 --> 00:07:38,806
Stay back!

100
00:07:40,825 --> 00:07:42,679
Move the fuck back,
while my partner...

101
00:07:43,993 --> 00:07:46,414
while my partner's taking
his sweet-ass time

102
00:07:46,457 --> 00:07:48,791
writing whatever the fuck
he's writing over there!

103
00:07:49,945 --> 00:07:51,854
Who'll give his last words
to the sister?

104
00:07:54,393 --> 00:07:56,596
None of you
better fucking move!

105
00:07:56,632 --> 00:07:59,980
Shit!
I'll do it.

106
00:08:13,081 --> 00:08:14,542
Thank you.

107
00:08:18,809 --> 00:08:21,591
- Let's go.
- Hee.

108
00:08:38,745 --> 00:08:40,817
Move ahead!
Move out of the way!

109
00:08:40,856 --> 00:08:43,408
- Move!
- Jesus Christ, come on!

110
00:08:45,017 --> 00:08:48,595
- What's going on!
- Move it up there!

111
00:08:48,632 --> 00:08:51,948
Same damn wagon that
broke down yesterday, Bill!

112
00:08:53,880 --> 00:08:55,406
That's the hold up, huh?

113
00:08:58,009 --> 00:08:59,918
Same wagon and no damn room
to maneuver.

114
00:08:59,960 --> 00:09:02,196
Sounds like it's
tighter out there

115
00:09:02,232 --> 00:09:05,461
than a bull's ass
in fly season.

116
00:09:06,520 --> 00:09:08,821
- How's your headache?
- Not bad.

117
00:09:08,856 --> 00:09:10,678
You want me
to canvass for whiskey?

118
00:09:10,712 --> 00:09:12,719
That's all right, Jane.

119
00:09:12,760 --> 00:09:15,148
Believe me, we're stuck here
a fucking while.

120
00:09:16,248 --> 00:09:18,320
I know your
canvassing techniques.

121
00:09:18,360 --> 00:09:22,735
I don't want any casualties
on my conscience.

122
00:09:30,392 --> 00:09:32,301
It's only
Wild Bill Hickok

123
00:09:32,344 --> 00:09:34,383
you got stalled here
in the muck!

124
00:09:35,384 --> 00:09:37,489
You ignorant
fucking cunts!

125
00:09:42,328 --> 00:09:44,400
We're out here
the whole goddamn day?

126
00:09:44,440 --> 00:09:47,123
What a goddamn circus!

127
00:09:47,160 --> 00:09:48,686
Shit.

128
00:09:53,272 --> 00:09:56,435
- We've got no water!
- All right, friend.

129
00:09:57,752 --> 00:09:59,180
Let's go!

130
00:10:16,664 --> 00:10:19,566
Come on, now,
come on, now, come on.

131
00:10:44,695 --> 00:10:46,255
Chickens for sale!
$3.00 a pair.

132
00:10:46,296 --> 00:10:48,662
Get your chickens here.

133
00:10:59,703 --> 00:11:01,841
This lot rents
at 20 a day, Seth.

134
00:11:01,879 --> 00:11:05,675
- $20 a day.
- Tent only, no construction.

135
00:11:06,648 --> 00:11:08,054
Corner location.

136
00:11:13,335 --> 00:11:16,334
In advance, every morning,
to Mr. Swearengen at the Gem.

137
00:11:16,375 --> 00:11:18,741
- Where's the Gem?
- You'll find it.

138
00:11:18,776 --> 00:11:20,204
Everybody does.

139
00:11:25,559 --> 00:11:28,373
Eight ounces of gold
at $20 an ounce is 160

140
00:11:28,407 --> 00:11:31,636
plus $10 for a half-ounce
makes 170 total.

141
00:11:31,671 --> 00:11:34,453
Inform your dealers
and whores of my credit,

142
00:11:34,487 --> 00:11:35,981
and pour me
a goddamn drink!

143
00:11:36,023 --> 00:11:37,713
Honor and a pleasure,
my good man.

144
00:11:40,759 --> 00:11:43,060
170 credit, Dan,
for Ellsworth.

145
00:11:43,095 --> 00:11:45,550
Yes, sir,
170 for Ellsworth.

146
00:11:45,591 --> 00:11:47,117
I'll let
everybody know.

147
00:11:48,087 --> 00:11:50,061
Lot four,
some hardware guys.

148
00:11:51,767 --> 00:11:53,589
First one today
with this hand.

149
00:11:55,351 --> 00:11:57,806
And pour me another,
my good man.

150
00:11:57,847 --> 00:11:59,669
Here comes another.

151
00:12:00,855 --> 00:12:03,854
- Lot four a stayer?
- Wagon loaded with goods.

152
00:12:03,895 --> 00:12:06,894
Now with that limey
damn accent of yours,

153
00:12:06,935 --> 00:12:10,317
are these rumors true that you're
descended from the British nobility?

154
00:12:10,359 --> 00:12:12,497
I'm descended from
all of them cocksuckers.

155
00:12:12,535 --> 00:12:15,120
Well here's to you,
Your Majesty.

156
00:12:15,159 --> 00:12:17,231
I'll tell you what,

157
00:12:17,271 --> 00:12:20,849
I may have fucked my life up
flatter than hammered shit,

158
00:12:20,886 --> 00:12:22,544
but I stand here
before you today

159
00:12:22,583 --> 00:12:25,332
beholden to no
human cocksucker,

160
00:12:25,367 --> 00:12:27,854
and working a paying
fucking gold claim.

161
00:12:27,895 --> 00:12:31,473
And not the U.S. Government
saying I'm trespassing,

162
00:12:31,511 --> 00:12:33,998
or the savage fucking
red man himself,

163
00:12:34,039 --> 00:12:36,340
or any of these
limber dick cocksuckers

164
00:12:36,375 --> 00:12:39,538
passing themselves off as prospectors
had better try and stop me.

165
00:12:40,694 --> 00:12:42,581
They'd better not
try it in here.

166
00:12:44,119 --> 00:12:47,435
God damn it, Swearengen, I don't trust
you as far as I can throw you,

167
00:12:47,478 --> 00:12:49,714
but I enjoy
the way you lie.

168
00:12:49,750 --> 00:12:52,749
- Thank you, my good man.
- You're welcome,

169
00:12:52,791 --> 00:12:55,027
you conniving,
heavy-thumbed motherfucker!

170
00:12:55,063 --> 00:12:56,972
Watch out!

171
00:12:57,014 --> 00:12:58,574
That's her derringer.

172
00:12:58,615 --> 00:13:01,614
I warned you about
that loopy cunt!

173
00:13:01,655 --> 00:13:03,061
Keep your own tally!

174
00:13:03,094 --> 00:13:05,482
Oh, have no fear
on that score.

175
00:13:07,030 --> 00:13:09,779
I said not to beat on me!
I told him!

176
00:13:09,814 --> 00:13:12,301
Ticonderoga, New York,
Barnett Robinson...

177
00:13:12,342 --> 00:13:15,189
- You got any other guns?
- No, I don't got any more.

178
00:13:15,222 --> 00:13:17,709
Ticonderoga, New York,
Barnett Robinson...

179
00:13:17,750 --> 00:13:20,783
Ticonderoga, New York...
did you find it?

180
00:13:23,542 --> 00:13:24,970
Barnett Robinson.

181
00:13:25,014 --> 00:13:27,469
That's who to notify
if this thing goes wrong.

182
00:13:27,510 --> 00:13:29,200
Yeah, I've got it
right here.

183
00:13:31,670 --> 00:13:35,150
- How you doing, Trixie?
- I told him, don't beat on me, Doc!

184
00:13:35,190 --> 00:13:37,491
- No one asked for your version!
- Said I robbed him

185
00:13:37,527 --> 00:13:40,593
and he started beating on me.
And I didn't rob you!

186
00:13:40,630 --> 00:13:43,564
- I don't remember.
- I didn't, God damn it!

187
00:13:45,174 --> 00:13:46,929
Aw, she shot me
right in the head.

188
00:13:46,966 --> 00:13:49,421
D-don't put
your fingers in it.

189
00:13:50,615 --> 00:13:53,484
Oh yeah,
is it bad, Doc?

190
00:13:55,126 --> 00:13:57,231
Shh, shh, shh.

191
00:14:15,798 --> 00:14:17,685
Get the Chinaman!

192
00:14:17,718 --> 00:14:21,744
Sure would like to know
how he lasted for 20 minutes.

193
00:14:22,805 --> 00:14:24,779
Shot straight to the brain.

194
00:14:24,821 --> 00:14:27,024
So prospect in him
till Dan brings the Chinaman.

195
00:14:27,062 --> 00:14:28,720
Do you mind if I take him
to my place?

196
00:14:28,758 --> 00:14:31,124
Sure. Help the doc with this guy, bring
the Chinaman to the Doc's.

197
00:14:31,158 --> 00:14:33,012
I'll bring that
sled right in, Doc.

198
00:14:33,046 --> 00:14:36,242
Doc,
you drink free today.

199
00:14:36,278 --> 00:14:38,066
And I hope
any word of this

200
00:14:38,102 --> 00:14:39,989
would keep the gun
out of the whore's hand.

201
00:14:41,590 --> 00:14:44,851
- That wouldn't come from me.
- Bastard did himself in.

202
00:14:44,885 --> 00:14:47,340
- Come here.
- I said to stop.

203
00:14:47,382 --> 00:14:48,974
Tell me in my office.

204
00:14:49,014 --> 00:14:51,086
Get the gimp
to clean this place up.

205
00:14:58,262 --> 00:15:00,149
Ugh, Doc!

206
00:15:04,437 --> 00:15:06,192
You know
there's something

207
00:15:06,229 --> 00:15:08,138
peculiar about
this man's cerebral setup

208
00:15:08,181 --> 00:15:10,155
or they can just
write off the forebrain

209
00:15:10,197 --> 00:15:13,545
as being the center
of thought and speech.

210
00:15:13,589 --> 00:15:15,563
Let's just get him
on the sled.

211
00:15:17,045 --> 00:15:18,637
Of course it...

212
00:15:18,678 --> 00:15:20,849
won't matter
to Mr. Wu's pigs.

213
00:15:31,254 --> 00:15:33,009
Whiskey.

214
00:15:36,373 --> 00:15:39,056
I've got an urge to see
that camp, Charlie.

215
00:15:40,150 --> 00:15:42,255
All right...

216
00:15:42,293 --> 00:15:44,714
- Can we leave you with the stock, Jane?
- Yeah.

217
00:15:44,757 --> 00:15:46,731
Bill and me are gonna
ride ahead into camp.

218
00:15:46,774 --> 00:15:49,195
I expect I'll be there
before sundown.

219
00:15:49,237 --> 00:15:51,025
Well, we'll know
where to find you.

220
00:15:51,061 --> 00:15:53,548
What in the hell
do you mean by that?

221
00:15:53,589 --> 00:15:55,377
That I enjoy
a fucking drink?

222
00:15:55,414 --> 00:15:56,974
I wasn't aware
that's outlawed.

223
00:15:57,013 --> 00:15:59,249
Thanks for looking
to the stock, Jane.

224
00:16:01,205 --> 00:16:03,660
Excuse my ill humor.

225
00:16:03,701 --> 00:16:06,089
Certain people wear
on my fucking nerves.

226
00:16:22,389 --> 00:16:24,211
She likes me better
than she likes you.

227
00:16:25,301 --> 00:16:27,756
I wish to hell I knew
what I ever did

228
00:16:27,797 --> 00:16:29,739
to get on that woman's
wrong side.

229
00:16:37,493 --> 00:16:40,013
- You know a back way into the camp?
- Whoa.

230
00:16:44,661 --> 00:16:46,253
We don't go
to the camp.

231
00:16:46,293 --> 00:16:48,878
We go home...
back to Minnesota.

232
00:16:48,917 --> 00:16:52,626
You probably
got the right idea.

233
00:17:01,045 --> 00:17:03,281
Jesus Christ Almighty,
move it!

234
00:17:03,317 --> 00:17:05,389
I can't get to my spot
until you finish!

235
00:17:05,429 --> 00:17:08,331
You got me circling my wagon
like a fly around shit.

236
00:17:08,373 --> 00:17:11,689
We're pretty near done.
We gotta long wait, same as you.

237
00:17:11,732 --> 00:17:13,706
This the first wagon
you ever fucking unloaded?!

238
00:17:13,748 --> 00:17:16,049
Hold on to my horse,
I'll show you how to do it!

239
00:17:16,085 --> 00:17:19,532
We know what we're doing. Put your hat
back on and stick with your wagon.

240
00:17:19,573 --> 00:17:23,915
- And what if I don't?
- Stand there mouthing off and find out.

241
00:17:23,956 --> 00:17:25,362
Sir...

242
00:17:26,868 --> 00:17:28,777
I have a commode
for your inconvenience.

243
00:17:28,820 --> 00:17:31,208
- You think I'm gonna pay for that?
- No, that's free.

244
00:17:31,253 --> 00:17:34,514
From Star & Bullock Hardware,
open in Deadwood soon as we locate.

245
00:17:38,325 --> 00:17:39,950
Hurry up
and get finished!

246
00:17:48,884 --> 00:17:50,858
My father's last words
there in Vienna,

247
00:17:50,900 --> 00:17:53,769
before he passed away,

248
00:17:53,812 --> 00:17:56,594
was "Sol, lose a can
to buy the goddamned fool.

249
00:17:56,628 --> 00:17:58,667
You could slow it down
and sell 'em at retail."

250
00:17:58,708 --> 00:18:01,675
I gotta put a book together
of your old man's deathbed sayings.

251
00:18:01,716 --> 00:18:04,137
That was Wild Bill Hickok
just riding past us, Seth.

252
00:18:04,180 --> 00:18:06,089
I seen him in photographs.

253
00:18:07,604 --> 00:18:09,359
He lost his
stake gambling.

254
00:18:09,396 --> 00:18:11,435
He told me before
he passed out.

255
00:18:11,476 --> 00:18:14,028
He said he lost his stake
and he hadn't found no gold

256
00:18:14,068 --> 00:18:16,686
and he was going back East
after one last piece of pussy.

257
00:18:16,724 --> 00:18:18,152
None of that's
anything to me.

258
00:18:18,196 --> 00:18:21,491
He wakes back up,
starts in beating on me.

259
00:18:21,524 --> 00:18:23,411
Where's his stake,
where's all his money?

260
00:18:23,444 --> 00:18:25,069
You call Danny,
you call Johnny.

261
00:18:25,108 --> 00:18:26,930
Must've been me
who took it from him.

262
00:18:26,964 --> 00:18:29,516
You don't shoot nobody 'cause
that's bad for my business

263
00:18:29,556 --> 00:18:32,206
and it's bad for
the camp's reputation.

264
00:18:33,492 --> 00:18:35,695
He beat the living shit
out of you, didn't he?

265
00:18:37,492 --> 00:18:39,314
Do what you
gotta do to me.

266
00:18:39,348 --> 00:18:41,900
Don't tell me
what to do.

267
00:18:46,388 --> 00:18:49,038
Either way this comes out,
we'll only have to do it once.

268
00:18:49,075 --> 00:18:51,147
What's it to be,
Trixie?

269
00:18:55,028 --> 00:18:56,456
I'll be good.

270
00:18:59,828 --> 00:19:01,486
All right now.

271
00:19:16,115 --> 00:19:17,969
We heard rumors
you might be coming,

272
00:19:18,004 --> 00:19:19,913
but you can't believe
every rumor.

273
00:19:19,955 --> 00:19:22,376
We heard you might be
coming from Cheyenne.

274
00:19:22,419 --> 00:19:24,807
- Here I am.
- If every rumor was true

275
00:19:24,851 --> 00:19:26,989
we'd all have been
scalped now by the Sioux,

276
00:19:27,027 --> 00:19:30,026
or the government would've tossed us out
as treaty violators.

277
00:19:33,971 --> 00:19:37,037
- E.B. Farnum, how do you do?
- Charlie Utter.

278
00:19:38,580 --> 00:19:42,060
You got some mighty
clammy hands there, partner.

279
00:19:42,099 --> 00:19:44,465
Damp palms run
in my family.

280
00:19:46,067 --> 00:19:48,936
Here to prospect, Mr. Hickok,
or on other business?

281
00:19:48,979 --> 00:19:51,051
I'm here
to get a room.

282
00:19:51,091 --> 00:19:54,865
Could we get two?
We're worn out looking at each other.

283
00:19:54,899 --> 00:19:56,589
Separate rooms.

284
00:19:56,627 --> 00:19:59,693
I'll arrange that by tomorrow,
but today I can't fix it.

285
00:20:01,843 --> 00:20:03,697
Unless you
kill a guest.

286
00:20:13,459 --> 00:20:16,328
Wild Bill Hickok.

287
00:20:16,371 --> 00:20:18,410
Nothing can
ever be simple.

288
00:20:18,451 --> 00:20:20,971
He didn't speak of having
lawman ambitions, Al.

289
00:20:21,011 --> 00:20:23,280
Starting with Custer
getting himself massacred,

290
00:20:23,315 --> 00:20:24,973
it's been one thing
after another.

291
00:20:25,011 --> 00:20:27,694
Leaves the godless savage cocksucker
Sioux on the warpath...

292
00:20:27,731 --> 00:20:30,218
if that long-haired
loudmouth had held his end up,

293
00:20:30,259 --> 00:20:31,917
we could be operating
here in peace.

294
00:20:31,955 --> 00:20:33,897
The New York dude's
downstairs, Al.

295
00:20:33,939 --> 00:20:36,873
- Did he order whiskey?
- Yeah.

296
00:20:36,915 --> 00:20:39,849
Did he down it
or is he sipping at it?

297
00:20:39,891 --> 00:20:41,516
He's sipping.

298
00:20:41,555 --> 00:20:44,337
Why'd I even ask, huh?

299
00:20:44,371 --> 00:20:46,193
Go get Tim Driscoll.

300
00:20:46,227 --> 00:20:47,982
Make sure the dude
sees you leave.

301
00:20:48,018 --> 00:20:50,090
- What should I tell Tim?
- Tell him to get over here.

302
00:20:50,131 --> 00:20:52,683
Tell him he's drunk,
sorry for himself, give me five minutes,

303
00:20:52,722 --> 00:20:55,056
- then you come back, do your part.
- All right, Al.

304
00:20:58,291 --> 00:20:59,719
As far as Hickok, Al,

305
00:20:59,763 --> 00:21:02,032
if I'd have pushed him
any harder on his plans,

306
00:21:02,066 --> 00:21:03,975
I was afraid
he'd shoot me.

307
00:21:08,082 --> 00:21:10,732
- Go get Driscoll.
- Yes, sir.

308
00:21:11,699 --> 00:21:12,942
Handmade!

309
00:21:12,978 --> 00:21:15,247
It's all handmade,
guaranteed.

310
00:21:15,283 --> 00:21:17,868
It ain't like something's
being foisted on 'em

311
00:21:17,907 --> 00:21:19,816
they'll be sorry
they bought come sun-up.

312
00:21:20,914 --> 00:21:23,783
- I know that.
- These are quality items.

313
00:21:23,827 --> 00:21:25,517
They meet
these folk's needs...

314
00:21:25,554 --> 00:21:28,815
offered at fair markup,
and we're announcing their availability.

315
00:21:28,850 --> 00:21:31,271
Brought through Indian country
figures into the markup.

316
00:21:31,314 --> 00:21:33,866
By us,
at personal peril.

317
00:21:36,082 --> 00:21:37,740
Let's go.

318
00:21:37,778 --> 00:21:40,527
Coming out with your fly down
might strike the wrong note.

319
00:22:04,562 --> 00:22:06,220
Come have a look, boys.

320
00:22:06,258 --> 00:22:08,429
Star & Bullock
Hardware and Mercantile

321
00:22:08,466 --> 00:22:10,571
just opened for business.

322
00:22:10,610 --> 00:22:12,104
We got boots
to sell you.

323
00:22:16,562 --> 00:22:19,595
Knee-boots, $10!
Hip-boots, 15!

324
00:22:19,634 --> 00:22:21,739
We got picks,
pans and shovels.

325
00:22:21,778 --> 00:22:25,454
Picks at $12,
shovels at 10, and pans at 8!

326
00:22:25,490 --> 00:22:28,457
We got plaster cradles,
prospector's best friend.

327
00:22:28,498 --> 00:22:30,385
Perfected at
the Montana strikes!

328
00:22:30,418 --> 00:22:31,912
We got chamber-pots
to sell you.

329
00:22:31,954 --> 00:22:33,612
If you don't know
what one of those is,

330
00:22:33,650 --> 00:22:36,170
the man living next to you
will appreciate your finding out.

331
00:22:36,210 --> 00:22:39,057
I'll look at your
biggest size hip-boot.

332
00:22:39,090 --> 00:22:41,937
- Got 'em right here.
- We stand by our stock.

333
00:22:41,970 --> 00:22:44,042
Any item that don't do
what it's supposed to

334
00:22:44,082 --> 00:22:45,805
will be exchanged
for one that does.

335
00:22:45,841 --> 00:22:47,531
And we'll be here
for you to find us.

336
00:22:47,570 --> 00:22:49,675
Son of a bitch!

337
00:22:49,714 --> 00:22:52,080
The man said I might
get a prize.

338
00:22:52,113 --> 00:22:54,665
I paid 50¢
for this bar of soap,

339
00:22:54,706 --> 00:22:58,502
there's a $5 prize
in the wrapper.

340
00:22:58,546 --> 00:23:01,677
- Where'd you buy that soap at?
- Man standing right over there.

341
00:23:01,713 --> 00:23:05,324
Front your game
away from our tent.

342
00:23:09,745 --> 00:23:12,494
Cash prizes,
every night's case of soap.

343
00:23:12,529 --> 00:23:14,023
Hey, storekeep!

344
00:23:14,066 --> 00:23:16,716
Hold me some of those
large hip-boots till I get over there

345
00:23:16,754 --> 00:23:20,102
- and I'll pay you $2 extra.
- Set prices, boys,

346
00:23:20,145 --> 00:23:22,250
and first come,
first to be served.

347
00:23:23,506 --> 00:23:25,164
We'll get you
squared away.

348
00:23:39,665 --> 00:23:42,217
No free feels
in this house.

349
00:23:42,258 --> 00:23:45,127
Brom Garret
of Manhattan,

350
00:23:45,169 --> 00:23:47,372
scourge of the Deadwood
faro tables.

351
00:23:47,409 --> 00:23:49,351
Don't think I
confuse two nights

352
00:23:49,394 --> 00:23:51,216
holding good cards
with being a faro shark.

353
00:23:51,249 --> 00:23:52,525
Two here, Dan.

354
00:23:53,521 --> 00:23:55,692
You... you see
a finish to that?

355
00:24:00,593 --> 00:24:02,502
Did you hear
Bill Hickok's in town?

356
00:24:02,545 --> 00:24:06,221
Oh yes, I did.
Does that give you the vapors?

357
00:24:08,081 --> 00:24:10,055
Are you mad
about something, Al?

358
00:24:10,097 --> 00:24:11,558
I'm not mad
about nothing.

359
00:24:13,042 --> 00:24:15,758
All's I can tell you, things sort out
fast in Deadwood.

360
00:24:15,793 --> 00:24:18,891
I vouched for you with Tim Driscoll
two hours in here last night

361
00:24:18,929 --> 00:24:21,416
when I gather you must have
been home in bed, sleeping.

362
00:24:21,457 --> 00:24:24,653
End result, Tim's just
about got his claim sold to E.B. Farnum.

363
00:24:24,689 --> 00:24:27,950
What? Where's
Driscoll now?

364
00:24:27,985 --> 00:24:30,603
He ain't here
so I'd assume at his hotel.

365
00:24:30,641 --> 00:24:33,390
- You told me he's here by 6:00.
- He ain't yet.

366
00:24:33,425 --> 00:24:36,458
Al, E.B. Farnum just saw me here
and headed for the door.

367
00:24:36,497 --> 00:24:38,831
I wouldn't know how
to interpret that.

368
00:24:40,049 --> 00:24:41,936
I was doing
the legwork, Al.

369
00:24:41,969 --> 00:24:43,529
I was doing
the due diligence.

370
00:24:43,569 --> 00:24:45,576
You tell me Driscoll's
got money troubles,

371
00:24:45,617 --> 00:24:47,504
and he's a motivated
seller, fair enough.

372
00:24:47,537 --> 00:24:49,391
But how did I know his
claim's not played out?

373
00:24:49,424 --> 00:24:51,366
- I had to do the legwork.
- I see, fair enough.

374
00:24:51,409 --> 00:24:54,343
- Oh that's what I had to ascertain.
- Did you do the legwork?

375
00:24:56,017 --> 00:24:57,577
Al.

376
00:25:01,937 --> 00:25:03,463
For God's sake,
close your fist.

377
00:25:03,505 --> 00:25:06,800
Cleaned up during the night
with five more just like it

378
00:25:06,833 --> 00:25:09,102
from Claim No. 9
above Discovery,

379
00:25:09,136 --> 00:25:10,696
panned
at the Driscoll claim.

380
00:25:12,272 --> 00:25:15,305
All I can say, Brom,
while you were out winning the battle

381
00:25:15,344 --> 00:25:17,383
I hope you didn't lose
the fucking war.

382
00:25:20,369 --> 00:25:21,481
Al.

383
00:25:26,353 --> 00:25:28,141
Who is that?

384
00:25:30,833 --> 00:25:32,938
Tim Driscoll...

385
00:25:32,976 --> 00:25:34,699
shit-faced.

386
00:25:34,737 --> 00:25:36,842
Let me handle
the play.

387
00:25:36,880 --> 00:25:39,214
Oh my God,
he is shit-faced.

388
00:26:04,912 --> 00:26:07,726
- Boys?
- Whiskeys.

389
00:26:07,760 --> 00:26:09,254
Two whiskeys.

390
00:26:11,376 --> 00:26:13,831
I'm... I'm respecting
your privacy

391
00:26:13,872 --> 00:26:16,621
not saying your name,
but I certainly recognize you

392
00:26:16,656 --> 00:26:18,761
and I'd like
to buy the round.

393
00:26:18,801 --> 00:26:22,445
- Charlie Utter.
- Tom Nuttall, Charlie.

394
00:26:22,480 --> 00:26:23,941
Tom.

395
00:26:23,984 --> 00:26:26,853
It's Bill Hickok.
I seen him kill Phil Coe in Abilene.

396
00:26:26,896 --> 00:26:30,191
Ahem, A.W. Merrick,
Mr. Hickok,

397
00:26:30,224 --> 00:26:32,362
of the...
"Deadwood Pioneer."

398
00:26:34,864 --> 00:26:36,969
- We're drinking whiskey.
- Certainly.

399
00:26:37,008 --> 00:26:39,822
Certainly.
Whiskeys here, Mr. Nuttall.

400
00:26:39,856 --> 00:26:42,605
I'm gonna say one thing
before anybody opens their mouth,

401
00:26:42,640 --> 00:26:44,462
and I won't say
no more on the subject,

402
00:26:44,496 --> 00:26:46,634
and I'll be through
for the fucking evening...

403
00:26:47,792 --> 00:26:49,701
I'm not impressed.

404
00:26:49,744 --> 00:26:54,086
So what brings you
to our camp, Mr. Hickok?

405
00:26:54,127 --> 00:26:55,468
May I tell my readers?

406
00:26:55,504 --> 00:26:57,740
Warrant out on me
in Cheyenne.

407
00:26:57,776 --> 00:26:59,815
Aw, get off
of that now, Bill.

408
00:26:59,856 --> 00:27:01,579
Well, I suppose
for a man like you,

409
00:27:01,616 --> 00:27:03,470
warrants are
a vocational hazard.

410
00:27:03,504 --> 00:27:05,870
Calling me
a professional vagrant.

411
00:27:05,903 --> 00:27:09,099
- The warrant was for vagrancy?
- He's kidding!

412
00:27:16,111 --> 00:27:18,477
Anyway, in this camp,
warrants don't count.

413
00:27:18,512 --> 00:27:22,090
I'm telling you he's
not impressed, all right?

414
00:27:22,127 --> 00:27:26,250
Now you may apply that
to whoever you feel may be my reference.

415
00:27:26,288 --> 00:27:29,735
And I intend to gut that son of a bitch
at poker whenever I get the chance.

416
00:27:29,776 --> 00:27:32,939
You run that game?
Can I buy 50 in chips?

417
00:27:32,975 --> 00:27:34,730
I do and you can.

418
00:27:34,767 --> 00:27:36,905
Just settle up
after you see how your luck runs.

419
00:27:36,944 --> 00:27:39,846
Feel like playing now, Bill, or you
wanna take in the rest of the camp?

420
00:27:39,888 --> 00:27:41,448
I feel like
playing now.

421
00:27:41,487 --> 00:27:43,526
Draw and five stud.

422
00:27:43,568 --> 00:27:46,415
Dealer calls the game.

423
00:27:46,448 --> 00:27:49,230
Sounds fair.
See you later, Charlie.

424
00:27:49,263 --> 00:27:51,434
All right, Bill.

425
00:27:54,736 --> 00:27:57,867
- You boys mind if I sit in?
- Not at all, have a seat.

426
00:27:58,959 --> 00:28:00,747
What a grand surprise.

427
00:28:00,783 --> 00:28:03,335
I never thought he'd live
long enough for me to meet him.

428
00:28:17,584 --> 00:28:19,406
I need another gun.

429
00:28:21,647 --> 00:28:24,614
What, in case
they beat on you?

430
00:28:24,655 --> 00:28:29,095
Never mind what for,
just take this and get me another gun.

431
00:28:29,135 --> 00:28:32,168
Go on, you can touch
my nipples if you want to.

432
00:28:32,207 --> 00:28:35,076
Now Mabel! Mabel!
Get your ass across that table!

433
00:28:35,119 --> 00:28:37,061
This dollar
is not for drink.

434
00:28:37,103 --> 00:28:40,485
- My name's Caroline.
- Well, you'll always be Mabel to me.

435
00:28:40,527 --> 00:28:44,105
Claim No. 9 above Discovery,
$14,000, yes or no?

436
00:28:44,143 --> 00:28:47,176
$14,000,
yes or no?

437
00:28:47,215 --> 00:28:50,727
All right, we'll
make it 14,000.

438
00:28:50,767 --> 00:28:52,141
Spit in your hand.

439
00:28:53,711 --> 00:28:55,685
Spit in your hand.

440
00:28:55,727 --> 00:28:59,174
- What's his fucking problem?
- Aw, nothing.

441
00:28:59,215 --> 00:29:01,124
Done, witnessed.

442
00:29:02,543 --> 00:29:04,430
- Am I too late?
- Mm.

443
00:29:04,463 --> 00:29:07,048
No, no, no, but you're
too late Farnum.

444
00:29:07,087 --> 00:29:10,348
I just sold to this goose-looking
fella for 14,000.

445
00:29:10,383 --> 00:29:13,350
- Will you take 16?
- No, thank you, but no.

446
00:29:13,391 --> 00:29:16,739
What a fucking
lying cunt you are.

447
00:29:16,783 --> 00:29:18,408
"12 and a half
thousand...

448
00:29:18,447 --> 00:29:20,835
that's every cent
I can get hold of, Mr. Driscoll.

449
00:29:20,879 --> 00:29:22,984
And more than
the claim is worth" you said.

450
00:29:23,022 --> 00:29:26,317
16,000, that's 2,000 profit,
standing over a drink.

451
00:29:26,351 --> 00:29:29,133
I believe events will prove
that Claim No. 9 above Discovery

452
00:29:29,167 --> 00:29:31,654
was worth far more
than 16,000, Mr. Farnum.

453
00:29:31,695 --> 00:29:33,156
Unhand me, Al.

454
00:29:34,927 --> 00:29:38,025
Though, you know, of course,
I haven't actually seen

455
00:29:38,063 --> 00:29:41,859
- his fucking money yet.
- I'm discounting his banknote. Dan.

456
00:29:42,959 --> 00:29:44,136
There's $10,000.

457
00:29:44,175 --> 00:29:46,346
I'll weigh four
out of the other sack right now.

458
00:29:46,382 --> 00:29:48,324
Al's holding
a full faith letter of credit

459
00:29:48,367 --> 00:29:50,057
for $20,000 from
the Bank of New York.

460
00:29:50,095 --> 00:29:52,069
Full faith is one thing,
but until the money

461
00:29:52,111 --> 00:29:55,144
has actually passed hands between us,
the deal isn't done.

462
00:29:55,182 --> 00:29:56,970
- The deal is done.
- The deal isn't done.

463
00:29:57,006 --> 00:29:58,794
- The deal is done.
- We spat in our hands.

464
00:29:58,831 --> 00:30:00,456
What the fuck
would you know?!

465
00:30:00,495 --> 00:30:02,916
I'll knock you into
the middle of next week.

466
00:30:02,958 --> 00:30:05,892
Now, would you offer me
the 16,000?

467
00:30:05,934 --> 00:30:08,072
I suppose, if you're open
to further offers.

468
00:30:08,110 --> 00:30:09,157
16,500.

469
00:30:09,199 --> 00:30:11,686
- What the fuck did you just do?
- Will you close at 16.5?

470
00:30:11,727 --> 00:30:14,093
- You just reopened the fucking bidding.
- 17,000.

471
00:30:14,126 --> 00:30:16,198
17,500,
I'll go no farther.

472
00:30:16,238 --> 00:30:17,699
- 18!
- 19!

473
00:30:17,742 --> 00:30:21,516
19,800 and that's every cent
I can put together.

474
00:30:21,550 --> 00:30:22,891
20,000.

475
00:30:22,926 --> 00:30:24,900
Damn it!
Damn it!

476
00:30:24,942 --> 00:30:27,243
20 once.

477
00:30:27,278 --> 00:30:28,838
- 20 twice.
- I can't.

478
00:30:28,878 --> 00:30:30,470
It's over,
he's through.

479
00:30:31,598 --> 00:30:34,500
- Is it over?
- All right.

480
00:30:34,542 --> 00:30:38,404
20,000 sold to the goose-looking man
in the shiny suit.

481
00:30:38,446 --> 00:30:40,617
- I got it, Al.
- Yes, you did.

482
00:30:51,118 --> 00:30:53,092
Comes to look for
a business opportunity,

483
00:30:53,134 --> 00:30:54,628
and sits there
losing at poker.

484
00:30:54,670 --> 00:30:57,452
Is he having a bad run?
I can't see that far.

485
00:30:57,486 --> 00:30:59,428
You'd have to see
back to Cheyenne.

486
00:30:59,470 --> 00:31:01,379
He lost his patience,

487
00:31:01,422 --> 00:31:03,843
stays in hands whether
he's holding cards or not.

488
00:31:05,678 --> 00:31:07,685
How's your crowd in here
tonight, anyway?

489
00:31:09,166 --> 00:31:10,791
Oh, it's all right.

490
00:31:10,830 --> 00:31:13,350
It's better than all right,
you could see that much.

491
00:31:13,390 --> 00:31:16,586
Bill Hickok's an asset to any saloon,
any joint he frequents.

492
00:31:16,622 --> 00:31:20,266
- You agree with me on that or not?
- You got a say in that?

493
00:31:20,301 --> 00:31:23,846
- As far as where he drinks and gambles?
- Suppose I did?

494
00:31:26,830 --> 00:31:29,382
50 a night if he'll
frequent here exclusive.

495
00:31:29,422 --> 00:31:32,007
50?

496
00:31:32,046 --> 00:31:34,118
What a sport
you turned out to be.

497
00:31:35,917 --> 00:31:38,633
- You quote a figure.
- Let's come to one understanding.

498
00:31:38,670 --> 00:31:41,572
Any figure I would've come up with,
part of that you give to him

499
00:31:41,613 --> 00:31:44,068
to gamble or piss away
however else he's gonna do it.

500
00:31:44,109 --> 00:31:46,345
That'd be the only part
he'd know about.

501
00:31:46,381 --> 00:31:47,755
I'd work with you.

502
00:31:47,789 --> 00:31:51,236
The rest you'd give to me
to hold in trust for his future.

503
00:31:52,749 --> 00:31:55,748
- Now that'd be your affair.
- Listen to me,

504
00:31:55,789 --> 00:31:58,155
that man's
recently married.

505
00:31:58,189 --> 00:32:00,098
He needs to put
a stake together.

506
00:32:00,142 --> 00:32:02,345
That's all
I'd be in this for.

507
00:32:03,725 --> 00:32:06,113
I'd work with you.

508
00:32:20,141 --> 00:32:21,569
Banish all headaches.

509
00:32:21,613 --> 00:32:24,198
Spit in your hand,
Alma!

510
00:32:24,237 --> 00:32:26,146
- What?
- Spit.

511
00:32:26,189 --> 00:32:27,977
I'm gonna
show you something.

512
00:32:29,677 --> 00:32:32,327
Promise you'll tell
my mother about this.

513
00:32:32,365 --> 00:32:34,568
I bought it.

514
00:32:34,605 --> 00:32:37,507
We own a gold claim.
This is how we sealed the deal.

515
00:32:37,549 --> 00:32:39,588
And then did everyone
dry their hands?

516
00:32:39,629 --> 00:32:42,017
Do you know who
I was bidding against?

517
00:32:42,061 --> 00:32:44,963
Farnum, who owns
this hotel.

518
00:32:45,005 --> 00:32:47,557
Oh and where was
your secret agent?

519
00:32:47,597 --> 00:32:50,346
Dan Dority?
He was tending bar.

520
00:32:50,381 --> 00:32:54,341
No one realized how Dan had helped me
wreck and order the claim.

521
00:32:54,381 --> 00:32:56,999
Now Swearengen...
runs the saloon...

522
00:32:57,037 --> 00:33:00,681
he was intermediary,
he brokered the deal.

523
00:33:00,717 --> 00:33:03,237
Driscoll, the seller,
legless with liquor.

524
00:33:03,277 --> 00:33:05,284
You will have a vivid
entry for an article

525
00:33:05,325 --> 00:33:06,983
and I've told you
all the details.

526
00:33:07,021 --> 00:33:09,387
Yes, I've already
begun to imagine it.

527
00:33:10,349 --> 00:33:12,770
It was a near thing
till the end.

528
00:33:12,812 --> 00:33:15,626
I had to go all our 20,000
to turn Farnum away.

529
00:33:15,661 --> 00:33:18,049
Oh well.

530
00:33:18,093 --> 00:33:20,427
I'll have to write the bank
to renew my credit.

531
00:33:21,485 --> 00:33:24,070
Of course
they'll contact Father.

532
00:33:25,261 --> 00:33:27,235
Well...

533
00:33:28,332 --> 00:33:30,306
I expect
that's inevitable.

534
00:33:32,620 --> 00:33:35,489
Wild Bill Hickok
is here.

535
00:33:35,533 --> 00:33:38,696
I'm sure he's going
to prospect too.

536
00:34:07,885 --> 00:34:10,983
- How much do you want?
- Well, we agreed on 30%.

537
00:34:11,020 --> 00:34:13,125
- 30% of 20 would be six.
- Mm-hmm.

538
00:34:13,164 --> 00:34:14,473
So I want
the 6,000.

539
00:34:14,508 --> 00:34:16,679
What's 30% of 14,000?

540
00:34:18,220 --> 00:34:21,449
- What the fuck, Al?
- Who told you to take him to 20?

541
00:34:23,980 --> 00:34:25,987
Well, I could feel that
he had more in him.

542
00:34:26,028 --> 00:34:28,100
It was just a spontaneous
fucking feeling

543
00:34:28,141 --> 00:34:29,896
and I knew that
there was more to get.

544
00:34:29,932 --> 00:34:33,706
And you thought six more would be
the jackpot, take him from 14 to 20.

545
00:34:33,740 --> 00:34:36,358
Oh Jesus Christ, you know,
if you had further plans,

546
00:34:36,396 --> 00:34:38,567
I wish you'd have just
said something to me.

547
00:34:38,605 --> 00:34:41,026
Should I tell you
when I plan to take a shit tomorrow

548
00:34:41,068 --> 00:34:43,206
or would that be none
of your fucking business?

549
00:34:49,676 --> 00:34:52,709
So... 14,000.

550
00:34:52,748 --> 00:34:56,293
30% of that's what...
what is that now... 4,200.

551
00:35:00,236 --> 00:35:02,788
What the fuck arrangement
do you suggest now?

552
00:35:02,828 --> 00:35:05,511
- What do you suggest?
- Oh Jesus Christ Almighty!

553
00:35:05,548 --> 00:35:09,257
You get in a mood like this and I just
as soon as not even discuss it.

554
00:35:09,292 --> 00:35:11,593
Look, let me just
have 500, you know,

555
00:35:11,628 --> 00:35:14,213
and we'll discuss the rest of it
some other fucking time.

556
00:35:14,252 --> 00:35:17,154
Cash or credit
at the tables?

557
00:35:17,196 --> 00:35:20,938
Fucking time of trial, the fucking
English in you comes out. Fine.

558
00:35:20,972 --> 00:35:24,354
I'll have the 500 at the fucking tables
then. Jesus Christ Almighty!

559
00:35:24,396 --> 00:35:27,712
- Are we holding markers?
- You're holding markers, all right.

560
00:35:27,756 --> 00:35:31,171
You've been holding markers against
my kind for the past several centuries,

561
00:35:31,211 --> 00:35:34,058
across both sides of the fucking water!
How the fuck do I know?!

562
00:35:34,091 --> 00:35:36,360
Ask Dority,
he'll know better than me.

563
00:35:38,091 --> 00:35:40,774
Credit it against
the fucking markers,

564
00:35:40,811 --> 00:35:44,007
but just let me hold 20,
in fucking cash.

565
00:35:46,156 --> 00:35:49,123
- Tell Dan to give you 20.
- And a piece of fucking pussy.

566
00:35:49,164 --> 00:35:51,530
Tell Dan, then tell him
to come see me.

567
00:35:54,124 --> 00:35:57,190
And thanks for stepping in on the side
of right and fucking justice,

568
00:35:57,227 --> 00:35:59,266
you deaf dumb bastard!

569
00:36:03,851 --> 00:36:06,917
I tell you, Al, you could
have knocked me over with a feather

570
00:36:06,956 --> 00:36:08,166
when he took him to 20.

571
00:36:08,203 --> 00:36:10,374
Did you see me struggling
to stay on the path?

572
00:36:12,972 --> 00:36:16,070
My wife and children
are in Louisville, Kentucky.

573
00:36:16,108 --> 00:36:18,442
I'm saving
to bring them out.

574
00:36:18,475 --> 00:36:21,257
Days I dig on
the Foster's water ditch

575
00:36:21,291 --> 00:36:25,185
and nights I watch folk's goods
like I'm going to do for yours.

576
00:36:25,227 --> 00:36:28,293
Schedule like that seems like you'll
have 'em here in no time.

577
00:36:29,931 --> 00:36:33,542
Then sabbaths I preach Christ crucified
and raised from the dead.

578
00:36:37,355 --> 00:36:39,329
I'm from Etobicoke,
Ontario.

579
00:36:39,371 --> 00:36:43,746
- So you were born in Canada?
- I come to Montana when I was 17.

580
00:36:43,787 --> 00:36:47,048
- That's when I met up with Mr. Star.
- Is that so?

581
00:36:47,083 --> 00:36:49,122
I was born in Austria.

582
00:36:49,164 --> 00:36:53,222
Austria? Wonderful
where people come from.

583
00:36:53,259 --> 00:36:56,935
I was born in Austria and then
I grew up in Chillicothe, Ohio.

584
00:36:56,971 --> 00:37:00,037
And then you partnered
with Mr. Bullock in Montana?

585
00:37:00,075 --> 00:37:02,627
That's where
we partnered up.

586
00:37:02,667 --> 00:37:05,001
The Lord is
our final comfort,

587
00:37:05,035 --> 00:37:08,613
but it's a solace
having friends.

588
00:37:08,651 --> 00:37:11,782
I know that
from past experience.

589
00:37:14,730 --> 00:37:17,118
You sure sold up a storm
here tonight, didn't you?

590
00:37:17,163 --> 00:37:19,977
- We did all right.
- We'll be a few hours, Mr. Smith.

591
00:37:20,011 --> 00:37:21,669
We want to look
around the camp.

592
00:37:21,706 --> 00:37:24,324
I will watch your goods
as if they were my own.

593
00:37:27,722 --> 00:37:29,958
- Thank you, Mr. Smith.
- Thank you.

594
00:37:33,099 --> 00:37:35,106
Whoa.

595
00:37:40,011 --> 00:37:42,149
I seen a terrible
thing tonight.

596
00:37:42,187 --> 00:37:43,779
What'd you see?

597
00:37:43,819 --> 00:37:46,950
I seen white people
dead and scalped and...

598
00:37:46,987 --> 00:37:49,921
men, women, and children
with their arms and legs hacked off.

599
00:37:49,962 --> 00:37:52,100
Where? How many dead?

600
00:37:52,138 --> 00:37:54,985
Well, it was a whole family
on the road to Spearfish.

601
00:37:55,018 --> 00:37:58,596
Oh my God, it's them heathen
bloodthirsty savages!

602
00:37:58,635 --> 00:38:02,791
- How many was it died?
- It was the whole family, they was...

603
00:38:02,827 --> 00:38:04,615
hacked and mutilated.

604
00:38:04,650 --> 00:38:06,308
The parents,
two children.

605
00:38:06,347 --> 00:38:09,030
The Metz family
took the Spearfish road

606
00:38:09,066 --> 00:38:11,269
going home to Minnesota.

607
00:38:12,938 --> 00:38:14,945
Then that was
probably them then.

608
00:38:14,986 --> 00:38:18,848
They had three children.
Were there three?

609
00:38:20,010 --> 00:38:21,832
There could've
been three 'cause...

610
00:38:21,867 --> 00:38:24,801
they was all hacked...
and spread around.

611
00:38:25,770 --> 00:38:27,493
Rest their souls.

612
00:38:29,003 --> 00:38:31,905
- Rest their souls.
- Yeah.

613
00:38:36,010 --> 00:38:37,700
You probably
need a drink.

614
00:38:45,354 --> 00:38:47,044
You called my bluff, Hickok.

615
00:38:47,082 --> 00:38:49,602
I was trying
to run one. Whoa!

616
00:38:49,642 --> 00:38:53,733
Wait on Mary.
I got a third eight under there.

617
00:38:54,923 --> 00:38:56,810
Three eights wins,
your pot.

618
00:38:56,843 --> 00:39:00,421
- Oh I absolutely did not realize that.
- Your chips.

619
00:39:00,458 --> 00:39:03,360
Here I am thinking I'm fucking
bluffing the third eight,

620
00:39:03,402 --> 00:39:06,663
and I mistakenly outdraw
the greatest gunfighter in the world.

621
00:39:08,618 --> 00:39:09,861
Meaning the third eight.

622
00:39:11,690 --> 00:39:14,886
- What?
- Saying you outdrew me.

623
00:39:14,922 --> 00:39:16,645
You meant
the third eight.

624
00:39:18,410 --> 00:39:20,100
Well, what else
would I have meant?

625
00:39:20,137 --> 00:39:22,144
Say it.

626
00:39:22,186 --> 00:39:24,902
Then we'll play cards.

627
00:39:26,538 --> 00:39:28,993
Third eight's
what I meant.

628
00:39:31,242 --> 00:39:33,511
- Deal.
- Ante's up, same again.

629
00:39:40,746 --> 00:39:44,422
Jesus Christ, can we
shake hands or something?

630
00:39:44,458 --> 00:39:46,530
Relieve the atmosphere?

631
00:39:47,850 --> 00:39:49,759
I mean, how stupid
do you think I am?

632
00:39:49,801 --> 00:39:53,543
I don't know.
I just met you.

633
00:39:53,578 --> 00:39:56,577
The paradox is the massacre
at Little Big Horn

634
00:39:56,617 --> 00:39:58,788
signaled the Indians'
death throes, Mr. Utter.

635
00:39:58,826 --> 00:40:01,695
History has overtaken the treaty
which gave them this land.

636
00:40:01,737 --> 00:40:04,584
Well, the gold we found
has overtaken it.

637
00:40:04,617 --> 00:40:06,242
I believe within a year

638
00:40:06,281 --> 00:40:08,550
Congress will rescind
the Fort Laramie Treaty,

639
00:40:08,586 --> 00:40:10,473
Deadwood and these hills
will be annexed

640
00:40:10,506 --> 00:40:13,767
to the Dakota Territory,
and we who have pursued our destiny

641
00:40:13,801 --> 00:40:15,491
outside law or statute

642
00:40:15,529 --> 00:40:18,049
will be restored
to the bosom of the nation.

643
00:40:18,089 --> 00:40:21,122
And... that's
what I believe.

644
00:40:29,385 --> 00:40:32,832
- Does bosom mean tit?
- Same thing.

645
00:40:34,089 --> 00:40:36,031
Ain't nothing
against y'all fellas,

646
00:40:36,074 --> 00:40:38,659
but I'd as soon do my drinking
and getting a piece of ass.

647
00:40:38,698 --> 00:40:40,869
First you want people
to know about that family.

648
00:40:40,905 --> 00:40:43,938
Yeah, well, what harm is it
in me meeting my needs

649
00:40:43,977 --> 00:40:45,919
before I circulate
the news?

650
00:40:45,961 --> 00:40:48,295
What if the third
child is alive?

651
00:40:48,329 --> 00:40:51,111
You listen, mister,
it was a massacre.

652
00:40:51,145 --> 00:40:53,927
I'm the one who saw it.
And there ain't no one was alive.

653
00:40:53,962 --> 00:40:56,383
Did you see
the massacre or not?

654
00:40:56,425 --> 00:40:58,334
I told you I got there
afterwards.

655
00:40:58,377 --> 00:41:00,100
So by then, the child
could've got away

656
00:41:00,137 --> 00:41:01,860
from where you saw
those other bodies?

657
00:41:01,897 --> 00:41:03,620
Or the child
could've been hiding

658
00:41:03,657 --> 00:41:06,177
and so afraid of
who you might be, it didn't call out.

659
00:41:06,217 --> 00:41:09,151
You listen to me, I ain't going back
out there again tonight,

660
00:41:09,193 --> 00:41:11,298
so you mind your own
goddamn business!

661
00:41:11,337 --> 00:41:13,725
You're saying a family
is massacred by Indians

662
00:41:13,769 --> 00:41:16,551
on the road to Spearfish
and one child may still be alive

663
00:41:16,585 --> 00:41:19,367
- and it's no one's concern...
- What's this about a massacre?

664
00:41:19,401 --> 00:41:21,288
Oh, for Christ's sake!
God damn it!

665
00:41:21,321 --> 00:41:23,230
I ain't going out there
again tonight

666
00:41:23,273 --> 00:41:27,015
after I just made camp with my scalp
by sheer dumb fucking luck!

667
00:41:28,745 --> 00:41:30,654
Ride out and show us
the place.

668
00:41:39,273 --> 00:41:41,280
I'll guarantee
your scalp.

669
00:41:45,577 --> 00:41:47,998
- You riding?
- Yeah.

670
00:41:49,033 --> 00:41:51,007
- We'll ride.
- May I ride?

671
00:41:51,049 --> 00:41:53,536
I'd be honored to ride,
infirmities permitting.

672
00:41:54,760 --> 00:41:56,134
Here we go.

673
00:42:07,528 --> 00:42:10,495
Wild Bill
fucking Hickok.

674
00:42:11,657 --> 00:42:13,479
You were a marshal
in Kansas?

675
00:42:13,512 --> 00:42:15,334
Yeah.

676
00:42:15,368 --> 00:42:17,888
- And you?
- Montana.

677
00:42:17,929 --> 00:42:21,540
- Come to your senses now?
- Yes, sir.

678
00:42:23,144 --> 00:42:25,794
The fella's story on this
don't hold water.

679
00:42:25,832 --> 00:42:28,166
No, it don't.

680
00:42:33,576 --> 00:42:36,390
- What'd you give Driscoll?
- 20 bucks.

681
00:42:36,425 --> 00:42:38,050
Free poke with Wanda.

682
00:42:38,089 --> 00:42:41,088
- Half-smart mick that he is.
- Yeah.

683
00:42:41,128 --> 00:42:43,233
Tim really fucked up
with the dude, huh?

684
00:42:43,272 --> 00:42:45,955
I guess the dude's case money.
Dude only out here three days.

685
00:42:45,992 --> 00:42:48,163
How's the dude ask
his people back home for more?

686
00:42:48,201 --> 00:42:51,168
- They're liable to send the Pinkertons.
- So shut the dude down?

687
00:42:51,208 --> 00:42:53,030
You being
his secret best friend,

688
00:42:53,064 --> 00:42:55,714
he'll want you out prospecting
in the morning beside him.

689
00:42:55,752 --> 00:42:57,278
That claim needs
to pinch out.

690
00:42:57,320 --> 00:42:59,775
Oughtn't take but a couple days,
he ain't got much sand.

691
00:42:59,816 --> 00:43:02,052
Tim Driscoll
needs to be seen to.

692
00:43:03,528 --> 00:43:05,120
- No kidding now?
- No kidding.

693
00:43:06,760 --> 00:43:08,582
Well, not that
anybody asked,

694
00:43:08,616 --> 00:43:11,266
but I'd look to Trixie
for danger before I'd look to Tim.

695
00:43:11,304 --> 00:43:13,059
No kidding!

696
00:43:14,600 --> 00:43:17,895
Jimmy says the Sioux massacred a family
on the Spearfish road.

697
00:43:17,928 --> 00:43:19,815
A hand come into
Nuttall's No. 10

698
00:43:19,848 --> 00:43:22,303
- telling the story, Mr. Swearengen.
- Who was he?

699
00:43:22,344 --> 00:43:24,067
- I never seen him before.
- Can you get him over here?

700
00:43:24,104 --> 00:43:25,762
Is he still at Nuttall's?

701
00:43:25,800 --> 00:43:27,971
They're riding back out
to where it happened.

702
00:43:28,008 --> 00:43:30,080
Hickok and some others
were riding with him.

703
00:43:30,120 --> 00:43:32,869
Did the hand look happy
to be riding back out with Hickok?

704
00:43:32,904 --> 00:43:34,758
He didn't look
too happy.

705
00:43:34,791 --> 00:43:38,303
How many people downstairs
did you tell about this?

706
00:43:39,687 --> 00:43:41,574
- A few.
- A few?

707
00:43:43,208 --> 00:43:46,655
You let him tell a few people downstairs
before you bring this to me?

708
00:43:46,696 --> 00:43:48,451
Al, I brought him
as soon as I heard!

709
00:43:48,487 --> 00:43:51,967
How many people do you think the people
he talked to have talked to by now?

710
00:43:52,008 --> 00:43:56,099
I guarantee at this minute my entire
fucking action downstairs is fucked up!

711
00:43:56,136 --> 00:43:59,397
Nobody's drinking, nobody's gambling,
nobody's chasing tail.

712
00:43:59,432 --> 00:44:01,603
I have to deal
with that!

713
00:44:05,288 --> 00:44:07,426
You want $10
or a bottle of dope?

714
00:44:07,464 --> 00:44:10,180
Bottle of dope please,
Mr. Swearengen.

715
00:44:10,215 --> 00:44:13,444
- Give him a bottle of dope.
- Come on, I'll take care of you.

716
00:44:17,031 --> 00:44:18,940
He's got a lot
on his mind, Johnny.

717
00:44:37,224 --> 00:44:39,776
Quiet! Al's got words!

718
00:44:43,592 --> 00:44:45,828
I guess when it starts
pissing rain in here,

719
00:44:45,864 --> 00:44:48,252
you know
who to blame, huh?

720
00:44:48,296 --> 00:44:50,434
I know word's circulating,

721
00:44:50,472 --> 00:44:53,090
Indians killed a family
on the Spearfish road.

722
00:44:53,127 --> 00:44:56,258
Now it's not for me to tell anyone
in this camp what to do,

723
00:44:56,295 --> 00:44:59,393
much as I don't want more people
getting their throats cut,

724
00:44:59,431 --> 00:45:02,245
their scalps lifted,
or any other godless thing

725
00:45:02,279 --> 00:45:05,278
that these godless
bloodthirsty heathens do...

726
00:45:05,319 --> 00:45:08,002
or even if someone wants
to ride out in darkest night,

727
00:45:08,039 --> 00:45:10,755
but I will
tell you this:

728
00:45:10,791 --> 00:45:13,758
I'd use tonight
to get myself organized,

729
00:45:13,799 --> 00:45:17,541
ride out in the morning,
clear-headed,

730
00:45:17,575 --> 00:45:19,746
and starting
tomorrow morning,

731
00:45:19,783 --> 00:45:23,044
I will offer
a personal $50 bounty

732
00:45:23,079 --> 00:45:24,988
for every decapitated head

733
00:45:25,031 --> 00:45:28,227
of as many of these
godless heathen cocksuckers

734
00:45:28,263 --> 00:45:31,262
as anyone can bring in,
tomorrow, with no upper limit!

735
00:45:32,295 --> 00:45:33,953
That's all I say
on that subject

736
00:45:33,991 --> 00:45:35,681
except next round's
on the house.

737
00:45:35,719 --> 00:45:39,428
And God rest the souls
of that poor family.

738
00:45:39,463 --> 00:45:40,837
Amen.

739
00:45:42,279 --> 00:45:44,864
And pussy's half-price
next 15 minutes.

740
00:45:53,990 --> 00:45:56,029
Okay, ladies,
let's go.

741
00:45:56,071 --> 00:45:59,845
She must have done some fancy fucking
to keep Al from killing her.

742
00:46:14,214 --> 00:46:16,450
Where's Bill Hickok?

743
00:46:16,486 --> 00:46:18,308
Where's Charlie Utter?

744
00:46:19,366 --> 00:46:20,642
Give me a drink!

745
00:46:24,774 --> 00:46:27,872
It's all right, Al, I know you got a lot
on your mind.

746
00:46:28,999 --> 00:46:30,973
That was one hell
of a good talk.

747
00:46:31,015 --> 00:46:33,535
Look, you got everybody
back at the tables,

748
00:46:33,574 --> 00:46:35,646
- doing what they do.
- Tell you the truth,

749
00:46:35,686 --> 00:46:39,166
for murdering people
on the road to Spearfish

750
00:46:39,206 --> 00:46:42,402
my money'd be on
Persimmon Phil.

751
00:46:42,439 --> 00:46:44,642
Make it look
like Indians.

752
00:46:44,678 --> 00:46:46,565
That is
his speciality.

753
00:46:48,551 --> 00:46:50,939
Is it true?

754
00:46:50,982 --> 00:46:53,021
Indians killing
white people?

755
00:46:53,062 --> 00:46:55,483
That's the sewer mouth
that follows Hickok around.

756
00:46:55,526 --> 00:46:56,802
Why are we
standing here?

757
00:46:56,839 --> 00:46:58,977
Riding out tomorrow,
daybreak.

758
00:46:59,014 --> 00:47:01,348
Oh, really?

759
00:47:01,383 --> 00:47:02,811
Tomorrow?

760
00:47:02,854 --> 00:47:04,861
What's your
fucking rush?!

761
00:47:05,990 --> 00:47:07,418
I'm going now.

762
00:47:08,742 --> 00:47:10,432
Even without Bill.

763
00:47:11,430 --> 00:47:13,055
Even without Charlie.

764
00:47:14,726 --> 00:47:17,311
I know the road
to Spearfish.

765
00:47:17,351 --> 00:47:20,285
And I don't drink where
I'm the only fucking one with balls!

766
00:47:26,726 --> 00:47:28,384
Let her go.

767
00:47:28,422 --> 00:47:30,396
She ain't taking
any business with her.

768
00:47:32,454 --> 00:47:34,363
And don't forget
to kill Tim.

769
00:47:53,318 --> 00:47:55,554
Yah.

770
00:48:17,541 --> 00:48:18,850
Wah! Yah!

771
00:51:07,812 --> 00:51:09,338
Get to your room.

772
00:51:09,380 --> 00:51:11,746
You should be sleeping
on a goddamn pew.

773
00:51:14,821 --> 00:51:16,479
You in love?

774
00:51:31,908 --> 00:51:34,111
Wake up, friend.
Come on now.

775
00:51:34,148 --> 00:51:36,995
You know I don't intrude
on the affairs of others.

776
00:51:38,724 --> 00:51:41,211
Problem enough keeping
my own life straight.

777
00:51:41,252 --> 00:51:45,507
When something's not my affair,
I don't pretend it is.

778
00:51:47,908 --> 00:51:50,329
Contrariwise,

779
00:51:50,372 --> 00:51:53,405
if you feel like talking
about that headlight...

780
00:51:54,980 --> 00:51:56,987
I'll pay a dollar
a minute to hear you.

781
00:51:58,468 --> 00:52:00,889
Get anything off
your chest you feel like.

782
00:52:02,436 --> 00:52:04,857
What I got on my chest

783
00:52:04,899 --> 00:52:06,654
don't concern you,
Ellsworth.

784
00:52:13,732 --> 00:52:17,823
And fuck us all anyway
for the limber-dick cocksuckers we are.

785
00:52:40,612 --> 00:52:43,514
- What is it?
- Just hush, Tim.

786
00:53:13,315 --> 00:53:14,689
Doc! Get up!

787
00:53:15,939 --> 00:53:17,727
Doc!

788
00:53:17,763 --> 00:53:19,191
Doc!

789
00:53:21,859 --> 00:53:24,247
Doc! Wake up!

790
00:53:25,603 --> 00:53:27,129
Doc!

791
00:53:31,396 --> 00:53:32,890
Oh God...

792
00:53:44,515 --> 00:53:47,449
Wait for me,
God damn it!

793
00:53:47,491 --> 00:53:49,116
Just hold on
till I'm with you.

794
00:53:52,579 --> 00:53:55,961
She don't mean nothing, Doc,
she's just excitable.

795
00:54:17,763 --> 00:54:20,762
What kinda hand is
your friend with a gun?

796
00:54:22,499 --> 00:54:24,637
I don't feel
qualified to say.

797
00:54:28,835 --> 00:54:31,617
I guess I done my duty

798
00:54:31,651 --> 00:54:34,072
and I was glad enough
to help.

799
00:54:35,618 --> 00:54:36,959
Stick around,

800
00:54:36,994 --> 00:54:38,237
see if she lives.

801
00:54:38,275 --> 00:54:40,991
Nah, I was...

802
00:54:41,026 --> 00:54:43,873
glad enough to have done my duty
and that little one

803
00:54:43,906 --> 00:54:45,432
will be in my prayers.

804
00:54:46,563 --> 00:54:50,141
- Get down off your horse.
- Listen to me.

805
00:54:50,178 --> 00:54:52,894
I'm an innocent man,
it...

806
00:54:52,931 --> 00:54:54,970
it was them Indians,
God damn it!

807
00:54:55,011 --> 00:54:58,458
Too much ransacking,
and too many goods left behind.

808
00:54:58,499 --> 00:55:00,321
Someone was after money.

809
00:55:00,355 --> 00:55:02,842
God damn it, if I had something
to do with what happened,

810
00:55:02,883 --> 00:55:04,289
why'd I come
to this camp, huh?

811
00:55:04,322 --> 00:55:07,038
Maybe when it got
thick out there you ran.

812
00:55:08,099 --> 00:55:10,008
Maybe the others
was going to ground,

813
00:55:10,050 --> 00:55:12,602
but you had
to have pussy.

814
00:55:12,643 --> 00:55:14,137
And get
to a faro layout.

815
00:55:14,178 --> 00:55:17,244
I felt that way
sometimes after a kill.

816
00:55:17,282 --> 00:55:19,289
Get down off
your horse,

817
00:55:19,330 --> 00:55:21,882
or face
the consequences.

818
00:55:37,762 --> 00:55:39,933
Was that you or me,
Montana?

819
00:55:41,347 --> 00:55:44,096
My money'd
be on you.

820
00:56:59,169 --> 00:57:01,056
Yeah?

