1
00:01:34,864 --> 00:01:38,508
He's down that hole
for a fact.

2
00:01:38,543 --> 00:01:42,252
Pitiful as
you pursued it,

3
00:01:42,287 --> 00:01:44,425
you better hope
he ain't got space enough

4
00:01:44,463 --> 00:01:48,237
to roll around holding his side,
and bust a gut laughing...

5
00:01:50,831 --> 00:01:54,889
tell all the other woodchucks
at the club this afternoon.

6
00:01:55,855 --> 00:01:59,716
He might not even
call it an escape.

7
00:01:59,758 --> 00:02:03,205
Might just call it
his "morning's entertainment."

8
00:02:03,246 --> 00:02:06,988
Hey! Hey, Ellsworth!

9
00:02:07,023 --> 00:02:08,910
Hey, Dan Dority!

10
00:02:10,638 --> 00:02:13,093
Where's
the Great Prospector?

11
00:02:13,134 --> 00:02:15,654
I guess Brom
slept in this morning.

12
00:02:15,694 --> 00:02:19,108
Suppose his enthusiasm's
on the wane?

13
00:02:19,150 --> 00:02:21,004
That's always
possible.

14
00:02:21,037 --> 00:02:24,036
He shows up, you tell him
I quit waitin'.

15
00:02:24,077 --> 00:02:26,727
- Sure will.
- See ya at The Gem.

16
00:02:26,765 --> 00:02:28,674
Always possible.

17
00:02:29,966 --> 00:02:31,907
Go on!

18
00:02:35,628 --> 00:02:38,791
"The earth is the Lord's
and the fullness thereof,

19
00:02:38,829 --> 00:02:41,065
the world, and they
that dwell therein.

20
00:02:41,100 --> 00:02:43,271
For He hath founded it
upon the seas,

21
00:02:43,308 --> 00:02:45,249
and established it
upon the floods.

22
00:02:45,292 --> 00:02:48,074
Who shall ascend
into the hill of the Lord?

23
00:02:48,108 --> 00:02:50,758
Or who shall stand
in His holy place?

24
00:02:50,796 --> 00:02:55,684
He that hath clean hands,
and a pure heart:

25
00:02:55,724 --> 00:02:57,796
Who hath not
lifted up his soul

26
00:02:57,836 --> 00:03:00,618
unto vanity,
nor sworn deceitfully.

27
00:03:00,652 --> 00:03:03,401
He shall receive
the blessing from the Lord,

28
00:03:03,436 --> 00:03:06,883
and justice from the God
of his salvation.

29
00:03:06,923 --> 00:03:09,224
Lift up your heads,
O ye gates

30
00:03:09,260 --> 00:03:11,398
and be ye lifted up
ye everlasting doors,

31
00:03:11,436 --> 00:03:14,250
and the King of Glory
shall come in.

32
00:03:14,283 --> 00:03:16,421
Who is the King
of Glory,

33
00:03:16,459 --> 00:03:19,306
the Lord of Hosts?
He is the King of Glory.

34
00:03:19,339 --> 00:03:21,193
Selah."

35
00:03:21,227 --> 00:03:23,714
Let me see them titties!
What's your name?

36
00:03:23,755 --> 00:03:25,893
What's your name?

37
00:03:53,033 --> 00:03:54,920
Pull that sign a little
to the right.

38
00:03:54,953 --> 00:03:57,091
No, no, no.
That way, that way.

39
00:04:09,737 --> 00:04:13,315
"Everyone proud in heart
is an abomination to the Lord.

40
00:04:13,352 --> 00:04:16,930
Though hand join in hand,
he shall not be unpunished.

41
00:04:16,969 --> 00:04:20,264
By mercy and truth
is inequity purged.

42
00:04:20,296 --> 00:04:23,678
And by the fear of the Lord,
do men depart from evil.

43
00:04:23,720 --> 00:04:25,988
A man's ways
please the Lord

44
00:04:26,023 --> 00:04:29,951
when he maketh even his enemies
to be at peace with him."

45
00:04:33,384 --> 00:04:35,293
Amen.

46
00:04:35,335 --> 00:04:37,538
Amen.

47
00:04:37,576 --> 00:04:41,569
Thank you.
Thanks for your help.

48
00:04:41,607 --> 00:04:43,810
May we edify my readers,
Mr. Bullock?

49
00:04:43,847 --> 00:04:45,788
I don't know
what "edify" means.

50
00:04:45,831 --> 00:04:47,740
Can we talk about
last night's gunfight?

51
00:04:47,783 --> 00:04:48,960
No.

52
00:04:50,439 --> 00:04:53,024
We can't talk about last night's
gunfight either.

53
00:04:57,510 --> 00:05:00,324
- What the fuck?!
- All's I can speculate, Al,

54
00:05:00,358 --> 00:05:02,397
is whoever these
Bella Union people are,

55
00:05:02,439 --> 00:05:04,707
they bought Artie Simpson's place
on the quiet.

56
00:05:04,742 --> 00:05:06,564
Pre-arranged
turnin' it into a joint.

57
00:05:06,598 --> 00:05:09,019
This no-good
fucking Judas!

58
00:05:10,533 --> 00:05:13,631
- Hey, fucknut!
- Just take it easy, Al.

59
00:05:13,669 --> 00:05:15,163
How long you been
hatching this?

60
00:05:15,206 --> 00:05:18,107
I made a practical
goddamn business decision.

61
00:05:18,150 --> 00:05:20,451
No chance for me to match
their fucking offer?

62
00:05:20,486 --> 00:05:23,355
You couldn't have. You'd have killed me
before you'd matched.

63
00:05:23,397 --> 00:05:25,284
But it's between
you and them now.

64
00:05:25,317 --> 00:05:27,291
Drive careful,
cocksucker!

65
00:05:27,333 --> 00:05:29,853
Don't think I haven't
taken precaution.

66
00:05:29,893 --> 00:05:32,064
Don't think
I don't know your mind!

67
00:05:37,989 --> 00:05:41,337
- I hate to press you on that lot.
- I ain't ready to settle yet.

68
00:05:41,381 --> 00:05:44,130
- We're anxious to build.
- If you want an answer now, it's no.

69
00:05:46,628 --> 00:05:48,537
Two.

70
00:05:53,764 --> 00:05:57,506
Same for me,
only better.

71
00:05:57,540 --> 00:06:00,060
Yeah, three to the dealer.
The dealer draws...

72
00:06:00,099 --> 00:06:03,644
trench mouth.
Opener bets.

73
00:06:03,684 --> 00:06:05,952
Well damn,
Wild Bill.

74
00:06:05,987 --> 00:06:09,248
Even a stopped clock's
gotta be right sometime.

75
00:06:09,284 --> 00:06:11,902
Common law just says you gonna
win one sooner or later.

76
00:06:11,939 --> 00:06:14,873
But I'm gonna keep
pushin' my luck.

77
00:06:14,915 --> 00:06:17,664
What do you got there?
$8.

78
00:06:17,699 --> 00:06:20,960
Are you ready to stand any more credit
to Wild Bill, Tom?

79
00:06:20,995 --> 00:06:23,067
I didn't hear him
ask for any.

80
00:06:23,106 --> 00:06:25,658
You want me to just
bet eight, Bill?

81
00:06:29,058 --> 00:06:31,130
Cover my call.

82
00:06:32,227 --> 00:06:35,455
Aw, Bill, I can't
let you put your gun up.

83
00:06:35,490 --> 00:06:39,832
That Colt's worth more than my raise
by a good 40 bucks.

84
00:06:39,874 --> 00:06:42,775
- Are you takin' the bet?
- I tell you what,

85
00:06:42,818 --> 00:06:47,225
I'll add 40 bucks to my raise,
to make the bet fair.

86
00:06:47,266 --> 00:06:49,949
And then 50 more,

87
00:06:49,985 --> 00:06:51,894
if you'll
put up a set.

88
00:07:04,897 --> 00:07:06,969
Pot's right.

89
00:07:12,416 --> 00:07:14,871
Would a nine-high straight
do the trick?

90
00:07:18,240 --> 00:07:20,411
Pot to the club flush.

91
00:07:20,448 --> 00:07:24,473
Well, that's one in a row
for you, Wild Bill.

92
00:07:24,512 --> 00:07:27,261
Who's hungry?

93
00:07:27,296 --> 00:07:29,303
What in the hell damn
time is it anyway?

94
00:07:29,343 --> 00:07:31,928
Sure you wanna
quit playing, Jack?

95
00:07:33,312 --> 00:07:36,159
The game's always between you
and getting called a cunt.

96
00:07:36,192 --> 00:07:38,558
Meeting adjourned, fellas,
take it outside.

97
00:07:38,591 --> 00:07:40,500
That dropped eye
of yours

98
00:07:40,543 --> 00:07:42,430
looks like the hood
on a cunt to me, Jack.

99
00:07:42,463 --> 00:07:46,718
When you talk, your mouth
looks like a cunt moving.

100
00:07:46,751 --> 00:07:49,533
I ain't gonna get
in no gunfight with you, Hickok.

101
00:07:49,567 --> 00:07:52,381
But you will run
your cunt mouth at me...

102
00:07:53,950 --> 00:07:56,568
and I will take it
to play poker.

103
00:07:59,327 --> 00:08:01,628
I'll tote up accounts,
Mr. Hickok.

104
00:08:01,662 --> 00:08:05,044
We'll do whatever business
we need to next you're in.

105
00:08:05,086 --> 00:08:08,533
Anyone wants to,
can find me at the Grand Central.

106
00:08:17,373 --> 00:08:20,689
- She's warm, isn't she?
- She ain't talk yet, neither.

107
00:08:20,733 --> 00:08:22,805
That's beside the point,
you shut up!

108
00:08:22,845 --> 00:08:25,048
She will get a fever,
bein' wolf bit.

109
00:08:25,085 --> 00:08:27,506
The reason we risked
bringin' her into camp.

110
00:08:27,549 --> 00:08:29,588
You don't need to fear
the saloonkeeper.

111
00:08:29,629 --> 00:08:32,149
- He's not a danger to her no more.
- He's not?

112
00:08:32,189 --> 00:08:34,610
Saloonkeeper worried
that the little one

113
00:08:34,652 --> 00:08:36,855
said road agents
killed her people...

114
00:08:36,892 --> 00:08:39,160
who the road agents
might say they worked for.

115
00:08:39,197 --> 00:08:41,335
Meaning him?

116
00:08:41,372 --> 00:08:44,633
He took a different
approach to the problem.

117
00:08:44,668 --> 00:08:47,351
She would do better
indoors.

118
00:08:47,388 --> 00:08:50,704
I told Jane she could
take my room with the little one,

119
00:08:50,748 --> 00:08:52,406
and I'd move
back in with Bill.

120
00:08:52,443 --> 00:08:55,541
I will not stay in no fuckin' hotel!
They won't give me a room!

121
00:08:55,579 --> 00:08:58,328
You two keep
your voices down.

122
00:09:09,499 --> 00:09:11,767
What'd I say
about noise?

123
00:09:11,803 --> 00:09:14,421
He snores the whole
fuckin' night!

124
00:09:15,643 --> 00:09:18,741
Snoring's past
a person's control.

125
00:09:18,779 --> 00:09:21,713
I was a field nurse
during the war,

126
00:09:21,754 --> 00:09:23,379
at Shiloh
and Second Manassas.

127
00:09:23,418 --> 00:09:25,752
That was a good deal
of violence.

128
00:09:25,786 --> 00:09:28,152
Is that when you
got your calling?

129
00:09:28,186 --> 00:09:31,414
Yes, it was, sir.
Out of that crucible...

130
00:09:31,450 --> 00:09:34,613
out of all that horror,
to come to God's grace.

131
00:09:34,650 --> 00:09:37,519
A man's heart
deviseth his way,

132
00:09:37,561 --> 00:09:41,586
but the Lord
directeth his steps.

133
00:09:41,626 --> 00:09:43,992
He directeth
all our steps, Mr. Bullock.

134
00:09:44,025 --> 00:09:45,912
All of us.

135
00:09:45,945 --> 00:09:47,886
If you're preaching
at me, Reverend,

136
00:09:47,929 --> 00:09:50,514
you need to put some more
light on the text.

137
00:09:50,553 --> 00:09:53,781
If I am preaching at you, sir,
I do you a disservice.

138
00:09:53,817 --> 00:09:56,020
Good morning,
Mr. Star.

139
00:09:56,057 --> 00:09:57,682
Good morning,
Reverend.

140
00:09:57,721 --> 00:09:59,957
Did we get the lot?
Can we start building?

141
00:09:59,992 --> 00:10:02,642
- The reverend's come to help.
- We're still hangin' fire.

142
00:10:02,680 --> 00:10:05,549
- What's the damn holdup?
- New gambling outfit come into town.

143
00:10:05,593 --> 00:10:07,087
Time wasn't right
to push him to a decision.

144
00:10:07,128 --> 00:10:08,589
I got all the lumber cut.

145
00:10:08,632 --> 00:10:11,730
- And I warned you that was premature.
- You said 98%

146
00:10:11,768 --> 00:10:14,418
after your last conversation
with that son of a bitch.

147
00:10:14,456 --> 00:10:16,495
98 is not 100.

148
00:10:16,536 --> 00:10:18,640
God damn it!

149
00:10:19,992 --> 00:10:22,806
- Good day, sirs.
- Good day, Reverend.

150
00:10:25,047 --> 00:10:27,348
I said they'd find
a way to stop me.

151
00:10:27,383 --> 00:10:30,197
If it's raising room rates,
you have to go ahead and raise 'em.

152
00:10:30,232 --> 00:10:33,428
Rates aren't the only factor.
There's a waiting list for occupancy.

153
00:10:33,463 --> 00:10:35,372
You undertaker-looking
son of a bitch.

154
00:10:35,415 --> 00:10:37,870
This little girl's doctor
ordered her to live indoors,

155
00:10:37,911 --> 00:10:40,015
and I'm assigned
to change her dressings!

156
00:10:40,055 --> 00:10:42,869
A sad story, that's none
of my affair, "madam,"

157
00:10:42,903 --> 00:10:44,495
if I guess
your sex correct.

158
00:10:44,535 --> 00:10:46,673
What's the problem,
innkeeper?

159
00:10:46,711 --> 00:10:49,099
Mr. Hickok.

160
00:10:49,143 --> 00:10:51,663
Little one took fever
in that wagon last night, Bill.

161
00:10:51,703 --> 00:10:54,069
And I thought Jane and her
could stay in my room

162
00:10:54,102 --> 00:10:55,760
and I'd move
back in with you.

163
00:10:55,798 --> 00:10:58,186
I'm not in opposition, sir.
Just the opposite.

164
00:10:58,230 --> 00:11:00,466
Who wouldn't want
to accommodate a sick girl?

165
00:11:00,502 --> 00:11:02,606
But the Simpson Hotel's
closed its doors.

166
00:11:02,646 --> 00:11:04,401
If Mr. Utter's vacating,

167
00:11:04,438 --> 00:11:07,733
shouldn't these people that have been
trying me all morning get first call?

168
00:11:07,766 --> 00:11:09,588
Isn't that
simple fairness?

169
00:11:09,621 --> 00:11:12,719
He don't give fuck all for fairness!
He just don't want me in here.

170
00:11:12,757 --> 00:11:14,644
How 'bout if he stays
in his room

171
00:11:14,677 --> 00:11:16,269
and the lady
moves in with me?

172
00:11:16,309 --> 00:11:18,316
That way no one's
vacating nothing.

173
00:11:18,357 --> 00:11:20,844
That would outflank
the checkout issue.

174
00:11:20,885 --> 00:11:22,794
But it might raise
questions of decorum.

175
00:11:22,837 --> 00:11:26,382
- With who?
- No one of consequence, I suppose.

176
00:11:26,421 --> 00:11:28,111
Let her in.

177
00:11:28,149 --> 00:11:30,221
I'm going to get
some breakfast.

178
00:11:33,845 --> 00:11:35,949
There will be
a rate adjustment!

179
00:11:38,740 --> 00:11:41,195
Good morning.

180
00:11:41,236 --> 00:11:44,235
I've heard the stories, madam,
I tell you that at flagfall.

181
00:11:44,276 --> 00:11:46,577
You are here
on sufferance.

182
00:11:46,612 --> 00:11:48,684
Kiss my ass!

183
00:11:49,908 --> 00:11:51,947
Cocksuckers.

184
00:11:51,988 --> 00:11:53,897
Where were they
when Dan and me were

185
00:11:53,940 --> 00:11:56,787
chopping trees
in this gulch?

186
00:11:56,819 --> 00:11:58,313
Hands all blistered,

187
00:11:58,356 --> 00:12:01,257
bucktooth fucking beavers
rolling around in the creek,

188
00:12:01,299 --> 00:12:03,306
slapping their tails
in the water

189
00:12:03,347 --> 00:12:05,713
like we was hired
entertainment.

190
00:12:05,747 --> 00:12:08,081
I'd have paid a nickel
to see you chopping wood.

191
00:12:08,114 --> 00:12:10,764
Yeah. Don't think I wasn't
blow for blow with Dan.

192
00:12:10,803 --> 00:12:12,690
I can play that shit
when I have to.

193
00:12:16,435 --> 00:12:18,442
But I've been
to Chicago too.

194
00:12:21,651 --> 00:12:23,309
How do I look?

195
00:12:23,346 --> 00:12:25,898
Like Christ crucified.

196
00:12:37,169 --> 00:12:39,307
Guess this ain't a hotel
no more.

197
00:12:40,465 --> 00:12:42,569
Come see us tonight
when we open,

198
00:12:42,610 --> 00:12:44,781
we'll find you a place
to lay down.

199
00:12:44,817 --> 00:12:46,889
And someone to keep
your feet warm.

200
00:12:46,929 --> 00:12:49,481
I'm Al Swearengen.
I own the joint across the street.

201
00:12:49,521 --> 00:12:51,528
- The Gem?
- That's it.

202
00:12:51,569 --> 00:12:52,746
Cy Tolliver, Al.

203
00:12:52,785 --> 00:12:55,435
Ed Sawyer,
Joanie Stubbs.

204
00:12:55,473 --> 00:12:59,433
You people must've
trained with the heathens.

205
00:12:59,473 --> 00:13:02,255
Yeah, you know, you come up
on us unbeknownst.

206
00:13:02,288 --> 00:13:04,076
How long you been
in camp, Al?

207
00:13:04,112 --> 00:13:06,119
This year, since March.
I was here last year too,

208
00:13:06,161 --> 00:13:07,949
but the fucking cavalry
drove us out.

209
00:13:07,985 --> 00:13:09,992
Put all the whites out,
didn't they?

210
00:13:10,032 --> 00:13:13,228
Deep fucking thinkers in Washington
put forward that policy.

211
00:13:13,264 --> 00:13:16,198
This year though, so many
soldiers deserting to prospect,

212
00:13:16,240 --> 00:13:18,378
gave up the ghost,
let us all back in.

213
00:13:18,416 --> 00:13:20,717
And of course, Custer sorted out
the Sioux for us,

214
00:13:20,752 --> 00:13:23,086
so now we're all as safe
as at our mothers' tits.

215
00:13:23,120 --> 00:13:25,224
Did a job for our side,
didn't he, Al?

216
00:13:25,264 --> 00:13:27,751
How about that long-haired
fucking blowhard, huh?

217
00:13:27,791 --> 00:13:29,863
I'll tell you this, son,
you can mark my words,

218
00:13:29,904 --> 00:13:31,692
Crazy Horse went
into Little Bighorn,

219
00:13:31,728 --> 00:13:33,996
bought his people one good,
long-term ass fucking.

220
00:13:34,031 --> 00:13:36,518
You do not want to be
a dirt-worshipping heathen

221
00:13:36,559 --> 00:13:38,314
from this fucking
point forward.

222
00:13:38,350 --> 00:13:41,284
- Pardon my French.
- Oh, I speak French.

223
00:13:43,406 --> 00:13:46,307
Well, here we are,
settling the world's problems.

224
00:13:46,350 --> 00:13:50,146
And I've been wondering, Cy,
um, perhaps we should

225
00:13:50,190 --> 00:13:52,197
talk about our areas
of overlap

226
00:13:52,239 --> 00:13:54,180
so we're not
at each other's throats.

227
00:13:54,222 --> 00:13:56,709
- Give me a for instance, Al.
- Uh, women.

228
00:13:56,750 --> 00:13:58,637
Would we want to agree
on rates?

229
00:13:58,670 --> 00:14:02,412
Well, far as pussy, Al, we'll want
to let the market sort itself out.

230
00:14:02,446 --> 00:14:05,828
Sounds to me like I'm
up against specialty acts.

231
00:14:05,870 --> 00:14:08,771
How about table games?
Any overlap there?

232
00:14:08,814 --> 00:14:10,853
We'll be featuring
craps, Al.

233
00:14:10,893 --> 00:14:12,616
I played that in Chicago.

234
00:14:12,654 --> 00:14:13,897
I don't offer it myself,

235
00:14:13,933 --> 00:14:17,194
gets these hoople-heads
confused, hmm?

236
00:14:18,285 --> 00:14:20,903
That's one area
of overlap avoided.

237
00:14:20,941 --> 00:14:22,915
- What about faro?
- We'll have it.

238
00:14:22,957 --> 00:14:24,647
That decision
hard and fast?

239
00:14:24,684 --> 00:14:27,651
I don't see overlap being a problem,
Al, even where we duplicate.

240
00:14:27,693 --> 00:14:29,831
We're offering
different atmospheres.

241
00:14:29,869 --> 00:14:33,097
You're a pioneering type,
a trailblazer type.

242
00:14:33,132 --> 00:14:35,236
You're gonna draw
a trailblazing element.

243
00:14:35,276 --> 00:14:37,380
Meaning I get the ones
that don't wash?

244
00:14:37,420 --> 00:14:40,900
Must cut through the stink when they
walk in with those sacks full of gold.

245
00:14:40,940 --> 00:14:43,841
Oh, the money spends,
definitely.

246
00:14:43,883 --> 00:14:46,566
Anyways, thanks
for the neighborly visit.

247
00:14:46,604 --> 00:14:49,059
Yeah, good to meet you.
Very good luck to you.

248
00:14:49,099 --> 00:14:50,921
You're opening
at 8:00, huh?

249
00:14:50,955 --> 00:14:52,896
That's what we're aiming at.

250
00:14:52,939 --> 00:14:55,906
8:00.

251
00:14:55,948 --> 00:14:58,249
Good for you.

252
00:14:58,283 --> 00:15:00,738
Wouldn't set a fire
right away.

253
00:15:01,739 --> 00:15:03,648
Come to case us, though.

254
00:15:03,691 --> 00:15:05,479
He would set a fire.

255
00:15:08,523 --> 00:15:10,049
The way you tell it, mister,

256
00:15:10,091 --> 00:15:13,319
the man didn't sell you that claim
holding a gun to your head.

257
00:15:13,354 --> 00:15:15,176
Frankly, Mr. Hickok,

258
00:15:15,210 --> 00:15:17,446
being a novice in these matters,
I was duped.

259
00:15:17,482 --> 00:15:20,710
And now the seller's disappeared.
You checked into his room.

260
00:15:20,746 --> 00:15:22,501
It sound like
you're up shit's creek.

261
00:15:22,538 --> 00:15:24,577
The seller had accomplices,
gentlemen.

262
00:15:24,618 --> 00:15:27,552
Men of... what passes
for position in this place.

263
00:15:27,594 --> 00:15:31,336
I would pay a handsome bounty, if they
were brought to make restitutions.

264
00:15:31,370 --> 00:15:33,409
Sorry you lost
your money, mister.

265
00:15:33,449 --> 00:15:36,383
But I ain't for hire
to rob it back.

266
00:15:36,425 --> 00:15:38,312
I make no terms as to method.

267
00:15:38,345 --> 00:15:41,028
You don't figure a good talking-to
would do the trick?

268
00:15:44,105 --> 00:15:46,112
I'm not leaving camp

269
00:15:46,153 --> 00:15:47,843
without my money.

270
00:15:47,881 --> 00:15:50,269
Mister, that fella you said
had my room before me?

271
00:15:50,313 --> 00:15:52,833
A man named Tim Driscoll,
yes, pure charlatan.

272
00:15:52,873 --> 00:15:56,221
Fresh stain on the floor
when I moved in.

273
00:15:56,265 --> 00:15:59,777
He may have checked out
short a useful amount of blood.

274
00:15:59,817 --> 00:16:01,475
It wouldn't surprise me
in the least.

275
00:16:01,512 --> 00:16:04,446
That would make these accomplices
you're talking about

276
00:16:04,488 --> 00:16:06,495
dangerous people
to deal with.

277
00:16:06,537 --> 00:16:09,668
Yes, I quite take your point...
no honor among thieves.

278
00:16:11,464 --> 00:16:13,351
Well...

279
00:16:13,384 --> 00:16:15,620
thanks for your time.

280
00:16:15,656 --> 00:16:18,405
I'll pursue my remedies
in some other fashion.

281
00:16:21,159 --> 00:16:23,547
I don't think
he took your point...

282
00:16:23,591 --> 00:16:25,117
quite.

283
00:16:25,159 --> 00:16:27,231
I think he quite
missed it.

284
00:16:28,583 --> 00:16:31,811
I believe I'll pass out,
Charlie.

285
00:16:31,847 --> 00:16:34,432
I guess you were
playing poker all night, huh?

286
00:16:34,471 --> 00:16:36,259
Yes, sir.

287
00:16:36,295 --> 00:16:39,590
When we was coming into camp
I saw that Montana fella

288
00:16:39,623 --> 00:16:41,477
you seem to like.

289
00:16:41,510 --> 00:16:44,379
Bullock had my back
again last night.

290
00:16:44,423 --> 00:16:46,844
Well, he was seeing
to the result this morning.

291
00:16:46,886 --> 00:16:48,827
Man has an active
conscience.

292
00:16:48,871 --> 00:16:51,718
What would you think of us
and him and his friend

293
00:16:51,750 --> 00:16:54,564
- having dinner tonight?
- Why?

294
00:16:54,598 --> 00:16:56,866
People gotta eat,
don't they, Bill?

295
00:16:56,902 --> 00:16:59,552
And maybe you'd enjoy
sitting with someone

296
00:16:59,589 --> 00:17:02,239
who wasn't looking
to beat you at cards.

297
00:17:02,277 --> 00:17:05,572
Or blow
your fucking head off.

298
00:17:05,605 --> 00:17:07,393
True enough.

299
00:17:08,357 --> 00:17:10,593
Mark me down
for a yes.

300
00:17:17,061 --> 00:17:19,395
I want to know
who did their legwork.

301
00:17:19,429 --> 00:17:21,251
You hit the nail
square, Al.

302
00:17:21,285 --> 00:17:23,423
Whoever went between
them Bella Union people

303
00:17:23,461 --> 00:17:26,079
and Artie Simpson would be
a prime source of information.

304
00:17:26,116 --> 00:17:28,003
Do not repeat
back to me

305
00:17:28,036 --> 00:17:31,352
what I just said
in different fucking words!

306
00:17:32,484 --> 00:17:35,036
I wanna know
who cut the cheese.

307
00:17:38,852 --> 00:17:40,761
I'll tell you this
for openers...

308
00:17:40,804 --> 00:17:43,007
we are gonna set off an area
on the balcony.

309
00:17:43,043 --> 00:17:44,952
And God help
whoever doesn't use it,

310
00:17:44,996 --> 00:17:47,417
because the next stink
I have to smell in this office,

311
00:17:47,460 --> 00:17:50,012
and whoever doesn't admit to it
is going out the window,

312
00:17:50,052 --> 00:17:52,418
into the muck,
onto their fucking heads

313
00:17:52,451 --> 00:17:56,411
and we'll see how they like
farting from that position, okay?

314
00:17:56,451 --> 00:17:59,200
"I hate to press you on the lot,
Mr. Swearengen."

315
00:17:59,235 --> 00:18:00,893
Wouldn't that be a setup?

316
00:18:00,931 --> 00:18:03,134
If they were all
of the same fucking party?

317
00:18:03,171 --> 00:18:05,058
You think them
hardware guys and Hickok

318
00:18:05,091 --> 00:18:08,058
might be the advance party
for them saloon operators?

319
00:18:08,098 --> 00:18:10,683
You did the same fucking thing
I told you not to.

320
00:18:10,723 --> 00:18:14,497
Get them too, say I'm ready
to conclude on their offer.

321
00:18:14,530 --> 00:18:18,206
Stop at Wu's. Tell him either he feeds
his pigs Persimmon Phil tonight,

322
00:18:18,242 --> 00:18:21,089
or I serve them
raw loin of Oriental.

323
00:18:21,122 --> 00:18:23,226
I thought you forgot
all about that, Al.

324
00:18:23,266 --> 00:18:26,113
I thought it just sorta
slipped through the cracks.

325
00:18:27,713 --> 00:18:31,160
The faro dude
at the new joint,

326
00:18:31,201 --> 00:18:34,266
dope-fiend.
Tall guy, skankly red beard.

327
00:18:34,306 --> 00:18:36,672
You want me to get next to him,
Mr. Swearengen?

328
00:18:36,705 --> 00:18:39,039
Let me take a few dollars,
I'll go play at his table.

329
00:18:39,073 --> 00:18:40,479
Stop hustling.

330
00:18:40,513 --> 00:18:43,774
I'll give you dope when you
bring that cocksucker here.

331
00:18:43,809 --> 00:18:46,776
He's as good as standing
in front of you, Mr. Swearengen.

332
00:18:48,513 --> 00:18:49,789
No.

333
00:18:49,825 --> 00:18:52,345
Stick around.

334
00:18:57,953 --> 00:19:00,767
Help me measure
where their loyalties lie.

335
00:19:00,800 --> 00:19:02,709
These hardware guys?

336
00:19:05,120 --> 00:19:08,087
The burden falls on me,
Alma.

337
00:19:08,128 --> 00:19:10,331
That much is now clear.

338
00:19:10,368 --> 00:19:12,506
Do you think there's
any possibility

339
00:19:12,544 --> 00:19:14,999
that Mr. Hickok
might reconsider?

340
00:19:15,040 --> 00:19:16,862
None.

341
00:19:16,896 --> 00:19:19,383
Nor was I sure that,
if he'd agreed,

342
00:19:19,424 --> 00:19:22,423
the man before me at that
breakfast table was equal to the task.

343
00:19:30,910 --> 00:19:33,081
Promise me one thing
then, Brom.

344
00:19:33,119 --> 00:19:35,835
Don't ask me
to amend my purpose.

345
00:19:35,870 --> 00:19:38,903
That before seeing
Mr. Swearengen,

346
00:19:38,942 --> 00:19:40,851
you take your walk.

347
00:19:45,278 --> 00:19:47,644
To clear my head
and reflect?

348
00:19:47,679 --> 00:19:50,100
If only to perfect
your arguments.

349
00:19:50,142 --> 00:19:52,051
I see.

350
00:19:54,590 --> 00:19:56,662
I accept the suggestion

351
00:19:56,702 --> 00:19:59,189
and a feeling for its author.

352
00:20:00,317 --> 00:20:01,909
Thank you.

353
00:20:04,029 --> 00:20:06,778
If I'm stooped when
next you see me, Alma,

354
00:20:06,813 --> 00:20:10,074
it won't be worry weighing me down
but bags of our recovered gold.

355
00:20:12,445 --> 00:20:14,549
Take your walk, dear.

356
00:20:37,532 --> 00:20:39,287
It's Hickok, Alma.

357
00:20:39,323 --> 00:20:41,526
- Unconscious.
- I see.

358
00:20:41,564 --> 00:20:44,433
I take this as proof
my reservations were well founded.

359
00:20:57,211 --> 00:20:59,577
Too considerate
to disturb us?

360
00:20:59,611 --> 00:21:01,715
Wouldn't have truck
with that...

361
00:21:01,754 --> 00:21:03,858
room clerk ghoul to get
let into Charlie's,

362
00:21:03,899 --> 00:21:07,281
I'd rather sleep in the fucking hallway,
that's the kind of man he is.

363
00:21:07,322 --> 00:21:10,518
Aw! I owe you
another fucking penny.

364
00:21:10,554 --> 00:21:13,041
I owe you another one.

365
00:21:14,330 --> 00:21:16,718
I don't know if you
ever should learn English,

366
00:21:16,762 --> 00:21:18,703
every mind foul.

367
00:21:18,746 --> 00:21:21,495
Spare you knowing
how ignorant people are.

368
00:21:23,354 --> 00:21:26,387
But then I couldn't
tell you about Bill...

369
00:21:26,426 --> 00:21:30,222
sleeping in the hallway
out of thought for others.

370
00:21:31,290 --> 00:21:34,006
And I know some other
fucking stories too...

371
00:21:35,321 --> 00:21:37,459
Owe you
another penny.

372
00:21:41,208 --> 00:21:43,574
Look at that jackass.

373
00:21:43,609 --> 00:21:45,397
Help you with anything?

374
00:21:45,433 --> 00:21:48,367
I tell you who's being done
a favor at this exact moment.

375
00:21:48,409 --> 00:21:50,448
Or would you care
to take a guess?

376
00:21:50,489 --> 00:21:52,081
A favor in this tent.

377
00:21:52,121 --> 00:21:54,160
I'd guess it's you
doing one for yourself,

378
00:21:54,200 --> 00:21:55,923
considering
the quality goods.

379
00:21:55,961 --> 00:21:58,710
The favor here's being done
for Wild Bill-fucking-Hickok.

380
00:21:58,744 --> 00:22:00,238
What are you
talking about?

381
00:22:00,280 --> 00:22:02,800
'Cause if I'm out
prospecting in the hills,

382
00:22:02,840 --> 00:22:04,727
then he ain't getting
his just desserts...

383
00:22:04,760 --> 00:22:08,142
at the poker table,
or otherwise.

384
00:22:08,184 --> 00:22:10,125
Don't ask me what I mean
by the last part.

385
00:22:10,167 --> 00:22:11,792
What do you mean?

386
00:22:11,831 --> 00:22:13,685
I said you'd do better
not asking.

387
00:22:13,719 --> 00:22:15,279
Get outta here.

388
00:22:15,319 --> 00:22:17,141
I'll buy this one.

389
00:22:17,176 --> 00:22:18,702
What's the price on that?

390
00:22:18,744 --> 00:22:20,653
You ain't buying nothing.

391
00:22:21,623 --> 00:22:23,215
I know you.

392
00:22:23,255 --> 00:22:25,807
- Where I know you from?
- Can't help you with that, partner.

393
00:22:25,847 --> 00:22:28,115
You follow him around.

394
00:22:30,263 --> 00:22:31,691
Hey!

395
00:22:35,478 --> 00:22:37,899
That tent's shut to you.

396
00:22:37,943 --> 00:22:39,852
Don't come back there.

397
00:22:42,135 --> 00:22:43,793
Fuck you...

398
00:22:43,830 --> 00:22:46,480
and any plans I might've
had to buy something,

399
00:22:46,518 --> 00:22:48,656
or prospect.

400
00:22:52,661 --> 00:22:55,082
I'd be lousy at retail.

401
00:22:55,125 --> 00:22:57,491
I guarantee you that much.

402
00:22:57,525 --> 00:22:59,183
Wouldn't have
the patience for it.

403
00:22:59,221 --> 00:23:01,741
I'm not sure how much
future he's got.

404
00:23:01,782 --> 00:23:03,756
Anyways, I want
to tell you fellas,

405
00:23:03,797 --> 00:23:05,935
several days I'll be
going back to Cheyenne...

406
00:23:05,973 --> 00:23:08,361
to try and secure
a mail route.

407
00:23:08,405 --> 00:23:10,379
I operate a freight business
outta there.

408
00:23:10,421 --> 00:23:13,803
You need resupply, I'll be bringing
several wagons back.

409
00:23:13,845 --> 00:23:15,786
That's good to know.

410
00:23:17,557 --> 00:23:20,622
And, uh, I was, uh,
half wondering too if...

411
00:23:20,660 --> 00:23:23,659
if you'd want to join
Bill and me for dinner.

412
00:23:23,700 --> 00:23:25,903
Tonight
or some other time.

413
00:23:25,941 --> 00:23:27,850
Let's do it tonight.

414
00:23:30,100 --> 00:23:32,587
I feel like I should've
brung posies.

415
00:23:33,556 --> 00:23:34,766
Afternoon.

416
00:23:34,804 --> 00:23:36,778
Can I help you
find something?

417
00:23:36,819 --> 00:23:38,891
Mr. Swearengen
wants to see ya.

418
00:24:15,218 --> 00:24:17,584
I only hope you understand me
being short with you

419
00:24:17,618 --> 00:24:20,138
- out in the street this morning.
- You had a lot on your mind.

420
00:24:20,178 --> 00:24:22,185
I had a lot of what's left
of my fucking mind,

421
00:24:22,226 --> 00:24:23,851
these new interests
coming in.

422
00:24:23,890 --> 00:24:26,508
I'd only hope you understand,
and see my thinking

423
00:24:26,545 --> 00:24:28,399
in not selling you
that lot outright.

424
00:24:28,434 --> 00:24:30,026
What's your thinking today?

425
00:24:30,065 --> 00:24:31,690
Gets dead set
at the fucking point,

426
00:24:31,729 --> 00:24:33,768
which I like
in most situations.

427
00:24:38,897 --> 00:24:40,904
Do you know these
new saloon interests?

428
00:24:40,945 --> 00:24:43,148
- Are you acquainted with them at all?
- Nope.

429
00:24:43,185 --> 00:24:45,126
Not them
and not Bill Hickok.

430
00:24:45,168 --> 00:24:47,623
And all we want to do is
run a hardware business.

431
00:24:47,664 --> 00:24:51,657
I have got to be satisfied.

432
00:24:51,696 --> 00:24:53,768
See, I'm the simple-type
cocksucker

433
00:24:53,808 --> 00:24:56,076
that when he sees lightning,
readies for thunder.

434
00:24:56,112 --> 00:24:58,478
And takes the thunder
if it comes from the same storm.

435
00:24:58,512 --> 00:25:00,399
Why wouldn't ya,
Mr. Swearengen?

436
00:25:00,432 --> 00:25:03,214
Thank you for saying that,
even if you don't fucking mean it.

437
00:25:03,248 --> 00:25:05,484
What would make you
comfortable selling to us?

438
00:25:08,752 --> 00:25:10,442
1,000.

439
00:25:10,479 --> 00:25:13,774
Plus right of first refusal
on any further sale.

440
00:25:13,808 --> 00:25:15,531
Accepted.

441
00:25:15,567 --> 00:25:18,119
And right to buy back
at the original price,

442
00:25:18,159 --> 00:25:20,875
- plus the cost of your improvements.
- Accepted.

443
00:25:20,911 --> 00:25:22,569
No gambling
on the fucking premises.

444
00:25:22,606 --> 00:25:25,453
No association of any kind
with these Bella Union cocksuckers.

445
00:25:25,486 --> 00:25:27,274
- Accept...
- We can't sell 'em our goods?

446
00:25:27,310 --> 00:25:28,422
No.

447
00:25:28,463 --> 00:25:30,121
What do you
think of that?

448
00:25:30,159 --> 00:25:32,133
Accepted.

449
00:25:32,174 --> 00:25:34,083
What do you think?

450
00:25:38,734 --> 00:25:40,457
Accepted.

451
00:25:43,694 --> 00:25:48,134
Or, they could buy
your wares

452
00:25:48,173 --> 00:25:51,718
in your normal course
of your normal fucking business.

453
00:25:51,757 --> 00:25:54,342
I'd guess it's okay to transact
with these cocksuckers.

454
00:25:54,382 --> 00:25:57,000
- We can sell them our wares?
- Your normal wares.

455
00:25:57,037 --> 00:25:59,753
No gambling,
whoring or whiskey

456
00:25:59,790 --> 00:26:02,789
on the fucking premises
is the chief fucking point.

457
00:26:02,829 --> 00:26:04,072
Agreed.

458
00:26:04,109 --> 00:26:05,734
I spit in my hand.

459
00:26:08,109 --> 00:26:10,694
Will that drive you
screaming into the hills?

460
00:26:18,317 --> 00:26:21,382
The thousand
would be nice.

461
00:26:22,348 --> 00:26:24,736
20, 40, 60, 80, 100.

462
00:26:24,780 --> 00:26:27,081
A happy outcome.

463
00:26:27,116 --> 00:26:28,741
20, 40, 60, 80, 200.

464
00:26:28,780 --> 00:26:30,667
...a shooting
exhibition.

465
00:26:30,700 --> 00:26:33,088
That idea for Mr. Hickok
has been had

466
00:26:33,132 --> 00:26:35,520
and acted upon by a few people
before you.

467
00:26:35,563 --> 00:26:40,069
And, then afterward,
we cut the bullets out

468
00:26:40,108 --> 00:26:43,239
and the fucking playing cards
he was using as targets.

469
00:26:43,275 --> 00:26:45,249
That's the point
I was trying to get to.

470
00:26:45,291 --> 00:26:48,422
How about the tree bark behind
the fucking playing card targets, huh?

471
00:26:48,459 --> 00:26:51,906
Hell, yeah, we'll sell
the fucking bark.

472
00:26:51,947 --> 00:26:53,856
- What do you say, fellas?
- We got our lot.

473
00:26:53,899 --> 00:26:55,459
Hooray for you boys.

474
00:26:55,499 --> 00:26:57,637
Two days for me
to get the word out.

475
00:26:57,675 --> 00:27:00,096
10¢ to watch, and we'll charge
for the souvenirs.

476
00:27:00,138 --> 00:27:02,406
Ain't taking you up
on that, mister.

477
00:27:02,442 --> 00:27:04,546
- Another 20 for you on the quiet.
- No.

478
00:27:04,586 --> 00:27:06,952
And the talk
between us is over.

479
00:27:06,987 --> 00:27:08,775
Soap!

480
00:27:08,810 --> 00:27:10,053
Soap with
a prize inside.

481
00:27:10,090 --> 00:27:12,545
Soap!

482
00:27:12,586 --> 00:27:14,276
Got that man
to sell, huh?

483
00:27:14,313 --> 00:27:16,614
Never had to strain so
to spend $1,000.

484
00:27:16,649 --> 00:27:18,852
Will you let us
outta dinner?

485
00:27:18,890 --> 00:27:21,737
You'd as soon
not do it, huh?

486
00:27:21,770 --> 00:27:23,460
We'd like to get
to building.

487
00:27:23,498 --> 00:27:26,367
Will we see you tomorrow
for breakfast?

488
00:27:26,409 --> 00:27:28,383
Sure.

489
00:27:28,425 --> 00:27:31,174
Maybe we'll catch Bill
coming back from cards.

490
00:27:31,209 --> 00:27:33,958
Well, congratulations
to both of you.

491
00:27:33,993 --> 00:27:35,487
Thanks, Mr. Utter.

492
00:27:35,529 --> 00:27:37,797
- Thank you.
- Good luck to you.

493
00:27:40,648 --> 00:27:43,069
Looks like
we're in business.

494
00:27:43,112 --> 00:27:44,966
Huh?

495
00:27:52,040 --> 00:27:54,461
My goodness.

496
00:27:54,504 --> 00:27:56,772
My heavens.

497
00:27:56,807 --> 00:27:58,367
My goodness gracious.

498
00:28:00,968 --> 00:28:03,651
Heavens to Betsy.

499
00:28:03,687 --> 00:28:06,207
What do you think, Hiram,
ever seen a craps layout?

500
00:28:06,248 --> 00:28:08,549
- My first.
- Shall I show you how it works?

501
00:28:08,583 --> 00:28:10,011
I might could follow.

502
00:28:10,055 --> 00:28:11,615
I do read and cipher.

503
00:28:11,656 --> 00:28:15,365
Well, you're well
in advance of the pack.

504
00:28:15,399 --> 00:28:17,057
Tell me what this says.

505
00:28:17,095 --> 00:28:19,298
C-o-m-e.

506
00:28:19,335 --> 00:28:20,829
It says "Come."

507
00:28:20,871 --> 00:28:22,845
You really can read,
can't ya?

508
00:28:22,886 --> 00:28:24,795
I wasn't raised to lie.

509
00:28:26,214 --> 00:28:28,286
I'm liable to be killed,
Eddie.

510
00:28:28,327 --> 00:28:30,268
He's on my scent
and closing.

511
00:28:30,310 --> 00:28:32,830
Curious tactics,
your coming here then, E.B.

512
00:28:32,871 --> 00:28:35,456
To remind you secrecy
is of the essence.

513
00:28:35,494 --> 00:28:37,184
Al Swearengen's
a dangerous man.

514
00:28:37,223 --> 00:28:39,110
Let him doubt
those he's trusted,

515
00:28:39,142 --> 00:28:40,832
this camp will run red
with blood.

516
00:28:40,870 --> 00:28:42,692
Argues for raising
your room rates,

517
00:28:42,726 --> 00:28:44,733
at least make the game
worth the candle.

518
00:28:44,774 --> 00:28:46,878
I wonder how cavalier
your attitude will be...

519
00:28:46,918 --> 00:28:49,536
with a pig gnawing
through your vitals.

520
00:28:49,573 --> 00:28:51,645
Bet on me
screaming for mercy.

521
00:28:51,685 --> 00:28:53,507
I turned down
your offer to buy

522
00:28:53,542 --> 00:28:55,134
and pointed you
to Artie Simpson.

523
00:28:55,173 --> 00:28:57,060
The whole damn extent
of my involvement.

524
00:28:57,093 --> 00:28:59,548
And I'm staring
straight at extinction.

525
00:28:59,589 --> 00:29:02,687
He may get you anyway, E.B.,
but if your nerve goes,

526
00:29:02,725 --> 00:29:04,579
he'll get you sure.

527
00:29:07,685 --> 00:29:10,619
Now, dope is not my own
preferred form of relaxation,

528
00:29:10,661 --> 00:29:13,694
but I did try the shit and believe me...
I nearly converted.

529
00:29:13,733 --> 00:29:16,515
Jimmy said you'd do right by me,
Mr. Swearengen.

530
00:29:16,548 --> 00:29:17,922
Everything...

531
00:29:17,956 --> 00:29:19,450
that goes on at that place.

532
00:29:19,492 --> 00:29:21,499
I'll give you a daily report.

533
00:29:21,540 --> 00:29:23,449
Yeah.

534
00:29:38,500 --> 00:29:40,703
He's the type
I'd wanna know about.

535
00:29:40,739 --> 00:29:42,593
Just left your joint.

536
00:29:42,627 --> 00:29:44,449
Judas goat-looking fella.

537
00:29:45,411 --> 00:29:47,101
Hey, you see him?

538
00:29:47,139 --> 00:29:49,375
Coyote-moving type?

539
00:29:49,411 --> 00:29:51,483
- You see him?
- The short guy?

540
00:29:51,523 --> 00:29:56,127
Yeah, with his paws always damp
like a just shit fucking turd.

541
00:29:56,162 --> 00:29:59,031
That's the type
I wanna know about.

542
00:30:00,802 --> 00:30:03,933
Comings, goings,
any dealings with your bosses.

543
00:30:03,971 --> 00:30:05,858
I'll keep a special eye
on him.

544
00:30:05,890 --> 00:30:07,777
- Al?
- Yeah.

545
00:30:07,810 --> 00:30:09,882
That cherry New York dude

546
00:30:09,922 --> 00:30:12,125
- is downstairs asking for ya.
- No good.

547
00:30:12,161 --> 00:30:14,135
Charlie him the fuck out.

548
00:30:20,065 --> 00:30:22,879
He keeps talking
about the Pinkertons.

549
00:30:26,209 --> 00:30:28,696
Dan Dority,
thought you were dead.

550
00:30:28,737 --> 00:30:31,125
Yes, I didn't go
to the claim this morning.

551
00:30:31,169 --> 00:30:32,957
You should've told him.

552
00:30:32,993 --> 00:30:35,960
I've had him here
the last several hours in tears.

553
00:30:36,001 --> 00:30:38,105
Dan, look!

554
00:30:38,144 --> 00:30:40,315
- He's alive.
- Thank God.

555
00:30:40,352 --> 00:30:42,293
Yes, I chose not to go
to the claim.

556
00:30:42,336 --> 00:30:43,513
Whiskey, Brom?
Snatch?

557
00:30:43,552 --> 00:30:45,374
Frankly, Al, I'm here
to speak with you.

558
00:30:45,408 --> 00:30:47,415
And I'm not to be
distracted.

559
00:30:47,456 --> 00:30:50,041
Then proceed, my son,
speak frankly.

560
00:30:50,080 --> 00:30:52,381
We needn't reach the question
of whether my claim

561
00:30:52,416 --> 00:30:54,074
has "pinched out,"
as the saying goes,

562
00:30:54,112 --> 00:30:56,446
or whether it was a sham
proposition to begin with.

563
00:30:56,480 --> 00:30:59,741
Let's just say,
I've lost faith in the property.

564
00:30:59,776 --> 00:31:02,645
- Have you?
- And I want my $20,000 back.

565
00:31:02,687 --> 00:31:04,923
In the heat you've confused me
with Tim Driscoll.

566
00:31:04,959 --> 00:31:08,024
I think we're both aware, Al,
that Driscoll's no longer in camp.

567
00:31:08,063 --> 00:31:10,451
And because I believe you
colluded with Tim Driscoll

568
00:31:10,495 --> 00:31:12,950
and perhaps were in cahoots
with other parties as well,

569
00:31:12,991 --> 00:31:15,063
I require satisfaction
from you.

570
00:31:15,103 --> 00:31:16,629
It's the heat again, Brom.

571
00:31:16,671 --> 00:31:18,678
I don't collude
and I don't cahoot.

572
00:31:18,719 --> 00:31:22,875
Al, are you familiar
with the Pinkerton Agency?

573
00:31:26,558 --> 00:31:28,924
- Why?
- Pursuing its business interests,

574
00:31:28,958 --> 00:31:31,892
my family's had several occasions
to engage the Pinkertons.

575
00:31:31,935 --> 00:31:34,073
We maintain
friendly relations.

576
00:31:34,110 --> 00:31:36,084
I'd prefer we two
settle this as gentlemen,

577
00:31:36,126 --> 00:31:39,474
but if need be, the Pinkertons
can be made a party to our dispute.

578
00:31:41,246 --> 00:31:43,896
Has he asked you to reconnoiter
the rims with him at all?

579
00:31:43,934 --> 00:31:45,079
Never.

580
00:31:45,118 --> 00:31:46,546
Did he ask to
and you refused?

581
00:31:46,589 --> 00:31:48,017
Didn't get around to it, Al.

582
00:31:48,061 --> 00:31:49,948
I thought he was in
for the long haul.

583
00:31:49,981 --> 00:31:51,890
What are you talking
about specifically?

584
00:31:51,934 --> 00:31:55,676
The gold you found washed down from
somewhere, that's the law of gravity.

585
00:31:55,709 --> 00:32:00,345
And your claim runs rim to rim
the width of the fucking gulch,

586
00:32:00,380 --> 00:32:03,413
so the original deposit
the gold you found washed down from

587
00:32:03,453 --> 00:32:06,714
is likely on your claim above,
near one of the rims.

588
00:32:06,748 --> 00:32:08,657
That's what you feel
I should reconnoiter?

589
00:32:08,701 --> 00:32:11,067
First place the Pinkertons
would look.

590
00:32:11,100 --> 00:32:13,783
Unless I'm fucking wrong.

591
00:32:13,820 --> 00:32:16,121
No, that's how they operate.

592
00:32:16,156 --> 00:32:18,577
So if he asks you,

593
00:32:18,620 --> 00:32:21,075
would you reconnoiter
the rims with him?

594
00:32:21,116 --> 00:32:23,537
Al, I waited out there
all morning for him...

595
00:32:23,579 --> 00:32:25,683
- Is that a yes or a no?
- Yeah.

596
00:32:25,724 --> 00:32:28,276
I'd be happy to reconnoiter
the rims with him.

597
00:32:28,316 --> 00:32:30,454
And if Dan's and mine
good faith reconnoitering

598
00:32:30,492 --> 00:32:33,808
don't show the source of the gold,
do you then make restitution, Al?

599
00:32:33,851 --> 00:32:36,119
Or do I have recourse
to the agency?

600
00:32:36,155 --> 00:32:38,358
If at that point you ask,

601
00:32:38,395 --> 00:32:40,566
yes, I'll make restitution,
all rights and wrongs aside,

602
00:32:40,603 --> 00:32:42,741
'cause you've got me
by the fucking balls.

603
00:32:42,779 --> 00:32:44,688
Let me go home
and change.

604
00:32:47,003 --> 00:32:49,337
Uh, do I need
climbing gear?

605
00:32:49,371 --> 00:32:52,338
You might want
to bring a pickaxe.

606
00:32:52,378 --> 00:32:54,133
Goodbye, then.

607
00:32:55,834 --> 00:32:57,906
Make it look
like an accident.

608
00:33:01,050 --> 00:33:02,675
Ain't this
a pretty picture?

609
00:33:02,714 --> 00:33:04,601
I can't wake people
I don't know about.

610
00:33:04,634 --> 00:33:06,324
Passed out
in the public hallway.

611
00:33:06,362 --> 00:33:07,987
He never knocked
on the damn door.

612
00:33:08,026 --> 00:33:09,781
By the time I looked out
he was snoring.

613
00:33:09,818 --> 00:33:12,086
Did you want me
to drag him in by the damn heels?

614
00:33:12,122 --> 00:33:16,016
I say leave him where he is
and go about your own business.

615
00:33:16,058 --> 00:33:17,486
He's up.

616
00:33:17,530 --> 00:33:19,951
I hope you're happy.
Congratulations, cocksucker.

617
00:33:19,993 --> 00:33:22,480
Dinner's been canceled, Bill.

618
00:33:22,521 --> 00:33:24,757
All right.

619
00:33:24,793 --> 00:33:26,931
Them two fellas
got their lot bought

620
00:33:26,969 --> 00:33:29,335
and they're started
right ahead with the building.

621
00:33:29,369 --> 00:33:31,059
Sure.

622
00:33:31,097 --> 00:33:33,682
I was that shocked seeing
you sleeping out here, Bill.

623
00:33:33,721 --> 00:33:35,608
First saw you
maybe an hour ago.

624
00:33:35,640 --> 00:33:37,941
Didn't want to disturb me
and the child, Charlie.

625
00:33:37,977 --> 00:33:41,075
He must've sought entry to your room,
wherever the fuck you were at.

626
00:33:41,113 --> 00:33:44,691
I'd like to know where that goddamned
innkeep was! He could've let Bill in.

627
00:33:46,904 --> 00:33:50,067
You're not gonna
let me sleep, are ya?

628
00:33:50,104 --> 00:33:52,973
I'd would have let you sleep
as long as you wanted.

629
00:34:01,655 --> 00:34:04,021
- How's that little one?
- Good.

630
00:34:04,056 --> 00:34:07,252
She's napping.
More than I can say for you.

631
00:34:07,287 --> 00:34:10,036
Are those hardware boys
looking for extra hands?

632
00:34:10,071 --> 00:34:12,754
In a roundabout way.

633
00:34:13,814 --> 00:34:15,723
I don't agree
with this plan.

634
00:34:15,767 --> 00:34:18,035
Reconnoitering the rims
is exactly the sort of

635
00:34:18,070 --> 00:34:20,371
due diligence that Father
would ask if I'd done.

636
00:34:20,406 --> 00:34:22,772
Nor do I see the need
to involve your father.

637
00:34:22,807 --> 00:34:26,123
It was my mention of the Pinkertons
which brought Al Swearengen around

638
00:34:26,166 --> 00:34:28,980
and the Pinkertons can't come
into this unless Father does as well.

639
00:34:29,014 --> 00:34:30,955
I wouldn't even know
where to look for them.

640
00:34:30,998 --> 00:34:33,364
Ought we possibly to take
a different view of this?

641
00:34:33,398 --> 00:34:37,194
Consider we've had an adventure
costing us $20,000

642
00:34:37,238 --> 00:34:39,026
and let matters rest there.

643
00:34:39,062 --> 00:34:41,200
Let them rest?

644
00:34:41,238 --> 00:34:42,896
Yes.

645
00:34:42,933 --> 00:34:46,347
If you still want to see more
of the West, let's go now and see it.

646
00:34:46,390 --> 00:34:48,658
Or else
return to New York.

647
00:34:48,693 --> 00:34:50,515
I don't think
we should linger here.

648
00:34:50,549 --> 00:34:52,556
I have no abiding affection
for this camp.

649
00:34:52,597 --> 00:34:55,149
But I won't leave
without my money.

650
00:35:02,389 --> 00:35:04,211
Why do you take
that medicine?

651
00:35:04,244 --> 00:35:07,243
You know why,
to relieve my headaches.

652
00:35:07,284 --> 00:35:10,251
The other day I had a whopper
of a headache and I sampled a bit.

653
00:35:10,293 --> 00:35:12,081
I would hardly call

654
00:35:12,117 --> 00:35:15,662
the dull, numb, floating feeling
I experienced "relief."

655
00:35:21,044 --> 00:35:25,582
Perhaps the sexes experience
the medicine differently?

656
00:35:27,220 --> 00:35:29,074
In any case, I, um...

657
00:35:29,107 --> 00:35:31,375
hope you feel better.

658
00:35:33,043 --> 00:35:34,471
Thank you.

659
00:36:06,962 --> 00:36:08,390
E.B.

660
00:36:09,585 --> 00:36:11,243
Thanks for coming.

661
00:36:11,282 --> 00:36:13,005
Whistle...

662
00:36:13,042 --> 00:36:15,856
and I'm underfoot.
Loyal as a damn dog.

663
00:36:15,889 --> 00:36:19,434
I tell you what, Al, you got a helluva
nice turnout downstairs.

664
00:36:19,473 --> 00:36:21,709
Hell of a nice
Monday crowd.

665
00:36:30,032 --> 00:36:32,933
Jesus Christ Almighty!

666
00:36:34,513 --> 00:36:37,993
- Go ahead in, E.B.
- I'm not in dutch, am I, Al?

667
00:36:38,032 --> 00:36:39,941
Go ahead in.

668
00:37:05,167 --> 00:37:07,883
Mr. Hickok?

669
00:37:07,919 --> 00:37:11,147
I'm Nathan Gordon.

670
00:37:11,183 --> 00:37:14,117
I come up from
Murfreesborough and...

671
00:37:14,159 --> 00:37:16,362
- How are you, Nathan?
- Fine.

672
00:37:16,399 --> 00:37:18,765
See, I'll tell you
this much, Mr. Hickok,

673
00:37:18,798 --> 00:37:21,164
and I'd say the same
to the angels in heaven.

674
00:37:21,199 --> 00:37:23,303
As a stage performer,

675
00:37:23,342 --> 00:37:26,189
you cannot act
a single damn lick.

676
00:37:26,222 --> 00:37:29,004
I'd call that
a fair judgment.

677
00:37:29,038 --> 00:37:31,852
I saw you on a stage
in Hartford, Connecticut.

678
00:37:31,886 --> 00:37:34,755
And I'd have bet U.S. Currency
that you'd been strangled

679
00:37:34,798 --> 00:37:37,383
and killed, and you just
didn't know you was dead yet.

680
00:37:37,422 --> 00:37:41,033
Was you born patient,
Montana,

681
00:37:41,069 --> 00:37:42,312
or did you cultivate it?

682
00:37:42,349 --> 00:37:44,934
I guess I'm patient for labor.

683
00:37:44,973 --> 00:37:47,111
Now why tell him
that type story?

684
00:37:47,149 --> 00:37:49,604
Why I saw him perform
with Buffalo Bill Cody

685
00:37:49,645 --> 00:37:53,474
and Texas Jack Omohundro
on a stage in Hartford, Connecticut.

686
00:37:53,517 --> 00:37:55,043
Who gives a fuck?

687
00:37:55,085 --> 00:37:58,313
You think he was put on earth
to hear you run him down?

688
00:37:58,348 --> 00:37:59,842
I'm all right, friend.

689
00:37:59,885 --> 00:38:01,772
No, why don't you get
outta my sight

690
00:38:01,804 --> 00:38:04,553
before I do something
I'll fucking regret?

691
00:38:04,588 --> 00:38:06,889
I'll tell whatever kinda story
I feel like telling.

692
00:38:06,925 --> 00:38:09,128
That's right,
tell it walking.

693
00:38:09,164 --> 00:38:12,840
Anyways, me and Sol are sure
grateful you and Mr. Utter

694
00:38:12,876 --> 00:38:14,436
are taking
the time to help.

695
00:38:14,476 --> 00:38:17,225
Go ahead about your work,
Mr. Hickok.

696
00:38:17,260 --> 00:38:19,082
He won't bother you
no more.

697
00:38:19,115 --> 00:38:21,635
Charlie encourages me
being in your company.

698
00:38:21,676 --> 00:38:24,643
He feels you're
a positive influence.

699
00:38:24,683 --> 00:38:27,716
No reason
you'd remember me

700
00:38:27,755 --> 00:38:30,176
but I saw you marshal
at Abilene.

701
00:38:30,220 --> 00:38:32,838
Saw you blow one
cocksucker's head

702
00:38:32,875 --> 00:38:35,111
right the fuck
off his neck.

703
00:38:35,147 --> 00:38:37,448
I also saw you...

704
00:38:37,483 --> 00:38:39,904
dead center three bullets
on an ace of spade

705
00:38:39,947 --> 00:38:42,434
playing card
at 25 goddamned paces.

706
00:38:42,475 --> 00:38:45,409
Some other loudmouth
like this loudmouth I just sorted out,

707
00:38:45,450 --> 00:38:47,337
said you'd doctored
that playing card

708
00:38:47,370 --> 00:38:49,125
before you ever tacked it
to that tree.

709
00:38:49,163 --> 00:38:52,359
- And did you sort him out too?
- Goddamned right.

710
00:38:52,394 --> 00:38:54,914
Well, thanks
for all that help.

711
00:38:54,954 --> 00:38:56,808
Now it's time
you moved along.

712
00:38:56,842 --> 00:38:59,143
I sorted him out proper.

713
00:38:59,177 --> 00:39:02,210
Gouged out the both
of his fucking eyes.

714
00:39:02,250 --> 00:39:05,381
- All right, friend!
- Move, I'm tired of listening to you.

715
00:39:05,418 --> 00:39:07,752
You're tired of listening?

716
00:39:07,785 --> 00:39:10,337
- That's what he said.
- Oh.

717
00:39:10,378 --> 00:39:12,549
I guess everybody's
talking to me now.

718
00:39:12,585 --> 00:39:14,210
Get the fuck outta here!

719
00:39:14,249 --> 00:39:15,972
All right, I hear you,
Wild Bill.

720
00:39:16,009 --> 00:39:18,659
You don't need
to insult me twice.

721
00:39:23,401 --> 00:39:24,829
I'll tell you what,

722
00:39:24,873 --> 00:39:26,498
I hope you get
what's coming to you

723
00:39:26,537 --> 00:39:28,446
and I hope it's sooner
rather than later.

724
00:39:28,488 --> 00:39:31,171
I hope they
sort you out!

725
00:39:31,208 --> 00:39:33,574
And I get to see it!

726
00:39:33,608 --> 00:39:36,193
I hope you're gut shot
and die slow!

727
00:39:36,232 --> 00:39:38,687
And I hope they get you
in this camp!

728
00:39:47,079 --> 00:39:49,380
Hand me... hand me some
of them pegs, would you?

729
00:39:49,415 --> 00:39:51,836
Hey, want some pegs,
Bill?

730
00:39:54,344 --> 00:39:56,383
I'm gonna desert you.

731
00:40:04,454 --> 00:40:06,657
Play some poker.

732
00:40:06,695 --> 00:40:09,280
Drink some whiskey.

733
00:40:09,319 --> 00:40:11,228
Thanks for your help.

734
00:40:11,271 --> 00:40:14,172
See ya later, Charlie.

735
00:40:14,214 --> 00:40:16,101
All right, Bill.

736
00:40:16,134 --> 00:40:18,654
Ready, lift.

737
00:40:20,294 --> 00:40:21,919
Oh, there we go.

738
00:40:29,382 --> 00:40:31,553
For having nothing to do
with him,

739
00:40:31,589 --> 00:40:33,955
these hardware cocksuckers

740
00:40:33,990 --> 00:40:35,899
sure seem to be joined
to Hickok at the hip.

741
00:40:35,941 --> 00:40:37,948
You made your judgment
on that situation.

742
00:40:37,990 --> 00:40:39,745
And I believe you
judged correct.

743
00:40:39,781 --> 00:40:41,504
No connection
between them and him?

744
00:40:41,541 --> 00:40:45,119
Or between any of them,
and these new saloon people?

745
00:40:45,157 --> 00:40:46,782
You saw it like that
and I did too.

746
00:40:46,821 --> 00:40:48,609
To the best of the both
of our thinking.

747
00:40:48,645 --> 00:40:50,783
- Which was important to me.
- Which was?

748
00:40:50,821 --> 00:40:52,762
- What?
- When you said "which was,"

749
00:40:52,804 --> 00:40:54,691
I didn't follow
what you were asking.

750
00:40:54,724 --> 00:40:57,789
I wasn't asking nothing.
I was saying.

751
00:40:57,828 --> 00:40:59,737
I didn't have full information

752
00:40:59,780 --> 00:41:01,721
so your impression
on this was important.

753
00:41:01,796 --> 00:41:03,900
Someone I could trust.

754
00:41:06,820 --> 00:41:08,543
What's wrong?

755
00:41:08,580 --> 00:41:10,140
What's the matter?

756
00:41:10,180 --> 00:41:12,219
- My palms are damp.
- They're always damp.

757
00:41:12,259 --> 00:41:15,903
- Yes, sir.
- So is something wrong?

758
00:41:15,940 --> 00:41:18,525
No, no.

759
00:41:26,531 --> 00:41:30,360
Well, the Great Prospector's
found his second wind.

760
00:41:33,122 --> 00:41:36,285
You tell me, Al.
Have you a doubt or misgiving?

761
00:41:36,323 --> 00:41:38,330
You tell me.

762
00:41:38,371 --> 00:41:41,338
Generally, if I have
a misgiving or a doubt,

763
00:41:41,378 --> 00:41:45,501
I kill the cocksucker I have
a doubt and misgiving about.

764
00:41:45,539 --> 00:41:47,327
But these are special
circumstances.

765
00:41:47,363 --> 00:41:49,883
I don't know what you mean
by "special circumstances."

766
00:41:49,922 --> 00:41:53,085
If I want to, I can burn
the whole fucking camp down.

767
00:41:53,122 --> 00:41:55,194
- Yes, you can.
- Cut your throat first,

768
00:41:55,234 --> 00:41:58,332
and then burn down
the whole fucking camp.

769
00:41:58,370 --> 00:42:01,686
- You can...
- I don't know what the fuck you mean.

770
00:42:01,729 --> 00:42:03,768
I mean, short of
burning it all down,

771
00:42:03,809 --> 00:42:05,783
you gotta trust someone.

772
00:42:14,785 --> 00:42:16,988
- What were you doing over there?
- Where?

773
00:42:17,025 --> 00:42:18,617
- Where?
- At the Bella Union?

774
00:42:18,657 --> 00:42:20,249
Get an impression,
scouting.

775
00:42:20,289 --> 00:42:23,038
Listen to me,
listen to me.

776
00:42:23,073 --> 00:42:24,665
I was the go-between,
it was me.

777
00:42:24,705 --> 00:42:26,744
But without
malicious intention.

778
00:42:40,448 --> 00:42:42,106
Well...

779
00:42:42,143 --> 00:42:44,117
I confess
to being winded.

780
00:42:47,103 --> 00:42:48,990
Oh no, Dan.

781
00:42:49,023 --> 00:42:50,299
No.

782
00:42:50,335 --> 00:42:51,796
No.

783
00:42:53,791 --> 00:42:55,613
Mother.

784
00:43:00,031 --> 00:43:03,675
Simple greed. One less hotel in camp,
shorten up the room supply.

785
00:43:03,710 --> 00:43:05,782
No conspiracy,
no betrayal.

786
00:43:07,358 --> 00:43:10,227
If you're gonna murder me,
I'd appreciate a quick dying.

787
00:43:10,271 --> 00:43:12,409
And not getting ate
by the pigs...

788
00:43:12,447 --> 00:43:15,163
in case there is
resurrection of the flesh.

789
00:43:21,949 --> 00:43:24,053
Stay friendly
with them cocksuckers.

790
00:43:24,094 --> 00:43:26,166
With them
Bella Union people?

791
00:43:26,206 --> 00:43:28,180
Can't help yourself,
can you?

792
00:43:52,124 --> 00:43:55,189
You fell,
but you'll be all right.

793
00:43:55,229 --> 00:43:58,011
I'm gonna
take care of you.

794
00:43:58,044 --> 00:44:00,083
Hold on a second.

795
00:44:00,124 --> 00:44:01,650
No hollering.

796
00:44:33,275 --> 00:44:34,801
I'll take care of you.

797
00:44:35,803 --> 00:44:37,112
Now, hush.

798
00:44:47,739 --> 00:44:51,797
Tina and Molly can be quiet
if you want him kept company.

799
00:44:51,833 --> 00:44:54,702
That man's already
doing all he wants to.

800
00:44:56,058 --> 00:44:57,967
If I send him anyone,
it'd be you.

801
00:45:10,905 --> 00:45:12,333
Are you loaded, Leon?

802
00:45:12,377 --> 00:45:14,231
Well on the path,
Mr. Tolliver.

803
00:45:14,264 --> 00:45:16,652
That man at The Gem
has got some serious shit.

804
00:45:16,696 --> 00:45:19,445
I know when you make
your first report on us to him,

805
00:45:19,480 --> 00:45:22,643
you'll remember
to say thanks.

806
00:45:22,681 --> 00:45:26,259
I hope you're not too fucked up
to deal the deuce for us, Leon.

807
00:45:26,296 --> 00:45:28,303
Opium ain't been
made yet, Mr. Sawyer,

808
00:45:28,344 --> 00:45:30,285
that can fuck me up
that bad.

809
00:45:32,792 --> 00:45:34,417
I'll tug his reins.

810
00:45:34,456 --> 00:45:38,612
- I hope our hero wins.
- Count on it.

811
00:45:45,111 --> 00:45:47,566
If Bill comes,

812
00:45:47,608 --> 00:45:50,291
I'm gonna move you

813
00:45:50,327 --> 00:45:53,774
to that nice pallet
over there,

814
00:45:53,815 --> 00:45:56,335
only 'cause he's far too big for it
and so too would I be.

815
00:45:56,375 --> 00:46:00,149
So if you wake up on the pallet,
that's what happened.

816
00:46:00,183 --> 00:46:01,873
And him and me
being where we are

817
00:46:01,910 --> 00:46:03,949
is the circumstances
of the room, period.

818
00:46:03,990 --> 00:46:05,812
And the grownups
are just sleeping.

819
00:46:05,847 --> 00:46:09,840
But don't be afraid to...
to... to wake me up.

820
00:46:12,694 --> 00:46:14,003
All right.

821
00:46:18,294 --> 00:46:21,839
Sweetheart, go to sleep.

822
00:46:26,773 --> 00:46:28,333
I'm right here.

823
00:46:40,405 --> 00:46:43,088
Not too fucking
deep, huh?

824
00:46:43,125 --> 00:46:44,685
I won't.

825
00:46:44,725 --> 00:46:46,350
Trust.

826
00:46:47,413 --> 00:46:49,616
Hell of a way
to operate, huh?

827
00:46:49,653 --> 00:46:52,173
Learning at all the ins
and outs of getting killed.

828
00:46:54,164 --> 00:46:56,585
Not too fucking deep.

829
00:47:05,012 --> 00:47:07,630
Every fucking beating
I'm grateful for.

830
00:47:07,668 --> 00:47:09,609
Every fucking
one of them.

831
00:47:10,708 --> 00:47:13,260
Get all the trust
beat outta you.

832
00:47:15,379 --> 00:47:17,615
Then you know what
the fucking world is.

833
00:47:20,147 --> 00:47:22,797
Al, open up,
it's me, it's Dan!

834
00:47:24,659 --> 00:47:26,960
You're gonna wanna
hear this, open up!

835
00:47:31,283 --> 00:47:33,170
Come in, sit down.

836
00:47:44,306 --> 00:47:47,153
- Well, it's a mixed report.
- You just tell me, is it done?

837
00:47:47,186 --> 00:47:49,225
Oh, it's done.

838
00:47:49,266 --> 00:47:50,727
Yeah, he's gone.

839
00:47:50,770 --> 00:47:52,231
So what's the mixture?

840
00:47:52,274 --> 00:47:55,372
He went owning one hell
of a fucking gold strike.

841
00:48:03,314 --> 00:48:05,168
Where's the dude now?

842
00:48:05,201 --> 00:48:07,110
Splattered at the bottom
of the ridge.

843
00:48:07,153 --> 00:48:09,487
Ride back out.
Bring him back in at dawn.

844
00:48:09,521 --> 00:48:11,081
All right.

845
00:48:15,985 --> 00:48:17,708
Trixie!

846
00:48:24,752 --> 00:48:27,086
You want the other foot?

847
00:48:27,120 --> 00:48:28,494
Yeah.

848
00:48:28,529 --> 00:48:30,416
Please.

849
00:48:42,191 --> 00:48:45,419
♪ Kick off your high heels ♪

850
00:48:45,455 --> 00:48:48,967
♪ Careful where you stand ♪

851
00:48:54,319 --> 00:48:57,318
♪ Kick off your high heels ♪

852
00:48:57,359 --> 00:49:00,358
♪ Careful where you stand ♪

853
00:49:05,326 --> 00:49:11,523
♪ Don't you move too close,
I'm a twisted little man ♪

854
00:49:18,062 --> 00:49:23,396
♪ Heaven help me,
I know what I am ♪

855
00:49:28,525 --> 00:49:35,748
♪ Don't you move too close,
I'm a twisted little man. ♪

