I raise 100.
Back 100.
That man's overplaying
his hand.
All right.
Whatever the fuck
I got left.
420 back to you.
As advertised,
you got more nerve
than sense, huh, Bill?
What have you got?
The man stays
on fours.
And they call this
a game of skill?
Well, you got me,
didn't you, Bill?
You son of a bitch!
You were told
about that talk.
Go eat, Jack.
All right.
I thank you
for that kindness.
You just bought yourself
something with that.
Some boys can't go near a cliff
without jumping off.
20 to the dealer.
Much appreciated.
Any ideas for the rest?
I believe
I'll stay with cash.
Montana.
No rest for the wicked.
Well, what are you
doing up?
Well, it's cooler working now.
Quieter.
Sorry you had to listen
to them drunken fools before,
Mr. Hickok.
When you and Mr. Utter
was helping us?
I come through unharmed.
And Bill would be easier
on my nerves.
Mr. Hickok makes me look
for the warrant in your hand.
All right.
Montana okay with you?
The only other nickname
I ever had was "Sloth."
Don't seem to fit.
Choice was among
the seven sins.
I guess I got out
before the others surfaced.
Camp looks like
a good bet.
My wife and boy
are with their people in Michigan.
I hope I can
bring 'em out soon.
They'll get the Sioux
making peace.
Pretty quick
you'll have laws here
and every other
damn thing.
I'll just settle
for property rights.
Will ya?
I'm recently married
myself.
Is that so?
The missus
operates a circus.
She's in Cincinnati
waiting for word
of my success.
Sol and I put our last sifting cradle
aside for you.
Why don't you go ahead
and use it, Bill?
What slows me down
is thinking
about freezing my balls off
in a creek.
Or the cocksuckers
I'd would lose the gold to at poker.
I'm flat out tired.
Turn in.
I got her covered.
I believe I will.
Good night, Montana.
Good night, Bill.
My pop
called me "Kite."
I was supposed to leave for Cheyenne
two damn hours ago!
What kept you,
Charlie?
You don't fuckin' sleep!
I don't know what in the fuck
is happening to you, Bill.
So you stayed in camp
to tuck me in?
If you don't
want to prospect,
I could put you in charge
of that mail route I'm gettin'.
I'm doing
what I wanna do.
Bullshit!
Some goddamned time,
a man's due to stop
arguing with hisself,
feeling he's twice
the goddamned fool he knows he is
because he can't
be something he tries to be
every goddamned day without once
getting to dinnertime
and not fucking it up.
I don't wanna fight it
no more.
Understand me,
Charlie?
And I don't want you
pissing in my ear about it.
Can you let me go to hell
the way I want to?
Yeah.
I can do that.
Good luck in Cheyenne.
Good luck
to you, too, Bill.
You know me, Al.
I don't scrutinize
or second guess.
If you wanted
to explain
why I'm to buy the dude
out of a worthless claim,
- I'd surely listen.
- Jesus Christ.
What is it?
The dude must've had
some kind of accident.
My word.
- Looks dead, don't he?
- Yes.
See, my reasoning was,
get the dude his money back,
keep him from asking in
the Pinkertons.
Well, appears now
that's unnecessary.
Make the offer
to the wife.
Al, once that dope fiend
throws her skirts over her head
and hightails back to New York,
you think she'll give one wet fart
about what happened at this camp,
let alone send
the Pinkertons out?
And 20,000's
a lot of money.
Let me tell you,
several things, E.B.
First, $20,000
is a lot of money.
Second,
it's my fucking money.
Third, the widow,
being a dope fiend,
might let matters rest.
But fourth,
well, this camp has a lot more
to offer me than $20,000
as long as I don't get killed
by the fucking Pinkertons.
Why take the chance?
Go see to the grieving
fucking widow.
All right, sir.
Mrs. Garret?
What a tragic turn.
Do you require
Dr. Cochran?
To treat
your terrible grief?
Yes. I would like
to see the doctor.
Of course,
who wouldn't?
I'll get him
right away.
Ask him, before
he sees me please,
to examine
my husband's injuries.
I'd like his opinion
on how they were sustained.
I assume your husband
died in a fall.
All I asked you to do was get
the goddamned doctor.
Of course, madam.
Is that what happened,
Mr. Dority?
A tragic turn?
Terrible,
accidental fall?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Oh yes.
Come on, stupid.
She wouldn't have
nothing to do with me, Al.
She told E.B.
To have Doc
go over the body.
You think he smells
the gold?
Nah.
E.B.'s too busy
sniffin'
what he can steal
being go-between.
Whereas you, Dan,
you show me foresight,
and loyalty,
the way you handled
making the find.
Just know
when I'm outta my depth.
Amateur.
Comes on a lark to dabble,
and falls to his death
from the ridge.
Yet the widow
suspects foul play.
I know Al wants
her leaving here
with as least of a sour taste
in her mouth as possible.
Wouldn't you expect
her husband's death
to be sour on her tongue
no matter how it happened?
Question's whether
it's fate she blames,
or people in the camp.
What are you looking for?
Morning, Seth.
When did you get up?
I didn't go to sleep.
The woman that newspaperman
pointed out to us yesterday
just lost her husband.
Fella bought the gold claim
at Swearengen's?
Innkeep just took the body
down to the doc's.
You weren't twiddlin'
your thumbs overnight, were you?
I've brought the doctor.
Please, come in,
Doctor.
I'm very sorry
about your husband.
Was he murdered?
I was told that he fell
from a ridge.
He had skull fractures
consistent with that.
Not been wounded
by bullets nor strangled.
No other sign
of foul play.
Leaving
how he came to fall?
As to that
I have no opinion.
And yet...
in treating me,
you were so full
of opinion.
You took the most
comprehensive view.
I said you needn't
make up symptoms
to get the laudanum
you want...
Perhaps,
you don't feel
at such perfect liberty
to opine
on my husband's case
as you did on mine.
Do other considerations
constrain you?
Do other men?
I do not know
how your husband's skull
got caved in.
You're a bright woman,
aren't you?
Must've gone
through hell here.
Go on home,
Mrs. Garret.
What's her mood?
Who is it?
Mr. Farnum,
Mrs. Garret.
May I be
of further service?
Once I've determined
my plans.
I'll certainly need
a coffin.
- I'll see to it.
- Thank you.
What is it?
Would you open
the door, ma'am?
I would like to say
something to your face.
I'm overcome with remorse,
Mrs. Garret,
that I failed to change
the course of events.
It was me your husband
outbid for the claim.
If it will simplify
your situation in any way,
I renew my offer
at $12,000.
I know it won't
bring him back.
No.
We both know that.
You'll have
your answer shortly.
All right, madam.
Is this
Mr. Hickok's room?
Who's asking?
My husband's just died
under suspicious circumstances.
Suspect someone else.
When Bill's killed a man,
he says so and states his reasons.
I don't
suspect him.
My husband had tried
to engage Mr. Hickok,
just before his death
and I thought,
though they hadn't
come to terms,
perhaps Mr. Hickok
would be willing
to advise me on my
current situation.
I'd pay whatever fee
he thought appropriate.
To talk to you?
I have no one else
in the camp.
I'll get him.
He's sleepin' one off.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about
your husband.
May I ask your name?
- Jane.
- Thank you, Jane.
Wait in your room.
It'll take him a while
to get the phlegm situated.
All right.
I'm sure you don't need me
explaining a place like ours.
A doc in frequent
attendance
can sow the seeds
of doubt.
All depends on your standards
of hygiene.
We want 'em shiny.
Make no mistake.
There's a wide range
of "normal."
Friday and Saturday mornings
and the mid-week day
of your choice
will be right for us.
I can... I can
work that out.
So what does Swearengen
pay for a visit?
$20 for routine call,
all girls in.
Ah. And what's his idea
of routine,
once every three
or four months?
Anyway, how's uh...
$50 a visit sound,
three times a week?
Done.
Lubricants.
Well, armed and ready,
madam.
Thanks very much.
Howdy.
Howdy yourself.
You the operator?
Cy Tolliver.
Name's Crane.
And I'd like a room,
I'd like exclusive
use of the safe
and I'd like
to shoot some dice.
I'd like to think
this is the first day
of a long friendship,
Mr. Crane.
We'll get you a room.
If you'll step into my office
we'll meet
your needs for a safe.
Help you
with your luggage.
Suitcases
go to the room.
Expect you'll
keep the valise.
Keep what you
"expect" to yourself
and you'll improve our chances
at that friendship.
- Young man.
- How are you, Cy?
Done some good work
on this place.
Eddie's work.
Hey, Andy.
Hello, sweetheart.
So let's go,
let's get something working.
We could rob Cy.
How 'bout a bath first
and a nap...
- and sex with an unfamiliar woman?
- Sure.
Signal when ready,
commander.
If I didn't make my point, I'd like
to get something fucking working.
Sure, Andy.
How's Andy look?
Like he spent three weeks
on a wagon.
I'm optimistic, Al.
And she's promised
a prompt reply.
I'd have thought
she'd say yes on the spot.
You did offer her
the whole 20?
How can you even
ask me that?
- E. B?
- I offered 12.
Did I ask you
to play her?
Can't you follow one
simple fucking instruction?
She will take the 12, Al,
and be happy to get it.
And all you'll
have to decide
is how much of the eight
you saved should go to me.
- You're incorrigible.
- I do my best.
I'll go with the 12.
She says yes, there should be
something in this for you.
Hint at the amount.
Don't get ahead
of yourself, E.B.
When she signs
the bill of sale,
and you come back here
and sign it over to me...
It is your 12 after all.
Once all that's done,
you should walk
outta here with 2,000.
Fair recompense.
For saving me money
in spite of myself.
I suggested to my husband
just last night
that we should try
to view our time here
as one experience
bought at a single price.
Even now he's murdered,
I feel that.
That to stake
the boundaries
at... at just that fact
is impossible.
For one, this camp
hasn't any laws or courts.
If it did, I've no evidence.
I'd have tried to take
the thing all whole if they
hadn't offered on the claim.
To receive their money,
would be a separate matter,
make me an accomplice
of another sort.
How have you been
an accomplice till now?
A wife inevitably feels
she's had some part
in what befalls her husband.
I'm answerable hereafter,
on different terms.
I need to know
what I'd be selling them.
You don't believe the money's
to keep the Pinkertons away?
Why pay me?
If it were a ransom
to keep the Pinkertons off,
why not pay Brom
instead of killing him?
It's this saloon operator
you think is pulling the strings?
Al Swearengen, it was certainly he
manipulating Brom.
The slimy
limey cocksucker.
All right, ma'am.
True sounding's
not guaranteed
but I'll try
for a feel of the bottom.
What shall I pay you,
Mr. Hickok?
I prefer you pick
the figure.
- Is $100 enough?
- Perfect.
Whiskey.
And how'd they take
to the craps game?
Like chimps
at their first fire.
Downstairs.
Thank you, Dan.
I'm Al Swearengen,
Mr. Hickok.
In the last few days,
I've been locked
in my room weeping,
searching my memories
as to where my path
might have crossed yours previous.
And as to how
I might have given offense
that you stay in this camp
not 50 feet from my joint
and never once walk in.
No poker.
Is it that simple?
Dan, dismantle the titty corner
and set up a poker table.
Not necessary,
Mr. Swearengen.
I always felt poker
slows a joint's action.
Bit of liquor, pussy,
and faro made my
entire fuckin' career,
but certain people
I do respect.
This man Garret,
who fell off the rocks...
The Eastern dude.
His widow's had an offer
on his claim
from that innkeeper
sitting in the corner.
But she's reluctant
to sell
till she understands
what's behind it.
Why have you
asked me?
She believes
you'd know.
Her husband came here
with childish ideas.
Bought himself a gold claim
with me an honest broker.
Claim pinches out,
which will happen.
But he can't take that like a man,
has to blame somebody.
Seller's left camp
so he picks on me.
Says he'll bring in
the Pinkertons
if I don't offer
restitution.
I got a healthy operation here,
and I didn't build it
brooding on the right
and wrong of things.
I do not need the Pinkertons
descending like locusts.
So I bend over for
the tenderfoot cocksucker.
"Reconnoiter
your claim fully," I say,
"and then,
if you're still unhappy,
I will give you
your fucking money back."
And the tenderfoot agrees.
Just as he's finishing
his reconnoiter,
cocksucker falls to his death.
Pure fucking accident.
But up jumps the widow
in righteous indignation.
Wants the doctor to examine him
for murder wounds.
My visions
of locusts return.
I see Pinkertons
coming in swarms.
Commissioned
by the widow.
Who I recognize is grieving,
and has better intentions probably
than to hold
on the truth.
How's the innkeep
come to make the offer?
Underbidder
on the sale I brokered
still believes
in the claim.
Even though the gold
is pinched out?
Well, this camp's
expanding.
We've already had
one hotel close.
He sees the property
as real estate.
I'll take this back
to the widow.
I only hope you
show it to her
in a favorable
fucking light.
What's that worth?
What?
The light
I show it in?
What's it
worth to you?
Why, Wild Bill.
They certainly don't
appear to be at odds.
What happened
to this little one
was the same
exact cocksucker.
Same as he was
pulling the strings
in your husband's fleecing
and gettin' him killed,
this Swearengen
operated the road agents
that done for this
little one's people.
Oh, poor child.
To lose her family,
to see them slaughtered.
Very same cocksucker.
It's Bill.
You stole off on me.
I had to come in here
to look after the little one.
I thought she might
want me present.
Yes, l... I'm
very grateful.
Didn't happen to put one
right between the shithead's eyes,
now did ya, Bill?
Unless you need the money
right away,
I'd defer a decision
until someone honest
and competent
did a second reconnoiter.
May I commission you?
Some question my fitness
on either count,
but I'll guarantee you
I'm not competent.
I do know
someone I trust to ask.
Please do.
Name's Bullock.
I'll go talk to him now.
How'd you leave it
with the cocksucker, Bill?
On terms
he'd understand.
Al, watchin' you
even at a distance
was a pleasure
and privilege.
If she don't come back to you
with an answer inside an hour,
you pay a call on her.
But Hickok's an ally,
am I right?
I mean if that wasn't
a damn ally leavin'
my eyes completely
deceived me.
- An hour, E.B.
- Yes, sir.
Pour me a drink.
And ask me the key
to a long life.
What is it?
Most important human quality
for a person to reach old age?
I'll buy the drink
if you tell me.
Same as a dog
who keeps his nose.
Don't poke it
where it don't belong.
Wise words.
A lesson hard to come by,
but thoroughly learned.
Something else I know.
My knowing what I know
and somebody else
knowing it,
is two entirely
different things.
I'm near losing your trail,
Ellsworth.
Say somebody thought I saw
something I shouldn't have.
- Whereabouts?
- On a ridge.
A man, pushed off
or whatever the hell else.
If it meant
my leaving camp
to prove I could
mind my own business,
it'd be a friend
who told me that...
instead of throwing me
to the pigs.
It's my whole philosophy
and outlook.
Make use of it
as you will.
Well, well, if he...
if he was here
sealing an appearance
arrangement,
then I'm glad it was you
that tied him up, Al,
not that new
fucking operation,
what with them fancy signs
and cleaned-up women
where I heard he was
gambling all night.
We made no appearance
agreement.
Well, uh...
- you and... you and Hickok...
- No.
Oh, I see.
Well, I mean, because
his game at my place yesterday
was this far
from coming to lead.
Him and this droop-eyed
hoople-head.
And I had
to shut it down.
I mean, if that gives him
offense or umbrage,
well, I can't worry
about his plans
as far as where he decides
to gamble elsewhere,
or this new joint
overwhelms the camp.
We made no agreement.
What do you think
of the new joint?
Nice sign.
This far from
fucking gunplay.
Jack fuckin' high!
That's what I have.
I bet every
fuckin' cent.
Miracle to me is you sit here
bragging about it.
I ain't braggin',
or a braggart,
or a blowhard.
I state a fact,
I live by a fact...
Anyways, it's over.
Yeah, you believe that because
you're a walkin' fuckin' cunt!
With your cunt...
your eye movin'.
No matter how
your day's going, Jack,
you're always fun
to talk to.
Give me a buck
then, Lou.
Send me off
for a meal.
Give me a buck, see
what part of you gets shot
because l...
I possess a fuckin' gun
that I didn't bet.
I'll pay you $5 for that gun,
sight unseen.
'Cause what you need
is a stake to make your comeback.
That'll get you out of this
brown study you're in.
What'd you
take off of me?
The tag from
your new suit.
All right then.
Name a price.
If it's close to fair,
I'll pay it.
For the suit?
For your gun.
No, I believe not.
I believe no.
He too is God's
handiwork.
Oh, double fucking
solitaire.
Where's your
fucking ballgowns?
Bring a bunch a chips
over here
and let's get
a poker game going!
I don't know
this camp.
I'd have to bring
someone from Montana.
Would the widow
give it that much time?
Yeah, she would.
She don't wanna be
stupid or fooled.
Wants to stand up
for her husband
better than he stood up
for himself.
Not that she ought
to stick around.
Far as that goes,
she could sign a proxy.
There's her $100 in it.
And what that saloonkeeper
gave me if you'd wanna take it on.
All right.
I guess she's all right
till that saloonkeep decides
I can't be trusted
to betray her interests.
Trust ain't
his long suit.
She oughta be
lookin' for a wagon.
Thanks for the favor,
Montana.
Sure.
I like Ellsworth, too.
There's a difference
between talking a lot,
which Ellsworth
does enjoy,
and oversteppin'.
He don't get into
other people's business.
Then what are we
talkin' about, Dan?
Well, my own standards
as to who's reliable
ain't the same
as Al's.
So Ellsworth has to leave camp
over the difference?
Yeah, he does if it's that
or kill him.
He said tell him
if those was the choices.
Don't you do it.
Which?
Either.
Asks a bribe for something
he never intends to do.
Takes my 150
then tells her not to sell.
Why are you so sure
he told her not to?
You went back there,
you knocked on her door.
She said Hickok reported
his conversation with you.
But she wasn't prepared yet
to give me an answer.
Does this make sense
to you, huh?
She pays Hickok
to come talk to me.
He goes back,
tells her to sell.
And then she says she needs more time
to make up her mind.
That idiot couldn't
put one in his ear.
If you're talking
about Tom Mason,
I'd say that's water
under the bridge.
I'd say Hickok has to die
if I have to kill him myself.
Jesus, Al.
With all that's going on?
How would it sit
with the widow, for one thing?
How would that
dispose her toward us?
Let me pose you a question,
E.B., you fuckin' cunt!
Someone comes at you,
what are you supposed to do about it?
And I pose you a question back,
Al Swearengen!
If a friend, or at least
a professional colleague,
has a mistaken impression
of who's coming at him
and who isn't, what are you
supposed to do then, huh?!
You don't think
he's coming at me?
I don't think Hickok's
coming at ya, Al.
No, I don't.
I think you're a man
with so many different responsibilities
you sometimes
get feeling beset.
And in that frame of mind,
take things personal.
I'd sooner the cocksucker was dead.
Simplify working the widow.
We don't get to choose
the world we live in.
Bella Union cocksuckers
to worry about
and every other
damn thing.
Well, you got
a full plate.
I need to fuck
something.
Trixie!
Hey, hey, hey!
Get the bottle.
That's using
your old noggin, Al.
Get yourself
some relief.
Let the world
do its own spinnin'.
Don't be pointing
your fucking thumb for me.
Me and you done
talked that subject out.
What's new, Dan?
Nothing.
No news at all?
If I had somethin' to tell you,
one way or another,
I'd tell it to you.
Well then I reckon
I'll have another drink.
Who is it?
It's Joanie.
Wait a second, honey.
Give me just
a second.
I fell asleep.
I broke up
three catfights, Andy.
Girls wanting
to give you a bath.
I fell right the hell
to sleep.
You ready to meet
some strange?
Tell you the truth,
Joanie, I'm...
feelin' outta sorts.
Well, you had
a long trip.
And I've heard
worse confessions.
That's the gospel truth.
Which I hope
you'll keep to yourself.
Yeah, sure I will, Andy.
I feel fucking
unwell to myself.
Won't you lie back
and let me get your boots off?
I don't think you should
touch me, honey.
That's the gospel
on that score.
No girl in the world
ever got sick
pulling off a pair of boots,
Andy.
But if you want,
I won't take more liberties.
$50 an issue.
Well, uh, frankly, sir,
that-that would purchase
your advertisement an amount
of space wildly incommensurate
with the accompanying articles.
See? I never heard
that word in my life.
That's his trade, Cy,
he's a wordsmith.
Do you shoot craps,
Mr. Merrick?
Excuse me?
Oh, oh, oh no!
Ah, no, I haven't shot
the craps in sometime.
Perhaps never?
If you'll keep
my secret, sir.
No, I've never
shot them.
Maybe that would
make an article:
A man learns
to shoot the craps.
Well, we're agreed
on $50 an issue.
Have we
actually agreed?
I feel almost duty-bound
to remonstrate you, sir.
Three months
in advance, Eddie.
$50 an issue.
Let's see the man
with the cash.
Seriously?
Don't let him take your money,
Mr. Merrick,
while he's teaching you
this game.
Who did you give
to Andy?
Nobody.
He's poorly.
Does he need
a doctor?
Maybe he does.
God damn it!
I told you I didn't like
the way he looked!
Stand outside room eight,
no one in or out.
Get the doc.
Tell him... someone fell.
I told you.
Thank you
for your help.
I'll look forward
to Mr. Bullock contacting me.
May I ask, ma'am,
when you'd expect
to leave the camp?
I'm not certain.
Bullock is honorable.
You can trust him
to see to your interests.
He couldn't come more
highly recommended.
You know the sound
of thunder, don't you?
Of course.
Can you imagine that sound
if I ask you to?
I can, Mr. Hickok.
Your husband and me
had this talk.
And I told him to head home
to avoid a dark result.
But I didn't say it
in thunder.
Ma'am...
listen to the thunder.
Very good luck to you.
Thank you for all your help,
Mr. Hickok.
- Thanks for coming, Doc.
- The boy said someone fell?
Room eight.
It's Jane, Bill.
Come ahead.
This little one's
cool as a cucumber.
Is that so?
Feel this little one's
forehead.
Fever and you parted ways,
young lady.
Did she just asked
to borrow money?
Anyways, how'd it go
with Bullock?
He'll help the widow.
Good for him.
Good for you.
- Did you tell her so?
- Hmm.
You think
she'd want company?
I'll bet
she'd enjoy yours.
Maybe she'd enjoy...
feelin' the little one's
forehead.
You're probably enjoying
your damn privacy
with Charlie headed
for Cheyenne.
I'm writing my wife.
Why didn't you say
something, damn you!
I owe you a penny.
So long, Jane.
So long, Bill.
All right,
breathe big breaths.
Oh, my back!
Oh, my aching back.
I'm gonna get you
something to ease that.
What's he got, Doc?
I guess it's his back
is what he landed on
when he fell.
My back is sweating
and broken.
I don't know
what he landed on.
Wait, who said
he fell?
Course, if little
pussy sores
rise up on his trunk
and his face,
more likely
he's got other trouble.
- Oh, give me a game. How I ache.
- Okay, Andy.
I'm gonna give you
somethin' to ease that.
You lost your friend
in the fire.
Hey!
Hey, Winkie!
Hey, wait a minute.
Does that look
American to you?
No, this ain't.
People don't eat
this shit!
It touched...
Meow, meow.
Aw hell.
Boys.
Howdy, Bill.
My father was
the best company.
From the time
I was ever so little.
Problems or...
difficulties or even
sadness, no such thing.
Not permitted.
The evening I was
presented to society
I found out later
he'd been able to attend
only by physically fleeing
some dismal legal difficulty.
In that sense,
my marriage to Mr. Garret
was a tremendous solution.
Tremendous.
At the ceremony I remember
father whispered to me,
"Darling...
I can never repay you
for what you are about to do
but I can repay
everyone else."
And he said,
"To think of you, with him,
in that godforsaken place
is almost unbearable."
Meaning your husband?
And I said,
"Maybe he'll die."
Take that,
God damn you!
Hang the bastard!
What happened?
He shot
Wild Bill Hickok.
Hey yah!
Do you see that?
? Life feels so empty ?
? You feel all alone ?
? How did I wander ?
? So far from my home? ?
? These thoughts
run through me ?
? Stolen my faith ?
? Please help me,
my Father ?
? For I've fallen
from grace. ?