Sync and corrections by kay sukri
(SIGHS)
Jake, hold on, buddy.
Cheer up, Finn.
So what if Jake got absorbed into
Slime Princess's rockin' body.
He's probably having fun
and doing way better without you.
Give me the Slime jewel.
(SING-SONG VOICE) Hooray!
Just two more of these
sweet princess jewels,
and I'll be able to fix everything.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
Your laugh is really annoying.
I changed my mind.
Skyhook me back to Slime Kingdom.
Ah!
Don't talk that way about the skyhooks!
Focus, Finn.
You're right. Let's go
get that Fire jewel.
Please keep your hands and bags
away from the cloud's edge.
Ding-ding.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
LSP: No!
Don't torture yourself.
And don't drop your phone
into Fire Kingdom, dummy.
Hey, I'm feeling some of my old zazzle.
Enough to cast the strongest
flame shield to protect you.
If I don't, you'll die. (CHUCKLES)
(RECITES INCANTATION)
(SCREAMS)
Pbht!
Look, guys. My Ice
powers are tapping out,
what with all the elemental
fire magic down there.
But I would never ever let you
down, so I'm sending Gunter.
Wenk.
So, you guys want to do something?
You got any music?
You guys aren't just like
boring and old, right?
Finn, wait for me!
This doesn't look so bad.
Ooh!
You see that bird?
Gross.
LSP? Be careful.
You don't have Flame shield.
Eh, it's fine. I've been in, like,
all four zones without a scratch.
Huh, that's weird.
No, I'm just super cool.
(SCREAMING)
Whoa! Tiny warrior.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
Oh, no, you don't!
Oof.
Show your face, you... Wyatt?
What are you doing?
I'm Fire Wyatt.
I got rage!
You cannot defeat me!
(GROWLS)
- Let's take his armor.
- Okay.
Wenk.
(GROANS) I'm going, but I
swear vengeance, okay?
Cool.
(GRUNTING)
Your cooking stinks.
Aah!
So sick of your face!
(SCREAMING)
Man, this place used to be nice... er.
(GROWLS)
(SPEAKING KOREAN)
Lady Raini... er, Flameicorn.
It's me... Finn.
I got important news about Jake...
Oof!
Get out of my way, Lady.
I'm gonna get the Fire jewel
even if I have to put you in the ground.
(GROANS) No, we're not gonna fight you.
Aah! Step off, Lady.
I'm fighting you!
Wenk, wenk.
I can't. She's like family.
Wenk.
Aah!
(SPEAKING KOREAN)
Wenk.
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
Don't make me.
CINNAMON BUM: Hyah!
Hyah!
Kyah!
Get out of here!
(GROANS)
(SPEAKING KOREAN)
Dang, Lady. Calm down.
It's no use, Finn.
Like all of the fire people,
Lady Flameicorn knows only fighting.
Cinnamon Bun.
You're still normal.
My Flame shield protected
me from the change,
but the rest of the kingdom is lost.
Not for long, man.
Will you take us to Flame Princess?
It won't do any good.
She is spicy with anger.
I know I can reason with her.
We used to really bond
over music and... stuff.
Comin' in.
- Mmm.
- Wha?
Mm.
(BARKING)
(GASPS)
That was the throne room.
This is as far as I go.
Don't you want to see FP?
She said some hurtful things.
I'll give her a good talking to.
I'll talk her into next week.
No!
I'm gonna let her do her.
I'm a loner now.
What about your wolf friend?
My wolf is also a loner.
We are both loners!
When did he get cool?
Everyone slept on that.
FLAMBO: Hey, yous mugs.
What for ya come to the
Fire Kingdom for, huh?
Flambo? Are you still normal?
Die in a ditch.
(ALL SCREAM)
Flambo, you used to be about the laughs.
This is what I think is funny.
Boi-oi-oi-oing.
Hyah!
Talk about a spicy meat...
If you can't run the saw,
then stay out of my woodshed!
(ROARS)
Dramatic boys.
Never again.
Wenk, wenk. Wenk.
Finn! The duck found a secret tunnel!
Okay. (SIGHS)
Wenk, wenk, wenk.
So, are you still into Flame Princess?
What? No, FP and I are just friends.
And I'm really proud of that friendship.
Getting there took a
lot of trust building
and emotional growth.
Okay. I believe you.
Do you do squats?
Gunter?
Dang. Just look at these ding-dongs.
(SWORDS CLASHING, SHOUTING)
(ROARS)
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
(GROWLS)
Hyah!
Bam. Bam. Bam. Bam.
Fire Wyatt's still in the game.
Aah!
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Wenk!
Oh, there he is.
Wait. Look at what's caught
in that dragon's teeth.
That's FP's jewel!
Oh, dang.
That big gross dragon ate your ex.
Give me... that... jujubee!
I'm gonna tear you apart if
you did anything to hurt...
Wait... Flame Princess?
Return the jewel, worm.
Oh! It is you.
Listen. I need this to fix Ooo.
'Cause Jake is slime,
and this place is a
toxic aggro machoscape.
This place is great.
(YELLS)
Fire Kingdom rules!
That was messed up and
not who you really are.
Aah!
(GRUNTS) (GROANS)
Stop talking to me like we're friends!
The only friend I have is violence,
and the only thing we do
when we hang is fight.
(GROWLS)
Finn, wait!
Flame Princess is the dragon!
- Ah! Ah! Ah!
- I'm being arrowed!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Wenk.
Gunter, you saved me!
Wenk. Wenk. Wenk.
Wenk!
I know you won't hurt me, Gunter.
Wenk. Wenk. Wenk.
Oh, no! I'm too trusting!
Finn, I want to leave! Wrap that up.
Give it!
(ROARS)
No! I have to save Jake.
Phoebe. Stop.
(GULPS)
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
Aaaaaah!
Hyah!
Aah!
I'm gonna ruin your universe.
(GRUNTS)
(ROARS)
Aah!
Honestly, I could still see
those two working out.
Oh, come on.
Ugh!
No one touches my charm!
Hey.
Hey!
- Wenk.
- This is terrible.
Nobody's paying attention to me.
Everyone just stop fighting!
What's wrong with you?
Why can't you be more like
those nice, boring losers
in the Candy Kingdom?
With their little faces and songs?
Or like me?
Why isn't everyone more like me?
Kill her.
No, she's right.
We must stop senselessly
attacking each other
and start senselessly attacking
those disgusting nerds
in the Candy Kingdom!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Clutch.
That's a huge extrapolation
from what I said.
ALL: Smash the nerds! Smash the nerds!
Smash the nerds!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Surely, this is the end of all things.
Gunter.
Finn!
Wyatt?