Sync and corrections by kay sukri
Dang.
What in Grod's name am I looking at?
Fire,
ice,
candy,
and slime.
Weird.
How did this happen, Ice King?
Look, I know it's a lot to take in.
Let's go to the living room.
(WHOOSH)
Now settle in, get comfortable,
'cause I am gonna tell you everything.
And it is going to blow your... Oop!
I gotta kiss my skyhooks good night.
Good night, my skookie-wooks.
(KISSES)
Okay.
Dude...
Why does it look like a four-way pizza?!
Is everyone in Ooo like a zombie?
Is everyone basically dead?
Everyone is not dead. It's much worse.
Let me start at the beginning.
No.
What am I gonna do without
my besties around?
Mm.
♪♪
Mm, okay. Bird watching sounds cool.
Hey, roomie! I'm going out to
pick up some magic ingredients.
Ooh! Are you making somethin' delicious?
Oh, I'm building a
magic battery to power
my elemental purification spell.
Cool. Bring me a snackie.
Like... a doughnut?
Surprise me.
Oh, I'll surprise you.
(UNDER BREATH) I'll surprise everyone.
Wait. What was Patience talking about?
Oh, it's not important.
Something ominous.
Anyways, it was then that I
really got into bird watching.
♪♪
What else we got here?
A penguin.
Oh. Right.
(GASPS) Something!
Is that...
Oh... my... glaah!
(GASPS)
You a toucan?
Simon, I've been trying
so hard to help you.
I've tried reprogramming...
nnn your... your crown,
Code-mapping, penguin-napping,
co-mingling with magic,
and grasping and grappling,
but it just hasn't been happening.
It's saddening, it's maddening,
and I'm rapping and... and...
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(INHALES)
So I'm trying the direct approach.
- Ugh.
- Wenk!
No, I don't remember who she is,
but I know how to find out.
Hey!
So good to see you!
You still working at that same place?
Mm, my work takes me all over.
I meant all over the place.
Oh! Before I forget, I
just got a new phone.
Would you mind reentering
your info for me?
It's okay. I know you don't remember me.
No, no, no. I can get this.
(INHALES SLOWLY, PFFT!)
I lost it.
A long time ago, you and
I were... colleagues.
My name is Betty Grof, and...
That's what I was gonna say! Betty!
(INHALES)
Hey, do you wanna go on
a date with me tonight?
(BABBLES) Uh, buh, buh, buh. Yes.
Meet me at 8:00 at my Magic Man House.
(LAUGHING)
♪♪
(RING)
Hello?
You are not gonna believe
what just happened.
What?
A lady touched me!
That's cool. Who is she?
I think she might be an exotic bird.
But guess who's going on a date tonight!
Wow. So what are you gonna wear?
Oh, probably my go-to... Blue muumuu.
Ugh!
No! You need to get a
nice bespoked suit.
A be-wudda-wa?
"Bespoke" means it's custom-made
to fit your specific dimensions
and emphasize what's
flattering about your shape.
Like my abs.
No, I'd say you're kinda bottom-heavy.
No, that's just the muumuu, dawg.
I'm jacked.
Hmm.
Oh, yeah.
- What the heck d...
- Shh!
'Kay, so then we went suit shopping.
It's very important to pick
a good, natural fabric.
As for color, for a first suit,
you should choose between
black, navy, or charcoal grey.
Why?
It's a wizard fashion rule.
If you stray, you'll look like a fool.
How's about if I make my suit a onesie?
(SMACK) Ow!
Whoa.
Let's get to work!
♪♪
And then Life-Giving Magus
checked an even darker...
- (WHISPERS) What is going on?
- Shade of gray against my face.
Until finally...
LIFE-GIVING MAGUS: Yep!
Pretty fly for an ice guy.
♪♪
MALE VOICE: (SINGSONGY)
Ding dong! Someone's here!
That's clever.
Hello, Simon.
Uh, flowers.
Come in. Come in.
I really like how you
decorated the place.
I'm really into skulls and
old teeth in jars, too.
Ready for our date?
You bet.
Bah-bam!
Aaaaah!
(PANTS) This a-way.
What is this place?
In the old days, we would meet here,
and you would give me books
because you had a subscription
to the Book a Day Club.
Book a Day?
You gave me the excess books
because I was associated
with Books for the Bookless.
(LAUGHS) Simon! You
want your usual booth?
Bogo! You remember him?
Lead the way, Bogo!
So...
Yes?
Are we going splitsies?
(SIGHS)
Okay, I'll pay for half your entrée.
But if you get an appy or
a dessert, it's on you.
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
(SMACKS LIPS)
(INHALING DEEPLY) Aah!
What? There something in my beard?
You don't remember any of this?
(THINKING) She's starting
to freak me out.
Ring, ring!
Sorry. I should take this.
Oh, hi, Gunter. No. I'm on my date.
(INHALING DEEPLY)
Gunter, I have to go.
(CHOMPING)
Technology, right? (CHUCKLES)
Aah! No!
(ZAPPING) It's all wrong!
- Ugh! Zap!
- Wha?
(WHOOSH)
Well, that was terrifying.
I've tried everything I can think
of to make Simon remember.
Is there something I'm missing?
What am I doing wrong?
Maybe you're going after someone
who doesn't exist anymore.
Why not take him as he is?
After all, you've been through
a lot of changes yourself.
You're making a lot of
sense, Tiny Manticore.
We're like two shadows, two
ghosts caught in limbo.
It sounds depressing when
you say it that way.
Think of a different way to say it.
(CRYING SOFTLY)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
Wenk.
Oh, uh, just stretching.
Wenk?
The date? Uh, yeah, it went great.
I don't know about a
second date, though.
I don't wanna be that guy
who just hangs out with his
girlfriend all the time
and doesn't see his friends.
Man, I wanna be that guy so bad.
(WHOOSH)
Hey, I was just talking
about you to my penguin.
Have you met Gunter?
Yes. I kidnapped him that one time.
Look, Simon... I mean, Ice King.
Yeah, who's this Simon guy
you keep yakking about?
Should I be jealous?
He's somebody I knew a long time ago.
Hey, you still into bird watching?
Watch this.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES) Mmm... zow!
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
- (LAUGHS) Amazing!
- (LAUGHS)
- Such beautiful birds!
They're all for you, Ice King.
Woof. What a bust.
These are some low-grade fairies.
My magic battery is going to su...
Who's this dancing with the I.K.?
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
Bird friend! (LAUGHS)
How delightful.
(LAUGHING)
Ha! (SIGHS)
Huh? Where did the weird lady go?
Uh... well, when you weren't looking,
her... her mom showed
up and told her that
her old boyfriend wanted
to be with her again,
and they ran off together. The end.
Her mom?
Well, I gotta go.
I almost forgot!
Surprise!
(CRYING, CHEWING)
(GROANS)
I wonder if my roomie has any more
of these soothing doughnuts.
Only one way to find out!
♪♪
PATIENCE: Elemental, elemental.
Stand, do not sit.
Cool.
Elemental, Elemental.
Can not quit.
Weird Lady!
Blast him!
(HUMMING)
Eee.
(ZAPS)
Then everything went nuts.
There was all this light and noise.
I grabbed as many penguins
as I could... one.
But now that you're here,
we can go back and save Weird Lady.
Sounds like we got our first lead.
All we needed was... a little patience.