Sync and corrections by kay sukri
Give me them jewels,
Finn. We're out of time.
(CACKLES)
Now, let's grab LSP and
get the buns out of here.
Huh!
(LAUGHS)
♪ Let me hear you whisper ♪
Aah!
You left my friend Finn down there.
I'm sorry, but we don't
need him anymore.
But don't worry, I've got a new plan.
A plan where nothing that
happens here matters.
Okay, but we should turn back still.
Finn loves me.
He sees me as, like, a
handsome older brother.
Mm, no. I'm doing the right thing.
Can't go around it,
got to go through it.
♪ That you love me, too ♪
Uh, guys? Getting a little too close.
♪ Keep the love-light glowing ♪
♪ In your eyes so true ♪
- ♪ Let me call you sweetheart. ♪
- (SCREAMS)
Finn, it's me, I'm
saving your tight butt!
(GRUNTS) Whoop!
Don't worry, my children.
I will send my joy out unto all of them.
"Bonbon ballad."
♪ Underneath the mountain ♪
♪ Overlook the sea ♪
♪ I find my sweet friends waiting ♪
♪ And bring them close to me ♪
♪ La-da-da-da, la-da-da ♪
Lumpy Space Princess,
you were buried in candy and
it didn't change you at all.
Why doesn't this elemental
stuff affect you?
I'm a tough tranch!
People don't tell me what to do,
I tell them what to do!
Okay, but it has to be more than that.
Like, you're not from
around Ooo, not really.
Maybe you're not made of
the same stuff as us.
Hmm.
Lumps! Lumps are the
subspace molecular lattice
that binds together the
scientific and magical
forces of Ooo... More powerful than
any one element, it's the force that
orders reality into its true shape.
And, LSP, this part is
very, very important...
Grrr! No more learning!
(CAR HORN BEEPS)
Hey, Michael! Let's get married.
Wait, what?
Michael.
LSP, This is important.
I think they were trying to tell you...
You're the anti-elemental.
Fire, Ice, Candy, Slime and...
Lumps! (GASPS)
(HUMS)
Huh?
I must have dozed off...
and bound myself.
Ouch!
(CLEARS THROAT)
People say you shouldn't
live in the past!
But I say, "Why not?"
I love it.
This book is strange,
but when you puzzle it out,
it's mostly all charges and frequencies.
Instead of fixing Ooo,
I can use these jewels to make a portal
to take me back in time and find Simon
before he discovers the crown.
Uh-huh.
This time I won't let him put it on.
I'll drop it in a volcano
before that happens.
Things will be back to
being just me and Simon,
and you won't exist!
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
No more Ice King, no more magic Betty...
Maybe I can even stop the Mushroom War!
(LAUGHS)
Cool. Now where do I come in?
You're not listening.
My wonderful Simon will
never become this sad,
pathetic creature strewn before me.
Wait, what?
I thought I could do it, but I can't.
Being with you is like
looking at my old life
through a funhouse mirror.
(LAUGHS) It's driving me mad.
Goodbye, Ice King.
(MACHINE WHIRS)
Okay, I think this is a
pretty good breakdown
of your components.
We just need to figure out a way
to tap into your pure
anti-elemental essence, LSP.
(SIGHS) Don't tell me what to do, Finn.
Yeah, like that.
PB is undiluted sweetness now,
and Slime Princess has
never been slimier.
I think you might need to be the
most you that you've ever been.
You just have to believe in yourself.
I do believe myself.
I'm a blossoming debutante
on the war path.
Wenk!
Ahhhhh!
Wenk! Wenk-wenk! Wenk, wenk, wenk, wenk.
(PURRS)
See?
It's working.
Ugh! You okay?
Just relax, you'll be obliterated soon.
Really? Lady, this Simon
sounds cool, but I'm Ice King.
I, uh, I guess I'm a special person
and I am worthy of respect.
Just... shh! It'll be over in a second.
Can you turn this off
and we can talk, maybe?
Nertz.
Huh.
♪ Underneath the prairie ♪
♪ Over sugar springs ♪
♪ We'll sing our song forever ♪
♪ This candy chorus rings ♪
♪ La-da-da-da, la-da-da ♪
Boy, did I fail deep.
Well, maybe I'll try again
in another 1,000 years.
I'm not sticking around
to see how this ends.
Mr. Fox, please roll me someplace safe.
Oh, oh, wow. Okay.
(GRUNTS)
♪ Overlook the valley ♪
♪ Under honeymoon ♪
What if? Oh!
We're running out of time.
I am. Glob!
Ding-dong.
It's me, classic Ice King!
Si-men!
I didn't like being ditched earlier,
but if you and Betty are cool now,
you can help us figure out
how to use LSP's power.
Wait, where's Betty?
Who?
Here, I bet this thing can help you.
(GASPS) It's Gunter! Hey,
Gunter! Come here, boy.
Okay, fair.
Hey, LSP, now that we've
got the Enchiridion,
maybe we can study it
for a way to figu...
No more studying!
All day long you've been
telling me what to do.
I already saved your life, so
quit telling me what to do.
Huh?
What's happening?
The jewels.
Oh! What if your force of will
is influencing and
attracting elemental magic.
You mean these jewels love me
more than they love those dumb-dumbs?
(LAUGHS)
- Wenk! Wenk! Wenk!
- And you!
Clam your face, you noid!
Okay.
Wenk!
My boy!
You bossed him back to
normal. Don't stop.
Uh, I don't think I can. The
jelly is out of the tube.
♪ Underneath the mountain ♪
♪ Overlook the sea ♪
♪ I find my sweet friends waiting ♪
♪ And bring them close to me ♪
Mama, Papa!
♪ Close to me ♪
Excuse me.
Whoop!
Oh, blessings, what a trip.
Hey, Slime Princess.
Oh! Hello, Jake.
Uh, did you recently get a haircut?
Unnnh. Lumps.
Oh, LSP.
Please be careful with yourself.
Ha-ha, fine, I guess.
Yeah, that's all of them!
(GROANS)
LSP!
(WEAKLY) I'm a hero.
Whoops.
You did it.
She did it!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Uh, I'd like to date you, LSP.
Thank you, Starchy.
(COUGHING)
Wait, where... Up here.
(CLICKS TONGUE) You really donked up.
Finn? Jake?
Finn!
Oh, my gosh!
Come here.
- What?
- Over here.
Hey, buddy.
Jake? Are you okay?
Yeah... (CHUCKLES)
You know, everything looks
different after a long trip.
You and I can fix whatever
this is together, whenever.
Fix what now?
I was really scared when you left.
You're my best brother.
I love you.