Sync and corrections by kay sukri
Oh... bananas.
Bananas.
BMO, it's your turn to say "bananas."
There is a strange cloud following us.
Come and see.
I'm too comfortable to move.
Can you just describe it?
Forget the cloud.
Tell us a story instead.
A nice campfire bedtime story.
Once upon a time, there was this...
cool guy and a banana with sunglasses.
Please, no.
Literally anything but bananas.
Once upon a time, there was a...
bandana with sunglasses.
Eh?
(BOTH SNORING)
Good night, bed.
Good night, weird cloud.
Good night, weird orb.
(SNORING)
- Hey, Jake home.
- (APPLAUSE)
- Hey, Joshua home too!
Whatcha doing, Dad?
Scrambling eggs?
Yes, in the refrigerator!
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, boy.
I can see where this is going.
(LAUGHTER)
Man, that got old quick.
What's going on here, Jermaine?
Wha... wha... What do you think?
It's a dream, dum-dum.
Oh, right.
'Cause dream bro times.
And 'cause we burned this place down.
Last year.
Anyway, what's up, Jermaine?
Fine.
What do you think all these
blank canvasses represent?
These are, um, mine actually.
I've really been getting
into landscape painting.
Mostly, like, forests and seascapes.
Strictly representational art.
Dude, that's awesome!
We should collab on an interdisciplinary
performance or something.
Ah, that's not really my scene, man.
I'm into real things.
(SNORING)
I'm flying!
No more walking for this guy.
You hear that dudes?
You're retired.
Just gonna float around
like a chubby bat.
WATER NYMPH: Hey, Finn.
I made these cloud sculptures for you.
Yes!
Flying Finn will never
miss out on anything.
People will be all, "Too
bad Finn's not here."
And I'll be like, "Look
up, surface dorks."
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYS)
Director!
Where are your accessories?
Let's get the director's
accessories, please?
Okay, time for the show!
(APPLAUSE)
We never have any fun
when BMO's not here.
All we do is hit things.
(LAUGHTER)
I love art.
Okay, boys, I got a job for you.
Think you can handle
it? Of course you can.
Now, dig.
JAKE: Yeah, okay.
Why are we doing this, Papa?
Never you mind!
Dig.
(THUMPING)
(SIGHING) Man, I'm out of shape.
I can hear my own heart palpitating.
Jeepers creepers.
Don't mind that. Just dig faster.
Dig faster, you dew droppers!
Brrr!
Hey, it's PB.
Finn, what are you up to?
Oh, nothing. Just using
my power of flight!
It's scientifically impossible
for a human boy to fly.
You're gonna wish it was
scientifically possible
to put those words back in your mouth.
Look!
Huup!
Huup! Grrr.
Stop holding me back!
(THUNDER CRASHES)
Huh?
Aah!
Finn, what are these?
Aaaaahhhh!
I'm bored.
I'm boring.
There's only one person
who can save this play.
- Yay, he's here!
- BMO!
- (APPLAUSE)
- A bootleg BMO?
I'm bad!
But you still like me.
Boo!
This show is terrible!
I want to talk to the director.
The director is right
this way, director.
Director, the director's
here to see you.
Listen, the play started out good,
but it didn't have any
relatable characters.
(GASPING) Football!
I'm not Football.
Oh, good.
I'm AMO!
Oh, bad!
(DIGGING)
(SHOVELS CLANGING)
The heck!
Dad, the hole is gone!
- Boys?
- Dad?
JOSHUA: Boys, the hole is gone!
Looks like you buried
me. Why'd you do it?
- Aah! Dig!
- Mom.
What are you doing?
Mm.
I'm sure this is all really symbolic,
but it's dang comfy.
(GASPING)
(SLURPING)
I don't like where this is headed.
I'm out of here.
Ohhh.
Mom, Dad...
(WHIMPERING)
How does it look?
I think it looks cool.
Nice.
Oh!
♪♪
What the plop?
- Help...
- Jake?
JAKE: I'm aging up here!
Okay, bird thoughts, Finn.
Eggs, nest, wings, worms!
Jake?
Jake!
Finn...
(COUGHS)
I'm old.
(BMO CRIES)
Now it's too relatable!
Cool, backup skin.
- Aah!
- That's not what I wrote!
Huh?
I really respect that
you do your own stunts.
You're brother's gonna
have to step up his game
to keep up with you.
We have to do something
about these crow's-feet,
or everyone's gonna know
you're too old to play Jake.
But I am Jake.
(HISSING)
What's he saying?
Your lines.
Hss, hss, shss, shss.
Uh, hss, sshs, hss.
Just read the cue cards.
BMO: It's just a rehearsal,
but it's not okay to be really bad.
BMO? What are you doing here?
This is my nightmare!
- No, this is my...
Oh, our nightmares, I guess.
And you're here with us.
- (RUMBLING)
- I am?
The unconscious is so complicated.
Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
Bird thoughts!
Perches, birdseed, hooting!
It's not working!
That weird eye cloud again.
This fall's taking longer
than I thought it would.
I wish I had a game to pass the time
while we're plunging to our death.
Or, like, a puzzle or something.
A puzzle.
So what if I put this here?
Um...
♪♪
Uh, who are you?
Okay, you're some kind
of nightmare princess.
But where are we?
We're dead. I knew it.
I'm guessing we're still
asleep on the boat.
I think she entered our nightmares
and mashed them up in order
to communicate with us.
What do you want to tell us?
Banana?
(GASPS)
She wants to hear my banana story!
(ALL GASP)
She's harvesting our mind-fruits!
Wait, do you just want us
to give you some bananas?
Well, there's loads on our boat.
You can take as many as you...
No, Finn! You have to negotiate first.
We won't trade them for anything less
than something pretty and/or cool.
Enjoy those bananas!
Pretty!
What is this, like, nightmare juice?
Let's drink it!
(YAWNS) Hey, look how
close to home we are.
Land ho!
Hm.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Ooh, la-la.
How's it look, BMO?
Like a dream.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com