(QUACKING)
(WARBLE, ZAP!)
(ROARS)
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very messed-up lands ♪
♪ With Finn and Jake,
Ice King, and Betty ♪
♪ Who knows how it will end? ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Sync and corrections by kay sukri
Okay, we'll find the
crown, grab the jewel,
and then give a couple
tugs on the skyhooks!
Got it!
Here's some trail mix for the road!
You think Betty and Simon
hanging out is a good thing?
Totally.
They're two wackadoo peas
in a wackadoodle pod.
Something about it makes me
feel weird in the ethics.
Well, you don't want to stare at
happiness too hard, you know?
Why?
'Cause it stares back, man.
Slime Town is mad nasty.
Let's blend in.
Yeesh.
This smells like the locker
room of a gym for dead fish.
Eh, you get used to it, though.
That's the great thing about smells.
Man, where is everyone?
(BASS THUMPING)
Skate size?
Uh, 10.
Universal.
Aw, man!
Okay, you look dope.
(MUSIC BLARES)
(GASPS)
Whoa.
Slime Princess got big.
(LAUGHS)
DJ Plop... DJ-DJ Plop Drops!
Get ready to plop drooop!
♪♪
Jake, look!
The crown!
Harness me, bro.
Gonna get that jewel!
Re-re-re-rejected!
Her slime's tougher than it looks.
LSP: Finn, Jake!
Over here!
LSP!
I'm not LSP anymore. I'm LSP.
Oh, 'cause you're Lumpy Slime Princess.
Bingo!
You guys on a team yet?
Why do we need teams?
No, you can't be on my team.
Me and Spurtle Princess
are gonna win it all.
Right, girls?
What are... What are you...?
(CROWD CHANTING "SNACK PACK!")
Oh, Glob!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
What's going on?
Blechfast Princess, Bileberry Princess,
and Hot Blob Princess
are about to skate.
The Snack Pack!
Oh, yay. The snack hacks are here.
(CHUCKLES)
Snack hacks. Did you hear that?
Party splat.
You got something to say?
Snack Pack, more like...
Stink Pack!
Ooh. Ooh. Ooh. Ooh.
We challenge you to a skate battle!
Skate battle! Byow-byow-byow!
Wawawa!
Classic street slime rules...
Quack grinds, sheering the duck,
or insincere hot-dogging
will result in instant disqualification!
First up...
The Bearnicks!
♪♪
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Move over, Party Splat.
♪♪
Time for the Midnight Snack.
Mid!
Night!
Snack!
Ah.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
And the winner is...
Wawa!
Snack Pack!
As always, the prize is absorption
into the body of our bumpin' leader.
(CROWD CHANTING "SKATE TO ASSIMILATE!")
(LAUGHTER)
Isn't assimilation amazing?
No! It's horrifying.
It might be comfy,
like a hug that turns you into a hug.
What happens to the losers?
They go in the losers' cage,
and they're stripped of
their skating rights!
Oh.
New plan!
- We enter the contest...
- Yeah.
- Win...
- Of course.
Then I grab the jewel
and you stretch us on out of that bod.
Won't we get absorbed, though?
We'll just believe in
ourselves way too much.
She can't absorb us if
we're self-absorbed.
Okay, but you need a
three-person team to compete,
and I'm taken!
What?
We had a vote and you're out.
But I'm the plucky underdog!
No, you're just terrible.
Abracajamiel can do the splits.
Whoo!
Whatever!
Nyah!
Attention, super cool party people!
My new, totally awesome team, The Lumps,
challenges my old team, The Stupids,
to a skate battle.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
First up...
The Lumps.
Start the beat, Plop-D!
♪♪
No, wait. Discontinue the beat.
(MUSIC STOPS)
What are you doing, man?
This!
(FIDDLE PLAYING)
Ah!
(CROWD MURMURING)
That's not dancing!
I know! It's better.
(GROANS)
Okay, we can still save this, Finn.
Lights!
♪♪
(CROWD MURMURING, WHISTLING)
Hyah!
Whoa! Aah!
(CROWD BOOING)
We got to do the lift.
(CROWD OOHS)
(APPLAUSE)
Wa.
They love me. I'm a
true Cinderella story.
Aah!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
Wa-waa!
The Stupids win by default!
Whoo!
Ahh.
No! I can still do this! I know I can.
Ah, well.
This isn't how it's supposed to happen.
We blew it.
Eh, it'll work out somehow.
The winners will now be rewarded
with glorious absorption!
(CROWD CHANTING "SKATE TO ASSIMILATE!")
(LAUGHTER)
Today's losers will now be punished.
P-P-P-Punished!
With shameful absorption!
Take them 'round back.
(WHEEL SQUEAKING)
Hey, this is gonna work out somehow.
I've got the loser sticks!
Poke the losers.
Whoo. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, whoo.
Yes!
Take me, Slime Princess!
Huh! Hold onto me.
This place really is supes comfy.
(GRUNTING)
Yoink.
Oh, I'm starting to turn.
Pull us out, Jake.
In a minute.
What?!
It's like being in a
warm bath full of snot.
Aah! We're trapped!
It'll work out somehow.
(GASPS) Jake, no! Fight the slime!
I'm having the slime of my life.
(CHUCKLES)
Jake.
I may as well give in to it.
Maybe Simon will save Ooo.
This isn't an uplifting underdog ending.
You're still here?
I'm not assimilating.
And no one can see my cool outfit
through all this lumpin's slime.
(GROANS)
Looks like LSP is too much of a
killjoy for our Slime Queen!
She's gonna be rejected!
Aah!
(BOTH GROAN)
Em-Em-Em-Embarrassing!
Y'all are bounced.
Jerks.
I got the jewel, but I lost Jake.
(WARBLES)
You're not a Slime person?
No, I totally faked it.
I just saw this lumpalicious party,
and I was like, "These are my people!"
But even though I shoplifted
this super-cool outfit,
I still didn't fit in.
I guess I don't fit in... anywhere!
(CRYING)
Jake could fit in anywhere.
Whatever happened, he was always like,
"It'll work out."
Stop being so selfish, Finn!
I'm the one hurting here!
You don't even know what
it's like to be an underdog.
You and Jake always win... Always!
You're right, LSP. We do.
Don't worry, Jake! I vow
to get you back in shape.
(GASPS)
Oh, my Glob, this is it!
The crowd-pleasing climax
where the beautiful
underdog gets the hunk.
Rom-com style!