(DUCK QUACKS, WIND WHISTLES)
(ZAPS)
(ROARS)
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very messed up lands ♪
♪ With Finn and Jake,
Ice King, and Betty ♪
♪ Who knows how it will end? ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Sync and corrections by kay sukri
(SHIP HORN BLOWS)
JAKE: Heck, yeah! We're home.
That was definitely
the longest adventure we've ever done.
What about when you got
trapped in a mind dungeon
for a buncha years?
This trip was longer in emotional time.
Yeah, I'm burnt out. No more
adventures for a while, okay?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
(BABBLES LOUDLY) B-b-b-b-b-b-b!
Let's go take hot showers.
Hey, look at this fish.
(SQUISH)
It's... gummy?
(HIGH-PITCHED VOICE) Hello!
- Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Hey!
(LAUGHING)
Well, that's weird.
We should defs check it out
after we hit up the tree house.
Yeah, we gotta get to the
bottom of this hot shower.
Hmm.
Does everything seem... pinker to you?
Home always looks different
after a long trip.
You're seeing it with fresh
eyes and newfound wisdom.
And sometimes there's also a
new strip mall or something.
So everything being pink is
probably not a big deal.
And also, I'm tired.
I like the pink.
Why you worry so much, worry baby?
Ha, ha, yeah! Why you worry
so much, worry baby?
Don't worry, Finn.
We're only teasing you
because you're a baby.
Whoa!
What the heck happened
to the tree house?
Candy...
Fern?
(SQUISH)
(DRIPPING)
Oh, I do not like this.
♪♪
Is this some kind of sick joke?
Because I love it!
FINN: Huh?
Big Baby root beer? No
one buys this brand.
It's too sweet.
Hello?
(BOTH GASP)
Aah!
Hey! You look like me!
Fern?!
Who's Fern? I'm Fun the Human.
And I'm Nectr, the little robot!
I'm Shelby the Worm... the gummy worm!
Welcome, strangers.
It's so cool that you're
inside our house.
Dude, when did you guys turn into candy?
We've always been candy,
you silly billy bean!
Ohh, okay. I get it.
We've obviously stumbled into
another alternate dimension
where everyone's a different
version of themselves.
Yawn.
But we haven't gone through any portals.
BMO would know.
Hello!
Neptr is so cute now!
I'm going to start
treating him as an equal.
You were supposed to take
care of Ooo while I was gone.
What happened with that?
What?
You used to be this volatile
plant boy. Remember?
Really? Well, I'm candy now.
And I'm in control of my emotions.
I'm in control, too...
of my body!
(LAUGHS)
Wow, gummy Shelby's a lot of fun.
I think I'm okay with Candyworld.
No way. Let's talk to PB.
I'm sure this is all one of
her experiments gone wrong.
You seem upset, friend.
The tower will fix you right up.
The what now?
(GULPING)
- (BELL DINGING)
- Oh, boy!
Let's run outside!
- (BELL DINGING CONTINUES)
- (NECTR WHIRRING)
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
Hello! It's me!
Lemonpink!
He was inside the lemon.
Mm! Drink up, babies!
(SPLAT) Squeeze!
(LAUGHING)
I used to have a lot
of fear and sadness,
but now I'm fine!
Hey, I want some of that.
No. That is body juice.
Hmm? What's that?
Do you spurn my fluids?
No.
Maybe someone's feeling a little sour!
Wuh-whoa!
You know what sours get.
Sours get the tower!
CANDIES: Sours get the
tower! Sours get the tower!
Sours get the tower!
Come on, Jake. Let's go see Bubblegum.
(SCREAMING)
Stop striding! It just
keeps you agitated!
I'm freaking out, Jake.
This place is weird.
What I'm hearing is you're stressed out
because everything's candy.
Aren't you?
Not really.
Lemongrab's always been a weirdo.
At least now he's helping people.
(RUMBLING) And Fern is, like,
laughing and joking around.
Maybe they don't need you to fix them.
Hmm.
I always believe you
when you use that voice.
(CRYING IN DISTANCE)
(CRYING CONTINUES)
Sweet P?
(SNIFFLES)
Hey, buddy, what are
you doing out... uh...
Hey! You're meat!
Yes, I'm meat. (SNIFFLES)
But everything else is weird.
Wow, Sweet P, that's almost
exactly what I've been saying.
Sweet P, do you remember what happened?
One day, the candy came
and turned Mommy and Daddy
into something... different.
TREE TRUNKS AND MR PIG: Sweet P!
There you are!
We've been looking for you everywhere!
We just love ya so much, son.
You're gonna get into a great college!
Tee-hee-hee-hee! Tee-hee-hee!
They look so happy, like dogs.
Don't worry, Sweet P.
We're headed to the Candy Kingdom
to see Princess Bubblegum
about all this.
She's not in the Candy Kingdom.
She's in the Terrible Tower.
Look!
Come on, Jake. That's
kind of weird, right?
I think it's magnificent!
Sweet P! Yoo-hoo!
We brought some rollers
and a bucket of sweet juicy caramel.
Let's get you back to normal.
But, Mama, I am normal!
Just sit tight there like a windowpane,
and you'll be back to
normal like a windowpane.
(ECHOING) Back to normal.
Hmm. Okay, you're right.
This is pretty freaky-deaky.
I'm gonna go now. (CRYING)
JAKE AND FINN: Sweet P, come back!
(TREE TRUNKS LAUGHS)
Uh... let's get to the tower.
♪♪
And never be the guy
with no phone, Finn.
You'll think it'll make people
wanna talk to you more,
but people just forget
to invite you to things.
You've convinced me.
Plus, I like late night bedtime calls
when you're sleeping over at Lady's.
(SNIFFS)
Ooh. Somethin' smells nice.
Nice and toasty.
(ROARS)
ALL: S'more!
Stay back, S'more!
JAKE: Get it! Get it! Get it! Get it!
(GROWLS) (LAUGHS) Whoa, dudes.
I was just playin'.
ALL: What?! Marceline!
(GIGGLES) No, it's Marshmaline...
the Campfire Queen.
Mar... Marsha...
Marsha... Mars... Marsha...
Marcine. Mar... Mar...
Marsh... Marshmi... Marshman... My...
Would you like to hear a song?
I've written just the ditty
that'll cheer up anyone
that's overwhelmed with
work or responsibility.
Yay! I love Marshmaline songs!
No time for tunes. Do you
know where Bonnie is?
Of course! Follow me.
(HUMMING "GREENSLEEVES")
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
(HUMMING ENDS)
Marshy... where's PB?
She's everywhere.
(RUMBLING)
Good tidings to you, my friends.
(GASPS) (GASPS)
Yahoo!
What... what happened to you?
Oh, this? (GIGGLES)
I've become what I was
always meant to become...
A pure candy elemental.
(VOMITS)
(LAUGHS, CHEERING)
(BELCHES) 'Scuse me.
What about Tree Trunks and Lemongrab
and Marceline and everyone else?
I fixed 'em, obviously.
Fixed 'em? But they're your friends!
Those aren't mutually
exclusive concepts.
That means it's fine.
No, it's not fine.
Don't fret.
I can fix you, too.
(SQUISHING)
Aah! Aah! Aah!
I can feel my bones turning gummy!
Me, too!
We gotta get out of here before...
Oof! Hugs!
I'm connected to all candy
throughout all the galaxies.
Once you're candy, you'll
be part of me, too!
No! That plan sucks!
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY) Oh, my gosh!
Aah! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- Ow!
Skyhooks!
Ice King?
Hold on to me, bro!
No!
Wait, we forgot... BMO!
Goodbye, boys! It's better this way!
(BEEPING)
(SIGHS) Oh, well. They'll be back.
(SNAPS)
They have nowhere else to go.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Yah! Ooh!
(GROANS)
Are we in...
Cloud Kingdom.
Looks like we got away
before the candy curse became permanent.
That's right. My skyhooks saved the day.
Thanks for getting us
out of there, Simon.
Aw, I can't take all the credit.
It's all thanks to my skyhooks.
Hey, why are you even up here?
We live here now, me and the skyhooks.
Finn, you gotta see this.
(GASPS)
Oh... my...
but...
ICE KING: Skyhooks!