Sync and corrections by kay sukri
Hmm.
Whoa, neat-o.
How do you make it bigger?
My magic skills are seriously drained.
Right now all I can do is
activate these thumbnails.
Come on, guys. Come on, guys.
Let's work the problem.
Let's fix Ooo.
Come on, guys.
I know I'm saying "Come on, guys" a lot.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Hmm.
Hey, if you need help turning
the pages, I'm your guy.
I do this thing where I lick my finger,
and then the moisture helps
grip the corner of the page.
I wonder if the
Enchiridion's been licked
by, like, thousands of wizards?
I know how to turn pages, man.
I was a graduate student!
"Graduate student"?
What the heck is that?
You graduated, but
you're still a student?
Doesn't make any sense.
Where's the dog?
Can the dog do something about this?
Okay, I'm a-comin'.
You're wired, buddy.
We've been going like
gangbusters since we got back.
(LULLABY PLAYS)
I don't got no time for this nonsense!
Shh, shh, shh.
What are you doing?
Are you swaddling me?
I'd hardly call this swaddling.
I'm just tucking you in.
This feels nice. Nice tucking, brother.
40 winks never hurt anybody.
(YAWNS)
Yeah, a dozen top...
(SNORES)
Wait! That symbol, I've seen it before.
Oh, that's great!
I'm proud of you, buddy.
(GUNTER SQUAWKS)
No, not you. I said "buddy" not "Gunty."
Jake was right. I feel great.
Hey Jake, you were... holy!
Jake, wake up!
Where's the rest of the Cloud Kingdom?
- Huh?
- Where's Simon and Betty?
I guess we must've broken
off and floated away
"loose-tooth-style."
Why'd you let me go to sleep?
Look what happens when you go to sleep!
How're we gonna get
down from here?! How?!
I can stretch us down.
Oh. Yeah.
(LEGS STRETCHING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
Windy.
What the jibbs, dude? I
can't even see the ground.
Hmm.
Hey, let's glide down!
Yeah!
(LAUGHTER)
- I love gliding!
- Yeah, Jake, yeah!
(LAUGHS) Whoo-hoo!
Oh, geez. I got to go back for a sec.
What? We just started.
Got to go back!
What is it?
Tell me what's wrong.
Emergency!
Jake, why can't you just
go while you're gliding?
We're on a clock here.
Hey! Turn around.
I can't go with you looking at me.
I'm sorry.
I can't go when I'm gliding.
Feels weird.
Just be quick, man. Ooo needs us.
- What is that?
- What?
It's another little cloud, but
this one has a small door.
Cloud with a small door, Jake!
Dude, face the other way!
Dude, it's getting away.
Aw, it's hopeless.
I got to wait until I can go again.
Just have to stop thinking about it.
Okay, come on, Jake. You can do it.
Come on, Jake. Just
stop thinking about it.
Come on, Jake. Come on, Jake.
Listen, I don't even think
gliding is a good plan.
We should sit tight, chill out,
and wait for Ice King and
Betty to look for us.
You know what you need?
What?
A haircut?
A haircut.
♪♪
Come on, man. We haven't done
this since we were kids.
Yeah, but I bet it works.
I bet it calms you the jibbs down.
Hmm.
All right.
(GIGGLES)
Yes, sir, I sure like cutting hair.
(GROANS) Mr. Mertens?
I know I'm just a
humble scissors jockey,
but you've been coming in my
shop for almost 20 years.
I can tell when you got
something on your mind.
(SIGHS)
I think...
I think what's bugging me is...
(VOICE OVER) The haircut
therapy is working.
All this elemental stuff happened
because I acted selfishly.
Oh, yeah?
It's like I'm employee of the month
at an ice cream store, and I
get someone to cover my shift,
and when I come back, the
place is burned to the ground
and everyone I love is doomed.
And now we're up here, and we
can't do anything to help.
Did I secretly want that to happen?
Like, deep down inside,
was I afraid Fern
would be better than me?
And my lizard brain put out bad vibes?
I guess the worst part of all is...
All right, you're all done, Mr. Mertens.
How's it look?
Jake! I was talking
about important stuff.
Sorry. I always get
caught up in the haircut.
Talcum?
Enough calm!
What are you doing?
I'm doing something...
for Ooo!
Nothing we do will help Ooo right now.
Don't you get it? I'm worried, too.
I've been trying to
distract you from all this,
but that doesn't mean I'm happy
with the way things are going.
Jake.
Look at all this beautiful
blue around us.
It's pretty, right?
But you know what I've been thinking?
What if we're dead?
I didn't say it because I
didn't want to worry you.
I'm the big brother, so I'm
supposed to keep it together.
And, okay, say I'm wrong
about being dead.
Here's the best case scenario...
My kids are candy zombies.
And Lady is made out
of taffy or something!
(SIGHS) I've got so many things
to worry about you don't even know.
I try to keep my worries hidden,
but where does that send them?
To my kidneys?
That can't be good.
Snip, snip.
Being stuck on a cloud isn't so bad.
It's weird, but we've gotten out
of weirder situations, right?
Right. Do you want the back tapered?
No, no thanks.
- Fade?
- No fade.
I feel a lot better now, thanks.
That'll be $6.50.
Here's 7 bucks.
- You're too generous.
- Here, take it, young man.
- No, sir, please.
- I'll put it in your backpack.
Please, sir, I have my dignity.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Well, whatever happens in the future,
I know what we should do.
What?
Open a barber shop.
I could get into that.
Maybe when I'm 35.
It happens sooner than you think.
♪ Time passes like a
little cloud, my friend ♪
♪ But don't be cowed, my friend ♪
♪ Just stay positive ♪
- That's the thing, right?
- Right!
♪ I'll try to remember
not to be sucky-like ♪
♪ But I'll be more plucky,
like the birdies who sing ♪
♪ Tra-la ♪
♪ Cheep, cheep, cheep,
cheep, cheep, cheep ♪
♪ Tra-laaa ♪
♪ Cheep, cheep, cheep,
cheep, cheep, cheep ♪
♪ Tra-laaaa ♪
♪ Cheep, cheep, cheep,
cheep, cheep, cheep ♪
♪ Tra-laaaa ♪
Hey, there's that cloud again.
Hey, what's behind that door, huh?
It's what everybody's been wondering.
Yeah, maybe it's our way out of here.
What's behind the door?
It's...
a cloud restroom.
If you'll excuse me for a minute.
Don't look.
There's a door.
I don't care! Don't
look in this direction!
It makes me feel like you can
hear my most private business.
(URINATING)
(GROWLS)
Hey, Jake! It's not a toilet.
It's some kind of angler lard!
I don't care what it is, I got to go.
Wah! What the...?
Hey, lard! Lard!
Go away!
Hold on, Jake.
It's Super Bespoke Jacket Guy!
Since when is it such a
hassle just to take a whiz?!
Hey, lard, do you mind
if I call you Cloudy?
Hey, Cloudy, what do you want
to eat a smelly old dog for?
Thanks.
Get a whiff of this.
- (INHALES DEEPLY)
- You like that?
This is a bespoke Ice King jacket.
You got his ancient man scent?
(SNORTS)
Go get him, boy!
Find the Ice King!
Are you being digested in there?
Just a little.
Hmph.
'Scuse me. Ouch!
Thanks for not digesting me.
You know, the way I see it,
all this elemental stuff
would have happened no matter what.
We're actually lucky
we were out of town.
Nothing happened to us, so now
we have a chance to fix it.
Thanks, Jake, that's kind of comforting.
I thought of it in the bathroom.
Hey, guys! Guess who's back.
Hmm, did you guys leave or something?
(CHUCKLES) It's always
good to see my bros.
Ew.
This is our new friend Cloudy.
He really wanted to meet you.
How did you like your
first taste of Ice King?
It wasn't that great.
The dog was better tasting, actually.
Although a little mangy.
A food critic.
Maybe this is what you want, Cloudy!
Go get it!
Mmm!
Dog. Dog. Dog.
Oh, there you are.
I made a real breakthrough.
I think I've figured out
exactly what we need
to do to repair Ooo.
We can use the Enchiridion
to create an elemental counter-spell.
First, we just need to retrieve
the three royal jewels
from the crowns of the
elemental princesses.
Easy.
That's great!
Finally a legit plan.
Thanks for making me chill, Jake.
That really helped me out.
Hey, did you guys get haircuts?
Without me?