(QUACKING)
(WARBLE, ZAP!)
(ROARS)
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very messed-up lands ♪
♪ With Finn and Jake,
Ice King, and Betty ♪
♪ Who knows how it will end? ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Sync and corrections by kay sukri
Okay, fellas.
Using these blueprints I acquired,
we're gonna take down Patient St. Pim
and rescue my new pal, Weird Lady.
But first, we have to crack through
the ice dome that covers the land,
avoid the Ice Kingdom peeps
who have all been turned
into vicious ice mutants,
and sneak into the ice fortress
without being ice-detected.
We'll enter via the sewer line.
So, that's the only way in and out.
I never said that.
"Can you help Captain
Tasty find the hidden"...
This is a place mat from
a seafood restaurant!
And this word search is way too hard!
That's 'cause you ain't
got spy skills like me.
With me, it's like, "Who's that hot guy?
The Ice King?"
No, it's not.
We're floating above Ice World now.
Brr!
I made these sweaters and
earmuffs for you guys.
They're bespoke!
And, they've got pictures of
your best friend on them!
FINN: Thanks.
All right, men, we need ideas
for how to breach that dome.
It's impervious to my skyhooks,
so we either burn, punch,
or stab our way in.
Maybe there's some kind of
weak point or secret entrance.
Right, right.
Hmm.
Good thinking.
Huh?
Aaaaaah!
Finn!
Oh, my glob!! Okay. Think, Finn.
What would Rattleballs do?
He would... draw his sword,
find a stress line in the dome,
and strike like a mighty scorpion!
Don't forget Ice King!
Turn into a parachute, Jake!
You got it!
(THUD)
Whoa.
Hold on. I got somethin'
in the pack that'll help.
(OBJECTS RATTLING)
Now, that's bespoke!
I never thought I'd think of the
old ice kingdom as cheerful.
Brrr! It's a lot colder now, too.
I've got fur.
Take my sweater!
Whoa! (LAUGHS)
Two Finns!
Huh?
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh! (WHIMPERS)
Huh? Huh?
(SNIFFLES)
Oh, I get it.
The top one's fake.
Okay, pals. This-a-way.
Y'all's in the Ice King's crib now!
This is crazy.
It's like being at the
bottom of an ocean.
Yeah, I'm feeling pretty weird.
♪♪
Snow golem.
Ice clops.
"Ice to meet you."
Look out!
Huh?
(SLED CRASHES)
What are you doing?!
This is my...
This is my house!
Carroll!?
Finn?
You've been turned into ice!
You better believe it, bucko!
You seem in good spirits, though.
Everyone else is sad and kind of empty.
I feel great. It sure beats the sky.
Boy, was I ever getting
sick of bein' a cloud!
Everyone looking at me,
saying things like,
"I think that looks like a sailboat!"
"I think that looks like a bird!"
I'm a woman! Ice Carroll!
Who are those other dudes?
This is Simon, the Ice King.
- And this is my brother, Jake.
- Hello.
Do you want to come with us?
We're on a secret mission.
Uh, that's really nice of you, actually.
Where are y'all going?
We're going to get Patient St. Pim.
She's in Simon's fortress,
and she's, like,
ruined the whole world
and all our friends.
Oh. On second thought, I
think I'm gonna stay here
and draw some elves and stuff.
You draw elves?
Yes, I draw elves! It's
what I like to do!
Aw, she seems a lot cooler than we are.
♪♪
Whoa.
Your place got weird.
Lookin' good, Pengy!
- Over here!
- Yup!
(ICE SHATTERS)
It's not a sewer, but
it will have to do.
♪♪
♪ It's a humid night ♪
♪ The moon is getting full again ♪
♪ Somewhere there's a slight
figure made of paraffin ♪
♪ And someone is turning its head ♪
♪ And someone is pulling its leg ♪
♪ It's maaaaaagic ♪
Jake? What's up with you?
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
Oh, no.
Jake, you have an icicle.
You look like your kids.
(MUTTERING) My sweater.
Ah, back in my old basement,
where it all began.
Psst!
I don't think this is
a basement anymore.
Cool boy says what?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Welcome to the party, sir.
May I take your coat?
Uh, I guess?
I don't know what I'm gonna
do with this but, whatevs.
ICE CARROLL: That's them!
The garbage who said they
were gonna take you out!
Carroll!!
I'm sorry, Finn.
I've got a good thing going on here.
Patient St. Pim, undo this mess!
(GROWLS)
Raa!
Cool boy!
(SHIVERING) Fix our home, Patience!
(SIGHS) Even if I felt like it, I can't.
Let me show you.
The princesses and I are
the elementals incarnate,
but the others didn't
want to play with me.
They denied their precious birthright.
So, I cast a mega-spell
that tapped into their true selves.
But the spell worked too well.
Instead of embracing their powers,
they were overrun by them.
I have distilled them
into something monstrous.
(MONOTONE VOICE) Monstrous...
like life itself.
Okay, that all tracks.
But what happened to Betty?
I used her as a magic
battery to power my spell.
My big, dumb spell. Ugh.
Enough of your mind games!
Tell us where you...
Wait, is that shrimp?
Ooh, is there shrimp here?
Ooh hoo hoo hoo hoo! (CHOMPING)
I planned this gorgeous
ball and shrimp buffet
to celebrate with the other elementals,
but none of them came.
If you're so upset about
this, you should fix it.
Fix it, don't fix it...
The universe is an abyss of suffering.
Y'all need to lighten up in here.
(MURMURING)
Brr.
(CHOMPING)
(GULP)
(SIGHS)
Aah!
Weird lady!
Raa! (DISHES SHATTER)
(GRUNTING)
Best-friends gang, retreat!
Ice King's ghosting,
man. We gotta leave!
Everyone leaves except me.
I remember father made
me stay at the table
until all the eggs were eaten.
Patience, let Jake go!
Jake is now part of my Ice Dominion.
He'll never leave here again.
Well, that sucks, and I hate it.
I'm just gonna take him anyway.
(SIGHS) Whatever.
Achoos Goose.
The goose... is loose.
We've lost another friend, Achoos Goose.
There's no point in having friends
because everything will... ends.
My mystic soup is great
for combating ice magic.
You sure put a magical
amount of pepper in it.
Nothing's changed since
we got you out of there.
I guess Patience doesn't need
your magic to sustain it.
Yeah, I feel drained
like a dirty bathtub.
Jake, how are you feeling?
This chicken soup does nothing
to warm the coldness of my heart.
- Are you serious?
- Just kidding!
Man, there's got to be
something we can do
about Patience's spell.
You know, ancient magic
was actually my major.
And there is one artifact
that could potentially help us...
A book called "The Enchiridion."
With that, I could formulate
a counter-spell, and...
We can't help you there.
We blew that thing up.
Uh, actually, I might have grabbed
another Enchiridion from
Farmworld Dimension.
(GASPS)
This biz is crazy powerful, though.
Well, I'm a little crazy
now, so I'm willing to try.
♪♪
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(LAUGHING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Phew.
What?