So then he goes
like this...
I go, "What is it, Dad?"
He goes...
like this.
He can't talk.
He's in the hospital,
the bed, you know?
So I lean in,
and he whispers in my ear.
He says to me,
"You're adopted."
- He said that?
- I think he said that.
Maybe he said,
"You're a doctor." I don't know.
But why would he say I'm a doctor?
I would know if I'm a doctor.
Why do you think he would wait
until now to tell you?
Maybe he thought
he was dying.
But I'm still not 100% sure
that he said it.
So basically
what you're saying is,
you want me to find out
if you're adopted or not.
Yes.
First, how did you
find me?
My friend said
he read this big article
about you
in the L.A. Magazine.
"Best Best Private
Investigator in Los Angeles."
Look, Mr. David,
I have to be honest
with you.
My business
and what I do...
what I do is
I service the community.
Basically
what I'm saying is,
I don't see a way
that you would, uh,
be helping my community.
What about...
calling some bingo games
or something?
You got, like, a community center
for bingo?
Bingo's a distraction.
Don't underestimate bingo.
I've got extra sneakers
that I don't wear anymore
- in pretty good condition, I must say.
- Extra sneakers?
I'd be more than happy
to donate 'em.
Mr. David, I don't think
this is gonna work.
It would mean
an awful lot to me.
Please please,
think about it.
If there's anything
I can do to convince you,
- I would.
- I can't promise anything.
What about a big brother
kind of thing?
Let me talk to some
of my community leaders
and see exactly what
the community needs...
I'm not talking about
for a long time.
Maybe for one afternoon,
to a movie or something.
Um, is that a key
to the men's room?
Well, it says "men"
on it. Yes.
It's a natural question
to ask.
- Yes.
- May I borrow the key?
- Yes, you may borrow the key.
- Thank you.
Okay.
Thanks, Mr. Jones.
- And you'll think about it?
- I will.
By the way...
Iove the bow-tie.
- What are you doing?!
- Using the bathroom.
That's my stall!
Did you see the plaque on it...
Yes, I know, but somebody was using
the other one, so l...
Well, then you wait!
I couldn't wait.
It was an emergency. I had to go!
There's one stall for me,
and you're in it!
If you were here,
I would have given you first dibs.
But honestly, I haven't seen
a handicapped person in the bathroom,
maybe ever. So I thought I could
perhaps take my chances.
"A handicapped person"?
That's nice.
Oh, that's nice!
- It's called disabled. Disabled.
- Disabled?
Well, that doesn't
sound so hot.
I don't really care what it sounds like
to you, okay? It's disabled.
I think I would prefer
handicapped.
God, you know how archaic that word is?
"A handicapped person"!
That's demeaning,
don't you know?
- I'm a disabled person.
- Oh, sorry.
- You're sorry.
Now you've learned a lesson.
Please, don't ever go
- in my stall again! All right?
- Fine, okay.
- Thanks so much!
- You're welcome.
- I appreciate it.
Douche-bag.
So you think
he's a Muslim?
- He had the bow-tie.
- Huh?
Do black men who aren't Muslims
ever wear bow-ties?
- I haven't seen it.
- It'd be interesting to find that out.
- I'm surprised you didn't ask him.
- Yeah, me too.
I mean, you know, I don't care
either way, I'm just curious.
Well, I'll tell you something,
that I think he's a Muslim.
Hey, that's
a handicapped spot.
Wh-wh-what?
What's with the walking?
Fuck you!
I have a stutter!
Yeah, but you can walk.
Look at my license plate!
I have permission,
you fucking prick!
Oh hey...
we got a dog.
Really? Why?
- She wanted a dog.
- You have to walk it and everything?
- I'm sure I'll wind up doing stuff.
- Oh, definitely.
I know, yeah, but you know what?
It's kind of cute.
- Larry!
- I kind of like it. Hi!
- Hi!
- Jodi!
- How are you?
- Great, great.
- So good to see you!
- Great to see you.
- Hi Jodi. How are you doing?
- Hi.
- How are you doing,
- Ms. Jodi Funkhouser?
- So what's going on?
- Nothing.
Seeking attention,
getting rejected.
- Are those new glasses?
- No, but I cleaned them.
You're so funny!
- I'm here with my dad.
- Oh yeah?
Are you coming to my parents'
25th anniversary party?
I am.
- Oh. Are you?
- Eh...
It'll be fun, really.
Think about it.
I'm not gonna think about it,
but whatever.
- I really hope you come.
- Well, thanks.
- It's so good to see you.
- Good to see you.
- Wow, great to see you.
- Yeah. Bye-bye.
Bye.
All right,
is it my imagination?
Does she like you that much or does
she dislike me that much?
Oh, lesbians love me.
They love me.
- How is that?
- Well, when I first got to L.A.
You remember... you know Patty,
my friend Patty.
- Patty, yeah.
- Well, she's a lesbian.
- Yes.
- You know, so, obviously,
they talk amongst themselves,
and the word got out
that I'm a friend
o' lesbians.
- You're a friend o' lesbians!
- Yes, they know that.
So the community
has completely embraced you.
Totally embraced me.
Completely.
More so than any other
community.
Including Jews.
- Ready? This way.
- Hi, two. Yeah.
Oh, Jeez.
The men's room key from the private
investigator's office.
I forgot
to bring it back.
- I'm always doing that.
- Hey,
check out
the bow-tie here.
It's a smart look.
I think I'm gonna
get me one of those.
You know what?
You oughtta try wearing a bow-tie.
- It'd be a good look for you. Hi!
- Hi.
- How are you doing? How are you doing?
- Great!
Hey, thanks for sending
the invite back.
- Oh, sure. I'm excited.
- We're gonna have a blast.
- It's gonna be... are you coming?
- Eh...
- Tell me you're coming. Please.
- I don't know.
25 years of marriage!
- Rosie's coming.
- Rosie O'Donnell?
And I have Larry David's place card
right next to hers.
- Really? You're sitting me next to her?
- Right next to her.
- You know Rosie O'Donnell?
- I know her from New York.
We used to hang out
together doing comedy.
You'll have a great time.
- Just send the invitation back, okay?
- Oh, thank you.
- I'll see you guys there. I'm excited.
- By the way,
- Jodie's really looking good.
- She does look great.
- Doesn't she look great?
- Oh, thanks a lot, yeah.
She's dating a guy.
I think it's serious.
She's dating a guy?!
Yeah, she's no longer gay.
What? You're kidding!
That's fantastic!
Congratulations!
Good for you.
She's not a lesbian
anymore.
Oh my God.
Good going.
All right,
I'll see you, uh, soon.
Yeah, I'll see you
at the party.
Larry, we need to talk.
It's over?
What's over?
The marriage.
Why would our marriage
be over?
You said,
"We need to talk."
Yeah, we need to talk about
Marty Funkhouser's party!
Oh, okay. I thought...
- eh, forget it.
- No no no, what did you think?
Well, you know, you said,
"We need to talk."
Generally,
when couples break up,
that's how they introduce it, you know,
"We need to talk."
- So I just thought it was...
- Well, why would you...
why would you
even think that?
Well, because women
have broken up with me many times,
and they've always introduced it with
"We need to talk."
So I'm just sort of conditioned
for that response.
And when women
broke up with you,
did you light up
like that?
Light up?
- Yeah.
- Did I light up?
"Oh, it's over?"
You know, it could have been
a defense mechanism.
That's how I react to things.
I go the other way,
so I don't get hurt.
I protect myself.
You understand. So what about the party?
Marty Funkhouser's party...
Have you been thinking
about this for a while?
No! Not at all!
No, of course not.
So what about
the Funkhouser party?
Well, I wanted to know
if we're going or not.
I need to send in
the RSVP and...
I wasn't going, and now
I've changed my mind.
Rosie O'Donnell's
gonna be there.
Our table.
And you know what else?
I might wear a bow-tie.
- What do you think of that?
- You're gonna wear a bow-tie?
Are you loving that?
Is that fantastic?
How about that
for an idea, huh?
I, well...
You're gonna love it.
- Well, look who's here.
- Wanda!
- Look who's here.
- How are you doing?
Welcome!
This is our new house.
- What do you think?
- Well, what do you think?
- Oh, the rental house.
- This is a rental.
It's just for a few months
until the renovation's done. You know.
Shit, I mean, you're renting,
so I can be honest.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I don't like it.
- Kinda cold, like a hotel.
- Yeah.
A hotel? Hotels are good.
You know, there's a lot of activity
in the hotel lobby.
I think that's a good thing.
Why don't you put
a little bellman's cap on...
- Okay, I'll put a bellman's cap on.
...and run around.
Put a little concierge desk
over there.
- Hey, Wanda, let me ask you a question.
- What?
Is it wrong to assume
that a black man wearing a bow-tie
is a Muslim?
Why are you asking me
some bullshit like that?
What the fuck, Larry?!
I'm not your link
into the black world, okay?
So stop asking me shit about black
people and stuff, all right?
Okay, but let me
ask you this:
Have you ever seen
a black man wearing a bow-tie
- who's not a Muslim?
- Who gives a fuck?
It's just something
you may have observed.
- Have you observed...
- Larry, I don't...
- Have you ever observed a black man...
...who's not a Muslim wearing
a bow-tie? That's all.
You think Farrakhan
went out and bought up
all the bow-ties
or something?
He's sitting there
holding on to bow-ties
and only Muslims get 'em?
What the fuck, Larry?
You... what... no.
I don't know.
Fair enough.
Good answer.
"I don't know."
I totally accept it.
- I got the dog.
- That's what I want to see.
- You've got to see him. Sheriff!
- Sheriff!
- Hello boy!
- He's a cutie!
- What the hell...
- I think it's you, Wanda.
- One of y'all wanna grab Cujo?
- Um...
Come on, it's just Wanda.
It's just Wanda.
I'm sorry.
He's very friendly.
We're all done in there.
Just, uh, you have to wait
overnight for the...
hey! Hey, little buddy.
Come here.
What's wrong
with your dog?
I don't know.
See how friendly he is?
Good dog!
He probably smells my dog.
- Hey! Shit!
- Oh my God!
- God!
- Hey, come on!
Get over here.
- What's with...
- I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
What did you do?
- I'm really sorry.
- It's okay.
I don't know
what's going on.
- I've never seen him like this.
- I'm really sorry.
- You know what's going on.
- Huh?
You have a racist dog!
- That dog hates black people.
- Wanda.
Larry, you trained the dog
to hate black people?
No, I didn't train it
to hate black people.
Has it barked
at any white people?
No, he's... he's...
He hasn't barked
at any white people.
Exactly.
The dog is racist.
Sheriff's racist?
Sheriff?!
That's a perfect name
for a racist dog.
Where did you get this dog,
the Klan meeting or something?
- Larry picked him out at the pound.
- The pound.
Sheriff the fucking dog
that eats black people.
What the fuck, man?
I'll tell you what,
y'all stay here
and pet your crazy-ass racist dog,
but I am not bringing
my black ass
back up into this
fucking hotel
until y'all get rid
of that fucking Klan dog.
Got a Klan dog!
Looking at me
like I'm a damn T-bone.
- I'll call you.
- Aw, shut up.
So we have three choices.
I'm sorry, the first
that we have is
a skirt steak...
Look, I can't...
I can't hear you.
I can't hear. Could you repeat that?
What's that?
It's a skirt steak, sir,
or stir fry,
uh, and that's...
Excuse me.
Excuse me, could you just
keep it down a little bit?
We can't hear the waiter.
We're trying to order.
- Keep it down?
- We're trying to hear the waiter.
I'm trying to have a good time with my
family over here. Know what I mean?
I'm not keeping it down.
I'm sorry,
we need to keep it down
for Tucker Carlson over here.
"Keep it down"!
- Tucker Carlson?
- Tucker Carlson.
There's a chicken rotisserie
and a portobello
mushroom salad.
- Salad?
- Yeah, well the portobello
is cut up
onto mixed greens.
- Are you a vegetarian?
- Yeah, it depends.
- She is.
- Yeah.
So that would sort of be the best
choice. It's really good.
I'm gonna get the skirt steak.
Want me to order for you?
- What do you want?
- Get me the chicken.
Excuse me.
Uh, I'll have
the portobello, yeah.
- Hey, Sue.
- What?
What's with the snub?
Oh, come on, Larry.
You're acting
like you don't know?
What?
I don't know why...
What did I do?
All right, let me
give you a clue, okay?
Starts with a "J"
and it ends with an "I."
Jedi?
- You know...
- What?
It's Jodi, okay?
Wh-what did you hear?
Well, I heard that you
just got so excited,
like you were so happy
that she wasn't with women anymore.
- That's ridiculous.
- It's not ridiculous.
- I was happy for him.
- I don't know what's happened to you.
I wasn't really happy for him,
I was pretending I was happy for him.
- Oh really?
- But that's all. I was just pretending.
- No no no no.
- No, I wasn't sincere.
I wasn't sincerely excited.
- You're not being sincere now.
- No, now I'm being sincere.
You know, the lesbian community
used to revere you.
- You used to be such a liberal guy.
- I'm liberal.
- No, you're not liberal.
- I am liberal.
Look what you look like.
Look at the bow-tie.
The bow-tie... I just tried out
a bow-tie, so what?
Excuse me, excuse me.
You know what? I'm sorry.
Don't even waste your time
talking to this man.
This man is a racist.
He has a racist dog.
He has a dog
that attacks black people.
Okay, I do...
the dog is racist.
- But I didn't train him to be racist.
- Larry, forget about it.
How do you know that?
Because we talk, Larry.
Are you having fun
or what?
What did you tell Jodi?
I told her you were just maybe
a little overjoyous
at the fact that she
was dating a boy.
- That's all I said.
- All the lesbians hate me now.
- Oh, so it's my fault?
- Yes it is!
You celebrated!
I was pretending to be happy
for your benefit.
- I don't need benefit!
- You need benefit!
- What do I need benefit for?
- You need benefit.
I'm happy if Jodi's happy.
You're overblowing this whole thing.
- I don't think so.
- We're at a party.
I don't like being
snubbed by lesbians.
- It's their prerogative.
- I'm their biggest supporter.
- You're their biggest supporter?
- Yes I am!
Well, they're in trouble then.
By the way,
where's Rosie O'Donnell?
She's not here yet.
Sure you invited her?
She'll be here.
- When?
- Soon.
Okay.
Dan, Danny, come over here.
I want you to meet somebody.
This is Jodi's new boyfriend.
This is Larry David.
- Hi, how are you?
- How are you doing?
- Have a good time.
- Okay.
Hey, by the way,
you and Jodi...
- fantastic, great news.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Pretty good.
- Yes it is indeed.
Pretty, pretty,
pretty, pretty good.
- Yeah.
- Terrific.
And to have to overcome
the whole situation,
the whole sexual thing,
you know?
Oh. Oh, there's nothing
to overcome, really.
Well, you know, the fact that she's been
with women before you.
- I know...
- I'd be really intimidated by that,
- because, you know, we really...
- Intimidated?
Well, because we don't know
what we're doing
as much as the women know.
You know, it's their equipment.
They own the equipment,
so they know what to do with it.
You know what's
going on down there?
- I don't have any idea.
- I'd like to think I do.
That whole area is so
mysterious to me, you know?
- I'm just saying it's...
- Well, I mean...
I'd be intimidated,
I know that.
Yeah.
I always wondered, do you walk around
in your bikini at home?
The way he talks,
you'd think that he's got...
Hey. I think I want
to go home.
Let's go home.
No, we haven't even
had dessert yet.
So what? We don't need dessert.
Come on.
Well, it's rude.
You stay for dessert.
- Then you can go.
- So what, dessert? It's no big deal.
- We can just go. Come on.
- Why do you want to go home?
I need to use
the bathroom.
- So go use the bathroom.
- I don't want to use this bathroom.
- I want my own...
- Why?
This project demands
I get back to my base.
I need my base.
- We're not going home...
- What's the matter?
- Larry wants to go home...
- What...
to use the bathroom.
It's like...
Cheryl, you need to tell
the whole table?
- Why don't you make an announcement?
- Hold on here.
You've never done that with me at lunch?
It's the craziest thing.
It's ridiculous.
He can use this bathroom.
- That's what everybody...
- You're a gentile.
You'll go in the middle of Fifth Avenue.
It's different for Jews.
- No, you're at an affair.
- What?
You cannot leave an affair before
the dessert is served.
What is this dessert thing?
We don't have to leave after.
- We can leave before dessert.
- Better to leave after.
No, you do not leave
before dessert.
Who made this up?
Where's this rule?
Everybody here seems to know,
but the rules don't apply to you?
What am I supposed to do?
Sit here for four hours
and be uncomfortable?
Should I go clean it for you
before you go in there?
- It's not even the cleanliness.
- Okay, just go.
We don't need to talk
about your bathroom...
- so just go.
- You're the one who's telling everybody
- in the whole place!
- Just go!
Hey, where do you think you're going,
pal? What are you doing?
I'm going to the bathroom.
- That's a handicapped stall.
- We're waiting in line.
I have a stutter,
you pricks!
Stutter my ass!
That's for people who can't walk.
Oh, all right, fine, okay.
Oh, your stutter's gone,
jackass!
- Give me a fucking break, asshole.
- Stupid ass.
All right, that sounds good.
All right, I'll see you
in about 10-15 minutes.
All right, great.
Hey.
- I'll see you in a few hours.
- Huh? Few hours?
- Yeah.
- Where are you going?
I'm meeting Julie.
- Don't forget to take the dog out.
- Hello.
Out? What do you mean?
Out for a walk or out with me?
Hello, Mr. David.
- This is Omar Jones.
- Oh, hi.
I gotta tell you, Mr. David,
I was thinking about taking the case,
but I got a distressing
call today
about your behavior
last night at the banquet.
What are you
talking about?
According to one
of the brothers, you said,
"Keep it down."
No no, all that happened was
I was trying to order
and I couldn't hear the waiter
because some of your brothers
were making too much noise
at the next table, that's all.
How do you even know
about this?
We talk, Mr. David.
We talk.
- Huh.
- And what about my bathroom key?
I'm really sorry about that.
I'm returning it today, I promise.
Well, like I said,
I'm gonna have to think about it.
Thank you.
How was everything?
- Pretty good.
- Great.
Do you want coffee,
dessert, on the house?
- On the house?
- Yeah.
I'll have a cupcake.
- I'll take a dessert on the house.
- Okay.
- Fabulous. Thank you.
- Are those new glasses?
No, I just cleaned them.
It's nice
to have you back, Larry.
You, my friend, are back
in the lesbian bosom.
Wow.
- I'm back.
- You are back.
By the looks of things,
better than ever.
But what... I wonder
what turned it around.
Oh dear. Uh-oh.
What?
- What does Funkhouser want?
- I don't know.
I'll be right back.
How did he even know I was here?
What did you say to Dan?
What did l...
hello, boy.
- Did you meet Sheriff, my dog?
- No, I didn't.
I said, "Dan, this is Larry David."
Then I left you.
- And I said hi, I said hello.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I said, "Hi, Dan."
- Yeah, what else?
You know, a little small talk,
"Hi, how are you doing?
- Where are you from?" and all that.
- That's it?
And then, what did
I say? I said,
"It must be hard,
as a guy, to follow..."
Why didn't you just say,
"Hello, I'm Larry. Nice to meet you"?
I said that after hi.
I said hi, then I said that.
- What is wrong with you?
- Problem?
Yeah, problem.
Now she's back with a woman.
No wonder why they're all being
so nice to me in there.
They're all smiling at me.
Of course, it makes perfect sense.
- I want to say something else.
- Uh-huh.
You left my party
before dessert!
How can you do that?!
It's not proper etiquette!
I don't subscribe
to the wait-for-dessert rule
before you can leave a party.
Yeah, no one cares
what you subscribe to, okay?
We were trying to recreate
what happened 25 years ago,
and I said, "Larry, would you like
to make a toast?"
And someone said,
"Larry went home to take a shit."
Ah.
You stay here.
Okay, boy?
You stay, Sheriff.
- Hey!
- Hey, Larry.
- Hey, hi!
- How are you?
- Great.
- Good to see you.
Hey, by the way,
I don't know
if you heard anything
about what's been going on...
- Come on, I heard. I'm in the loop.
- Yeah, right. Yeah, yeah.
It's all right, though.
I don't think you should
worry about it. Just...
it's all good now.
You know, what happened
that day was
I just got a little excited,
but not...
Hey hey hey hey, Larr.
I stood up at the meeting,
I told everybody,
"I know the guy."
I vouched for you.
You're all right.
- You're something, you know that?
- Come on, come on!
- It all worked out, right?
- It's great.
- She's happy, we're happy, you know?
- Fantastic.
She's back on the team. Everything's
good. Don't even think about it.
- Fantastic.
- All right.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
You know, we missed you
at Funkhouser's party.
The what?
Marty Funkhouser's
25th anniversary party.
- Oh, Jodi's dad?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I don't really
know him. No.
- You weren't invited to that?
- Nope, no no no.
Was it good?
Did you go?
- Yeah, yeah, I went.
- Yeah, it was good?
And don't worry
about that other thing.
I just want you to know,
gone, like it never happened.
- Okay? Like it never happened.
- Thanks, sweetheart.
- All the lesbians love you.
- Okay, love you.
- I love you back.
- Love you.
I love you.
Everyone loves you. All of us.
You are a Muslim!
Go, pray, pray.
Let me ask you something.
Are brothers and sisters
a little overly sensitive
to being told
to keep it down?
Because I know in the movies
you guys tend to make
a lot of noise sometimes.
Am I right?
'Cause that's kind of
what happened at the party.
What, did l...
No, go back.
Did I interrupt the praying?
I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
- All right.
- Listen, Mr. David...
- Look at the way you fold that up.
It's like a yoga mat, huh?
I just want you to know
that Muslims are
a very forgiving people.
They are?
- Yes we are. We're very forgiving.
- Really? Huh.
- Well, it's true.
- There's a lot
of meshugana Muslims,
though, running around, are there not?
Being that we are a forgiving people,
I have decided
to take on your case.
But I'm gonna have
to charge you
a higher rate
than I charge most people.
Well, whatever you have
to do.
- You're gonna take the case?
- I'm gonna take the case.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Do Muslims shake?
- Yes, we do.
- You do?
- Great.
To tell you the truth,
I'm very excited
about this.
The whole adoption thing...
I mean, this could be
a huge thing for me.
All right, Mr. David.
Oh, guess what.
Bathroom key.
You know what?
I gotta go again.
I'm so sorry.
All right.
Well, looky here!
Look what's doing here!
Aren't you supposed
to be in here?
It seems to me you're
using the wrong toilet.
Somebody was in there.
I had to use the normal one.
Really?
First of all,
we don't like to be referred
to as "normal," okay?
We're "able-bodied."
"Able-bodied," not "normal."
That's like from the '80s.
Who doesn't know that?
I had to go to the bathroom.
Somebody was in there.
Well, then you wait.
You wait.
All right, Sheriff!
Okay, good boy!
Good boy.
Mr. David.
My bathroom key.
Hey, nice dog.
No, don't!
I love dogs.
I have a couple of my own.
All right,
just give me my key.
Oh, I can't believe
I forgot.
Hopefully we won't have to keep going
through the same thing.
I'm sorry. Won't happen again.
Won't happen again.
- Nice dog.
- Thank you. Good to see you.
Hey!
Good boy, good boy!
Yeah!
Oh, look!
You got yourself
a doggie!
Sorry.