- Jones Security.
- Larry David for Omar Jones.
All right, Mr. David.
What's this call regarding?
Uh, he... he'll know
what it's about. I'm a client.
Got that, but what
is the call regarding?
- To be honest, it's kind of personal.
- I'm sure it is.
You can't speak to him until you
tell me what this is regarding.
But it has nothing to do with you.
It has to do with him.
I don't really wanna
tell you what it's about.
Sir, you're gonna need
to control your levels and tell me
- what this call is regarding.
- Do me a favor,
tell me the details
of your last conversation.
That's none
of your business!
Exactly.
Oh, fuck.
Ahh.
Schmuck!
Fucking idiot!
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
- Hey, what's up?
- I locked myself out of my car.
Oh, Jeez.
All right,
I'll come get ya.
Welcome to Jack in the Box.
May I have your order?
I'd like, um...
two Jumbo Jacks,
French fries,
and a Diet Coke.
Sir, are you
in a car?
No.
Sir, this is
a drive-thru line.
You have to be
in a car to order.
- What's the difference?
- It's our policy.
This is a drive-thru line.
One second!
Come on, I'm starving.
There's no... everything...
everything's closed.
- I wish I could help you, sir.
- Oh, yeah, right.
Could you do me a favor?
They won't let me order any food
unless I'm in a car.
Will you...
They won't let me order
any food unless I'm in a car.
- Would you mind if l...
- No, I'm sorry.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry to bother you.
I'm trying to get some food.
They won't let me order
unless I'm in a car.
- No kidding.
- It's crazy.
Huh? It's just insane.
- I'll tell you what.
- Yeah.
- Get in.
- Really?
- Get in the car.
- Oh.
I tell you, Pete,
- should have got the Jumbo Jack.
- Do yourself a favor...
- Yeah.
- The next time you come through,
- go for the Bacon Bacon Cheeseburger
- Huh.
And the Asian salad.
A strange combination,
but it goes down easy,
and it comes out fast.
I don't need
to tell you more.
- Mmm.
- What kind of work you do, Pete?
Good question.
I'm in...
I'm in a transition
at the moment.
I'm...
- I was involved in the dental field...
- Dental field?
- For about eight months.
- What'd you do in the dental field?
Uh, I worked alongside
a dental hygienist.
Really?
What does somebody do
working alongside
a dental hygienist?
I watched and worked closely
with a dental hygienist.
Hmm.
- And...
- And what happened?
Um, we ran
into some problems.
And I prefer
to leave it at that.
- Okay.
- I found myself...
drawn to landscaping work.
It's...
it's... it's...
it's a slow transition.
I'm... I'm...
- You got some...
- Huh?
- Some porno back there?
- Yeah...
No, that's not mine.
That was...
that was left by a couple
of my co-workers.
- Boy, that's quite a collection.
- Yeah.
Well, I had no idea
that that was there.
L... that's not mine
to begin with, so...
I find it all...
- Oh, hey!
- Jesus!
- Hey.
- You ready to go?
Scared the hell
out of me.
- This is Pete.
- Hey, Pete, how you doing?
- Hey.
- This is Jeff.
- Jeff.
- Thank you for helping out my friend.
Okay.
So are you involved
in "Seinfeld" as well?
No. No no no.
How do you fellas
know each other?
- Mmph...
- He's my manager.
- I'm his manager.
- Okay.
- Oh, man. Jumbo Jack.
- Did I tell you? Huh?
- Best thing ever!
- How unbelievable is that?
Unbelievable.
I'm sorry,
but I got some bad news.
- Oh. Lewis?
- Yeah.
- Ah.
- Kidney?
- Yeah, both of them.
- He's gonna need a new one.
- Oh, well,
- is there a donor?
- I don't know.
What's he gonna do?
I don't know.
He's gotta find
somebody who can...
who can match. Hopefully, he knows
somebody who's...
got the right
kidney for him
and then it's a whole process
of... you know,
first, the person who...
has to be tested,
and then if they have the right kidney,
then they have the surgery...
- Can you believe it?
- Yeah.
No donor. No donor.
Oh, God.
My luck.
With all
the people I know.
Oh, God.
What about your relatives? They're the
ones who're supposed to be doing it
'cause they have
the same blood and all that.
Didn't you have some idiot cousin living
out here or something?
- Louis Lewis?
- Louis Lewis.
- Please.
- What about him?
Might as well be called
Manson Manson.
He's a nutcase. He's... he works
at Jack in the Box and...
Jack in the Box.
I was just there the other night.
Had a Jumbo Jack...
pretty good.
I'm glad
you liked it.
So did you ask this Louis Lewis?
What did he say?
He wants to donate
all his organs after he dies,
but not a minute before.
Thank you, Louis Lewis.
Doesn't help me any.
Schmuck.
I'm gonna have to get
on that kidney list
like everybody else.
Shit.
I mean, the only
other option is if...
you know, if a... you know, if a...
if a good friend
or a buddy comes through.
Then I'm... you know,
then I'm golden.
Hmm.
I don't know what to do.
Just the test
isn't gonna hurt you.
I gotta choose
healthier friends.
This is no good.
The next time there's any sign
of anything wrong
with any of my friends... if I think
they're gonna be going to the hospital,
any sign of anything,
I'm just...
I'm just gonna drop them
like a hot potato.
- Smart.
- And you too.
I mean, as soon as you get sick,
I'm out.
- You know that, right?
- Oh, well,
I'm glad you're bringing it up
'cause it's...
- Well, I mean, come on.
- No, it's nice to know.
- Yeah, and I'm giving you...
- Although, I thought
that that's what
the whole deal was.
It's one of the reasons
you get married.
Normally, that is the deal,
but we...
we're losing the sickness
and health clause.
- I'm out if anything's wrong with you.
- Okay.
- And look, same for you.
- Thank you.
- You go too, as soon as...
- I will.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- I can't be around illness.
- But for now?
- Freaks me out, okay?
It'll be such
a nice gesture
and he'd really
appreciate it.
All right,
I'll take the test.
- I think you're doing the right thing.
- Yeah, great.
He's going to feel
very good about that.
- Yeah, I know.
- You're a very sweet friend.
It's very sweet.
- Good night.
- What are you doing?
How 'bout
a nice snuggle here?
I know, but your snuggle
always leads to sex.
So what's wrong with that?
Why shouldn't it lead to sex?
Sometimes you just want to snuggle
and you don't want to have sex.
What's the advantage
of that?
Because it's nice.
You connect
and it's warm
and sweet.
- Okay, let's just snuggle.
- You can do that?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Without it turning into anything?
- Yeah, we'll just snuggle.
- See? It's sweet. That's nice.
See...
how nice it is?
- Okay, what are you doing?
- What? What?!
- That's exactly what I'm talking about.
- What's the problem?!
- The ass is part of my snuggle.
- No, it's not.
- It is!
- Okay, then good night.
We'll snuggle
another time.
- It's just... it's just a lever.
- Good night.
I'm using the ass
as a lever to draw you in.
That's all.
And it gets...
the snuggle tighter.
Good night.
- Richard Lewis's office.
- Larry David calling.
Sure.
What's this regarding?
It's regarding
his kidney transplant.
What?
It's regarding
his kidney transplant.
Mr. Lewis is getting
a kidney transplant?
What?
What are you saying?
He didn't say anything
to me about it.
You didn't know about this?
- Are you kidding?
- Oh my God!
He didn't tell you this?
He didn't tell you that there was
a problem with his kidneys?
- No, he didn't tell me anything!
- How could he have not
- told you about this?!
- I don't know, but he didn't
tell me anything about this!
Oh Jeez. You asked me
what it was regarding!
I didn't know it was going to be about
something like this!
But l... I wouldn't have said anything!
You asked me!
I could have sworn he...
I figured he told you!
He didn't say
anything to me.
Oh my God.
- Take it easy.
- No.
Could you tell him
I called?
- Okay.
- Thanks.
What did you
do to my assistant?
- What are you talking about?
- What am I talking about?
She's freaked out, having a nervous
breakdown, and might even quit.
It's un-fucking-believable.
Why would you do that?
She asked me what the call
was regarding!
It's personal!
She asked what it's
regarding, I told her!
Jeez, what am I going to do?
She was a basket case.
Christ's sake.
What am I
going to do?
Hey, um, first of all,
I want to tell you that,
uh...
I thought about our conversation
and, uh...
I'II, uh,
I'll take the test.
- Big fucking deal.
- That's it?!
I mean, you're my friend.
You should have jumped right on it.
You're right, you're right,
but I'm making up...
I'm making it up now.
I'll take the test.
Just close your eyes and think if it was
reversed you'd be really bummed out.
Let me do that. I'm closing my eyes,
but now I'm asking you...
the situation's reversed.
I need the kidney.
- Yeah?
- What are you saying?
Would you take
the test?
- I'd probably want to leap at it.
- Probably leap at it?
- L...
- You'd leap out the window.
Let me say this: I would have gone on
record at the deli.
Hello.
Yeah, this is
Larry David.
Um...
yeah, I was at
a Jack in the Box.
Yeah. Pete.
Oh, Christ.
Really?
Well, what's the address?
So, um, you know,
I've decided
to take the test.
- The kidney test for Lewis?
- Oh, good for you.
That's really noble.
- It's the right thing to do.
- Yeah.
- Absolutely.
I was kind of wondering
why you're not doing it.
Why should I do it?
You're his manager. You're his friend.
Why shouldn't you do it?
A lot of people who have managers
and friends need kidneys.
What does that have
to do with anything?
I don't even know
what that means.
- You're his friend. You're his manager.
- Yeah yeah?
You're close to him.
You should be taking the test too.
You're his oldest
and closest friend.
So it's a question of longevity?
That's it?
You're his oldest and closest friend.
That makes the most sense.
If you're married to your wife for three
years and I've known her for 20,
who should give your wife the kidney?
I've known her longer.
By your logic,
I'm the one who should.
If my wife needs a kidney,
you can give it to her.
Oh, okay, so it's
longevity no matter what,
even if you're
married to her.
No, I'm saying
you seemed like
you want to give her a kidney, so I'm
gonna let you.
You know, I'm loathe
to mention this, okay,
but you are
an employee of mine.
Okay, you're
really reaching now.
- You're desperate, aren't you?
- A little.
Yeah, I know. You don't want to
give up your kidney.
- No, why should I?
- I know. Why should I?
- Why should I?
- Well, why should I?
- If I am, you should too.
- When did that rule come into effect?
- What's wrong with it?
- It's not a good rule.
- It's a good rule.
- You have to draw a line.
Kidneys is past the line.
Hey!
- Hey.
- Mr. Jones!
Mr. David, what
are you doing here?
Oh. It's kind
of a long story,
but I had a
burger with a...
at a Jack in the Box
with some guy and now I'm his alibi.
Apparently, I've got to spot him
in a line-up or something.
- I don't know.
- Right.
- Really, that's not the issue here.
- It's true, uh-huh.
- I have a bone to pick with you.
- Me?
Do you have something
against receptionists?
I called up, I was very polite
and respectful,
and she wants to know
what it's regarding.
- I don't see how it's her business...
- I had to talk her into staying.
I'm a private eye,
not a psychologist.
She comes into
my office crying,
you know, wondering
what's going on.
- She's a part of my business.
- Still, it's not you.
I mean, what if you
were a psychiatrist
- and she said "What is it regarding?"
- There's protocol.
"I'm planning on killing myself.
I want to talk to him."
It helps me save time and we ask
those questions so that we're prepared
when the phone call
does get to me.
Okay. I'm sorry
if I did anything that...
Hopefully we can we can avoid these
conflicts, you know?
How's the adoption
thing coming?
I'm working on some things.
I have some really nice leads
and I should have
something to you soon.
- Really? No kidding.
- Pretty soon.
- Omar, good to see you.
- Hey, Ray, how you doing?
- How's Ellen?
- She's good. Pregnant again.
- Really? Third one.
- You Mr. Greene?
- Mr. David.
- Mr. David. Ray.
- That's... that's Mr. Greene.
- This is Larry?
- That's Mr. Greene.
- I'm Mr. David.
- You guys ever do a line-up?
- No.
- Piece of cake. They can't see you.
- Nothing to worry about. Come with me.
- Okay.
- Gentlemen, if you'll come in, please?
- I changed my mind.
- Move up to the glass please.
- I'll take the test.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Good for you.
- I'll take the test. Who knows?
You're taking the test,
I'll take the test.
Gentlemen, could I have you
step up to the glass?
- That's very nice, very nice.
- He'll be very happy.
- No hurry here.
- All right, there he is.
Second from the right.
That's him.
- You're certain of that?
- Yeah. Pete.
- That's Pete?
- That's Pete.
- The gentleman you had dinner with.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
- What time of evening was this?
- 10:15.
- 10:15? That's a late dinner.
- Yeah, 10:15.
My mother used to call
it a late night snack.
Dinner's between 5:00 and 8:00
generally.
- And this was with number two?
- Yeah, 5:00 and 8:00.
You could start
at 8:00 though.
You know who Peter is?
He's a... he worked alongside
of a dental hygienist.
I know that.
- And he did some landscaping.
- Yeah, I don't think so.
Are you gentlemen used to hanging
out with known felons?
'Cause number two
is Peter Hagen,
AKA Peter the Tork,
Peter the Crybaby,
Wendell the Conspirator,
Joshua Lancel Stigmeyer.
You two gentlemen
shared a meal
with number two on the 23rd...
approximately 10:15 P.M.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right.
Let him go. You're
done here, gentlemen.
How do I let you
talk me into this?
What was I thinking?
Who needs this?
I have good news,
gentlemen.
Both of your blood types
are compatible with Mr. Lewis
for his kidney transplant.
Good night, nurse.
Good night.
It's just a saying.
- I never heard of it.
- It's an old one.
- That's nice.
- It is.
- I know it is.
- Do you?
- I do.
- Good for you.
- It is good for me.
- You think so?
- I know so.
- I'm glad.
- So am I.
- That makes two of us.
- So you say.
So I did.
Well, how are
we gonna decide?
We could...
we could play bingo.
Bingo?
- You know, it's... it's fair.
- Me play you in bingo?
That's like asking me to play golf
against Tiger Woods. Play you in bingo?
- What? It's fair... it's a fair game.
- No, thank you.
No. No.
Doesn't he have a...
a cousin?
- Yeah.
- Louis Lewis.
What's going on there?
He doesn't want to give up
his kidney until he's dead.
Louis Lewis.
All right,
you know what?
We'll let Lewis decide.
How about that?
Fine, let Lewis decide.
Yeah, sure sure.
I'll abide by his decision.
Will you?
Yeah, most definitely,
most definitely.
- I'm for that, I'm for that.
- Okay.
- Let's shake on that. Okay.
- Sure sure.
Sure.
No campaigning.
- No. No campaigning.
- No campaigning.
I don't want to find out you've been
calling him up and saying,
- "Oh, he's a lot thinner than I am."
- Find out I've been saying?!
Oh, I'm more likely
to do it than you?
Hey.
Hey, Mr. David.
Um...
first of all, I'm really sorry
about the other day.
I really had no idea
that you didn't know about that.
I'm... I never would have
said anything, obviously.
Is he... is he in?
He's on the phone
with Jeff right now.
Ah.
Well, what's
it regarding?
- I don't know.
- Hmm.
- You didn't ask?
- Nope.
Hmm. I wonder if he's campaigning in
there.
Oh, Jeez.
He didn't even
tell me now.
Now, you... you would
have found out eventually.
No, you...
you would have... oh, Jeez.
He's was... I'm sure
he was gonna tell you.
No, don't...
don't cry.
Oh, poor thing.
Oh, Jeez.
Oh my gosh.
Oh dear.
It's all right,
it's okay.
Don't... don't worry.
I'm sure he was gonna tell you.
Yeah, no, don't worry.
There there, it's okay.
- Wait, what are you doing?
- What?
- What was that?
- What are you talking about?
What the hell, man?
Why did you touch my hair?
I was consoling.
- I was consoling you.
- That wasn't consoling.
Touching hair is part
of my consolation routine.
No, it's really weird.
You're being really inappropriate.
- What? Inappropriate? Are you crazy?
- Yeah, you were.
Hey, what's... what is this?
Again?! Again?!
She's... she's crazy!
I was consoling her!
- He was coming on to me!
- Are you a sociopath?!
I was consoling her
and I touched her hair.
- He was coming on to me!
- That's such baloney!
- I'm leaving.
- I was consoling her.
I touched her hair. She thinks
that's coming on, she's nuts.
What... what a whack job.
Are you kidding me?! I was consoling
her! I was touching her hair.
- That's ridiculous!
- Mm-hmm.
She thinks I'm coming on to her? Get out
of here. Get the hell out of here.
- You think she's leaving or quitting?
- That's a good question.
I don't know.
She said she's leaving.
- Oh, what a hassle.
- Is that leaving or quitting?
- I don't know.
- Same thing happened with Cheryl.
She said she was leaving.
I thought she was leaving me.
She's just going out
to have lunch with her friend.
Cheryl... right now,
look at this... are you...
- you really have evidenced...
- What?
...some pretty
erratic behavior.
Get out of here.
I was touching her hair. She's crazy.
Unbelievable.
So um...
did you get the news?
Huh?
- Thanks. Yeah yeah.
- Huh? How about that?
I'm a lucky man
to have two of you guys
come through for me.
Thank you.
Hey, far out.
So there you go.
You've got your choice.
- Two... two kidneys.
- Wow!
- Of course...
- Very grateful, man.
You know, I...
I am considerably
older than him.
And I'm not gonna... I don't want to get
into that whole game.
But, you know, he's...
there's a difference
when you're younger, obviously.
Nah, a kidney's
a kidney's a kidney.
I'm not so sure about that,
but you know, whatever.
His are bigger too.
It's a big hefty kidney,
could handle a big load
I think, you know?
You could start drinking
again if you wanted to with that thing.
- That, uh...
- Well, in case...
...that hurt my feelings
a little bit, buddy.
- Maybe not that.
- 11 years sober. Thank you.
But, you know, uh...
that's all.
Other than the fact that, you know,
there's a lot about me that
when I got out of college,
you don't know about.
I really didn't
know you then, so...
Please, I've been
through everything.
Well, I don't think
you did what I did, but...
Trust me. Times 30.
Uh, you're not really
getting my drift.
- Listen, it... you're both a match?
- Yeah.
I don't care how you figure it out.
You know what?
Flip a coin, man.
Eeny meeny miney moe.
What do I care?
- Okay.
- All right?
And stay away
from her, will you?
Whack job.
I got to start with me.
Eeny meeny miney moe, catch a tiger
by the toe. If he hollers, let him go.
My mother says to pick this one
and out goes Y-O-U.
Start with me.
Start with me. Start with me.
Okay, I'm gonna
flip this coin
and this will be
the kidney decider, all right?
Um, why don't we do
Eeny meeny?
I thought we were
gonna do a coin flip.
Let's do Eeny meeny.
- We agreed on a coin flip.
- I think I'd rather do Eeny meeny.
- Fine.
- We'll do Eeny meeny miney moe.
- Let's just do it, okay?
- Fine.
- All right, go.
- All right.
And before we go,
I want to say something to you guys
and I mean this.
I admire the both of you.
What you're doing
is an unbelievable act of friendship.
I just wish I had a kidney match
so I could be involved.
Well, you haven't
taken the test.
Are you ready
to do Eeny meeny?
- Yeah.
- Do you want to take the test?
No, I don't think I'm a match anyway.
Let's just do Eeny meeny.
Who wants to be Eeny?
- I'll be Eeny.
- Yeah, you can be Eeny.
- Okay.
- He'll be Eeny.
How come you want me
to be Eeny?
No, it's good.
You should be Eeny.
That's what you want, right? Don't you
want to be Eeny?
Want me to be Eeny?
Do you want me to be Eeny?
- I'll be Eeny. I'll be Eeny.
- Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Eeny meeny miney moe,
catch a tiger by the toe.
If he hollers,
let him go.
My mother says
to pick this one
and out goes Y-O-U.
Yeah yeah yeah!
- What are you excited about?
- No, what do you mean?
- What are you so happy about?
- I won!
- No, you lost!
- Out goes Y-O-U!
No, you lost!
You're out. You're it.
- No no no no no.
- Yes yes.
- No, out goes Y-O-U. You're the loser.
- You you!
- You're the loser.
- No, you're the loser.
- Tell him, tell him, tell him.
- Hold on a minute.
Out goes Y-O-U
give the kidney.
- You give the kidney.
- No no no.
You stupid idiots! You don't even know
how to play Eeny meeny miney moe.
- We're idiots?!
- I don't know how to play Eeny meeny?
You don't know the first
thing about Eeny meeny!
- Y-O-U. Your'e out.
- No, I'm safe.
What the hell is all
this screaming about?
- Lose with dignity.
- All right, wait a second.
We're playing
Eeny meeny miney moe, okay?
- Out goes Y-O-U.
- Right, you're it.
- Who's it?
- You're it.
- Out goes Y-O-U.
- No, that person's safe.
- He's you.
- No, and out goes Y-O-U.
You're it.
- You're it. You lose.
- You fucking idiots here!
What are we talking about anyway?
Losing what?
They're giving a kidney
to Richard Lewis.
- He's the one.
- He lost.
Excuse me, you're not giving
your fucking kidney.
What if one your kids
needs a kidney one day?
You're gonna give a kidney
to Richard Lewis? No no no!
- You'll give it to 'em.
- I might not be the match.
He needs his kidney, number one. Number
two, he's a fat fuck.
- He can't even survive surgery.
- How do you know?
You are healthy and thin.
You're giving the kidney.
End of discussion,
moot point.
Out goes Y-O-U.
So I'm out.
I'm the winner.
No, that means
you're out
and the other people
stay in.
That's if you're playing
with more than two.
If you're playing
with just two people,
then the one who's out
is the winner...
out goes Y-O-U.
I'm out, he's in.
He's the winner.
Have you ever played
Eeny meeny miney moe?
- Yeah, I have. That's how it works.
- Have you?
Listen, I grew up with Eeny meeny
miney moe... grew up with it.
- I did too!
- I know the rules of the game.
I think you're being
a baby right now.
You know,
it's totally unfair.
I take care of myself
all these years...
the diet, the exercise,
the whole thing,
for what?
I'd have been better off
just eating crap and smoking.
That's what I should have been doing all
these years... eating crap and smoking.
Maybe this is why
you were saved
when you were
drowning that day.
Maybe this is...
the reason.
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
Oh, he saved me
so I can give up a kidney?
That's why?
If he wants to get so involved,
why doesn't he just fix his kidney
tonight while he's sleeping
instead of going through
all this drowning-saving business?
Well, I think you're
doing the right thing.
Don't you feel good
about doing this for Richard?
- No.
- Yes you do.
I don't.
I feel awful.
Think about how
he's feeling right now.
He feels good.
- Well, doesn't that make you feel good?
- No.
- Well, you should.
- I don't.
- You're gonna be okay.
- I'm not.
- Yes you are.
- No I'm not.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Aww.
- Thank you.
Okay, you're welcome.
I'll be here.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you...
- What are you doing?
- What?
- You're turning consolation into sex?
Well, that's the ultimate
form of consolation.
- No, it's not.
- Yeah, sure it is.
Okay, just forget it.
You were consoling me
and that's... that's consolation to me.
Sex is consolation.
Isn't that consolation. No?
This has been
the third hold-up
of a Jack in the Box
in the past two months.
Police believe that the suspect,
Peter Hagen, is responsible.
Hey, that's that guy Pete...
the guy I got out of jail.
The victim of the shooting
in this case,
a Mr. Louis Lewis...
cousin of actor-comedian
Richard Lewis, is in a coma
and is not expected
to survive.
This is Kelvin Han Yee
live from Studio City.