So far this year, Simon's pursuit of
carly hadn't been going that well.
Simon.
But at least it could only get better.
Or stay the same.
Are you wearing a
homeless person's shoes?
Uh...
Or get worse.
[Retches]
[Screaming]
Oh, no.
But if Simon thought he had
it bad, at least he wasn't
sitting in the student lounge
with a bucket on his head.
[Laughing] Bucket.
Good one, Donovan.
Don't talk to me.
Cool.
Can someone please help me?
Hey, maybe he needs air holes.
Ow. Ow.
Could someone other than Neil help me?
Oh, sorry, Will.
Donovan won't allow it.
Understood.
So what are we up to this weekend?
I don't know about you guys, but
I'm gonna go to an RV resort
where I'm playing some
womb raider with my dong.
[Laughter]
Right, anyone doing something
not made up this weekend?
It's not made up, bucket.
Bucket on your head.
I would have just gone
with bucket head.
Ah, sorry.
I'm a little distracted by how many
lady caves I'm gonna be spelunking...
With my dong!
[Laughter]
I love that you can
add that to anything.
"With my dong."
[Laughter]
Nice try.
Keep practicing.
Or just add it to a ridiculous lie.
Pfff, I'm not lying.
RV resorts are certified
fur-trapping zones.
Come if you don't believe me.
All right, I'm in.
Sure, let's go.
What?
We'll all come along. Neil?
Yeah, I'll come.
With my dong.
[Laughter]
[Laughs wheezingly]
Good, then.
Come.
Come and we'll see who's lying.
You are.
You're lying.
Hey, guys.
Will.
Hi, Carly.
So what's going on?
Big plans this weekend?
Yeah, Jay's taking us to an RV park.
RV resort.
Oh, right.
It's not a place poor people live.
It's a place poor people visit.
But if you want to do
something, I can get out of it.
An RV resort sounds awful.
Oh, I think it sounds fun.
It will be.
You should come.
Oh, sorry, I can't.
Bobby's taking me free climbing.
It's his big passion, so
he wants to teach me.
Wow.
That's, like, no ropes, right?
Mm-hmm.
I bet the best way to learn is just to
hang out on the ground and watch him fall.
[Snickers]
Have a nice weekend.
They're doing extreme sports together?
I can't compete with that.
Don't compete, okay?
Forget about Carly and get some
other girl on your dipstick.
I don't know if I can.
But going to an RV park is
better than sitting in my
room writing songs
about her all weekend.
So you guys are really gonna come?
Yeah.
Yeah, with my dong.
[Laughter]
That is so good.
Do you get it?
That was the best one so far.
But do you get it?
Stop it!
You're a joke stealer, Neil.
[Bell rings]
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
The next day, we headed to Sandy Springs
RV Resort, Jay's promised land of low
income, hedonistic delight.
I think we should stop
and get some gas.
Hell, no, man.
We're almost there.
I can smell the minch.
We're on empty.
Is the light on?
No.
Then we're fine.
Now it's on.
Okay, that means we have
20 miles left in the tank.
It's actually not as simple as that.
How big is your tank?
I don't know.
As small as one can be?
Well, let's say you
have one gallon left.
If you get about 18 miles per gallon and
you're going under 60 miles an hour--
Ah, shut up with the math, Aristotle.
Not sure what Aristotle
has to do with math.
Simon, have I ever lied to you?
Trust me, man.
We're gonna make it.
[Grunting]
Told you we'd make it.
We didn't make it.
We'll be inside, Simon.
Stupid car.
Really?
Ooh, boobies.
Oh, man.
What?
Those are totally real.
I think so.
I'd have to titty-titty bang-bang
them to know for sure.
They're fake.
You can see the incision
scars right there.
Maybe she just had a c-section.
No, they're fake.
Aren't we smart, Dr. Copernicus?
Copernicus was not a doctor.
Dentist, whatever.
Come on.
[Grunting]
Come... I hate you.
[Phone chiming]
Get out.
There's something really
beautiful about print porn.
It's a lost art.
Where we're going, we don't need porn.
[Chuckles]
I just got a text from a girl
named Becky at the resort.
Mm-hmm.
She said, "Hi, Simon.
I'm Becky.
Jay gave me your number.
Can't wait to meet you this weekend."
Smiley face.
Boom!
See what I mean?
Who needs Carly?
Becky is an RV'er, and she loves sex.
You don't want her for yourself?
No, Becky's bringing her
cousin rose this weekend,
who apparently is even hornier
than she is, so I'm definitely
gonna be tapping that.
Maybe Slytherin to her Gryffindor.
[Chuckles]
Maybe send my Harry
Potter after her snitch.
Maybe Hufflepuff... Moaning Myrtle...Her...
What do I text back?
As many question marks as you can type.
How about, "Pleasure
to meet you, Rebecca.
I look forward to seeing
you this weekend."
No, try this.
"I can't wait to 'eight equals
equals P hyphen hyphen'
all over your smiley face."
[Chuckles]
I just wrote, "Can't wait."
Winky face.
[Makes farting noise]
[Phone chimes]
X mouth face.
What the hell's an X mouth face?
It means mouth marks the spot...
Both: For your dong.
Stop it!
Don't steal my setups.
I don't know if I could lose it
to someone other than Carly.
"Ooh, I don't know."
Then you're never gonna lose it, Simon.
Because with Carly, you want it too
bad, and girls can sense that.
You need to push her out of your
mind and bang some hoes, okay?
Get some lady pelts on your wall.
Sounds like he's gonna kill them.
He is.
With his--
Don't! Damn it!
God damn it.
That one was perfectly teed up.
Are you even sure this girl will do it?
I am positive she'll do it,
as long as you have this.
This, my friends, is the legacy
condom, passed down from my brother
which was passed down by
his friends before him.
This will definitely
get you laid, Simon.
So can use this?
No, no, no, no.
It's more of a good luck charm.
Why is an unused condom good luck?
Because it got 50 guys laid, Will.
That's why.
That's a lot of guys.
[Chuckles]
I'm gonna Hufflepuff...
Pump number six and this gum, please.
You know, this one
comes with a free DVD.
Yeah.
Go get that.
Could I-- can I just get
20 on number...
Really?
It's for my friend.
And finally we arrived
at the promised land.
Oh, yeah, Jay, sex here
looks very promising.
If they die while we're
doing it, is it murder?
It's manslaughter.
Then I guess I'd be in prison.
Ooh, looks like your chariot awaits.
Becky!
Don't forget about your
slutty little cousin.
[Slowed down] Jesus Christ.
Jay, she's not that bad.
Not that bad?
I've seen bean bags in better shape.
That's rude.
I can feel her walking.
She's a human being.
Looks like she ate a human being.
Hey, Simon.
You're cuter than the
picture Jay sent me.
You're, uh, cuter than the
smiley face you texted.
[All chuckling]
Hey, you're a lot cuter
than your picture too.
[Chuckles] No one sent me any pictures.
We got to run.
But I'll see you at the dance tonight?
Absolutely.
Save a dance for me, muffin.
Yeah, yeah, cool, great, ten muffins.
It was a pleasure to meet you too.
I'm Will. That's Neil.
Thanks for your time.
Unbelievable.
Isn't that our old librarian?
Aw, man, she's living the good life.
Getting fired was the best thing
that ever happened to her.
[Flies buzzing]
The RV resort was seeming less like
a resort and more like a place
fun came to die.
And dinner with Jay's family
didn't exactly revive it.
This is a lovely meal, Mrs. Cartwright.
Thank you.
[Grunting distantly]
[Farting]
[Plopping]
Did you sautee these vegetables
with olive oil and garlic?
I can really taste the garlic.
Oh, it's from a box.
I just microwaved it on
high for three minutes.
Mm.
[Straining distantly]
[Ketchup bottle farting]
[Grunting and farting]
[Ketchup bottle squirting]
[Toilet flushing]
Oh.
Whoo!
Oh, guess I should let
this one air out a bit.
My nose burns.
I can taste it.
You boys excited for the dance tonight?
Yeah.
I'm sure Jay's gonna make
some moves, on his left hand.
[Laughs]
Dad.
I'd like to let you know
that I actually have a girl
who's pretty interested in me.
Yeah? Is she fat?
Her face is a little.
Yeah, I knew it.
Hope you boys have better luck
spelunking lady caves than Jay.
The apple does not fall
far from the tree.
Shut up, Newton.
That one actually makes sense.
[Choking]
And later we arrived at the dance,
where not only had the fun died,
but someone was now beating
its corpse with crappy music.
Don't worry, guys.
This party's gonna amp up real soon.
♪♪.
It would seem that our weekend had
hit bottom, which meant that things
could only get better.
Here they come.
Do you have the legacy condom?
Rub it. Rub it right now.
It's not a genie lamp.
It is if your wish is to get laid.
I don't know if I can do this.
It was gonna be so special with Carly.
Yeah, because you'd be 70.
Look, if you want to save
your first time for your lady
love, just go back door.
It doesn't count.
Back door doesn't count?
No, it's not considered a premium hole.
Becky doesn't care either.
She'll take it from any direction.
I know from experience.
Do you?
Here they come.
Rub it. Rub it!
Oh, let me get some of that.
Dude. Dude.
Let me get in there.
Hey, Simon.
So I think it's time for that dance.
[Both chuckling]
No way.
This is my jam.
[Giggles]
Right.
So lovely to see you again.
Becky, was it?
Be at the food table
if anyone needs me.
♪ 'Cause she's watching him ♪
♪ with those eyes ♪
and she's loving him ♪
♪ with that body ♪ I just know
it ♪ yeah, he's holding her ♪
♪ in his arms ♪ late, late at night
♪ you know I wish that I had
So you like hummus?
Actually it's pronounced hummus.
You're so worldly.
I love that.
You have a little hummus on your vest.
I'm sorry.
Allow me.
I'm Will.
I'm horny.
♪ You know I feel so dirty whoa.
Actually, you know how we can
make this more romantic?
If we got to know each other, just slowed
things down-- you know, run around,
fall tirelessly into each other's
arms at the very end of the night.
That sort of thing.
You know what?
I know what we can do.
We can slide.
Used to love sliding as a child.
[Giggles]
Doesn't this look like fun?
Whoo!
We can just slide across the floor.
Where are you going?
Hey.
Hey, real mature.
Real mature.
Saw you talking to
fatty-fatty boom-boom.
Yeah, so?
I'm Simon's wing man.
I take that job very seriously.
You don't have to lie to me, son.
With your looks, I'd have taken
the fatties a long time ago.
How's your night going?
Better than Jay's, I hope.
I made out with a girl who
licked hummus off my vest.
Atta boy!
And kinky.
Oh, see you that, Jay?
Even Will's getting some.
How do you smell that
bad after a shower?
Ugh.
[Chuckles]
Kissed so good, it knocked
your socks off, huh?
[Laughs]
Yeah, I know it's not a perfect joke.
You still got your socks on, but...
You're actually getting
a little bit--
You're, uh... right?
Atta boy.
[Splashing]
You got stage fright there?
Maybe we should go somewhere more...
Just somewhere else.
I got to go to the bathroom, but
meet me outside in five minutes?
[Sighs]
Is this seat taken?
It is now.
It's a nice night.
Yeah.
Both: Full moon.
[Chuckle]
Twilight.
You want to take this
to the next level?
What?
Yeah. Yes.
Absolutely.
Mmm.
You like that?
This feel good?
I think we make a good couple.
[Chuckles nervously]
I like this.
What are you doing?
Next level?
That is my stomach.
Second base.
Oh.
Let me just get this.
What is that?
A condom.
Why are you wearing a condom?
For protection.
And luck?
What?
Jay said--
What did Jay say?
You like sex.
I am not having sex with you.
Back door?
Oh...
I'm learning your tricks.
Will, what are you doing?
We got to go.
Stop playing around.
Oh, yeah.
You nailed it, Jay.
That's exactly what I'm doing.
Playing around with your
father's urine coating my socks.
Yeah. What?
[Chuckles]
Got you now.
Who's immature now?
Eat it!
Eat my foot.
Relax.
[Breathing rhythmically]
Hey, it's Simon.
Hey, what's up, guys?
You're such a liar!
What?
She likes sex?
Why would you say that?
Uh, we had that one night together?
What night?
We had never had a night.
We were so drunk.
Stop lying.
The legacy condom?
What have you done?
Becky, you out here?
He tried to back door me.
And we're off.
I want that condom back
in any condition, Simon.
Any condition!
[Whimpers]
And now the conclusion
of The Inbetweeners.
[Baby squealing]
The next morning, we
were hoping to leave
without anymore humiliation.
Hey, boys.
So much for that.
Thanks for the hospitality,
Mr. Cartwright.
I'm sorry about
everything that happened.
No, no, no, no worries.
No worries.
I just worked everything
out with Becky's dad.
We get it, guys.
Okay, we were boys once before.
Of course we didn't try
to stick it in somebody's
chimney till college, but you
kids these days work fast.
Like lightning.
Unless you're Jay.
What's the opposite of lightning?
The opposite of lightning would
be, I got some last night,
so booyah.
Yeah, yeah, you got some.
The girls dad told me you
fingered her fat roll, you moron.
[Laughter]
She liked it.
Did she?
That's weird.
Check this out.
Look at that.
There you go.
I dare you not to get a boner.
What do you think of that, Jay?
Look at that.
Should we go steady?
We should have a baby.
[Laughter]
Neil, hey.
Where have you been?
I slept in the car last night.
Did I miss anything?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
I can't believe you used this thing.
I can't believe you're touching that.
It didn't work.
It's bad luck.
Of course it didn't work.
You unwrapped it.
Those wraps should be pregnant by now.
Yeah, exactly.
I think having a lucky condom
you can't use is a bad idea.
Oh, yeah?
Tell that to the 50 girls that
got banged because of it.
Yeah, I would like to.
You know, even though
you didn't have sex,
you did forget about Carly.
You're right.
She didn't cross my mind once.
You're welcome.
Until now.
I can't stop thinking about her.
Great job, Neil.
What did I do?
Just leave Simon's love life to me.
Uh, you thought a stomach was a vagina.
[Laughter]
Whatever. It was wet.
You know, speaking of
wet, my seat is damp.
Yeah, mine too.
Neil, did you piss in my car?
No.
Then why is it wet?
I just hooked up with
some girl in here.
I think her name was Amber.
She tasted like chummus.
That was my girl.
You had sex in my car?
No.
It's too small.
She just yanked me a few times.
All: Oh!
Pull over! Pull over!
Oh, I'm gonna be sick.
Gross, gross!
Pull over!
Pull over! Pull over!
Oh, God.
Out of the car.
Ah, God.
[Grunting]
All over my pants!
Clean out my car now!
It's your car.
It's your stuff!
That's gross.
I don't even want to ride in it now.
You think I do?
I told you.
I told you you were
lying about RV resorts.
What are you talking about?
Neil got some action, didn't
he, that's soaked in my pants!
That's not the point.
You're still a liar.
Clean it up!
I'm not going to because it's your car.
I don't care.
And in the end, everything was
pretty much back to normal.
We were still virgins, Neil was
still doing inappropriate things
in Simon's car, and Jay was still Jay.
I don't get a hand job!
What are you doing?
What are you two doing?
Simon, move!
I'm gonna [bleep] kill you!
Next on The Inbetweeners...
Schools from all over
the state descend on this battlefield.
And I will descend on their ladies.
The girl, who is she?
New girl, I guess.
Lauren?
Lauren's great, isn't she?
And I think she really likes me.
Well, I saw her first.
I think there's a party down the hall.
You want to go?
Yeah, sure.