My name is Will Mackenzie, and
these are my closest friends.
So you're sticking
with the briefcase.
It's a messenger bag.
It's definitely a briefcase.
Or a purse.
Well, my last school
discouraged backpacks.
They don't want us to look
like a bunch of ninja turtles.
They wanted you to
look like dickheads?
I've known them since yesterday,
which is also when I met
the school's vice principal.
Simon.
Come here.
This right here is
William Mackenzie.
He is just transferred here, and you
have been selected to show him around.
What?
Why me?
Because you were standing
closest to the door.
What is that?
A briefcase?
It's a messenger bag.
Oh, is it delivering the
message "My mom dressed me"?
[Laughter]
He's like a miniature
grown-up, but full-sized.
[Laughter]
Stop it.
Why do I have to
show him around?
Because William suffered from
bulling issues at his last school.
What?
[Snickers]
No, I didn't.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Sorry, but it is, and I wasn't, so...
It was your face, I bet.
You know, you do have one of those faces
that just makes people wanna... boom.
What?
Nothing.
Welcome to grove high.
Get to class!
[Paper rips]
It wasn't my idea to transfer here...
[Imitates explosion]
But it also wasn't my idea
for my dad to run off
with his secretary and leave my mom with
no way to pay my private school fees.
But this place is real and
try to put a fee on that.
Oh, I think these are
my sister's pants.
Yeah, I wasn't gonna say anything, but
you have a rhinestone butterfly on
the back.
Oh, son of a bitch.
All right, there's carly.
Give it.
Give me the ball.
You really think throwing a
football will make a girl like you?
Yeah.
It makes her see
him as an athlete.
It's subliminal advertising.
It's the opposite of
subliminal, actually.
It's true.
It's liminal.
Not a word.
You know we don't
like you, right?
And as I came from a school
where popularity was determined
by how early you got into Harvard...
You see that throw?
It was nice to be somewhere you could
have it by throwing a football.
Oh!
[All gasp]
Yep, this was going to be great.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
So far, my time in public school
has been a wonderful
voyage of discovery...
Hi.
About how different public schools
work, especially the toilets,
which have no doors on them
to discourage drug use.
This also, curiously enough,
discourages [bleep].
But at least I got to spend some
more time with my new friends.
[Door slams]
I'm telling you guys, I spent the
entire summer trapping beaver.
Okay, that's the thing about RV
girls, is that they all have
the same thing in common.
They're poor?
No, these girls are sluts, dude, and
they'll do it to you for hours.
I'm so good at sex now.
Really?
So what is the best
way to do it, then?
Deep.
Just like real
deep to the balls.
Do you put the balls in?
What?
I heard you gotta put your balls in
if you really want to get a girl off.
Yeah, you can.
It's preference.
Some girls like it.
Some girls don't.
Personally, I like to
go in past the balls.
That doesn't even make sense.
Yes, it does.
No, because you've never had
sex with anyone, and neither
have I, and neither has Neil.
Okay, well, you guys can think what
you want, but I--I have busted enough
condoms to tell you
that-- [Door slams]
Oh, [Bleep].
[Water running]
Oh, sorry.
Go huskies.
And as much as I wished I didn't fit
in with these idiots... [gasps]
I did.
[Camera shutter clicks]
♪ Run ♪ 'cause you're gonna go ♪
♪ down, down, down ♪ run ♪
'cause you're gonna go ♪
♪ down, down, down ♪
so don't look back ♪
♪ into the sun ♪ look back ♪ you
better run ♪ you're gonna go ♪
♪ down, down, down ♪ run ♪
'cause you're gonna go ♪
♪ down, down, down
Jesus Christ.
What?
Good manners cost nothing.
My dad brang me new pants.
Oh, yeah?
Did you "brang" him his back?
Those were my sister's.
Yeah, your dad's more
of a cutoffs guy.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means there isn't room in his closest
for anything besides cutoffs and him.
My dad is not gay.
Does an awful lot of gardening.
Yeah, but he lifts
up weights too.
You should see him
with his shirt off.
Yeah, he's always telling
us the same thing.
My dad is not gay!
[Cafeteria chatter stops]
I can sit anywhere, right?
Tables aren't assigned?
You're lucky we let you sit
with us, dress 4 less.
That blazer makes all
of us look uncool.
We're barely above
the wall eaters now.
Oh, no.
Those guys aren't gonna have
sex until they're dead.
But we will be banging bitches
by the end of the week.
It's time we turn the panty
tide in our direction.
We're skipping school tomorrow.
What?
Girls love rebels, and it's time
to show them who we really are.
By not showing them who you are.
Does seem a little backwards.
Well, that's how the
female mind works.
But, whatever, do what you want.
I mean, I'm already up
to my nuts in guts.
I was just trying to help you guys bang
something other than your right hands.
Oh, it's left for me.
It feels more like someone
else is doing it.
Just do what your dad does
and have someone else do it.
My dad is not gay.
You know, it'd be
fine if he was.
I actually have a gay uncle who's
actually single right now.
Oh, why does he have to garden?
I'm trying to help.
Well, if skipping school
helps me with Carly, I'm in.
I mean, I've had a crush on
her since we were eight.
You had a crush on
an eight-year-old?
Our families are friends, Neil.
We were both eight.
Yeah, but still, you were
attracted to an eight-year-old.
Well, she's not eight anymore,
and she's looking good.
Who's looking good?
Ah, nobody.
Our football team.
We're gonna be great this year.
Go huskies!
Shut the [Bleep] up.
Yeah, piss off.
So I didn't see much
of you this summer.
I guess you stopped going to
church with your parents, huh?
Yeah.
I spent most of my Sundays
just jamming on my strat.
Music's my church now.
Yeah, your mom told me you got
a job at the cracker barrel.
Did she?
But that wasn't our agreement.
No, it's cool.
Are you wearing aftershave?
Kind of an all-over body spray.
I like it.
It's like a leathery musk.
That part's just me.
I'm headed to the
science building.
Are you?
No, I-- go ahead.
Just do it.
Okay, bye.
Bye, Wendy.
Bye, nobody.
Dude, are you mental?
Why didn't you
walk her to class?
I'm good.
[In British accent] Oh.
Did the pretty little
lady give Simon a boner?
No.
Oh, man, I think she did.
Seriously?
[Laughing]
Simon's got a boner!
[Laughter]
Just kidding, man.
If I was going to survive this school,
I knew I couldn't do it alone.
So looks like I don't have any
grade-determining assignments
tomorrow, if you guys are
serious about skipping.
Who said you were invited?
Oh, man, we have to be invited?
Oh, my God.
And given enough time...
[Car honks]
People will always find
something they like about you.
Holy [bleep].
Even if it's not you.
Dude, is that your mom?
Yes.
I told her not to
come and pick me up.
She is hot.
Yeah, I'd renob her in a second.
I'm not gonna ask
what that means.
"Renob" is "boner" backwards.
I'd literally renob her so hard
that my penis would be pushed
back into my body.
[Laughs]
Thanks.
She's so hot she could
be a prostitute.
Nobody be afraid to say
what you're thinking.
When was the last time
that you saw her naked?
I'm walking away now.
Um, Simon's gonna email you his address,
so we'll meet there in the morning.
Maybe mom can drop you off.
So you made some
friends already?
I wasn't very selective.
Oh, well, just make sure
they're nice to you, okay?
I don't want to see you
get bullied again.
Did you tell them I was bullied at St.
Mary's?
I thought you were.
No, I got wedgied a few times,
but that was just a fad.
Oh.
The next morning, I headed to
Simon's house to skip school
for the first time ever.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So who was this new boy that's
dropping you to school?
Oh, there he is.
Good morning, all.
You're old enough to drive?
Yes.
Yeah--yes, I am that
old enough to drive.
I drive everywhere.
I drove here, even.
I parked right over there.
The panel van.
Yes.
It is a little molestery, but I got
it at a great deal from a molester,
but he never molested in it.
You know, just
transported to molest.
Stop saying "molest."
I can't.
Bye, mom.
That was flawless.
Guys.
Molester.
I should have pointed
to the Volvo.
Dude, you think?
Hey.
You guys need a lift?
Sure.
Neil?
Oh, maybe later, I guess.
You got cool muscles.
Neil!
All right.
So so far, skipping school
had consisted of lying
to Simon's mom, dodging a rape,
and hanging out with the only
other people not in
school or at work:
Two-year-olds.
What?
All right, this is totally lame.
Yo, we should get a game of red
rover going with them or something.
No, Neil, we should
get some booze.
How?
Well, we could have used my
fake I.D., but I totally lost
it in this drug rave last night.
It's so stupid.
Yeah, you'd think you'd be more
careful in your made-up fantasies.
Actually they're not
made up, dickhead.
'Cause if you tested my piss right
now, it'd be, like, 80% coke.
You know, it's the middle
of the school day.
Liquor stores are
expecting adults.
I mean, somebody just
has to look the part.
[Bell dings]
Good afternoon.
Hey.
Yes.
Uh, I am a man who has recently
bought a house in the area,
and I'm gonna be throwing a housewarming
party, which I'll be inviting a lot
of my work friends to-- other adults,
you know, hence the potato chips.
And I am probably gonna need some
alcohol to go with the potato chips.
What type of thing
are you looking for?
Uh, can I have a
bottle of, uh, Babnik?
Vodka.
Yes.
Is it a good year?
What?
I'm sure it is.
Can I have two bottles
of that, please?
Right.
That'll be $49.50.
Anything else?
Hmm, what's on special?
Me letting you buy this if you're
outta here in five seconds.
I think this'll do it.
♪ Doom-doom-doom-doom ♪ doom-da-doom
♪ doom-doom-doom ♪ 3, 6, 9
♪ very, very fine ♪ hoping she can
sock it to me ♪ one more time drink.
♪ Low ♪ get low, get low
♪ get low oh, my God.
I can't feel my throat.
[All cough]
Maybe we're supposed to
mix it with something.
Are you serious, man?
This is awesome.
You still have half
of yours left.
I know, man.
I'm making it last.
[Splash]
I wish Carly could see me now.
I should text her
a picture, huh?
Show her how much
of a badass I am.
I don't think badasses text
pictures of themselves, though.
Only of their [bleep].
I do it all the time.
It's like a bat
signal for snizz.
Chicks always text
back a beaver shot.
Really?
Let's see one, then.
You wouldn't be able to tell what it was,
because they take it from the inside.
[Glass shatters]
You know, guys, if this skipping thing
helps us with chicks, I don't want to
have sex with just anybody.
I want to lose it
with someone I love.
I love Carly.
[Blows raspberries]
I do.
I love her.
I mean, she's beautiful.
She's smart.
She makes me laugh.
Why don't you tell her that?
Girls like being
told guys like them.
Just be direct and spray
paint it on an overpass.
No, no, no, no.
That's not romantic enough.
You want to get the girl?
Gotta aim straight
for the heart.
Like milk.
Catch.
[Playful reggae music]
This is cool, right?
Oh, yeah, man.
Super cool.
It's so cool.
I think writing her last name
is especially important,
even though it's her driveway.
What the hell is that?
What?
Simon?
Why are you spray-painting
my driveway?
Um... what is it-- you love me?
[Laughter]
I can easily wash this off,
and we can pretend this never
happened, and you could not
tell anyone, and I could not
tell anyone, and your friends
could not tell anyone.
Oh, I'm telling everyone.
Simon, we've known each
other since we were eight.
Why are you doing this now?
I--it was a dare.
So what then?
You're in love with me?
Maybe we could just talk
about this another time.
This couldn't have
gone any better.
[Laughter]
She doesn't love you, man.
You wasted all that paint.
[Laughter]
Actually I think this is cool.
It's like some underground
graffiti artist thing.
Wait, huh?
Yeah, you know what?
Why don't you come over later?
I'm babysitting my brother.
We can talk about it then.
Really?
Come after 8:00, 'cause
my parents will be gone
by then, and you should probably
avoid them until this washes off.
Not sure it washes off.
See you tonight.
I-- I can't believe that worked.
I second that.
Dude, it's because
you're so drunk.
You're like Kurt Cobain.
I think he was on heroin.
Do I have to do heroin?
Probably won't hurt.
Well, it's really hard to
find, and I don't want to dip
into my personal stash, so... okay,
so what do I do about tonight?
Easy.
Get way more drunk.
Dong, dong, dong.
Between all the vodka we drank
and what Jay poured on the
ground in honor of dead
rappers, we were out of booze.
But luckily I found a few bottles
my mom hadn't thrown at my dad.
Hey, when's the
MILF getting home?
Not until 6:00.
We're fine.
No, I wasn't afraid
of getting caught.
I was asking because I want to
go through her panty drawer.
I'm guessing all thongs.
Or crotch-less teddies.
[Chuckles]
Please stop.
You should be proud, Will.
None of our moms are attractive.
I can barely look at mine.
Neither can you dad.
[Snickers]
What?
My dad's not gay.
Then why did your mom leave him?
Because they have issues.
He needed some space.
Space for another penis.
[Laughter]
Okay, I'm not sure the gold
flakes are supposed to be in
there, so try and
drink around them.
Great.
So what do I do tonight?
I need a plan.
Easy.
You bring one of us along to
watch the little brother,
and then you and Carly go at it,
and I'm thinking you take me.
Dude, she might want double
penetration, and I'm the only
one with experience
in both holes.
Ill.
What?
So after three hours of drinking what
tasted like mouthwash and formaldehyde,
Simon was ready.
Hi.
Hello.
Oh, hey.
Will, right?
Is he your chaperone?
Uh, it's cool, baby.
He's just here to look after your
brother while we chat, you know?
About our feelings.
Hmm.
Let's not call me
"baby," though.
Really?
Come in.
I was just about
to grab a drink.
Dylan's in the TV room, Will.
Dad totally lost it when
he saw the driveway.
He's gonna make your parents
pay for a stone cleaner.
It's worth it.
Do you smell windex?
God, I really hate
that smell, you know.
Shh.
Ew.
Is it you?
What have you been drinking?
Shoot.
My manners.
You want some?
Oh, God.
What homeless guy did
you steal that from?
I think I'll stick with wine.
Wine's for girls.
I am a girl.
Well, I'm a man, and this is a man's
drink, and if you can't take me like
this, then I'm sorry, baby.
But this is the package.
[Ominous music]
[Boom]
Oh, I've seen this one.
It's about what would happen if
a chemical bomb hit the city.
Streets would pile up with corpses,
stacked up on the curb like recs.
My parents are in the city.
Would they be killed?
Yep.
Stacked up on a curb.
My mom and dad are dead?
What?
Come on.
You know why I'm here, and I know why
I'm here, and you know why I'm here.
Just kiss me.
Simon, you know I
have a boyfriend.
But we're meant to be together.
Come on, let's just renob.
What?
Sex me.
Jesus, Simon.
[Swallows deeply]
Simon?
[Moans]
Are you all right?
Oh, [bleep].
[Coughs]
Oh... I don't feel very...
[Splash]
[Dylan screaming]
Dylan!
Ooh.
Look, I'm very sorry.
I--good, still warm.
Um, I was just explaining the effects
of chemical warfare.
To an eight-year-old?
He won't sleep for a
week now, you idiot.
I am really sorry.
I think I ate something.
Maybe we could just sit down and we
could talk about us and... [retches]
[Screams]
I think we'll be going now.
Oh, no.
Though the night was a
complete disaster, it actually
brought the two of us closer--
friends forged out of failure.
We were the golden flakes
floating in the pool of vomit,
and there was comfort knowing it
would never get any worse than this.
Is that your mom's car?
I stand corrected.
I mean, did you think the
school wouldn't call us, Simon?
And why do you smell like
vomit and cheap alcohol?
Wasn't cheap.
It had gold in it.
And you, Will, you've never
done anything irresponsible.
Now all of a sudden
you're skipping school?
Why?
I...
It was all my idea.
I couldn't go back to school.
I'm getting bullied again, mom.
It's happening all over again.
[Crying]
So I think it's safe to say
public school is going to work out fine.
I have three friends that seem
to accept me, and a lifetime
of superior private education to get me out
of any jam this environment can present.
Who knows, I might
even get laid.
Morning, students.
First off I want to report
that we have had a formal suit
filed by the mother of William
Mackenzie regarding his
treatment by the student body.
Let me just say this, any
student caught bullying him
or causing him any emotional
or physical distress will be
severely disciplined by the school and
possibly outside law enforcement.
Will is a good boy with
a great big heart.
Even though his body isn't maturing
as fast as others might be...
He deserves your respect.
[Laughter]
Then again, I'm a [bleep] idiot.
[glass shatters]
[Laughter]
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com