The first few weeks at my
new school hadn't gone well
for either my popularity...
Or Simon's pursuit of carly.
You love me?
Grove high school:
A sea of jocks, nerds, criminals,
mothers-to-be, and everything in between.
And when I say in
between, I mean me.
♪ Take me to the other side
But I wasn't alone.
I had these guys...
♪ Take me to the other side
...which admittedly wasn't much.
♪ Enjoy the ride
♪ I'm the poster child ♪
♪ for the other side
But they were friends,
partners on the turbulent road
to adulthood.
Give you a dollar if you eat it.
A road paved with stupidity
and embarrassment.
Is it cool if I pay
you in nickels?
But thanks to Simon, a road
we could now drive on.
Here we go.
Took me a minute to get it
out of the display sleeve.
I have the same
problem with my dong.
I can't believe you
can drive now.
How are you a year
older than us?
I got held back in kindergarten.
My dad wanted me to be
more dominant in sports.
Didn't work.
I have brittle bones.
My school tried to hold me
back every year, but my mom
just changed the spelling of
my name and reenrolled me.
How many different ways
are there to spell Neil?
Oh, I wasn't Neil until
the sixth grade.
Jay, what are you doing?
Making you over 21.
It's really easy when
you're born in 1995.
All you do is change the nine into
an eight, and then you're a child
of the '80s.
Flower power.
Jay, I don't think that you--
Dude, I used to do this
for a living until the
feds started tailing me.
On your bicycle?
Well, I'm not gonna jack a
car with the feds on me.
Now, shut up so I
can concentrate.
One false move and
this thing is ruined.
What?
Is your dad gonna hold
up his end of the deal?
Yeah, I passed my test, so he
said he's gonna get me a car.
Oh, man, cars are the best
[bleep] magnets there are.
Get ready to troll for
some [bleep], boys.
I'm bringing my stiffest rod.
Ooh.
I'd like to get off the boat.
Let me just ease it into a slip.
Ooh.
Man overboard.
What kind of car is it?
He wouldn't say, but he did
tell me it was a sport edition,
and a sport edition of
anything is awesome.
Dude, we should race it.
Yeah.
What?
It's a car.
There's no way we'd win.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing, where are my nickels?
Here she is.
Carly, the love of Simon's life.
Unfortunately, she was going out with
Bobby watts, the love of her life.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
I have a shot now, okay?
Having a car will level
the playing field.
I don't think you could win
on a level playing field.
I think you need it slanted
dramatically in your direction.
Yeah, anything level he's
just gonna bang her on.
Hey, Simon.
Hey.
You know, if you ever need
a ride that moves a little
faster, you can give me a call.
Those your house keys?
Shut up.
Did you get a car?
Nope, I got a sport edition
of a car--no, I got a car.
You're doing great.
That's awesome.
You passed your test.
It was easy.
I was born driving.
Eww, must have been
painful for your mom.
We should grab a pizza
soon and celebrate.
Yeah, what about tomorrow?
Oh, I can't tomorrow.
Bobby's taking me to Sunshine Mountain
for our two-month anniversary.
Wow, it's a shame there's not an
anniversary for friends, huh?
I'd have him beat by,
like, eight years.
Maybe we should make one up.
Yeah, why not?
You and Bobby did.
I'll see you guys later.
Hey, if you're going to Sunshine
Mountain, I'll probably see you there.
I work weekends as
poncho the parrot.
So if a giant parrot hugs you,
it's me or my friend Toby.
You work at Sunshine Mountain?
Triple-inverted triscareatops
rollercoaster Sunshine Mountain?
It's actually just called
Sunshine Mountain.
Why don't we go there tomorrow?
You could show Carly that you drive to
cool places just like Bobby, which will
totally get into her head.
You think so?
Yes, psychological warfare always
works, plus we can ride that ride
a few times.
I'm up for a road trip.
And now that you're over 21, we can
take a little swim in the beer garden.
1895?
What?
You changed the wrong nine.
You made me 117, you idiot!
Where are you going?
Jay!
Come here!
This is so awesome.
I'll probably hear it
before I see it, huh?
V8?
All I know is it is a Ford.
A Ford?
Yes.
Mustang, I bet.
Dad.
Oh, I can't believe
you're getting a car.
Such a waste.
What are you gonna do, take out that
fat redheaded girl you're always with?
That's Jay.
Oh, must've been
thrown by his [bleep].
Todd!
It's fine, mom.
It doesn't matter what he says.
I'm the one getting a new car.
No!
No, you can't be serious.
It's cute.
It's yellow like the sun.
Doesn't look like much,
but it runs great.
Sport edition.
Of what sport, ultimate frisbee?
Could be a little
more grateful, Simon.
It's a good starter car, and you won't
be able to get up enough speed in it
to kill yourself.
I'll find a way.
I'll find a way to
kill myself in it.
Tell you what:
You show me that you can take
care of this, and next summer
we'll see if we can find
you an upgrade, eh?
Fine.
Thanks, I guess.
You betcha.
Hey, I made you a mix tape of
all the songs I used to cruise
to when I was your age.
It has a tape player?
Hell yeah!
It's a sport edition.
Dad.
♪ I want you to show me ♪
♪ I want to feel what love is
♪ when the morning comes
The next morning, Simon arrived
to pick me up in his new car.
New to him, old and ugly to us.
It's not that bad.
It's...jazzy.
It's better on the inside, except
then people see you're in it.
The color is a
little unfortunate.
What is it, a kind of gold?
It's called Muppet yellow.
Well, I'm sure it
gets great mileage.
Let's go.
Triscareatops awaits.
Are you sure a rollercoaster
won't be too scary for you?
I'll be fine, mom.
At least let me put a
safety tattoo on your arm.
Be right back.
Go.
Go now before she comes back.
Hold on.
♪ No, I won't stop staring ♪
♪ and I can't stop ♪
♪ from watching ♪ no, I
won't stop staring ♪
Oh, my God.
Oh-ho-ho, my God.
No way.
Oh, my God.
This is it?
This is your car?
What is it?
A Ford Festiva.
More like a Ford celibacy.
Ugh, does this thing have a
motor or do we have to stick
our feet through the bottom?
Back in the day, this
thing was awesome.
Back in the day when you decided
never to get laid again?
Just get in.
We're already late.
Shotgun!
What, I'm in the car.
No, your feet are on the ground.
You're out of the car.
To let you in.
Mmm, sorry, William,
rules are rules.
♪ Well, I'm ♪
♪ hot blooded ♪ check the
disease ♪ I got a fever of 103
I'd like to see the
shotgun rules.
I'd like to see where
those are posted.
They're in the
library of congress.
No, they're not.
Yes, they are.
It was established in 1865
when some dude wanted Lincoln's seat in
the theater, so he blew his head off
with a shotgun.
Oh, check out that
bleep wrangler.
What's the bleep stand for?
[Bleep].
Follow them.
I can't.
They're going right.
Yup, and Sunshine
Mountain is straight.
We're already late.
Are you kidding me?
Who cares about some dumb
little theme park when we could
be stuffin' some muffin?
Follow them.
Simon, don't.
Okay.
Whoa-ho.
Dude.
Hello.
Oh, yeah.
What are you writing?
Don't--
No, no, no.
Jay-- take it down!
Take it down!
It won't come down!
Come on!
Just go, okay?
Was she dialing?
It looked like--
You wrote down my number?
What'd you do that for?
Just turn around.
Turn around and go to
Sunshine Mountain.
Okay.
Sorry, everybody!
Oh, this is so boring.
Come on, people.
We ain't getting any younger!
Just go around them.
We're already late.
God, what's the holdup?
Come on, people!
Oh, no.
What's wrong with
you, you monsters!
It had been a long journey, but we
finally arrived at Sunshine Mountain
in one piece.
Come on, Simon.
Just park.
I'm trying to.
Oh, there are hot girls.
Dude, there are bikini
chicks getting on that tram.
Park!
I can't--I can't do
this any faster.
You couldn't do this any slower.
Do you have a license?
Are you a licensed driver?
I'm a licensed busherman.
You know, bush?
Can you just park?
Why are you going backwards?
Every other car is forwards.
Come on!
No, Jay, wait.
Unfortunately, Simon's
car wasn't so lucky.
Oops.
What'd you do?
What--what'd you do?
What did you do?
What?
We got to get this fixed.
Now?
Yes, now.
We can't just leave
it like this.
It's just a door, Simon.
A door?
Yeah.
Just a door.
I'm gonna be driving
Carly around in this.
I prefer she doesn't go flying
out on the first sharp turn.
I'm not sure you're gonna be
driving around Carly in this.
Oh, Neil's sister's boyfriend
works at a body shop.
We'll get it fixed
on the way home.
Problem solved.
There you go.
We go in, get Neil, ride the
triscareatops a few times,
let Carly see you're having
the time of your life, come
back, and get the car fixed.
It's a perfect plan.
What about the door?
Somebody might take it.
Not a problem.
I'm sure the park has
somewhere to store it.
Yeah, it's a park policy.
Every park has it.
We have stroller rentals and
disabled access on certain rides.
That's not really
what I asked though.
We don't have anywhere
to store car doors.
Well, turns out they don't really
have anywhere to store car doors.
Knew it.
Fine, we're just gonna have to
take turns carrying it then.
I'm not carrying this.
You broke it!
You reversed.
Are you really gonna try
to make this my fault?
Are you really gonna not try and
make this my fault... or not?
Thought not.
What?
So we went to find Neil with the
unspoken hope that maybe he would turn
our luck around.
Oh, there's Neil.
Neil!
Neil.
Neil, Neil!
This wasn't him.
Ow!
What the [bleep]?
Neil.
[Bleep].
What was that about?
That was.
Neil?
No way.
Neil isn't that tall.
The parrot feet give me two extra
inches, plus I got this built-in cup.
I'm not gonna ask.
Oh, it's so you don't get
boners around the kids.
It's much worse than I thought.
Did you see Carly anywhere?
No, but maybe poncho did.
We have to find her.
Bobby probably took her
to the haunted castle.
It's the one ride in the whole park without
a lap bar if you know what I mean.
Oh, no.
Uh, oh, dude!
What?
You're naked under there?
That's a little
disturbing, isn't it?
Oh, man.
Those guys swiped
my clothes again.
They're always playing
pranks on me.
Just put anything on, Neil.
I have to go find Carly.
Let's try the
triscareatops first.
Good chance she'll
be on that, huh?
It's possible.
We can definitely get a
pinkie in on the scareatops.
Oh, no.
It's cool.
I'll just find something
in the lost and found.
Oh!
Neil, stand up.
♪ I didn't mean to hurt you ♪
♪ baby ♪ no, no, no, no, no ♪ I just
want to be your man ♪ I ain't lying ♪
♪ about that now ♪
and I'm trying ♪
♪ darling, now
oh, this outfit--
I can't believe
it went unclaimed.
Neither can I.
This shirt is awesome.
It lets my belly breathe.
Doesn't look like the rest of you
is struggling for air either.
You sure your sister's boyfriend
works at a body shop?
Yeah, she's really
into blue collar guys.
Must take after your dad.
My dad is as straight as I am.
You might want to say that
in a different outfit.
Oh, there's Carly.
♪ She was alone tonight
I'm going in.
Somebody hold this.
♪ And she played them right
oh, come on!
I can't go up to her
holding a car door.
Maybe you could say you won it?
Maybe you could use it
to hide your erection.
Simon, hey!
Hey.
♪ And then she said ♪ I, I could be
lonely ♪ I could be lonely ♪ in your arms
♪ I know that I
Hey.
Hey, what's up, man?
Good to see you again.
Good to see you too.
Is that your car door?
Mine?
Yeah, it detaches like a radio
faceplate but a car door.
Isn't it heavy?
Nah.
Well, we should be going
to the triscareatops.
It'll be closing soon.
Do you want us to watch
your door for you?
It's cool.
You guys have fun.
I'm gonna give this girl a little
beat down on the squirt game.
Not if I squirt first.
You're going down.
Oh, yeah.
You're gonna have
some competition.
Here.
And Simon took his shot, raising
his monkey high into the air,
and he was winning.
Stop.
He was just in the wrong race.
♪ I could be lonely
♪ in your arms
♪ I know that I
I...
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
♪ In your arms ♪
I'll take that.
A day as disastrous as this
one had been could only
be saved by one thing:
Our own shrieks of terror.
You guys hear that noise?
That's a magnetic launch.
Most coasters use momentum.
Not this one.
This one throws you like
a [bleep]damn catapult.
I hope it kills me.
So you sprinkled her
with some water.
Big deal.
Nothing the triscareatops
can't fix.
How, how will a rollercoaster
fix this, will?
Hey, isn't that our
old librarian?
Oh, man, she's living the life.
I wish they would
fire me from school.
And why are we in the slow line?
We've been standing
here an hour.
This is the line for the
front, and it'll be worth it.
Front of this coaster's gonna
take you to place you've only
dreamed of.
Is it a rollercoaster
into your mom?
Lovely.
I can't believe I
squirted Carly.
How hot was that bra though?
That's the kind you can undo
in the front with your teeth.
Are you serious?
Those exist?
They do.
I watched Jay chew his way through
the bra department at Ross.
Got to practice somewhere.
Let's get moving.
Come on.
Who cares about a coaster, will?
We were supposed to be
coming here for me.
But you never cared
about that, did you?
You don't give a crap who
I squirted as long as
it wasn't the triscareatops, which
admittedly wouldn't hurt it.
Simon.
We're up.
Room for one more at the front.
What?
One more at the front.
How is there room for just one?
We were at the head of the line.
Well, there are three people at
the front now so that leaves
one more seat open, but there
are plenty more further back.
I'm sorry.
Can we just rewind a bit?
Why is there room for just one?
Sir, if you could just get on the ride...
I'll tell you why:
Because they cut.
We have been waiting in line
for over an hour, and you just
let them cut.
Sir.
No!
Get them off!
Make them move.
It doesn't matter.
Let's just sit in the back.
No, it does matter!
What, are they stupid?
Are they such idiots they think
that line cutting is okay, Jeff?
Sir, if you could
please just get on.
Yeah, let's just get on.
All right, fine, just fine.
I'm gonna sit in the front
with these line-cutting
inconsiderate ass[bleep]!
I'm the worst human
being in the world.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
This is so [bleep] funny!
Dude, check this out.
You had to buy that.
If it makes you feel better, a
ball popped out of my shorts
and was flopping
around the whole ride.
It's still out.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have used you to
get to the triscareatops.
I wasn't being a
very good friend.
To any of us.
How was I not being a
good friend to you?
I don't know.
I just feel left out sometimes.
It's okay.
Picture kind of makes up for
it, and I got it in a little
keychain too.
So where to next?
We're leaving.
I have to get this
door put back on.
Does your sister's
boyfriend work late?
Yeah, but he'll never
be able to fix that.
What?
You said he works
at a body shop.
Yeah, but they just do paint.
Well, how does that
help me, Neil?
It's already painted.
They do pin-striping too.
Son of a--God!
And with that our afternoon at
an amusement park had ended...
God!
Without a single second of
amusement, and we couldn't even get
the leaving part right.
Where did we park?
Shotgun!
What--you can't call it yet.
We haven't even found the car.
I don't have to.
We're in the parking lot.
Rules are rules.
What rules?
Would you guys just try
to help me find my car?
What color is it?
Muppet yellow.
My dad's gonna freak.
I'm never getting another car.
Look, we'll find a mechanic.
He's gonna fix it
up as good as new.
There's absolutely no reason
that we can't-- oh, dear God.
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, oh, who?
Why?
Who would do this?
Good one, you guys.
Had that one coming.
They didn't do it to you.
This is my car.
Simon, they're
intellectually disabled.
Let them have this.
And it's fine, man.
It's just graffiti
and a flat tire.
We can fix this in a hour.
Well, that's gonna make
it more difficult.
It's over.
My life's over.
We don't have a way
to get home now.
Simon?
And our visit to Sunshine Mountain
did help Simon get between
Bobby and Carly.
Thanks again for
the ride, Bobby.
Oh, sure, man.
Any friend of Carly’s
is a friend of mine.
Just not in the
way he had hoped.
Speed bump.
Ow.
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ what love is
♪ and I want you to show me
Yeah!
♪ I want to know what love is
Come on, everybody.
♪ and I want
you ♪ to show me ♪
Yeah!
♪ I want to know
♪ what love is ♪
I hate this song.
♪ I want to know ♪ I
want you to show me
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com