- HE ASKED YOU?
- MM-HMM.
- AW!
WE NEED TO CELEBRATE.
- DADCHELOR PARTY! DADCHELOR
PARTY! DADCHELOR PARTY!
- THIS IS GONNA BE
A LONG NIGHT.
[crash]
- OH!
OH, MY GOD!
all: CHEERS!
- WHOO!
I'VE BASICALLY BEEN A SAINT FOR,
LIKE, TEN MONTHS,
SO I TOTALLY DESERVE
TO GO CRAZY TONIGHT.
[club music]
* *
WHEN AM I GONNA
SEE YOU AGAIN, JENNI?
- BYE. PUMP AND DUMP!
- I'M A GOOD FIANCEE,
AND I'M A MOM!
[I Love It by Icona Pop]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
*I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
- * PASSED OUT ON THE COUCH
LAST NIGHT *
* RIGHT BEFORE SUNRISE *
*I WOKE UP HERE *
* YOU DISAPPEARED *
- I FINALLY MAKE IT HOME.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE DEENA AND LAURA WENT.
BABE?
I JUST KNOW A CAB GUY
GOT ME HOME SAFE.
OH, GOD,
EVERYTHING IS DIZZY.
AND THANK GOD.
NOW I'M CRAWLING INTO BED.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- DRANK TOO MUCH.
EVERYTHING'S SPINNING.
- NOW?
- RIGHT NOW.
I MADE OUT WITH NICOLE.
IS THAT OKAY?
- YEAH.
- YOU DON'T MIND?
- WHY WOULD I MIND?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN TONGUE.
IS THAT OKAY?
- I DON'T CARE.
- I'M JUST TELLING YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- HOW ABOUT SLEEPY TIME NOW?
THAT WOULD BE NICE.
- HUH?
- HOW ABOUT SLEEPY TIME NOW?
- OKAY, SLEEPY TIME.
GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- I'LL STOP.
[door closes,
Lorenzo coos]
- HI, BABE.
HI, LORENZO.
DO YOU THINK HE MISSED ME?
OR HE DIDN'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT ME?
[laughs]
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
[squeals]
I'M NOT KIDDING.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
- YOU STINK LIKE SMOKE.
- NO, I DON'T.
I THINK THIS IS
ONE OF THESE NIGHTS
WHERE, WHEN I WAKE UP
IN THE MORNING,
I HAVE TO BE LIKE, "WHAT THE
[bleep] HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?"
AND I KIND OF DON'T MISS
THOSE NIGHTS
BECAUSE I ACTUALLY LIKE
REMEMBERING THINGS NOW.
- YOU STINK LIKE CIGARETTES.
YOU'RE TOO CLOSE TO ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[laughs]
WHY ARE YOU SLEEPING
OVER THERE?
- 'CAUSE I SMELL.
- JUST GET OVER HERE.
I SEE THE GOOGLY EYES,
WHERE IT'S A BLACKOUT NIGHT.
I KNOW SHE HAD FUN.
I'M HAPPY SHE HAD FUN.
SHE NEEDED THIS NIGHT,
YOU KNOW?
HOW WAS IT?
- FUN.
[Lorenzo fusses]
[upbeat music]
* *
[alarm beeping]
TURN THAT [bleep] OFF!
JIONNI, TURN THAT OFF
BEFORE IT--I KILL SOMEONE.
OW, MY [bleep].
I THINK MY HEAD HURTS.
MY HEAD HURTS.
[slapping]
- HOW YA FEELING?
- MY HEAD HURTS.
SO BAD.
WHERE'S MY BABY?
- UPSTAIRS.
YOU WERE [bleep] SO BOMBED...
WHEN YOU GOT HOME.
- I'M SORRY.
- HOW HUNG OVER ARE YOU
RIGHT NOW?
- THE WORLD IS SPINNING.
I'M NAUSEOUS.
- BEEN TEN MONTHS, HUH?
- I HATE MY LIFE.
- FIRST MOMMY HANGOVER.
- [sighs]
NO!
- HOW WAS GIRLS' NIGHT OUT?
- UM, I DIDN'T REALLY--
DIDN'T GET TO ASK NICOLE YET.
SHE'S SLEEPING.
- OKAY, GO GET READY.
TAKE HIM OUT.
LET HIM GET
SOME FRESH AIR.
- NICOLE'S STILL COMATOSE.
SHE'S HUNG OVER.
I'M GONNA LEAVE HER ALONE.
I'M GONNA TAKE LORENZO
FOR A WALK.
IT'S A NICE DAY OUT.
GOT A NEW STROLLER.
GET SOME BONDING TIME
WITH LORENZO.
YOU THINK MOMMY'S SLEEPING
RIGHT NOW?
SHE'LL BE WALKING WITH US
NEXT TIME.
[upbeat music]
* *
- *ONE LOOK IN YOUR EYES *
* AND I FEEL LIKE
I'M SO HOME *
* I DON'T EVEN TRY *
- HERE WE GO.
- SO I FEEL LIKE THE BIGGEST
DIRTBAG KNOWN TO HUMAN MANKIND.
I FEEL LIKE A TRUCK HIT ME,
AND SOMEONE PUNCHED ME
IN MY STOMACH 1,000 TIMES
LIKE A SPEED BAG 'CAUSE
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA VOMIT.
* *
- I BROUGHT YOU
A SOBER RELIEF KIT.
ELECTROLYTES,
CHICKEN NOODLE SOUP.
- [mutters indistinctly]
- THIS?
- THANK YOU.
- OKAY.
NOW YOU HAVE 15 MINUTES
TO GET YOUR ASS UP.
- WHAT?
- NO, I'M KIDDING.
I WOULD LIKE TO DO SOMETHING
LATER, THOUGH.
[groans]
[phone ringing]
YO.
- YO, ROG, WHAT'S UP?
- WHAT'S GOING ON, BUDDY?
- TOOK LORENZO FOR A WALK.
- WHAT, AROUND, LIKE,
YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD?
- YEAH. SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST RELAXING ON THE COUCH.
JENNI'S STILL SLEEPING.
IS NICOLE UP YET?
- HELL, NO.
HOW'S, UH, HOW'S SHE FEELING?
- SHE FEELS LIKE CRAP, SO--
- WHEN NICOLE GOT HOME
LAST NIGHT,
SHE HAD THE GOOGLY EYES.
- DID SHE THROW UP?
- NO, NICOLE'S NOT
A BIG THROW-UP PERSON.
- JENNI DIDN'T THROW UP
EITHER,
BUT I HEARD
NICOLE'S FRIEND DID.
- AT THIS POINT,
NICOLE IS ON HER DEATHBED,
JENNI'S ON HER DEATHBED,
SOMEBODY THREW UP.
THEY DEFINITELY WENT HARDER
THAN, YOU KNOW, I EXPECTED.
THEY HAD MORE FUN
THAN WE DID.
- WE DIDN'T DO [bleep],
ACTUALLY.
WE REALLY DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
- I KNOW.
- WE STOOD AROUND
LIKE TWO BUMPS ON A LOG
'CAUSE WE'RE BOTH
SCARED AS [bleep]
THAT OUR GIRLS ARE GONNA GO
PSYCHOTIC ON US.
- WE SAT THERE, AND THEY
PROBABLY, UH, WENT NUTS.
- IT'S DOUBLE STANDARDS.
- ALL RIGHT, PAL.
TALK TO YOU SOON.
- OKAY. LATER, BUDDY.
- BYE.
- [groans]
IT'S 1:00.
WASTING A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
- OH, IT'S MAKING ME
NAUSEOUS.
WHY ARE YOU KICKING?
- ARE YOU GONNA GET UP, BABE,
OR AM I GONNA GO,
LIKE, DO SOMETHING?
WE WERE ALREADY SUPPOSED TO BE
OUT OF THE HOUSE BY NOW.
WE'VE HAD PLANS FOR A WEEK.
AND STILL,
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO MOVE.
I DON'T WANT TO WASTE THE DAY.
- I'M TIRED
AND JUST NAUSEOUS.
- YOU KNOW, I WORK A LOT.
I'M NOT A GUY THAT HAS
A TON OF FREE TIME AT ALL,
SO DAYS LIKE THIS, I REALLY LIKE
TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF,
AND I'M A LITTLE BOTHERED
BY THE FACT THAT I HAD
THE SAME EXACT HANGOVER
EXPERIENCE LAST WEEKEND,
AND I SUCKED IT UP.
YOU'RE TEN YEARS YOUNGER
THAN ME. SUCK IT UP.
[phone ringing]
- HEY, GIPPER.
- HEY, BOO.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M SO HUNG OVER.
- OH, GOD,
I FEEL LIKE [bleep].
I'M STILL, LIKE,
LAYING IN BED.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU SO DRUNK
IN MY LIFE. I LOST IT.
- DID YOU GUYS HAVE FUN?
- I HAD A [bleep] AMAZING TIME,
FROM WHAT I REMEMBER.
- I'M GLAD THAT I'M NOT
THE ONLY ASS[bleep]
THAT GOT WASTED
LAST NIGHT.
- NICOLE'S GOT BRUISES
ON HER KNEES,
AND SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHY.
- [laughs]
- I THINK SHE FELL.
- WE WERE ALL REALLY DRUNK.
WELL, FEEL BETTER, POOP.
- BYE, GUYS.
- WHAT?
HE'S NOT GONNA FART.
YOU WANT TO TEST
MY BREAST MILK?
- NO!
- IT'S PROBABLY LIKE--
- PURE VODKA?
- VODKA.
- DID YOU PUMP?
- YEAH.
- DUMP THAT [bleep].
- LAST TIME I DRANK
AND I TESTED MY MILK,
IT DIDN'T SAY IT
WAS NEGATIVE
JUST BECAUSE I HAD, LIKE,
TWO GLASSES OF WINE.
BUT LAST NIGHT, I HAD PROBABLY
THREE BOTTLES OF VODKA,
SO I KNOW THIS MILK IS GONNA BE
GROSSLY CONTAMINATED.
IT'S LIKE A PREGNANCY TEST.
IF IT TURNS BROWN,
IT'S CONTAMINATED.
OH, IT'S TURNING BROWN.
- LET ME SEE.
- OH, YEAH,
IT'S CONTAMINATED.
- IT'S, LIKE, TOXIC.
- YEAH.
LIKE IT'LL BURN YOUR SKIN.
- LET ME SMELL IT.
- MY MILK?
[groans]
- WHAT?
- IT SMELLS.
- THIS STUFF'S GOTTA HAVE
EVERY DIFFERENT LIQUOR
IN THE WORLD IN IT--
SHOTS, WINE,
VODKA, TEQUILA.
- DO YOU THINK IF YOU DRANK
THIS, YOU WOULD GET DRUNK?
- IF I DRANK
NICOLE'S BREAST MILK RIGHT NOW,
I'D PROBABLY BLACK OUT.
YAY!
- SEE YA.
OH, [bleep].
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- WANT TO TAKE A SHOT?
- NO!
- JUST ONE.
- NO.
- I'M GETTING PAINTED
LIKE THIS BAD GUY.
- NOBODY--
YOU'RE PAINTING YOURSELF.
LIKE,
NOBODY'S DOING ANYTHING.
- OKAY. PROBLEM SOLVED.
[door slams]
- AND THERE HE GOES.
- AH!
[laughs]
- THIS KID IS STRONG.
HE'S LIKE AN OX.
- OW! BABE!
[laughs]
[rock music]
- *A BALL OF CLOUDS *
* THEY'LL ONLY
LEAD YOU DOWN *
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- OH, GOD, I CAN'T
EXPLAIN IT TO YOU.
- I DID THE SAME EXACT THING
LAST WEEKEND.
- WE MIXED [bleep] SAKE BOMBS
WITH WINE...
- I DID PATRON.
- SANGRIA, CHAMPAGNE, VODKA.
IT'S LIKE,
IT'S ALL RIGHT HERE.
IT FEELS LIKE
I'M GONNA BARF.
BUT MY STOMACH'S SAYING,
"I'M HUNGRY,"
BUT RIGHT HERE, IT'S SAYING,
"[bleep] YOU, I'LL THROW UP."
- I FELT THE SAME WAY.
- AND I HAVE A HEADACHE.
IT WAS JUST
ONE OF THOSE NIGHTS.
A NIGHT THAT I WILL NEVER
HAVE AGAIN THE REST OF MY LIFE
BECAUSE I CAN'T TAKE
WHAT I FEEL LIKE TODAY.
- BABE, YOU CAN GO
AS HARD AS YOU WANT.
YOU KNOW I DON'T CARE.
IT'S JUST, YOU MADE PLANS
TO DO SOMETHING
AT, LIKE, 1:00 TODAY,
AND IT'S ALMOST 4:00 NOW.
- I'M READY. I'M RIGHT HERE.
LET'S GO.
- YOU JUST GOT DOWN HERE,
SO LET'S NOT ACT LIKE
YOU'VE BEEN SITTING HERE,
WAITING ON ME.
- OH, I KNOW, BUT YOU--
I TOLD YOU YOU COULD HAVE DID
WHATEVER YOU WANTED TODAY.
- YOU DID NOT TELL ME THAT.
YOU SAID WE'RE GOING
TO BLACKBEARD'S CAVE.
- I UNDERSTAND, BUT DON'T
MAKE IT BE, LIKE, MY FAULT.
[dogs barking]
IT'S NOT.
- DON'T MAKE WHAT
YOUR FAULT?
THE FACT THAT YOU MADE PLANS
WITH ME YESTERDAY
TO DO SOMETHING TODAY,
AND IT'S NOW 4:00?
- IT'S NOW 4:00 ONLY BECAUSE
WE COULDN'T GO TO BLACKBEARD'S,
AND I TOLD YOU TO GO--
- YOU'RE DOING
THE SPIN THING YOU DO.
- YOU ARE.
- NO, YOU ARE.
- I'M HANGING OUT.
I'M READY TO GO WHEN YOU ARE.
I'M TRYING TO DO THE BEST I CAN
DO UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
- I'M JUST SAYING,
YOU'RE GETTING THIS 'TUDE,
LIKE, "DON'T BLAME ME.
NOTHING'S EVER MY FAULT."
YOU'RE GIVING ME
THIS 'TUDE RIGHT NOW.
"DON'T BLAME ME.
NOTHING'S EVER--"
- YOU'RE GIVING ME ATTITUDE.
- I MEAN, DON'T COME AT ME
LIKE YOU'VE BEEN WAITING
ALL DAY, JENNI.
I'M THE ONE
THAT'S BEEN PATIENTLY
SITTING AROUND,
WAITING FOR YOU.
I'M GETTING PAINTED
LIKE THIS BAD GUY.
- NOBODY--
YOU'RE PAINTING YOURSELF.
LIKE,
NOBODY'S DOING ANYTHING.
- OKAY. PROBLEM SOLVED.
- LET'S GO.
- NO. I'M GONNA GO DO
SOMETHING WITH MAX.
I'VE JUST REACHED MY LIMIT.
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT.
I DON'T WANT TO ARGUE.
THE BEST THING FOR ME TO DO
IS JUST LEAVE, AND, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
I'M JUST GONNA LEAVE.
- DO YOU WANT TO JUST GO?
- NO, I'D LIKE YOU
TO ADMIT FOR ONCE
THAT, YOU KNOW, YOU JUST DON'T
PUT EVERYTHING ON ME.
YOU'LL NEVER DO THAT.
- I'M NOT PUTTING ANYTHING
ON YOU.
[door slams]
AND THERE HE GOES.
BACK TO LAY DOWN.
SORRY, BOOGER BUTTS.
MOMMY NEEDS TO LAY DOWN.
[groans]
SOMEONE BRING ME ICE CREAM.
[upbeat music]
**
- SO I WAS THINKING, SINCE I'M,
LIKE, A REALLY GOOD FRIEND,
I WANT TO THROW JENNI
AN ENGAGEMENT PARTY HERE.
- IS IT A SURPRISE,
OR IT'S, LIKE, GONNA BE
AN ENGAGEMENT PARTY?
- A SURPRISE!
I WANT TO CELEBRATE
AND BE, LIKE,
YOU KNOW,
"HAPPY ENGAGEMENT,"
AND I FEEL LIKE
SHE DESERVES IT
BECAUSE SHE'S BEEN WAITING
TO BE ENGAGED FOREVER.
AND I'M THINKING I TELL HER
IT'S, LIKE, A PARTY FOR LORENZO,
FOR EVERYONE TO COME
AND MEET LORENZO,
BUT REALLY,
IT'S THEIR ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
I LOVE SURPRISE PARTIES!
- WE GOTTA ASK MY MOM FIRST.
- I NEVER THREW ONE BEFORE.
OKAY.
- OKAY.
- NICOLE AND I
GOTTA ASK YOU SOMETHING.
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU WANT TO ASK ME SOMETHING
OR TELL ME SOMETHING?
- I LOVE MESSING
WITH MY MOM
'CAUSE MY MOM'S A NERVOUS WRECK
ALL THE TIME.
SHE'S A KOOK.
- REMEMBER WHEN WE SAT YOU DOWN
AND SAID WE WERE PREGNANT?
- YEAH.
- THAT WAS FUNNY.
- WELL, WHEN I WENT OUT
LAST WEEK, SOMETHING HAPPENED.
- IS THIS A JOKE?
- [laughs]
- ALL RIGHT,
'CAUSE I'M NOT IN THE MOOD.
OH, MY GOD. I CAN'T
TAKE IT ANYMORE, I SWEAR TO GOD.
I GOTTA SIT EVERY TIME
YOU TWO TALK TO ME.
- WE WANT TO THROW JENNI
AND ROGER
A SURPRISE ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
- OKAY.
- BUT WE WANT TO DO IT HERE,
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF WE COULD.
- OKAY.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING.
- YOU'RE GONNA DO EVERYTHING?
- YEAH, LIKE, I'LL ORDER FOOD
AND, YOU KNOW.
- WE'LL GET IT CATERED.
- SO YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO ANYTHING.
- OH, I HATE THAT.
CAN'T WE JUST DO THINGS?
- BUT I DON'T WANT YOU
TO FEEL OBLIGATED
THAT YOU HAVE TO COOK
AND CRAP.
- NO, WE COULD DO IT.
- I MEAN, I'LL HELP.
YEAH, I'LL HELP.
- WHY DO YOU GOT
LORENZO'S POOP FACE ON?
- 'CAUSE YOU TWO MAKE ME--
- WE JUST SCARED HER.
- YEAH, YOU TWO JUST--
- GET HER A XANAX!
[laughter]
- AND A VODKA, PLEASE.
A CHASER.
- BUT LISTEN TO ME.
IT--IT'S A SURPRISE.
- OH.
- DON'T TELL NOBODY.
- YEAH.
- WHO WOULD I TELL?
- YOU'RE BAD AT SURPRISES.
I KNOW YOU.
- BUT WHO WOULD I TELL
THAT KNOWS JENNI?
- WE'RE INVITING, LIKE,
HER FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
- JENNI'S FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
- GIVE OR TAKE 100.
- SERIOUSLY, STOP. REALLY.
- [laughs] NO.
- * AND I WANT TO SLEEP
BESIDE YOU *
- CAN YOU IMAGINE
IF HE STARTED WALKING?
MAKE HIM WALK.
HE'S SO CUTE!
- HE'S SO LITTLE.
HE CAN CRAWL. OOH!
- NOW DO SOME TUMMY TIME.
- BABE, YOU GOT TO START
THESE THINGS EARLY.
- ALL RIGHT.
DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
- SO HE DEVELOPS FAST,
YOU KNOW?
I'M GIVING LORENZO
AN EARLY START.
WE'RE DOING TUMMY TIME.
WE'RE TRYING TO WALK.
HE'S GONNA BE A BEAST.
THE MORE I TRAIN HIM
AND GET HIM READY,
THE FASTER HE'LL BE WALKING
AND GOING NUTS.
- TO THE OLYMPICS.
- LOOK.
SEE, HE'S SO STRONG.
- GOOD.
HE'LL BE A GOOD WRESTLER.
- [laughs]
HE'S GONNA FART SOON.
I KNOW IT.
[laughs]
- WHAT'D HE DO?
- BRRRRRRR!
IS IT NORMAL?
- WHAT?
- THAT KIDS FART
AS MUCH AS OURS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HE'S TRYING SO HARD,
HE'S FARTING.
- [laughs]
- HIS LEGS ARE UP.
[laughs]
I LOVE THIS KID, I SWEAR.
- LORENZO IS
THE COOLEST KID EVER.
I MEAN, HE'S ALREADY
DOING TUMMY TIME
AND LIFTING UP HIS NECK.
I MEAN,
HE'S A STRONG BABY.
HE'S LIKE A GENIUS.
I'M GOING TO BED.
- BED, LITTLE GIPPER.
- GOOD NIGHT, LORENZO.
I LOVE YOU.
[kisses]
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
AH!
[laughs]
OW! BABE, OW!
- THIS KID IS
A FRIGGIN' MUTANT.
HE'S STRONG.
HE'S LIKE AN OX.
HE'S PULLING NICOLE'S HAIR,
AND I'M LOVING IT.
- HE'S NOT EVEN
SUPPOSED TO DO THAT YET.
- OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
*I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, I'M-- *
- [laughs]
[laughing]
- STILL DRUNK?
- WE'RE THROWING A PARTY.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE
A "MEET LORENZO" PARTY.
- I'LL COME BY MYSELF.
- I WANT BOTH OF YOU
TO COME.
- ROGER--HE LEFT YESTERDAY.
- WHERE'D HE GO?
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT?
- MASSIVE.
- KILL IT NOW.
JIONNI, PLEASE KILL IT.
- [groans]
I CAN'T WATCH IT.
- *SOMETIMES *
* I CAN'T SLEEP *
*SO I *
- YOU'RE HERE?
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE HERE.
- I'VE BEEN HERE.
- ARE YOU ANGRY?
- NO.
- OH. WHY DIDN'T YOU
GO UP AND SEE ME?
- I WAS JUST DOWN HERE,
WATCHING TV, JENNI. THAT'S ALL.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE,
HONESTLY, SLEEPING.
I'M AMAZED YOU'RE AWAKE.
- I KNOW.
I'VE BEEN IN BED ALL DAY.
- ALL DAY.
YOU'RE IN NO DIFFERENT POSITION
THAN I WAS IN LAST WEEKEND,
BUT I GOT UP WITH WORSE
OF A HANGOVER THAN YOU HAVE,
AND I WENT
AND GOT YOU BREAKFAST.
WE DIDN'T HAVE PLANS
TO DO ANYTHING TOO STRENUOUS.
WE'RE TALKING MINIATURE GOLF
AND HANGING OUT
AT AN AMUSEMENT PARK,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, IT'S NOT THAT HARD
TO DO.
- PLANS GOT [bleep] UP.
PLANS GET [bleep] UP
EVERY DAY.
IT'S ACTUALLY NOT THAT BIG
OF A DEAL.
- REMEMBER YOU SAID THAT.
- I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHERE THIS, LIKE, ANIMOSITY
COMES FROM.
IT DRIVES ME NUTS.
- YOU MADE PLANS FOR TODAY,
AND YOU SAID, NO MATTER
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT,
YOU WOULD BE ABLE TO GO TODAY
'CAUSE MY EXACT WORDS WERE,
"YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET OUT OF
BED. YOU'RE GONNA BE HUNG OVER."
YOU SAID, "NO, I WON'T DO THAT.
I'LL ABSOLUTELY GET UP."
- 'CAUSE I HONESTLY
THOUGHT NICOLE
WASN'T GONNA DRINK
THE WAY SHE DID.
- SO I GET A VERY LIMITED AMOUNT
OF--
YOU'RE BLAMING THIS
ON NICOLE NOW?
- NO, I JUST SAID THAT THIS
WOULD BE A VERY LIMITED NIGHT,
AND SO I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE LIKE--
- SO WHAT DOES THAT
HAVE TO DO WITH YOU?
HOW MUCH NICOLE DRINKS--WHAT
DOES THAT HAVE TO DO WITH YOU?
- I WANTED TO LET LOOSE
AND HAVE FUN.
- OH, MY GOOD LORD, SO YOU'RE
BLAMING THIS ON NICOLE.
- I'M NOT BLAMING IT
ON NICOLE AT ALL, BUT--
- I JUST SAID--MY QUESTION
TO YOU--LET'S JUST REITERATE.
MY QUESTION WAS--
- MY ANSWER TO YOU IS...
- I CAN'T BELIEVE--I SAID--
- I GOT [bleep] UP
JUST AS MUCH AS NICOLE
BECAUSE I ACTUALLY WAS HAVING
A GOOD TIME WITH HER.
I AM OBVIOUSLY GETTING CRUCIFIED
FOR THAT RIGHT NOW.
- NOT CRUCIFIED.
DOUBLE STANDARDS.
YOU HAVE DOUBLE STANDARDS.
- IT'S NOT A DOUBLE STANDARD.
- JENNI STILL IS NOT EVEN
GRASPING THE CONCEPT
OF WHY I'M MAD.
I DON'T CARE THAT YOU GUYS
HAD THE TIME OF YOUR LIFE.
I DON'T CARE.
YOU STILL SHOULD
HAVE BEEN UP TODAY
AND KEPT THE PLANS
THAT WE HAD.
I DIDN'T DO THIS, JENNI.
YOU DID THIS.
- NOR DID I. CAN I EXPLAIN IT,
OR ARE YOU GONNA CUT ME OFF?
- YOU GOT OUT OF BED AT 4:00.
- CAN I EXPLAIN IT,
OR ARE YOU GONNA CUT ME OFF?
- DON'T TALK TO ME LIKE THAT.
YOU'LL LOSE.
DON'T TALK TO ME
LIKE THAT, JENNI.
- I WOKE UP.
- YOU WILL LOSE. ARE WE CLEAR?
- I WOKE UP TO YOUR FOOD
AND WHATEVER.
I SAID I WAS GOING BACK TO BED.
I GO BACK TO BED.
YOU COME UP. YOU SAY THAT YOU--
WHATEVER--WHAT,
THAT YOU WERE GOING OUT.
OH, NICE, SO YOU'RE NOT GONNA
LET ME FINISH, RIGHT?
- DON'T TALK TO ME
LIKE I'M A LITTLE KID.
- YOU WERE TALKING TO ME
LIKE I'M A KID.
- YOU ARE A KID, JENNI.
YOU ARE A KID.
- NO, I'M NOT.
I'M A 27-YEAR-OLD ADULT.
- YOU'RE A 27-YEAR-OLD ADULT
THAT ACTS LIKE YOU'RE 5.
- OKAY. SO WHY DID YOU--
WHY DID YOU GET ENGAGED TO ME?
- 'CAUSE YOU BEGGED ME
TO GET ENGAGED TO YOU.
- OH.
- DO YOU WANT TO ASK
THAT QUESTION AGAIN?
YOU BEGGED ME.
- NO, YOU DON'T--
YOU'RE A GROWN MAN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
- YOU BEGGED ME
TO PROPOSE TO YOU.
- DIDN'T BEG.
- WE JUST GOT ENGAGED,
AND WE'RE FIGHTING
AND BICKERING
OVER FOOLISH,
PETTY THINGS.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
THIS BICKERING OVER,
YOU KNOW, SILLINESS
WAS BEHIND US.
IT DEFINITELY MAKES ME QUESTION
THE TIMING OF MY ENGAGEMENT.
YOU WILL LOSE,
LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO.
- I DIDN'T LOSE ANYTHING
IF I DON'T CARE.
LEAVING?
THANK YOU FOR ANSWERING ME.
VERY ADULT OF YOU.
[groans]
NOW I'M GOING TO BED.
I'M CONCERNED WITH ROGER
BEING REALLY UPSET
'CAUSE SOMETIMES I DON'T KNOW
HOW UPSET HE IS.
AND THAT'S
WHAT I'M KIND OF SCARED OF
BECAUSE I COULD HAVE
REALLY PISSED HIM OFF,
AND HE DOESN'T WANT TO COME
BACK, SO I'M UPSET ABOUT IT.
IT MAKES ME SAD.
THIS ENGAGEMENT
MIGHT BE OVER.
[pop music]
- * I WONDER WHAT I'D DO
IF I LOST YOU *
* *
* I WONDER WHAT I'D DO
IF I LOST YOU *
- YOU'RE, LIKE, BEATING HIM.
- YEAH,
BUT WHAT'S THE ALTERNATIVE?
- YEAH, LET'S JUST PUNCH
A BABY.
- ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE, PFFT.
- YOU HARDCORE MADE OUT
WITH RYDER
FOR, LIKE,
A MINUTE AND A HALF.
LIKE, SHE WAS
STRADDLING YOU.
- WELL, I MIGHT NOT BE
ENGAGED AFTER THIS.
- * YOU TAKE ME BACKWARDS *
* FORWARDS *
*MAKIN' ME CRAZY *
* I CAN'T LIVE
WITHOUT YOUR LOVE *
- IT'S QUIET IN THE HOUSE
WITHOUT ROGER AND DIESEL HERE,
SO I FEEL LIKE I REALLY
PUSHED HIM TO HIS LIMITS,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I KNOW
THAT HE'S NOT READY TO TALK
BECAUSE HE WOULD HAVE
CAME HOME,
SO I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA
HAVE TO GIVE HIM TIME.
SOMEONE'S EXTRA HAPPY.
IT'S 'CAUSE DIESEL'S NOT HERE
TO GIVE YOU GUYS HEADACHES, HUH?
- 20 BUCKS,
JENNI TELLS THE CPR LADY
SHE ALREADY KNOWS
HOW TO DO IT.
- 20?
- YEAH.
- I'LL BET YOU 20 THAT JENNI--
- CORRECTS HER?
- YEAH.
OR MAKES FACES.
- THIS MORNING, I HAVE A LADY
COMING OVER
TO TEACH ME, JIONNI, AND JENNI
HOW TO GIVE CPR ON BABIES,
AND I KNOW JENNI IS GONNA,
YOU KNOW, BE LIKE,
"I ALREADY KNOW CPR."
- SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
HERE SHE COMES.
- BOO?
- HI.
YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
- HEY.
THANKS.
- HI.
- CAN I HOLD HIM?
- OKAY.
ARE WE GETTING, LIKE,
CPR CERTIFIED?
- I AM.
I JUST KNOW IT'S ONE BREATH.
YOU DON'T DO A BREATH.
YOU, LIKE, FILL YOUR MOUTH UP
LIKE THIS,
WHERE YOU NEVER BREATHE,
FILL IT UP LIKE A CHIPMUNK,
AND YOU EXHALE INTO THE BABY,
AND IT'S TWO FINGERS.
YEAH, AND WHEN YOU HEIMLICH 'EM,
YOU FLIP 'EM TO YOUR LEFT,
LIKE, TUCKED
UNDERNEATH YOUR ARM.
I HAD TO DO THAT ONCE
IN MY LIFE. SCARY.
- YOU--YOU WHAT?
YOU HAD TO DO IT?
- I HAD TO HEIMLICH
A TWO-YEAR-OLD.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE HE--
- HOLY [bleep].
[doorbell rings]
[Lorenzo fusses]
- BABE, CAN YOU GO
GET THE DOOR?
- HI.
- HELLO.
- I CAME TO TEACH CPR.
- OKAY.
- THE FATHER.
- YES.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- JIONNI.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M AMY.
- COME ON.
COME DOWNSTAIRS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT CPR STANDS FOR.
RESPIRATORY SOMETHING?
I JUST KNOW
WE'RE GONNA LEARN IT,
AND MY SON
AIN'T CHOKING AROUND ME.
[Lorenzo fusses]
- HI.
- I'M AMY.
- NICOLE.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
- GOOD HANDSHAKE.
THIS CPR TEACHER, AMY,
SHE LOOKS LIKE A KOOK,
SHE LOOKS LIKE A CRAZY LADY,
AND THIS IS GONNA BE
INTERESTING.
- WE'RE GONNA START
WITH CHOKING.
YOU KNOW IT'S A SEVERE,
LIFE-THREATENING EVENT
IF THERE IS NO NOISE--
- PURPLE.
- IF HE'S TURNING BLUE
OR PURPLE OR A COLOR.
- I HAD A KID DO THAT
WITH, UM, CARROTS, BABY CARROTS.
- WHAT YOU DO FOR AN INFANT,
AND THAT MEANS BIRTH
TO ONE YEAR OF AGE,
IT GOES LIKE THIS.
[banging]
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE, LIKE, BEATING HIM.
- YEAH,
BUT WHAT'S THE ALTERNATIVE?
- MM-HMM.
- OKAY.
- YEAH, LET'S JUST PUNCH
A BABY.
- THIS LOOKS LIKE CHILD ABUSE
RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE SMACKING THE BABY.
YOU'RE TOSSING IT AROUND.
I GUESS
THAT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO
IF THE BABY IS, LIKE, CHOKING,
BUT IT'S A LITTLE ROUGH.
LIKE, LET THE BABY
BE LIKE THAT. FABULOUS.
- YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE HIM, LIKE,
AT AN ANGLE GOING DOWN.
- 20 BUCKS.
- BUT THEY USED TO.
FLIP THE BABY BACK.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE.
[laughs]
- ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE, PFFT.
[whispers]
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE.
- AH.
- DO YOU KNOW THE HEIMLICH?
YOU KNOW IT?
YOU WANT HER TO LEARN
THE HEIMLICH, I'M THINKING.
HERE, COME STAND UP.
- STAND UP.
- JIONNI.
SO JIONNI COMES UP TO YOU
LIKE THIS.
- [laughs]
- ARE YOU CHOKING?
- AND YOU SAY--
- [groans]
- "I'M GONNA HELP."
JUST AN UPWARD PUSH, THOUGH.
SO WHERE'S HIS BELLY BUTTON?
IT'S WAY DOWN HERE.
SO YOU'RE GONNA COME IN
JUST ABOVE THE BELLY BUTTON.
NICE.
- NICOLE MAKES AN ATTEMPT
ON GIVING ME THE HEIMLICH.
SHE GETS BEHIND ME
AND JUST STARTS RIDING ME
LIKE SEABISCUIT.
- WELL, I'M TRYING.
AND I NEVER DID HEIMLICH BEFORE.
[laughs]
- WHY NOT?
- YOU'RE GONNA
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
- IF SHE'S REALLY NOT
GONNA HELP YOU--
- GO TO THE BACK OF A CHAIR
AND DO IT MYSELF?
- YES.
- YOU'D HAVE BETTER LUCK
WITH A CHAIR, JIONNI.
- YOU MIGHT.
- YEAH.
- BUH-BUH.
OKAY?
WHICH IS NOT OFFICIAL,
BUT IT'S KIND OF WHAT PEOPLE DO.
- I'LL STICK WITH THE CHAIR.
- HEIMLICH YOURSELF.
- I RECOMMEND TO PEOPLE
THAT THEY PRACTICE ONCE A MONTH.
THEY NEVER PRACTICE,
BUT THEY SHOULD.
- WE'LL PRACTICE.
- WAS THAT A FIST BUMP?
HAVE I DONE--
- THAT'S HOW YOU BLOW IT UP.
YOU GOTTA BLOW IT UP, LIKE--
- THAT'S A POUND.
- THERE YOU GO.
- A LITTLE MORE PRACTICE.
ONCE A MONTH,
YOU GOTTA DO IT.
- [laughs]
WILLY-NILLY, THAT'S GOOD.
- I HONESTLY THINK ME AND JIONNI
ARE DOING A GREAT JOB,
AND IF, GOD FORBID,
SOMETHING HAPPENS TO LORENZO,
I THINK
WE'LL KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- WOULD YOU LIKE TO MAKE
A VISIT OVER TO YOUR CRIB?
- HE HASN'T SLEPT IN THAT YET.
- HE DOESN'T SLEEP IN IT.
- SO BUMPERS GO OUT
WHEN HE COMES IN.
I'M A RESPECTER OF GRAVITY.
I'D BE NERVOUS,
HAVING THIS IN.
YOU DON'T WANT ANYTHING
IN THE CRIB OR THE BASSINET.
- I FEEL LIKE
AMY'S JUST VERY NEUROTIC,
AND SHE'S A HIPPIE,
AND SHE JUST NEEDS TO RELAX.
- YOU WANT
A TIGHT-FITTING SHEET.
SO I'M GONNA SAY THIS IS NOT
- OH, MY GOD.
GO AWAY.
- PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS SORRY
I CAME AFTER I LEAVE.
- AT THIS POINT,
I'M LIKE, "BITCH,
"YOU CAME HERE
TO TEACH ME CPR.
"DON'T TELL ME WHAT'S GOOD
AND WHAT'S NOT GOOD FOR MY BABY.
LIKE, SHUT UP."
- AND YOU PUT HIM
ON HIS BACK TO SLEEP, RIGHT?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
- IT THAT FIRM? NOT REALLY.
- NO.
- SHE PROBABLY LIVES
IN A BOMB SHELTER.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER NOW
BECAUSE...
[laughter]
DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS?
- NO.
- [clears throat]
- NONE? NO QUESTIONS?
- NO. PRETTY GOOD, SO FAR.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- GREAT MEETING YOU.
- THANKS.
- I'LL CARRY THIS UPSTAIRS
FOR YOU.
[laughter]
- ENJOY THE BABY.
- YOU'RE GONNA HIT HER
IN THE FACE.
- YEAH, HE ALMOST
BITCH-SMACKED HER.
HE LEFT YESTERDAY.
- WHERE'D HE GO?
- HE MADE RUDE COMMENTS,
SAYING THAT HE PROPOSED TO ME,
AND HE TOOK IT AS I WAS,
LIKE, SHOVING IT DOWN
HIS [bleep] THROAT TO DO IT.
- * WE'RE ALWAYS
ON THE RUN *
- CIAO.
- BYE.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT?
JIONNI, JIONNI, JIONNI!
- A [bleep] SPIDER!
- MASSIVE.
SO I FIND
THIS GIANT [bleep] SPIDER,
CRAWLING ACROSS THE GROUND.
I'M FREAKING
THE [bleep] OUT
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
IT JUST CAME FROM, YOU KNOW,
LORENZO'S BASSINET,
AND IT'S A JUICY ONE,
AND I'M LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD,
[bleep] SOMEBODY KILL THIS
RIGHT NOW."
- KILL IT NOW.
- THAT IS NOT A [bleep] DADDY,
RIGHT?
- WOW! WHAT IS THAT?
- THAT'S PROBABLY
WHAT THE SPIDER WEB WAS FROM.
IT'S GONNA JUMP ON YOUR FACE.
- THAT LOOKS LIKE A, UH,
AN AFRICAN, UH--
- JIONNI, IT'S NOT AFRICAN.
CAN YOU JUST STEP ON IT?
- GOOGLE IT
AFTER YOU STEP ON IT.
- COME HERE, BITTY BABY.
- UGH!
- EW!
EVERYONE KNOWS
I'M AFRAID OF SPIDERS
AND ANYTHING ELSE WITH 12 LEGS
TO 16 LEGS OR WHATEVER.
- JIONNI, PLEASE KILL IT.
- [groans]
I CAN'T WATCH THAT.
- GET IT!
IT'S MOVING, IT'S MOVING!
- OOH!
- GOOD EYE, BOO.
'CAUSE I [bleep]
HATE SPIDERS.
EW, JIONNI, WASH YOUR HANDS.
JIONNI!
- EW, HE'S TOUCHING IT
BARE-HANDED.
- THAT COULD HAVE,
LIKE, SALMONELLA.
- THAT'S CHICKEN, BUT OKAY.
- WHATEVER.
LIKE, THAT'S DISGUSTING
BECAUSE I LIVE DOWN HERE,
AND WHAT IF THIS SPIDER
JUMPS ON LORENZO?
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
[Lorenzo fusses]
OH, WE'RE THROWING A PARTY
ON FRIDAY FOR LORENZO.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE
A "MEET LORENZO" PARTY.
- OKAY.
- LIKE, FOR ALL MY FRIENDS
AND FAMILY.
I WANT YOU AND ROGER TO COME.
- FRIDAY NIGHT?
I'LL COME BY MYSELF.
- I WANT BOTH OF YOU TO COME.
- HE LEFT YESTERDAY.
- WHERE'D HE GO?
- ROGER IS MAD AT ME ABOUT,
UH, EVENTS THAT TOOK PLACE
YESTERDAY, SO HE LEFT,
AND HE'S PROBABLY GONNA BE
GONE FOR A COUPLE DAYS,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU TAKE BUBBA,
THAT MEANS YOU'RE GONE
FOR A COUPLE DAYS.
HE MADE RUDE COMMENTS,
SAYING THAT HE PROPOSED TO ME,
AND HE TOOK IT AS I WAS,
LIKE, SHOVING IT DOWN
HIS [bleep] THROAT TO DO IT.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE, THOUGH.
- NO, IT REALLY ISN'T.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
HE ACTUALLY TOLD ME NOT TO SPEAK
HIS NAME TODAY HERE,
SO I'M PROBABLY GONNA
GET YELLED AT FOR THAT.
- IS HE HUNGRY?
- YOU CAN GIVE HIM
THE LITTLE 2-OUNCE BOTTLE,
AND THEN I'LL PUMP AGAIN.
- HOW MUCH DID YOU
HAVE TO DUMP?
DID THE STRIPS WORK
THIS TIME?
- OH, MY GOD. IT TURNED,
LIKE, BROWN AND FUZZY.
- IT WAS LIKE--
- IT WAS DEFINITELY [bleep] UP.
- CONTAMINATED.
- SERIOUSLY?
- SO I DUMPED TWICE,
JUST IN CASE.
AFTER THE LIMO RIDE, WHEN I
GOT HERE, I DON'T REMEMBER.
- I DON'T REMEMBER
ANY OF THE RIDE HOME,
EXCEPT FOR, LIKE,
BEING IN THE PARKING LOT
AND HER BEING LIKE, "I HAVE
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM,"
AND I, LIKE, BLACKED OUT.
- HOW MUCH DID WE DRINK?
- I DRANK BEFORE I GOT HERE.
THEN THE SANGRIA I HAD.
THEN THE CHAMPAGNE
AND VODKA AT DINNER.
THEN THE--THE SAKE BOMB.
THEN WE WERE DOING SHOTS AT--
- HE'S STILL FARTING.
- HI, BOOGIE.
FOR SOME REASON, I REMEMBER YOU,
LIKE, DANCING CRAZY.
- YOU WIPED OUT 'CAUSE YOUR HAIR
WAS SOAKING WET.
SO YOU, LIKE, STARTED
GIVING ME A LAP DANCE,
AND I PUT MY HAND ON YOUR HAIR,
AND IT WAS DRIPPING.
- OH, 'CAUSE IT
WAS RAINING OUTSIDE,
AND I KEPT GOING
TO HAVE CIGARETTES.
- YOU, LIKE,
MOPPED THE FLOOR.
- I WOKE UP, AND JIONNI'S LIKE,
"YOU STINK."
- [laughs]
- REMEMBER?
YOU TOLD ME I SMELL.
- HERE,
I'LL TAKE HIM UPSTAIRS.
- I DON'T WANT
TO LET YOU GO.
- I'M GONNA BRING HIM
TO MY GRANDMA'S.
- IS HE HUNGRY?
- HE HAS MILK UPSTAIRS TOO.
BE RIGHT BACK.
- I TOLD ROGER WE MADE OUT.
- WHAT? WE MADE OUT?
- YEAH.
- I DON'T REMEMBER THAT.
- WE ONLY MADE OUT FOR,
LIKE, TWO SECONDS.
YOU HARDCORE MADE OUT
WITH RYDER
FOR, LIKE,
A MINUTE AND A HALF.
LIKE, SHE WAS
STRADDLING YOU.
- WE MADE OUT?
- MM-HMM.
- [bleep] IT.
- I HOPE JIONNI
DOESN'T MIND.
- HE'LL PROBABLY
GET MAD AT THAT.
- FROM WHAT I RECALL,
NICOLE IS AN AMAZING KISSER.
LOTS OF TONGUE.
- OH, GOD!
I DIDN'T KNOW WE MADE OUT.
- YOU WERE ON TOP OF LAURA,
LIKE, MADLY IN LOVE WITH HER,
TRYING TO MAKE OUT WITH HER.
- OH, MY GOD.
- AND I BASICALLY
TOOK ONE FOR THE TEAM
'CAUSE LAURA WAS,
LIKE, SCARED.
SHE WAS LIKE,
"DO I KISS HER? DO I NOT?"
AND I'M LIKE,
"NICOLE, YOU WANT TO MAKE OUT?"
AND YOU'RE LIKE...
AND THEN YOU ENDED UP
ON RYDER.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
RIGHT WHEN JENNI TELLS ME
THAT I DID ALL THIS [bleep],
I HONESTLY FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA GO TO THE PRINCIPAL'S
AND GET IN A LOT OF TROUBLE
BECAUSE I KNOW JIONNI'S GONNA BE
VERY PISSED OFF AT ME.
- I ASSUMED YOU KNEW.
I WAS JUST NOT GONNA, LIKE,
BRING IT UP WITH HIM.
- NO, I HAD NO IDEA.
- YOU WERE JUST DRUNK
'CAUSE YOU WERE HAPPY.
I HONESTLY--
- I HAD THE BEST TIME EVER.
- NEVER THOUGHT
IN A MILLION YEARS,
YOU WERE GONNA BE
LIKE THAT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
REALLY GONNA BE RESERVED.
- ME TOO.
- YOUR ALTER EGO CAME OUT.
- WELL, I'M NEVER
DOING THAT AGAIN THAT CRAZY.
IT'S NOT, LIKE,
A GOOD LOOK FOR A MOM.
- I KNOW SO MANY MOMS
THAT DO THAT.
- NOT FOR JIONNI.
- [laughs]
- AND HE WON'T BE WITH ME
IF I DO THAT.
JIONNI DOESN'T MIND ME
GOING OUT,
GOING CRAZY WITH MY FRIENDS,
GETTING DRUNK,
BUT, LIKE, BEING HIS FIANCEE
AND, LIKE, BEING A MOM,
HE DOESN'T WANT ME TO,
YOU KNOW,
BE MAKING OUT WITH MY FRIENDS
ANYMORE.
THAT'S LIKE--
- HIGH SCHOOL?
- THAT'S, LIKE, SINGLE ME,
AND I KNOW, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS GONNA CAUSE
A SERIOUS PROBLEM.
WELL, I MIGHT NOT BE
ENGAGED AFTER THIS.
- YEAH. ME EITHER.
- [bleep].
- I MIGHT HAVE TO RETURN
MY RING.
- ME TOO.
I'M LIKE, OH, DEAR.
I TEXT JIONNI,
"LISTEN, AT THE CLUB LAST NIGHT,
I DID BLACK OUT,
AND I MADE OUT WITH RYDER."
- HOW MANY MOMS DO YOU KNOW
THAT HOOK UP WITH GIRLS
AT CLUBS?
- SO YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE WITH ME NOW?
- YOU CAN LEAVE NOW.
[alternative music]
* *
- WELL, I MIGHT NOT BE
ENGAGED AFTER THIS.
JIONNI MIGHT BREAK UP
WITH ME.
- OVER THAT?
- YEAH.
- OVER WHAT PART?
- MAKING OUT.
- YOU MADE OUT WITH DEENA
BEFORE THIS.
- YEAH, AND HE HATED ME
FOR IT.
DO YOU THINK THAT MAKES ME
LOOK LIKE A BAD MOM?
- YOU'RE NOT A BAD MOTHER.
EVERY MOTHER'S
GONNA MAKE MISTAKES.
EVERY MOTHER WANTS TO HAVE
A DRINK AND HAVE A GOOD TIME
AND LET LOOSE AFTER MONTHS
OF [bleep] CARRYING A CHILD.
NOBODY HAS A RIGHT
TO TELL SOMEONE
THAT CARRIES A CHILD
FOR NINE MONTHS HOW TO ACT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YOU CAN BE THE BEST MOTHER
YOU CAN BE,
AND YOU CAN STILL BE SNOOKI.
STOP BEING THE PERSON
THAT YOU THINK YOU HAVE TO BE,
AND JUST BE YOU.
- I'M ONLY LIKE THAT
'CAUSE OF JIONNI.
- I KNOW. STOP.
- HE, LIKE--
- HE--IF HE DOESN'T MARRY YOU
FOR YOU,
THEN YOU SHOULDN'T
GET MARRIED.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO BE FAKE.
I CAN SEE IT SOMETIMES.
I SEE HOW [bleep] RESERVED
YOU ARE.
IT DRIVES ME NUTS
'CAUSE I LOVE YOU,
AND I'M LIKE--
- IT'S KIND OF GETTING
UNDER MY SKIN A LITTLE BIT.
- NICOLE'S JUST TRYING
TO BE A STEPFORD WIFE.
SHE'S TRYING TO BE SOMETHING
THAT SHE'S NOT.
SHE'S TRYING TO SAY THAT
SHE LOVES BEING IN THE BASEMENT
AND SITTING THERE ALL DAY AND
WATCHING TV SHOWS WITH JIONNI,
BUT I KNOW, DEEP DOWN,
SHE DOESN'T.
- DON'T EVER SAY ANYTHING
'CAUSE IT WILL JUST
CAUSE PROBLEMS.
- OH, I KNOW, BUT HE HAS
TO [bleep] CUT HIS [bleep] OUT,
SERIOUSLY,
OR HE'S GONNA LOSE YOU.
- NO, BUT WHEN I TELL HIM THIS,
WE'RE GONNA--
- FIGHT. YOU DIDN'T CHEAT,
YOU DIDN'T LIE.
- I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT.
- YOU DIDN'T DISRESPECT HIM.
- I HATE FIGHTING.
- OH, I KNOW.
BUT, LIKE, THEN,
LET HIM FIGHT WITH HIMSELF.
LET HIM FIGHT THE [bleep] WALL,
AND YOU BE LIKE,
"I HAD A GOOD TIME.
NOW DEAL WITH IT."
I THINK NICOLE
IS BOWING DOWN TO JIONNI.
FIGHTS HAPPEN, BUT YOU
SHOULD BE THE REAL YOU.
THERE'S NO LONGEVITY
IN THAT RELATIONSHIP
BECAUSE SOMEBODY'S GONNA HAVE TO
STOP BEING FAKE SOONER OR LATER.
JIONNI IS TRYING TO CHANGE YOU
INTO, LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST HURTS ME,
SEEING THAT.
IF YOU WERE OKAY WITH IT,
I WOULD BE COMPLETELY FINE.
IF YOU WERE LIKE, "I'M TOTALLY
INTO BEING SUSIE HOMEMAKER.
I [bleep] LOVE WASHING DISHES,"
I WOULD BE SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
BUT YOU'RE NOT HAPPY.
- SHUT UP.
- I KNOW.
- I'M NOT, LIKE, MISERABLE.
- I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE NOT YOU.
- WELL, I DON'T WANT
TO LOSE HIM.
- NO, AND I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
AND MAYBE A REALITY CHECK
FOR HIM WILL BE GOOD.
HE GIVES YOU REALITY CHECKS
ALL THE TIME, NO?
- YEAH, HE TRIES TO.
- EXACTLY.
SO [bleep] GIVE HIM ONE.
I'M NOT TELLING YOU TO GO
[bleep] BREAK UP WITH HIS ASS.
GOOD LORD.
- WELL, ME MAKING OUT
WITH YOU AND RYDER
IS DISRESPECTING HIM,
TO HIM.
- HOW?
- TO HIM.
- BUT THAT'S
HIS OWN INSECURITY.
"WHAT IS THIS PERSON
GONNA SAY?
"WHAT IS
THAT PERSON GONNA SAY?
"MY FIANCEE SNOOKI MADE OUT
WITH TWO GIRLS
"ON THE NIGHT
THAT SHE WENT OUT
'CAUSE SHE HASN'T DRANK
IN TEN MONTHS."
IS THAT REALLY
THAT BIG OF A DEAL?
DOES SHE HAVE ANY REGRETS?
AND IF THEY ALL ADD UP
IN A POSITIVE,
WHY DOES HE HAVE
TO MAKE IT A NEGATIVE?
IT'S NOT THAT BIG
OF A DEAL.
- I'M SCARED.
RIGHT NOW, I KNOW I'M GONNA BE
IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
I'M JUST SO NERVOUS
TO TELL JIONNI,
AND I HONESTLY JUST WANT
TO HIDE IN A HOLE.
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
- MAKE HIM REALIZE
WHO HE FELL IN LOVE WITH.
BUT JUST KNOW,
I CAN TELL,
AND IF I CAN TELL,
OTHERS CAN TELL.
- ALL RIGHT.
GET OUT OF HERE.
- LOVE YOU. BYE.
TOODLES.
DON'T DROWN YOURSELF IN THE TUB
AFTER THAT CONVO.
- OH, MY BOOB HURTS.
I'VE GOT TO PUMP SOON.
- * I KIND OF KNEW
ALL ALONG *
* THAT THIS WOULD HAPPEN *
- OH, MAN, I'M SCREWED.
SO JIONNI'S IN THE ROOM
WITH ME, AND HONESTLY,
LIKE, I CAN'T GET
ANY WORDS OUT.
I'M SO SCARED TO TELL HIM
THAT, YOU KNOW,
I JUST WANT TO TEXT HIM
AND TELL HIM INSTEAD
BECAUSE I HONESTLY CAN'T
TELL HIM TO HIS FACE.
I TEXT JIONNI, "LISTEN,"
LIKE, "I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA
BE UPSET WITH ME.
"I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
"BUT AT THE CLUB LAST NIGHT,
I DID BLACK OUT,
"AND I MADE OUT WITH JENNI,
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY,
AND JUST PLEASE
DON'T HATE ME."
- *IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE YOU
BREAK MY HEART IN TWO *
* OH, BABY, I HOPE *
* YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING TO ME *
*OH, BABY, I HOPE... *
- TOO MUCH OF A COWARD
TO TELL ME BEFORE?
STAY AWAY FROM ME, OKAY?
FAR, FAR AWAY.
- * IT WON'T BE LONG
BEFORE I CRY A TEAR FOR YOU *
- YOU KNOW, IT JUST HURTS
BECAUSE I LOVE HIM,
AND HE KNOWS I LOVE HIM,
AND JUST TO TELL ME
TO [bleep] OFF,
AND HE DOESN'T WANT ANYTHING
TO DO WITH ME,
IT'S JUST LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"DO YOU LOVE ME?
BECAUSE I COULDN'T
THROW YOU AWAY LIKE THAT."
- * OH, BABY, I HOPE *
* YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING *
- I DON'T GET IT.
- * OH, BABY, I HOPE *
* YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING *
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- *IF I TRIED
MY VERY BEST *
* TOLD YOU EVERYTHING,
CONFESSED *
* WOULD YOU SAVE ME? *
* WOULD YOU
SAVE ME? *
*IF I LAUGH *
* IF I CRY *
- SO RIGHT WHEN I TELL JIONNI,
YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENED,
"I MADE OUT WITH JENNI,
I'M SO SORRY,"
JIONNI TEXTED ME, "YOU NEED
TO MOVE OUT OF THE HOUSE.
STAY AWAY
FROM LORENZO AND ME."
I'M A PIECE OF [bleep].
I'M A HORRIBLE MOM.
I'M A HORRIBLE FIANCEE.
CAN YOU SIT DOWN?
- YEAH.
HOLD ON.
- * IF I MADE
A BIG MISTAKE *
* WOULD YOU FORGIVE ME? *
- YOU KNOW,
IT BREAKS MY HEART
THAT HE'S BEING SO MEAN
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
I DESERVE IT.
- * SAVE ME *
- WHY ARE YOU GONNA END US
JUST BECAUSE I KISSED JENNI?
- WHAT'D YOU SAY TO ME
BEFORE YOU LEFT?
"I'M NOT THAT GIRL ANYMORE.
"I HAVE A SON NOW.
I'M A FIANCEE."
OH, "YOU'RE MAKING ME
FEEL GUILTY
FOR HAVING FUN
WITH MY FRIENDS."
HOW DO YOU FEEL
RIGHT NOW? GUILTY?
- I FEEL LIKE [bleep].
- YOU FEEL LIKE [bleep].
SO AM I A BAD PERSON
FOR BEING MAD ABOUT IT?
- I'M NOT SAYING
YOU'RE A BAD PERSON,
BUT WHY DO YOU NOT WANT
TO GET MARRIED NOW
JUST BECAUSE OF THIS?
AND I'M A HORRIBLE MOM
AND A FIANCEE.
- HOW MANY MOMS DO YOU KNOW THAT
HOOK UP WITH GIRLS AT CLUBS?
- SO YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE WITH ME NOW?
- I DIDN'T SAY I DIDN'T
WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
- DO YOU WANT ME TO READ THE
TEXT MESSAGES? BECAUSE I WILL.
- HOW MANY FIANCEES GO OUT
AND HOOK UP WITH GIRLS AT CLUBS?
- OKAY, I WENT
A LITTLE OVERBOARD.
- I DON'T CARE
IF YOU HURT ME.
YOU [bleep] ME OVER IN ITALY
PRETTY DAMN BAD.
ALL THE RUMORS ABOUT MIKE
HURT PRETTY BAD.
I COULD DEAL WITH THAT
MY OWN WAY.
BUT NOW YOU'RE [bleep]
HURTING HIM.
- 'CAUSE I KISSED JENNI,
I'M HURTING MY SON?
- YOU KISSED JENNI? YOU THINK
THAT'S ALL THAT HAPPENED?
WHEN YOU WERE HOOKING UP
WITH JENNI,
WERE YOU THINKING ABOUT ME
OR LORENZO? OBVIOUSLY NOT.
IF NICOLE DOESN'T THINK
SHE'S WRONG FOR WHAT SHE DID,
THEN IT'S GONNA BE A WHILE
BEFORE WE GET MARRIED, IF WE DO.
NOW, YOU EITHER COULD GO GET
HELP ABOUT YOUR DRINKING
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
- JIONNI, THIS IS MY FIRST TIME
GOING OUT IN TEN MONTHS.
I DRANK A LITTLE BIT TOO MUCH,
AND [bleep] GOT WILD.
SO I NEED TO GO GET HELP?
- YEAH.
WHEN YOU DRINK,
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
NICOLE,
IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME
YOU BLACK OUT AND DRUNK
AND [bleep] UP.
- JIONNI, I WAS HAVING FUN.
- I HAD SO MUCH FUN
WITH MY GUY FRIENDS,
BUT IN THE BACK OF MY MIND,
WE WERE LIKE,
"HEY, COME ON,
LET'S TAKE ANOTHER SHOT."
"SORRY, GUYS, I CAN'T.
I HAVE A SON TOMORROW
TO LOOK AFTER."
- OKAY, THAT'S YOU,
BUT I CELEBRATED ANOTHER WAY
WITH MY FRIENDS.
- OKAY, WELL,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T WANT TO BE WITH SOMEBODY
THAT DOES THAT.
- I HONESTLY COULDN'T IMAGINE
LOSING JIONNI.
HE'S LEGIT, LIKE,
MY BEST FRIEND,
SO THE FACT THAT HE'S SAYING
THESE THINGS,
AND I THOUGHT HE WAS, YOU KNOW,
LIKE, THE LOVE OF MY LIFE
AND HE WOULD NEVER HURT ME,
I MEAN,
HE'S HURTING ME RIGHT NOW.
YOU JUST DON'T LIKE ME.
- WHEN YOU DO THAT, NO.
SO WE'VE GOT
TO FIGURE SOMETHING OUT AND--
- THERE'S NOT GONNA BE
ANYTHING TO FIGURE OUT
BECAUSE THIS ALWAYS HAPPENS.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN,
"THIS ALWAYS HAPPENS"?
- I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU WANT ME TO READ THE TEXT
MESSAGES THAT YOU SENT ME?
- NO.
- 'CAUSE IT'S NOT OKAY.
- IT'S NOT OKAY WHAT YOU DID.
- JIONNI, I'M NOT GONNA
DO THAT ALL THE TIME.
I'M NOT GOING OUT LIKE THAT.
IT WAS ONE TIME.
- IT WAS ONE TIME. OKAY, WHAT'D
YOU SAY TO ME BEFORE THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO THEN.
- YOU NEED TO FIX IT.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT SAYING
ANYTHING VERY, UH--
- I JUST DON'T LIKE
THE THINGS YOU SAID TO ME.
IT WAS REALLY MEAN.
- OKAY, OF COURSE.
TURN IT AROUND ON ME.
- I'M NOT, I'M JUST--
I HAVE FEELINGS TOO,
AND I CAN SAY WHAT I WANT.
- OKAY.
- GOD.
I HONESTLY FEEL LIKE I'M NOT
THE GIRL THAT JIONNI WANTS.
LIKE, HE WANTS ME TO BE
SOMEBODY THAT, YOU KNOW,
DOESN'T GO OUT
AND HAVE A GOOD TIME,
AND I LOVE TO GO OUT
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE JIONNI
JUST DOESN'T LIKE ME.
- IS THAT IT? JENNI'S
THE ONLY THING THAT HAPPENED?
GIVING HER LAP DANCES,
DANCING LIKE THAT,
HOOKING UP WITH HER IS THE ONLY
BAD THING THAT HAPPENED?
YES? NO? MAYBE?
- WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
- I WANT TO KNOW.
WHAT ELSE HAPPENED?
- SHE SAID I MADE OUT
WITH RYDER TOO.
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN LEAVE NOW.
[Lorenzo crying]
AND ON YOUR WAY OUT,
GO TELL MY MOM
WE'RE NOT HAVING
THE PARTY HERE.
GO RENT A HALL.
DON'T TELL HER WHY 'CAUSE
YOU'RE GONNA BREAK HER HEART.
YOU JUST HOOKED UP WITH JENNI
AND RYDER? THAT'S IT?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S IT? ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOT A BIG DEAL.
BUT I'M THE ASS[bleep].
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN, THIS IS THE LAST THING
I WANTED TO EVER HAPPEN,
YOU KNOW, WAS TO FIGHT
LIKE THIS WITH JIONNI,
AND I JUST HOPE
WE CAN WORK IT OUT
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WOULD DO
IF WE DIDN'T WORK OUT.
[Lorenzo fusses]
[crying]
- *I CAN'T MAKE YOU CARE *
* IF THERE'S NOTHIN' THERE *
* I CAN'T MAKE ME FORGET *
* I CAN'T MAKE YOU
LOVE ME *
- I'M A GOOD MOM,
I THINK.
- * YOU KNOW
YOU NEVER DID *
- I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW MUCH YOU [bleep] HURT ME.
EVERY TIME I LET YOU GO OUT,
I GOTTA THINK
ABOUT IF YOU'RE GONNA BLACK OUT
AND HURT ME.
I DON'T WANT TO MARRY YOU
IF THAT'S HOW YOU'RE GONNA BE.
- IT'S DEFINITELY QUIET
IN THE HOUSE WITHOUT ROGER.
I AM REALLY MISSING HIM.
- HELLO?
- HEY, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WANTED
TO COME OVER AND TALK.
- UM...
- ISN'T IT FUNNY
HOW WE WERE SO EXCITED
TO BE, LIKE, ENGAGED,
AND WE'RE BOTH FIGHTING?
- IS IT THAT BAD?
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF I'M GETTING MARRIED.