- I WAS THINKING
ABOUT BRINGING ROGER UPSTATE
TO SEE MOM.
- OH.
- YOU THINK
THAT WON'T SCARE HIM?
MY MOM LIVES
IN UPSTATE NEW YORK.
SHE'S BEEN LIVING
IN AN ASSISTED LIVING HOME.
SINCE I WAS TWO,
THAT'S ALL I'VE KNOWN.
I HAVEN'T INTRODUCED
REALLY ANYONE TO MY MOM.
- DO YOU THINK
THERE WILL EVER BE A POINT
WHERE YOU'RE COMFORTABLE
WITH ME MEETING HER?
- WE DON'T CUDDLE ANYMORE.
- YEAH, WE DO.
- NO, WE DON'T.
DO I LOOK ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, YOU LOOK GOOD.
- YOU THINK I'LL COME BACK
LIKE, "HEY."
- I HOPE SO.
- I'M SO EXCITED TO JUST,
YOU KNOW,
TRY AND GET
THE ROMANCE BACK WITH JIONNI,
AND ALSO
HAVE A GLASS OF WINE.
WHOA.
I HAVEN'T BEEN OUT THIS LATE
IN YEARS.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'T CARE
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'T CARE
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'T CARE
- CHEERS.
- TO LORENZO.
UGH.
IT JUST TASTES WEIRD
TO ME,
MAYBE 'CAUSE
I'M NOT USED TO IT ANYMORE.
- FEELIN' IT?
- I MIGHT FEEL DRUNK.
- A LITTLE--OH, GOD.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
- OH, [bleep].
OH, GOD.
- [laughs]
- SO IT BEGINS.
- [snorts]
- [laughs]
JUST HALF A GLASS.
PLEASE--
- ICE CREAM?
- OH, THANK YOU.
- [laughs]
- SORRY. SORRY.
- [snorts, sighs]
- NO, ALL RIGHT.
- [laughs]
- CRACK ME UP.
- HERE.
- [laughs]
I'M CRYING.
- AS A PARENT,
IT'S HARD TO LEAVE YOUR CHILD.
BUT NICOLE AND I NEED
THIS ALONE TIME,
AND I JUST WANT HER
TO HAVE FUN.
IT'S BEEN NINE MONTHS FOR HER
TO HAVE ONE GLASS OF WINE,
AND SHE DESERVES IT.
- OH.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- MY [bleep] ARE KILLING ME.
- PUMP WHEN YOU GET HOME.
- UGH.
- HICCUPS.
[baby hiccups]
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
GET THAT LITTLE FOOT UP
OUT OF THERE.
GET HIS FOOT UP.
[baby coos]
- YOU KICKING UNCLE ROGER?
- WHAT YOU DOING,
LITTLE BUDDY?
- ROGER HOLDING LORENZO
IS SO CUTE.
- WHAT YOU DOING,
WHAT YOU DOING, LITTLE MANNY?
- LIKE, I CAN HONESTLY SAY,
LIKE, "THIS WILL BE THE MAN
THAT I WILL SPEND
THE REST OF MY LIFE WITH."
CAN I CALL MY MOM?
- YEAH, SURE.
- I REALLY APPRECIATE
ROGER WANTING TO MEET MY MOM.
HE'S BEEN VERY PATIENT,
AND I REALIZE
I JUST WANT THIS
TO HAPPEN.
JUST ASK IF WE CAN
GO OVER THERE TOMORROW,
AROUND 11:30, YEAH.
I LOVE YOU. BYE.
- [farts, laughs]
- EW.
- [laughs]
- OH, [bleep].
[murmuring]
JIONNI, YOU'RE ON MY DRESS.
- SHE'S DRUNK.
LORENZO?
- SHH!
- WHERE IS HE?
- SHH.
JESUS.
"WHERE IS MY BABY?"
"LORENZO!"
LIKE HE'S GONNA ANSWER.
- [laughs]
- LIKE HE'S GONNA BE LIKE,
"HEY, MOM, DOWN HERE."
- I WISH.
- HE'S OUT LIKE A LIGHT.
- SHE HAVE A DRINK?
- THIS CRAZY ONE?
- YOU MENTAL?
- I HAD TWO GLASSES.
- SHE'S SO LOOPY.
- I'M NOT.
- UH-OH.
- [laughs]
- I SWEAR, I'M NOT.
- YOU HAD TWO GLASSES?
- YEAH.
- HOW YOU FEEL?
- GOOD.
FEEL GOOD?
- I'M FINE.
- LITTLE LOOPY?
- JIONNI GETTING LUCKY
TONIGHT?
- NO, I CAN'T HAVE SEX
FOR SIX WEEKS.
- REALLY?
- I HAVE A STITCH
IN MY VAGINA.
- T.M.I.
- HI, BABE.
- THE BABY WAS GOOD.
I HELD HIM FOR A WHILE.
- REALLY?
- YEAH. HE'S BEEN, LIKE,
QUIET AS A CHURCH MOUSE
FOR THE LAST HALF HOUR OR SO.
- YEAH,
UNTIL IT'S 1:00 IN THE MORNING.
- WE WERE PLAYING WITH HIM
FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR AND A HALF.
- HE'S ALL YOURS THEN.
- YEAH.
- I TRIED TO KEEP HIM UP
AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
I WAS, LIKE,
EVEN HOLDING HIM STRAIGHT UP,
AND HE WAS LIKE...
[snores]
[laughs]
- DID YOU PUT
HIS DUCKY PAJAMAS ON?
- MM-HMM.
HE DRANK A FULL BOTTLE.
- OF MINE?
- YOURS.
- THIS BIG, BIG WORLD
YOU LIVE IN.
WE'RE GONNA GET GOING.
GOT A LONG DRIVE TOMORROW.
- WHERE?
- UPSTATE.
- OH, YOU'RE GOING?
- 7:00 IN THE MORNING.
[kiss]
- HAVE FUN.
- TOMORROW,
ME AND ROGER ARE GONNA HEAD UP
TO UPSTATE NEW YORK
TO VISIT MY MOM,
AND, YOU KNOW, EVEN THOUGH
I ORIGINALLY CANCELLED,
I FEEL LIKE, HE'S GOTTA
MEET HER, WHY NOT TOMORROW?
I'M ABOUT
TO FALL ASLEEP.
[clatter]
[gasps]
- WE'RE GETTING READY
TO LEAVE.
OF COURSE, I HAVE TO GET
ONE LAST DIG IN AT JIONNI.
I SEE A WRESTLING TROPHY
THAT LOOKS
LIKE TWO GAY GLADIATORS
GOING AT IT.
- HOMOSEXUAL.
- YEAH, HE'S GONNA DO
A GAY JOKE.
- I KNOW.
[all gasp]
- [laughing] OH, MY GOD.
- JIONNI!
- OH--
- WHAT?
- ROGER JUST BROKE ALL YOUR--
- I JUST DESTROYED
YOUR [bleep] COLLECTION.
[laughs]
THE WHOLE THING
GOES LIKE THIS, LOOK.
- YOU JUST BROKE JESUS
ON HIS CROSS.
- THAT'S THE WORST THING
OUT OF ALL OF 'EM, JESUS.
- I WAS GONNA MAKE
A GAY JOKE
AND THEN BROKE
YOUR ENTIRE COLLECTION.
[baby crying]
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
DO WE--CAN YOU THROW
A JESUS OUT OR NO?
- NO. THIS ISN'T ANYTHING
TO DO WITH JESUS, IS IT?
- NO, THAT WAS
A CHRISTENING GIFT.
[laughs]
- NO, IT WASN'T.
- YEAH.
- I JUST KILLED THE MOOD.
- IT'S TIME TO GO.
WE NEED TO GO.
- SORRY FOR DESTROYING
YOUR ROOM.
- SEE YOU LATER.
- I DID FIX YOUR SHELF,
THOUGH.
AND NOW IT'S NOT A SAFETY HAZARD
FOR THE BABY ANYMORE.
- GRAB YOUR PHONE, BABE.
- THANKS, ROG.
- I FELT REALLY
LIKE AN ASS[bleep],
BUT I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT HAVE
SAVED THE KID'S LIFE TOO,
BECAUSE IF THE KID
WAS OVER THERE
PLAYING WITH THAT SHELF
ONE DAY--
- IT'S JUST SAFE TO SAY
THAT WE CAN LEAVE NOW.
- YEAH.
- OOH. OOH.
STILL GOIN'.
OH, MY GO--OOH.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M SCARED
TO CHANGE THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE A KID.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT YET?
THAT, LIKE--
- IT HASN'T HIT YOU YET?
- SOMETIMES, LIKE,
THIS IS MY KID.
- MM-HMM. OUR.
- OUR KID.
MMM!
I JUST WANT TO STARE AT LORENZO,
I WANT TO HANG OUT WITH JIONNI,
AND, YOU KNOW, I JUST
WANT TO BE WITH MY FAMILY.
LIKE, I LOVE THIS
RIGHT NOW.
I'M HAPPY WE'RE HOME.
MM. MMM.
- I LOVE HIM.
WHEN WILL YOU HAVE
ANOTHER ONE?
- JIONNI.
- I WOULD LIKE
TO MEET HER ONCE, YOU KNOW,
EVEN IF IT'S ONLY ONCE.
- I WOULD DEFINITELY SAY
THIS IS A PRETTY BIG STEP
FOR ROGER TO MEET MY MOM.
ARE YOU EXCITED?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- ME AND ROGER
ARE ABOUT TO GO TO DINNER.
- IS IT A FANCY RESTAURANT?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF IT,
SO I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S FREAKING ME OUT
WITH THIS DINNER.
- IS HE PROPOSING?
- ♪ I'LL SAVE
A LITTLE PIECE OF TOMORROW ♪
♪ FOR YOU, CHILD
- GIVE ME--GIVE ME
THE GAME PLAN REAL QUICK AGAIN.
YOUR MOM WILL ALREADY BE THERE
WHEN WE GET THERE OR NO?
- YEAH, I'LL DO HER HAIR,
AND YOU COME BACK AND MEET HER.
- OKAY.
[clears throat]
- SO THIS MORNING, IT'S THE DAY
THAT ROGER'S MEETING MY MOM,
AND RIGHT NOW
I'M KINDA ANXIOUS,
OVERWHELMED, BUT I AM EXCITED
FOR ROGER TO MEET HER.
IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW,
GONNA BE A LONG DAY.
- LET'S DO THIS.
YOU DON'T NEED YOUR PURSE?
OKAY, WE'RE DONE.
[baby crying]
- WHERE'S NICOLE?
- COME ON.
[doorbell rings]
- UH-OH,
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
- TODAY, STEPH AND MY MOM ARE
COMING OVER TO SUNDAY DINNER,
AND I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE THEM.
- HEY.
- HI.
- I MISSED YOU.
- HEY, MA.
- YOU LOST
A LOT OF WEIGHT ALREADY.
- YOU THINK?
THE BELLY'S GONE.
DO YOU WANT TO TEST
MY BREAST MILK?
- DO I WANT TO TEST IT?
NO, NOT REALLY.
- THAT'S GROSS.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TRY IT?
- WELL, SINCE I DRANK,
I HAVE TO--
- OH, TEST IT?
- NO, NOT, LIKE, DRINK IT.
- UGH.
- OH. [laughs]
- THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT
SHE MEANT.
- RIGHT? YEAH. [laughs]
- I WAS LIKE, "WHY WOULD SHE
DRINK YOUR BREAST MILK?"
- ME AND JENNI ARE GONNA TRY IT.
LET'S TEST IT.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- EVEN THOUGH I DIDN'T REALLY
GET THAT DRUNK LAST NIGHT,
YOU KNOW, I DEFINITELY
WANT TO TEST MY BREAST MILK,
BECAUSE EVEN ONE SIP, LIKE,
I FEEL WEIRD ABOUT IT,
SO I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
TO THROW OUT THE BAD STUFF.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO DO THIS AGAIN,
'CAUSE I'M HAVING SANGRIA TODAY.
I DON'T CARE.
IT'S LIKE A...
PEE STRIP.
- JUST DIP IT IN THE MIDDLE.
YEAH.
- FEEL LIKE
I'M BACK IN PATHOLOGY.
- A POSITIVE IS INDICATED
BY ANY COLOR CHANGE
IN THE TEST PATTERN,
TWO MINUTES.
- AND IT MEANS
THERE'S ALCOHOL IN IT?
- MM-HMM.
- IT'S BEEN TWO MINUTES.
- MM-HMM. YOU'RE GOOD.
- SO IT DIDN'T EVEN
GET AFFECTED.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON,
BECAUSE ALL THE MILK
THAT I JUST PUMPED,
IT'S SAYING IT'S NEGATIVE,
SO I DON'T KNOW
IF I DIDN'T DRINK ENOUGH
TO CONTAMINATE MY MILK,
BUT I'M JUST GONNA
THROW IT AWAY ANYWAY
BECAUSE I DON'T TRUST IT.
MAYBE I DIDN'T DRINK
ENOUGH.
- GUESS YOU'LL HAVE
TO TRY AGAIN.
[car horn honking]
- DOES EVERYBODY CALL YOUR MOM
BY HER FIRST NAME, OR--
- CINDY.
- YEAH, BUT EVERYBO--
ALL YOUR FAMILY
CALLS HER "CINDY"?
- YEAH.
I WOULDN'T SAY I'M NECESSARILY
EXCITED TO SEE MY MOM.
I'M HAPPY TO SEE HER,
IF THAT MAKES SENSE.
- NO, BUT YOU COULD
TRY TO EXPLAIN IT TO ME.
- IT'S NOT
LIKE CHRISTMAS,
SOMETHING
I'M JUMPING UP AND DOWN FOR.
IT'S JUST LIKE I'M HAPPY
I'M GONNA GO SEE HER.
- I WOULD LIKE
TO MEET HER ONCE, YOU KNOW,
EVEN IF IT'S ONLY ONCE.
I MEAN,
I UNDERSTAND
THE COMPLEXITY OF THE SITUATION.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
DID SHE EVER MEET,
LIKE, YOUR EX?
- NO. NOPE.
- SHE'S NEVER MET
ANYBODY YOU'VE DATED?
- NO.
I WOULD DEFINITELY SAY
THIS IS A PRETTY BIG STEP,
FOR ROGER TO MEET MY MOM,
ONLY BECAUSE MY MOM HASN'T,
YOU KNOW,
MET ANYONE NEW
IN THE PAST 15 YEARS
WHEN IT COMES TO BEING
IN MY LIFE.
- ADDS
A LITTLE PRESSURE.
- ARE YOU EXCITED?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- I FEEL LIKE WE'RE
CORRUPTING YOU ALL OVER AGAIN.
- DO I SMELL?
- A LITTLE BIT.
- I DON'T WANT JIONNI
TO SMELL SMOKE ON ME
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE
HE'S GONNA KILL ME.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
- [Bleep].
WHEW!
- THIS IS GONNA BE
A BIG DAY FOR ME,
SO IT HAS TO BE
JUST PERFECT, YOU KNOW?
- THIS IS GONNA RUN
ABOUT 600,000.
- WHOA.
- ♪ THE FUTURE'S ALL I
♪ WHO-O-OA
- HERE YOU GO, HONEY.
- ♪ WE'RE HOME FREE
- IT'S SANGRIA TIME.
- IT'S GONNA BE LIKE
YOUR FIRST HANGOVER.
- COOL.
[laughs]
I HAVEN'T EVEN TRIED
JANICE'S SANGRIA
BECAUSE I WAS PREGNANT
THE WHOLE TIME.
LET'S DO IT
LIKE WE USED TO.
SO I WANT TO SEE
WHAT EVERYONE DRINKS.
THIS IS GOOD.
IS THIS WINE?
SANGRIA WINE?
- I'M LIKE, "UGH."
- IT'S, LIKE, SYRUPY.
I'M LIKE, OH, [bleep],
I'M BUGGIN' OUT.
[laughter]
I HAVE TO GO POOP.
- I HAVE TO PEE.
[overlapping chatter]
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
WILL YOU GO OUT WITH ME?
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- TO HAVE A CIGARETTE.
- OH, YEAH.
- THAT'LL BE YOUR FIRST?
- YEAH.
- WHY DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU NEED ONE?
- 'CAUSE I WANT ONE.
- YOU'VE BEEN SMOKE-FREE
FOR NINE MONTHS.
- I JUST WANT TO TRY IT.
- I THINK
YOU'RE GONNA TRY IT,
AND YOU'RE NOT EVEN
GONNA LIKE IT.
- I JUST DON'T WANT JIONNI
TO BE MAD AT ME.
- WHY ARE YOU ARGUING
WITH YOURSELF?
- I DON'T KNOW, LET'S GO.
I'M DOING IT.
- OKAY.
- I DON'T KNOW WHY
I'M FEELING SO GUILTY RIGHT NOW.
I JUST FEEL LIKE,
YOU KNOW, SMOKING,
AND I'M A MOM--
IT'S JUST TRASHY.
AND ALSO, I DON'T WANT
JIONNI TO BE PISSED AT ME.
- I'M, LIKE, SHAKING.
I'M SCARED
WE'RE GONNA GET CAUGHT.
- I KNOW, I'M REALLY SCARED.
I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE IN HIGH SCHOOL AGAIN.
OH, A CHIPMUNK!
LET'S HIDE.
- WE COULD GO UNDERNEATH.
- YEAH.
- I FEEL LIKE WE'RE
CORRUPTING YOU ALL OVER AGAIN.
- I'M SCARED. YOU LIGHT IT.
- HOW DO I EVEN USE THIS THING?
UGH.
I HATE CIGARETTES.
- OH, GOD, I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE DOING DRUGS.
- QUICK, BEFORE ANYBODY SEES.
- I'M SCARED.
- YEAH.
- DO I SMELL?
- A LITTLE BIT.
- [Bleep].
I'M JUST GONNA TAKE A SHOWER,
RIGHT?
- DON'T EVEN
GO NEAR JIONNI.
- CAN I TELL JIONNI
YOU WANTED ONE?
- [laughs]
- SHOULD I BURY IT?
- LOOKS NATURAL.
- ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S IT.
- OKAY.
GLAD I COULD HELP.
- [sniffing]
OH, I SMELL.
PUT THE LIGHTER AWAY.
- [laughs]
- OKAY.
- YOU'RE BETTER OFF
JUST SHOWERING.
OH, IT'S COLD.
- SO?
- I JUST WANTED ONE.
KEEP HIM AWAY.
I DON'T WANT TO HOLD LORENZO
IF I SMELL LIKE SMOKE
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
HE'LL GET CANCER.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
- [Bleep].
WHEW!
- HEY, BABE.
- HI.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOIN'?
- HANGIN'.
- [laughs]
- WHY DO I FEEL SO GUILTY?
- ME TOO.
- [laughing]
I DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
- OH, GOD.
I FEEL LIKE
I KILLED SOMEONE AND I'M TRYING
NOT TO GET CAUGHT.
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOIN'?
- [laughs]
- WHAT?
- SHE'S JUST CUTE.
- I'M EXHAUSTED.
- SHUT UP.
- I FEEL LIKE WE JUST
GOT AWAY WITH MURDER.
- ♪ TALK TO ME
♪ LIKE I TALK TO YOU
♪
- WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
- THANK YOU.
- NO, THANK YOU. I ENJOYED IT.
YOU KNOW, HAVING JUST MET
JENNI'S MOTHER,
I REALIZE KINDA WHAT A MILESTONE
THAT IS IN OUR RELATIONSHIP
BECAUSE IT JUST KINDA
LETS ME KNOW
WHERE I FALL IN JENNI'S LIFE
THAT SHE TRUSTS ME ENOUGH
TO MEET HER MOM 'CAUSE, REALLY,
NOT MANY PEOPLE HAVE.
- I'M GLAD THAT I GOT
TO MEET YOUR MOM FINALLY.
- YEAH?
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF HER?
- I--LIKE I SAID, I FELT
LIKE I KINDA KNEW HER ALREADY
'CAUSE I'VE HEARD SO MANY
PHONE CALLS WITH YOU TWO, BUT--
- SHE WAS--
YOU WERE THE FIRST PERSON
SHE SAID SHE GOT NERVOUS
MEETING.
- THAT'S CRAZY.
I DON'T--WH--
- SHE'S LIKE, "I MET PEOPLE
OF YOUR--YOU KNOW,
FRIENDS AND STUFF BEFORE,
BUT I'M REALLY NERVOUS."
- WONDER WHY THAT IS.
- SHE WAS LIKE--
SAID SHE WAS, LIKE,
INTERNALLY-BLEEDING NERVOUS.
[laughs]
- SHE SAID THAT?
- YEAH, SO I WAS LIKE,
"SHUT UP!"
- OH. IT'S DEFINITELY
YOUR MOTHER THEN
'CAUSE IT SOUNDS
A LITTLE LIKE YOU.
- SHUT UP.
I'M RELIEVED RIGHT NOW
ROGER MET MY MOM.
FEEL LIKE THIS MOMENT
MAKES ME AND ROGER A FAMILY.
AND IT SHOWS OUR LOVE
FOR EACH OTHER.
IT SHOWS THE LOVE FOR HIM
AND THE DEDICATION
HE WANTS IN OUR RELATIONSHIP,
AND HE KNOWS HOW, YOU KNOW,
I WANT TO BE DEDICATED TO ROGER.
- I COULD TELL THAT SHE,
YOU KNOW, SHE WAS A LITTLE SHY,
BUT I TRIED TO LET HER
KIND OF WARM UP TO ME
AT HER OWN PACE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
SHE GAVE ME A HUG AT THE END.
SHE SEEMED VERY SINCERE
ABOUT IT, SO--
- SHE SAID SHE LIKED YOU
IN THE KITCHEN.
- THAT'S COOL.
[line ringing]
- HELLO.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
CHILLIN' WITH LORENZO.
- MM. I HAD A GOOD TIME
WITH HIM LAST NIGHT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ON MY WAY BACK
FROM MY MOM.
- HOW WAS IT?
- IT WAS GOOD. ROGER MET HER.
- WAS IT COOL?
- YEAH, IT WAS VERY COOL.
IT WAS EASY.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO EXPECT.
BUT, YEAH, IT WAS TOTALLY COOL.
IT WAS...
IT WAS, UH, SHE WAS
A REALLY NICE LADY.
- AW. YOU'RE DRIVING A LOT.
- YEAH, I'M COMING UP
TOMORROW TOO.
- MAYBE YOU GUYS CAN DO SOME
GIRL STUFF TOMORROW TOGETHER.
- YEAH. CAN YOU BRING ME
TO GET MY NAILS DONE?
'CAUSE I JUST CHIPPED
THREE OF THEM.
- I HAVE TO GET
MY NAILS DONE TOO.
- OH, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
SO ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
BYE, GUYS.
- BYE.
- ♪ CALL IT
WHATEVER YOU MAY ♪
♪ SOME KIND OF WITCHCRAFT
IS WHAT I'D SAY ♪
- OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT HIM!
- GET THEM OFF HIS EYES.
- LOOK AT HIM!
LOOK HOW COOL YOU LOOK.
- GET THEM OFF HIS EYES.
- YOU LOOK SO COOL!
OH, MY GOD, I LOVE THEM.
- THEY'RE NOT PRESCRIPTION,
RIGHT?
- NO. OH, MY GOD,
HE'S SO COOL.
- ALL RIGHT.
ENOUGH.
- OH.
DADDY DOESN'T LIKE IT.
I HAVE
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
- WHAT?
WHAT?
- [giggling]
I'M SCARED.
- AM I GONNA BE MAD?
- MAYBE.
- WHAT?
- [muttering] I HAD A CIGARETTE
TODAY.
- WHAT?
[mutters] I HAD
A CIGARETTE TODAY.
- WHAT?
- [laughs]
- YOU HAD A CIGARETTE.
- YEAH.
- WHEN?
- TODAY.
- WHAT?
- WHAT TIME
DID YOU HAVE THE CIGARETTE?
- AFTER DINNER.
- WITH WHO?
- STEPH.
- I DON'T CARE.
WHY--WHY'D YOU HIDE IT?
- 'CAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE MAD AT ME.
- I'M MORE MAD YOU HID IT.
I DON'T LIKE BEING LIED TO.
THAT'S MY BIGGEST PET PEEVE
IN LIFE.
ESPECIALLY MY FIANCEE,
MOTHER OF OUR CHILD,
DELIBERATELY LIED--
Y-YOU KNOW, IT REALLY HURTS.
IS THAT WHY YOU'VE BEEN
DUMPING THIS WHOLE TIME?
- YEAH. AND I HAD SANGRIA.
- WHAT ELSE
DID YOU NOT TELL ME?
- I THOUGHT YOU KNEW
I WAS DRINKING SANGRIA.
- SO WHY ARE YOU HOLDING HIM?
- JIONNI, I'M NOT DRUNK.
- DID YOU TELL STEPH
NOT TO TELL ME?
- YEAH. BUT I WAS GONNA
TELL YOU ANYWAY.
I'M SERIOUS, IN THE SHOWER,
I'M LIKE, "I'M GONNA TELL HIM."
- SO YOU SAID TO STEPH,
"I'M HAVING A CIGARETTE.
DON'T TELL JIONNI,
AND I'M NOT GONNA TELL HIM"?
- YEAH. BUT THEN
I CHANGED MY MIND.
- WHAT KIND OF FIANCEE
ARE YOU?
- I KNOW, THAT'S WHY
I CHANGED MY MIND.
I FELT GUILTY NOT TELLING YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
- JIONNI, I TOLD YOU.
- OKAY.
- I FEEL LIKE [bleep]
BECAUSE BEING JIONNI'S FIANCEE,
I SHOULDN'T BE GOING
BEHIND HIS BACK LIKE THAT,
SO I DEFINITELY [bleep] UP,
AND, YOU KNOW,
I FEEL LIKE AN ASS[bleep].
MOMMY WAS WRONG,
AND SHE TOLD DADDY.
- AND DADDY WAS RIGHT.
SAY IT.
- ONE MORE TIME.
- MOMMY WAS WRONG,
AND DADDY WAS RIGHT.
- I JUST FIGURED WE'D, UH,
MAYBE SKIP THE GYM,
GO TO DINNER.
- WHERE?
- UH, A NEW SPOT.
- DON'T BE WEIRD.
- [laughs]
- WHAT THE [bleep] IS GOING ON?
IT'S DEFINITELY A LITTLE ODD
FOR ROGER RIGHT NOW
'CAUSE HE NEVER SKIPS
THE GYM.
- IT'S ROMANTIC.
YOU KNOW HOW ROMANTIC I GET.
- I HAVE AN IDEA FOR TOMORROW.
- WHAT?
- I REALLY WANT A LADY
TO COME OVER
AND DO PICTURES OF LORENZO.
YOU KNOW HOW, LIKE, JENELLE
DID PICTURES OF MIKEY?
- LIKE FAMILY PORTRAIT-TYPE
STUFF?
- YEAH, BUT, LIKE, CUTE ONES,
LIKE...
IN A SHOE OR IN A BASKET.
- OKAY.
- I WANT A LADY
TO COME OVER AND DO THAT.
- ALL RIGHT, DEFINITELY.
- I FOUND SOME GIRL.
CAN I SHOW YOU?
- YEAH.
- I WANNA GET LORENZO,
LIKE, IN CUTE PICTURES,
SO WE'LL ALWAYS REMEMBER HIM
AS THIS LITTLE PEANUT.
JUST, LIKE, A COUPLE SHOTS
LIKE THAT.
SEE?
HOW CUTE IS THAT?
- THAT'S KINDA WEIRD.
- LIKE, AND NAKED.
- NAKED?
- [laughing]
- I DON'T WANT HIM NAKED.
THAT'S CUTE.
- HOW CUTE IS THAT?
LIKE, IN A LITTLE BASKET.
- YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
BUT I DON'T LIKE
SOME OF THOSE NAKED ONES.
- OKAY, THEN WE WON'T DO
THE NAKED ONES.
- COULD DO, LIKE,
A FAMILY PHOTO,
SEND IT OUT DURING CHRISTMAS.
- YEAH.
MM-HMM.
- YOU HAVE HER NUMBER?
- YEAH.
- WHAT'S HER NAME?
- LAUREN.
- LAUREN WITH AN "L"?
- NO, A "K."
[line ringing]
- HELLO, THIS IS LIFE VIA LENS.
LAUREN SPEAKING.
- SEE?
- HI, LAUREN?
- YES.
- WE WERE LOOKING UP YOUR SITE,
AND WE WERE VERY INTERESTED
IN SOME PICTURES
FOR OUR LITTLE SON.
- OH, CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- WE WANT PICTURES
OF THE BABY.
LIKE, YOU HAVE CUTE THINGS
AND, LIKE, PROPS AND STUFF,
AND WE WANT PICTURES
WITH THE BABY ALSO.
- I'M A NATURAL LIGHT
PHOTOGRAPHER,
MEANING LARGE WINDOWS,
THINGS LIKE THAT.
- SHE DOES NATURAL SUNLIGHT.
LAUREN, I LIVE IN A BASEMENT.
NO NATURAL LIGHT
COMING IN THERE.
- CAN YOU COME TOMORROW?
- TOMORROW...
WE CAN MAKE IT WORK.
THANK YOU, NICOLE.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
[pop music]
- ♪ I SEE IT
- HEY, JENNI.
- HI, BOOGER.
- HOW'S THE LITTLE MAN?
- HE'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, I'M LEAVING.
I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU TOO.
IT'S JUST ME AND YOU,
BUDDY.
- HOW WAS YESTERDAY?
- RELATIVELY EASY.
- I WANNA MEET YOUR MOM.
- SHE'S SO QUIET.
WE'RE NOTHING ALIKE.
- NOTHING LIKE YOU?
SO SHE'S, LIKE, PROBABLY
REALLY SWEET AND LOVING.
[laughs]
- THANKS.
[beep]
- [gasps]
WHAT THE [bleep] WAS THAT?
- SORRY?
[beep]
- I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING!
- I THINK YOU HIT THE BUTTON
BY ACCIDENT.
- DID I? SHE SCARED ME.
- YEAH.
IT'S ON YOUR STEERING WHEEL.
- WHAT A PSYCHO.
[dog barking]
- ♪ I BELIEVE
♪ IN DESTINY
♪ A FALLING FEELING
♪ WHEN I STAND NEXT TO YOU
- HEY! HOW ARE YOU?
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU? COME IN.
- NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
- SO THIS MORNING
WHILE JENNI IS AWAY,
LAYNA
FROM ALAN FRIEDMAN DESIGNS
IS COMING OVER TO SHOW ME
SOME ENGAGEMENT RINGS.
- ARE YOU EXCITED?
- I AM VERY EXCITED.
I'M VERY EXCITED.
- THIS IS A BIG, LIFE-CHANGING,
EXCITING MOMENT.
- YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
A BIG THING FOR ME--
FOR US, SO I'M EXCITED.
- HAVE YOU GOT ANY IDEAS?
I KNOW WE TALKED
A LITTLE ON THE PHONE.
- I DO. JENNI IS JUST A HUGE FAN
OF PINK DIAMONDS, SO--
- SHE LOVES PINK.
- LOVES PINK.
JENNI WANTS
A VERY UNIQUE RING.
DEFINITELY HAS TO HAVE
PINK DIAMONDS IN IT.
SO I'M GONNA REALLY LEAVE IT
UP TO LAYNA
TO COME UP
WITH THE FINAL DESIGN.
THIS MIGHT BE A LITTLE BIG.
- NO GIRL EVER RETURNS
A STONE...
- RIGHT, RIGHT.
- BECAUSE IT'S TOO BIG.
- TOO BIG, RIGHT?
THIS IS GONNA BE
A BIG DAY FOR ME, SO...
IT HAS TO BE
JUST PERFECT, YOU KNOW?
- I KNOW ON THE PHONE WE TALKED
A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT A THREE TO FOUR...
- Y-YEAH.
- CARAT.
- SURE. FOR THE CENTER STONE.
- YEAH.
WHAT CUT?
- DO YOU HAVE A PREFERENCE?
- YOU KNOW, CUSHION
IS THE HOTTEST STONE NOW.
- OKAY.
- IT'S SO GORGEOUS.
- CUSHION CUT--
WHAT IS THAT?
AM I BUYING PILLOWS
FOR THE COUCH OR WHAT?
CAN YOU SHOW ME?
- THIS ONE--
WELL, THIS IS A PRINCESS.
- LIKE--OKAY.
- AND THEN OF COURSE,
WE HAVE THE ROUNDS.
THIS IS THE YELLOW DIAMONDS
AND RADIANTS.
THIS IS A MARQUISE.
- MARQUISE CUT.
LAYNA'S, YOU KNOW,
THROWING OUT A LOT OF TERMS--
CUSHION CUT, CLARITY, FIRE.
- I THINK I WOULD GO
WITH THE CLUSTERS.
WE COULD DO SOMETHING
JUST WITH THE SINGLE BAND.
- RIGHT.
- WE WANNA BALANCE IT.
WE PROBABLY WANNA PUT ROUND,
BRILLIANT CUT WHITES AROUND IT.
- OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I GUESS MAYBE
SHE THINKS THAT I KNOW
WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT,
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU KNOW, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
I'M JUST A DUDE.
- NOW, THIS IS A PRINCESS.
YEAH.
- THAT IS AMAZING.
- THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL,
BEAUTIFUL PINK.
- NOW, HOW MUCH IS THIS?
- THIS IS GONNA RUN
ABOUT 600,000.
- WHOA!
[both laughing]
- HI, I'M LAUREN
FROM LIFE VIA LENS.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- THE PHOTOGRAPHER'S
COMING OVER TODAY
TO TAKE PICTURES OF LORENZO.
- YOU COULD JUST MOVE THIS...
- OKAY.
- MOVE THAT,
AND CLEAR THAT OUT.
- WE'RE PAYING YOU
TO TAKE PICTURES FOR US,
AND I'M GONNA DO THE LABOR?
- RROWW!
- THIS IS GONNA RUN ABOUT...
600,000.
- WHOA!
- OOH!
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE THINKS
I DO FOR A LIVING,
BUT JENNI WANTS A RING
THAT I THINK ONLY PROBABLY
BILL GATES COULD AFFORD.
CLEARLY, THAT'S OUT OF MY, UH,
BALLPARK FOR A CENTER STONE.
- WOULD YOU CONSIDER
A FIVE-CARAT?
- SURE, SURE, I MEAN...
- OKAY.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- I THINK IF YOU GO
WITH A WHITE CENTER...
- RIGHT.
- AND WE COULD MAYBE PUT
CLUSTERS OF PINK...
- THAT'S WHAT I WAS THINKING.
- ON EITHER SIDE.
- EXACTLY.
- THEN SHE'LL GET HER PINK.
AND IT'S STILL A BEAUTIFUL RING.
- EXACTLY.
WELL, I KNOW THAT SHE LOVES
THE PINK DIAMOND,
BUT I KNOW SHE DOES WANT
THE CENTER STONE
TO BE, YOU KNOW,
A CLEAR CUT DIAMOND.
IT ACTUALLY HELPS ME OUT
TOO BECAUSE...
- RIGHT, I MEAN, IT'LL SAVE YOU
$1/2 MILLION.
- I'LL HAVE TO SEE IF I HAVE
SOME COUPONS AROUND...
[both laughing]
- DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TAKE YOUR FIRSTBORN.
- YOU MIGHT TAKE
THE FIRST TWO, ACTUALLY,
IF WE GO
INTO SEVEN-CARAT RANGE.
WE'VE COME UP
WITH A GREAT DESIGN,
AND I JUST HOPE
THAT IT'S DONE IN TIME
BECAUSE I'M ALREADY PLANNING
ON POPPING THE QUESTION.
OKAY.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- LAYNA, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
AND I'LL SEE YOU NEXT WEEK.
- I'M GONNA HEAD BACK.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH, LAYNA.
- BYE.
TAKE CARE.
- THANK YOU.
- [belch]
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- HA HA!
- DRIVING A MINIVAN.
- AW, LOOK AT THE LITTLE BABY.
- AW. I LOOK AT KIDS
SO DIFFERENT NOW.
- I WAS GONNA SAY--
THIS, A YEAR AGO,
AND, LIKE, TWO YEARS AGO
IN SEASIDE--
YOU'D BE LIKE, "EW, JENNI,
WHY ARE YOU LOOKING?"
[laughing]
- NOW I'M LIKE...OHH.
I USED TO NOT LIKE BABIES
JUST BECAUSE THEY WERE LOUD
AND THEY WOULD NEVER
STOP CRYING.
I'D BE LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,"
LIKE, SHUT YOUR KID UP.
BUT NOW I LOVE BABIES.
- I DON'T KNOW, I JUST WANT
A REALLY CHUBBY BABY
WHEN I HAVE A BABY.
- YOU PROBABLY WILL
'CAUSE YOU WERE CHUBBY.
- BUT LORENZO, HE'S SO TINY
AND SKINNY, I'M LIKE...
- THAT'S 'CAUSE WE'RE LIKE
[bleep].
- [laughing]
- HE'S GONNA BE TINY.
POOR THING.
- CAN'T WAIT FOR NEXT YEAR
TO START MAYBE TRYING.
THEN I'LL PROBABLY HAVE
BABY FEVER.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M, LIKE, SCARED.
- I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA
GET PREGNANT
AT THE SAME TIME.
- FOR THE SECOND ONE.
YOU'LL PROBABLY WANT ONE
IN A YEAR.
'CAUSE HE'LL BE A YEAR OLD,
SO BY THE TIME YOU'RE DONE
BEING PREGNANT, HE'LL BE TWO.
- BUT I WANNA, LIKE, HAVE SEX
THE SAME NIGHT,
SO WE CAN HAVE OUR DUE DATES,
LIKE, CLOSE TO EACH OTHER.
- OKAY, BUT WE'D HAVE
TO OVULATE THE SAME DAY.
- WE KIND OF HAVE OUR PERIODS
THE SAME TIME.
- MM-HMM.
- JUST HAVE TO GET
BACK ON TRACK.
I WOULD LOVE IF JENNI
HAD A BOY AND I HAD A GIRL
BECAUSE THEN THEY CAN DATE
AND GET MARRIED,
AND THEN THEY CAN MAKE
A SNOOKI-JWOWW BABY.
I SMELL A DIAPER.
OH. IT'S THIS.
- THAT SMELLS LIKE A DIAPER?
REALLY?
[both chuckling]
[upbeat pop music]
♪
- YO, BOY.
- WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
WHAT ARE YOU RINGING
MY BELL FOR?
- JUST CHILLIN'.
- YOU KNOW
YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOME.
- THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
- MY BUDDY SEAN COMES OVER,
AND I WANT HIM TO BE
THE FIRST ONE OF MY FRIENDS
TO KNOW THAT, YOU KNOW,
I'M GONNA PROPOSE TO JENNI.
SO, UM, I GOTTA
PICK YOUR BRAIN A LITTLE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- IF ANYBODY KNOWS--
YOU KNOW JENNI AND I
AS WELL AS ANYBODY.
I BEEN GETTING, YOU KNOW,
PRETTY SERIOUS.
- YEAH.
- I REALLY WANNA ASK HER
TO MARRY ME.
- SWEET.
- I WANNA DO IT
IN MY OWN WAY,
BE ORIGINAL ABOUT IT,
BUT I NEED A LITTLE HELP
WITH THAT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- SEE WHAT I MEAN?
YOU KNOW,
I'M ASKING YOU, OBVIOUSLY,
'CAUSE YOU'VE DONE THIS.
- WHAT DO YOU GOT IN MIND?
- I THOUGHT SKYDIVING.
- THAT'S COOL.
THAT'S COOL.
- I'M NOT THE TYPE OF GUY
THAT'S GONNA GET DOWN
ON ONE KNEE IN A RESTAURANT
AND PROPOSE--
IT'S TOO CLICHE FOR ME.
I WANT IT TO BE THAT FAIRY-TALE
KIND OF PROPOSAL FOR HER.
YOU KNOW, EVERY GIRL'S ENTITLED
TO A DAY LIKE THAT,
AND JENNI ESPECIALLY.
- NICE.
THAT'S GONNA BE FUN.
- YOU KNOW, THE NEXT BIG STEP
IS, OF COURSE, THE RING.
- MM-HMM.
- AND, UM, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN ADVISE ME HERE
A LITTLE TOO
'CAUSE I KNOW YOU BOUGHT LAURA
A BEAUTIFUL RING.
- OKAY.
- I'M NERVOUS.
YOU KNOW ME.
I NEVER GET NERVOUS
ABOUT ANYTHING.
- I WAS A LITTLE NERVOUS TOO.
- I'M NOT NERVOUS
ABOUT THE HEIGHTS THING.
I'M MORE NERVOUS ABOUT
THE ACTUAL PROPOSAL PART, BUT...
- I WAS A LITTLE NERVOUS.
- WERE YOU?
- YEAH.
- YOU WANT ME TO SHOW YOU...
- [Bleep], YEAH.
- SOME OF THESE RINGS
SHE'S BEEN LOOKING AT?
- HELL, YEAH.
I WANNA SEE THIS.
- I'M GONNA HAVE TO REFINANCE
MY HOUSE FOR THIS RING, I THINK.
I KEEP HAVING TO DELETE
MY HISTORY UP HERE,
SO REMIND ME TO DO THAT.
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU SHAKING AT ALL OR--
- I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS, BUDDY.
I'M NOT LYING.
- A LITTLE NERVOUS?
- IT'LL BE
IN THIS GENERAL IDEA.
IT'S NOT GONNA BE
A ROUND STONE.
- OKAY.
- UM...YOU KNOW, IT'LL HAVE
A CUSTOM BAND WITH IT,
A CUSTOM SETTING.
- OKAY.
- I THINK YOU NEED TO BE,
YOU KNOW, A PRETTY SECURE MAN,
PRETTY SECURE WITH YOUR
MASCULINITY, WHEN YOU'RE TALKING
TO YOUR BUDDY ABOUT PRINCESS CUT
RINGS AND PINK DIAMONDS.
AND--YOU GOTTA BE PRETTY SECURE
WITH YOURSELF.
I DON'T THINK
SHE'S GONNA HAVE ANY IDEA,
BUT I THINK I WANNA MESS
WITH HER A LITTLE BIT TOO.
I DON'T WANT TO BE MEAN-SPIRITED
ABOUT IT,
BUT I DEFINITELY WANT--
- GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
- MAYBE GET HER HOPES UP
A LITTLE BIT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- 'CAUSE THIS
IS GONNA HAPPEN SOON.
BUT IT'LL THROW HER OFF,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
SHE'LL HAVE NO IDEA
THAT I'M ACTUALLY
GONNA DO IT, DO IT FOR REAL.
- MM-HMM.
- I WANT TO DO, LIKE,
A REALLY NICE
KIND OF FAKE-OUT
DINNER DATE NIGHT
WHERE SHE'S GONNA THINK
IT'S THE NIGHT
I'M POPPING THE QUESTION.
JUST ME BEING ME...
- YEAH.
- I HAVE
TO MESS WITH HER A LITTLE BIT.
- WITHOUT A DOUBT.
- YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- THAT'LL BE FUNNY.
- I'M GONNA COMPLETELY
PSYCH HER OUT,
AND SHE'S GONNA THINK,
"OH, MY GOD,
"THIS IS THE NIGHT
HE'S GONNA DO IT.
"HE'S GONNA ACTUALLY
POP THE QUESTION
AND ASK ME TO MARRY HIM
TONIGHT."
ALL RIGHT, BROTHER.
- ALL RIGHT.
- APPRECIATE IT.
- YEAH.
I'LL TALK TO YOU TOMORROW.
- DEFINITELY.
- LATER.
- WHEW!
GOD, I WAS NERVOUS
JUST DOING THAT.
- WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- IT MIGHT BE ALL THEY HAD.
- I'M, LIKE, STANDING HERE
DUMBFOUNDED, SHAKING.
OH, MY GOD, THIS IS IT.
LIKE...I'M GONNA BE
PROPOSED TO.
MY HEART'S IN MY THROAT
RIGHT NOW.
- THERE YOU ARE.
- HI.
- THANK YOU FOR DOING
THE DISHES.
- NO PROBLEM.
I DIDN'T REALLY DO 'EM.
I JUST PUT THEM
IN THE DISHWASHER.
HOW'S NICOLE?
HOW'S THE BABY?
- GOOD.
- EVERYTHING GOOD UP THERE?
- MM-HMM. NICOLE KEEPS ASKING
IF I HAVE BABY FEVER.
- [clicks tongue]
AND YOUR ANSWER...
- NO, NOT YET.
- NOT YET?
- I WANNA PLAN IT.
- YOU'RE A PLANNER?
- YES.
- I WOULD LIKE TO PLAN IT TOO.
I THINK THAT NO MATTER
HOW MUCH YOU PLAN FOR ANYTHING,
YOU'RE NEVER FULLY PREPARED--
- NOBODY'S EVER READY,
BUT AT LEAST I'D LIKE TO GET
A FEW MORE THINGS
UNDERNEATH MY--
- YOUR BUCKET LIST?
MY GOD, I THOUGHT THAT
WOULD BE LOST FOR MONTHS.
UM, YEAH, I'VE GOT SOME THINGS
I WANNA DO TOO
ON A BUCKET LIST, SO...
- LIKE WHAT?
- I WANNA DO ADVENTUROUS STUFF.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- YOU CAN BE THE ADVENTUROUS--
NO, I WON'T ALLOW YOU
TO BE THE ADVENTUROUS ONE
ONCE WE HAVE KIDS.
I DON'T NEED YOU JUMPING
OUT OF A [bleep] PLANE
AND THEN DYING ON ME,
AND I GET TO BE A SINGLE MOM.
THAT WOULD SUCK.
I'M GONNA PUT THE KIBOSH
ON THAT REAL QUICK.
- I ACTUALLY WANTED TO DO THAT
'CAUSE I SAW THAT
ON A COMMERCIAL
THE OTHER DAY AT THE GYM.
- I KNOW.
- WOULD YOU DO IT?
- NO. I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
AT THE BOTTOM.
- I WANNA START WARMING JENNI UP
TO THIS IDEA
OF GOING SKYDIVING
JUST TO SEE
WHAT SHE SAYS ABOUT IT,
TO SEE IF I CAN EVEN
MAKE THIS PROPOSAL
HAPPEN THERE.
BUT I KNOW
HOW TO PLAY JENNI,
SO I STILL FEEL CONFIDENT THAT
I CAN GET HER ON THAT PLANE.
I'M GONNA WRITE
MY BUCKET LIST DOWN.
YOU WRITE
YOUR BUCKET LIST DOWN.
WE'LL COME
TO SOME HAPPY MEETING.
- OKAY.
IS IT BEFORE MARRIAGE
BUCKET LIST,
OR IS IT JUST BEFORE KIDS?
- BEFORE KIDS.
MAYBE BEFORE MARRIAGE.
PROBABLY BEFORE MARRIAGE TOO.
I GOTTA KNOW--
GOTTA KNOW WHAT I'M BUYING.
GOTTA KNOW WHAT KIND
OF GIRL I'M BUYING.
- DON'T DRINK THE MILK
BEFORE WHATEVER?
SOMETHING ABOUT A COW
AND MILK?
- WHY BUY THE COW WHEN YOU
GET THE MILK FOR FREE?
IS THAT
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
- THERE YOU GO!
I'M NOT A COW.
- NICE AND CLEAN.
[doorbell rings]
- [clears throat]
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
- HI!
JIONNI?
- YES.
- HI, I'M LAUREN
FROM LIFE VIA LENS.
I'M THE PHOTOGRAPHER.
- NICE TO MEET YOU. HI. JIONNI.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HI, I'M HELENE.
- THIS IS HELENE
FROM HANDCRAFTERS.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- THE PHOTOGRAPHER'S
COMING OVER TODAY
TO TAKE PICTURES OF LORENZO,
AND I'M REALLY EXCITED
BECAUSE I KNOW HE'S GONNA LOOK
SO CUTE IN THESE PICTURES.
HELLO.
- HI!
- OH, MY GOODNESS!
LOOK AT THE BABY!
- HI.
- I'M LAUREN.
- HI. NICOLE.
- I'M THE PHOTOGRAPHER.
both: NICE TO MEET YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS!
- THIS IS LORENZO.
SAY HI.
- AW!
I TOLD JIONNI
I'M JUST GONNA LOOK AROUND
AND SEE WHERE THE BEST PLACE
TO SET UP IS.
- OKAY. COOL.
- OKAY?
DO YOU WANNA SHOW ME UPSTAIRS?
- YEAH.
WELL, THIS IS PROBABLY
THE BRIGHTEST ROOM WE CAN MAKE--
SO YOU COULD USE THIS ROOM
AND THE...
- THIS IS PERFECT.
- PIANO ROOM IF YOU WANT.
- PERFECT.
- DO YOU MIND IF WE SHOOT
IN THIS NURSERY?
- NO.
- OKAY.
SO I THINK THIS IS BETTER.
YOU COULD JUST MOVE THIS...
- OKAY.
- MOVE THAT...
AND JUST THE ANIMALS,
CLEAR THAT OUT.
AND EVEN IF YOU DON'T MIND
JUST SHOVING THE CARPET OVER
A LITTLE?
- WE'RE PAYING YOU
TO TAKE PICTURES FOR US.
- DO YOU MIND?
YOU LOOK LIKE A STRONG GUY.
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- WE'RE GONNA START
LOADING IT IN.
- AND I'M GONNA DO
THE LABOR?
WHAT IS THIS?
- ONE MORE TRIP.
- DO YOU WANNA MOVE THIS OUT?
'CAUSE THEN I CAN SLIDE
MY SUITCASE THERE.
- UH-HUH.
- YOU CAN JUST LEAVE THOSE
IN THE HALLWAY.
OR, YEAH, RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S FINE.
- I DON'T CALL A LANDSCAPER
AND ME MOW THE LAWN, DO I?
NO. YOU COME HERE,
YOU'RE DOING A JOB.
DO YOUR JOB!
- RROWW!
ISN'T HE THE CUTEST BABY?
- HE'S SO PERFECT.
- THE HAIR IS TO DIE FOR.
- LIKE, THE CUTEST
YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
- OF COURSE!
- BUT YOU SAY THAT TO EVERYONE.
- NO, I DON'T.
LOOK, HE HAS
A PERFECT ROUND HEAD.
DON'T CRY, LORENZO.
- HE'LL BE OKAY.
- SHH.
- HI, POOP.
- AW!
- SMOOSH!
THAT'S OKAY, LOVEY.
LET'S GET COMFORTABLE.
YOU HAVE TO JUST FIND
YOUR SOUL.
SHH.
[Lorenzo cooing]
UH-HUH. UH-HUH.
[camera lens clicking]
- LIKE, THAT LITTLE DIMPLE
IN HIS ELBOW...
HE'S THE BEST!
- REALLY?
- OH, HE'S THE BEST.
LOOK AT HIM.
- HE'S BEING GOOD!
- ISN'T THAT TOO CUTE?
- HE TAKES AFTER MOMMY.
COULD YOU GET SOME
WITH US THREE?
- OH, YEAH,
WE'RE GONNA DO THAT.
- 'CAUSE WE WANNA DO
A CHRISTMAS CARD.
- OH, NO, DEFINITELY.
- OH, MY GOD,
HE'S SO CUTE.
I'M SO EXCITED.
- ALL RIGHT.
[laughter]
- OH, HE'S GOOD.
- GOOD JOB, LORENZO.
I WANNA DO THE PASTA POT.
- OH!
- RIGHT THERE.
- HE'S SUCH A GOOD BOY.
LORENZO IS A NATURAL.
HE'S COOPERATING,
AND HE'S LIKE
MY LITTLE MODEL.
[Lorenzo crying]
- I KNOW, IT'S OKAY.
[crying]
OH! SHH.
SHH.
[crying fades]
[whispering]
SHH, SEE? IT'S OKAY.
- OKAY, LORENZO,
IT'S OKAY.
[loudly]
SHH!
[Lorenzo fussing]
- SHH, SHH, SHH.
[Lorenzo crying]
SHH.
- SHH!
ENOUGH OF THE SHUSHING.
I'M GETTING ALL AGGRAVATED.
[Lorenzo crying]
- SHH, SHH, SHH.
SHH.
- SHH!
WHAT IF I DID THAT TO YOU?
WOULD YOU LIKE IT, LAUREN?
- I'M GONNA DO A COUPLE
WITH THE BABY.
DO YOU HAVE
A SPECIAL SIDE OR...
- THIS IS MY BAD SIDE.
- SO THEN JUST SWITCH.
- I WANNA MAKE SURE
I GET MY GOOD SIDE.
FOR SOME REASON, I POSE
REALLY GOOD ON THIS SIDE LIKE...
BUT THEN THIS SIDE,
IT'S LIKE [bleep],
LIKE, I CAN'T--IT JUST--
IT DOESN'T WORK.
SO I HAVE TO POSE
ON THIS SIDE.
- YOU'RE GOING TO BRING HIM
FORWARD JUST A LITTLE.
YEAH, SO THAT HE'S NOT
SO SUNKEN BETWEEN YOU.
AND YOU'RE GONNA--
PERFECT.
LOOK AT HIS LITTLE MOUTH
OPEN TOO.
AND NOW YOU'RE BOTH...
AWESOME.
NO, I THINK YOU SMILED THOUGH
TOO IN A COUPLE.
- YEAH, I LIKE IT.
- I THINK OVERALL
THE PHOTO SHOOT WENT GREAT,
A LITTLE BIT TOO LONG,
BUT MY FAVORITE PICTURE
WAS OF LORENZO IN THE PASTA BOWL
'CAUSE I THINK
IT'S SO CUTE.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY...
- AND IT STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
- HELLO. YOUR FAVORITE
WORKING MAN IS HERE.
MONKEY SLEEPING?
- ♪ HE KNOWS
THAT HE'S A MODERN MAN ♪
♪ BUT HE DOESN'T
REALLY UNDERSTAND ♪
- I'M BORED.
- WHAT YOU DOING,
POOP MONKEY?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
NOW THAT I HAVE EVERYTHING
AS FAR AS THE PROPOSAL GOES,
AS MAPPED OUT AS I THINK
I CAN POSSIBLY HAVE IT,
IT'S TIME TO [bleep]
WITH JENNI A LITTLE BIT.
I WANNA PUT THOUGHTS
IN HER HEAD
WHERE SHE'S GONNA BE LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD, IS THIS IT?
"IS TONIGHT THE NIGHT?
IS HE GONNA PROPOSE TO ME
TONIGHT?"
I FIGURED WE'D, UH,
MAYBE SKIP THE GYM...
GO TO DINNER.
- WHERE?
- UH, A NEW SPOT.
- DON'T BE WEIRD.
- [laughs]
NO, A PLACE IN BRICKTOWN
THAT YOU HAVEN'T BEEN TO BEFORE.
I'VE ONLY BEEN THERE ONCE.
- WHAT'S IT CALLED?
- IT'S CALLED
THE PILOT HOUSE.
- OKAY.
- YOU TURNING ME DOWN?
YOU GOT THAT LOOK ON YOUR FACE
LIKE YOU'RE TURNING ME DOWN.
- NO, JUST--
YOU DON'T SKIP THE GYM.
WHAT THE [bleep]
IS GOING ON?
IT'S DEFINITELY A LITTLE ODD
FOR ROGER RIGHT NOW
'CAUSE HE NEVER SKIPS
THE GYM.
- IS THAT COOL?
- MM-HMM.
IS IT A NICE SPOT
OR CASUAL?
- UH, IT'S A NICE SPOT,
NICE PLACE.
WE'LL DRESS UP.
- OH,
IT'S A DRESS UP NIGHT TOO?
- CAN'T HAVE A DATE NIGHT
WITH MY BABE?
WHAT'S UP?
TODAY'S A SPECIAL DAY.
[laughs]
- SHUT UP.
I'M READY TO GET READY.
- LET'S GET READY
TO GET READY.
I CAN READ HER BODY LANGUAGE
AND TELL THAT, YOU KNOW,
SHE'S THINKING,
"TONIGHT COULD BE
A BIG NIGHT FOR ME."
[line ringing]
- HEY, BOO.
- HEY.
- HOW WAS THE PHOTO SHOOT?
- GOOD. UM...
HE LOOKED REALLY,
REALLY CUTE.
- AW. ME AND ROGER
ARE ABOUT TO GO TO DINNER.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- THE PILOT SOMETHING?
- IS IT A FANCY RESTAURANT?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF IT,
SO I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S FREAKING ME OUT
WITH THIS DINNER.
IT'S A TUESDAY.
I WAS THINKING MUSCLE MAKER
OR TEA KETTLE.
- IS HE PROPOSING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, WE'RE SKIPPING THE GYM,
WHICH, YOU KNOW,
I'M NOT USED TO.
- WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU WALKED IN,
IT WAS FIRST CLASS
AND CANDLES AND, LIKE,
VERY CLASSY?
- I THINK
IT WOULD BE COOL!
- WELL, GOOD.
HAVE FUN AND GET DRUNK.
- I GUESS.
WE'RE TAKING A CAB.
- YEAH.
YOU'RE GETTING DRUNK.
- I WILL CALL YOU EITHER
LATER TONIGHT OR IN THE MORNING.
- ALL RIGHT, HAVE FUN.
- I WILL. LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU. BYE.
- BYE.
- PUT ON YOUR SUNDAY BEST, KID.
WE'RE GOING TO SEARS.
- YE-AH.
- IF I COULD READ
JENNI'S MIND RIGHT NOW,
I THINK HER MIND
WOULD BE SAYING,
"PLEASE LET THIS BE IT."
SO...IT JUST MAKES IT
THAT MUCH MORE ENJOYABLE.
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
AS ALWAYS.
I HAVE SEX WITH THIS GIRL
FROM TIME TO TIME.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU KNOW HER OR NOT,
BUT OCCASIONALLY.
OCCASIONALLY BEING
THE KEY WORD THERE.
READY?
- JUST STARTING TO GET HUNGRY.
I'M LOOKING
AT THIS PINK LIMO,
AND I LEGIT
ALMOST [bleep] MY PANTS.
- MAYBE THAT'S ALL THEY HAD
FOR A TAXI.
- WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- IT MIGHT BE ALL THEY HAD.
- WHY ARE WE GOING
IN A PINK THING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST ORDERED A TAXI.
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
LIKE, I CAN'T THINK.
I'M, LIKE, STANDING HERE
DUMBFOUNDED, SHAKING.
- THEY MIGHT NOT HAVE HAD
ANY LINCOLN TOWN CARS.
- [laughing]
WHY ARE WE GOING IN THAT?
- ROGER KNOWS MY FAVORITE
COLORS ARE PINK AND BLACK.
ROGER ALSO KNOWS THAT I WANT
A PINK DIAMOND RING.
OH, MY GOD, THIS IS IT,
LIKE...
I'M GONNA BE PROPOSED TO.
MY HEART'S IN MY THROAT
RIGHT NOW.
- THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING
TO DO SOMETHING NUTS TONIGHT.
- HOW SO?
- I JUST REFERENCED PINK LIMO
WITH PINK DIAMONDS.
- ALL RIGHT.
- OH, I'M LEAKING!
- CAN I SEE?
- AAH! HA HA!
- I DON'T LIKE HEIGHTS.
- I'M SURE YOU WON'T BE
THE FIRST PERSON
THAT [bleep] THEIR PANTS.
I MIGHT [bleep] MY PANTS,
BUT I'M STILL GONNA DO IT.
BASICALLY, IF [bleep] JENNI
DOESN'T JUMP OUT OF THIS PLANE,
I DON'T HAVE
A BACKUP PLAN.
IT'S REALLY
ALL OR NOTHING.
- STOP!
I DON'T WANT TO DO IT!