- [screams]
- GOT HIM. REEL HIM IN.
REEL HIM, BABE.
REEL HIM, REEL HIM.
- AGH! I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
THE FISH IS BITING ME!
- I THOUGHT SHE WAS GONNA THROW
THE FISHING ROD IN THE WATER.
BRING IT IN CLOSER.
OH!
- [screams]
- HE'S HOME!
- OH, HE'S SO CUTE.
- BASICALLY, EVERYTHING'S
JUST COMING NATURALLY.
IS THIS THE RIGHT DIAPER?
- IT'S ON BACKWARDS.
YOU--
- [laughing]
- UH-OH.
I'M STUCK.
- LOVE THE SMELL OF MUD
IN THE MORNING.
- NEW JERSEY AND MAINE
ARE LEGIT TWO DIFFERENT WORLDS.
- WHOA, THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
SEE HIM?
- EW, EW, SOMETHING
WAS SQUISHING RIGHT THERE.
WHAT IS THAT?
- [laughs]
- DID ROGER POP THE QUESTION?
- OH, DON'T EVEN GO THERE.
NICOLE KEEPS ASKING IF ROGER
HAS PROPOSED YET.
HE'S SITTING RIGHT HERE.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
*
* I DON'T CARE
- I GUESS WHAT I'M TRYING
TO SAY IS THINGS, UH,
THINGS HAVE BEEN GOING
REALLY WELL LATELY,
AND I THINK SHE'S DEFINITELY
THE GIRL FOR ME,
AND I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE IT
TO THAT NEXT STEP,
WHICH, OBVIOUSLY,
IS GETTING ENGAGED.
AND HOPEFULLY SHE'LL ACCEPT,
AND, YOU KNOW, THEN--
- WOW, THAT WOULD BE
EMBARRASSING, IF SHE SAID--
- YEAH, I WOULD BE
QUITE EMBARRASSED.
- [laughs]
I THINK SHE'LL SAY YES.
I DO.
I REALLY DO.
- DID SHE GET THE MAINE STAMP
OF APPROVAL?
- SHE'S BEEN--
SHE'S BEEN, UH,
APPROVED, YEAH.
SHE'S GOT THE APPROVAL.
- I CONSIDER MYSELF
TO MAKE
GOOD CHOICES IN MY LIFE.
AND, YOU KNOW,
IT MAKES ME FEEL GOOD
TO HAVE MY DAD ENDORSE
THAT WHOLE IDEA
AND THAT WHOLE CONCEPT
OF ME PROPOSING
TO JENNI, YOU KNOW?
LET'S CATCH A FISH THEN.
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
ENOUGH OF THAT SOB,
SOB STUFF, YEAH.
- AM I TEARING UP?
- YEAH.
- AM I WELLING UP AT ALL?
AM I--
[laughter]
[peaceful music]
*
- HI.
- HEY, DEE.
- HEY, SWEETIE.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HI, DAD.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- THANKS FOR COMING.
- HOW YOU DOING, BUG?
- GOOD. OH!
- MWAH.
- HOW YOU FEELING?
- GOOD.
- I BROUGHT--I GOT YOU--
- OH, MY GOD!
- AND--YES.
I KNEW YOU WERE GONNA
LOVE THAT.
- [gasps]
I FORGOT I CAN EAT SLIM JIMS!
- SEE, DON'T I KNOW YOU
TOO WELL?
- YEAH, YOU KNOW ME.
- AND I GOT YOU A PUPPET.
- OH, THAT'S CUTE.
- SO YOU CAN PLAY, LIKE,
PEEKABOO AND STUFF.
- THANKS, DEE.
DON'T LOOK.
I'M GONNA GET--
- DON'T LOOK AT WHAT?
- I'M GONNA GET HIM.
- OKAY.
OH, I CAN'T WAIT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- NOTHING.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- GOOD. IT'S AWESOME.
- YEAH?
- YEAH.
- YOU LOVE IT?
- AUNTIE MEATBALL'S HERE.
- I'M EXCITED.
OH!
- HERE HE IS.
- HE'S SO LITTLE!
- I KNOW.
- [gasps]
OH, MY GOD.
- OH, MAKE A CUTE FACE,
NOT AN UGLY ONE.
- OH, HE'S SO SMALL.
HE'S SUCH A PEANUT.
JUST TO THINK, THIS WAS--
HE WAS IN YOUR BELLY
THE WHOLE TIME WE WERE
IN THE SHORE HOUSE.
[laughs]
HOW'S IT FEEL?
- IT'S AWESOME.
YOU'RE GONNA--YOU'RE GONNA LOVE
TO BE A MOM, I SWEAR.
- HE'S, LIKE,
THE PERFECT BABY.
- MM-HMM.
YOU DON'T WANT TO HOLD HIM?
- NO, I DO.
I WANT TO JUST SIT DOWN
WHEN I HOLD HIM.
- I'VE SEEN YOU WALK.
YOU FALL ALL THE TIME.
[clattering]
IF DEENA IS GONNA HOLD
MY SON,
THERE'S DEFINITELY
MEATBALL RULES.
YOU'RE NOT STANDING UP.
- [laughing]
- YES!
- HOLD MY BABY
WHILE SITTING DOWN.
- MM-HMM.
GOT HIM?
- YEAH.
HE'S SO LITTLE.
[giggles]
HE'S LIKE A LITTLE--
A LITTLE PEANUT.
I WANT ONE.
[laughs]
- OH, GOD.
- OH, BOY.
- * YOU GOT
A PRETTY LITTLE FACE *
* OH, IT KEEPS US
FROM AN EARLY GRAVE *
- WHAT YOU DOING, BABE?
- WE'RE GONNA COOK
SOME LOBBIES.
SOME "LOBISTOS".
EVER HEAR ABOUT JENNI'S LOBSTER?
SHE THOUGHT
SHE RESCUED IT
BY PUTTING IT IN FRESHWATER.
- [laughs]
OH!
- SO IT DIED.
- ZAP.
- [sarcastically]
WAH, WAH, WAH.
[water bubbling]
OH, YEAH,
WE'RE LOBSTER TIME.
- ALL RIGHT,
JENNI HAS TO PUT THE--
YOU'RE--YOU CAUGHT 'EM.
YOU GOTTA PUT 'EM IN.
[dog yipping]
- WOW, HE'S DEMANDING.
- IN THE HOT WATER.
OH, HE IS.
- OH, C--WHAT?
GET OUTTA HERE.
I AM NOT LISTENING
TO THEM SCREAM.
- [laughing]
- I KNOW LOBSTERS MAKE
A SCREAMING NOISE
WHEN THEY'RE BEING BOILED.
I HEARD IT IN MIAMI.
- OH, THERE YOU GO, BUDDY.
- SEE YA.
NOT LOOKING.
- OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT,
BROTHER.
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE SO AWFUL.
IT FREAKS ME OUT.
- THEY DON'T SCREAM.
- THEY [bleep] SCREAM.
- [chuckles]
- OOPS.
- WELL, I JUST PUT THEM
IN THERE,
AND NOT ONE OF 'EM
MADE A PEEP.
- THEY EEK.
EEK!
- NO, THEY DON'T MAKE
ANY NOISE WHATSOEVER.
- EEK.
- PFFT.
LOBSTERS DO NOT SCREAM
WHEN BOILED.
THEY DON'T HAVE
VOCAL CHORDS.
EVER SEEN A LOBSTER
ON AMERICAN IDOL?
NO.
I SHOULD CHECK THESE THINGS.
- I GOTTA GO FIX AN EYELASH.
IT'S BUGGING ME.
EW, YOU PUT THE SEAWEED
IN WITH THEM?
- YEAH.
PUT THE SEAWEED ON THE TOP
TO HOLD THE HEAT IN.
- RED LOBSTER DOESN'T COOK
THEM WITH SEAWEED.
- [chuckles]
- OH, MY GOD.
I'D SAY THOSE ARE DONE, NO?
WHEN I WAS IN LABOR,
I FARTED IN THE DOCTOR'S FACE.
- DID YOU POOP?
- NO, I DIDN'T POOP.
I THOUGHT I HAD TO.
THAT'S WHAT LABOR--
- DOESN'T THAT HAPPEN, THOUGH?
- THAT'S WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
IT FEELS LIKE YOU HAVE TO TAKE
A HUGE [bleep].
- HOW WERE YOU?
DID YOU FAINT?
- NO.
- [laughs]
- I SAW HER "PLUCENTA"
COME OUT.
- PLACENTA.
- WAIT A SECOND.
WHAT IS THE PLACENTA?
I THOUGHT THAT'S
THE LITTLE THING
THAT STICKS OUT
OF THEIR BELLY BUTTON.
- THAT'S THE UMBILICAL CORD.
- [laughs]
OH.
- PLACENTA IS WHAT
HE STAYS IN.
- THAT'S STILL ON HIM.
- RIGHT.
- PLACENTA IS DEEP INSIDE HER,
WHICH I WASN'T TOUCHING.
- DO YOU KNOW
SOME DADS EAT IT?
- EAT IT? NO, NO.
THEY--THEY EAT PLACENTA.
- OH.
- THEY--YEAH.
THEY PUT IT IN A MILKSHAKE.
- DID YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU, SICK?
I COULDN'T LOOK AT IT.
- OH.
- TASTE IT?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- YOU LOOK GOOD.
- I JUST CAN'T WAIT
TO GO TO THE GYM.
I HAVE TO WAIT
LIKE FIVE WEEKS, HE SAID.
- WHY, 'CAUSE YOU'RE
BREASTFEEDING?
- 'CAUSE IT'S STILL,
LIKE, RECOVERING.
AND I HAVE STITCHES
IN MY VAGINA.
- DO YOU FEEL NORMAL
DOWN THERE?
- I ACTUALLY LOOKED
IN THE MIRROR YESTERDAY,
LIKE, OPENED IT.
I BENT DOWN.
SHOULD'VE NEVER DONE THAT.
- WHY, WAS IT SCARY-LOOKING?
- I SAW THE STITCHES.
YEAH, IT WAS REALLY GROSS.
DON'T EVER LOOK TO SEE
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE AFTER.
- [laughs]
OKAY.
- YOU LOOKED AT IT?
- YEAH, I BENT OVER.
- OOF.
- I KNOW.
IT LOOKED LIKE THERE WAS,
LIKE, ANOTHER HOLE.
- LIKE WHERE THE PLACENTA WAS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST LOOKED LIKE
IT WAS TWO VAGINAS.
- I AIN'T LOOKING.
- I DON'T WANT YOU TO LOOK.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU MADE HIM.
- IT'S A COOL FEELING.
- COOL.
- YAY.
- [laughing]
MONKEY, EVEN--
EVEN CAMEL TOE--
- I DON'T [bleep] THINK
I GET CAMEL TOE.
YOU'RE A [bleep],
AND YOU JUST SAY I DO.
SHUT UP.
- YOU'RE THE QUEEN
OF CAMEL TOE.
- YOU DON'T WANT TO STAY
WITH YOUR MOMMY, RIGHT?
JUST ME AND YOU?
- YOU LOVE MOMMY, RIGHT?
- THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE GETTING JEALOUS
THAT I'M GIVING
MY NEWBORN SON ATTENTION,
MORE ATTENTION THAN YOU--
- NO, I LOVE THAT YOU'RE
GIVING HIM ATTENTION.
- THAT'S FUNNY TOO.
- BUT YOU IGNORE ME.
KEEP TALKING TO HIM
SINCE HE'S YOUR BEST FRIEND.
- BYE.
- RAVIOLI.
- OH, YOU'RE SO CUTE!
IS HE YOURS?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
HE LOOKS NOTHING LIKE ME.
- OH, HE'S SO--
- LET'S SHOW LORENZO
HIS NEW ROOM.
- I'LL HOLD HIM.
- NO, BABE, I WANT TO. STOP.
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
YOUR NEW ROOM.
DOES IT MATTER
IF HIS EYES ARE CLOSED?
HE'LL GET THE POINT.
- HE'D HEAR US.
OKAY, LORENZO.
THIS IS...
YOUR--
- ARMOIRE.
I'M ALLOWED TO SPEAK TOO.
- YOU'RE GONNA HANG STUFF
THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO FOLD,
AND, YOU KNOW, ALL YOUR--
- HE'S GONNA HANG IT?
- THIS IS WHERE
YOU'RE GONNA BE
TAKING ALL YOUR BATHS.
- YOU'RE GONNA BE
NICE AND CLEAN.
- SO YOU DON'T SMELL
LIKE YOUR MOMMY.
- YOU'RE SO ANNOYING.
- YOU WANT DADDY
TO HOLD YOU?
YOU WANT YOUR DAD
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL BETTER NOW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO STAY
WITH YOUR MOMMY, RIGHT?
JUST ME AND YOU?
- YOU LOVE MOMMY, RIGHT?
DADDY'S ANNOYING, RIGHT?
LET ME HAVE TIME
WITH LORENZO,
AND YOU CAN HAVE YOUR TIME.
KEEP TALKING TO HIM...
SINCE HE'S YOUR BEST FRIEND.
- THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE GETTING JEALOUS
THAT I'M GIVING
MY NEWBORN SON ATTENTION,
MORE ATTENTION THAN YOU--
- NO, I LOVE THAT
YOU'RE GIVING HIM ATTENTION.
- THAT'S FUNNY TOO.
- BUT YOU IGNORE ME.
AND THAT JUST BUGS ME OUT.
- NICOLE, THE TOUR'S OVER.
ALL RIGHT, LORENZO.
- NO.
- AND THAT'S THE TOUR
OF YOUR BASEMENT.
- I WANT TO SHOW HIM--
- NOW LET'S GO TO BED.
- STOP.
- IT'S TIME FOR BED NOW.
- JIONNI, STOP IT.
- WE'RE GOING TO BED.
- OKAY, BUT GET SOME OF ME.
- GET SOME OF ME
WITH HIM, PLEASE.
- WE'RE GOING TO BED.
- LET'S SWAP.
COME ON.
- MOMMY'S THIS ANNOYING
ALL THE TIME.
- COME ON.
- SHE'S ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
- I KNEW MAYBE WE'D START
BICKERING A LITTLE BIT,
BECAUSE WHEN PEOPLE
GET MARRIED,
THEY HAVE
THE GREATEST MARRIAGE,
LIKE, THE FIRST YEAR,
AND THEN THEY HAVE A KID.
THEN THEY WANT
TO GET DIVORCED.
HI, LORENZO.
- [sighs heavily]
- JIONNI, STOP IT.
- LET'S GO TO BED.
- YOU'RE SO RUDE.
STOP IT.
DADDY'S REALLY ANNOYING,
AND HE JUST RUINED
THIS WHOLE THING.
- NOW WE'RE TALKING.
EASY.
- YOU RUINED IT.
THANKS.
- [snickers]
NOT TO BE MEAN,
BUT I KINDA THINK IT'S FUNNY
'CAUSE, LIKE, SHE GETS SO MAD
OVER THE DUMBEST THINGS.
- OKAY, SO HE DOES IT
ON PURPOSE.
- IT'S NOT FIGHTING
FOR, LIKE, SERIOUS PROBLEMS.
- OKAY, BUT I REALLY GET
MY FEELINGS HURT.
- 'CAUSE YOU'RE A KOOK.
- THIS IS MY SIDE.
- OH, [bleep].
- I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO HUG YOU.
- SO GO ON THE OTHER SIDE.
- NO.
MOVE OVER.
- [groaning and laughing]
- [giggles]
I HOPE YOU SUFFOCATE.
- * I CAN FEEL IT
* I KNOW IT'S COMING ON
* I FEEL IT IN MY BLOOD
- CHEERS.
I HAD A GREAT THREE DAYS
UP HERE WITH YOU.
- ME TOO.
YOU GOT TO ACTUALLY SEE ME.
- AND YOU REALLY, HONESTLY
DID NOT COMPLAIN AT ALL.
- NOPE.
- AND YOU DID IT ALL.
- YEP.
- YOU'VE DONE MORE
THAN SOME MAINE GIRLS HAVE DONE,
SO...I'M IMPRESSED.
- BETWEEN CLAMMING
AND FISHING
TO EATING BEAR BALLS,
I LOVED EVERY SINGLE PART.
- AND WE DID A LOT.
WE FIT A LOT IN.
IT WAS ONE OF MY BEST TRIPS
BACK TO MAINE
AND ONE OF MY MOST MEMORABLE.
- AW, MINE TOO.
- [grunts]
- YAY.
SLUMBER PARTY.
- [laughing]
MONKEY, EVEN--
EVEN CAMEL TOE WHEN YOU'RE
IN A ONESIE.
- SHUT UP.
- YOU'RE THE QUEEN
OF CAMEL TOE.
- I'M HIGH-HIPPED.
I DON'T [bleep] THINK
I GET CAMEL TOE.
YOU'RE A [bleep],
AND YOU JUST SAY I DO.
- YEAH, YOU DO.
- [laughing]
GO TO BED.
- GLAD YOU PUT UP
WITH MY JOKES.
WITH MY OVER-DRAMATIC-NESS.
- MM-HMM.
IN MAINE, IT'S NOT KNOWN
AS CAMEL TOE.
- WHAT'S IT CALLED?
- MOOSE KNUCKLE.
- [laughs]
EW.
I [bleep] HATE YOU.
- HEY, GUYS.
- OH, MY GOD.
- HI.
- YOU COULD PUT, LIKE,
PINS ON IT AND STUFF.
- THERE'S DADDY'S BUBBA.
OKAY, THERE HE IS!
MY BUBBA LOVES TO CHASE.
[dog yipping]
OH, HE PEED!
OH, MY--
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD!
HE'S HIDING FROM YOU.
- HIS TAIL'S WAGGING.
- LOOK AT YOU.
- NICE.
- LITTLE M.I.L.F.
- JUST HAD A BABY? REALLY?
- WHOA, YOU JUST HAD
A BABY?
- REALLY?
- REALLY.
- YOU GUYS
ARE JUST SAYING THAT.
- NO.
- SO TODAY, WE'RE GOING
TO BABYS"R"US.
I NEED A FEW BRAS
'CAUSE MY BOOBS ARE HUGE
FROM BREASTFEEDING.
- YOU NEED A PUMP BRA.
WHAT ELSE DO WE NEED?
WE HAVE A LIST.
- [bleep].
- IT'S YOU AND ME, KID.
- WE'LL BE BACK
IN LIKE AN HOUR.
- CIAO. HE'S WAVING GOOD-BYE.
- DO YOU MISS HIM ALREADY?
- YEAH.
"STORK PARKING.
EXPECTANT MOTHERS."
NICOLE WAS CLOSE ENOUGH
TO EXPECTING.
SHE ALREADY EXPECTED.
THERE WAS PLENTY
OF MORE SPACES
FOR OTHER PREGNANT MOTHERS.
- LET ME GET A CART.
I HAD NO IDEA
YOU PARKED THERE.
- OH.
- WHO CARES?
CAN I LOOK
AT THESE BRAS REAL QUICK?
- YEAH.
DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
- MY BOOBS ARE HUGE.
UGH, THESE ARE NOT SEXY
AT ALL.
- SINCE NICOLE'S GIVEN BIRTH,
I'VE REALIZED
HER BOOBIES
ARE DOUBLE THE SIZE.
- UGH.
- THEY'RE BIG.
- I DON'T THINK...
- THEY FEEL GREAT.
- THAT'S A GREAT THING.
- WHY?
- BECAUSE THEY KILL ME,
AND THEY HURT SO BAD,
AND THEY'RE SO HEAVY.
OH, MY GOD,
THEY HURT SO BAD.
- EVERYBODY LIKES
BIG BOOBIES.
- WELL, AS FOR A GUY.
FOR A GIRL,
AND YOU HAVE TO CARRY
THESE BIG KNOCKERS AROUND,
AND THEY'RE KILLING YOU
IN YOUR SLEEP,
NO.
- HI.
WE HAVE SOME QUESTIONS
ABOUT, UM,
BREASTFEEDING.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY, LIKE,
HANDS-FREE STUFF?
LIKE, HE'S JUST SITTING THERE.
- AS FAR AS, LIKE, BREAST PUMPS?
- YEAH.
- YES.
THIS IS THE ONE
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE TO USE
YOUR HANDS.
YOU CAN USE THAT.
YOU JUST PUT THAT ON.
- AND IT STAYS?
- YEP, IT STAYS.
- [laughs]
- IT'S HANDS-FREE.
- YEAH, WE'LL DO THAT.
- IF I WAS BREASTFEEDING,
I'D GET ONE
OF THESE BRAS MYSELF.
- MM-HMM, SO YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT
WHILE YOU'RE BREASTFEEDING.
- TEXT, TWITTER,
GO ON THE COMPUTER,
ORDER STUFF ON AMAZON.
- VACUUM.
- ALL RIGHT.
THINK WE'RE GOOD.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO TRY OUT
MY BREAST PUMP.
- * BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE
IN THE LIGHT *
- IT'S BEAUTIFUL OUT THERE.
- * SURROUNDED
BY EVERYTHING RIGHT *
- DEFINITELY BITTERSWEET THAT WE
HAVE TO GO BACK TO JERSEY.
EVERYTHING JUST WENT AS WELL
AS IT COULD POSSIBLY GO,
EXCEPT FOR SEX.
WOULD'VE SOMEHOW FACTORED SEX
INTO THAT EQUATION SOMEHOW.
READY?
- YEP.
- LET'S DO IT.
[sighs]
AND HERE WE GO,
BACK TO JERSEY.
I LOVE COMING UP HERE.
- IT WAS AMAZING.
CAN'T WAIT TO COME BACK.
- IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL
COUPLE DAYS UP HERE.
YOU GOT THE MAINE STAMP
OF APPROVAL.
- AND I'M GLAD
I'M PART OF YOUR FAMILY.
IF ANYONE MET ROGER'S FAMILY,
THEY WOULD KNOW
THEY'RE SO NICE, SO SWEET,
AND SO COOL.
AND WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
A PART OF THAT FAMILY?
- YOU JUST SEEMED TO REALLY
ENJOY YOUR TIME OUT THERE, SO--
- SO YOU SEE A FUTURE WITH ME?
- OF COURSE I DO.
- YAY.
- I WOULDN'T BE HERE THIS LONG
IF I DIDN'T.
- HOW DOES THIS WORK?
- [laughing]
- THIS IS A GOOD LOOK.
HEY, GUYS.
- OH, MY GOD.
- HI.
- I CAN MOVE AROUND.
- YEAH.
- PUT THE BACKPACK ON.
- GO TO THE MALL.
- [laughs]
NO, I WOULDN'T--
- GO OUT TO DINNER.
- WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- YOU COULD PUT, LIKE,
PINS ON IT AND STUFF.
- ALL RIGHT,
GO DO YOUR BUSINESS.
GO TAKE THAT THING OFF.
YOU BETTER NOT BE WEARING THAT
IN PUBLIC.
- HE DOESN'T LIKE IT.
- NO. NOT AT ALL.
- UNH-UH.
- [squeals]
- MOM?
SOMEONE'S LOOKING FOR YOU.
- HUH? WHAT?
I'M BUSY, BABE.
- YOU DON'T EVEN CARE
ABOUT YOUR SON.
- EXCUSE ME?
- ALL RIGHT, YOU WANT ME TO MAKE
YOU SOMETHING TO EAT?
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- NOTHING.
- THAT'S NOT EVEN
A FUNNY JOKE.
- DO YOU WANT ME
TO MAKE YOU SOMETHING?
WHAT'S NOT A FUNNY JOKE?
I WAS KIDDING.
- WHO SAYS THAT?
- SAID YOU DON'T CARE
ABOUT YOUR SON.
- WHAT?
- RELAX.
YOU WANT ME TO MAKE YOU
SOMETHING?
- WHAT? WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- [sighs]
RELAX.
WANT ME TO MAKE YOU SOMETHING?
- NO, IT'S NOT FUNNY.
WHO SAYS THAT?
THAT WAS ANNOYING!
- GET US A THERAPIST,
PLEASE.
- NO! JIONNI, NO.
THAT'S FOR WEIRD PEOPLE.
- OH, WHAT,
YOU THINK I'D GO ANYWAY?
- UGH.
- CAN YOU GO RELAX, PLEASE?
WE'RE NOT HAVING
RELATIONSHIP PROBLEMS.
- FEELS LIKE IT.
- NO, IT DON'T.
THAT'S WHY
I'M PROBABLY LAUGHING,
BECAUSE IT'S FUNNY.
TO ME, IT'S FUNNY.
- I'M NOT LAUGHING.
- I THINK IT'S FUNNY.
- SO IS IT ALL RIGHT IF I LEAVE,
OR DO YOU NEED ME
TO STICK AROUND TO HELP
WITH SOMETHING ELSE?
- WE'RE GOOD.
- JIONNI'LL BE HOME--
YOU'LL BE HOME FOR THE BABY?
- YEAH, I'M NOT GOING
WITH HER TO DO HER NAILS.
- OH, ALL RIGHT.
- I'M NERVOUS LEAVING LORENZO
HOME WITH JIONNI
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
BUT I FEEL GROSS.
I WANT TO FEEL GOOD.
I NEED TO BE PAMPERED.
I HAVE TO GO GET
MY NAILS DONE.
- I LOVE YOU.
I'M GONNA MISS HIM TONIGHT.
- UGH, JESUS, TAKE THE WHEEL.
- MOM, CAN YOU GO DOWNSTAIRS
REAL QUICK?
STAY WITH HIM?
- BYE.
YOU LOOK TIRED.
- DO I?
- MM-HMM.
- THANKS.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING, MOM.
- WHO'S WATCHING THE BABY?
- BYE.
MY MOM.
- OH.
- THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
APPRECIATE IT.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TALK TO YOU TOMORROW.
- HOPE TO SEE YOU SOON.
- LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU TOO.
- SHE'S GONNA CRY
ALL THE WAY HOME.
YOU'LL BE FINE?
WISH YOU WERE COMING.
- MM.
SEE YOU.
- I'LL BE, LIKE, AN HOUR.
DON'T DO THE BATH
WITHOUT ME.
- OKAY.
GONNA GET SOME LO--
SOME BONDING TIME.
- YOU'RE HAPPY I'M LEAVING.
[horn honks]
- SEE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU TOO.
- [chuckles]
HE'S SO HAPPY I'M LEAVING.
[engine turns over]
- AH, NOW I CAN RELAX.
- YOU NEED TO STOP
BEING SO MEAN.
- WHAT'D I DO?
- YOU'RE, LIKE,
PUSHING ME AND [bleep].
IT'S ANNOYING.
- YOU'RE SUCH A BABY.
- I'M NOT.
YOU PUSH ME LIKE THIS.
LIKE, IT'S ANNOYING.
IT'S NOT FUNNY ANYMORE.
- [snickers]
- I'M NOT FUN--
I'M NOT LAUGHING.
- RELAX, DUDE.
- [flatulence]
- OH, HE FARTED.
- HE'S A LITTLE
FARTING MACHINE.
- SEE?
- THAT WAS A LOUD FART.
- [flatulence]
- HE'S A BIG FARTER.
- OH, THAT'S SO LOUD.
- WHERE'S JI?
HE'S HOME?
- YEAH, HE'S WATCHING
THE BABY.
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO COME.
BUT WE DIDN'T WANT TO ASK
JANIS TO BABYSIT.
- SO HOW'S JI WITH THE BABY?
HE'S GOOD AT IT?
- OH, YEAH.
A NATURAL.
- [laughs]
[cheerful music]
- DON'T GIVE HIM A BATH,
WHATEVER YOU DO.
- YOU THINK I CAN PICK HIM UP
AND GIVE HIM A BATH?
*
- READY?
- WHOA!
- OH!
- [grunts]
*
[line trilling]
[phone rings]
- HELLO?
- HI.
- WHAT'S UP?
- HOW'S MY BABY?
- GOOD.
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- UH, WE'RE JUST, UM,
FEEDING.
- OH.
- HE MISSES YOU, HE SAID.
- REALLY?
- YEAH--OH, I GOTTA BURP HIM.
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
- BYE.
I LOVE YOU.
- * RAIN CLOUDS
* IN THE SKY
- GLASSES YOU CAN PUT
IN THAT GREEN BAG.
AND I WILL GET,
AS YOU SAY,
THE "LUGGAGES."
OH, IT'S THE BITCHES.
- "HI, DADDY.
HOW WAS YOUR TRIP TO MAINE?
HOW WAS YOUR TRIP TO MAINE?"
YEAH.
- IT'S WEIRD, YOU KNOW?
WHEN YOU SEE 'EM EVERY DAY,
AND THEY'RE BEING ANNOYING,
YOU GET A LITTLE TIRED
OF THEM.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE AWAY FROM THEM
FOR A COUPLE DAYS,
YOU REALLY MISS 'EM.
EXCEPT FOR BELLA.
- SHUT UP.
- THERE'S DADDY'S BUBBA.
OKAY, THERE HE IS!
MY BUBBA LOVES TO CHASE, YEAH.
[dog yipping]
- YES, RIGHT BEFORE BED,
GET HIM [bleep] RILED UP.
AW, HE'S FEARED YOU.
- HEY, BUBBA.
OH, HE PEED!
OH, MY GOD.
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD!
HE PEED.
- WHY DID YOU SCARE HIM?
- I DIDN'T SCARE HIM!
LOOK, HIS TAIL'S WAGGING.
- LOOK AT HIM!
HE'S SCARED!
- HIS TAIL'S WAGGING.
- HE'S HIDING FROM YOU, LOOK.
- HE'S--LOOK AT--
HE'S HIDING FROM YOU.
- [laughs]
- IT'S SO NICE TO BE BACK.
DOGS PISSED AND [bleep]
EVERYWHERE.
IT'S COOL, THOUGH.
I'M USED TO IT.
AND JUST GONNA CLEAN IT UP
AND GO TO BED.
[The Handcuffs'
Baby I Love You]
- * YOU TAKE THE BAD
* RIGHT OUT OF MY DAY
- I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- * YEAH, YOU MAKE IT GOOD
* LIKE IT'S HERE TO STAY
*
- [bleep].
UGH.
HELLO?
[door closes]
- SHH.
- HELLO?
[footsteps approach]
WHY AREN'T YOU SAYING HI?
YOU'RE NOT SLEEPING.
I SEE YOUR EYES OPEN.
LOOK.
DID MY LITTLE MAN-SY
MISS ME?
- YEAH.
- HE LIKES MY BREAST MILK,
HUH?
- YEAH.
OH, NOW HE'S SPITTING UP.
OH, BOY.
- YOU'RE MAKING
ALL OF HIS SHIRTS DIRTY.
I'M GONNA GET
HIS JAMMIES READY.
[gasps]
WE HAVE TO GIVE HIM A BATH.
- WE WON'T DO IT TONIGHT.
LET'S GO TO BED.
- [flatulence]
- OH.
HE JUST FARTED
REALLY LOUD.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I LOVE
LORENZO'S FARTS.
I JUST THINK IT'S BECAUSE
I'M SO OBSESSED WITH HIM
THAT I JUST LOVE
EVERYTHING ABOUT HIM,
EVEN HIS [bleep].
OH!
JIONNI, IT SMELLS
LIKE ROTTEN EGGS.
OH, MY GOD.
- I LOVE TO SMELL--
I LOVE SMELLING HIM TOO,
BUT NOT HIS FARTS.
- WELL, THEN I'M A CRAZY,
OBSESSED PARENT.
WHATEVER.
- [chanting]
* WHO SMELLS SO CLEAN?
- YAY!
- * WHO SMELLS SO CLEAN?
* NOT MOMMY
- YOU NEED TO STOP
BEING SO MEAN.
- WHAT'D I DO?
- YOU'RE, LIKE,
PUSHING ME AND [bleep].
IT'S ANNOYING.
- YOU'RE SUCH A BABY.
- I'M NOT.
YOU'RE, LIKE, ANNOYING.
- [coos]
- HERE, GET THIS UP.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
- [fussing]
- ALL RIGHT, YOU DO IT.
COME ON, YOU DO IT.
- NO, I'M NOT--
- HERE.
[whispers]
MOMMY'S A BABY.
- YOU DO IT.
- NO, GO AHEAD.
- I DID IT--
I DON'T WANT TO.
- YOU JUST SAID--
- 'CAUSE YOU PUSHED ME,
LIKE THIS.
LIKE, IT'S ANNOYING.
IT'S NOT FUNNY ANYMORE.
- [snickers]
- I'M NOT FUN--
I'M NOT LAUGHING.
- RELAX, DUDE.
HOLY [bleep].
GOOD NIGHT.
LOVE YOU.
- JIONNI.
- WHAT?
WHAT?
- YOU'RE, LIKE, SMOTHERING HIM.
- I LOVE HIM.
- WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
YOU SAID YOU LOVED ME?
- [laughs]
- IT'S JUST THREE WORDS.
WHY CAN'T YOU SAY IT
MORE OFTEN, MAN?
- [laughing]
BECAUSE.
BECAUSE LORENZO'S
ON MY MIND,
AND IT JUST--I'M--
HE'S MY FIRST PRIORITY
RIGHT NOW.
- I SAID I LOVE YOU
AT THE NAIL SALON,
AND YOU JUST HUNG UP.
- I DIDN'T HEAR. YOU DID?
- YEAH.
- NO.
- I SAID, "I LOVE YOU, BYE."
YOU SAID, "BYE."
- NO, I WAS FEEDING HIM.
I STILL LOVE YOU,
OBVIOUSLY.
- I WISH WE SAID IT MORE.
- ALL RIGHT,
WE'LL START TONIGHT.
- LOVE YOU.
LOVE YOU.
- SEE, HE SAYS IT LIKE THAT.
- I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
[smooching]
- OH, DIESEL.
YOU NEED TO GO
TO A VET IMMEDIATELY.
- WELL, WHY--HOW COME
YOU COULDN'T WATCH HIM THEN?
- I WATCH HIM
THE BEST I CAN, ALL RIGHT?
- NO, YOU DIDN'T WATCH HIM
THE BEST YOU CAN, JENNI.
- AT THE TIME, I DID.
I HONESTLY DIDN'T THINK
HE WAS EATING IT.
- KATIE!
KATIE, MY BEST FRIEND FOREVER,
FROM HIGH SCHOOL...
DON'T CRY.
OH, MY GOD.
SHE GAVE ME
THE NICKNAME SNOOKI.
SO IT'S ALL HER [bleep] FAULT.
- ISN'T HE CUTE?
- HE'S SO CUTE.
- I HATE YOU.
- * HEART ATTACKERS
AND RUNAWAYS *
* TICKET TAKERS
GONNA MAKE YOU PAY *
- YOU NEED TO GO
OUTSIDE, OKAY?
ROGER!
- WHAT?
- DO YOU WANT SOME SALAD?
- I'M OKAY.
THANK YOU.
THANKS FOR YELLING UP HERE.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
[light groovy music]
*
- DON'T BE EATING GRASS,
DIESEL.
I FEEL LIKE DOGS
ARE LIKE HAVING KIDS.
YOU KNOW,
THEY'RE A BIG RESPONSIBILITY.
WHEN THEY GET SICK,
YOU TAKE THEM TO THE VET.
WHEN THEY NEED LOVE,
YOU GIVE THEM LOVE.
WHEN THEY'RE HUNGRY,
YOU FEED THEM.
YOU KNOW, WHEN THEY NEED
ATTENTION,
YOU PLAY WITH THEM.
STOP IT.
I'M GONNA MAKE A BIG SALAD.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
STAY OUT HERE?
IF I HAD KIDS
AND MY DOGS,
I WOULD DEFINITELY GET A MAID
AND/OR A NANNY.
'CAUSE I WOULD NEED HELP.
OH, DIESEL.
[sighs]
THERE GOES EATING.
BABE!
- WHAT?
- DIESEL'S THROWING UP
ALL OVER AGAIN.
- WAS HE OUTSIDE?
- YEAH, HE WAS OUTSIDE.
BUT I WAS WATCHING HIM.
DIESEL, WHAT ARE YOU EATING
OUT THERE?
- I KNOW YOU WERE OUT THERE
WITH HIM,
BUT YOU--WERE YOU WATCHING HIM
THE ENTIRE TIME?
HE NEVER GOT
OUT OF YOUR SIGHT?
- HE WAS JUST, LIKE--
- BUT DID YOU WATCH HIM?
YOU WEREN'T, LIKE,
TEXTING ON YOUR PHONE
OR NOTHING LIKE THAT?
- I WAS EATING
AND WATCHING HIM, BUT--
- I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
IT'S, LIKE,
GRASS SEED AND FERTILIZER.
AND I THINK
THAT'S WHAT HE'S EATING.
- I'M TRYING TO WATCH DIESEL.
I TREAT ALL MY BABIES
LIKE THEY ARE MY BABIES.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M JUST--
IT'S LIKE A KID.
LIKE, IF MY KID WANTS
TO PLAY OUTSIDE,
I'M GONNA LET HIM
PLAY OUTSIDE.
I'M NOT GONNA BE LIKE...
AND [bleep] STARE AT HIM
FOR 24/7.
I'M GONNA LET HIM
DO HIS THING,
COME BACK WHEN HE'S READY.
WELL, IT'S SAYING...
A DOG WITH THESE SIGNS,
YOU NEED TO GO
TO A VET IMMEDIATELY.
- OKAY, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO RUN HIM
TO THE EMERGENCY ROOM
RIGHT NOW THEN?
- I DON'T KNOW,
AT THIS POINT.
THIS IS DRIVING ME NUTS.
LOOK AT HIM.
- OKAY, WELL, WHY--
HOW COME YOU COULDN'T
WATCH HIM THEN?
- I WATCH HIM
THE BEST I CAN, ALL RIGHT?
- NO, YOU DIDN'T WATCH HIM
THE BEST YOU CAN, JENNI.
- AT THE TIME, I DID.
I HONESTLY DIDN'T THINK
HE WAS EATING IT
OR GETTING INTO IT
WHEN HE WAS WALKING AROUND.
ROGER DOESN'T LIKE
TO DROP ANYTHING,
SO EVEN THOUGH I ADMIT
TO ROGER
THAT I WASN'T WATCHING HIM
LIKE A HAWK OUTSIDE,
ROGER STILL WANTS TO DIG
HIS LITTLE [bleep] HOLES
IN MY SIDE
AND, YOU KNOW,
BITCH AT ME.
- IS YOUR STATEMENT
RIGHT NOW
THAT YOU ARE NOT CAPABLE
OF WATCHING THAT DOG...
- I'M GOING TO TRY, BUT--
- FOR FIVE OR TEN MINUTES
TO A TIME?
'CAUSE IF THE DOG GOES,
I'M GOING.
[birds chirping]
- NOT TOO MUCH SALT.
- DON'T LOOK.
- OKAY--WHOA.
OH, GOD.
- JUST LEAVE MY RECIPE ALONE.
- NO, I'M JUST GONNA
JUST LOCK THINGS UP.
YOU CAN'T USE THAT.
- STEP ASIDE.
- OKAY.
- I AM MAKING MY SPECIALTY,
SEAFOOD PASTA.
THE SPOON ITSELF WILL GIVE IT
SOME SEAFOOD FLAVOR.
IT'S MY FAVORITE.
I'M GONNA SHOW MY MOTHER
I CAN COOK.
GET OUT--JUST GO.
GET OUTTA HERE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK THOSE
THREE CLAMS ARE GONNA DO?
- THERE'S FOUR CLAMS.
NOW GET OVER THERE.
I SOMEWHAT KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING.
I KNOW WHAT I NEED.
I KNOW THE FLAVOR.
I KNOW THE TIME.
I'M JUST TRYING TO DO THIS
ON MY OWN.
- DADDY THINKS HE CAN COOK.
BUT HE CAN'T.
- PLEASE, HUH?
- DO YOU HATE ME?
ME AND ROGER
DEFINITELY FIGHT DIFFERENTLY
THAN WE USED TO.
WE SEPARATE OURSELVES,
COOL OFF,
AND THEN COMMUNICATE,
RATHER THAN SCREAMING MATCHES,
NOT TALKING FOR DAYS,
PUNCHING EACH OTHER,
[bleep] LIKE THAT.
[sighs]
HI, HANDSOME.
HELLO, HANDSOME MAN.
- PLEASE, JUST IN THE FUTURE,
JUST KEEP AN EYE ON HIM,
LIKE, THE ENTIRE TIME.
- WELL, NOW I'M PARANOID
WITH ALL THREE OF THEM.
- OR CALL ME.
- I SAW [bleep] NOEL
SNIFFING AROUND.
- JUST SAYING,
KEEP AN EYE ON ALL THE DOGS
WHILE THEY'RE OUT HERE.
THAT'S THE EASIEST WAY
TO DO IT.
LIKE, A CONSTANT EYE.
I'M FRUSTRATED,
MORE BECAUSE JENNI KNOWS
HOW MUCH I LOVE DIESEL,
AND, YOU KNOW,
JUST KEEP AN EYE ON HIM
WHEN HE'S IN THE BACKYARD.
THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE TO DO.
IT'S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE.
- GOD, I FEEL LIKE
PUNCHING YOU
RIGHT IN THE [bleep] THROAT.
- PROBABLY HURT YOUR HAND.
[toilet flushes]
WHOA.
WHAT HAPPENED IN HERE?
[chuckles]
WHAT HAPPENED IN HERE, MONKEY?
MONKEY, WHAT HAPPENED IN HERE?
SOMETHING HAPPENED
IN HERE.
- MAYBE I HAD TO POOP.
- WELL, THAT'S A SERIOUS POOP.
YOU WERE APPARENTLY
CONSTIPATED.
CAN YOU LOOK
AT THIS REAL QUICK?
ARE MY--
ARE MY NOSE HAIRS BURNED?
- I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
- I JUST WALKED
IN THE BATHROOM,
AND I SWEAR I BURNT
MY NOSE HAIRS.
- THINK YOU'RE SO [bleep] FUNNY.
- HELLO?
- HEY, GAL.
- HEY, SAM.
I'M WITH RON.
HE SAYS HI TOO.
- WHAT UP, CHICK?
- HEY, RON.
- WE'RE EXCITED TO COME SEE
YOU AND THE BABY AND JIONNI.
LIKE, WE'RE SO HAPPY
RIGHT NOW.
- I'M SO EXCITED
TO SEE YOU GUYS.
WHEN ARE YOU COMING?
- BE THERE SOON.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY NOW.
- ALL RIGHT.
LOVE YOU GUYS. BYE.
- BYE.
- I'M SO EXCITED.
MY BITCHES ARE COMING OVER.
- IS SAM AND RONNIE COMING?
- MM-HMM, AND KATIE.
KATIE, MY BEST FRIEND FOREVER
FROM HIGH SCHOOL,
AND SHE GAVE ME
THE NICKNAME SNOOKI.
SO IT'S ALL HER [bleep] FAULT.
YOU LOOK PERFECT.
- YOU HAVE COMPANY.
- KATIE!
- COME IN.
- THANK GOD,
I JUST DRESSED HIM.
- SHUT UP.
- OKAY, HE'S GOOD.
- HI.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- DON'T CRY.
OH, MY GOD.
- OH, MY GOD.
HI, BABY.
HI.
- ISN'T HE CUTE?
- HE'S SO CUTE.
- I HATE YOU.
[sniffles]
ME AND KATIE,
YOU KNOW, WE'VE BASICALLY
BEEN BEST FRIENDS
SINCE PRESCHOOL.
- OH, MY GOD.
- YOU'RE SUCH AN ASS.
STOP CRYING.
YOU'RE ANNOYING.
- GIMME A KISS.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
- I LOVE YOU.
SHE'S MARRIED.
I'M HAVING A BABY.
WE'RE GROWING UP.
IT'S JUST CRAZY TO, YOU KNOW,
SEE OUR LIVES, LIKE,
SO DIFFERENT.
- AH, HI, SUGAR.
OH, MY GOD.
WERE YOU AFRAID
TO HOLD HIM?
- NO.
SURPRISINGLY,
'CAUSE I HATE BABIES.
- REALLY?
- REMEMBER?
I HELD YOUR SISTER'S,
AND I WAS LIKE, UGH.
[camera beeps]
- WAIT, I CAN'T TAKE THAT LIP.
IT'S YOURS.
- I DIDN'T WANT HIM
TO HAVE MY LIPS.
[cell phone chimes]
- NO, I LOVE THEM.
- OH, THERE GOES MY MOM.
SHE DOESN'T EVEN SAY HI
TO ME ANYMORE.
- YEAH, THOSE DAYS ARE OVER.
GET USED TO IT.
- "HOW'S HE DOING?"
NO ONE CARES ABOUT ME ANYMORE.
- NOPE.
- JIONNI DOESN'T LOVE ME.
HE'S GONNA TAKE HIM AWAY.
IT'S GONNA BE
JIONNI AND DADDY FOREVER.
- THAT'S HOW IT IS.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
WHEN WE HAVE TIME,
WE NEED TO GO ON VACATION
SO WE CAN GET IT BACK.
IT JUST SUCKS THAT,
YOU KNOW,
WE DON'T HAVE
THAT SPARK ANYMORE.
I JUST WANT JIONNI
TO LOVE ME.
WE LOST IT.
- [giggles]
- CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS YOUR KID.
- I KNOW.
- HE'S GONNA BE LIKE A RON.
HALF ITALIAN, HALF SPANISH.
- LITTLE CHILEAN GUIDO.
- COULD WE CUDDLE
AND KISS TONIGHT?
- WE ALWAYS CUDDLE.
- WE DON'T KISS.
- SWEET.
- IS HE GETTING HEAVY?
- NO, I LOVE HIM.
- OKAY.
- YOU'RE GETTING JEALOUS,
AREN'T YOU?
HE'S SO GOOD.
- I KNOW.
- SO GOOD.
- DON'T JINX US.
I THINK WHEN HE GETS OLDER,
HE'S GONNA PAY ME BACK
FOR ALL THE [bleep] I DID.
- NO, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A GIRL,
AND SHE'S GONNA PAY YOU BACK.
- UGH.
- JIONNI, IF YOU EVER HAVE
A GIRL,
DON'T LET HER
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
- YEAH, RIGHT?
- SHE'S GONNA BE REALLY BAD.
- REALLY BAD.
[doorbell chimes]
A SURPRISE?
- RON AND SAM.
- REALLY?
- DID YOU MEET THEM?
- NO.
[doorbell chimes]
- [creepy voice]
YOU RANG?
- YO!
- OH, THE BABY GOT SO BIG!
[laughter]
- WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- WHAT'S UP, MAN?
- WHAT'S GOING ON? HI.
- HI.
- OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- I TEXTED YOU.
YOU NEVER TEXTED ME BACK.
- YOU NEVER TEXT ME.
- I DON'T HAVE
YOUR NUMBER THEN.
- YOU LOOK AMAZING.
- HI.
WINE?
- HE GOT SO BIG.
- OH, WINE.
- THANK YOU.
- OKAY, I CAN'T WAIT
TO MEET HIM.
- COME ON.
- OH.
- THIS IS MY FRIEND KATIE.
- HEY, GUYS.
- THAT'S RON AND SAM.
- HI.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
- DON'T CRY.
- HE LOOKS A LITTLE
LIKE ROGER.
- I CRIED ALL OVER HIM.
- HE IS BEAUTIFUL.
- [laughing]
HE LOOKS LIKE ROGER?
IS THAT WHAT YOU JUST SAID?
- SO LITTLE.
- DO YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM?
- YEAH, BUT I WANT TO JUST
SEE HIM FIRST.
- WASH YOUR HANDS.
- YEAH, I DON'T--
I'M NERVOUS.
JUST WANT TO SEE HIM.
- I FEEL LIKE RONNIE
IS GONNA BE
IN ROGER'S BOAT.
- SAM DOESN'T WANT KIDS.
TRUST ME.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
- DOES--ME?
- YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
- YOU WANT TO SEE OUR HOUSE?
- WE'LL SHOW YOU
OUR MAN CAVE.
- JIONNI, YOU'RE SUCH
A GOOD DAD ALREADY.
- ISN'T HE?
- SO, LIKE, YOU'RE READY
FOR YOUR SECOND ONE?
- RON, SHUT UP.
- OH, WOW, THIS IS COOL.
- THIS IS WHERE WE LIVE.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WE JUST GOT A BABY CRIB.
- I WANT TO HOLD HIM.
- SAM AND RON ARE DEFINITELY
NOT GONNA WANT KIDS.
SAM DOESN'T EVEN WANT
TO GET MARRIED
TILL SHE'S 40 YEARS OLD.
- HE'S ACTUALLY--
- HE GOT HAIRY LITTLE ARMS.
- I WAS EXPECTING HAIRIER.
- "HE'S SO CUTE.
I MIGHT WANT ONE."
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- AND THAT IS A PANTS-POOPER
FOR RON.
- HE'S NOT THAT HAIRY.
IT'S OKAY, BABY.
- HE MIGHT WANT A BUB, SO--
- WHAT'S A--
OH, A BOOB.
- YEAH, HE SAID BUB.
- A BUB. YOU SAID A BUB?
- A BUB.
- HE MIGHT--
- [laughs]
YEAH.
- [coos]
- OH, MY GOD.
HE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS YOUR BABY.
- MM-HMM.
- HE JUST HAS HAIRY--
LIKE, A HAIRY HEAD.
THAT'S IT.
- YEAH, HE DOES.
- YOU GUYS SHOULD HAVE ONE.
- HELL, NO.
IN LIKE TEN YEARS.
TEN YEARS.
- TEN YEARS? YOU'LL BE 40.
- LORENZO CAN BABYSIT OUR KIDS
IN LIKE TEN YEARS.
- [laughs]
- SO YOU HAVE TO GO BACK
AND GET THE STITCHES OUT,
NICOLE?
- NO, THEY DISSOLVE.
THEY DISSOLVE.
- YOU GOT AN EPISIOTOMY?
- NO, THEY DIDN'T CUT IT.
I JUST RIPPED A LITTLE BIT.
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- [hisses]
- I RIPPED.
- [shudders]
- WELL, USUALLY,
WHEN YOU GIVE BIRTH,
YOUR VAGINA RIPS
BECAUSE YOU DON'T REALLY HAVE
ANYTHING THAT BIG IN YOU,
UNLESS YOU'RE, LIKE,
A RAGING WHORE.
- POOR VAGINA
GOES THROUGH SO MUCH.
IT'S LIKE--
[laughs]
- IT'S DEFINITELY [bleep] UP.
- ALL I'M THINKING ABOUT IS
YOUR THROBBING VAGINA.
- UGH, IT'S NOT THROBBING.
FEELS LIKE I HAD SEX
FOR TEN HOURS.
- UGH!
- OH.
- YEAH. HELLO.
- WE'LL GO IN HERE.
- I'M MAKING
HOMEMADE MOZZARELLA.
- YUM!
- ARE YOU?
JUST WANT TO SIT
IN HERE WITH HIM?
- YEAH.
- PEOPLE JUST COME OVER
NONSTOP ON SUNDAYS.
- IT'S FAMILY DAY, RIGHT?
- YEP.
- I LOVE BIG MEN
WITH SMALL CHILDREN.
- WOW.
DO I COUNT?
- YES, OF COURSE.
- RONNIE HOLDING LORENZO,
HE LOOKS CUTE.
RONNIE LOOKS LIKE AN UNCLE,
AND, YOU KNOW,
THEY LOOK RELATED, KIND OF.
- [giggles]
- CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS YOUR KID.
- I KNOW.
- HE'S GONNA BE LIKE A RON,
HALF ITALIAN,
HALF SPANISH.
- YEAH, A LITTLE "CHUIDO".
LITTLE CHILEAN GUIDO.
[chuckles]
- CAN I TAKE HIM BACK?
- MM-HMM.
- MY NIPPLES ARE BURNING.
- YOUR NIPPLES?
- MM-HMM.
- THEY BURN?
- YEAH.
- UGH.
- [flatulence]
- OH, HE FARTED.
- SEE? HE'S--
HE'S A LITTLE
FARTING MACHINE.
- SEE?
- THAT WAS A LOUD FART.
- [flatulence]
- HE'S A BIG FARTER.
- OH, THAT'S SO LOUD.
- * BA BA
* BA DA-DA
DA-DA DA-DA *
- HI, AUNT PAT.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- OH, THERE'S OUR JIONNI.
- HI, GRAN.
- OH, GRANDMA'S HERE.
- HI.
- YOU GUYS GOTTA
GET OUT OF HERE.
- COME ON, COME SAY HI
TO THE BABY.
- A MILLION PEOPLE
ARE GONNA COME.
- OH, HE'S BEAUTIFUL.
- THANK YOU.
- SO PRETTY.
- ARE YOU READY, BABE?
- YEAH.
- WE'LL GET GOING.
YOU GUYS CAN ENJOY
YOUR BARBECUE.
- ALL RIGHT.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
- BYE, GUYS.
- BYE.
- I'M VERY HAPPY
THAT RON AND SAM CAME OVER
TO MEET LORENZO.
SEE YOU GUYS.
- BYE.
- NICE SEEING YOU.
- OH.
- MAKE BABIES.
- NO. EW.
- 'CAUSE IT JUST SHOWS
THAT THEY CARE,
AND NO MATTER HOW MUCH
OUR LIFE CHANGES,
WE'RE ALWAYS GONNA BE THERE
FOR EACH OTHER.
- USUALLY BABIES ARE UGLY
WHEN THEY'RE BORN.
- NO, HE'S CUTE.
- HE'S REALLY CUTE.
- SEE WHO POPS OUT
THE NEXT ONE,
DEENA OR [bleep] JENNI.
- DEENA.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[cheerful music]
*
- WANT ME TO FINISH,
YOU GUYS GO EAT?
- YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM
SO BAD.
- WE FIGHT OVER HIM.
- YOU NEEDED TWINS.
- WHY'S HE SO RED?
- WHEN HE GETS EXCITED,
HE GETS RED.
- GO EAT.
- I WANT TO CUDDLE.
- WITH WHO?
- LORENZO.
- [laughs]
- I KEEP GETTING HER MAD
BY, LIKE,
PUSHING HER OUT OF THE WAY
WHEN WE'RE HOLDING HIM.
- I WOULD TOO.
I KEEP TELLING HER,
I WAS LIKE,
JIONNI'S GONNA RUN AWAY
WITH LORENZO.
- OH, YES.
- HE DOESN'T LIKE ME ANYMORE.
- LEAVE MOMMY AT HOME.
- I SAY IT ALL THE TIME.
- [snickers]
- HE SAYS,
"IT JUST ME AND LORENZO.
I DON'T NEED YOU."
- NO, I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
WHAT DO I SAY?
- BASICALLY, YOU SAY THAT.
- I DON'T--
WHAT DO I SAY?
EXACT WORDS.
I DON'T SAY THAT.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
- CAN YOU GUYS
JUST GET MARRIED ALREADY?
UGH, LISTEN TO YOU.
- HE DOESN'T WANT TO.
ME AND JIONNI
HAVE BEEN BICKERING
EVER SINCE LORENZO
WAS BORN,
AND I DON'T LIKE IT.
- [sighs]
YOU WANNA LAY DOWN
A LITTLE BIT?
YOU WANNA CUDDLE
WITH DADDY?
WE'RE DEFINITELY TIRED.
IT'S TIME TO GO TO BED.
I'M EXHAUSTED.
LORENZO'S EXHAUSTED.
LET'S HIT THE MAN CAVE.
- BYE, BOO.
- BYE, AUNT KATIE.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
SEE? HE LEFT ME OUT.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
- I FORGOT.
- "I'M EXHAUSTED.
LORENZO'S EXHAUSTED."
I'M NOT IN THE PICTURE.
- GOOD NIGHT, BUDDY.
GOOD NIGHT, BUDDY.
GOOD NIGHT,
MY "WITTLE" BUDDY.
[grunts]
- [giggles]
- ARE YOU SICK?
GET OFF ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU'RE--
YOU'RE JUST MESSED UP.
- I'M SO EXCITED.
I FEEL LIKE I FEEL
SEXY AGAIN,
AND HE DOESN'T GIVE A [bleep].
[scoffs]
THIS IS BULL[bleep].
- I'M OVER HERE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO TO ME.
IF I DON'T LOOK
AT YOU, YOU--
- 'CAUSE YOU NEVER LOOK
AT ME ANYMORE.
- OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO TIRED.
- YOU DIDN'T KISS ME.
- WHAT A LONG NIGHT.
- [hiccups]
- [gasps]
HE HAS THE HICCUPS.
- I DON'T DELIBERATELY
IGNORE YOU.
I JUST AM PAYING
A LOT OF ATTENTION TO HIM,
AND YOU'RE NOT USED TO IT.
TALK TO HIM.
- YOU JUST TOLD ME
TO TALK TO YOU.
- GET THAT OFF HIS FACE.
- RELAX.
OKAY, BUT I WANT
SOME LOVIN' TOO.
LIKE, WHEN HE GOES TO SLEEP,
HUG ME.
- I DO.
EVERY NIGHT,
WE CUDDLE BEFORE BED.
- WE DON'T CUDDLE ANYMORE.
- I PUT MY ARM AROUND YOU
AND GIVE YOU--
AND GO TO BED.
- NO, YOU--
- CALL ME A LIAR.
- YOU SLEEP OVER HERE.
I SLEEP OVER HERE.
- IT SMELLS LIKE THROW-UP
IN HERE.
- YOU SEEM LIKE YOU'RE NOT
IN A GOOD MOOD.
- IT HAS TO DO
WITH YOU MEETING MY MOTHER.
I HAVEN'T INTRODUCED
HARDLY ANYONE TO MY MOM,
LET ALONE A BOYFRIEND.
- DO YOU THINK THERE WILL
EVER BE A POINT
WHERE YOU'RE COMFORTABLE
WITH ME MEETING HER,
OR NO?
[fire alarm beeps]
- [screams]
- [crying]
- I HATE YOU.
- WE'RE NOT WORKING.
- NO, WE'RE NOT.
- START PACKING YOUR [bleep].
- A BABY CHANGES
THE RELATIONSHIP,
SO ME AND JIONNI
JUST NEED TO WORK ON IT.
- I WAS INTERESTED
IN SPEAKING
TO SOMEBODY
ABOUT ENGAGEMENT RINGS.
MY HEART TELLS ME
THAT SHE'S THE ONE FOR ME.
- YOU DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING,
DID YOU?
- YEAH. WHAT?
- WHAT?
- HEAR ABOUT WHAT?