- I'’M--I'’M SO SCARED.
- I LOVE YOU MORE THAN YOU CAN
EVER IMAGINE,
AND I WANT TO SPEND THE REST OF
MY LIFE WITH YOU.
- OH!
- WILL YOU MARRY ME?
- OH, MY GOD!
- IS THAT A YES?
- YES!
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- LET ME CALL MY FRIENDS, OKAY?
JUST LIKE THE BACHELOR.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO.
- GERARD.
- WHAT'’S UP, BUD?
- ARE YOU WITH JOHNNY BOY?
- I AM WITH JOHNNY BOY.
- ALL RIGHT.
UM, WE'’RE HAVING
MY "DADCHELOR" PARTY.
- YOU'’RE NOT COOL.
- WE ARE GOING TO, UH,
PALS CABIN, BABY,
AND THEN MAYBE 4SIXTY6,
IF I'’M ALLOWED TO.
- HAVE THEY GOT LIQUOR
AT PALS CABIN?
I'’M GONNA HAVE TO BRING
A BOTTLE IN THE LIMO.
- YOU'’RE GETTING A LIMO?
IT'’S GONNA BE A [bleep] SHOW.
- THE DADCHELOR PARTY IS,
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
BEFORE YOU BECOME A DAD,
A LITTLE PARTY CELEBRATION.
CONGRATULATIONS,
YOUR SON'’S COMING.
IT'’S SUPPOSED TO BE
BEFORE THE BABY.
LORENZO CAME A LITTLE EARLIER,
SO--
- NOW YOU'’RE CELEBRATING
BEING A FATHER
AND HAVING A HEALTHY BABY.
- HEY, ROGER, TOMORROW
IS THE DADCHELOR PARTY.
HEY, BABA GHANOUSH, WHAT'’S UP,
YOU CRAZY SON OF A BITCH?
HALLIE!
- JESUS [bleep].
- WHAT'’S UP, YOU OLD [bleep]?
[laughs]
YO, TREESY B,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- STOP. YOU'’RE EMBARRASSING.
- WHAT'’S UP, MAN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHO AM I KIDDING?
IT'’S JUST AN EXCUSE TO GO OUT
WITH THE GUYS,
GET DRUNK,
AND HAVE SOME FUN.
- YOU LETTING HIM GO OUT,
NICOLE?
YOU'’RE TRUSTING THIS GUY?
- YEAH, TRUST ME, I'’LL KNOW.
- I'’M ALLOWED TO GO TO 4SIXTY6
NOW?
- YEAH, I NEVER SAID NO.
- OH.
- YOU HAVING
A LITTLE GIRLS'’ TRIP?
- YEAH, I'’M GOING OUT NEXT WEEK.
- OH, YEAH?
- OH, NO, YOU'’RE NOT.
- YEAH, I AM.
- IF I WAS A PSYCHO BITCH
AND DIDN'’T ALLOW JIONNI OUT
AND GO OUT WITH HIS BOYS,
WE WOULDN'’T BE HERE RIGHT NOW.
SO BASICALLY, NO RULES, BUT TRY
AND BE HOME BEFORE 3:00.
- 3:00?
- 3:00'’S NOT THAT BAD.
- FINE. FORGET IT, CHAD,
WE'’RE NOT GOING OUT.
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- OH, MAN, THAT COOKS QUICK.
- SO, THIS MORNING I WAKE UP
AND I LOOK AT MY HAND
AND I NOTICE MY RING, AND, LIKE,
YESTERDAY WAS NOT A DREAM,
AND I AM LEGIT ENGAGED.
I'’M ENGAGED!
I DON'’T KNOW IF YOU NOTICED,
BUT YOU'’RE COOKING
A [bleep] KING KONG PANCAKE
IN THERE.
- THAT'’S THE AMOUNT OF BATTER
THAT YOU PUT IN THERE, NOT ME.
I SAID THERE WAS ENOUGH FOR
ANOTHER ONE.
- I HAVE A BIG BOY
OF A BOYFRIEND--OF A FIANCE.
I GOTTA GET USED TO NOT SAYING
"BOYFRIEND" ANYMORE.
- FIANCE.
- IT SOUNDS FRENCH, YOU KNOW?
- IT IS FRENCH.
- IT IS?
- YES.
- I DIDN'’T KNOW THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TONIGHT
WITH JIONNI?
- UH, I GUESS
WE'’RE GOING TO DINNER
WITH, UH, HIS BUDDIES FIRST
AND THEN WE'’RE GOING TO A CLUB,
I GUESS.
[groans]
- FOR THE BEST BREAKFAST.
SO.
- SO.
- IF I CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN FOR
NEXT SPRINGISH, BEFORE SUMMER--
- THE WEDDING?
- YEAH.
- I JUST THINK IT'’S GONNA BE--
I WOULD NEVER SAY "NO,"
BUT I FEEL LIKE WE'’RE ONLY
ENGAGED ONE DAY
AND WE HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
- EVEN THOUGH WE'’VE ONLY BEEN
ENGAGED FOR ABOUT SIX HOURS,
I FEEL LIKE IT'’S NECESSARY THAT
WE TALK ABOUT WEDDING PLANS
IN OUR NEAR FUTURE,
AND HOW THIS IS GONNA GO DOWN.
- I DO NOT FEEL LIKE
IT'’S NECESSARY--
- I DO.
- RIGHT NOW--
- SIX HOURS
INTO AN ENGAGEMENT.
- IT'’S OKAY, BABE.
- HERE'’S WHAT I REFUSE
TO HAVE HAPPEN.
I REFUSE TO BE
STRESSED OUT OVER IT.
IT'’S NOT WHAT GETTING MARRIED'’S
ALL ABOUT.
I REFUSE TO HAVE ANY KIND
OF WEDDING WARS
OR BRIDEZILLAS
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT,
AND I THINK THE MORE TIME YOU
GIVE YOURSELF--WE'’RE IN NO RUSH.
EVERY GIRL WANTS TO BE
COMPLETELY OVER THE TOP.
- YES, I WANT TO PLAN--I WILL
PICK OUT THE CENTERPIECES,
THE FLOWERS, THE CANDLES,
THE ARRANGEMENTS.
I WILL HAVE EVERYTHING, MYSELF,
PICKED OUT AND ARRANGED,
AND YOU JUST HAVE TO DO IT
IN BULK,
'’CAUSE I WANT EVERYTHING BIG,
LIKE MY RING.
- IF YOU BECOME A BRIDEZILLA,
I WOULD LIKE YOUR WORD RIGHT NOW
THAT WE CAN HAVE A SIMPLE,
SIMPLIFIED BUT BEAUTIFUL--
- I TOLD YOU I WILL NOT BE
A BRIDEZILLA TO YOU.
- RIGHT.
WELL, WE'’LL SEE.
- BABE!
- ♪WE BEGAN WITH... ♪
- JIONNI GOT A BOW AND ARROW.
- I'’M SHOOTING THIS BITCH.
- JIONNI!
- JIONNI, YOU'’RE NOT
SHOOTING THAT HERE.
- I'’M GOING TO GO
IN THE BACKYARD.
- I THINK IT'’S ILLEGAL.
- ILLEGAL!
I ORDERED A COMPOUND BOW
AND ARROW.
ARCHERY GOT ME JACKED UP
FROM THE OLYMPICS.
JOHNNY RAINBOW GETS ME JACKED UP
EVERY DAY,
AND I JUST WANT TO KILL
SOMETHING,
I WANT TO HUNT AND,
YOU KNOW--
- THAT'’S SCARY.
YOU DON'’T SAY THAT.
I DON'’T WANT YOU KILLING
ANY ANIMALS.
- IT'’S, LIKE, SURVIVAL MODE,
SO IF THE DATE EVER HAPPENS
THAT I HAVE TO HUNT,
LIKE THE[bleep] HUNGER GAMES.
- OH, MY GOD.
I'’M OPPOSED TO HUNTING. I LOVE
ANIMALS. I LOVE SQUIRRELS.
I DON'’T WANT JIONNI
SHOOTING ANY LIVING THING.
- WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
OF ME ACTUALLY KILLING
A SQUIRREL, BY THE WAY?
- THAT'’S TRUE.
YOU DON'’T EVEN HURT ANYONE
WITH THOSE.
THEY'’RE PLASTIC.
- HOW DO YOU USE IT?
I'’M NOT A JABRONI.
I FEEL LIKE I COULD FIGURE OUT
HOW TO SHOOT THIS BOW.
I PUT A LITTLE BOX
BY THE SHED.
YOU KNOW, I COULD FIGURE
I COULD SHOOT IT STRAIGHT.
I'’M NOT GONNA HIT NOBODY.
YOU KNOW,
TAKE SOME TARGET PRACTICE.
HOW DO I GET IT STRONGER?
- I THINK IT'’S CALLED
DIRECTIONS.
[bow clatters]
THIS IS TROUBLE.
- CAN YOU PUT AN APPLE
ON YOUR HEAD?
- NO, I DON'’T THINK SO.
THERE GOES MY SHED,
RIGHT THROUGH MY SHED.
- [laughs]
OH, SNAP.
IT HIT MY DAD'’S SHED.
WENT RIGHT THROUGH IT.
HE GOT A LITTLE MAD,
BUT IT WAS JUST A SHED.
- GAS CANS IN THERE. YOU HIT ONE
OF THEM, YOU'’RE GONNA EXPLODE.
- THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN BAD.
- YEAH, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN BAD
FOR YOU.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- I DON'’T WANT TO, LIKE,
GET RID OF IT RIGHT NOW.
I'’M PUTTING MY RING IN ITS BOX
RIGHT NOW
TO HIDE IT FROM NICOLE
SO SHE DOESN'’T SEE IT,
'’CAUSE I WANT TO WAIT TO
TELL HER, YOU KNOW, PRIVATELY,
WHEN THE BOYS GO OUT,
ONLY BECAUSE WE DON'’T WANT TO
SPOIL THE FUN FOR JIONNI
AND MAKE IT A ROGER NIGHT.
IT SHOULD BE A JIONNI NIGHT.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK NICOLE IS
GONNA SAY ABOUT YOUR RING?
- SHE'’S PROBABLY GONNA SAY,
"FINALLY."
BUT, LIKE, YEAH,
IN HER NICOLE VOICE.
- [laughs]
- YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
[upbeat music]
- ♪ YOU TURN ME UPSIDE DOWN ♪
♪ STAND ME ON MY... ♪
- HI. OH, MY GOD.
YOU LOOK AMAZING!
- I'’M COMING OUT WITH YOU
TONIGHT.
- ARE YOU?
- YEAH.
- ARE YOU? NOW I'’M JEALOUS.
- [bleep].
- WE'’RE SPENDING THE NIGHT.
- OH, AWESOME!
JIONNI'’S DOWN BY THE BABY.
- OH. HELLO?
- AUNT JENNI'’S HERE.
HEY, BOO.
- I GOT US CHAMPAGNE.
- WHERE'’S THAT LITTLE MAN?
- WE'’RE TAKING A NAP.
- OH, ARE WE? OH!
- OH, HE'’S WITH YOU?
- YEAH.
- OH, MY GOD, HE'’S ADORABLE.
- WE TAKE NAPS SOMETIMES.
- OH!
- HE'’S SO PRECIOUS.
YOU CAN LAY WITH US.
- HOW CUTE.
- HE'’S TRYING TO POOPIES.
YOU COULD CHANGE
HIS POOPY DIAPER.
- OKAY.
- HOW WAS SKYDIVING?
- OH, IT WAS SO COOL.
IT REALLY WAS.
- I'’VE NEVER BEEN MORE SCARED
IN MY LIFE, DURING THAT FALL.
LAST NIGHT,
I COULDN'’T EVEN SLEEP
'’CAUSE I WAS
GETTING FLASHBACKS.
- '’CAUSE YOU WERE, LIKE,
TRAUMATIZED.
- YEAH. I'’M, LIKE, DROPPING.
- GOOD JOB, ROGER.
- I'’M A LITTLE TRAUMATIZED
OVER IT. I'’M SCARED.
LIKE, HE HONESTLY THOUGHT
I'’D BE BETTER AFTER IT,
BUT I WAS SHAKING.
LIKE, WHEN I LANDED,
I WAS, LIKE...
I'’M REALLY EXCITED TO TELL
NICOLE TONIGHT THAT I'’M ENGAGED,
AND I'’M SURE SHE'’LL BE EXCITED
TO HEAR IT,
BECAUSE SHE'’S BEEN WAITING
JUST AS LONG AS I HAVE.
[Lorenzo crying]
- OKAY, POOPERS.
- ALL RIGHT.
- LOVE YOU.
- HAVE A [bleep] TIME.
- I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- [whining]
DON'’T FORGET I'’M HERE.
- "DON'’T FORGET I'’M HERE."
- YEAH, I'’M GONNA BRING A GIRL
BACK AND SAY,
"OH, I FORGOT YOU WERE HERE."
- THEY KNOW THAT, YOU KNOW,
THEY CAN'’T TALK TO GIRLS
OR ANYTHING.
THEY ALREADY KNOW THE RULES.
SO, JUST GO OUT AND HAVE FUN,
BUT DON'’T CROSS THE LINE.
- LET'’S GET [bleep] UP.
- LET'’S GET SOMETHING STARTED.
YUCK YUCK, YUCK YUCK YUCK.
YUCK YUCK.
- THEY'’RE SO OLD, THEY DON'’T
EVEN WANT TO GO OUT.
- [laughs]
- FOR SURE.
- WHAT'’S WRONG WITH IT?
I THINK IT LOOKS CUTE.
- I LOOK LIKE A FAT BANANA.
- [laughs]
all: DADCHELOR PARTY! DADCHELOR
PARTY! DADCHELOR PARTY!
[cheering]
- THIS IS GONNA BE
A LONG NIGHT.
all: OH!
[upbeat music]
- OH, MY GOSH,
I'’M SO NERVOUS.
♪♪
MAJOR BUBBLE GUTS.
- FEEL BETTER?
- YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST SITTING HERE.
♪ ♪
- I HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
I'’M REALLY NERVOUS.
- WHY?
- I'’M, LIKE, SHAKING.
- HE ASKED YOU?
- MM-HMM.
- WHY DIDN'’T YOU TELL ME?
- '’CAUSE I DIDN'’T WANT TO RUIN
JIONNI'’S NIGHT.
- I'’M SO HAPPY FOR JENNI
THAT SHE'’S ENGAGED,
BUT I'’M PISSED BECAUSE SHE
DIDN'’T TELL ME. LIKE, BITCH.
- SORRY, BOO, I WANTED TO--
- THIS IS, LIKE, BIG NEWS.
- I WANTED TO DO IT
IN FACE TO FACE,
AND THEN,
WITH THE DADCHELOR PARTY,
AND THE BOYS GETTING DRUNK--
- OH, WHO GIVES A [bleep]?
JUST TELL ME.
- HONESTLY, I DIDN'’T EXPECT IT
DURING SKYDIVING.
- I DID.
- YOU'’RE THE FIRST PERSON
I LEGIT TOLD.
I HAVEN'’T TOLD MY DAD
OR ANYONE.
- WHY?
- I WANTED YOU TO BE THE FIRST.
- DUDE, THAT'’S, LIKE,
NOT EVEN REAL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU'’RE IN THE CLUB.
- [laughs]
THIS IS A CLUB?
- I LOVE IT.
- I'’M EXCITED TO BE ENGAGED
AT THE SAME TIME AS NICOLE.
- NOW I FEEL LIKE
SHE'’S IN MY BOAT.
- THE FIANCEE BOAT?
- YEAH. WE'’RE GETTING MARRIED.
- LOOK OUT.
- WE NEED TO CELEBRATE.
- THAT'’S WHY I GOT
THE CHAMPAGNE.
- WE GOTTA GO OUT NEXT WEEK.
- I'’M DOWN.
- I'’M GONNA HEAT UP MILK.
- OH, IT'’S A BABY.
- I CALLED IT.
I KNEW HE'’D PROPOSE.
all: DADCHELOR PARTY, DADCHELOR
PARTY, DADCHELOR PARTY,
DADCHELOR PARTY!
- WE ARE GOING TO PALS CABIN
FIRST.
MY BUDDIES WANT ME TO TAKE
A LOT OF SHOTS.
I'’M TRYING TO BE CONSERVATIVE,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I WANT TO GET DRUNK,
I WANT TO HAVE FUN,
BUT I CAN'’T OVERDO IT.
- IS HE THE FIRST ONE OF YOU
GUYS TO, LIKE, HAVE A KID?
- OH, YEAH. YEAH.
- YEAH.
NICHOLS'’ IS ON THE WAY.
- TREES MIGHT HAVE A COUPLE
HE DON'’T KNOW ABOUT.
- I'’M WELL OVER A DECADE OLDER
THAN HIM AND HE STILL PASSED ME.
I STILL DON'’T HAVE A KID.
- SO, WERE YOU A LITTLE UPSET
ABOUT THE BABY,
LIKE, COMING EARLY?
- NOT AT ALL.
- WHEN IT'’S TIME, IT'’S TIME.
- NO, HE'’S NOT UPSET.
- I WAS READY.
- IT CAME A LITTLE EARLY,
THOUGH.
WE WERE EXPECTING SEPTEMBER
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
- FATE, BABY.
- HE'’S JUST TRYING TO CASH IN ON
HIS TWO MORE NIGHTS OUT A WEEK.
- I'’M A LITTLE UPSET.
- YOU OWE HIM TWO.
- YOU OWE ME TWO!
- HERE'’S TO JIONNI'’S
DADCHELOR PARTY.
- TO LITTLE LORENZO.
- TO LORENZO, THE SECOND TINIEST
MAN I'’VE EVER MET IN MY LIFE.
[laughter]
- CONGRATS.
- HERE WE GO. IT'’S JUST
BEGINNING. THE SHOTS ARE COMING.
IT'’S HARD TO SAY NO
TO MY FRIENDS,
'’CAUSE THEY JUST RIDE YOU.
YO, FOR REAL, GUYS, THANKS--
HONESTLY, I'’M BEING SERIOUS--
THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
YOU GUYS ARE MY--MY FRIENDS.
YOU GUYS--YOU GUYS
LEFT THE GIRLS AT HOME.
WE'’RE DOING IT TONIGHT.
- I LEFT MY GIRL
WITH YOUR GIRL.
- THAT'’S RIGHT.
- ANYTIME.
- AND THEY'’RE HOME.
HEY, GUYS, SERIOUSLY,
THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
I'’M BEING SERIOUS.
- OF COURSE.
- I'’M GONNA PUT MY ONESIE ON.
- PEEK-A-BOO PLAY.
[laughs]
- I LOOK LIKE A FAT BANANA.
- [laughs]
- THIS IS BULL[bleep].
- LET ME SEE.
- COME ON, DUDE.
- WHAT'’S WRONG WITH IT?
I THINK IT LOOKS CUTE.
- I LOOK LIKE A FAT BANANA.
- [laughs]
HER BOOBS LOOK ENORMOUS.
THE ONLY THING FAT ABOUT NICOLE
IS HER TA-TAS.
- NOW, YOU GO GET YOURS ON.
- WHO CAN'’T HELP BUT LAUGH
AT THAT?
- IT DOESN'’T SAY HOW MUCH
THE DRESSES ARE.
YOU LOOK CUTER.
- DO I?
- YEAH.
- I'’D SWITCH WITH YOU
IF I COULD FIT IN THAT ONE.
- I LOOK LIKE A BANANA.
WE'’LL POP SOME BUBBLY.
POP IT OVER HERE,
BY THE BABY BOTTLES.
- ROGER ALMOST PUT
A HOLE IN THE WALL YESTERDAY
WITH THE ONE HE POPPED
IN THE BEDROOM,
BEFORE HE GOT NAKED ON THE RUG
AND PUT STRAWBERRIES AND--
- UHH!
- CHOCOLATES ON HIS CHEST.
HE TRIED TO MAKE AN ARROW,
GOING DOWN HIS--
- LIKE, BEING SEXY?
- YEAH.
- AND HORNY?
- IT WAS SO BAD.
I COULDN'’T STOP LAUGHING.
- UHH!
- ALL RIGHT, LET'’S MAKE FUN
OF EVERYONE IN THE MAGAZINES.
I THINK
THAT'’S GONNA BE BETTER.
- I BET YOU I WON'’T BE
A BRIDEZILLA.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- I SWEAR. I'’M GONNA BE SO NICE.
- YOU'’RE A BABYZILLA.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
- I'’M NOT.
- I'’M STILL IN SHOCK.
I STILL CAN'’T BELIEVE
I'’M ENGAGED.
- I CAN. I'’VE BEEN WAITING FOR
THIS MOMENT MORE THAN YOU HAVE.
- I KNOW.
- EWW.
[cork pops]
AAH!
OH, I HATE LOUD NOISES.
- I FEEL LIKE THIS IS OLD TIMES
RIGHT NOW,
DRINKING WITH MY BOO
ON THE COUCH,
SNUGGLING,
AND GIRL TALK.
- LOVE IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANKS.
- FINALLY.
- WHY DO YOU SAY IT
WITH SUCH HATE?
- CONGRATULATIONS!
- [laughs]
- I'’M NOT A HATER.
- NO.
- WE'’RE BOTH ENGAGED.
- MM-HMM.
- OH, YOU CALLING WIFEY?
- YEAH. I'’M GONNA
CHECK UP ON THE KID.
- SHOULDN'’T LORENZO
BE ASLEEP?
- WHAT, DOES HE GO OUT,
EVERY TWO, THREE HOURS
OR SOMETHING, RIGHT?
- ARE YOU SLEEPING?
- YOU ARE A PAIN IN THE ASS.
- HEY, DAD, WHERE YOU STAYING?
- DAD, WHERE ARE YOU STAYING?
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- WE'’RE AT DINNER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
JUST CHILLIN'’ WITH JENNI.
- HOW'’S LORENZO?
- HE'’S GOOD. HE'’S SLEEPING.
ARE YOU HAVING FUN?
- YEAH.
WE'’RE GONNA, UH,
GO TO 4SIXTY6 NOW.
- WELL, HAVE FUN, WHATEVER.
- ALL RIGHT.
DO YOU WANT ME TO
TELL ROGER YOU SAID HI?
I CAN'’T FIND HIM.
HE LEFT WITH A WAITRESS.
- THAT'’S FUNNY.
- JIONNI,
PUT YOUR SHIRT BACK ON.
[laughter]
- WHATEVER. YOU GUYS ARE
PISSING ME OFF. GOOD-BYE.
[phone beeps]
[silence]
- WAS THAT A HALL PASS?
all: OH!
[overlapping chatter]
- THIS IS GONNA BE
A LONG NIGHT.
WE'’RE JUST BOYS BEING BOYS.
I MEAN, COME ON.
HOW MUCH TROUBLE COULD WE
POSSIBLY GET INTO?
IT'’S ONLY A DADCHELOR PARTY.
[cheering]
- IT SHOULD BE A GOOD NIGHT!
- BOTTOMS UP, KIDS.
- I DON'’T KNOW WHY THESE
THREE SICK INDIVIDUALS
WANT TO TRY BREAST MILK.
- UHH! IT TASTES
LIKE [bleep].
[laughter]
I'’LL NEVER DO THAT AGAIN.
[upbeat music]
- I'’M WALKING IN WITH
ALL MY FRIENDS RIGHT NOW.
THERE'’S GONNA BE DRINKING,
THERE'’S GONNA BE GREAT MUSIC,
THERE'’S GONNA BE PARTYING.
WE'’RE GONNA HAVE
AN AWESOME TIME.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I'’M GONNA GET THIS PARTY
GOING!
- OH, [bleep]!
IT'’S GONNA GET REAL LOUD!
- OH!
- ONE MORE BOTTLE!
[cheering]
- WE'’RE PICKING ROGER UP.
WE'’RE YELLING,
"LOOK AT THE OLD GUY!
"LOOK AT HIM!
HE'’S STANDING WITH US!
OUR FATHER IS WITH US!"
HE'’S LAUGHING.
HE'’S DOING THIS [bleep].
HE DON'’T KNOW
WHAT HE'’S [bleep] DOING.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK THE GIRLS
ARE DOING RIGHT NOW?
- EITHER SLEEPING
OR WATCHING THE BABY.
- I DON'’T THINK THEY'’RE
GOING TO BED UNTIL WE GET HOME.
- THEY'’RE PROBABLY TALKING
[bleep] ABOUT US!
- WHAT TIME YOU WANT TO
GET UP?
- IT DEPENDS ON HOW
"WHITE GIRL" THE GUYS ARE.
- I HOPE HE'’S NOT HUNG OVER.
- YEAH, WE'’LL MAKE THEM
MAKE US BREAKFAST.
- LET'’S SLEEP IN OUR BED--
MY BED,
AND THEN THE BOYS
CAN SLEEP ON THE COUCH,
'’CAUSE THEY'’RE PROBABLY
GONNA BE DRUNK.
- OKAY.
- I'’M VERY HAPPY THAT JENNI'’S
SPENDING THE NIGHT,
BECAUSE NOW I CAN CATCH UP
ON MY SLEEP
AND JENNI CAN TAKE CARE OF
LORENZO.
MY BED IS COMFY, KIND OF.
AND THERE'’S NO, LIKE,
SEMEN,
'’CAUSE WE HAVEN'’T HAD SEX
IN NINE MONTHS.
- GOOD NIGHT.
I'’M GLAD YOU TRUST ME
WITH HIM.
- MM-HMM.
- IT MEANS A LOT. MWAH!
I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
ARE YOU COMFY?
- REALLY COMFY.
[dance music]
♪ ♪
- CAN YOU [bleep] CATCH UP?
- BRO, THIS IS ALL VODKA
RIGHT HERE.
- SO, TASTE THIS.
IT'’S MY SECOND ONE!
- I FEEL LIKE, YOU KNOW,
I'’M DEFINITELY THE OLDER GUY
TONIGHT.
THEY'’RE ALL YOUNGER THAN ME,
SO I DO KIND OF FEEL LIKE A DAD
WITH THE KIDS
AT THE KIDS'’ TABLE.
- WHOA!
♪ ♪
- WHAT TIME DO YOU WANT TO
ROLL OUT OF HERE?
- I'’M READY WHENEVER.
THIS DADCHELOR PARTY
WAS SUCCESSFUL.
WE KILLED IT.
BUT...IT'’S GETTING LATE.
ROGER'’S YAWNING.
THE OLD MAN'’S TIRED.
- WE'’RE ROLLING OUT!
- I MISS LORENZO.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'’S TIME TO GO.
[upbeat music]
OH, I LOVE THIS [bleep].
♪ ♪
- HOLY [bleep], WE'’RE HERE.
THANK YOU, SIR.
- OKAY, ROG.
- CHARLIE, A PLEASURE,
MAN, A PLEASURE.
I LIKE YOU. YOU'’RE GOOD PEOPLE.
YOU'’RE GOOD PEOPLE.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[clears throat]
- YO, MY GIRL'’S NOT DOWN HERE,
YOU DIP[bleep].
- YES, SHE IS.
THEY'’RE SLEEPING.
- OH, MY GIRL IS DOWN HERE!
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- [grunts]
- OW!
- DID YOU HAVE FUN?
- WE HAD FUN.
I THINK I'’M GOOD FOR ABOUT
ANOTHER YEAR FOR GOING OUT.
I DON'’T EVER NEED TO GO OUT
AGAIN.
- JENNI AND ROGER
ARE ENGAGED!
- THEY ARE?
- SHH!
- MM-HMM.
- WHEN? WHAT? WHAT?
- TOLD YOU!
- HOW'’D HE COME TO MY DADCHELOR
PARTY AND NOT TELL ME?
[bleep]!
- FOR ONE REASON
AND ONE REASON ONLY.
I WENT OUT WITH YOU
AND ALL YOUR FRIENDS TONIGHT.
IT WAS HIS NIGHT. YOU KNOW,
IT'’S A DADCHELOR PARTY.
IT'’S NOT ABOUT ROGER.
IT'’S NOT ABOUT JENNI.
IT'’S A DADCHELOR PARTY.
HE'’S THE DAD.
IT'’S ABOUT HIM.
SO, I DIDN'’T WANT TO TAKE
ANYTHING AWAY FROM HIS NIGHT.
- YOU COULD HAVE WHISPERED IT.
WHEN? HOW?
- SKYDIVING!
TOLD YOU!
- OH, MAN.
BRING IT HERE, ROG.
I'’M PROUD OF ROGER.
I'’M HAPPY FOR JENNI.
IT'’S ABOUT TIME.
YOU CAN UPSTAGE THAT, MAN.
IT'’S IMPORTANT [bleep].
- IT IS IMPORTANT [bleep],
BUT IT DOESN'’T GET ANY MORE
IMPORTANT THAN THIS.
IT'’S JUST THE FOUR OF US
HERE.
[Lorenzo crying]
- HOW DID YOU--WAIT.
- WE'’LL TALK OVER BREAKFAST.
- I COME HOME TO
MY LITTLE BABY LORENZO.
I'’M STARVING.
- YOU WANT ME
TO BREASTFEED YOU?
- MY GOD, I HATE YOU GUYS
AT THIS HOUR.
- [laughs]
- I JUST WANT TO SLEEP.
[whimsical music]
- WHAT THE [bleep] DID I DO?
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- HUNG OVER.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
- I EITHER GOTTA [bleep]
OR THROW UP.
MAYBE [bleep] AND THROW UP.
I DON'’T KNOW YET.
THIS IS
MY FIRST DAD HANGOVER.
IS THIS WHAT IT'’S SUPPOSED TO
FEEL LIKE?
I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE [bleep].
OH, DEAR GOD.
[upbeat music]
[crash]
- OH!
OH, MY GOD!
DID I REALLY JUST DO THAT?
JIONNI.
- YEAH?
- [laughing]
I BACKED INTO YOUR CAR.
- WHAT'’S WRONG WITH YOU?
- OH, MY GOD, SHE'’S GONNA
DEFLATE HER [bleep].
- OW!
[laughter]
- ♪ I WANT TO BUILD
A HAPPY HOME ♪
♪A HOME FOR YOU AND ME ♪
- HE LOOKS LIKE ME.
- HE LOOKS LIKE YOU TODAY.
- AH, HE LOOKS LIKE ME TODAY.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- EWW!
- [laughs]
- DO I LOOK LIKE YOUR SON?
[laughter]
- I FEEL LIKE ROGER'’S MORE HUNG
OVER THAN JIONNI RIGHT NOW,
JUST BECAUSE ROGER'’S,
LIKE, 50 YEARS OLD.
HE CAN'’T DRINK LIKE
HE USED TO.
- ROGER, YOU WANT TO TRY
BREAST MILK?
OH, I SHOULD HAVE
PUT THAT IN YOUR COFFEE.
- I'’LL DO ANYTHING.
I'’LL PROBABLY THROW UP, BUT--
- HE SAID HE'’LL HAVE IT.
- I'’LL PROBABLY THROW UP, BUT IT
WON'’T BE FROM THE BREAST MILK.
IT'’LL BE FROM
MY SEVERE HANGOVER.
HAS JIONNI TRIED IT YET?
- YEAH.
- NO, YOU HAVEN'’T.
- IF ROGER TRIES IT RIGHT NOW,
WILL YOU JUST TRY IT?
- NOPE.
- WHY? YOU'’RE SUCH A [bleep].
- HE THINKS IT'’S GROSS.
- THE LAST TIME YOU GUYS
MADE ME DO SOMETHING
I DIDN'’T WANT TO DO,
A DUDE WAS DRY-HUMPING ME.
I DON'’T KNOW WHY THESE
THREE SICK INDIVIDUALS
WANT TO TRY BREAST MILK.
I JUST DON'’T WANT TO TRY IT.
- WOULD YOU GUYS PREFER 9/14
OR 9/6?
- I LIKE A VINTAGE.
- YOU LIKE A VINTAGE? 9/6 IT IS.
- DON'’T HEAT IT TO WHERE
IT'’S REALLY HOT, THOUGH.
- I'’M NOT MAKING IT WARM.
I'’M DEFROSTING IT.
- OH, CAN'’T--CAN'’T JIONNI
AND I JUST KNEEL DOWN
AND YOU JUST SQUIRT IT IN?
SQUIRT IT AT US?
- EWW! THAT'’S SEXUAL THEN.
[laughter]
- ALL RIGHT, BADASSES.
- IS IT WARM?
- EWW!
TO MY [bleep].
[glasses clink]
- WHICH [bleep] IS THIS?
I HOPE THIS IS THE LEFT.
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- BOTTOMS UP, KIDS.
THAT WAS, LIKE, NOTHING.
- [bleep].
- [bleep] WITH YOU.
- AM I THE ONLY ONE
THAT DID IT?
- YEAH!
- [laughs] YEAH.
- I DON'’T CARE.
- COME ON. I THOUGHT
YOU WERE SO TOUGH.
- THAT'’S--YOU JUST
ALLOWED ANOTHER MAN
TO DRINK YOUR OWN WOMAN'’S
BREAST MILK BEFORE YOU.
- YOU KEEP TALKIN'’ ALL THAT
[bleep]. GO AHEAD.
- YOU GO AHEAD.
- I DIDN'’T SAY
I WANTED TO DO IT.
- GO AHEAD.
HE JUST DID IT.
- IT'’S CLUMPY GOING DOWN.
- COME ON. WHERE ARE YOU?
- SHUT UP.
- IT'’S GOT CLUMPS IN IT.
IT'’S VERY CLUMPY.
- COME ON, JENNI.
- WELL--
- BACK UP--
- HE'’S A LIAR.
- JENNI, BACK UP THE MOUTH.
LET'’S GO.
- IT WAS LIKE CHUGGING
MASHED POTATOES.
- JENNI, BACK IT UP. LET'’S GO.
- YOU BACK IT UP.
- I SAID I DIDN'’T WANT TO DO IT.
- BABE, YOU HAVE TO DO IT.
ROGER, COUNT.
- ONE. ON THREE?
- YEAH. BABE, YOU HAVE TO,
FOR LORENZO.
- ONE, TWO, THREE, GO.
- NO, TIP IT UP.
- TIP IT!
- UHH!
IT TASTES LIKE [bleep].
[laughter]
SO, IN THE LAST NINE MONTHS,
THE ONLY SHOT THAT I'’VE TAKEN
IS MY OWN BREAST MILK,
AND SOMETHING IS DISGUSTING
ABOUT THAT.
- IT'’S KIND OF WEIRD,
DRY, STALE [bleep].
- IT TASTED LIKE [bleep].
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
I'’M OUT.
- HEY, GUYS, THANK--
THANKS FOR THE SHOT.
- OF COURSE.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
SKIM OR LOW-FAT OR--?
- I DON'’T KNOW,
BUT MY LIPS ARE TINGLING.
- [belches]
- [groans] I DON'’T LIKE IT.
I'’LL NEVER DO THAT AGAIN.
HOW DO YOU DRINK THAT?
- SOMEHOW I FEEL LIKE
WE'’RE CLOSER NOW, NICOLE.
[whistling sound effect]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- WHAT'’D YOU GET?
- SOME LUNCH.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- GROCERY SHOPPING.
- OH.
- TOOTLES.
- BYE.
GET, LIKE, SNACKS.
- SO, TODAY I NEED TO GO
GROCERY SHOPPING
BECAUSE WE HAVE NOTHING
IN THE HOUSE,
AND I FEEL LIKE IT'’S MY DUTY
AS A WIFE
TO PROVIDE GROCERIES
FOR MY FAMILY.
WHAT THE [bleep]?
[crash]
OH!
OH, MY GOD!
DID I REALLY JUST DO THAT?
[laughs]
OH, [bleep].
OH, MY GOD,
HE'’S GONNA KILL ME.
MOTHER[bleep].
OH, GOD!
[laughs]
AT THIS POINT, I JUST FEEL LIKE
A [bleep] DUMBASS.
I DON'’T EVEN HAVE
PREGNANT BRAIN.
I HAVE, LIKE,
A MUSH BRAIN.
[bleep] BALLS.
[laughs and snorts]
AW.
[laughs] MAN.
OH, MY GOD,
HE'’S GONNA KILL ME.
OH, [bleep].
THIS IS, LIKE, THE SECOND TIME
THAT I HIT HIS CAR,
AND I JUST DON'’T
WANT HIM MAD AT ME.
IT'’S LIKE A SIMPLE ACCIDENT.
JIONNI.
[whistling sound effect]
- YEAH?
- I JUST DID A BOO-BOO.
- WHAT?
- [laughing]
[snorts]
I BACKED INTO YOUR CAR.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT'’S WRONG WITH YOU?
- [laughs]
- IT'’S THE THIRD ACCIDENT
YOU'’VE GOTTEN IN WITH MY CAR.
- I DIDN'’T SEE IT.
I'’LL BUY YOU A NEW ONE.
- YEAH, YOU'’LL BUY--MY ASS,
YOU'’LL BUY ME A NEW ONE.
OH, MY GOD.
- SHOULD I JUST
LEAVE THIS HERE?
- GO, LEAVE, GET OUT.
LEAVE.
- DO YOU WANT ME
TO LEAVE IT HERE?
- LEAVE. KEEP THAT HERE.
[clears throat]
GET OUT.
- CAN YOU MOVE YOUR CAR?
- WHAT'’S THE DIFFERENCE NOW?
JUST KEEP GOING.
- I'’M GONNA BUY YOU
SOMETHING SPECIAL, OKAY?
- I DON'’T WANT NOTHING.
- I'’M SORRY. I LOVE YOU.
- [bleep].
- OH, [bleep].
[club music]
- SHE'’S LIKE...
NICOLE IS LITERALLY
RAPING EVERYONE.
- I'’M SURPRISED
I DIDN'’T, LIKE,
TEAR MY VAGINA OPEN,
WITH MY STITCHES.
- OH!
- ♪ GET ALL MY HIGHS
WITH YOU ♪
♪ I WON'’T MIND,
I WON'’T MIND... ♪
- OH, MY GOD,
I THINK I HAVE TO POOP.
- GOOD FOR YOU.
- I KNOW, IT'’S NASTY.
- ME AND NICOLE ARE ON OUR WAY
TO MANDEE'’S TO GET OUR SHOP ON.
I WOULD LIKE TO GET A SEXY DRESS
FOR GIRLS'’ NIGHT OUT.
- I WANT TO GET A SKIRT
AND, LIKE, SOMETHING THAT
I'’M GONNA WEAR TO THE CLUB.
- I FEEL LIKE GIRLS'’ NIGHT OUT
IS GONNA BE EXCITING.
SO MUCH BETTER
THAN THE GUYS'’ NIGHT.
- MM-HMM.
THIS ONE'’S NICE.
NO.
- [laughs]
- THESE ARE CUTE.
HMM?
- ARE WE ALLOWED TO DO
THE SAME, OR WHAT?
- YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT--
- LOOK AT THIS.
- I WOULDN'’T EVEN--
I THINK I'’M A MEDIUM.
- ME TOO.
ONLY BECAUSE MY BOOBS
WILL NOT FIT A SMALL.
- I'’M BREASTFEEDING.
- YEAH.
- I WANT TO WEAR, LIKE,
A TIGHT, BANDAGE DRESS.
- I DON'’T KNOW WHAT I WOULD
WEAR THIS FOR, BUT I LIKE IT.
- IT SMELLS LIKE SKUNK.
- WHOA!
- CAN I TRY THEM ON?
- YES.
- SO, NOW THAT I DON'’T HAVE
THE PREGNANT BELLY,
I'’M DOWN TO TRY DRESSES,
BECAUSE NOW I FEEL GOOD LOOKING.
KIND OF.
I'’M SO FAT.
- NO, YOU'’RE NOT.
- OH, I GOTTA [bleep].
- LET ME SEE.
- I COULD GET, LIKE,
A BODYSUIT.
- THAT'’S HOT.
YOU LOOK BADASS.
NICOLE IS LOOKING AMAZING
IN ALL HER OUTFITS.
- LIE.
- I CAN'’T BELIEVE--OH!
- I GOT THIS LOOSE SKIN THAT'’S
DISGUSTING, AND I HATE IT,
AND I FEEL LIKE IT SHOWS
IN EVERYTHING THAT I WEAR.
- SHE'’S MENTAL.
- YOU HAVEN'’T SEEN ME NAKED.
- NOT THAT I WANT TO,
BUT I'’M SURE YOU LOOK FINE.
- [groans]
- WILL YOU GET WHITE GIRL--
HAND GIRL WITH ME?
- YEAH.
- I'’M REALLY EXCITED.
LIKE, I WANT TO, LIKE,
BLACK OUT.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- I HOPE DEENA WILL COME.
- BITCH BETTER.
SHE BETTER SEPARATE US OUT
FROM CHRIS FOR ONE NIGHT.
- OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
SHE'’LL PROBABLY MAKE HIM GO.
- [laughs]
- GIRLS'’ NIGHT OUT, I KNOW
WE'’RE DEFINITELY GONNA GO HARD.
I MEAN, ALL OF OUR GIRLFRIENDS
ARE CRAZY,
AND I JUST WANT TO, LIKE,
ENJOY MY NIGHT,
BECAUSE
I HAVEN'’T REALLY DRANK
OR EVEN WENT OUT WITH
MY FRIENDS IN TEN MONTHS.
- I HAVEN'’T BEEN HANGING OUT
WITH MY MEATBALLS.
WHEN ARE YOU CALLING DEENA?
WHEN YOU GET BACK?
- OH, RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO.
I'’M GONNA TELL HER,
"DON'’T BE BORING!"
- YES.
[phone ringing]
- [man'’s voice] HELLO?
- DEENA?
[both laugh]
WHO'’S THIS?
- IT'’S JOHN.
- WHO'’S JOHN? BYE.
[both laugh]
WHAT THE [bleep]?
- I THINK IT WAS CHRIS,
JOKING AROUND WITH YOU.
- OH, REALLY?
- "WHO'’S JOHN? BYE."
- WILL YOU CALL?
WHO THE [bleep] IS JOHN?
- [laughs]
- MAYBE IT'’S HER DAD.
- I DON'’T THINK
THAT'’S HER DAD'’S NAME.
HE SOUNDED YOUNG.
HE DIDN'’T SOUND LIKE A DAD.
[phone ringing]
- I'’M GONNA SAY, "CHRIS."
- SAY, "SHUT UP, CHRIS."
- HELLO?
- DEENA!
- HEY!
- IT'’S ME
AND NICOLE ON THE PHONE.
- WHO WAS JUST--WHO ANSWERED
YOUR PHONE?
- CHRIS.
IT WAS CHRIS.
IT CAME UP BLOCKED, SO HE
JUST SAID A RANDOM NAME.
- OH.
- IT SCARED ME.
- [laughs]
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING SATURDAY?
I'’M HAVING A GIRLS'’ NIGHT AND
YOU HAVE TO COME WITHOUT CHRIS.
SORRY.
- [laughs]
- NO. NO, SHE CAN'’T GO.
- SHUT UP!
- CAN YOU COME?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
- SO, WE'’RE MAKING SURE
THAT DEENA DOESN'’T BRING CHRIS
THIS WEEKEND,
ONLY BECAUSE IT IS GIRLS'’ NIGHT
AND NO GUYS ALLOWED.
- AND THEY'’RE--THEY'’RE ATTACHED
AT THE ASS,
SO WE JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
IT'’S JUST GIRLS.
- [laughs] YES.
NOT EVEN THE HIP? THE ASS?
- YEAH. THE ASS[bleep].
- I CAN'’T WAIT TO SEE NICOLE
DRUNK AGAIN.
I HAVEN'’T SEEN THAT
IN A WHILE.
- WAH-WAH-WAH-WAH-WAH-WAH.
- YEAH, ME EITHER.
I WANT HER
FALLING OFF THE STAGE.
- GOD. I'’M A MOM NOW.
- OH, GOD.
- YOU'’RE STILL ALLOWED.
- I'’VE SEEN PLENTY OF MOMS
FALLING OFF THE STAGE.
- YEAH. ALL RIGHT,
WE'’LL SEE YOU SATURDAY.
- ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU. BYE.
THE LAST TIME
I HAD A MEATBALL NIGHT
WAS PROBABLY THE LAST TIME
I WAS AT THE SHORE,
WHEN I WASN'’T PREGNANT,
SO I'’M READY.
ARE WE GONNA PRE-GAME?
- I HOPE.
- I REALLY DON'’T
WANT TO BLACK OUT.
- WHAT? WHY?
- JIONNI WILL BE SO UPSET,
I FEEL.
- YOU'’RE A GROWN-ASS WOMAN
THAT PAYS HIS BILLS.
- OW! WHAT ARE THESE PAINS
IN MY ASS?
[laughs]
- DID YOU HAVE [bleep] SEX?
- NO, I SWEAR.
NO, I SWEAR.
I'’M SCARED TO TAKE A POOP
BECAUSE MY BUTT HURTS
AND I DON'’T KNOW WHY
MY BUTT HURTS,
BECAUSE THE BABY DIDN'’T
COME OUT OF MY BUTTHOLE.
OH, MY GOD, I THINK
I HAVE TO POOP.
- GOOD!
GO TAKE A TURTLE OR WHATEVER.
- OH, MAN.
YOU KNOW, EVERYTHING
JUST HURTS DOWN THERE,
SO I'’M SCARED TO PEE
AND POOP.
IT'’S THE WORST.
- WHO HAD MEXICAN
LAST NIGHT?
- ME!
- [laughs]
- DON'’T LEAVE ME.
- DON'’T LEAVE ME!
- DON'’T LEAVE!
- TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT
WHERE I JUST MADE UP
FOR EVERYTHING
THAT I MISSED OUT ON.
I'’M A GOOD FIANCEE
AND I'’M A MOM!
[overlapping shouting]
I'’M A GOOD MOM!
- ♪ CERTAIN THINGS CAN'’T
END THIS WAY ♪
- WHAT'’S YOUR PLAN
FOR TONIGHT?
- WE'’RE GOING TO DINNER
AND THEN GOING TO A CLUB.
- A CLUB?
- YOU WENT TO A CLUB.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I'’M SO EXCITED
FOR GIRLS'’ NIGHT,
AND I CANNOT WAIT TO DRINK
WITH MY FRIENDS.
I CAN'’T WAIT TO GO CRAZY,
BECAUSE I THINK I DESERVE IT.
I JUST WANT TO DANCE
AND HEAR MUSIC.
- ARE YOU GONNA BE GOOD?
- YES.
- OKAY.
- NO CUCA OR CARTWHEELS.
[Lorenzo fusses]
I'’M A MOM NOW.
- ME AND LORENZO ARE GONNA BE
HOME WAITING FOR YOU.
- I'’LL MISS YOU.
- YOU BETTER.
[upbeat music]
- ♪ I DON'’T KNOW ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ BUT I'’M READY TO GO ♪
♪GO, GO, GO ♪
♪THE DRIVER'’S WAITING
OUT FRONT ♪
♪ SO LET'’S GET ON
WITH THE SHOW ♪
- IT'’S BEEN SO LONG SINCE
I'’VE SEEN NICOLE DRUNK.
I'’M EXCITED.
- SERIOUSLY.
- SHE'’S DUE.
- YEAH.
I'’M REALLY EXCITED.
- IT'’S HER NIGHT.
WHATEVER WE CAN DO TO FORCE
THE SHOTS DOWN HER THROAT.
- DO YOU THINK SHE'’S GONNA BE,
LIKE, AN OLD MEATBALL?
- I HOPE SO. I WANT TO BE ABLE
TO CARRY HER HOME.
I MISS THOSE NIGHTS, CARRYING
YOU HOME AND CARRYING HER HOME.
- YOU MISS '’EM? SEE?
- I KNOW!
- YOU MISS WHAT YOU DON'’T HAVE
ANYMORE.
- I KNOW.
I REALLY DO. YEAH.
- ♪ ARE YOU READY
FOR A GOOD TIME? ♪
- WHOO! WE'’RE HERE.
[doorbell rings]
- HELLO?
FOR GIRLS'’ NIGHT,
JENNI'’S COMING WITH LAURA...
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
AND DEENA.
SO HAPPY YOU CAME.
AND THEN MY BEST FRIENDS
FROM HOME, FRANKIE, NINA...
OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS
LOOK SO PRETTY.
AND RYDER.
MWAH!
- ARE YOU EXCITED TO GO OUT?
- YEAH.
- YOU GUYS WANT A GLASS
WHILE YOU'’RE HERE?
- WE'’RE ALL GONNA FALL ASLEEP
IN THE LIMO, THOUGH.
- LISTEN, JUST BECAUSE
YOU HAVE A BABY
DOESN'’T MEAN YOU CAN'’T
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
- I KNOW. I DON'’T WANT TO
DO ANY SHOTS. MAYBE LIKE ONE.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
SAY BYE.
CAREFUL. HAVE FUN.
- BYE, BABY.
- GIVE HIM ANOTHER KISS.
- CAN I SEE HIM?
- I SO MISS YOU.
SO JIONNI AND LORENZO
HEAD DOWNSTAIRS
SO THEY CAN START
THEIR BOYS'’ NIGHT,
AND I'’M GONNA MISS THEM
SO MUCH.
BUT RIGHT NOW,
I'’M JUST READY TO DANCE,
I'’M READY TO DRINK.
I'’M JUST, LIKE,
READY TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
LIMO'’S HERE.
WHERE'’S MY PUMP?
- YOU'’RE BRINGING YOUR BACKPACK?
- IT'’S HER PUMP.
[laughter]
- IT'’S, MY PUMP, ASS[bleep].
- ARE YOU REALLY PUMPING THEM?
- IT'’S A PUMP-N-GO.
- SEE, MY [bleep] HURT
IF I DON'’T.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- DO THEY SQUIRT MILK?
- ARE YOU TAKING CARE
OF US TONIGHT?
- YES, I AM.
- COOL. HI.
- MMM.
- MWAH.
- LOVE YA.
- COME ON, LET'’S GO.
- I KNOW.
- LET'’S GO.
TAKE IT OUT THERE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- SEE YA. OH. OH, [bleep].
- BYE. THANK YOU.
- BYE. YOU'’RE WELCOME.
BYE NOW. SEE YA.
THANK GOD.
THANK GOD I HAVE SONS.
- WHY?
- DEH-DEH-DEH-DEH-DEH-
DEH-DEH-DEH-DEH-DEH-DEH-DEH.
- I FEEL LIKE I'’M 16 AGAIN.
- YEAH, I'’M FEELING
A LITTLE BUZZED ALREADY.
- I AM TOO.
- [bleep].
OH, LOOK. CHAMPAGNE, VODKA.
- I'’LL HAVE A BEVERAGE.
[laughs]
- I MAKE '’EM STRONG.
- I'’M ALREADY SPILLING.
- I'’M DRUNK ALREADY.
- ARE YOU?
- YEAH.
- THERE YOU GO.
- I HAVE NO TOLERANCE,
AND I'’VE BEEN DRINKING
FOR, LIKE TEN YEARS.
TWO DRINKS, I'’M GONE.
- I-I THINK I CAN DRINK
LIKE A BOY.
- ME TOO.
- I CAN DRINK ANY GUY
UNDER THE TABLE.
- LET'’S DO SHOTS
OF PATRON!
- THESE TWO, BOTH OF THEM,
THEIR EYES SEPARATE,
AND THAT'’S WHEN YOU KNOW
THEY'’RE COMPLETELY GONE.
LIKE, THEY'’RE RUNNING
FROM EACH OTHER.
- YEAH, THAT'’S LIKE WHEN NICOLE,
LIKE, ISN'’T LOOKING.
- RUNNING.
- YEAH.
- BUT HER EYES ARE LIKE--
- SHE'’S LIKE, UH,
LOOKING ABOVE YOU.
- NONE OF THAT ANYMORE.
[cheering]
- HIGH FIVE!
- AAH!
[overlapping chatter]
- MEATBALL POWER!
- IT'’S LIKE A NIGHTCLUB IN THE--
- I [bleep] HATE THAT.
- BOOBIE.
- ARE YOU SHOWING IT?
- WHAT? YOU REALLY PUT THAT
GIANT THING ON YOUR BOOB?
- OH, MY GOD.
- ON THE WAY TO THE CLUB,
I THINK I SHOULD PUMP,
JUST SO MY BOOBS AREN'’T SORE
AND, YOU KNOW,
I'’M NOT LEAKING MILK
EVERYWHERE.
JENNI, DO YOU WANT TO
FEEL THE SUCTION?
- YEP.
- YOU HAVE TO TAKE
YOUR [bleep] OUT.
I WANT JENNI
TO TRY MY BREAST PUMP.
I WANT ALL THE GIRLS TO TRY
MY BREAST PUMP
TO KNOW THE PAIN
THAT I GO THROUGH
WITH MY NIPPLES BEING, LIKE,
PULLED ON EVERY THREE HOURS.
- OH, MY GOD. SHE'’S GONNA
DEFLATE HER [bleep].
- OW!
[laughter]
- DID IT HURT?
- NO, IT WAS, LIKE,
GNAWING ON MY NIPPLE.
- EWW!
- NOT AS FUN FOR ME!
ASS[bleep].
[upbeat music]
- ARE YOU GUYS READY
FOR THIS?
♪ ♪
- OH, MY GOD.
THAT REALLY JUST HAPPENED?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- "CHARLIE BIT ME!"
- TIME OUT. TIME OUT.
SHE JUST PUKED ALL OVER ME.
- WHO DID?
- NINA DID?
- YEAH.
- OH.
- PLEASE HELP ME.
I DON'’T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I DON'’T WANT TO LOOK.
- YOU SHOULD GO IN THE BATHROOM.
- I DON'’T WANT TO LOOK
AT IT.
IT SMELLS LIKE TUNA,
AND I DON'’T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- NIN!
NINA IS LEGIT THROWING UP
EVERYWHERE.
I'’M LIKE, OH, MY GOD.
- SHE DIDN'’T CARE.
IT'’S LIKE, TO THE POINT
WHERE SHE DOESN'’T EVEN KNOW
WHAT'’S GOING ON.
- I'’LL JUST GO HOME.
- IT WAS JUST COMING OUT.
I FEEL SO AWFUL FOR HER.
- SO BAD.
- BUT I'’M SO DRUNK,
ALL I CAN DO IS LAUGH.
I MEAN, WE'’VE ALL BEEN THERE,
SO--
- YEAH.
- IT IS WHAT IT IS.
[laughter]
- IT'’S ON ME!
- RYDER SMELLS LIKE TUNA!
RYDER SMELLS LIKE--
- YEAH, IT'’S ON MY SHOE!
- RYDER, I AM SO SORRY.
- NINA, DO YOU WANT TO
TAKE THE LIMO HOME?
- YEAH.
- GET HOME SAFE.
WE HAVE THE LIMO TAKING YOU
BACK, SO YOU'’RE GOOD.
- ONE DOWN ALREADY.
- THANK YOU.
I FEEL BAD, BUT YOU'’VE
GOT TO LAUGH AT IT.
- DID SOMEBODY GIVE HER NAPKINS?
- NO, SHE'’S ALL RIGHT.
- I HOPE THERE'’S NO HIP-HOP
IN THIS BITCH.
- LET ME CHECK.
- UHH! WHY ME?
- THERE'’S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY...
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- I SHOULDN'’T HAVE TO SHOW
ANYONE MY I.D.,
'’CAUSE
I GOT [bleep] PUKED ON.
[club music]
- I'’VE BASICALLY BEEN A SAINT
FOR, LIKE, TEN MONTHS,
SO I THINK THAT I TOTALLY
DESERVE TO GO CRAZY TONIGHT.
♪ ♪
[cheering]
♪♪
- I AM DEFINITELY BUZZED
AT THIS POINT.
- BUZZED? I'’M [bleep] DRUNK
- ♪READY, READY, READY,
READY, READY FOR YOU ♪
- ♪ I'’M READY FOR YOU ♪
- ♪ YEAH ♪
- ♪YOU KNOW I'’M READY, READY,
READY, READY, READY FOR YOU ♪
- ♪I'’M READY FOR YOU ♪
- IT'’S DEFINITELY
A [bleep] SHOW RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN, WE'’RE BASICALLY ALL
GONNA BLACK OUT. I KNOW IT.
- I'’M A MOM!
- GO, GO, GO, GO,
GO, GO, GO!
GET IT, GET IT!
OH, OH, OH!
- ♪ THAT'’S WHERE
I WANT TO BE ♪
♪ THAT'’S WHERE I WANT
TO BE ♪
♪ THAT'’S WHERE I WANT TO BE ♪
- I LOVE IT.
- ♪YOU KNOW I'’M READY ♪
♪ ♪
- ALL I REMEMBER AT THE CLUB
IS DANCING, GOING CRAZY,
DANCING ON YOU A LITTLE BIT.
- YOU WERE ON LAURA, LIKE,
YOU WANTED TO MAKE OUT,
AND LAURA'’S, YOU KNOW--
- PROBABLY SCARED
THE [bleep] OUT OF HER.
- YEAH. LAURA WAS
A LITTLE INTIMIDATED.
- ♪ LIKE, LIKE, LIKE,
LIKE IT HOT ♪
- SHE LOVES BLONDES.
- ♪ IF YOU LOVE IT,
BUT IF YOU LOVE IT ♪
- SHE'’S LIKE...
- ♪BUT IF YOU LOVE IT ♪
- SORRY, LAURA.
♪♪
- I LOVE YOU!
[laughter]
- ARE YOU TRYING
TO MAKE OUT?
- OKAY, THAT KIND OF PARTY.
THE MAKE-OUT KIND.
I MADE OUT WITH A GIRL BEFORE.
THERE'’S NO SHAME.
- ♪ WE IN THE CLUB,
TURN THE MUSIC UP ♪
♪ TURN IT UP ♪
♪YOU FEEL FIRE ♪
- I FEEL LIKE THE MEATBALLS
ARE IN FULL EFFECT TONIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE EVERYONE IS
AT THEIR "A" GAME RIGHT NOW.
NICOLE IS LITERALLY
RAPING EVERYONE.
LIKE, SHE IS ON LAURA,
SHE'’S ON DEENA,
SHE'’S ON RYDER,
SHE'’S ON ME.
SHE IS JUST--SHE'’S HAVING
AN AMAZING TIME.
- MY PLACENTA
IS GONNA FALL OUT!
- I'’LL CATCH IT!
- EWW!
LEGIT GIRLS'’ NIGHT.
IT'’S LIKE A GUIDETTE
SORORITY HOUSE RIGHT NOW.
- I'’M SURPRISED
I DIDN'’T, LIKE,
TEAR MY VAGINA OPEN,
WITH MY STITCHES.
- THANK GOD.
- GOOD NIGHT, EVERYONE.
- I'’M LEAVING, SMILING, SO I
FEEL LIKE I HAD A GOOD TIME.
- ME TOO, BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT WENT ON.
- ME EITHER.
- I GOT ABDUCTED.
- I AM ABDUCTED. YEAH.
- I THINK WE BOTH DID.
DON'’T LEAVE ME.
- DON'’T LEAVE ME!
- DON'’T LEAVE!
- JENNI! JENNI!
WHEN AM I GONNA
SEE YOU AGAIN, JENNI?
- JUST KISS ME
ONE LAST TIME.
- NO, JENNI!
OW, MY EARRING!
- [laughs]
- JENNI!
YOU PICK UP MY EARRING!
[bleep]!
- [laughs]
- YOU [bleep] BITCH.
- I LOVE YOU AND I'’LL [bleep]
SEE YOU IN TWO DAYS.
- ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
- BYE. PUMP AND DUMP!
- TONIGHT WAS DEFINITELY
THE NIGHT, YOU KNOW,
TO MAKE UP FOR NEVER BEING ABLE
TO DRINK WITH MY FRIENDS
AT THE SHORE, GOING CLUBBING,
GOING CRAZY.
TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT
WHERE I JUST MADE UP FOR
EVERYTHING THAT I MISSED OUT ON.
BUT I KNOW JIONNI'’S GONNA BE
VERY PISSED OFF AT ME.
I'’M A GOOD FIANCEE
AND I'’M A MOM!
[overlapping shouting]
I'’M A GOOD MOM!
- NICOLE IS ON HER DEATHBED,
JENNI'’S ON HER DEATHBED.
THEY HAD MORE FUN THAN WE DID.
- THOSE ARE DOUBLE STANDARDS.
- YOU WANT TO TEST
MY BREAST MILK?
IT'’S PROBABLY LIKE--
- PURE VODKA?
- VODKA.
OH, YEAH, IT'’S CONTAMINATED.
LIKE, IT'’LL BURN YOUR SKIN.
- I'’M GETTING PAINTED
LIKE THIS BAD GUY.
- NOBODY--YOU'’RE PAINTING
YOURSELF.
LIKE,
NOBODY'’S DOING ANYTHING.
- OKAY.
[groans]
PROBLEM SOLVED.
[door slams]
- AND THERE HE GOES.
- DO YOU THINK THAT MAKES ME
LOOK LIKE A BAD MOM?
- EVERY MOTHER'’S GONNA MAKE
MISTAKES.
IF HE DOESN'’T MARRY YOU FOR YOU,
THEN YOU SHOULDN'’T GET MARRIED.
- HOW MANY MOMS DO YOU KNOW
THAT HOOK UP WITH GIRLS
AT CLUBS?
- SO, YOU DON'’T WANT TO BE
WITH ME NOW?
- YOU CAN LEAVE NOW.
- [crying]