- ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
- NO, I'M NOT READY.
- ME EITHER!
SINCE I LEFT THE SHORE,
MY AND JIONNI ARE LIVING
WITH HIS PARENTS.
WE HAVE A NICE APARTMENT
DOWNSTAIRS.
- CAN YOU GUYS STRAIGHTEN UP
A LITTLE BIT?
SOPHIE'S COMING DOWN
IN A COUPLE MINUTES.
- WHY DO WE GOTTA CLEAN
FOR THE CLEANING LADY?
- SO SHE DOESN'T THINK
YOU'RE SLOPPY.
- JANIS IS LIKE
THE SUPER MOM,
AND I DEFINITELY ADMIRE THAT
ABOUT HER,
'CAUSE I WANT TO BE
LIKE THAT AS A MOM.
- THIS IS REALLY CRAZY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE HAVING A KID.
- IT DIDN'T HIT US YET.
- THE BELLY DIDN'T DO IT
FOR YOU?
- NO, IT JUST FEELS LIKE
AN ACCESSORY ON ME.
BUT ME AND JIONNI
ARE BASICALLY CLUELESS.
- REALISTICALLY,
NEITHER ONE OF US
KNOW HOW TO HANDLE
A NEWBORN.
- WOULD YOU AND JIONNI BE
RIGHT NOW?
- ENGAGED?
- IF YOU WEREN'T PREGNANT?
- PROBABLY NOT.
[both laugh]
- SINCE ME AND NICOLE
HAVE LEFT THE SHORE,
I'M LIVING WITH ROGER.
ONE DAY WILL YOU PROPOSE?
- ONE DAY.
NO PRESSURE FROM ANYBODY.
- IF I HAVE TO WAIT
FOR YOUR PACE,
I'LL BE WAITING
TILL I'M 50.
I WOULD LIKE A RING,
A VERY FAT, JUICY RING,
BUT NO PRESSURE.
- NO PRESSURE.
- ME AND NICOLE--
WE TALK ALL THE TIME.
IT'S JUST THAT WE'RE NOT
ABLE TO SEE EACH OTHER
LIKE WE DID IN JERSEY CITY,
DUE TO THE FACT THAT
SHE'S UP NORTH, AND I'M SOUTH.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- CLEANING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
ABOUT TO GET IN THE SHOWER.
JUST WANTED TO SAY HI.
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD BE THIS HARD.
- IT SUCKS.
- MM-HMM.
- BUT WE'RE STILL BEST FRIENDS.
- STILL.
- AND, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE STILL CRAZY BITCHES.
I WENT
TO THE DOCTOR'S TODAY.
- HOW IS THE VAGINA FEELING?
- I'M JUST, I GUESS,
PREPARING TO GIVE BIRTH.
- I STILL WANT TO HANG OUT
WITH YOU, THOUGH.
- OH, ME TOO.
- BEFORE [bleep] CHANGES.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO HAVE
A BABY.
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA GO
ON YOUR DUE DATE,
OR DO YOU ACTUALLY THINK
YOU'RE GONNA GO BEFORE IT?
- WE DON'T HAVE
OUR FURNITURE,
SO I KIND OF
DON'T WANT TO RUSH IT.
- [bleep] YOUR FURNITURE.
LET'S MEET LORENZO.
- YAY.
- * I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT
* I LOVE IT
*
* I DON'T CARE
[upbeat music]
- * LIFE IS WONDERFUL
* YEAH, IT'S GREAT
* YEAH-EAH-EAH
- EW! WHEN YOU LAUGH,
YOUR BELLY BUTTON POPS OUT.
- NO.
- DO IT AGAIN.
- RIGHT NOW
I'M EIGHT MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND I'M JUST TIRED
OF BEING PREGNANT.
- DO IT AGAIN.
- NO.
- PLEASE.
- [laughs]
HOPEFULLY, OUR DELIVERY
WILL BE SOON.
I FEEL LIKE
IT'S TAKING FOREVER,
BUT I'M DEFINITELY
NERVOUS ABOUT IT
BECAUSE IT CAN RIP YOU,
AND YOU CAN POOP
AND ALL THIS KIND OF STUFF.
- GO, PUSH ON IT. EW!
NICOLE, I'M NOT KIDDING.
- [groans]
- STOP, STOP.
- I'M GONNA POOP.
- [laughs]
- I WOULD SAY WE LIVE
IN A MAN CAVE,
AND I KIND OF LIKE IT,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA LIE.
WE HAVE A LOT TO DO.
- I WANT THE CRIB
ALONG THIS CORNER.
WE GOT TO...
- SET UP EVERYTHING,
MAKING IT, LIKE, BABY-PROOF.
- WE'RE GONNA MIX
THE TWO AND TWO TOGETHER.
IT'S GONNA BE A MAN CAVE
WITH A BABY.
- A MAN CAVE FROM THE BAR
TO THE KITCHEN, OVER.
- ALWAYS NEED A BAR.
- WELL, NOT IN A NURSERY.
- YOU CAN HANG
THE BABY BOTTLES ON THE BAR.
- YES, YOU CAN.
[laughs]
SURE YOU WANT TO DRIVE?
- YEAH.
- SO TODAY WE'RE GOING TO GO
SHOPPING FOR THE BABY,
BECAUSE WE HAVEN'T DONE
ANY SHOPPING YET.
WE HAVE NOTHING.
MY, LIKE, BOOB IS OUT.
- * PA-PA-PAPA SAID,
"BOY, NOW, BE SOMETHING" *
* AND MA-MA-MAMA SAID,
"STAY AT HOME AND BE NOTHIN'" *
*
- WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO GET?
- A THINGY TO PUT
ALL THE [bleep] ON.
- HUH?
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT BABY FURNITURE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO GET.
- THAT'S WHY I TOLD YOU
TO READ THE BOOKS,
SO YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
- HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
I JUST KNOW WE'RE EIGHT MONTHS.
YOU'RE DUE IN A MONTH.
AND LET'S [bleep]
GET THROUGH THIS.
- OH, WOW.
- OOH.
- THIS IS CUTE.
- I'M MICHELLE.
WELCOME TO BELLINI.
- HI. NICOLE.
- HI.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
JIONNI.
- WHAT CAN I HELP YOU GUYS
WITH TODAY?
- UM...
- EVERYTHING.
- EVERYTHING?
- YEAH, WE NEED A NICE SET.
- LET'S GO OVER HERE.
SO WE HAVE THE DARK,
DARK ESPRESSO.
- YEAH, I THINK
WE LIKE THIS.
- I DON'T HAVE MUCH SAY
ON--ON THE COLORS
OR WHAT TO PICK RIGHT NOW.
- YES, YOU DO.
- I DO?
- THIS IS A CHANGING TABLE?
- RIGHT.
- WHAT ABOUT THAT GUY?
- THAT'S THE ARMOIRE.
- WHAT'S A--IS THAT
WHERE YOU HANG CLOTHES?
- YEP. YOU CAN HANG CLOTHES
IN THERE.
- OH, COOL.
- ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S
LOOK AT THE CRIBS
THAT WE CAN MATCH
WITH THIS FURNITURE.
YOU CAN EITHER DO
THE DOMANI OR ALEX CRIB,
OR WE CAN DO THE JESSICA.
- OH, JESSICA.
- WHO'S JESSICA?
- [laughs]
WHY'D YOU SAY IT LIKE THAT?
"JESSICA."
THAT BUGS ME OUT.
IT'S ALL THE HORMONES,
I SAY,
BUT, LIKE, DON'T SAY ANOTHER
GIRL'S NAME OUT OF YOUR MOUTH.
- SO WHEN'S YOUR
ACTUAL DUE DATE?
- THE 10TH.
- OF SEPTEMBER?
OH, IT COULD GO
EITHER WAY.
LIKE, SOME OF THE STUFF'S
COMING IN
SORT OF MID-SEPTEMBER.
- WE NEED OUR FURNITURE
BEFORE LORENZO COMES.
IF I GO INTO LABOR
RIGHT NOW
AND I DON'T HAVE
THE FURNITURE,
THE BABY'S GONNA PROBABLY
SLEEP ON THE BEAN BAG--
MY LEOPARD-PRINT BEAN BAG,
AND I DON'T THINK
THAT'S SAFE.
SO, THE FURNITURE
NEEDS TO GET HERE.
- BYE.
- OH.
[upbeat music]
*
- I WORK.
I HAVE A FULL-TIME JOB.
SO EVERY DAY IS--
IS BASICALLY
GETTING UP AT, LIKE,
5:00 IN THE MORNING FOR ME.
- I DON'T HAVE A 9:00 TO 5:00
LIKE ROGER,
SO THEREFORE, I DON'T HAVE
TO, LIKE, HAVE A SET SCHEDULE.
I JUST KIND OF GO
WITH THE FLOW.
GOOD MORNING, GUYS.
HOW'S YOUR DAY?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT JENNI DOES
DURING THE DAY.
SHE TELLS ME WHAT SHE DOES.
- ALL RIGHT, SHOWER TIME.
- SHE'LL TELL ME
SHE CLEANED,
SHE TOOK THE DOGS
FOR A WALK.
- WHO PEED?
WHO DID THAT?
- SHE GOT HER HAIR DONE.
SHE MAYBE DID HER NAILS.
AND SHE WENT SHOPPING.
- [yawns]
- I FEEL LIKE I COULD DO THAT
IN, LIKE, THREE HOURS.
[whimsical music]
*
[knife tapping]
- I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE I'M
A HOUSEWIFE WITHOUT THE RING.
- LOOKS LIKE DADDY'S BOWL
OF LOVEKINS RIGHT THERE.
- AND HE KNOWS I WOULD REALLY,
REALLY LIKE AN ENGAGEMENT RING,
BUT THERE ARE THINGS
THAT I HAVE TO WORK ON
TO GET THAT RING.
- [laughs]
I NEED TO LEARN HOW TO COOK.
- WHO?
- ME.
- WHY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I NEED A SIGNATURE DISH,
YOU KNOW,
IN CASE WE EVER BREAK UP.
I NEED TO TREAT A LADY
SPECIAL.
I'M KIDDING.
I'M KIDDING. I'M KIDDING.
- JUST GOT TO TEACH
THE OLD DOG NEW TRICKS.
IT TAKES A WHILE.
- OKAY.
IT TAKES A WHILE
TO GET A BIG RING TOO.
- OH.
- [laughs]
CHEERS TO YOU FARTING LATER
'CAUSE YOU'RE EATING THIS.
- I KNOW.
- "OH, I JUST GOT TO CHECK
MY FACE REAL QUICK
IN THE BATHROOM."
[imitates flatulence]
- * I CAN'T HELP
BUT BREAK IT DOWN *
* I'VE GOT A HEART THAT'S FULL
OF MUSHROOM CLOUDS *
* WHEN I SELF-DESTRUCT
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
- THIS MORNING
I GOT LUMINEERS ON MY TEETH,
BECAUSE WHEN LORENZO SEES ME
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I WANT HIM TO BE LIKE,
"HOLY [bleep].
MY MOM IS [bleep] AWESOME."
I THINK HE FEELS
MY ANXIETY.
- I'M JUST GONNA POLISH
IN BETWEEN THE TEETH.
[tool whirring]
- IF I'M DEFINITELY
GONNA BE A MILF,
I NEED TO DRESS THE PART.
EVEN WHEN YOU ARE
GIVING BIRTH,
YOU HAVE TO LOOK HOT.
[tool whirring]
THAT HURT.
WELL, I JUST GOT THEM
PUT ON,
SO THEY'RE NOT, LIKE,
100%, BUT...
THEY'RE NICE AND WHITE
AND PERFECT.
WELL, THAT WAS SCARY.
- * TOLD ME
WHEN I GREW UP *
* I'D BE JUST LIKE
MY MOTHER *
*
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
LOOKING AT NICOLE'S TEETH
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I WASN'T EXPECTING THESE
HUGE LUMINEERS IN HER MOUTH.
SHE DIDN'T REALLY TELL ME
SHE WAS GETTING THEM.
SHE CAME HOME,
AND THERE THEY WERE.
OH!
- [laughs]
- THE FRONT ROW IS JUST
A LITTLE ULTRA BIG.
THEY NEED TO FILE IT DOWN
A LITTLE BIT.
YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE GETTING,
LIKE, ONE DONE
AND SEEING IF YOU LIKED IT.
- THEY DID
THE WHOLE TOP ROW.
- YOU DID NOT TELL ME
- OKAY.
- LET ME SEE.
- NO.
- NICOLE MIGHT HAVE DEVELOPED
A LITTLE LISP.
- I DON'T HAVE A LISP.
- [sucking his teeth]
I SLID THE SHEET.
- "I SLID THE SHEET."
- THE SHEET SLID ME.
- THE SEAT-- [laughs]
"THE SHEET SLID ME."
- SLID WAS THE SHEET.
- SLITHER WAS THE SEAT.
[laughs]
- YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE WEARING A RETAINER
AND FAKE TEETH.
- [laughs]
- THIS TESTS THE, UH,
AMOUNT OF ALCOHOL
IN YOUR BREAST MILK.
- OOH, I NEED THAT.
I'M HAVING WINE
RIGHT AFTER.
I DEFINITELY DON'T WANT
A DRUNK BABY ON MY HAND.
I'M NOT A HILLBILLY.
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
- NICOLE GOT
THE DEENA JOB DONE.
[whimsical music]
- [laughs]
- I WANT WAFFLE FR--
[laughter]
- YOUR TEETH
GOT IN YOUR WAY.
[laughter]
- * YOU HAD ME FALLING,
FALLING, FALLING FOR YOU *
* YOU HAD ME WORKING, WORKING,
WORKING FOR YOU *
- MY MOM IS COMING
TO GET ME
BECAUSE WE ARE REGISTERING
FOR MY BABY SHOWER.
- COME ON.
- AAH!
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT I NEED TO GET
WHEN IT COMES
TO, YOU KNOW, REGISTERING,
BECAUSE I NEVER HAD
A KID BEFORE.
SO HOPEFULLY MY MOM, LIKE,
KNOWS WHAT TO DO.
- WHY DON'T WE START
WITH CAR SEATS?
- I COULD PROBABLY
FIT IN THESE.
NIPPLE SHIELDS?
- YEP.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- AFTER A WHILE,
IT WILL HURT.
THERE'S NIPPLE CREAMS
AS WELL.
- OH.
[scanner beeps]
- YOU MIGHT WANT TO SCAN THIS
MULTIPLE TIMES.
[scanner beeps]
- OH, I LIKE IT.
- HE DOESN'T SUFFOCATE IN THERE?
- NO. THEY'RE SAFE.
[scanner beeps]
- THIS IS GOOD.
THEY'LL GET THE IDEA.
REGISTERING
IS NOT AS MUCH FUN,
LIKE I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
I MEAN, PICKING OUT
BREAST PUMPS
AND A SAFETY KIT AND OINTMENTS
AND [bleep] FOR THE ASS.
TOOTHBRUSH?
- NOT ANYTIME SOON.
- OH, YEAH.
HE HAS NO TEETH.
I NEVER REALLY KNEW HOW MUCH
[bleep] YOU REALLY NEEDED,
YOU KNOW, TO HAVE A BABY.
- THIS TESTS
THE AMOUNT OF ALCOHOL
IN YOUR BREAST MILK.
- OOH, I NEED THAT.
LORENZO'S DEFINITELY GETTING
VIRGIN BREAST MILK
BECAUSE HE CANNOT DRINK
UNTIL HE'S 21.
THAT'S MY JOB.
I'M HAVING WINE RIGHT AFTER.
[scanner beeps]
- [laughs]
- I DON'T WANT A DRUNK BABY
ON MY HANDS.
I'M NOT A HILLBILLY.
- WE'RE GOOD.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[upbeat music]
*
- NICOLE?
BABE? IT'S 11:30,
AND JENNI'S ON HER WAY.
- WHO CARES?
- WELL, YOU DON'T WANT HER TO
GET HERE AND YOU'RE SLEEPING.
IT'S A BAD IDEA TO CALL NICOLE
BEFORE NOON,
ESPECIALLY PREGNANT.
- [groans]
LIKE WAKING UP A DRAGON.
- [laughs]
- YOU DON'T DO IT.
*
YOU CHANGED YOUR HAIR.
- YEAH.
- I LIKE IT SO MUCH BETTER.
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
- THE FIRST THING I NOTICE
WHEN I SEE NICOLE IS HER TEETH.
SHE GOT THE DEENA JOB DONE.
[laughs]
- YES.
WAFFLE FRIES.
[mumbles]
I WANT WAFFLE FR--
[laughter]
- HEADS UP.
YOUR TEETH
GOT IN YOUR WAY.
[laughter]
SHE'S GONNA THROW UP.
- SHE'S GONNA VOMIT.
SHE'S GONNA VOMIT.
- SHE'S GONNA THROW UP.
- I ALMOST SPIT UP
THE [bleep]...
NICOLE'S GONNA HAVE TO GET
USED TO HER NEW TEETH.
IT'S LIKE MY BOOBS
BEFORE THEY SETTLED--
JUST OUT THERE.
- HOW ARE YOU AND ROGER?
- GOOD.
- NO RING?
- I THINK I WOULD HAVE
TOLD YOU.
- I THINK HE'LL ASK YOU.
ROGER WANTS TO SETTLE DOWN,
I THINK.
YOU KNOW, HE'S OLD.
I'VE BEEN READY FOR ROGER
TO POP THE QUESTION TO JENNI
FOR, LIKE, TWO YEARS NOW,
AND THE FACT THAT HE'S,
LIKE, [bleep] OLD,
LIKE, HURRY UP.
- [laughs]
- AND I THINK
HE WILL DO IT SOON.
BYE.
- HAVE FUN.
[upbeat music]
- EW, IT SMELLS LIKE RAIN.
ME AND JENNI ARE GOING
SHOPPING AT ANNIE SEZ,
AND I ALWAYS GO
SHOPPING THERE.
THEY HAVE, LIKE, NICE BLOUSES
AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
AND HOPEFULLY, BOO-BOO CAN FIND
A DRESS FOR THE SHOWER.
*
OH, THEY LOOK LIKE
THEY HAVE GOOD STUFF.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS GOOD.
THIS IS PRETTY.
- TOO MUCH?
- NO.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT EVERYONE'S
DRESSING UP IN--
LIKE, FANCY CLOTHES.
- IF YOU COULD WEAR
THE DRESS TO KARMA,
YOU SHOULD NOT BE WEARING
THE DRESS TO THE BABY SHOWER.
- IT SHOULD LOOK
A LITTLE CLASSY,
BUT NOT, LIKE, TOO CLASSY,
WHERE IT'S LIKE,
TEA AND CRUMPETS,
YOU KNOW?
- MIDWAY.
- YEAH.
- SO IT'S PINKY UP?
- PINKY UP,
WITH A GLASS OF WINE.
NOTHING [bleep] FITS ME
ANYMORE.
I JUST HATE MY LIFE.
I JUST THINK THAT I'M, LIKE,
SO READY TO GIVE BIRTH
RIGHT NOW.
I'M JUST SO OVER
BEING PREGNANT.
SOMETHING'S GOTTA FIT
IN HERE.
I HAVE NOTHING
THAT FITS ME,
AND I JUST FEEL DISGUSTING.
THIS IS [bleep].
DO A RUNWAY.
I THINK YOU LOOK VERY PRETTY.
- YEAH?
- LET ME SEE THE BLUE.
I LOVE BOTH.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- THEY BOTH LOOK GREAT.
IT MAKES ME JEALOUS THAT
JENNI'S, LIKE, SEXY AND TAN.
- I'LL JUST BUY BOTH AND FIGURE
IT OUT THAT MORNING.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE THEN YOU COULD
WEAR IT TO ANOTHER EVENT.
I WANT TO HAVE THIS BABY
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE
JUST BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
A HUGE MEATBALL RIGHT NOW.
I DEFINITELY DON'T LOOK HOT.
BYE, POOP.
- BYE. LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU TOO.
[rock music]
*
- HI, HONEY.
- HEY.
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- WITH HER LITTLE BELLY.
- YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
- YOU LOOK CUTE.
- I THINK HE DROPPED
A LITTLE.
- DON'T BE DROPPING.
- HE WAS UP HERE.
NOW HE'S A LITTLE DOWN.
- WAIT TILL AFTER SUNDAY.
AFTER SUNDAY, YOU CAN DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
- I KNOW HOW TO DELIVER,
AND I KNOW CPR ON A BABY.
- I NEED AN EPIDURAL.
- YOU DON'T NEED AN EPIDURAL.
- YEAH, I DO.
- YOU DON'T, REALLY.
- WAS JIONNI A MISTAKE?
- NO, HONEY, HE WAS NOT
A MISTAKE.
- I'M STANDING RIGHT HERE!
- [laughs]
- NO. ACTUALLY, I WANTED
ONE MORE AFTER JIONNI.
- REALLY?
- MY MOM SAID SHE WANTED
TO HAVE ANOTHER ONE AFTER ME,
SO I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN
A MISTAKE.
- OKAY.
- TRUE.
- IT'S FINE,
'CAUSE YOU'RE HERE.
BUT LORENZO WAS A MISTAKE.
WE DIDN'T PLAN HIM,
BUT WE'RE SO EXCITED
TO HAVE HIM,
AND WE'RE GONNA LOVE HIM
NO MATTER WHAT.
HE JUST WASN'T PLANNED.
IT WOULD BE RUDE
IF IT WAS LIKE,
"OH, YOU WERE A MISTAKE,"
AND THEN YOU DIDN'T WANT THEM
AND YOU GAVE 'EM AWAY.
- I NEED A DRINK.
- WHAT--WHAT IS THIS [bleep]?
- THE FIGHTS
ARE ABOUT TO START,
AND PAY-PER-VIEW
SHUTS OFF.
- SOMEBODY BETTER [bleep]
FIGURE THIS OUT RIGHT NOW.
- SO CLASSY.
TOO CLASSY.
WE NEED SOME ANIMAL PRINT
IN THIS BITCH.
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
*
- ARE WE GOING IN HERE?
IS THIS IT?
IT'S OVER THERE.
- DUM-DUM.
NICOLE'S HAVING
A BABY SHOWER,
SO OBVIOUSLY I HAVE TO GET
NICOLE AND LORENZO PRESENTS.
- EVERY MAN'S DREAM.
- SHOP FOR BABIES?
- DRAGGING ME,
KICKING AND SCREAMING.
- YEAH.
- HAVE YOU BEEN
TO BABY SHOWERS BEFORE?
- WHEN I WAS IN HIGH SCHOOL,
ONE OF MY FRIENDS GOT PREGNANT.
- OH, MY GOD, WHERE'D YOU
GROW UP--IN THE GHETTO?
- I THINK I'M REALLY EXCITED
TO SEE LORENZO BORN,
BUT I DEFINITELY FEEL
LIKE I NEED TO ACCOMPLISH
WHAT I WANT TO ACCOMPLISH
IN LIFE, UH,
BEFORE SETTLING DOWN
AND HAVING A KID,
'CAUSE THAT'S A COMPLETELY
NEW CHAPTER IN OUR LIFE.
- 'CAUSE YOU'D ACTUALLY
HAVE TO HAVE SEX WITH ME
TO GET PREGNANT.
- THAT TOO.
- BREAST PUMP?
- I GOT HER A BREAST PUMP.
- YOU DID?
- AND I GOT HER
A TRAVEL BREAST PUMP.
IT COST, LIKE, 300 BUCKS.
SHE CAN HAVE THOSE [bleep]
SUCKED ON THE GO.
[upbeat music]
*
I HAVE TO GO TO THE GYM.
I CAN'T GET THEM
PAINTED YET.
ME AND ROGER ARE HEADING
TO GET OUR WEEKLY PEDICURE.
- I'D LIKE TO SHATTER
THAT MYTH
THAT TOUGH GUYS
CAN'T GET PEDICURES.
- HE GOES WITH ME EVERY WEEK.
- ALL THE TIME.
GOT A PROBLEM WITH IT,
COME SEE ME.
- [laughs]
I'M REALLY EXCITED
FOR TONIGHT,
BUT VERY NERVOUS
AT THE SAME TIME.
- I'VE HAD, LIKE,
THE JITTERS FOR TWO DAYS
ABOUT THIS FIGHT.
I'M VERY EXCITED
ABOUT THE MMA FIGHT TONIGHT--
SUPER EXCITED.
MY FRIEND FRANKIE'S
FIGHTING IN IT.
HE'S A LOCAL.
HE'S FROM TOMS RIVER.
HE IS
THE FORMER UFC, UH, CHAMPION
AT THE LIGHTWEIGHT DIVISION.
UH, BUT TONIGHT'S
A HUGE NIGHT.
HE'S CHALLENGING
FOR THAT BELT BACK.
JUST IN CASE
FRANKIE LOSES,
WHERE WILL YOU BE SLEEPING
TONIGHT?
- THAT'S RIGHT. I LEARNED
MY LESSON LAST TIME.
I DO NOT WANT TO BE
ANYWHERE NEAR YOU.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M MORE NERVOUS ABOUT--
THE FACT THAT FRANKIE
MIGHT NOT WIN
OR THE FACT THAT ROGER
WILL FLIP THE [bleep] OUT
IF FRANKIE DOESN'T WIN.
OH, MY GOD, I FORGOT
TO TELL YOU.
- WHAT?
- NICOLE GOT HER TEETH DONE.
- SHE GOT VENEERS?
- SHE JUST GOT THE TOP DONE.
- DOES SHE LOOK LIKE
SHE CAN CHEW A TREE DOWN?
- [laughs]
- SHE DOES?
- I WAS LIKE, "HOLY CHIPMUNK."
- REALLY?
- WITH THE WOOD--
KIND OF WOODCHUCKS.
[upbeat music]
*
- HI.
- HELLO.
- WHAT'S UP?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HI.
- MWAH!
- YANICE IS MY GOOD FRIEND
FROM LONG ISLAND,
THE ONE I TOOK TO CANCUN.
- THE SUN'S PERFECT
RIGHT HERE.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
- RIGHT HERE.
- HI. HOW DRUNK ARE YOU?
- I'M NOT DRUNK AT ALL.
- AND MY GAY
BEST FRIEND, JOEY...
MADONNA?
- MARILYN MONROE.
- MARILYN.
OH, YEAH.
HE'S BEEN MY BEST FRIEND
FOR TEN YEARS.
[laughs]
- OW.
- I HAVE JOEY AND YANICE
COMING,
BECAUSE THEY'RE GONNA BE GOING
TO THE BABY SHOWER WITH ME
IN THE MORNING.
- YOU KNOW SOMEBODY
WHO'S FIGHTING TONIGHT?
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
- FRANKIE EDGAR.
- YOU MET THEM.
- YEAH, YOU MET THEM.
- OH, GET OUT OF HERE.
- IS THERE A LOT OF
PEOPLE COMING, JENNI?
- NOT REALLY.
- I CAN ONLY HAVE
DIE-HARD FRANKIE FANS.
IF YOU'RE NOT A DIE-HARD FAN
AND YOU DON'T REALLY
CARE ABOUT IT--
LIKE YANICE--
THEN YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
- YEAH, HE INSTIGATES.
- OFF!
- HE INSTIGATES.
- DON'T!
[Jenni shouts]
- GET HIM OFF.
OH, MY GOD.
- ROGER.
- OH, MY GOD.
[laughter]
HOLY [bleep].
HORN DOG.
[whimsical music]
- OOH, LET'S GET READY...
- OH, GOD.
- [laughs]
ME AND JIONNI
ARE THROWING A PARTY
FOR OURSELVES TONIGHT,
BECAUSE OUR FRIEND FRANKIE
IS FIGHTING.
- WE GOT CHIPS, DOUGHNUTS,
DRINKS, GATORADE, DIP.
- TWISTEDS.
ALLS WE NEED IS THE PEOPLE.
- THESE ARE OUR GUESTS--
HORTON AND TEDDY.
- I DIDN'T WANT TO BRING
REAL FRIENDS,
'CAUSE SHE'S PREGNANT--
I WANTED TO SHOW RESPECT.
- AND I HAVE TO GET UP EARLY
TOMORROW FOR MY BABY SHOWER.
- EXACTLY.
- SO WE COULDN'T
HAVE A REAL PARTY.
- WE THROW ONE SICK PARTY,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
- [laughs]
- DUDE, I CAN'T WAIT
FOR THIS [bleep] FIGHT, MAN.
- YO!
HERE'S THE SHOTS.
- FRANKIE'S THE LAST FIGHT ON,
WHICH IS USUALLY THE MAIN EVENT,
SO THERE'S A LOT OF PRE-GAMING
UP TO THAT POINT.
- SHOT.
FOOD, FRIENDS, AND ALCOHOL.
- FOOD...
IT'S WHAT WE LIKE TO DO,
ESPECIALLY WHEN FRANKIE'S
FIGHTING, YOU KNOW?
- IS IT BAD
OF THE GRANDMOTHER NOT SHOWING
UP FOR THE BABY SHOWER?
- YOU'RE GOING TOMORROW.
- I KNOW.
- YOU'RE GOOD.
- DID IT START YET? NO.
- IT MUST BE ABOUT TIME
TO SWITCH OVER.
- WHOO!
- ME AND LAURA SLAVED
OVER THESE [bleep] DIPS.
- SO YOU GUYS BETTER
EAT THEM.
- SO YOU BETTER
[bleep] EAT THEM.
- ORDER THAT [bleep].
YO, WHAT--WHAT IS THIS [bleep]?
YO, WHAT IS THIS [bleep]?
"ORDER BY PHONE ONLY."
- RIGHT AS THE FIGHTS
ARE ABOUT TO START,
PAY-PER-VIEW SHUTS OFF.
- YO, SOMEBODY BETTER [bleep]
FIGURE THIS OUT RIGHT NOW.
- WE ORDERED IT, AND NOTHING'S
[bleep] WORKING.
- JESUS. COME ON, MAN.
SOMEONE [bleep] DO SOMETHING.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS REMATCH FOR SIX MONTHS.
I WOULD KILL KITTENS
TO SEE THIS FIGHT.
- NO.
- YES.
- BABIES.
- AND BABIES.
- NOT KITTENS.
- YO, WE GOTTA--WE GOTTA--
WE GOTTA GO.
WE HAVE TO GO SOMEWHERE WHERE
THIS FIGHT IS GONNA BE ON
AND IS GONNA WORK.
I'M NOT MISSING THIS FIGHT.
- I DON'T WANT TO TRANSFER.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I AM FREAKING OUT. THE FIGHTS
HAVE ALREADY STARTED.
- ALL RIGHT.
SO STOP FREAKING OUT.
JUST GIVE ME ONE SECOND HERE.
- RELAX.
- SHUT THE [bleep] UP,
THEN.
- DON'T TELL ME TO
SHUT THE [bleep] UP.
- SHUT THE [bleep] UP.
- BIG MOUTH, LITTLE PEOPLE.
- BIG MOUTH,
BIG [bleep] PEOPLE.
- STOP!
- ALL OF A SUDDEN,
OUT OF NOWHERE...
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A LITTLE BIT.
MY BODY'S
STARTING TO SHUT DOWN.
I'M GETTING SICK.
I'M NUMB.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE HECK'S GOING ON.
- HEY, ORDER THAT [bleep].
YO, WHAT--
WHAT IS THIS [bleep]?
YO, WHAT IS THIS [bleep]?
"ORDER BY PHONE ONLY."
YO, WE GOTTA--
WE GOTTA GO.
WE HAVE TO GO SOMEWHERE WHERE
THIS FIGHT IS GONNA BE ON
AND IS GONNA WORK.
- WHAT ABOUT ALL THE FOOD?
EVERYBODY, BRING A PLATTER.
- WE NEED IT ON
WITHIN 30 SECONDS,
BEFORE I LITERALLY THROW THE BOX
OUTSIDE THE [bleep] WINDOW.
- JENNI, JUST HANG UP
ON THE GUY.
WE HAVE TO GO.
- WE'RE BASICALLY GONNA JUST TRY
AND FIND ANYWHERE
TO WATCH THIS FIGHT,
SO WE'RE LEAVING.
WE'RE GONNA FIND A PLACE.
- I'M NOT MISSING IT.
NO MATTER WHAT,
I'M NOT MISSING THIS FIGHT.
[playful music]
- OH, YOU GOT THE DIP.
SHE'S GOT THE DIP!
- I GOT ALL YOUR DIPS.
[laughs]
- IT [bleep] TOOK ME FOREVER
TO MAKE THIS.
- YOU NEED THE DIP
FOR THE FIGHT.
WHAT'S A FIGHT GONNA BE
WITHOUT DIP?
- I WAS DYING.
*
- GET IN. JOEY!
- I'M COMING IN.
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
- JOEY'S BACK THERE.
- YO, GUYS, GUYS, IT'S ON.
COME ON, IT'S ON, IT'S ON.
COME ON.
- IT'S BACK ON!
- SO NOW WE ALL GO
RUNNING BACK IN THE HOUSE.
- OH!
[laughter]
- MAN DOWN!
HEARD THAT!
- I DID NOT CLEAR THE COUCH.
I THINK I GOT ONE FOOT OVER
AND THE OTHER ONE CAUGHT ON IT,
AND IT WAS JUST--
IT LOOKED LIKE A YARD SALE
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE LIVING ROOM FLOOR.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
WHO WENT DOWN?
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA
STEAL MY SEAT.
- OH, MAN.
- I JUST WANNA WATCH THE FIGHT.
- HE JUST TUMBLED
EVERYWHERE.
- IT WAS NOT A PRETTY SCENE.
- IT'S FIGHT TIME!
- CHEERS TO TONIGHT.
- YAY!
- FIGHTING
OUT OF TOMS RIVER, NEW JERSEY,
FRANKIE "THE ANSWER" EDGAR!
- LET'S GO, FRANKIE!
LET'S GO, FRANKIE!
- WHOO!
- FRANKIE!
- MAYBE ROGER AND JENNI'S PARTY
IS BETTER THAN OURS.
- THEY'RE NOT HAVING A BABY.
WHOO!
- YEAH!
- OH!
- HE CAUGHT THAT ONE. OH!
- OH! OH!
[cheering]
I AM SO INTO THIS.
THERE COULD HAVE BEEN NOBODY
ELSE IN THE ROOM.
I DIDN'T CARE.
I'M--I'M INTO THIS FIGHT.
YOU KNOW HOW I GET, BABE.
- IT'S TRUE,
'CAUSE I GET THE SAME WAY.
- MM-HMM.
- THERE'S THE UPPERCUT.
- OH, HE HURT HIM!
- YEAH, BUDDY.
- COME ON, COME ON!
COME ON! FRANKIE!
[overlapping shouting]
- IT'S SO BACK AND FORTH.
THE ACTION
IS SO KIND OF EVENLY PACED
FOR THE MOST PART OF IT.
- IT WAS DRIVING ME NUTS.
- YEAH.
AND THE ANXIETY
IS JUST BUILDING.
LAST ROUND, MAN,
COME ON.
- GO!
- COME ON!
- OH!
[overlapping shouting]
- DON'T LET HIM UP!
- DO NOT GET UP!
- COME ON, FRANKIE,
COME ON!
[overlapping shouting]
- UNDER 90 SECONDS
ON THE CLOCK HERE.
[cheering]
- COME ON,
TAKE HIM DOWN!
- KNOCK HIM OUT.
- MAN, THAT IS
A CLOSE FIGHT.
- I'M GONNA HAVE
A [bleep] ANEURYSM.
- THE WINNER,
BY SPLIT DECISION...
HENDERSON!
- NO!
- WHAT?
- OH, MY GOD!
- AW!
- I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW WHO WAS
JUDGING THAT FIGHT THAT NIGHT,
'CAUSE CLEARLY,
THEY WERE BLIND.
I'M DONE, MAN.
I JUST WANT TO GO TO BED NOW.
- THE PARTY JUST GOES
A TURN FOR THE WORSE.
- HE'S WEARING
A "GIRLS SUCK" SHIRT.
YOU COOL WITH THAT, ROGER?
- GIRLS DO SUCK.
- GIRLS, WE SUCK?
- YEAH. SO SHUT UP.
- WE SUCK?
- YEAH, YOU SUCK.
- ROGER, YOU USED TO BE
A LOT NICER.
- OOH.
- I USED TO BE A LOT NICER?
- YOU USED TO BE.
WHEN I FIRST MET YOU,
YOU WERE.
- I USED TO BE A LOT NICER?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
- I'M CLEANING UP THE KITCHEN,
AND LEGIT, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
YANICE AND ROGER
START GOING AT IT
IN A NON-JOKING WAY.
LIKE, THEY'RE SERIOUS.
- I'VE REALLY GOT AN ACTIVE
INVOLVEMENT WITH PETA,
AND YOU KILLED SO MANY BIRDS
TO MAKE THOSE EARRINGS,
I CAN'T SEE YOU
IN THE SAME LIGHT.
- WHO'S PETA?
[laughter]
- WHO'S PETA? YOU ONLY MET
ONE OF MY BOYFRIENDS.
- PETA-PETA-PO-PETA.
- PETA.
PETA, PETA,
BIG [bleep] PUMPKIN EATER.
- OH, MY GOD.
- YEAH.
- YANICE, SHUT UP.
- IT WAS A JOKE.
RELAX. RELAX. RELAX.
- SHUT THE [bleep] UP, THEN.
- DON'T TELL ME
TO SHUT THE [bleep] UP.
- SHUT THE [bleep] UP, THEN.
- YANICE-AH.
[laughter]
- STOP PISSIN' ME OFF,
OR I'LL--
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- [laughs]
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
BITE MY ANKLE?
- YOU'RE [bleep] OBNOXIOUS.
- DON'T PISS ME OFF, SERIOUSLY.
- DON'T PISS ME
THE [bleep] OFF.
- YOU WILL LOSE,
I ASSURE YOU.
- OH, I WILL LOSE?
DON'T [bleep] PISS ME OFF.
- YOU WILL LOSE.
I THINK SHE DRINKS
A LITTLE TOO MUCH, AND...
- YEAH.
- SHE DOESN'T HAVE
A VERY GOOD PERCEPTION
OF WHAT'S GOING ON
AROUND HER.
- SHUT UP, ROGER.
- ME?
- HE'S [bleep] OBNOXIOUS.
- I FEEL LIKE ROGER'S,
YOU KNOW,
AGGRESSION RIGHT NOW
IS COMING FROM FRANKIE'S FIGHT.
- BIG MOUTH, LITTLE PEOPLE.
- [laughs]
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
BIG MOUTH,
BIG [bleep] PEOPLE.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
- I HAVE MY GIRLFRIEND
OF, LIKE, TEN YEARS.
I HAVE MY BOYFRIEND
OF TWO YEARS.
SO BOTH PARTIES JUST NEED
TO SHUT THE [bleep] UP.
- YOU'RE [bleep] OBNOXIOUS.
- SHUT UP!
- ...BY HIS [bleep] ARROGANT.
- BOTH OF YOU.
- THERE'S A BIG SHIELD
OF ARROGANCE ALL ABOVE YOU.
- BOTH OF YOU.
- OKAY.
- YEP.
[laughter]
- I GOTTA GO.
- I'M NOT APOLOGIZING.
- [sighs]
- [bleep].
- WHERE'D HE GO?
- WHO [bleep] CARES?
- OH!
- YANICE-SA.
- YOU BREAST-FEED,
YOU STILL CAN'T DRINK.
- YEAH, PUMP AND DUMP.
I DESERVE
A FEW GLASSES OF WINE
AFTER CARRYING
THIS BIG WATERMELON AROUND--
MAYBE EVEN A COUPLE BOTTLES.
- ALL I CARE ABOUT IS THIS BABY
SHOWER GOING RIGHT FOR NICOLE,
AND ME BEING SICK
RIGHT NOW
IS, BY FAR, THE WORST THING
THAT COULD HAPPEN.
- * DARK IS THE NIGHT
* AS IT FALLS
* ON THESE SHADOWED FACES
- [groans] THIS PLACE SMELLS
LIKE BEER AND SHAME.
LAST NIGHT THERE WAS
A BIG ARGUMENT
BETWEEN ROGER AND YANICE,
AND ROGER DIDN'T COME HOME
LAST NIGHT,
AND I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM HIM
THIS MORNING,
AND I HAVE TO GO
TO THE BABY SHOWER.
[knocks on door]
GOOD MORNING.
- HI.
- GOOD MORNING.
- HOW DO YOU GUYS FEEL?
- LIKE [bleep].
- BUT, YOU KNOW,
IT IS WHAT IT IS,
AND AS LONG AS
HE'S NOT MAD AT ME,
I'LL BE FINE WITH IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT, WHAT?
- THIS WASN'T 100% MY FAULT.
- HE WAS MAKING JOKES
YOU DIDN'T GET.
YOU GOT REALLY ANGRY
AND NASTY.
YOU WENT ON ATTACK MODE.
- FIRST OF ALL,
HE WAS DISRESPECTING ME.
IT WASN'T A JOKE.
- YOU DIDN'T GET A JOKE
HE REFERENCED,
AND YOU GOT NASTY
WITH HIM, DUDE.
- NO, HE--HE WAS BEING
VERY DISRESPECTFUL TO ME
THE ENTIRE [bleep] TIME.
- NO, HE WASN'T.
YOU WERE BELLIGERENT, DUDE.
YANICE IS TRYING TO SAY
THAT ROGER WAS RUDE LAST NIGHT,
AND I'M DEFENDING MY MAN.
SHE WAS RUDE.
- NOW YOU'RE TAKING
HIS SIDE,
AND IT'S LIKE, I'M YOUR
[bleep] BEST FRIEND, AND--
- YEAH, BUT HE'S MY MAN.
- LISTEN, I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT
WITH YOUR BOYFRIEND,
BECAUSE HE IS
YOUR BOYFRIEND.
BUT I AM YOUR BEST FRIEND ALSO.
- YEAH. THAT'S WHY
I WAS LIKE--
- AND HE NEEDS TO UNDERSTAND
THAT, LIKE--
HAVE SOME RESPECT
FOR ME TOO.
- EVERYONE HAS A FRIEND THAT,
YOU KNOW, IS OVERDRAMATIC
AND, YOU KNOW, DRAMA,
AND THAT'S MY YANICE.
- YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
BOTH OF YOU TOOK IT OVERBOARD.
- MAYBE, 'CAUSE WE
WERE [bleep] DRINKING.
NOW I FEEL [bleep] BAD,
AND NOW I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE
TO ROGER AGAIN.
I HATE TALKING TO ROGER.
I FEEL LIKE HE'S MY FATHER.
- [laughs]
WELCOME TO MY WORLD.
- * WE CAN MAKE IT
ALL NIGHT *
* EVERYTHING IS ALL RIGHT
* ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT *
- SO, WAKING UP THIS MORNING,
MY STOMACH FEELS WEIRD,
AND I FEEL LIKE
I'M HAVING CONTRACTIONS,
AND I'M SCARED
I'M GONNA HAVE THIS BABY.
- HOW WE DOING, PAL?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT UP, G?
- WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- THIS DAY COULDN'T HAVE
WORKED OUT ANY BETTER.
NICOLE'S SHOWER
IS AT A COUNTRY CLUB.
I GET TO PLAY GOLF
WITH MY BROTHER
AND EIGHT OF OUR FRIENDS.
NICOLE, YOU REMEMBER
GEOFF AND JOHN, RIGHT?
- HI, NICOLE.
ARE YOU READY? BIG DAY.
- I HAVE TO SHOWER.
- A GUY'S RESPONSIBILITY
AT A BABY SHOWER
IS TO COME AT THE END,
HELP WITH THE PRESENTS.
LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- SEE YOU OVER THERE?
NICOLE INVITED
OVER 100 PEOPLE.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO SEE HOW
MANY GIFTS I HAVE TO BRING HOME.
- NIC?
- YEAH?
- HOW WE DOING?
- JUST PUTTING JEWELRY ON.
- OH, OKAY.
- I REALLY DON'T CARE IF
MY WATER BREAKS AT THE SHOWER,
BECAUSE THAT
WOULD BE AWESOME.
I COULD HAVE ALL THESE PRESENTS,
AND I WOULD BE GIVING BIRTH.
BUT I'M JUST NERVOUS FOR, LIKE,
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TODAY.
- [groans]
- I THINK I'VE GONNA
GIVE LABOR TODAY.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I'M NOT KIDDING.
[upbeat music]
I NEED A GLASS OF WINE.
I'M DYING.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOT THREE MORE WEEKS.
- YEAH.
- AND THAT'S IT.
- IF YOU BREAST-FEED,
YOU STILL CAN'T DRINK.
- BUT I NEED, LIKE,
PROTEIN.
YOU CAN DRINK.
- NO, YOU CANNOT.
- YOU CAN DUMP.
- DUMP?
- YEAH, PUMP AND DUMP.
I DEFINITELY THINK I DESERVE
A FEW GLASSES OF WINE
AFTER CARRYING
THIS BIG WATERMELON AROUND--
MAYBE EVEN A COUPLE BOTTLES.
- PUMP AND DUMP WHAT?
- IF YOU DRINK, THEN YOU PUMP
YOUR BREAST MILK OUT
AND THEN DUMP IT,
AND THEN YOU TEST YOUR MILK
TO SEE IF IT'S ALCOHOL-FREE.
SO, RIGHT AFTER
I GIVE BIRTH,
THE BOTTLE OF PINOT GRIGIO--
YEAH, IT'S DEFINITELY
GONNA BE CHILLING
AS I'M PUSHING OUT LORENZO.
AND THAT'S OKAY,
BECAUSE A LOT OF MOTHERS DO IT.
- LET'S JUST NOT DRINK.
- * VICTORIOUS,
VICTORIOUS *
* COUNT IT DOWN NOW,
5, 4, 3, 2, 1 *
- PULL UP RIGHT UP HERE.
- VALET? I HATE VALET.
- WHY?
- 'CAUSE I JUST FEEL LIKE
RICH PEOPLE DO THAT.
SO MY SHOWER IS AT
FALKIRK ESTATE AND COUNTRY CLUB,
SO IT'S LIKE A CLASSY JOINT.
THIS IS REALLY PRETTY.
- ISN'T IT PRETTY HERE?
- * VICTORIOUS,
VICTORIOUS *
* COUNT IT DOWN NOW,
5, 4, 3, 2, 1 *
- HI, MOM.
- YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- I HAVE TO FART
REALLY BAD.
- [laughs]
- YOU CAN DO THAT.
- THIS IS OVERWHELMING.
- JUST GO WITH IT, HONEY.
JUST GO WITH IT.
- IT'S SO CLASSY...
TOO CLASSY.
WE NEED SOME ANIMAL PRINT
IN THIS BITCH.
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
[overlapping chatter]
- HI, BOO. YOU LOOK--
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
- YOU TOO.
- HI.
- LET ME SEE.
- OH, I LOVE YOU.
LET ME SEE.
YOU LOOK SO GOOD.
- I'M HUGE.
- THIS DRESS LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
- RIGHT?
HI, SAM.
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
FEEL MY BELLY BUTTON.
- [laughs]
- THAT'S MY MOM, EVELYN.
- HI.
- NICOLE.
- HI, BOO.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I THINK EVERY GIRL SHOULD HAVE
A GAY FRIEND NAMED JOEY,
BECAUSE EVERY GUY NAMED JOEY
WHO'S GAY IS [bleep] AMAZING.
- DO I LOOK LIKE
A JUICEHEAD GUIDO, NICOLE?
- YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
FINALLY!
- I'M REALLY EXCITED
FOR NICOLE'S BABY SHOWER,
BUT, UH, I AM
SO BEYOND HUNGOVER.
- SO YOU WORE THE BLUE?
- I DID.
- WHY ARE YOU
WEARING STOCKINGS?
- 'CAUSE I DIDN'T SHAVE
MY LEGS.
- OH.
- [laughs]
- MY GOD. CAN YOU NOT WEAR
STOCKINGS EVER AGAIN?
- I-I DIDN'T SHOWER
THIS MORNING.
- ARE YOU HUNGOVER?
- A LITTLE BIT.
- KEEP DRINKIN'.
I'M DEFINITELY GLAD
THAT JENNI IS HERE WITH ME,
YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE I NEED HER,
AND I'M SO GLAD THAT ALL
MY BEST FRIENDS ARE HERE.
IT FEELS REALLY GOOD.
WANT TO COME GET A DRINK?
- YEAH. WHERE'S YOUR MAN?
- HE'S GOLFING.
[upbeat music]
*
- * I'LL CALL IT QUITS
* SO JUST CALL ME CRAZY
- I'M SWEATING PROFUSELY.
- YOU ARE SWEATING, MAN.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
I TOOK MY BROTHER.
I'M WITH MY FRIENDS,
HAVING FUN,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, OUT
OF NOWHERE, I'M GETTING WEAK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
MY BODY'S STARTING
TO SHUT DOWN. I'M NUMB.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE HECK'S GOING ON.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A LITTLE BIT.
I COULDN'T EVEN FINISH
A ROUND OF GOLF.
I HAVE SOMEBODY DRIVE ME
BACK TO MY CAR.
I THOUGHT OF MAYBE JUST
GETTING SOME FRESH AIR.
I'LL SIT IN THE VAN AND JUST
HAVE THE AIR BLASTING,
HOPING THAT, YOU KNOW,
IT GOES BY.
- [laughs]
WE CAN'T STOP!
- [screams]
- IT LOOKS LIKE A SAFARI.
WHERE ARE ALL THE GUYS?
- BABE.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- THE HOSPITAL.
[overlapping chatter]
- THE SCRATCH-OFFS ARE--I HAVE
A DOOR PRIZE FOR EVERYBODY.
WHO WON? YOU WON?
- DID I WIN?
- SEE THE SECURITY GUARD
AT THE FRONT DOOR?
HE'S YOURS.
YOU TAKE HIM HOME.
[laughter]
- YOUR MOM IS GOING NUTS
RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT'S SHE DOING?
- SHE'S IN HER GLORY.
[laughter]
- IS HE NICE?
- HE WILL BE
WHEN I GET DONE WITH HIM.
[laughter]
- I'M WITH CHRIS' MOM,
AND I'M TALKING
ABOUT ROGER
AND HOW JENNI AND ROGER
HADN'T HAD SEX OR WHATEVER,
AND SHE'S LIKE, "WHY?
I LOVE--I LOVE ROGER."
- WELL, I GET EXCITED AS WELL
ABOUT ROGER,
AND I WAS UPSET
HE WASN'T HERE.
I WANTED TO HIT ON HIM AGAIN.
I TWEETED HIM A PICTURE OF ME
IN A THONG THE OTHER DAY,
AND HE SAID HE THREW UP
IN HIS MOUTH.
- I FEEL LIKE
HE'S LIKE A MEATBALL.
- THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL ME.
THEY CALL ME, LIKE, A GAY
MEATBALL VERSION OF SNOOKI.
- HE KILLS ME.
- KATIE. OPEN PRESENTS.
- YES!
- HEY, EVERYONE.
OH, MY GOD.
[laughter]
I'M OPENING UP PRESENTS
RIGHT NOW.
I REMEMBER THESE WINE GLASSES.
- YEAH.
- VERY HOT.
IS THAT A BEAR?
- IT'LL FIT NICE DOWNSTAIRS.
- THANKS, JUSTINE.
A CHANGING PAD COVER.
- IS THAT A DIAPER BAG
OR JUST A BAG?
- A DIAPER BAG.
THANK YOU!
SO THERE'S, LEGIT, LIKE,
A MILLION PRESENTS RIGHT NOW
THAT I HAVE TO OPEN,
AND I'M SO EXCITED,
BUT HOLY [bleep],
THERE'S A LOT OF PRESENTS.
SAMANTHA. AW!
- OH, MY GOD!
THEY'RE SO CUTE.
[laughter]
- YAY.
[laughs]
- YEAH, SHE'S OPENING
OURS NOW.
- THAT'S CUTE.
- I PICKED THOSE ONES.
- VERY CUTE.
- [laughs]
- NOW WHAT?
- I'M GONNA GIVE IT
MY BEST EFFORT,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA BE CHECKING OUT
OF THIS ASSEMBLY LINE
REAL QUICK.
- OH, MY GOD,
I LOVE THIS!
[overlapping chatter]
- AM I ALLOWED TO TAKE...
- A SINGING THING?
- A POTTY BREAK?
- OW.
A SINGING TOY.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW NICOLE
IS CONTINUING TO OPEN GIFTS.
LIKE, IT GOT TO A POINT
WHERE I WAS LIKE,
"I CAN'T DO THIS [bleep]
ANYMORE."
IT WAS PRETTY RIDICULOUS.
- JIONNI'S APPARENTLY
ON THE GOLF COURSE SOMEWHERE.
MAYBE I SHOULD GO OUT ON A HUNT
AND LOOK FOR HIM.
I THINK THAT'S HIM
IN THE RED.
- DO YOU WANT TO STEAL A CART?
- CAN WE?
- HMM.
- [gasps]
THINK WE'LL GET IN TROUBLE?
- MAYBE IF WE, LIKE,
SURPRISE HER WITH JIONNI--
- IN IT.
- WE HAVE TO FIND HIM.
- WE'RE LOOKING
FOR THE MOTHER-TO-BE'S FIANCE.
- FIANCE. DO YOU KNOW
WHERE JIONNI IS?
[dramatic music]
- I'M SITTING IN MY CAR,
AND I LITERALLY CAN'T FEEL
ANYTHING IN MY BODY.
SOMETHING'S WRONG RIGHT NOW,
AND IT'S A SCARY FEELING
NOT KNOWING WHAT'S GOING ON.
- HERE, I BROUGHT
SOME WATER FOR YOU.
- HELP ME.
- WHAT?
- I'M TIRED.
I JUST WANNA...
CLOSE MY EYES.
MY AUNT COMES
TO CHECK ON ME,
AND SHE'S LIKE,
"YOU HAVE A--
"THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOU.
LET ME GET YOU OUT OF HERE."
ALL I CARE ABOUT IS THIS BABY
SHOWER GOING RIGHT FOR NICOLE,
AND ME BEING SICK
RIGHT NOW IS, BY FAR,
THE WORST THING
THAT COULD HAPPEN.
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW ON THE WAY.
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[whimsical music]
*
- I JUST SENT THE JOEYS OUT
ON A GOLF RUN.
- HEY!
- IS THAT A GIRL?
- WHAT?
- COME ON, JEN.
- WHEN IT COMES
TO BABY SHOWERS,
THEY'RE, LIKE,
OVERWHELMING.
IT'S TEDIOUS WORK OPENING UP
THAT MANY PRESENTS,
AND IT GOT A LITTLE BORING,
SO WE GOT TO MAKE
THE BEST OF IT.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO THIS.
YEAH, SHOW YOUR BOOBS
A LITTLE BIT.
SHOW YOUR PECS.
- [laughs]
- THIS IS WHAT WE DO.
- GAY JOEY!
- WHERE IS HE?
- WHERE ARE YOU?
IS HE, LIKE,
DRUNK SOMEWHERE?
- [laughing]
WE CAN'T STOP!
- [screams]
- IT LOOKS LIKE A SAFARI.
WHERE ARE ALL THE GUYS?
- THE GOLF-CART TRIP
IS SO MUCH FUN RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE NOT SEEN JIONNI AT ALL.
BUT WE'RE MAKING IT LIKE
AN AMUSEMENT PARK RIDE.
WE'RE TRYING TO FIND GAYS
WHEN THERE'S ONLY STRAIGHTS.
IT'S PRETTY FUN.
- OH, THERE'S SOME BOYS
FOR YOU, JOE.
- HEY!
- WE WERE LOOKING FOR YOU.
- COME BACK HERE.
- [squeals]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- CAN YOU--CAN YOU
REVERSE IT, PLEASE?
- IS THAT
YOUR OWN GOLF CART?
- ME AND JENNI HAVE
A QUESTION FOR YOU.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- TYLER.
- TYLER, I'M JOEY.
- WHAT'S UP, BRO?
- DO YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
- NOT AT ALL.
- DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
[laughter]
- I WOULDN'T GO THAT WAY.
- OH.
- AW.
- WE HAVE TO LEAVE.
BYE, TYLER.
- I'M SORRY.
- THAT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN'T COME
TO OUR PARTY ANYMORE.
AND JENNI'S NOT GONNA
SHOW YOU HER [bleep].
- OH, THAT SUCKS.
- SORRY.
- "PARTY, MY CRIB,
2:00 A.M., BRING A BOTTLE."
[laughter]
- WELL, THIS WAS LOVELY.
- THANK YOU, JOE.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU HAVE MY NUMBER.
CALL ME LATER.
- THANK YOU.
- OH, SHE'S OPENING
PRESENTS AGAIN.
- HI, GUYS.
[laughs]
I'M OPENING YOUR GIFT.
THIS IS FROM JWOWW.
[laughter]
BUT WE CALL HER JENNI,
MY BOO-BOO.
- NO, I JUST SIGNED IT "JWOWW"
TO PISS HER OFF.
- OH, MY GOD!
ALCOHOL TESTING STRIPS!
[laughter]
OH, I NEED THAT SO BAD.
- [laughs]
MY GIFT DEFINITELY TOPS
ONE OF NICOLE'S TOP TEN--
ALCOHOL TEST STRIPS
FOR THE BREAST MILK
TO MAKE SURE THAT SHE'S NOT
GETTING LORENZO DRUNK
ON OUR NIGHTS OUT.
- WHERE'S JIONNI?
I WANT YOU TO OPEN GISELLE'S
GIFT. THAT'S SO CUTE.
- [gasps]
OH, JIONNI REALLY WANTED ONE.
WHERE IS HE?
SO JIONNI WAS SUPPOSED TO MAKE
IT TO THE SHOWER, BUT HE DIDN'T,
AND RIGHT NOW I'M JUST WONDERING
IF HE'S HAVING FUN PLAYING GOLF,
OR WHAT IS HE DOING?
WHERE IS HE?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I MISS HIM.
SO THANK YOU GUYS
FOR COMING OUT.
I HOPE YOU GUYS
HAD A GOOD TIME.
- DON'T HOG THE MIC.
- OH. MY MOM TOO.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH,
EVERYONE.
IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE
TO SEE EVERYBODY HERE.
- HONESTLY, I'M VERY HAPPY
THAT THE SHOWER'S OVER.
I LOVE YOU.
- BYE. I LOVE YOU.
- BUT I STILL HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM JIONNI,
AND I'M WONDERING WHERE HE IS
AND WHAT HE'S DOING.
I WISH JIONNI WAS HERE.
SO I NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE
AND FIGURE OUT, LIKE,
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- LOVE YOU.
I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY.
- LOVE YOU, BOO.
[dramatic music]
*
CAN I CALL JIONNI?
[line trilling]
BABE.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- THE HOSPITAL.
- MY WATER JUST BROKE!
- HAVING A BABY
IS COOL AND SCARY.
WE GOTTA GO.
- GO!
[horn honks]
OH, MY GOD, WE'RE LOST!
- ARE YOU READY
FOR THIS, BUDDY?
- CAN'T--CAN'T WAIT.
- I'M SCARED.
I'M FINALLY GOING TO
MEET MY SON.
LIKE, THIS IS A HUGE DEAL.
LET'S DO THIS.
- HERE WE GO.
LITTLE MORE, LITTLE MORE.
- [groans]
[cheering]
- YAY! A BOY!
- [voice breaking] I'M SO HAPPY
THAT LORENZO'S FINALLY HERE.
[sniffles]
HE'S PERFECT.
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS THAT?
- THAT'S ALL THEY HAD
FOR A TAXI.
- WHO GETS A PINK LIMO
WITHOUT PROPOSING?
- WHY NOT CELEBRATE?
- CELEBRATE WHAT?
- US, JUST HAVING
A NIGHT OUT.
- ALL SET?
- THINK SO.
- REALLY?
SO IT'S JUST DINNER?
- YOU'RE GETTING ENGAGED.
- HE NEVER PROPOSED.
I JUST WANT TO GO OUT.
[club music]
- [screams]
I'M BACK, AND I'M, LIKE,
A MEATBALL AGAIN, AND I LOVE IT.
- * I LIKE THE WAY
YOU SHAKE THAT ASS *
all:
SURPRISE!
- THESE LAST FOUR YEARS
HAVE BEEN CRAZY.
[thud]
- OH, MY GOD!
JIONNI.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- I DIDN'T SEE IT.
[laughs]
[cork pops]
[squeals]
[screams]
- NO, NO, NO.
STOP!
[flatulence]
- [laughs] OH, GOD.
HIS FARTS ARE SO LOUD.
HE'S SO COOL.
- * I WANT TO FLY AWAY
WITH YOU *
- OH, MY GOD. NICOLE!
- [screams]
- WHO'S THAT?
- CHEERS. BEST FRIENDS.
- BEST FRIENDS.
FOREVER?
- FOREVER.
- MWAH! LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU.