- I THINK SHE'’S DEFINITELY
THE GIRL FOR ME
AND I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE IT
TO THAT NEXT STEP.
- SHE'’S BEEN,
UH, APPROVED, YEAH.
SHE'’S GETTING THE APPROVAL.
- I CONSIDER MYSELF TO MAKE
GOOD CHOICES IN MY LIFE
AND IT MAKES ME FEEL GOOD
TO HAVE MY DAD ENDORSE ME
PROPOSING TO JENNI, YOU KNOW?
- NO ONE CARES ABOUT ME ANYMORE.
- [laughs]
- LIKE, SERIOUSLY
WHEN WE HAVE TIME,
WE NEED TO GO ON VACATION,
SO WE CAN GET IT BACK.
IT JUST SUCKS THAT, YOU KNOW, WE
DON'’T HAVE THAT SPARK ANYMORE.
I JUST WANT JIONNI TO LOVE ME.
WE LOST IT.
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- ♪ ONE, TWO ♪
♪ I JUST WANT BACK MY SHOE
FROM YOU ♪
♪ I JUST WANT BACK MY SHOE ♪
- YAY!
OH, MY GOD.
GOT MY FEET BACK.
AWESOME.
THANK GOD.
MY FEET ARE BACK TO NORMAL
AND I CAN WEAR MY SEXY SHOES.
HO, HO.
YEAH.
I DON'’T HAVE CANKLES ANYMORE.
I FEEL LIKE A BRAND-NEW WOMAN.
[cackles]
[clicks tongue]
FORGOT WHAT THIS FEELS LIKE.
LOOK!
- WHOA.
- I FIT IN MY SHOES AGAIN.
- WHY ARE YOU ALL DRESSED UP?
SHOULD I PUT
A SUIT AND TIE ON?
- JIONNI?
DO YOU EVEN CARE THAT
MY FEET ARE BACK TO NORMAL?
JUST PRETEND YOU CARE.
- OH, MY GOD, YOUR SHOES FIT!
- YEAH!
JUST STOP TALKING.
YOU'’RE REALLY PISSING ME OFF.
- OKAY.
JUST STOP TELLING ME
YOUR SHOES FIT.
- I SAID IT ONCE!
- OKAY.
- THEY FIT.
I COULDN'’T EVEN
GET MY BIG TOE IN THIS.
- [whistles]
- ARE YOU TURNED ON?
- YEAH.
- YOU'’RE NOT EVEN LOOKING.
- WHY ARE YOU DRESSED UP?
- BECAUSE IT MAKES ME
FEEL BETTER.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'’M GONNA PUT JEANS ON THEN.
- OH, MY GOD.
ISN'’T THAT COOL THOUGH?
- YEAH, IT'’S AWESOME.
- SO I DON'’T HAVE TO RETURN
ANY OF MY SHOES.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
THEY WOULD BE TOO SMALL.
- YEAH, PUTTING ON
A BUTTON DOWN.
[sighs]
- DON'’T BE ANNOYING.
- WHAT?
I WAS GONNA PUT A SHIRT ON.
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'’RE DRESSED UP TO THE T.
- BECAUSE I'’M A GIRL.
- LOOK AT ME IN MY GYM OUTFIT.
- WHO CARES?
- ARE YOU HUNGRY?
- I'’M STARVING.
- ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- UM, A SANDWICH.
- OKAY.
HOW'’S OUR SON DOING?
YOU PAYING ATTENTION TO HIM?
- YES.
- [giggles]
WE KINDA BICKER A LITTLE BIT
BACK AND FORTH.
IT'’S SOMEWHAT OF A JOKE, BUT I
SOMEWHAT KNOW SHE'’S NOT JOKING.
AND THAT'’S WHY I KEEP IT GOING
BECAUSE I TRY TO PISS HER OFF
A LITTLE BIT.
IT'’S KINDA FUN.
WE NEED TO GO FOR A DRINK OR--
- NO DRINKS.
[baby farts]
- [giggles]
THIS KID FARTS MORE THAN YOU.
- JIONNI, SHUT UP.
GO. GO.
- I'’LL HOLD--I'’LL GET THE DOOR.
- CAN NICOLE SLEEP
UP HERE TONIGHT?
- NO.
- WE'’RE NOT GETTING ALONG.
- WHY?
- '’CAUSE.
- SHE HAS A BUG IN HER BUTT.
- NO, I DON'’T.
- JIONNI, JUST BE NICE.
THEY HAVE HORMONES.
- WE'’RE NOT WORKING.
- NO, WE'’RE NOT.
- START PACKING YOUR [bleep].
LEAVE THE KID.
- SO JIONNI'’S JOKING AROUND,
TELLING ME TO PACK MY BAGS,
WE'’RE NOT WORKING.
ONLY BECAUSE
WE'’RE BOTH SO TIRED.
WE'’RE NEW PARENTS.
AND YOU KNOW, I THINK A BABY
CHANGES A RELATIONSHIP.
SO ME AND JIONNI
JUST NEED TO WORK ON IT.
OW. STOP.
- I DIDN'’T KNOW.
- YOU HURT ME.
- IT'’S NOT WORKING.
- ALL RIGHT, MOVE OUT.
- IT'’S MY HOUSE.
- NO, IT'’S NOT.
IT'’S YOUR MOM'’S HOUSE.
- ♪ WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU TRY TOO HARD ♪
- WHAT IS IT,
ABOUT AN EIGHT HOUR DRIVE?
- 12.
- [giggles]
- IT DEPENDS ON HOW FAST
YOU GET TO THAT BLUE BRIDGE
AT NEW HAMPSHIRE TO MAINE.
- HOW'’S ROGER'’S DAD DOING?
- HE'’S ACTUALLY REALLY GOOD.
GAINING HIS WEIGHT BACK.
- AWESOME.
- SO THAT'’S EXCITING.
- YEP.
WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
- YOU'’RE GONNA LOVE IT.
- THANK YOU.
- YAY.
THANK YOU.
- HERE YOU GO.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
ME AND ROGER GETTING ENGAGED?
- OH?
- NOT THAT I'’M SAYING
HE'’S GOING TO.
- WAS THAT THE REAL REASON
YOU BROUGHT ME HERE?
I THINK IT'’S FANTASTIC.
- REALLY?
- YEAH, YOU GUYS ARE
THE TYPICAL COUPLE,
ARGUING ALL THE TIME,
SO WHY NOT?
- YOU DIDN'’T
HEAR ANYTHING, DID YOU?
- YEAH. WHAT?
- WHAT?
- HEAR ABOUT WHAT?
- HE DIDN'’T ASK YOU?
- WHAT? FOR, LIKE, MY BLESSING
AND, UH, ALL THAT?
- YEAH.
- NO.
I THINK THAT'’D BE KIND OF WEIRD.
- ASKING YOU?
- BECAUSE WE KNOW EACH OTHER.
WE'’VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR A WHILE.
SO IT WOULD BE LIKE HIM TRYING
TO GET ME AT A POINT
AND BEING ALL SERIOUS.
- YEAH, IT'’S LIKE
MEET THE FOCKERS.
- [laughs]
- IF ROGER DID COME TO MY DAD
FOR MY HAND IN MARRIAGE,
I FEEL LIKE MY DAD WOULD LAUGH
AND GO OUT TO, LIKE,
A STRIP CLUB WITH HIM.
THE LAST THING I'’M DOING
IS PRESSURING HIM.
ESPECIALLY
WITH A BIG RING I WANT.
SO I KNOW
THAT'’S GONNA TAKE TIME.
- YOU'’RE NOT BEING SELFISH,
ARE YOU?
JUST WANTING A BIG ROCK.
- THAT TOO.
THE RING IS LIKE A STATUS.
- WELL, GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
- THANK YOU.
- [laughs]
- BUT WHAT I HIT YOU UP
EARLIER ABOUT...
- YEAH?
- I WAS THINKING ABOUT
BRINGING ROGER UPSTATE.
- WELL, YOU MENTIONED, LIKE,
A LOT OF MORE RELATIVES
THAT HE HASN'’T MET YET
AND STUFF, BUT I'’M--
- NO, WELL, THE ONE BIG ONE
WOULD BE MOM.
- OH, OKAY.
I DIDN'’T THINK OF THAT,
I'’M SORRY.
- IS THAT A GOOD IDEA?
- I MEAN, DEPENDING ON
HOW YOU DO IT.
- YOU THINK
THEY WON'’T SCARE HIM?
- NO.
- MY MOM LIVES
IN UPSTATE NEW YORK.
SHE'’S BEEN LIVING
IN AN ASSISTED LIVING HOME.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT, I DON'’T
GET TO SEE HER VERY OFTEN.
SINCE I WAS TWO,
THAT'’S ALL I'’VE KNOWN.
IT'’S SO COMPLICATED.
- YEAH, I DON'’T KNOW
IF IT WOULD WORK.
- I HAVEN'’T SEEN MOM IN--WHAT?
TWO YEARS? 16 MONTHS?
- YEAH, SO BEEN A WHILE.
- I DON'’T KNOW, UM,
IF SHE'’D BE INTERESTED...
- RIGHT.
- IN MEETING ROGER.
HOPEFULLY.
IT'’S A VERY, LIKE,
TOUCHY SUBJECT
AND IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH ROGER.
IT ONLY HAS TO DO WITH MY MOTHER
AND HER CONDITION.
SO, FOR ROGER TO MEET HER,
THAT WOULD BE COOL,
BUT, LIKE,
IT'’S TOTALLY UP TO MY MOM.
ONE DAY I WAS TALKING
TO HER AND SHE'’S LIKE,
"I'’M NOT [bleep] MEETING HIM."
- I THINK
YOU TOLD ME THAT.
- ON SPEAKER PHONE,
AND ROGER HEARD IT.
- OH, JEEZ.
DID YOU EXPLAIN TO HIM?
- YEAH,
SHE'’S [bleep] MOODY, MAN.
- RIGHT, SHE'’S LIKE
A LIGHT SWITCH.
BOOP BOOP.
- ROGER MIGHT GET FREAKED OUT.
- ♪ ARE WE IN LOVE,
ARE WE IN LOVE ♪
♪ OR IS IT IMPOSSIBLE ♪
♪ TO GET BACK TO WHERE WE WERE ♪
- NICOLE, THE FOOD'’S READY.
- I HAVE A HEADACHE.
OUCH.
EW.
I DON'’T LIKE THAT.
- YOU DON'’T GOTTA EAT IT.
THIS IS IT, BABE.
THIS IS WHAT DINNER'’S
GONNA BE LIKE.
JUST US THREE.
OUR FIRST FAMILY DINNER.
COULD I CHANGE MY SHIRT?
- UH-HUH.
- NOT EATING WITH A STAIN ON IT.
- SO I FEEL LIKE YOU'’RE GETTING
MAD '’CAUSE OF THE BABY.
- I AM.
- WHY?
- '’CAUSE YOU'’RE TAKING CONTROL
OF EVERYTHING.
- I'’M NOT TAKING CONTROL
OF ANYTHING.
- YOU ARE THOUGH.
- I'’M GOING BY
WHAT THE DOCTOR SAYS.
I DON'’T KNOW [bleep].
- I JUST FEEL LIKE YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO CORRECT ME,
AND IT'’S GETTING ANNOYING.
I JUST WISH YOU WOULD PAY
ATTENTION TO ME A LITTLE BIT.
- WELL--
- IT'’S LIKE I'’M NOT
HERE ANYMORE.
AND YOU DON'’T CARE.
- IT'’S NOT THAT I'’M NOT
PAYING ATTENTION TO YOU.
IT'’S WE GOTTA PAY A LOT MORE
ATTENTION TO HIM.
WHY ARE YOU MAD NOW?
- I'’M NOT.
I DON'’T KNOW
WHY WE'’RE TALKING ABOUT THIS.
'’CAUSE I DON'’T REALLY WANT
TO TALK ABOUT THIS RIGHT NOW.
NOT AT DINNER.
- THEN WHEN?
- MAYBE WHEN WE'’RE CUDDLING
ON THE COUCH OR SOMETHING.
- WHY WOULD I WANNA RUIN
A CUDDLING MOMENT?
- I DON'’T WANNA RUIN DINNER.
I KNOW, BUT EVEN, LIKE,
IN BED WE DON'’T CUDDLE ANYMORE.
- YEAH, WE DO.
- NO, WE DON'’T.
- YES, WE DO.
- YOU NEVER KISS ME ANYMORE.
- YEAH, I DO.
- NO, YOU DON'’T.
- THAT'’S NOT HOW IT IS.
- YEAH, IT IS.
- THIS OBVIOUSLY
PUT YOU IN A BAD MOOD.
AND I DON'’T WANT YOU
IN A BAD MOOD.
- SO STOP TALKING ABOUT IT.
HOW LONG DOES TACOS TAKE?
- 1/2 HOUR, 20 MINUTES.
- I'’M DEFINITELY A LITTLE WARY
ABOUT MAKING DINNER TONIGHT
BECAUSE I DON'’T KNOW
WHERE TO BEGIN.
OW!
[baby fusses]
UGH.
[smoke detector beeps]
[screams]
[Lorenzo cries]
I HATE YOU.
- AND I JUST WISH YOU WOULD PAY
ATTENTION TO ME A LITTLE BIT.
- WELL--
- I JUST FEEL LIKE
YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO CORRECT ME,
AND IT'’S GETTING ANNOYING.
- AND THAT'’S NOT MY INTENTIONS.
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU HAPPY?
- THIS HEADACHE TO GO AWAY.
[Lorenzo fusses]
- JUST WAIT A LITTLE BIT.
[slight laugh]
- SEE?
- I WAS JUST SAYING
'’CAUSE HE'’S--
ALL RIGHT, GO AHEAD.
THAT'’S NOT CORRECTING YOU,
IT'’S--
- NO, IT'’S LIKE YOU'’RE THE BOSS.
- I'’M NOT THE BO--
- IT HAS TO GO
HOW YOU WANT IT TO GO.
- ALL RIGHT, FEED HIM.
- I FEEL LIKE I'’M DOING
A GOOD JOB RIGHT NOW.
AND, YOU KNOW, HE'’S JUST MAKING
ME FEEL BAD AND IT SUCKS.
- HE'’S MY SON, I WANNA MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING'’S GOOD.
- OKAY, HE'’S MY SON TOO.
- JEEZ.
- ANNOYING.
- WHAT ARE YOU
GETTING AT THE STORE?
- FORMULA.
FOOD.
- ARE YOU STILL COOKING DINNER?
- YOU WANT ME TO COOK?
SORRY.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- OKAY.
- IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
I GUESS.
- WHY'’D YOU HESITATE?
- BECAUSE I DON'’T KNOW
HOW TO COOK.
I THINK IT'’S A TERRIBLE IDEA
FOR ME TO COOK DINNER, BECAUSE
I DON'’T KNOW HOW TO COOK,
BUT I'’M EXCITED
TO GO GROCERY SHOPPING
BECAUSE THIS IS WHAT MOMS DO.
YOU GO TO THE GROCERY STORE,
YOU GET FOOD FOR YOUR FAMILY,
AND I'’M JUST EXCITED
TO PLAY HOUSE.
- YOU WANT ME
TO MAKE YOU A LIST?
- SURE. CAN I HAVE
YOUR CREDIT CARD?
- YEAH.
- JOKING.
- SO WAS I.
- YOU'’RE ANNOYING.
I'’M NOT COOKING FOR YOU.
- WE NEED MEAT.
THAT'’S IT.
- YOU WANT TACOS TONIGHT?
- IT'’S TACO THURSDAY.
- FINE.
I GUESS.
- BYE, LORENZO.
- GO.
- I LOVE YOU.
- NICOLE HAS A BETTER CHANCE OF
ANSWERING A CALCULUS QUESTION
THAN COMING HOME
WITH EXACTLY WHAT SHE WANTED
FROM THE GROCERY STORE.
[upbeat pop music]
♪ ♪
- HI.
THE [bleep] DO YOU GET IN
THIS PLACE?
I NEED A CART.
THE LAST TIME I WENT TO THE
GROCERY STORE WAS IN COLLEGE,
AND I BOUGHT MYSELF
CEREAL AND APPLE JUICE.
LIKE, I'’VE NEVER REALLY
BEEN GROCERY SHOPPING
FOR A FAMILY BEFORE.
I FEEL VERY OUT OF PLACE.
THESE ARE ALL DAMN APPLES.
IS THIS AN APPLE?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHERE'’S THE FUZZY ONES?
OH.
I'’M TRYING TO FIND PEACHES,
BUT I'’M IN THE APPLES.
EVERYTHING SHOULD BE LABELED
WITH, LIKE, BIG LETTERS.
HOW MANY DO YOU TAKE?
YOU SPELLED "MEAT" WRONG, IDIOT.
ON THE GROCERY LIST,
JIONNI WROTE "M-E-E-T."
LIKE, REALLY?
[metal clangs]
OOH, [bleep].
I DON'’T KNOW WHAT
THE [bleep] I'’M DOING.
DO YOU USE THIS FOR TACO MEAT?
- YEP.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- POSITIVE.
- OKAY.
IT'’S LIKE AN ALL DAY PROJECT.
DO YOU HAVE DORITOS?
THANK YOU.
- YOU'’RE WELCOME.
- SQUASH SOUNDS DISGUSTING.
SO I'’M BUYING BABY FOOD BECAUSE
I DEFINITELY WANNA TEST IT
AND SEE HOW NASTY IT IS.
MAC AND CHEESE
AND VEGGIES.
EW.
I AM NOT ONE THAT WANTS TO FEED
MY BABY, LIKE, STORE FOOD.
PRUNES!
[bleep] GROSS.
I WANNA MAKE MY OWN BABY FOOD.
[gasps]
SPAGHETTI WITH CHEESE.
[bleep] NASTY.
I'’M A LITTLE WARY
ABOUT MAKING DINNER TONIGHT
BECAUSE I DON'’T KNOW
WHERE TO BEGIN,
BUT I'’M GONNA TRY.
OW!
[pan sizzles]
OH!
THESE ARE COOKED.
AHH!
OW!
OOH.
[Lorenzo fusses]
UGH.
AS I'’M COOKING RIGHT NOW,
I'’M KINDA PLAYING HOUSE
IN MY HEAD,
BUT, UM, IN REALITY,
I MEAN, I'’M HORRIBLE.
[smoke detector beeps]
[screams]
[laughs]
I HATE YOU.
[Lorenzo cries]
UGH!
- DID HIS THING FALL OFF YET?
- YEP.
GOT IT OFF.
- OH, I'’LL SHOW YOU.
- SHE KEPT IT.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BACON STRIP.
I DON'’T KNOW
IF THIS IS GROSS TO SAVE.
- I WOULD STOP TOUCHING IT.
- [laughs]
- YOU SEEM LIKE
YOU'’RE NOT IN A GOOD MOOD.
IT HAS TO DO WITH
YOU MEETING MY MOTHER.
I HAVEN'’T INTRODUCED REALLY
ANYONE TO MY MOM,
LET ALONE A BOYFRIEND.
- DO YOU THINK
THERE'’LL EVER BE A POINT
WHERE YOU'’RE COMFORTABLE
WITH ME MEETING HER OR NO?
[smoke detector beeps]
- [screams]
MY GOD.
[laughs]
[Lorenzo cries]
I HATE YOU.
UGH.
- THE SMOKE ALARM WENT OFF?
- JUST ONCE.
- YOU DIDN'’T TELL ME--
- LORENZO--
- WHY DIDN'’T YOU TELL ME THAT?
- '’CAUSE IT WASN'’T A BIG DEAL.
OH, THIS SUCKS.
AY-YI-YI.
SOMETIMES THE ALARM GOES OFF
WHEN YOU COOK
BECAUSE THERE'’S SMOKE.
- MY SON'’S IN THE HOUSE!
- HE'’S FINE.
I JUST TOLD YOU
HE DIDN'’T EVEN WAKE UP.
MMM!
I'’M A CHEF.
MMM.
I LIKE THIS FEELING
OF PREPARING FOOD FOR MY FAMILY.
MAYBE I CAN LEARN HOW TO COOK.
THAT'’S GOOD.
- OOH.
WOW, LOOK AT THIS.
OH, MAN.
- DIG IN.
- YOU DID ALL THIS?
- YEAH.
- YOU PUT DORITOS IN YOUR SALAD.
I'’VE NEVER HEARD OF THAT.
- IT'’S MY MOM'’S RECIPE.
- MY MOM MUST HAVE HELPED YOU.
- NO, I SWEAR.
ASK HER.
- OKAY.
- I SWEAR.
- WHAT, ARE YOU
TURNING OVER A NEW LEAF?
- IT'’S NEW LEAGUE.
- NEW LEAF.
- NEW LEAGUE.
LEAGUE, LEAF.
YOU'’RE TURNING OVER SOMETHING
AND THAT MEANS
YOU'’RE DOING A GOOD JOB.
- I WAS REALLY IMPRESSED.
- YAY.
AT LEAST I COULD DO SOMETHING.
- AND YOU'’RE CLEANING THE TABLE.
SOMETHING MUST BE UP.
YOU MUST WANT SOMETHING.
I CAN TELL.
- NO.
- YOU WANT SOMETHING.
- NO, I DON'’T.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- JUST TELL ME.
- I DON'’T WANT ANYTHING.
- YOU SHOULD ASK FOR IT NOW.
- YOU WANNA DO IT?
- NO.
- OH.
- SICKO.
WHAT'’S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOUR VAGINA WILL BURST.
- [laughs]
EW.
- ♪ I GOTTA LET YOU KNOW ♪
- HELLO, MONKEY.
- HI.
- WANT ME TO MASSAGE
YOUR BOOBIES?
- NO.
- WOW.
- WHAT?
- HOLY CRAP,
YOU JUST HATE THE WORLD TODAY.
- YEAH.
UGH, MY CALVES HURT.
- NOT SURPRISED THERE.
SOMETHING ON YOU HURTS?
NO WAY.
- WILL YOU STOP?
- NO, I CAN'’T BELIEVE IT.
- HEY, BILLY.
- WHAT'’S UP, GUYS?
- BASICALLY MY MOOD TODAY
IS BASED OFF THE FACT
THAT TOMORROW I WAS
SUPPOSED TO GO SEE MY MOM,
AND I REALLY DON'’T
FEEL LIKE IT,
AND I HAVEN'’T EVEN BEEN ABLE
TO TELL ROGER ABOUT IT.
- ONE, AND TWO, AND THREE.
- PUSH THAT [bleep].
[struggling breath]
THAT'’S HEAVY, YEAH.
- HALF MY FAMILY DOESN'’T EVEN
KNOW MY MOTHER.
SO FOR MY BOYFRIEND TO MEET
MY MOM, THAT'’S A BIG THING.
I'’M GOOD, I WANNA GO HOME.
- I DO WORK, MAN.
I DON'’T COME HERE
TO WALK, YOU KNOW?
- LET'’S GO.
- YOU KNOW, THE LAST COUPLE
OF DAYS WITH JENNI,
SHE'’S NOT HERSELF, YOU KNOW?
I GUESS MAYBE
IT'’S THE MAINE TRIP
THAT TOOK A TOLL ON HER,
OR I REALLY DON'’T KNOW.
SHE JUST HASN'’T BEEN HERSELF.
WHAT UP, BUSTER BROWN?
WHAT UP?
- I'’M SORRY
IF I'’M IN A BAD MOOD.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
- YOU WOULD NEVER KNOW.
- ♪ I KNOW WHY ♪
♪ I WAS LOST IN MY OWN MIND ♪
- HELLO?
- HEY, BOO.
- WHATCHA DOING?
- OH, NOTHING.
SO WHAT'’S GOING ON OVER THERE?
IS LORENZO SLEEPING FINALLY?
- YEAH, HE'’S SLEEPING.
I JUST COOKED SO.
- WHAT DID YOU COOK?
- TACOS.
- YUM.
- SO CAN I SEE YOU TOMORROW?
- YEAH.
UM, I WAS THINKING
ABOUT GETTING UP EARLY,
SHOWERING, AND HEADING UP
IF YOU DON'’T MIND
BECAUSE I'’M AGITATED.
- WHY?
- WE'’LL TALK ABOUT IT TOMORROW.
I'’M NOT EVEN FEEDING
INTO IT AT THIS POINT.
- WELL, THAT SUCKS.
- WELL, I CAN'’T WAIT
TO SEE YOU
AND LORENZO
AND JIONNI TOMORROW.
- ME TOO.
- I LOVE YOU.
- GOOD LUCK.
- THANKS.
I'’LL NEED IT.
- BYE.
[snaps fingers]
DO YOU WANNA BE LEFT ALONE?
- I DON'’T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
YOU SEEM LIKE YOU'’RE NOT
IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY, SO.
- I WASN'’T IN
A GOOD MOOD TODAY,
BUT IT HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
IT HAS TO DO
WITH YOU MEETING MY MOTHER.
IT'’S NOT LIKE, "OH, HI.
I'’M JUST GOING TO SEE MY MOM."
LIKE YOU GO SEE
YOUR MOM IN FLORIDA.
I'’M NOT COMFORTABLE
WITH SEEING HER.
I'’VE ALWAYS, SINCE DAY ONE,
SINCE I WAS TWO YEARS OLD,
KEPT MY MOTHER AT A DISTANCE.
- I'’LL BE THERE IF YOU WANT ME
TO MEET YOUR MOM, I'’M--
- IT REALLY HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
I DON'’T MIND--I KNOW YOU HAVE
ENOUGH RESPECT TO MEET HER
AND UNDERSTAND THE CONDITION.
IT'’S ME AND THIS
IS WHAT I GREW UP WITH.
THIS IS WHAT I D--HALF MY FAMILY
DOESN'’T EVEN KNOW HER.
- I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'’RE SAYING JENNI.
HOWEVER, I ALSO KNOW THAT YOU
HAVE A MOTHER WHO YOU LOVE.
AND YOU LOVE HER TO THIS DAY,
I KNOW THAT YOU DO.
SO IT'’S NOT LIKE
SHE'’S JUST SOME FORGOTTEN PERSON
THAT WE DON'’T SPEAK OF.
EVERY TIME
YOU SPEAK TO YOUR MOM,
WHICH IS PRETTY REGULAR,
YOU TELL HER
YOU'’RE COMING TO SEE HER.
SO IS THAT EVER
ACTUALLY GONNA HAPPEN?
- SOON.
- OKAY.
- SOON WHEN I'’M MENTALLY ABLE
TO GO THERE
AND THEN D--HAVE ENOUGH TIME
TO DEAL WITH IT
WHEN I GET OUT OF THERE.
- OKAY.
IT'’S A VERY UNIQUE SITUATION.
IT'’S A DELICATE SITUATION.
I'’M NOT GOING TO PRESSURE HER
IN ANY WAY, SHAPE, OR FORM.
I'’M COMFORTABLE MEETING HER MOM
WHEN JENNI'’S COMFORTABLE
INTRODUCING ME TO HER MOM,
YOU KNOW?
IT'’S CLEAR TO ME IT HAS A LOT OF
EMOTIONAL MEANING TO YOU.
SO IF YOU'’RE THAT ADAMANT
ABOUT IT, JENNI,
THEN--THEN THAT'’S FINE.
- NO, I GET THAT.
- YOU--YOU THINK
THERE WILL EVER BE A POINT
WHERE YOU'’RE COMFORTABLE
WITH ME MEETING HER OR NO?
- [laughs]
[gags]
- PLEASE DON'’T THROW UP.
I'’M BEGGING YOU, PLEASE.
- YOU'’RE EATING A TONGUE.
I DON'’T THINK THERE'’S ANYTHING
THAT JENNI WON'’T PUT IN HER
MOUTH BESIDES ROGER'’S [bleep].
- DO YOU THINK
THERE'’LL EVER BE A POINT
WHERE YOU'’RE COMFORTABLE
WITH ME MEETING HER OR NO?
- MAYBE.
I DON'’T MIND
PEOPLE MEETING MY MOTHER.
- I'’M JUST CURIOUS WILL THAT
DAY--WHEN WILL THAT DAY EV--
WILL IT EVER COME
OR NEVER COME?
- I'’M SURE IT'’LL COME.
I WILL SEE HER.
I'’VE NEVER SET A DATE
FOR MY MOM TO SEE HER.
I'’VE ALWAYS SAID
I WOULD BE UP THERE.
- SOON?
- WHEN I'’M COMFORTABLE
WITH SEEING HER.
- I UNDERSTAND THAT, SO, AGAIN,
NO PRESSURE FROM ME AT ALL.
I'’M SURE IT'’S TOUGH.
I'’M--I'’M--I--
- NOBODY GETS THAT.
- IT'’S COMPLETELY UP TO JENNI
WHEN WE DO THIS, YOU KNOW?
SO I'’M COMFORTABLE WITH IT
WHEN JENNI'’S COMFORTABLE
WITH IT, YOU KNOW?
YOU DON'’T HAVE TO EXPLAIN
ANYTHING FURTHER TO M--TO ME.
I-I UNDERSTAND.
- THANK YOU.
- NO PROBLEM.
- [kisses]
LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU.
- [laughs]
- ♪ OH, WE ALL COPE ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'’S GOT THEIR WAYS ♪
♪ YEAH, I KNOW I'’VE GOT MINE ♪
- HEY, YOU WANNA
TRY SOME BABY FOOD?
SOME DAY WE ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO MAKE THIS FOR OUR SON.
I'’M GONNA BLINDFOLD YOU
AND YOU'’RE GONNA TRY
EVERY ONE OF '’EM.
YOU'’VE GOTTA TELL ME
WHAT YOU THINK IT IS.
[chuckles]
PLEASE?
- OKAY, BUT YOU ALSO.
- NO, IT'’S NOT FUNNY.
- JIONNI!
- IT'’S ONLY FUNNY IF YOU DO IT.
- NO!
I'’M GETTING A BLINDFOLD.
YOU'’RE A BULLY.
I WANNA TEST BABY FOOD
BECAUSE I KNOW
IT GETS RECALLED ALL THE TIME.
- WELL, YOU'’RE GETTING
BLINDFOLDED.
- WELL, SO ARE YOU.
- OKAY.
- AND I WANNA KNOW, LIKE,
HOW BAD THE [bleep] TASTES.
AND I WANT JIONNI
TO KNOW HOW BAD IT SUCKS.
WATCH MY EYELASHES!
- WHAT?
YOU CAN SEE.
- I CAN'’T SEE [bleep].
- OKAY, LET'’S SEE
WHICH ONE YOU LIKE THE BEST.
- DON'’T GIVE ME A LOT.
- ONLY ONE?
- YEAH.
- OR TWO?
- JUST ONE!
- NICOLE IS GONNA
HAVE A TASTE OF SOME CORN,
SOME MASHED POTATOES,
SOME GABAGOOL.
I'’M MIXING EVERY ONE OF THESE.
- [giggles]
[gags]
- PLEASE DON'’T THROW UP.
I'’M BEGGING YOU, PLEASE.
PLEASE.
- TOO BAD.
- PLEASE.
ARE YOU CRYING?
GO TO THE BATHROOM.
AND WE'’RE GONNA
FEED OUR KID THIS?
- I DON'’T EVEN THINK
BABIES HAVE TASTE BUDS,
BECAUSE IF THEY WERE
TO EAT THIS,
I THINK THEY WOULD
ALL THROW UP.
THAT WAS SO BAD.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
IT DOESN'’T EVEN TASTE LIKE FOOD.
UGH!
YOUR TURN.
- DO YOU KNOW
LITTLE KIDS EAT THIS
AND WE'’RE ACTING LIKE BABIES?
- IT TASTES LIKE [bleep].
JIONNI!
I'’M GONNA DO
WHAT YOU DID TO ME.
[laughs]
- OH, GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, IT'’S DISGUSTING.
- I KNOW.
- WHICH ONE DID YOU DO?
- THESE TWO.
- YOU MIXED?
- LIKE YOU DID.
- ALL RIGHT, CAN I TELL YOU
WHAT I REALLY GAVE YOU?
- WHAT?
- I GAVE YOU ALL OF THEM.
- YOU'’RE AN [bleep].
IT TASTES LIKE [bleep].
- I'’M GONNA THROW UP.
- ♪ I WAS WALKING
DOWN THE STREET ♪
♪ KEPT SHUFFLING,
SHUFFLING MY FEET ♪
- IT'’S JEWISH.
- WHAT'’S JEWISH FOOD
TASTE LIKE?
IT TURNS OUT
IT'’S A JEWISH RESTAURANT,
AND IT'’S DEFINITELY
A DIFFERENT PLACE.
- OH, WHAT'’S THAT?
- IT'’S A COLESLAW
AND THE SOUR PICKLES.
- WHAT THE [bleep] IS THIS?
- WANNA CHEERS?
- WHY ARE THEY DIFFERENT COLORS?
- ONE'’S A GREEN, ONE'’S A...
- [laughs]
I WANNA KNOW
WHAT A SALTY LOX IS.
- KOSHER SALAMI.
- SEASIDE PLATTERS.
- WHAT IS TONGUE?
- ASK HIM.
- WHAT KIND OF TONGUE?
IS IT JUST CODE WORD FOR
SOMETHING OR IS IT LEGIT TONGUE?
- ASK HIM.
- HELLO.
- SHE HAS A QUESTION.
- YES, ABSOLUTELY.
- UNDER THE HOLLYWOOD SALAD,
WHAT IS TONGUE?
- TONGUE IS A BEEF TONGUE WHICH
WE TAKE IT AND WE CURE IT.
HERE'’S A SAMPLE.
- TONGUE?
- YEAH.
- SO THAT'’S A COW TONGUE?
I DARE YOU TO TRY IT.
- YOU JUST EAT IT LIKE THIS?
- WE MAKE SANDWICHES OUT OF IT.
WE CAN MAKE
A HOT SANDWICH OUT OF IT.
- YOU'’RE EATING A TONGUE.
- YEAH, IT'’S GOOD.
- IT ACTUALLY TASTES LIKE HAM.
- UGH.
I DON'’T THINK THERE'’S ANYTHING
THAT JENNI WON'’T PUT
IN HER MOUTH AT THIS POINT
BESIDES ROGER'’S [bleep].
SO HOW IS ROGER?
- UM, WERE FIGHTING YESTERDAY.
- WHY?
- I DIDN'’T REALIZE HOW BIG
OF A [bleep] I WAS BEING.
I WANTED TO PLAN US
TO SEE MY MOM,
AND THEN YESTERDAY
I WAS CHANGING MY MIND.
- BUT DO YOU WANT HIM
TO MEET YOUR MOM?
- OF COURSE HE'’D LIKE TO MEET
HER, BUT HE DOESN'’T WANT TO,
LIKE, PRESSURE ME.
LIKE, "I HAVE TO MEET YOUR MOM."
IT'’S JUST WEIRD.
YOU AND JIONNI
ARE STRESSED OUT?
- WE'’RE JUST LACKING SLEEP
SO, LIKE, WE'’RE BOTH GRUMPY.
- YOU'’RE A LEGIT FAMILY.
- THAT'’S WHY I LOVE
JIONNI'’S FAMILY SO MUCH.
EVERYONE'’S, LIKE, HAPPY
AND IN LOVE.
SUCH A FAMILY.
THAT'’S NOT MY FAMILY.
- MY PARENTS GOT DIVORCED
AROUND THE SAME TIME YOURS DID.
- THAT'’S WHEN I BECAME
A BAD CHILD.
- THAT'’S PROBABLY ROGER'’S
BIGGEST CONCERN ON MARRIAGE.
- DIVORCE?
- I THINK IT'’S A LOT HARDER
TO TRUST IN A RELATIONSHIP
AND WANNA GET MARRIED
WHEN YOU'’RE A CHILD OF DIVORCE.
AND ME AND ROGER ARE BOTH
CHILDREN OF DIVORCES,
AND, YOU KNOW, IT'’S HARD
TO LOOK TOWARDS THE FUTURE.
MARRIAGE IS SUCH
A, LIKE, HUGE COMMITMENT.
SCARY.
TO ONLY THINK
YOU'’RE GONNA BE WITH ONE PERSON
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
- I'’M READY FOR IT.
- I KNOW YOU ARE.
- ARE YOU?
- YEAH, I-I WANNA SAY I AM.
I'’M JUST--I GUESS YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS IN THE FUTURE.
IF TODAY YOU WERE TO BE LIKE,
"YOU WANNA GET MARRIED TO HIM?"
I WOULD SAY YES.
AND I WOULD GET MARRIED TO HIM.
I LOVE HIM, I WANNA BE WITH HIM
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
I'’M HAPPY WITH HIM.
I WOULD NEVER CONSIDER
BEING WITH SOMEONE ELSE.
LIKE, IT FREAKS ME OUT TO THINK,
LIKE--TO GO NEAR SOMEONE ELSE.
- LIKE, KISS SOMEONE ELSE?
- YEAH, IT FREAKS ME OUT.
- ME TOO.
- SO I ALREADY KNOW THAT.
I JUST WANNA KNOW THAT,
IN 20 YEARS,
I'’LL STILL FEEL THE SAME WAY.
- I THINK YOU'’LL FEEL THAT WAY.
- YEAH, I DO.
BUT I CAN'’T WAIT
TO GET MARRIED TO HIM.
I HOPE HE [bleep]
POPS THE QUESTION--
[plate clatters]
OOH--SOONER THAN LATER.
- WHY DON'’T YOU
JUST GET KNOCKED UP?
[both laugh]
- DO YOU HAVE "YOU" TIME
AT ALL OR NO?
- LIKE, ME AND HIM?
- YEAH.
- NO.
- WE GOTTA GIVE MOMMY
AND DADDY A BREAK.
- I WAS INTERESTED
IN SPEAKING TO SOMEBODY
ABOUT ENGAGEMENT RINGS.
MY HEART TELLS ME
THAT SHE'’S THE ONE FOR ME,
AND I WANNA MARRY HER.
- ♪ OOH BABY BABY ♪
♪ I DON'’T WANNA
BE ALONE ANYMORE ♪
- HONEY, I'’M HOME.
WHOA!
- HOW WAS MAINE?
- IT WAS GOOD.
- YEAH?
- SEE AUNT JENNI?
- DOES HE LOOK DIFFERENT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- SINCE THE HOSPITAL?
- HE LOOKS--
- '’CAUSE HE GREW.
HIS HANDS ARE, LIKE, HUGE NOW.
- YOU WANNA HOLD HIM?
- YEAH.
- ARE YOU CLEAN?
- YEP.
I WASHED AND HAND SANITIZED.
- OKAY.
- WANNA GO WITH AUNT JENNI?
- HI, BUDDY.
HELLO!
[Lorenzo fusses]
- I LOVE YOU.
I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU ALL WEEK.
DID HIS THING FALL OFF YET?
- YEP.
- IT DID?
HOW GROSS WAS IT?
- OH, I'’LL SHOW YOU.
- SHE KEPT IT.
- IT LOOKS LIKE A BACON STRIP.
- IT'’S DEFINITELY ODD THAT
NICOLE IS WALKING AROUND
WITH THIS LITTLE STRIP OF BACON
WHICH IS LORENZO'’S, YOU KNOW...
BELLY BUTTON THING.
I FEEL LIKE
THAT SHOULD BE SOMEWHERE.
- I DON'’T KNOW
IF THIS IS GROSS TO SAVE.
- PUT IT IN WRAP
AND PUT IT IN THE BABY BOOK.
RIGHT? THAT'’S WHAT
PEOPLE DO IN THE--
I WOULD STOP TOUCHING IT.
- [laughs]
- AND, LIKE, CARRYING IT AROUND
LIKE IT'’S--
- SANITIZE YOUR HANDS.
- SHOULD I PUT IT IN A BAGGY?
- NOT SANITARY.
SO YOU GUYS ARE GOOD?
- MM.
- DO YOU HAVE
"YOU" TIME AT ALL OR NO?
- LIKE ME AND HIM?
- YEAH.
- NO.
IT'’S NOT ROMANTIC ANYMORE.
- WE GOTTA GIVE
MOMMY AND DADDY A BREAK.
HOW ABOUT THAT, BOY?
- I WANNA, LIKE, KISS AND DANCE.
- KISS AND DANCE WHO?
both: YOU!
- DO YOU WANT TO BABYSIT?
- JENNI CAN BABYSIT.
- TOMORROW NIGHT IF YOU GUYS
WANNA GO GET DINNER OR SOMETHING
ME AND ROGER WILL COME OVER.
I'’M GIVING YOU ALONE TIME.
YOU DESERVE IT.
ME AND ROGER ARE GONNA
GET HERE AS SOON AS WE CAN.
GO OUT WITH JIONNI,
HAVE ALONE TIME.
YOU KNOW, BE ROMANTIC,
HAVE A GLASS OF WINE, MAKE OUT,
TOUCH EACH OTHER
UNDERNEATH THE TABLE.
- OH, NO, WE'’RE NOT DOING THAT.
I'’LL GET PREGNANT AGAIN.
[bleep].
- ♪ WHERE DO WE GO FROM HERE
I DON'’T KNOW ♪
♪ YOU'’RE THE ONLY ONE I WANT ♪
♪ THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ WE'’RE SO MEANT TO BE ♪
[phone rings]
ALAN FRIEDMAN JEWELRY.
HI, UH, I WAS INTERESTED
IN SPEAKING TO SOMEBODY
ABOUT ENGAGEMENT RINGS.
- OH, SURE, LET ME
GET ONE OF OUR DESIGNERS.
I'’LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
- PEOPLE SAY YOU KNOW
WHEN YOU MEET THE RIGHT ONE.
I'’M NOT A BELIEVER IN THAT,
YOU KNOW.
I DON'’T BELIEVE
IN FAIRY TALE MOVIES,
AND, YOU KNOW,
UNICORNS AND RAINBOWS AND...
I DON'’T BELIEVE IN THAT.
I BELIEVE JENNI AND I
HAVE GROWN TO LOVE EACH OTHER
AND WE ARE STILL GROWING TO LOVE
EACH OTHER MORE EVERY DAY.
AND, YOU KNOW, MY HEART TELLS ME
THAT SHE'’S THE ONE FOR ME,
AND I WANNA MARRY HER.
HI, THIS IS LAYNA FRIEDMAN.
- HI, LAYNA, MY NAME IS ROGER.
I WAS JUST LOOKING
AT YOUR WEBSITE.
UM, I'’M LOOKING
FOR AN ENGAGEMENT RING
FOR MY GIRLFRIEND.
- AHA, HI, ROGER.
both: HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
WELL, YOU CALLED
THE RIGHT PLACE.
WE'’RE REALLY, REALLY KNOWN
FOR ENGAGEMENT RINGS.
WE SPECIALIZE IN, YOU KNOW,
NATURAL COLOR DIAMONDS
SUCH AS YELLOWS
AND PINKS AND BLUES.
- YES, PINKS ARE
DEFINITELY A MUST.
UM, SHE LOVES PINK DIAMONDS.
I'’M SUPER EXCITED, YET SUPER
NERVOUS AT THE SAME TIME.
SO I-I THINK
THAT'’S A GOOD THING THOUGH.
- DON'’T BE NERVOUS,
BECAUSE WE'’RE GONNA
MAKE IT REALLY EASY FOR YOU.
- OH, GREAT.
- WE'’LL SET UP A PLAN
AND I CAN BRING SOME GOODIES
FOR YOU TO LOOK AT.
- SOUNDS GREAT.
I'’M EXCITED TO DO THIS.
- YEAH, I LOOK FORWARD
TO MEETING YOU.
AND DON'’T WORRY.
IT'’S GONNA BE
VERY EASY AND A LOT OF FUN.
- OKAY,
THANK YOU SO MUCH, LAYNA.
WE'’LL TALK SOON.
- OKAY, ROGER.
TAKE CARE.
- OKAY. BYE-BYE.
- BYE.
- LET'’S HOPE SHE LIKES IT.
WE WANNA MOVE ON TO THE NEXT
PHASE OF OUR LIVES, YOU KNOW?
WE--WE'’RE TALKING
ABOUT CHILDREN,
WE'’RE TALKING ABOUT MARRIAGE.
THE FIRST STEP IN ALL THAT
IS GETTING ENGAGED.
- HI, BABIES.
BABE?
- I NEED A XANAX.
- CAB'’S HERE.
- LOOKING BACK,
I WOULDN'’T THINK
I WOULD HAVE
JWOWW BABYSITTING MY BABY.
- LET ALONE ME BABYSITTING
SNOOKI'’S BABY.
- EW.
- BYE.
- BYE, LORENZO.
- YOU KNOW, JIONNI HAS FEATURES
OF A LITTLE PERSON.
- OH!
- PLEASE DON'’T TELL HIM THIS.
- PLEASE.
IT'’S LIKE CHRISTMAS MORNING,
YOU KNOW?
ANY TIME I LEARN
INFORMATION LIKE THIS
ABOUT JIONNI IS A GOOD DAY.
EXPLAINS YOUR
DANCE MOVES AT LEAST.
- [laughs]
- HEY.
- ♪ I'’M AN APRIL FOOL ♪
♪ I'’D GO TO THE EDGE ♪
♪ OF THE WORLD
AND BACK FOR YOU ♪
♪ I GUESS THE JOKE'’S ON ME ♪
- ARE YOU GONNA BREASTFEED?
- YEP.
- ME?
OH, LOOK AT THAT THING.
NO STORK BROUGHT THAT BABY.
PATRON BROUGHT THAT BABY
TO THIS PLANET.
- I'’M REALLY EXCITED TO BABYSIT
LORENZO TONIGHT WITH MY BOO.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS BURP HIM,
CHANGE HIM, FEED HIM,
AND HE'’S GOOD TO GO.
- HEY.
SAME AS HANGING OUT WITH JIONNI.
- [laughs]
- WHAT'’S UP, BROTHER?
WHAT'’S HAPPENING?
- WHAT'’S UP, PAL?
- WHAT'’S GOING ON?
- HEY, ROG,
PUT THESE ON THE TABLE.
- JANICE IS AMAZING.
SHE ALWAYS HAS FOOD.
ALWAYS.
OH, LOOK WHO IT IS.
SLEEPING BEAUTY.
- HEY, ROG.
- YOU CAN SEE WHY NICOLE AND
JIONNI DON'’T WANNA GO ANYWHERE.
- HE'’S HEAVY.
- HE'’S BULKING UP.
- YEAH, HE'’S BULKING UP.
ALL FIVE PERCENT OF HIM.
- [laughs]
- HE'’S AT FIVE PERCENTILE
IN HIS HEIGHT.
- THAT GOOD?
OR THAT'’S THE BOTTOM?
- THE BOTTOM.
LIKE, HE'’S GONNA BE SMALL.
- CONSIDERING THAT GOES TO 100.
- IT'’S PRETTY LOW.
- OH, YEAH.
- WELL, IT'’S FIVE--FIVE--FIVE
PERCENT MORE THAN I WAS.
- YEAH.
- YOU WERE ZERO?
- IF HE WAS BIG, I WOULD BE
GETTING A PATERNITY TEST.
- THAT'’S WHAT SHE SAID.
I THINK SHE'’S LYING
JUST TO BE FUNNY.
MOM, I WASN'’T ZERO.
THAT'’S IMPOSSIBLE.
- ONE TIME
WE WENT TO THE DOCTOR
SO HE SAYS TO ME,
"YOU KNOW
JIONNI'’S REALLY SHORT."
- PLEASE DON'’T TELL HIM THIS.
- "YOU KNOW, HE HAS FEATURES
OF A LITTLE PERSON."
- OH!
- SO HE MAKES ME
TAKE HIM TO A DOCTOR.
SO I TAKE HIM TO A DOCTOR.
AND I WALK IN,
THE DOCTOR SAYS TO ME
HE HAS A BIGGER UPPER BODY
THAN HE HAS A LOWER BODY.
- HE WAS TALKING
ABOUT YOUR PEE-PEE.
- HE USED TO BE--
[laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
I LOVE JANICE SO MUCH.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
IT'’S LIKE CHRISTMAS MORNING,
YOU KNOW?
ANY TIME I LEARN
INFORMATION LIKE THIS
ABOUT JIONNI IS A GOOD DAY.
[all laugh]
- HE USED TO
BE REALLY TINY HERE
AND THEN UP HERE,
HE WAS, LIKE, HUGE.
- MA, PUT THE SANGRIA DOWN.
- YOU GOOD FOR ABOUT A YEAR?
- YEAH.
- STOP GIVING ROGER AMMUNITION.
HE MAKES FUN OF ME ENOUGH.
ZIP IT.
- BRACES?
- OH, YOUR BRACES.
HIS SHOES WERE SCREWED ON,
BUT THEY WENT THIS WAY.
- A FEW YEARS, I'’LL BE GOOD.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
MY FEET WERE THAT WAY?
- EXPLAINS
YOUR DANCE MOVES AT LEAST.
- HEY.
[all laugh]
- THAT'’S SO MEAN.
- OH, CAN YOU DRINK?
WE BROUGHT A RED AND A WHITE.
- YEAH, I'’M READY
TO DRINK TONIGHT.
- SO WHAT ELSE, MAN?
HOW'’S THINGS SINCE LORENZO'’S
BEEN HOME AND STUFF?
- HE'’S THE FIRST THING
ON OUR MINDS NOW, YOU KNOW?
- DOES THAT TAKE AWAY
FROM TOGETHER TIME?
- YEAH, IT DEFINITELY DOES.
NICOLE DOESN'’T LIKE IT, BUT...
- SHE DOESN'’T LIKE--
- SHE WANTS
TO CUDDLE AND KISS
AND I'’M JUST, LIKE--
- NOT ABOUT IT?
- NO.
- REALLY?
- NOT REALLY.
- SHE PROBABLY
WANTS TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU'’RE STILL LIKE--
- YEAH. NO, SHE DOES.
- THAT'’S HOW WOMEN ARE,
YOU KNOW?
- DO I LOOK ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, YOU LOOK GOOD.
- YOU THINK
I'’LL COME BACK LIKE "HEY!"
- I HOPE SO.
- I'’M SO EXCITED TO JUST,
YOU KNOW,
TRY AND GET THE ROMANCE BACK
WITH JIONNI
AND ALSO TO HAVE
A GLASS OF WINE.
- OR TWO.
- BECAUSE I HAVEN'’T HAD
A GL--YEAH.
BECAUSE I HAVEN'’T HAD
A GLASS OF WINE IN NINE MONTHS.
- LAST NIGHT I HAD TWO GLASSES
OF WINE AND I WAS...
- YOU'’RE A LIGHTWEIGHT.
- ALL OVER THE PLACE.
[Lorenzo cries]
- JUST FOR [bleep].
OH, MY GOD.
SORRY. SORRY.
- [grunts]
- THIS IS MY LIFE, ROG.
FEEDING BABIES,
CHANGING DIAPERS.
- HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE HIM
TO DRINK THAT BOTTLE?
- UH, I DON'’T KNOW.
BABIES HAVE THE NATURAL--
IF YOU STICK SOMETHING
IN THEIR MOUTH,
THEY SUCK ON IT.
IT'’S LIKE--IT'’S LIKE
THEY'’RE BORN WITH--
- I DON'’T THINK JENNI
WAS BORN WITH THAT.
I HONESTLY THINK JENNI
MISSED A GENE THERE.
[both laugh]
- OH, MY GOD.
- I'’M GONNA GO UPSTAIRS, OKAY?
WHOA!
[bleep].
- WHAT?
- I HAVE TO GET USED
TO THESE HEELS.
- BEING THAT THERE ARE TENSIONS
BETWEEN ME AND NICOLE,
I THINK THIS DINNER'’S
GONNA BE HUGE.
IT'’S GONNA BE
REALLY ROMANTIC FOR US.
AND I THINK WE NEED THIS.
- HEY, HANDSOME.
- HI.
I GOTTA GET MONEY FIRST.
- LOOKING BACK FOUR YEARS AGO,
I WOULDN'’T THINK I WOULD HAVE
JWOWW BABYSITTING MY BABY.
- LET ALONE ME BABYSITTING
SNOOKI'’S BABY.
- EW!
- [laughs]
- CAB'’S HERE.
- GOOD LUCK.
TAKE CARE OF OUR SON.
HEY, I LOVE YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, GOOD LUCK.
YOU CALL ME
IF ANYTHING GOES WRONG.
- MOMMY LOVES YOU.
- DO NOT CALL US.
- IS THIS FOR US?
- YES, THAT'’S FOR THEM, RIGHT?
THAT WINE?
- [glugs]
- BYE.
- BYE, LORENZO.
- ENJOY.
- I LOVE YOU.
- BYE.
- MAKE SURE YOU BURP HIM.
MAKE SURE YOU CHECK
HIS DIAPER.
MAKE SURE YOU--
- JIONNI!
- GOOD BYE.
- GET OUT OF THE HOUSE.
- TIME FOR YOUR FEEDING.
I FEEL LIKE I'’M VERY NATURAL
WITH LORENZO.
I DON'’T KNOW
IF IT'’S MOTHERLY INSTINCTS.
I DON'’T KNOW IF IT'’S JUST
BECAUSE, LIKE--
- THERE'’S NOTHING NATURAL ABOUT
YOUR "MOTHERLY INSTINCTS."
- I HAVEN'’T BEEN OUT
THIS LATE IN YEARS.
I FEEL YOUNG AGAIN.
- THIS AUTOMATIC?
- [laughs]
- IS THIS A JOKE?
- WE'’RE PARENTS.
WE DON'’T KNOW.
- YOU COULD FIT HIM
IN THAT SHOE.
DEFINITELY.
- JANICE.
- YEAH?
- LOOK AT THIS.
- I WAS SAYING HE'’S ABOUT
THE SAME SIZE AS MY SHOE.
SO I PUT MY SHOE UP HERE.
HE'’S PRETTY MUCH THE SAME.
- [gasps]
- HOW TINY IS HE?
ROGER'’S SHOE AND LORENZO
ARE ACTUALLY THE SAME SIZE.
- AND IT'’S KINDA SAD
BECAUSE I HAVE A TINY PENIS.
HE'’S ADORABLE.
- THERE'’S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- ♪ WE OUT LATE NIGHT ♪
♪ WE ON A MISSION
IN THE MOONLIGHT ♪
♪ WE GONNA MOVE RIGHT ♪
- IT'’S PACKED.
- YO, WHAT'’S UP?
WHAT'’S GOING ON?
HOW ARE YOU?
- ALL RIGHT.
- HOW'’S EVERYTHING?
- DO YOU HAVE
A PICTURE OF THE BABY?
- WE HAVE A MILLION
IN OUR PHONE ALREADY.
- LORENZO.
- MM-HMM.
- YEAH.
- AWW, HE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
- HE HAS MY LIPS.
JIONNI'’S A REALLY
GOOD-LOOKING GUY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I WISH HE LOOKED
LIKE ME JUST A LITTLE BIT.
DOES THAT MAKE YOU HAPPY?
- WHAT?
- WHEN PEOPLE SAY
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU?
- YES AND NO.
- BECAUSE I'’M JEALOUS.
I WANT PEOPLE TO SAY THAT TO ME.
- IT'’S JUST RIGHT NOW.
HE'’S GONNA GO THROUGH
5,000 CHANGES.
- AS LONG AS LORENZO
HAS JIONNI'’S BUTT,
THAT'’S ALL THAT MATTERS.
- YOU THINK LORENZO'’S SLEEPING?
- UM, YEAH.
- I BET YOU ROGER'’S SLEEPING.
- ROGER'’S JUST SLEEPING.
- ROGER'’S SLEEPING
AND JENNI'’S DOING ALL THE WORK.
[baby grumbles]
- YOU SLEEPY?
- NO, I'’M JUST--
ONLY SO MUCH I CAN DO.
- DO YOU WANNA FEED HIM?
- NO, I'’M ALL RIGHT.
I DEFINITELY WANNA BE HERE,
AND I WANNA HELP '’EM OUT,
AND HELP WITH LORENZO,
BUT IT IS PRETTY BORING.
- LOOK AT THIS.
HOW CUTE.
[Lorenzo whines]
- ROCK HIM OR BURP HIM
OR SOMETHING.
[Lorenzo burps]
- OH, THERE IT IS.
YOU HEAR THAT?
- BURPED OR FARTED?
BURP?
- IT WAS A BURP.
YOU HEAR THAT?
- OH, YEAH.
- THAT WAS ENORMOUS.
ARE YOU POOPING?
YOU LOOK CONTENT.
- WELL, YOU STOPPED
BEATING HIM.
- HE'’S LIKE I--
- STOPPED BEATING HIM
ON HIS BACK,
HE'’S PROBABLY
A LITTLE MORE CONTENT.
- I'’M NOT BEATING HIM.
- I REALLY DO MISS HIM.
DO YOU THINK
IT'’LL ALWAYS BE THIS WAY
IF WE TRY AND GO OUT?
- IF NOT, WE'’RE NEVER GOING OUT.
- BUT I WANNA GO OUT
TO DINNERS WITH YOU.
- HAVE YOUR FIRST SIP.
CHEERS.
- TO LORENZO.
[glasses clink]
I'’M SCARED.
UGH!
I DON'’T KNOW IF I LIKE THAT.
[shudders]
AFTER NINE MONTHS,
IT JUST TASTES WEIRD TO ME.
MAYBE '’CAUSE I'’M NOT
USED TO IT ANYMORE.
IT'’S WEIRD,
THIS IS MY FAVORITE WINE.
- WHY DON'’T YOU WANT IT?
- TASTES...UGH.
AS SOON AS THE WINE
TOUCHES MY LIPS,
IT TASTES LIKE CRAP, BUT...
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
- IT'’S JUST STRONG.
I LIKE FEELING GIGGLY.
I GUESS I JUST HAVE
TO GET USED TO IT AGAIN.
- YOU FEELING IT?
- I MIGHT FEEL DRUNK.
- OH, GOSH.
OH, [bleep].
- [giggles]
- NICOLE'’S GIGGLING.
SHE'’S GETTING DRUNK.
OH, GOSH.
SHE'’S BACK.
OH, GOD.
- [giggles]
[snorts]
- SO IT BEGINS.
- THIS IS GONNA BE
A BIG DAY FOR ME
SO IT HAS TO BE
JUST PERFECT, YOU KNOW?
- THIS IS GONNA RUN
ABOUT $600,000.
- WHOA!
I DON'’T THINK
SHE'’S GONNA HAVE ANY IDEA.
BUT I THINK I WANNA MESS
WITH HER A LITTLE BIT TOO.
NOW I DON'’T WANNA BE
MEAN-SPIRITED ABOUT IT,
BUT I DEFINITELY...
- WELL, GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
- WANNA MAYBE GET
HER HOPES UP A LITTLE BIT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I WANT TO DO,
LIKE, A REALLY NICE
KIND OF FAKE OUT
DINNER DATE NIGHT.
- I FEEL LIKE WE'’RE CORRUPTING
YOU ALL OVER AGAIN.
- DO I SMELL?
- A LITTLE BIT.
- I DON'’T WANT JIONNI
TO SMELL SMOKE ON ME,
'’CAUSE I FEEL LIKE
HE'’S GONNA KILL ME.
[door opens]
[gasps]
WHEW!
- I'’M LOOKING AT THIS PINK LIMO.
OH, MY GOD, THIS IS IT.
LIKE, I'’M GONNA BE PROPOSED TO.
WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- IT MIGHT BE ALL THEY HAD.