- YOU GOT ME A BEAR?
- IT'’LL FIT NICE DOWNSTAIRS.
- SO, THERE'’S LEGIT, LIKE,
A MILLION PRESENTS RIGHT NOW
THAT I HAVE TO OPEN.
AND I'’M SO EXCITED...
BUT HOLY [bleep],
THERE'’S A LOT OF PRESENTS.
- YOU'’RE PISSING ME OFF,
ROGER.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
IT WAS A JOKE, RELAX.
- YOU'’RE BEING OBNOXIOUS.
- DON'’T PISS ME OFF.
- SHUT UP!
- BOTH PARTIES JUST NEED
TO SHUT THE [bleep] UP.
- I GOT TO GO.
- I'’M NOT APOLOGIZING.
- MY BODY'’S STARTING
TO SHUT DOWN.
I'’M GETTING SICK.
I'’M NUMB.
I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT THE HECK'’S GOING ON.
ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS THIS BABY SHOWER
GOING RIGHT FOR NICOLE,
AND ME BEING SICK RIGHT NOW
IS BY FAR THE WORST THING
THAT COULD HAPPEN.
HEY, WHAT'’S UP?
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- IN THE HOSPITAL.
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- BABE!
- YEAH.
- WHAT'’S WRONG?
- GETTING AN IV NOW.
- YOU'’RE GETTING IVs?
- IT WAS FROM JUST
BEING DEHYDRATED,
BEING OUT IN THE SUN.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- I WAS LITERALLY
THROWING UP
TO THE SECOND I GOT HERE
- HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA
STAY THERE?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU DON'’T KNOW?
- I JUST GOT HERE.
- ARE YOU GONNA COME HOME
TONIGHT?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- EW.
I'’M GOING THERE.
KIND OF FREAKING OUT.
LIKE, I WANT TO CRY.
BUT I DON'’T WANT TO CRY
IN FRONT OF JANICE.
I HONESTLY DON'’T KNOW
WHAT I WOULD DO
IF SOMETHING BAD HAPPENED
TO JIONNI.
I LOVE HIM.
CAN WE GO SEE HIM?
- NO, YOU'’RE NOT GOING
DOWN THERE.
- WHY?
- HE'’LL BE FINE.
YOU JUST GO HOME AND REST
AND I'’LL FIND OUT
WHAT'’S GOING ON.
- I'’M NOT GOING
TO BE ABLE TO REST.
- LAST NIGHT WAS
A [bleep] [bleep] SHOW.
I'’VE NEVER HAD A PROBLEM WITH
ANY OF YOUR BOYFRIENDS, EVER.
- THIS WOULD BE MY FUTURE
HUSBAND, HOPEFULLY.
- WELL, THEN HE NEEDS TO--
I'’M YOUR BEST FRIEND.
HE NEEDS TO RESPECT THAT TOO.
- WELL--
- WHATEVER. END OF STORY.
END OF CONVERSATION.
- I FEEL LIKE IF ME AND EUNICE
DON'’T WORK THIS OUT,
THAT I'’M GOING
TO PROBABLY END UP
DISTANCING MYSELF FROM HER,
BECAUSE I'’M NOT GOING
TO TOLERATE
HOW SHE'’S ACTING
TOWARDS MY BOYFRIEND.
[burps]
OH, GOD, THAT SMELLS
LIKE PENNE ALLA VODKA.
- OKAY?
- I'’LL GO GET HIM.
- YOU'’RE NOT GOING TO GET HIM.
- WHY?
- BECAUSE YOU'’RE NOT.
HE'’LL BE FINE.
HE ALWAYS DOES THAT.
YOU REST.
GET YOUR FEET UP.
- '’CAUSE HE NEVER
DRINKS WATER, EVER.
- I'’VE HAD THIS CONVERSATION
WITH HIM FOREVER.
HE'’LL BE FINE.
DON'’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- I DON'’T CARE
IF I'’M EIGHT MONTHS PREGNANT,
I'’M GOING TO THE HOSPITAL
AND I'’M GOING TO SLEEP
WITH JIONNI,
BECAUSE HE NEEDS ME,
I NEED HIM,
AND I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
HE'’S OKAY.
- ♪ YOU AND ME ONLY ♪
- WHOA!
- HEY.
- HI.
- YOU LOOK COMFY.
- LAST NIGHT,
THERE WAS A BIG ARGUMENT
BETWEEN ROGER AND EUNICE,
BUT I'’M JUST HAPPY
HE'’S FINALLY HOME,
'’CAUSE I HATE
THAT HE HAS TO FEEL
LIKE HE HAS TO LEAVE
HIS OWN HOUSE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES
TO ONE OF MY FRIENDS.
THAT'’S PRETTY [bleep] UP.
- WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU REMEMBER
FROM LAST NIGHT?
'’CAUSE MY INTERPRETATION
OF IT--
AND I COULD BE WRONG--
WAS, I THINK,
EUNICE HAD A LITTLE
TOO MUCH TO DRINK,
WHICH IS ALWAYS THE CASE,
AND SHE GOT INCENSED
ABOUT SOMETHING,
AND THEN STARTED LIKE--
- I THINK WHAT I HEARD
FROM THE GROUP WAS
YOU MADE A FUNNY JOKE
THAT SHE DIDN'’T GET.
- RIGHT.
- EVERYONE ELSE GOT.
- THAT'’S WHAT I HEARD HER SAY--
I LOOKED UP,
AND SHE LOOKS ME
RIGHT IN THE FACE AND SAYS,
"YOU'’VE CHANGED.
YOU USED TO BE A NICE GUY.
YOU'’RE AN ASS[bleep] NOW."
- I THINK IT'’S SHE DIDN'’T
REALIZE YOUR JOKE.
- YOU KNOW, IF IT
WAS AN ISOLATED INCIDENT,
MAYBE THE NEXT DAY,
EUNICE AND I
COULD'’VE CALLED EACH OTHER
OR GOT TOGETHER
AND SAID, "HEY, LISTEN,
WE WERE BOTH DRINKING.
IT GOT A LITTLE OUT OF HAND.
I'’M SORRY."
IT WASN'’T
AN ISOLATED INCIDENT.
THIS HAS HAPPENED BEFORE.
NO, I WASN'’T
EVEN MAD AT YOU.
YOU TOLD HER TO SHUT UP.
YOU TOLD ME TO SHUT UP.
SO AT LEAST
YOU WERE UNBIASED ABOUT IT,
BUT IT WAS GOING TO GET WORSE,
SO I JUST SAID,
"YOU KNOW WHAT?
SEE YOU LATER."
I DON'’T CARE
IF I EVER TALK TO HER AGAIN.
SHE CAN DO WHATEVER
SHE WANTS TO DO, YOU KNOW?
- I'’M JUST GOING TO DISTANCE
MYSELF FROM HER FOR AWHILE.
- NO!
- I AM PRETTY [bleep]
DISAPPOINTED
BECAUSE MY GIRLFRIEND
WAS BEING A BITCH.
SHE WAS TOO DRUNK TO COMPREHEND
ANYTHING THAT NIGHT,
SO SHE SHOULD
JUST LET IT GO.
SHE WANTS TO PLAY THAT GAME
OF BEST FRIEND VERSUS BOYFRIEND,
SHE'’LL LOSE, REAL QUICK.
- I DON'’T NECESSARILY HAVE TO BE
SUPER TIGHT WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
I WOULD BE FINE WITH IT
IF YOU DIDN'’T, REALLY, YOU KNOW,
GET ALONG GREAT
WITH ONE OF MY FRIENDS.
IT'’S FINE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
WHATEVER.
LET'’S NOT EVEN TALK
ABOUT IT ANYMORE.
- ALL RIGHT, I'’M TIRED.
I NEED TO GO TO BED.
- ♪ WAKE UP EARLY
IN THE MORNING ♪
♪ AND I'’M WAITING
FOR THE SUN TO RISE ♪
♪ OPEN YOUR EYES,
STAND BY MY SIDE ♪
- COMING HOME
FROM THE HOSPITAL
KNOWING THAT
EVERYTHING'’S OKAY
AND HE'’S GOING TO BE FINE,
I'’M VERY HAPPY, YOU KNOW,
THAT NOTHING BAD HAPPENED,
AND RIGHT NOW I JUST WANT ME
AND JIONNI TO REST
BECAUSE
WE HAD A [bleep] NIGHT.
- ♪ WHOA, OH, OH,
WHOA, OH, OH ♪
♪ SHINE THE LIGHT ♪
- NICOLE COMING TO THE HOSPITAL
TONIGHT SHOWED ME
HOW STRONG WE ARE,
HOW MUCH SHE LOVES ME.
- BUT YOU MADE ME MORE WORRIED
BY NOT TELLING ME.
- I WAS AFRAID TO RUIN THE DAY.
- I DON'’T CARE.
- WELL, I DIDN'’T WANT
TO STRESS YOU OUT.
- I'’D RATHER KNOW
THAT YOU'’RE OKAY THAN A SHOWER.
- I DIDN'’T WANT
TO STRESS YOU OUT.
- WELL, YOU DID.
- I DIDN'’T WANT TO RUIN
YOUR DAY, AND I'’M SORRY.
- YOU DIDN'’T.
- GOOD.
ALL I CARED ABOUT WAS YOU.
THREW UP, I THINK,
48 TIMES.
I'’M NOT EXAGGERATING.
- IT'’S NOT THE PROPOSAL
THAT I ACTUALLY WANT,
OR THE ENGAGEMENT.
IT'’S THE RING THAT I WANT.
- [laughs]
- DO I LOOK LIKE A DAD?
- YEAH, YOU DO.
A HOT DAD.
YOU'’RE A D.I.L.F.
- MY MOM'’S HERE.
- BIG TRUCK IS GONNA COME
WITH ALL LORENZO'’S PRESENTS.
- HEY, WHAT'’S UP?
- HI, ANDY!
I'’M UPSTAIRS.
COME UP HERE FOR A MINUTE.
- WHAT'’S GOING ON?
HOW ARE YOU?
- THIS IS THE SPARE ROOM.
IN CASE THEY DON'’T WANT
THEIR KID FOR THE NIGHT.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW DO YOU LIKE IT?
- GOOD.
- IT'’S THE SAFARI ROOM.
- WHERE'’S NICOLE?
- THEY'’RE DOWNSTAIRS.
- THEY'’RE IN BED?
- YEAH.
- THEY'’RE SLEEPING?
- THEY OUGHT TO GET
THEIR TAILS UP, MAN.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'’S GO SEE
WHAT THEY'’RE DOING.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
NIC...
YOUR DAD IS HERE.
I NEED TO MOVE YOUR CAR.
WHERE ARE YOUR KEYS?
DID IT ALL FIT?
- IT'’S FULL.
- OH, MY GOD.
- COMPLETELY FULL.
- HOLY CRAP!
- GOT IT?
- THERE'’S NO ROOM.
- IS THAT IT?
- ISN'’T THAT ENOUGH?
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- JOE.
I'’LL SEE YOU.
- WILL YOU GUYS
COME UP AND EAT?
PLEASE?
BURGERS.
- I THINK IT'’S SWEET THAT JANICE
CARES ABOUT US SO MUCH
THAT SHE ALWAYS WANTS
TO TAKE CARE OF US.
I LIKE IT.
MY DAD CAME?
- I ASKED YOUR DAD TO STAY.
I FELT BAD, HE HAD--
- HE SAID HE HAD
A LOT OF THINGS TO DO.
- THE TRUCK WAS--
- HE'’S A BUSY MAN.
- THE TRUCK WAS REALLY PACKED.
- LIKE A BIG U-HAUL?
- YEAH.
- NOT, YOU KNOW--
- DECENT SIZED.
- NOT HUGE.
- YOU WANT TO TRY
MY HOMEMADE PICKLES?
THEY'’RE REALLY DILL, THOUGH.
- WHAT'’S "DILL" MEAN?
- LIKE TART.
- WHAT'’S "TART" MEAN?
- REALLY--YOU'’LL KNOW
AS SOON AS YOU TASTE IT.
- THAT'’S WHAT HOMEMADE PICKLES
TASTE LIKE.
I LIKE THEM.
- THANKS.
SHE LIKES THEM,
AND SHE'’S A PICKLE EXPERT.
- TAKE THIS OFF NOW?
- YEAH, IF YOU WANT.
DUDE, I GOT
THREE BAGS OF IV.
- AND YOU ONLY PEED TWICE.
- THAT'’S HOW DEHYDRATED
YOU WERE.
- THAT'’S WHAT I SAID.
- ♪ BABY, BABY, BABY,
I'’M READY FOR YOU ♪
♪ I'’M READY FOR YOU ♪
- I HAVE TO LEARN
HOW TO BECOME A LADY AGAIN.
I'’M SO USED TO WEARING
MY GYM OUTFITS.
ME, JOEY, AND LAUREN ARE HAVING
JUST REGULAR GIRL TIME,
AND WE OBVIOUSLY GET
INTO GIRLY CONVERSATIONS.
- HOW'’S NICOLE DOING?
- VERY PREGNANT.
IF I COULD HAVE
A PERFECT WORLD,
ONE OF MY KIDS
IS GONNA MARRY NICOLE'’S,
AND ONE OF MY KIDS
IS GONNA MARRY YOURS.
- OH, THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
- THAT'’S MY PERFECT WORLD.
- LET'’S ARRANGE THEIR MARRIAGES.
[laughs]
- SO SERIOUSLY, THOUGH, WHEN
ARE YOU GOING TO GET MARRIED?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- I WANT IT TO HAPPEN.
- ME TOO.
- CAN WE, LIKE,
DESIGN YOUR DRESS?
- DRESS SHOPPING
IS SO MUCH FUN.
- IS IT?
- MM-HMM.
- IS IT [bleep] UP
TO GO TRY ON DRESSES
BEFORE YOU'’RE ENGAGED?
- NO.
- NO, THAT'’D BE FUN.
- YES!
THAT'’S LIKE--YOU'’RE LIKE
A WEIRD WOMAN AT THAT POINT.
- THAT'’S TYPICAL WOMAN.
- WHAT'’S THE HARM
IN TRYING ON, LIKE,
SOMETHING JUST TO SEE
WHAT TYPE THAT YOU LIKE?
- MIGHT GET YOUR HOPES UP.
- YOU KNOW THAT IT'’S GONNA
HAPPEN EVENTUALLY.
- IT'’S NOT THE PROPOSAL
THAT I ACTUALLY WANT,
OR THE ENGAGEMENT.
IT'’S THE RING THAT I WANT.
- [laughs]
- I DON'’T EVEN CARE
ABOUT THE MARRIAGE PART.
I'’M NOT TRADITIONAL
IN ANY SENSE.
I JUST WANT
A REALLY SPECIFIC RING,
AND I WOULD LIKE HIM
TO GET THAT FOR ME.
WE'’RE ALREADY BASICALLY
MARRIED.
IF THERE WAS, LIKE,
A COMMON LAW
OF TWO YEARS,
WE'’D BE MARRIED.
- SO YOU JUST WANT HIM
TO GIVE YOU THAT RING?
- YEAH.
- LOOK AT THAT TEDDY BEAR.
- OH, MY GOD!
- NICOLE'’S HAVING ONE CHILD.
SHE'’S NOT HAVING TRIPLETS
OR ANYTHING.
I'’VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
I'’VE NEVER SEEN SO MANY GIFTS
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
- LOOK AT ALL THIS [bleep]
HE HAS.
- I FEEL LIKE IT'’S MY BIRTHDAY.
- OH, I LOVE THIS.
- DUDE, THERE'’S MORE [bleep]
IN THIS CORNER.
- YEAH, WHY DON'’T YOU GO
IN THAT CORNER?
- OH, MY GOD.
I AM NOT PREPARED.
I DON'’T KNOW WHERE
WE'’RE GOING TO PUT THIS STUFF.
HE'’S NOT EVEN BORN YET
AND HE'’S GOT TOO MANY TOYS.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- OH, IT'’S TO DO MY BELLY--
A MOLD.
- CAN I DO IT FOR YOU?
- YEAH.
- NICE.
- NO.
- WHY?
- LET ME READ THAT.
- WHA--?
- EVERY PREGNANT LADY DOES IT.
- JESUS, GET HER OUT OF HERE.
- BELLY CASTING KIT,
I NEVER--
- YOU HAVEN'’T HAD KIDS IN,
LIKE, 20 YEARS.
- "DIP PLASTER STRIPS INTO WATER
AND PRESS THEM ONTO THE SKIN."
I DON'’T KNOW.
- LOOK HOW SMALL
HE'’S GONNA BE.
- NEVER EMBARRASS BABY AGAIN.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- A DUMBBELL.
- IT'’S ACTUALLY A RATTLE.
- IT'’S A RATTLE.
RATTLE GOES--
UH, TOYS, OVER HERE.
RATTLES HERE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'’S A 2-OUNCE DUMBBELL.
- OH, ALCOHOL STRIPS.
TOLD YOU, YOU CAN TEST YOUR--
YOU CAN DRINK.
JENNI IS A GENIUS
BECAUSE SHE GOT ME
THE ALCOHOL TESTING STRIPS
FOR BREAST MILK,
AND I'’M LIKE "THANK GOD,"
BECAUSE I PUT IT
ON MY REGISTRY,
BUT THEN MY MOM TOLD ME
TO TAKE IT OFF
'’CAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE
I'’M TRASHY,
I'’M LIKE,
"MOM, BUT I NEED THEM."
I WONDER IF I COULD PUMP NOW.
WE SHOULD TRY.
- NO.
- YES.
- SERIOUSLY--
- YES!
- NO, YOU CAN NOT--
- YOU DON'’T DO STUFF
LIKE THAT.
- I'’M PUMPING
YOUR [bleep] TONIGHT.
- YOU WILL MILK ME.
JIONNI'’S GONNA MILK ME.
- CAN'’T WAIT.
- JIONNI, STOP IT.
NO, YOU'’RE NOT DOING
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- AS SOON AS YOU FALL ASLEEP,
YOU'’RE GETTING PUMPED.
- I REALLY WANT TO SEE IF MILK
COMES OUT OF MY BOOBS TOO.
LIKE, FOR REAL.
- I THINK IT'’S ON BACKWARDS,
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
- OH, IT'’S A TWO-WAY CARRIER.
- YEAH, TWO-WAY.
[sneezes]
[laughter]
- HE JUST SNEEZED ON THE BABY.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT KID'’S ALREADY DEAD.
- SORRY.
DO I LOOK LIKE A DAD?
- YEAH, YOU DO.
A HOT DAD.
YOU'’RE A D.I.L.F.
- MY MOM'’S HERE.
- [screaming]
- SHUT UP.
- I WANT TO SHOW LORENZO,
WHEN HE'’S 13,
LIKE, WHAT HE DID
TO MY BODY.
- HOW MANY CARATS
DO YOU WANT?
- I WANT A 5 MIDDLE.
I WOULD LIKE 1- TO 2-CARAT,
EACH SIDE BEING PINK,
AND A BAND
WITH PINK DIAMONDS.
- WOW.
- YEAH.
- READY?
MAKE SURE MY NIPPLE
DOESN'’T POP OUT.
- WE'’RE PLASTERING
OVER THE BRA?
- ONE OF MY GIFTS THAT I GOT
FROM MY BEST FRIENDS
IS A BABY CAST.
- OH, THE LUBRICANT.
- BASICALLY,
YOU JUST PUT CLAY
OVER YOUR BABY BUMP
AND YOUR BOOBS,
SO THEN YOU'’LL ALWAYS
REMEMBER,
LIKE, HOW BIG YOU WERE
WHEN THE BABY WAS INSIDE OF YOU.
IT'’S COLD.
OH, MY GOD.
[screams]
- [laughing]
SHUT UP.
- I WANT TO SHOW LORENZO,
WHEN HE'’S 13,
LIKE, WHAT HE DID
TO MY BODY.
- MOVE--YOUR SHORTS
ARE, LIKE--
- OH, MY GOD, YOU CAN'’T
PULL THEM DOWN ANYMORE.
STOP!
- MAYBE A LITTLE BIT.
- NO ONE WANTS TO SEE
A PREGNANT VAGINA.
- [laughing] I'’M NOT LOOKING
AT YOUR VAGINA.
- STOP IT.
- GO FOR IT.
- JIONNI, STOP!
STOP.
- IT'’S NOT YOUR--
IT'’S--
- IT IS.
- NO, IT'’S NOT.
IT'’S RIGHT HERE.
- [screams]
STOP!
- I WAS TRYING TO BE
A GOOD SCULPTURIST,
AND YOU WERE JUST YELLING
ABOUT YOUR VAGINA,
WHICH YOU HAVEN'’T SEEN
IN EIGHT MONTHS.
I HAVEN'’T SEEN IT
IN EIGHT MONTHS EITHER.
- GOOD.
YOU'’RE LIKE A SCULPTURIST.
IT WAS VERY ROMANTIC.
- IT WASN'’T ROMANTIC--
- YES, IT WAS.
- IT WAS JUST FUN.
- NO, IT WAS ROMANTIC.
- IT WAS FUN.
- [laughing]
EW.
'’CAUSE YOU WERE, LIKE,
MOLDING ME AND...
- RUBBING YOUR BOOBS.
- CARESSING ME.
SO ROMANTIC.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS HURTS SO BAD.
OW.
PUT A BIG BAND-AID
ON YOUR STOMACH,
AND THEN RIP IT OFF.
- NOW, WHY WOULD I WANT
TO DO THAT?
- '’CAUSE THIS IS
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
OH, MY GOD, IF THIS
IS WHAT LABOR FEELS LIKE,
I'’M GONNA KILL MYSELF.
- DOES SHE HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT IT'’S GOING TO BE LIKE
TO GIVE BIRTH?
- THANK YOU,
CAPTAIN OBVIOUS.
- NOT BY THE COOKIES.
- OH, IT'’S BEAUTIFUL!
[dog barking,
Jenni coughing]
- YOU BE NICE, YOU FATSO.
YOU BE NICE.
- IS IT WEIRD IF I TRY ON
WEDDING DRESSES FOR FUN?
- KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
IT'’S NOT WEIRD, I GUESS.
IF THAT'’S WHAT YOU--
- YOU DON'’T CONSIDER THAT
PSYCHOTIC?
- IT'’S A LITTLE ODD, FOR YOU,
BUT WHATEVER.
YOU'’RE A LITTLE BIT
OF AN ODD INDIVIDUAL ANYWAY.
- WHAT IF I GO LOOK
FOR RINGS?
- THAT'’S PRESSURE ON ME.
- OKAY, I WON'’T DO THAT.
- THAT'’S A DIFFERENT STORY.
ISN'’T THAT MY JOB TO DO?
- YEAH.
- SHOULDN'’T YOU LEAVE THAT
UP TO ME?
SO LEAVE IT UP TO ME.
- I'’M NOT SAYING WE HAVE TO RUSH
TO THE ALTAR OR ANYTHING.
- WHAT IF I WAS POOR AS A PAUPER
AND ALL I COULD--
- PAUPER?
- YOU'’VE NEVER HEARD THAT?
YOU'’RE TOO YOUNG.
- OH, MY GOD,
THAT'’S ANOTHER ONE ALREADY.
- AND ALL I COULD AFFORD
WAS JUST A MINISCULE,
LIKE, 1/2-CARAT RING.
WOULD YOU MARRY ME THEN?
- I'’LL SELL A KIDNEY TOO
ON eBAY.
- OKAY.
- THAT'’S A LOT OF BOOB
WITH A LITTLE SHIRT.
♪ BIG BOOBS
IN A LITTLE SHIRT ♪
- DO YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH MY WIFEBEATER NOW?
- NO, I'’M JUST SAYING.
YOU LOOK AMAZING...
FIVE SHIRTS LATER.
LET'’S DO THIS.
I LOOK LIKE A WINO.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
I'’M TOO BIG FOR THAT THING.
- I KNOW.
IT'’S LIKE A CLOWN CAR
FOR YOU.
SO ME AND ROGER ARE GOING
TO MEET SEAN AND LAURA
AT DEENA'’S FOR DINNER.
SEAN AND ROGER HAVE KNOWN
EACH OTHER FOR, LIKE, TEN YEARS.
THEY'’RE JUST LIKE ME
AND NICOLE--TWO PEAS IN A POD.
- WHAT'’S THAT?
- SPICY MAYO.
- OH, OH, OH.
- I JUST USE A LOT OF WASABI.
- NO WAY.
- YOU WANT TO SEE WHO CAN EAT
A BIGGER PIECE ALL BY ITSELF?
- YEAH.
- CUT THAT IN HALF.
I'’LL EAT HALF,
AND YOU EAT HALF.
- YEAH?
I'’LL JUST MATCH YOU.
- NO!
- GAME ON, BROTHER.
- THERE'’S NOTHING LEFT!
- I FEEL LIKE SEAN AND ROGER
SHOULD BE IN COLLEGE RIGHT NOW.
"LET'’S DRINK 20 BEERS.
LET'’S THROW UP."
- AND HE CHEWED IT!
ALL RIGHT.
- ARE YOU--
- OOH!
- ALL GUYS ON THIS PLANET
JUST DO THE DUMBEST [bleep]
TO, YOU KNOW, PASS TIME.
- THAT'’S ABOUT THE SAME, RIGHT?
- OH, MY GOD.
- I'’M NOT CHEWING IT.
- CHEW IT!
YOU GOT TO CHEW IT.
CHEW IT.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU GUYS?
- "LET'’S EAT WASABI,
AND THEN SEE
WHO DOESN'’T PASS OUT FIRST."
LIKE, REALLY?
- HOW LONG WERE YOU GUYS
TOGETHER BEFORE YOU GOT MARRIED?
- 5 1/2 YEARS.
- SO AT TWO YEARS
IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP,
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE SAID
IF ONE DAY LAUREN
LOOKED AT YOU AND SAID,
"BABE, TODAY I'’M GONNA
GO WITH MY FRIENDS
AND TRY ON WEDDING DRESSES?"
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE SAID?
- HAVE FUN.
- I'’D BE LIKE "HAVE FUN.
DON'’T GET NO THOUGHTS."
- I'’M, LIKE, "SHUT UP."
IT TOOK '’EM FIVE YEARS
TO GET ENGAGED,
AND I HOPE THAT'’S NOT ME.
- ALL RIGHT, I DON'’T TELL YOU
WHAT YOU CAN AND CAN'’T DO.
IT'’S JUST JOKING AROUND,
RIGHT?
- I DON'’T WANT TO PUT
ANY PRESSURE ON A MARRIAGE
OR ENGAGEMENT
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT,
BUT I JUST WANT A RING.
I JUST REALLY WOULD LOVE THIS,
LIKE, FAT, JUICY RING.
WILL YOU CARRY ME OUT?
- SURE.
- I HAVE NO IDEA HOW YOU'’RE
GOING TO TAKE THAT APART.
- HONESTLY, I'’M GOING TO HAVE
TO TAKE IT ONE PIECE AT A TIME.
I HAVE TO TAKE
THE POOL TABLE APART,
BECAUSE THIS IS WHERE
LORENZO'’S GONNA BE LIVING.
WE NEED TO MAKE ROOM
FOR OUR SON.
- IF THE BABY COMES EARLY,
WE'’RE SCREWED.
WHERE IS IT GOING TO SLEEP?
- HE'’S STUCK IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE POOL TABLE.
- THAT'’S A LOT OF BLANKETS
AND PILLOWS.
- REMEMBER THAT ONE TIME
WE MADE SWEET LOVE.
THAT WAS WHEN WE WERE COOL.
WE DID FUN THINGS.
NOW WE'’RE OLD.
- LAST TIME THIS GUY
GETS FOLDED OVER.
THIS IS A SAD MEMORY.
- ME AND JIONNI PROBABLY
HAD SEX MORE ON THAT POOL TABLE
THAN ACTUALLY PLAYED IT.
- HOW MANY TIMES?
ONCE, TWICE?
- THREE TIMES.
- I PAID FOR THIS WHOLE THING
TO GET IT REDONE,
AND I TOOK IT APART.
IT'’S NOT GOING TO BE THAT HARD.
I DON'’T READ INSTRUCTIONS.
I REALLY AM NOT
A GOOD READER.
BUT TAKING APART A POOL TABLE,
IT'’S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE.
YOU KNOW, YOU JUST GOTTA
START RIPPING [bleep] APART.
[snap]
[groaning]
IDIOT.
THIS THING'’S STUPID.
THIS POOL TABLE
IS A PAIN IN THE ASS.
I DON'’T REALLY KNOW
WHAT I'’M DOING.
I'’M KIND OF BREAKING THINGS.
[phone trilling]
IT'’S NOT A ONE-PERSON JOB.
I'’M GONNA NEED SOME GUYS
TO HELP ME OUT.
- YEAH, WHAT UP?
- J.B.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'’S UP?
- UH, NOTHING.
I'’M STARTING THE POOL TABLE.
YOU HELP ME OUT,
I'’LL BRING YOU OUT FOR A DRINK.
- DEFINITELY.
- ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, BUDDY.
- I'’LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
- ALL RIGHT, BYE.
SO DO WE HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
FOR THE GUY OR NO?
- YES, WE DO, AND I TOTALLY
FORGOT ALL OF THEM.
- WHAT?
- I FORGOT.
WE'’RE GOING
TO THE DOCTOR'’S TODAY,
AND I'’M JUST EXCITED
TO MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING IS GOING TO BE GOOD
FOR WHEN THE TIME HAPPENS.
- I CAN'’T WAIT TO SEE MY SON.
- OH, WE HAVE TO SEE
A PSYCHIATRIST.
- [laughs]
- PSYCHIATRIST?
- WHATEVER IT'’S CALLED.
- YOU GOTTA SEE
A PSYCHIATRIST.
- YOU MEAN A PEDIATRICIAN?
- A PEDIATRICIAN.
- YOU GOT TO GO
TO A PSYCHIATRIST.
- ALL RIGHT.
I DEFINITELY
HAVE PREGNANT BRAIN,
BUT IT'’S OKAY '’CAUSE--
- SHE'’S GONNA NEED TO SEE
A PSYCHIATRIST AFTER THIS.
- THAT'’S RUDE.
NO, I'’M NOT.
DO YOU THINK
HE'’LL GO UP MY CROTCH?
- I HEARD YOU SAY,
"I GOT TO SCRUB DOWN THERE."
THAT WAS SO GROSS.
- JUST IN CASE HE GOES UP.
IF THE DOCTOR DOES GO UP,
YOU DON'’T WANT TO BE GROSS.
- THAT'’S A WEIRD CONVERSATION.
A LITTLE DISGUSTING.
- EVERY GIRL DOES IT.
THEY MAKE SURE
THEY'’RE CLEAN UP THERE.
- THAT'’S JUST WEIRD.
YOU KEEP IT TO YOURSELF.
YOU DON'’T HAVE TO YELL IT.
- SO, HOW OFTEN
DO YOU FEEL CONTRACTIONS?
- I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT THEY FEEL LIKE...
BUT IT HURTS.
- ARE WE 100% IT'’S A BOY?
- UH, LET'’S SEE.
- OH, MY GOD.
- LET'’S SEE
IF HE HAS A SHADOW.
- THAT'’S NOT EVEN FUNNY.
- HAVE TO CHANGE THAT "O"
TO AN "A"--LORENZA.
- YEAH.
- IT'’S HARD TO SAY.
- UH-OH.
WE CAN'’T FIND
THE SHADOW.
- I DON'’T SEE THE SHADOW
IS RIGHT.
- OH, BOY.
I'’VE NEVER WANTED TO SEE
A WIENER SO BAD IN MY LIFE.
I CAN'’T BELIEVE
I'’M ADMITTING IT, AND I'’M JUST--
- IT'’S YOUR SON'’S WIENER.
IT'’S OKAY.
- OH.
- YOU KNOW, PART OF THE REASON
IS THE BABY IS FACING DOWN.
OKAY,
THIS IS THE BABY'’S SPINE,
SO IT'’S FACING DOWN,
AWAY FROM ME,
SO WE REALLY CAN'’T SEE IT.
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MANY
PRESENTS WE GOT FOR A BOY.
- I REALLY CAN'’T SEE IT.
- [groans]
I'’M GETTING OUT OF HERE.
- GO, GO, GO!
THE THING'’S--
- SHUT IT OFF.
SHUT IT OFF.
- JIONNI, STEP AWAY.
WHOA!
I DON'’T THINK
THAT'’S HOW YOU LIGHT A GRILL.
- NEWBORNS CAN SEE
A DISTANCE OF--
- 10 FEET.
- "50 FEET."
LET'’S TRY 8 TO 14 INCHES.
- WHOA, THEY DON'’T
SEE [bleep]!
- ARE WE 100% IT'’S A BOY?
- UH, LET'’S SEE.
- OH, MY GOD.
THAT'’S NOT EVEN FUNNY.
- HAVE TO CHANGE THAT "O"
TO AN "A"--LORENZA.
- STILL NOT COOPERATING.
- LORENZO'’S ALREADY
BEING STUBBORN, JUST LIKE DADDY,
AND WE JUST WANT TO SEE
HIS LITTLE WIENER
SO WE CAN GET THE DAY
OVER WITH.
- I CAN'’T WAIT TO SEE
MY SON'’S WIENER.
- THESE ARE THE TESTICLES
RIGHT THERE.
SEE THOSE UP THERE?
- OH, THANK GOD.
- [bleep].
- [laughing]
- OKAY?
- [exhales]
- OKAY.
- IS THAT HIS SACK?
- OH, I SEE THEM!
LOOK AT HIS LITTLE BALLS!
- THERE'’S THE PENIS RIGHT THERE.
- WHERE?
- THIS LITTLE THING
RIGHT THERE.
THERE YOU GO.
- YES.
- ALL RIGHT,
THE BABY'’S COMING OUT
TO ABOUT 6 POUNDS,
2 OUNCES.
- 6 POUNDS ALREADY?
I'’M GONNA DELIVER
A 10-POUND KID.
- [laughs]
OH, MY GOD.
- I'’M A VERY TINY GIRL,
AND THE FACT THAT, YOU KNOW,
JUST EVEN THINKING ABOUT
PUSHING OUT
A BABY MORE THAN 6 POUNDS,
IT'’S A LITTLE SCARY.
IT'’S BULL[bleep].
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY.
- 6 POUNDS?
- I'’M HAPPY.
- WELL, YOU'’RE NOT DELIVERING.
GIVING BIRTH DEFINITELY
MAKES ME NERVOUS.
I'’M SCARED [bleep]LESS.
I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW IT'’S GOING TO FEEL.
I DON'’T WANT
MY VAGINA RIPPING.
IT'’S JUST VERY SCARY.
BUT I FIGURE
IF I GOT PREGNANT,
GOD IS SAYING
THAT I CAN TAKE IT.
BUT I THINK GOD GOT ME MIXED UP
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE,
BECAUSE I DON'’T THINK
I CAN DO IT.
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
[phone ringtones]
HEY, BOO,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- MAKING DINNER.
I WANTED TO STOP UP TOMORROW.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- IT'’S GOING TO BE REALLY,
REALLY NICE TOMORROW.
DO YOU WANT TO GO, LIKE,
OUTSIDE SOMEWHERE AND EAT?
- YEAH, I'’LL FIND A PLACE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I WENT TO THE DOCTOR'’S TODAY.
- YOU DID!
- YEAH, HE'’S 6 POUNDS ALREADY.
- AW, THAT'’S, LIKE,
THE PERFECT WEIGHT.
- JENNI, HE'’S HUGE.
- HE IS KIND OF BIG.
IS HE JIONNI'’S?
- NO.
- I'’M KIDDING.
- COOL.
- DID HE SAY
HE'’S GOING TO GO EARLY?
- NO, HE HAS NO IDEA.
- BABE, LORENZO'’S
6 POUNDS ALREADY.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- JESUS.
THAT'’S CRAZY.
I THINK THE MOMENT THAT JIONNI
AND NICOLE'’S KID IS BORN,
HE'’S PROBABLY GONNA BE ABLE
TO TAKE HIS DAD...
- [laughing]
- IN A FIST FIGHT,
IN THE STREETS.
- ALL RIGHT, BOO,
I'’LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
- ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU TOO.
BYE.
- BYE.
- HOW MUCH LONGER'’S SHE GOT?
- LESS THAN A MONTH.
SHE'’S SUPPOSED TO BE GROWING
A POUND A WEEK NOW.
THAT'’S NOT GOOD, '’CAUSE
IF HE'’S 6 POUNDS ALREADY--
IF SHE GIVES BIRTH,
HE'’LL BE 9 POUNDS.
- THAT'’S THE SAME WEIGHT
AS HIS DAD'’S HEAD.
- ♪ I NEED SOMEONE WHO'’S CLEAN
WITH A DIRTY MIND ♪
- HELLO!
- WE'’RE GONNA GO
TO GODFATHER'’S.
I KNOW YOU WANTED
TO EAT OUTSIDE,
BUT THERE'’S REALLY
NOWHERE TO EAT OUTSIDE HERE.
- OKAY.
HOW CUTE IS YOUR BELLY?
- UGH.
- ♪ DOWNTOWN, ALL AROUND ♪
♪ TAKE ME ON A JOURNEY RIDE ♪
- I LOOK PREGNANT.
- WELL, YOU'’RE
ABOUT TO GIVE BIRTH.
- YOU'’RE ANNOYING.
- WHY?
- '’CAUSE YOU'’RE, LIKE, SKINNY,
AND I LOOK LIKE A WHALE.
- BECAUSE ME AND NICOLE
ARE IN COMMITTED RELATIONSHIPS,
SHE'’S ABOUT TO HAVE A BABY,
BUT YET, WE STILL TALK
TO EACH OTHER EVERY DAY.
- AND WE STILL MAKE TIME
FOR EACH OTHER.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
THIS WEEKEND?
- NOTHING.
- WANT TO COME DOWN?
JUST DON'’T MENTION
THE ENGAGEMENT.
- THAT'’S ALL I WANT
TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT.
- I THINK
HE'’S GETTING REALLY ANNOYED.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH.
- MAYBE I WON'’T TALK TO HIM.
I DON'’T WANT TO GET HIM MAD.
- IT IS, LIKE,
A STATUS SYMBOL FOR ME.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- LIKE A RING, ENGAGEMENT.
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS HOW I PICTURE MY RING.
I DATE SOMEONE 6'’4",
LARGER-THAN-LIFE
PERSONALITY AND PHYSIQUE.
- HUGE PEE-PEE.
- THAT'’S HOW I LOOK AT IT
WHEN IT COMES TO HIS RING--
HAS TO BE
LARGER THAN LIFE.
EVEN THOUGH
WE'’RE AVERAGE PEOPLE,
WE DON'’T ACT AVERAGE.
MY [bleep] ARE NOT [bleep]
AVERAGE [bleep].
LIKE, THEY'’RE [bleep] LARGE
AND IN CHARGE.
SO, BY SAYING THAT,
LIKE FOR US,
TO ASK ROGER TO GET ME
AN AVERAGE RING,
IT WOULDN'’T HAPPEN.
I WANT THE RING THAT I WANT,
WHICH I KNOW IS GOING TO TAKE
A LONG TIME TO MAKE.
I CAN'’T EVEN EXPLAIN IT
TO YOU.
- I WANT TO TAKE YOU
TO THE JEWELER'’S.
SINCE I'’M SEEING ROGER
TOMORROW,
MAYBE IF I DO TALK TO HIM
ABOUT THE RING,
HE'’LL HAVE AN IDEA,
AT LEAST.
- I ASKED ROGER
FOR HIS PERMISSION.
HE SAID LOOKING FOR RINGS
HE DIDN'’T WANT ME TO DO,
BUT I'’LL DO IT ANYWAYS.
- I DEFINITELY
WOULD LIKE JENNI
TO SHOW ME A COUPLE RINGS
THAT SHE WANTS,
SO, THEN, YOU KNOW, IF ROGER
DOES ASK ME TO GO WITH HIM,
THEN I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT TO GET.
HOW MANY CARATS DO YOU WANT?
- I WANT A 5 MIDDLE...
- OKAY.
- PRINCESS CUT,
AND THEN I'’M GONNA--
LOOKING AT GETTING
PINK DIAMONDS AROUND IT.
I LOVE PINK
AND BLACK DIAMONDS,
SO I WOULD LIKE
1- TO 2-CARAT,
EACH SIDE BEING PINK,
AND A BAND WITH PINK DIAMONDS.
- WOW.
- THAT'’S WHY ROGER'’S
LIVER AND KIDNEY
ARE CURRENTLY BEING SOLD
ON THE BLACK MARKET.
- WE SELL A SIX-CARAT NATURAL
PINK DIAMOND,
AND IT'’S ABOUT
A MILLION DOLLARS.
- YEAH.
- SO, IF I HAD TO GUESS--
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- $40,000 OR $50,000
FOR A ONE-CARAT STONE.
- YEAH.
- $200,000?
- WHAT!
- THAT'’S CRAZY.
THAT'’S A HOUSE.
I THINK JENNI'’S RING IS ABSURD,
AND THAT'’S A BIG WORD.
I DON'’T THINK
THIS IS A CLASSY RING.
I JUST THINK
THIS IS A VERY EXPENSIVE RING.
A CLASSY RING WOULD
BE JUST, LIKE,
A LITTLE ROCK AND THAT'’S IT.
BUT TO HAVE, LIKE, PINK IN IT,
AND, LIKE,
DIFFERENT PINK STONES,
I MEAN, THAT'’S A TOTAL
JENNI RING.
I HAVE A TUMMY ACHE
JUST FOR ROGER.
- I LOOK AT IT LIKE THIS.
WE'’RE TOGETHER.
I KNOW WE'’RE GOING
TO BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
SO NOW IT'’S ON HIM,
AND EVERY YEAR HE WAITS,
EVERY YEAR I CHANGE MY MIND
ON WHAT RING I WANT.
- SO, CLEAN--
- AND MY MIND DOESN'’T GO DOWN.
- RIGHT. IT ALWAYS GOES UP.
- IT ALWAYS GOES UP.
- THE LONGER YOU WAIT,
THE BIGGER THE STONE HAS TO BE.
- YEAH, GOOD LUCK.
- [laughter]
- I'’M GOING TO BEAT UP
THIS LITTLE KID OVER HERE.
I'’M NOT THE TYPE OF GUY
THAT CAN GO OUT, PACE HIMSELF,
AND ONLY HAVE
ONE OR TWO DRINKS.
IT WOULD DEFEAT
THE PURPOSE OF GOING OUT.
- OH, MY GOD,
HE'’S GOING TO THROW HIM.
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
- I JUST DON'’T FEEL GOOD.
MY HEART'’S RACING.
MY STOMACH IS HUGE.
I'’M OVER BEING PREGNANT.
I CAN'’T DO IT.
I FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
- WHERE WERE YOU JUST NOW?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT,
CHICKEN PARM TONIGHT?
- YEAH.
SO TONIGHT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE DATE NIGHT
WHERE JIONNI'’S GONNA
TAKE ME OUT,
BUT HONESTLY,
I DON'’T FEEL LIKE GOING OUT.
I DON'’T FEEL LIKE DRESSING UP
IN A DRESS.
I JUST WANT TO BE IN PAJAMAS,
SO JIONNI COOKING ME DINNER
TONIGHT IS THE PERFECT SOLUTION.
- WHY DON'’T YOU GO LAY DOWN?
- I JUST WANT TO CUDDLE.
- GO LAY DOWN
AND I'’LL GO GET EVERYTHING.
- WHERE YOU GOING?
- GROCERY SHOPPING.
- WHERE?
- THE BEST PART
ABOUT LIVING AT HOME,
I GOT A GROCERY STORE
RIGHT UPSTAIRS.
I JUST WRITE
MY LITTLE GROCERY LIST DOWN,
I GET MY BAG,
I GO UPSTAIRS AND GO SHOPPING.
AW, I NEED A BLENDER.
I NEED A SALAD BOWL.
WHERE'’S THAT, UH, THINGAMAJIG?
GEE, GOLLY, THANKS, MOM.
- SERIOUSLY,
DON'’T YOU HAVE STUFF?
YOU HAVE A KITCHEN.
- TONIGHT, I AM MAKING NICOLE
A FEAST OF MASHED POTATOES,
CHICKEN PARM, SALAD,
BROCCOLI, AND CORN.
[gasps]
- OH, MY GOD,
YOU SCARED ME.
DO YOU HAVE POT HOLDERS?
- NO, I HAVE RAGS.
- NO, NO, NO.
YOU'’RE GONNA BURN YOURSELF.
I'’LL THROW THEM DOWN.
- NO, I'’M NOT.
- NO?
- NO.
- AHH!
CAN I HAVE POT HOLDERS?
- OH, MY GOD.
- BABE?
- WHAT?
- WHAT YOU THINK?
- I LIKE IT.
YOU'’RE A SEX MACHINE...
WITHOUT THE SEX.
THE PLAN IS TO GO
TO KARMA TONIGHT.
WE HAVEN'’T BEEN THERE
IN A LITTLE BIT.
- BABE, THE CAB'’S HERE.
- YOU KNOW, GOT MY LITTLE CIRCLE
OF FRIENDS OVER.
YOU KNOW,
I'’M GONNA GET WHITE-BOY WASTED,
BUT STILL GONNA BE
THE MATURE ONE IN THE GROUP.
- OH, MY GOD, I CAN'’T BELIEVE
WE'’RE AT KARMA RIGHT NOW.
- IF THERE'’S NOT A FIGHT
RIGHT NOW,
THERE WILL BE
IN FIVE MINUTES, HANG ON.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW YOU DOING, JENNI?
- GOOD.
- ♪ YOU SEND ME FLYING ♪
♪ WITHOUT EVEN TRYING ♪
- SO WE'’RE ALL PARTYING
AT KARMA, AND I INVITED DANNY,
AND I'’M SO EXCITED,
BECAUSE I HAVEN'’T SEEN
MY FELLOW SHORE STORE EMPLOYEES
IN FOREVER.
- THIS GUY,
THIS FREAKIN'’ GUY RIGHT HERE.
DANNY'’S A GOOD GUY.
DANNY'’S REAL EASYGOING,
REAL LAID-BACK.
SO, YOU KNOW, I DECIDED TO
LIVEN UP HIS MOOD A LITTLE BIT.
- THAT'’S OUR BOSS!
OH, MY GOD,
HE'’S GOING TO THROW HIM.
- I MADE YOU DINNER.
- I'’M SO HUNGRY.
- I AM GOING ALL OUT TONIGHT.
I WANT TO MAKE THIS ROMANTIC.
I WANT TO MAKE THIS SPECIAL.
YOU KNOW, NICOLE'’S UNDER
THE WEATHER, SHE'’S PREGNANT.
I WANT TO MAKE HER FEEL GOOD.
- I LOVE IT.
- DO YOU KNOW I LEGIT
MADE EVERYTHING MYSELF?
- I BELIEVE YOU.
LOOKS DELICIOUS.
YOU MADE THAT YOURSELF?
- SWEAR TO GOD.
- I THINK JIONNI'’S
AN EXCELLENT COOK.
I THINK HE TAKES AFTER HIS MOM,
AND YOU KNOW,
IT'’S KIND OF SEXY
KNOWING THAT YOUR MAN CAN COOK.
- ARE YOU NERVOUS
FOR TOMORROW?
- NO.
- YOU SHOULD GET A LIST
OF QUESTIONS FOR THIS LADY.
- I'’M GONNA GET A PAD.
- WELL, I'’M GONNA GO SIT
ON THE COUCH WATCHING FOOTBALL
WHILE YOU DO THE DISHES.
- OH, GET REAL.
- SO TOMORROW WE'’RE HAVING
A BABY TEACHER COME OVER
TO BASICALLY TEACH US
HOW TO DEAL WITH NEWBORNS,
AND WHAT WE'’RE GOING
TO GET OURSELVES INTO.
HOW OFTEN DO YOU BATHE HIM?
- HOW OFTEN DO YOU BATHE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JUST WRITE BATHE.
HOW OFTEN DO YOU CHANGE
A DIAPER?
IF HE'’S CRYING,
AND HE'’S NOT HUNGRY,
AND HIS DIAPER'’S BEEN CHANGED,
WHAT COULD IT BE?
- HE WANTS TO BE HELD.
- YOU DON'’T KNOW.
- HE WANTS MY NIPPLE.
- HE ALREADY ATE.
- HE WANTS TO BE HELD.
HE WANTS TO BE LOVED.
- I'’M NOT ASKING YOU.
WE'’RE ASKING HER.
- HE WANTS TO BE CUDDLED.
- PUT IT DOWN.
HOW MANY OUNCES OF FORMULA
DO YOU USE?
- HE'’S SUCKING ON MY BOOB.
- HOW DOES HE KNOW
WHEN TO STOP?
- '’CAUSE HE'’S FULL.
- NO, MAYBE
HE'’LL JUST KEEP GOING.
- IF THE BABY'’S FULL,
HE'’S FULL.
- OKAY.
HOW DO YOU HOLD HIM?
- ♪ WE IN THE CLUB ♪
♪ TURN THE MUSIC UP,
TURN IT UP ♪
- I'’M GOING TO BEAT UP
THIS LITTLE KID OVER HERE.
I'’M NOT THE TYPE OF GUY THAT
CAN GO OUT, AND PACE HIMSELF,
AND ONLY HAVE
ONE OR TWO DRINKS.
IT DEFEATS THE PURPOSE
OF GOING OUT.
I MIGHT AS WELL
STAY AT HOME.
- ♪ WE IN THE CLUB ♪
♪ TURN THE MUSIC UP,
TURN IT UP ♪
♪ THE ROOF IS ON FIRE ♪
♪ BURN IT UP,
BURN IT UP ♪
- ROGER HAS
THE BEST DANCE MOVES EVER.
EVEN IF YOU GET, LIKE,
45 SECONDS OF HIS DANCING,
IT'’S LIKE
THE BEST 45 SECONDS EVER.
- IT IS HORRIBLE.
I THINK I MIGHT DANCE
MORE THAN YOU GIVE IT UP.
YEAH? NO?
FEEL BETTER?
- FEEL BETTER?
I LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU.
- OW!
WHERE IS THE NEAREST HOSPITAL?
THESE PAINS RIGHT NOW,
I THINK I'’M GOING EARLIER.
- NOW I'’M NERVOUS.
- JESUS, TAKE THE WHEEL.
- WAKEY, WAKEY, WAKEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'’M TOO HUNGOVER FOR--
NO, NO, NO.
NO, I'’M FREAKING OUT.
STOP!
I FEEL LIKE IT WAS AN AMAZING
NIGHT LAST NIGHT AT KARMA.
ALL THOSE SHOTS WERE WORTH IT,
BUT I FEEL LIKE [bleep].
YOU'’RE AWFUL!
JUST MAKE IT STOP.
JUST MAKE IT STOP!
I'’M GOING TO THROW UP!
[doorbell rings]
- LILLIAN.
- HI, GOOD MORNING.
- OUR BABY COACH LILLIAN
IS COMING TODAY,
AND SHE'’S GOING TO TEACH US
HOW TO DEAL WITH NEWBORNS.
I'’M NOT GOING TO LIE.
I DON'’T KNOW [bleep]
ABOUT NEWBORNS.
- SO, I WANT TO KIND OF GET
AN IDEA OF WHAT YOU KNOW,
AND WHERE DO YOU NEED
A LITTLE BIT MORE OF
REINFORCEMENT OR CLARIFICATION.
- EVERYTHING.
- OKAY, SO WE CAN DEAL
WITH EVERYTHING.
YOU HIDE YOUR ANSWERS
FROM HER.
- BUT WE'’RE PARTNERS.
- OH, GOD.
I AM REAL NERVOUS
ABOUT THIS.
NICOLE'’S READ ABOUT
TWO OR THREE PREGNANCY BOOKS,
AND I'’VE READ
HALF A PREGNANCY BOOK.
- WE'’RE SCREWED.
- LET'’S START.
NEWBORNS
CAN SEE A DISTANCE OF...
- 10 FEET.
- 50 FEET.
- LET'’S TRY 8 TO 14 INCHES.
- WHOA, THEY DON'’T SEE [bleep]!
- HOW MANY SOFT SPOTS
DOES THE BABY HAVE IN HIS HEAD?
IT'’S TWO.
HAVE ONE UP HERE,
AND ONE IN THE BACK.
- I FEEL LIKE I'’M GOING TO BE,
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
EXPELLED FROM HIGH SCHOOL.
ME AND JIONNI
ARE BASICALLY CLUELESS.
- TO REDUCE YOUR BABY'’S RISK
OF S.I.D.S.,
HE SHOULD SLEEP ON HIS--
DO YOU KNOW WHAT S.I.D.S. IS?
- NO.
- HE SHOULD SLEEP ON HIS--
- SIDE.
- BACK.
- CORRECT.
- WHOO!
LOSER.
- SHOULD WE BE
WRITING THINGS DOWN?
- MAYBE.
- ♪ LEAVE ME ALONE,
THEN YOU CALL MY HOUSE ♪
- ROGER AND JENNI ARE WAITING
FOR US. YOU ALMOST READY?
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY!
I'’M SERIOUS.
I'’M NOT JUST SAYING THAT.
YOU'’RE PREGNANT.
- PUSH ME UP THE STAIRS.
YEAH!
ISN'’T THAT NICE?
- BIG DRIVEWAY.
I LIKE IT.
- I'’M SO EXCITED
TO SEE YOUR DOGS.
- HI!
LOOK HOW PRETTY YOU ARE.
- HI.
- NOELLE--HI!
- HOW YOU FEELING THERE,
PREGNANT LADY?
- UNCOMFORTABLE.
WE'’RE GONNA HAVE DINNER
WITH JENNI AND ROGER,
AND I'’M VERY EXCITED
FOR ALL FOUR OF US TO HANG OUT,
BECAUSE IT'’S FUN TO BE WITH,
YOU KNOW, OTHER COUPLES,
AND PLUS,
IT'’S YOUR BEST FRIEND.
I'’M STARVING.
- [barks]
- [gasp]
GOD, DON'’T DO THAT
TO A PREGNANT PERSON.
- NICOLE'’S GONNA POOP.
- OH, I SMELL GAS.
- WE'’RE GOING TO HAVE TO LIGHT
SOMETHING ON THE STOVE
AND DO IT THAT WAY.
FIRE!
- ARE YOU SURE THAT'’S SAFE?
- NO.
- I'’M GETTING OUT OF HERE.
- GO, GO, GO!
- SHUT IT OFF.
SHUT IT OFF, FIRST OF ALL.
- JIONNI, STEP AWAY.
- MOVE YOUR HAND!
- MONGRELS.
WHOA!
OH, MY GOD,
IT'’S GONNA BLOW UP.
I DON'’T THINK
THAT'’S HOW YOU LIGHT A GRILL.
- I'’M STARVING.
- OW!
WHERE IS THE NEAREST HOSPITAL?
- MOUNT ZIMMER.
- NICOLE, IF YOUR WATER BREAKS,
I GUARANTEE I'’LL GET HOME IN...
HALF HOUR.
- I'’M NOT KIDDING.
I'’M GETTING SEVERE PAINS
RIGHT NOW.
- SO CRAZY.
- BURNERS.
YOU SAID YOU LIKE YOURS RARE,
RIGHT?
I LIKE MINE RARE, SO I'’M GOING
TO EAT MINE LIKE THIS.
- YEAH.
NICOLE, IS THAT COOKED ENOUGH?
- I THINK SO.
- YEAH, THAT'’S COOKED.
- WHAT KIND OF SAUCE IS THAT?
- ON THE STEAKS,
PETER LUGER'’S.
STEAK SAUCE.
REALLY GOOD.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- LET'’S FAST FORWARD
SIX MONTHS
AFTER THE BABY'’S HERE.
WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF?
- SIX MONTHS?
PLANNING OUR WEDDING.
- PLANNING A WEDDING.
- YEAH?
- I WANT LORENZO PART
OF OUR WEDDING.
- OKAY.
- HE CAN BE A RING BEARER.
- [bleep],
HE MIGHT BE TEN BY THEN.
- [laughter]
- DID YOU SEE HER FACE?
SHE'’S KIDDING.
- GAVE A LOOK.
- NO. NOBODY'’S PRESSURING ME.
I'’M MOVING AT MY OWN PACE.
- SO I DON'’T WANT
TO THINK ABOUT THAT,
BECAUSE I DON'’T WANT
TO GET DISAPPOINTED
IF IT DOESN'’T HAPPEN
IN THE NEXT COUPLE OF MONTHS.
I'’D RATHER
JUST BE BLINDSIDED.
SIDEBLINDED.
[bleep], ONE OF TH--I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT THE HELL IT'’S CALLED.
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
- ARE YOU SURE LORENZO'’S
SIX POUNDS RIGHT NOW?
- YEAH.
- THAT'’S WHAT HE SAID.
THAT'’S, LIKE,
A LOT OF WEIGHT I'’M CARRYING.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL, THOUGH?
BACK HURT?
- SUFFERING.
- SLEEPING GOOD?
- NO.
NERVOUS AT ALL?
- YEAH.
- SHE'’S JUST NERVOUS
ABOUT THE ACTUAL BIRTH.
- I'’M SO NERVOUS.
- YOU NEVER KNOW IF SHE COULD
GO NEXT WEEK, YOU KNOW?
YOUR WATER BREAKS, WE ARE
HIGHTAILING IT OUT OF HERE.
- I HONESTLY THOUGHT
IT WAS GOING TO
IN THE BATHROOM JUST NOW.
- I MEAN HIGHTAILING IT.
- [screams]
- STOP!
- ESAU, GET OVER HERE.
- MY STOMACH IS KILLING ME.
CAN WE GET GOING SOON?
- YEAH.
- I'’M VERY UNCOMFORTABLE.
IT'’S HARD FOR ME TO EVEN SIT,
TO WALK, TO DO ANYTHING.
I JUST WANT TO GET HOME
AND LAY DOWN.
- BYE!
- BYE, GUYS!
- THANK YOU!
- THANK YOU.
- BYE. GET HOME SAFE.
DRIVE SAFE.
- BYE!
- DID YOU HAVE FUN?
- YES, MINUS THE CRAMPS.
THESE PAINS RIGHT NOW,
I THINK I'’M GOING EARLIER.
OH, DEAR.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- MM.
- IF YOUR WATER BREAKS--
- STOP IT.
UGH. I'’M IN SO MUCH PAIN.
- WHAT IF IT'’S NEXT WEEK?
- I'’M NOT KIDDING,
I THINK IT IS.
- AW, [bleep].
NOW I'’M NERVOUS.
- SO ON THE RIDE HOME,
I'’M JUST FEELING
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE
TO THE POINT WHERE I HAVE
TO PUT MY SEAT BACK.
I'’M, LIKE,
HOLDING MY STOMACH UP,
AND I'’M JUST FEELING, LIKE,
THESE SEVERE CRAMPS.
AND I DON'’T KNOW WHAT'’S GOING ON
RIGHT NOW. I'’M SCARED.
THIS [bleep] HURTS.
JESUS, TAKE THE WHEEL.
- THERE'’S MORE
SNOOKI AND JWOWWON THE WAY...
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- OOH, I'’M GOING TO MAKE
SOMETHING.
WATCH THIS, MOTHER.
THERE'’S TONS OF FOOD
ON SUNDAY DINNER.
MY MOM LEGIT WAKES UP
AT PROBABLY 4:00 OR 5:00
AND JUST COOKS LIKE A MANIAC.
I'’M GONNA TEACH YOU SOMETHING
FOR ONCE.
- YEAH, GO AHEAD.
IT'’LL BE A REAL MIRACLE.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- NOTHING.
- ITALIANS DO IT RIGHT
ON SUNDAY.
WE HAVE THE WHOLE FAMILY.
WE EAT LIKE MANIACS.
ALL MY BROTHERS
AND SISTERS COME.
NO MATTER WHERE THEY ARE,
YOU HAVE TO BE HERE AT MY HOUSE
FOR SUNDAY DINNER.
- JIONNI, DID YOU SEE
THE ROOM UPSTAIRS?
- YEAH, IT LOOKS AWESOME.
NICOLE'’S GONNA LOVE IT.
BABE, HOW YOU FEELING?
- OH, GOD,
I'’M SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
I JUST DON'’T FEEL RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE I'’M GONNA
HAVE THIS BABY SOON.
AND RIGHT NOW,
I JUST WANT TO BE ALONE.
AND IT KIND OF SUCKS
BECAUSE IT'’S SUNDAY DINNER.
AND EVERYONE'’S GONNA BE HERE.
- HI!
- HI, JANELLE.
- HI, NELLY.
JIONNI'’S COOKING
THE WHOLE DINNER FOR YOU.
- '’CAUSE YOU'’RE
MY FAVORITE SISTER.
- YOUR ONLY SISTER.
- WE HAVE THE WHOLE FAMILY.
WE GOT MY MOM,
MY DAD, JOSEPH.
I GOT MY BROTHER JOE, HIS BABY
JOEY, AND HIS WIFE GISELLE,
MY SISTER JANELLE,
MY BROTHER-IN-LAW MIKE,
MY LITTLE NEPHEW BABY MIKE,
ME AND NICOLE,
JACKIE.
EVERYONE'’S
THERE JUST TO EAT,
AND EVERYONE'’S
JUST HAVING A GOOD TIME.
- OH, HE'’S GOT A LITTLE
BLACK AND BLUE ON HIS HEAD.
WHERE'’D HE GET THAT FROM?
- SCRATCHING HIMSELF.
- HEY, JACK.
HI, BOO.
- HI.
HOW YOU FEELING?
- HURT REALLY BAD.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING
INTO LABOR LAST NIGHT.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
I'’M TRYING TO PUT ON
A FACE RIGHT NOW,
BUT HONESTLY, LIKE,
I JUST WANT TO DIE.
WELL, NOT DIE,
BUT I JUST DON'’T FEEL
LIKE BEING
AROUND PEOPLE TODAY
BECAUSE I'’M SO TIRED OF TRYING
TO MAKE THIS PREGNANCY
SEEM LIKE IT'’S SO EASY,
WHEN REALLY IT'’S NOT
AND IT'’S KILLING ME.
- ALL RIGHT, COME ON, GUYS,
SIT OUTSIDE.
NICOLE'’S SITTING BY HERSELF.
HERE, PUT THIS OVER HERE.
PUT IT ON THE TABLE?
MOVE THAT HUGE THING
IN THE MIDDLE.
- SAUSAGE IS DONE.
WE NEED MORE PLATES?
- IS THIS YOUR RETIREMENT PARTY?
[laughter]
- NO.
- WAIT, ARE YOU PREGNANT,
MOM?
- THAT'’S A DEFINITE NO.
- YEAH, THAT WOULD REALLY BE
SOME SURPRISE.
[laughter]
- JOE.
- JI, GOOD JOB
WITH THE DINNER.
- THANKS, JOE.
- MOMMY HAS A SURPRISE
FOR NICOLE.
- MUST BE A BABY SURPRISE.
- MAYBE.
- MY MOM HAS BEEN
HAVING A SURPRISE FOR NICOLE
FOR ABOUT TWO WEEKS NOW.
SHE HAS A LITTLE NURSERY
GOING ON.
- JUST IN CASE ANYBODY WANTS
TO SLEEP AT NANA'’S HOUSE.
JUST IN CASE
ANYBODY TRUSTS NANA OVERNIGHT.
- SO I'’M HOPING THIS
CHEERS HER UP,
AND I'’M VERY EXCITED FOR MOM
TO SHOW THIS TO NICOLE.
- OKAY, READY?
- [gasps]
PRETTY!
- THIS IS YOUR NEW ROOM.
- NICOLE, IS THAT--REMEMBER
THE TIGER YOU WANTED TO GET?
- YEAH.
- YOU LIKE IT?
- I LOVE IT.
I'’M DEFINITELY THANKFUL
AND VERY, VERY HAPPY THAT,
YOU KNOW,
JANICE DID THIS NURSERY.
THIS IS SO NICE.
- COME ON, LEELEE.
- SO THEY COULD SLEEP OVER.
- BUT RIGHT NOW,
MY HEART'’S RACING.
MY STOMACH IS HUGE.
I'’M OVER BEING PREGNANT.
I JUST WANT
TO HAVE HIM ALREADY,
BECAUSE I CAN'’T TAKE
FEELING LIKE THIS ANYMORE.
- WHERE'’D YOU GO?
WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
- [crying]
I JUST DON'’T FEEL GOOD.
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
- I CAN'’T BREATHE.
I FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
- WHERE WERE YOU JUST NOW?
- UPSTAIRS.
I JUST DON'’T FEEL GOOD.
I'’M SO OVER THIS.
- I DON'’T FEEL GOOD.
I'’M SORRY, BUT I CAN'’T SIT
IN THE CAR FOR AN HOUR.
I HAVE NO ENERGY,
MY STOMACH HURTS,
AND I JUST NEED
TO GET HOME AND REST,
BECAUSE
I JUST DON'’T FEEL RIGHT.
BABE!
I'’M SCARED!
- WHAT?
- I THINK MY WATER BROKE.
- I'’M NOT READY FOR THIS.
- MY WATER BROKE.
- WHAT!
YOU'’RE LYING.
- I SWEAR TO GOD.
- IT'’S EARLY.
- NEXT TIME YOU SEE ME,
I'’LL BE IN SCRUBS, ALL RIGHT?
- I'’M JUST SCARED.
I REALLY DON'’T WANT TO TALK.
PLEASE DON'’T MAKE ME TALK.
- YOU'’RE GONNA BE FINE, HON.
- THIS IS IT.
- YOU'’RE MAKING ME
SO STRESSED.
I DON'’T LIKE IT.
- YOU'’RE GONNA BE FINE.