- LOOK HOW SMALL
HE'S GONNA BE.
- ALL RIGHT,
THE BABY'S COMING OUT
TO ABOUT 6 POUNDS,
2 OUNCES.
- 6 POUNDS ALREADY?
I'M GONNA DELIVER
A 10-POUND KID.
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD.
- IS IT WEIRD IF I TRY ON
WEDDING DRESSES FOR FUN?
- KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
- WHAT IF I GO LOOK
FOR RINGS?
- THAT'S PRESSURING ME.
- OKAY, I WON'T DO THAT.
- IT'S A DIFFERENT--
THAT'S A DIFFERENT STORY.
- IF I HAD TO GUESS...
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- $40,000 OR $50,000
FOR A ONE-KARAT STONE.
- YEAH.
- $200,000?
- WHAT?
- IT'S CRAZY.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I JUST DON'T FEEL GOOD.
MY HEART'S RACING.
MY STOMACH IS HUGE.
I'M OVER BEING PREGNANT.
- [crying]
I CAN'T BREATHE.
I FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
- * I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
[gentle piano music]
*
- WHERE'D YOU GO?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- [sniffles]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I JUST DON'T FEEL GOOD.
- [sniffling]
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
I FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
- WHERE WERE YOU JUST NOW?
- UPSTAIRS.
I JUST DON'T FEEL GOOD.
[crying]
- I DON'T SEE NICOLE UPSET
THAT OFTEN,
AND I NEVER SEE HER EMOTIONS
REALLY TAKE OVER LIKE THIS.
AND IT'S TOUGH, YOU KNOW?
AS A FIANCE,
AS THE FATHER, IT JUST--
I WISH I COULD, YOU KNOW,
TAKE THE PAIN AWAY.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
HERE.
DRINK SOME WATER, PLEASE.
- I'M SO OVER THIS.
- PLEASE DRINK SOME WATER.
- MY HEART IS RACING.
I JUST FEEL WEIRD.
- WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
- I JUST WANNA DIE.
- [clicks tongue]
NICOLE.
- I'M SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL,
IT'S GONNA BE LIKE THIS
FOR ANOTHER WEEK OR TWO.
- I HATE IT.
- DON'T CRY.
YOU GOT ME NERVOUS.
I THOUGHT SOMETHING
WAS WRONG WITH YOU.
- I'M NOT BEING A BABY.
- [snickers]
YOU'RE NOT BEING A BABY.
YOU'RE [bleep] PREGNANT.
YOU'RE DOING AWESOME.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
YOUR MOM'S PROUD.
EVERYONE'S PROUD OF YOU.
YOU'RE DOING AWESOME.
YOU JUST GOT A FEW MORE WEEKS.
THAT'S IT.
YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY.
I WOULDN'T LIE TO YOU.
WHEN YOU'RE A BRAT,
I TELL YOU YOU'RE A BRAT.
IF YOU'RE BEING A BABY,
I'LL TELL YOU.
YOU'RE NOT.
- [sniffles]
- IF YOU DID THIS
EVERY NIGHT, THEN MAYBE.
- [giggles]
- BUT YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH A CRAZY TIME.
AND ONCE HE'S OUT,
I GUARANTEE YOU,
YOU'RE GONNA BE FEELING
AWESOME.
- PROMISE?
- I PROMISE.
- JUST AS LONG AS JIONNI'S
HERE FOR ME,
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
- WE'RE HAVING A KID TOGETHER.
- JIONNI'S MY BEST FRIEND,
AND HE'S THE ONLY ONE
IN THIS WORLD THAT KNOWS,
LIKE, HOW I FEEL.
- A FEW MORE WEEKS.
THEN WE'RE GONNA HAVE
OUR BABY.
[gentle rock music]
- * CAN WE KEEP THIS
GOING ON? *
*
- WELL, HELLO THERE.
- HI.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
TODAY WE'RE HAVING
A BARBECUE.
- IT'S REALLY NOTHING SPECIAL.
IT'S JUST A COUPLE
OF FRIENDS OVER.
AND MY DAD.
- AND BIG DADDY PAIN.
NEED A DRINK?
- SURE.
- BEER, OR YOU WANT
A DRINK DRINK?
- DRINK DRINK.
- YOU KNOW MAX.
- YEAH.
- YOU KNOW RENEE.
- HI. I DON'T KNOW IF WE EVER--
- NOPE.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T?
- NEVER.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH.
- THIS IS DJ LICIOUS.
- THAT'S HER--
- THAT'S HER DJ NAME.
- OKAY.
- NO, THAT'S ON MY BIRTH
CERTIFICATE.
[laughter]
- I PUT SOME BURGERS ON.
WE GOT A HOT TUB OUT THERE
IF ANYBODY WANTS
TO GET CRAZY.
- LET'S GO OUTSIDE.
- OKAY, THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING OUTSIDE.
[laughs]
- I THINK I NEED
TO KEEP AN EYE ON MY DAD
WHEN IT COMES TO RENEE
BECAUSE HE THINKS
THAT HE HAS,
LIKE, THIS MACK DADDY GAME,
WHICH MAKES ME WANT
TO THROW UP.
- I HAVE SO MUCH
TO UNDO RIGHT NOW.
WILL SOMEBODY COME HELP ME,
PLEASE?
[laughs]
- ALL RIGHT,
IF NOBODY ELSE WILL.
[cheers and laughter]
- MY DAD'S GOING?
HE HAS SUCH A BIG BELLY.
[laughter]
- TERRY, COME ON!
I'M GETTING NAKED IN HERE.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU READY?
- LET'S GO!
- LET ME GET THE DOOR
FOR YOU.
- HOT TUB!
[cheers]
[dog barks]
- OKAY, SHE'S READY.
- [cheers]
HERE WE GO!
TERRY, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GOING IN.
- JUMPING IN, BUDDY?
- I DON'T THINK
I BROUGHT A SUIT.
- I GOT ONE FOR YOU,
IF YOU WANT ONE.
- TERRY, LET'S GO!
COME ON!
- TERRY, YOU'RE WANTED.
YOU'RE A WANTED MAN, SIR.
- [chuckles]
- COME ON, TERRY.
- GET IN THERE, BUDDY.
- LET'S GO!
- I'M IN TROUBLE.
- GET IN THERE.
MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- TERRY, COME ON!
- ALL RIGHT.
IF NOBODY ELSE WILL.
- HE'S MOVING.
HE'S MOVING.
- DOES THAT MEAN HE'S CHANGING?
- I ACTUALLY THOUGHT IT WAS
GONNA BE A BORING BARBECUE.
- I KNOW.
- COME ON!
HOT TUB TIME.
- IF YOU GO IN THE HOT TUB...
- THEN YOUR DAD SHOWED UP.
- YEAH.
- IT'S HOT TUB TIME!
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS MY DAD DOING?
- I THINK TERRY'S DRANK
JUST ENOUGH
WHERE HE THINKS HE MIGHT HAVE
A SHOT WITH RENEE.
- [laughing]
- THIS IS HOW
IT ALL STARTS.
- I'M IN, BABY!
- OH, GOD.
- JENNI WANTS A BROTHER.
- UH-OH.
- WHOO!
[both laughing]
- DAD, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S VERY WEIRD TO SEE MY DAD
IN THE HOT TUB RIGHT NOW.
HE'S MY DAD.
IT'S GROSS.
DAD, YOU JUST BECAME
UNCLE NINO.
- OH, NO.
- [laughing]
- I DON'T NEED A CANE.
I HAVE A DIFFERENT KIND
OF WOOD.
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD.
[line rings]
- HEY, BOO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING, JUST HAVING
A FEW PEOPLE OVER.
I'M GOING INSIDE.
- ARE YOU HAVING A PARTY?
- NO, JUST A FEW PEOPLE.
- MUST BE NICE TO BE THEM.
- DO YOU STILL WANT
TO GET TOGETHER?
- YEAH, I WANT TO GO
WEDDING DRESS SHOPPING.
- YEAH, AND THEN I HAVE TO GET
A NICE OUTFIT
TO LEAVE THE HOSPITAL.
- UH-HUH.
WE'LL GO DO THAT
AND THEN WEDDING DRESSES.
- YEAH.
- WHEN DOES SHE GO TO MAINE?
- WHEN ARE YOU GOING
TO MAINE?
- NOT THIS WEEK.
NEXT WEEK.
- I'LL BE IN LABOR.
- NO, YOU WON'T.
- I GUARANTEE IT.
- I--
- WATCH.
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE GOING LATE.
- YEAH, BUT LEAVING
YOUR HOUSE YESTERDAY,
I WAS LEGIT, LIKE,
HAVING FAKE CONTRACTIONS.
- DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU JUST MADE ME NERVOUS.
- NO, IT HURT SO BAD.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
I WANTED TO KILL MYSELF.
IT MIGHT BE SOON.
I DON'T KNOW.
- YOU THINK THEY'RE
LEGIT CONTRACTIONS
OR JUST GAS PAINS?
- NO, IT DEFINITELY WASN'T
GAS PAINS.
IT WAS FAKE CONTRACTIONS.
- MAYBE HE'S DROPPING.
- I HOPE SO.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'LL CALL YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
TRY AND GET SOME SLEEP.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
- IT'S LOUD OVER THERE.
- LORENZO, IT'S ME.
[imitating Darth Vader]
I AM YOUR FATHER.
[laughs]
KICK IF YOU C--
- [gasps]
HE JUST DID!
- HE'S KICKING.
- I DEFINITELY LUCKED OUT
WITH JIONNI
BECAUSE HE'S A GREAT GUY.
HE'S GONNA BE A GREAT DAD
AND A GREAT HUSBAND.
AND I'M, LIKE, SO EXCITED
TO START MY FAMILY WITH HIM.
[Kill the Complex's Shine]
- HE LOVES ME ALREADY.
- * MAYBE I SHOULD WAIT HERE
- WE MADE HIM.
- * FOR THE SUN TO RISE
* SHINE ME THROUGH THE NIGHT
- MY BOY.
- YOU'RE TALKING
IN HIS BUTT.
OH, [bleep],
MY WATER JUST BROKE!
I DEFINITELY WANT TO FREAK
JIONNI OUT
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE
ON THIS DRY RUN.
DO YOU KNOW
WHERE THE HOSPITAL IS,
OR ARE YOU JUST DRIVING?
- BABE, HOLD ON.
I GOTTA CALL SOMEBODY.
- JENNI, HELP ME NOW.
[laughter]
- WHAT? ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- NICOLE'S WATER JUST BROKE.
WHAT DO WE DO?
- WHAT'S UP?
- READY TO HIT SOME BALLS?
- HELL, YEAH.
- YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN GOOD
WITH BALLS.
- YOU KNOW IT.
- JIONNI'S BEEN
KIND OF DROWNING
IN THIS WHOLE
BEING A DAD THING LATELY,
SO WE'RE GONNA GO DO
MAN STUFF TODAY.
YOU GOLF?
- YEAH.
- I DON'T, SO...
[chuckles]
AS YOU CAN SEE.
[comical music]
*
[bleep] [bleep].
- ROGER LOOKS LIKE
CONAN THE BARBARIAN
HACKING AT SOMEBODY.
- [grunts]
[grunts]
DUDE, WHY CAN I NOT
MAKE CONTACT?
- "ME ROGER.
WANT TO HIT BALL."
LIKE, HE JUST DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT HE'S DOING.
[whack]
- [bleep], BRO.
I LOST TWO IN A ROW.
- YOU'RE HAZARDOUS
TO THE SPORT.
KIDS HALF MY SIZE
CAN HIT THE BALL FURTHER
AND BETTER.
- [grunts]
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE WHERE IT WENT.
WHERE'D IT GO?
[whack]
OH.
[clatter]
PFFT.
ALMOST KILLED A MAN
RIGHT THERE.
- NOW I KNOW WHY THE KID
MAKES FUN OF ME.
HE'S ABOUT 2 FEET TALLER
THAN ME.
HE'S STRONG.
HE'S GOT TATTOOS.
BUT HE SUCKS AT SPORTS.
- [bleep] DAMN, BRO.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE'VE ESTABLISHED
I'M NOT A GOLFER.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK, MAN?
YOU GONNA BE, LIKE,
A LENIENT DAD, OR--
- LENIENT?
- GONNA HAVE CURFEWS?
- I'VE COME TO THE CONCLUSION
IF YOU RAISE YOUR KID
TOO STRICT,
TOO BY THE BOOK...
- YEAH.
- THEN HE'LL GO OFF TO THE EDGE.
GIVE HIM A LITTLE SPACE.
LET HIM HAVE FUN.
- [grunts]
- NOW HE'S HITTING 'EM.
SO WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- [grunts]
HOW YOU AND JENNI DOING?
- WE'RE GOOD, MAN.
WE'RE ACTUALLY GOOD.
WE, UH, YOU KNOW,
I MEAN,
WE BUTT HEADS
ONCE IN A WHILE STILL,
BUT FOR THE MOST PART,
OUR RELATIONSHIP'S GOING
REALLY GOOD.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- DEFINITELY NEXT STEP IS--
- MARRIAGE?
- WELL, GETTING ENGAGED
WOULD BE THE NEXT STEP.
- ANYTIME SOON?
- I THINK, FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN OUR RELATIONSHIP,
I'M REALLY SERIOUSLY
THINKING ABOUT IT
AND CONSIDERING IT,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- YOU AT LEAST GETTING LAID?
- NAH, THAT DIDN'T CHANGE.
[grunts]
THAT'S NEVER GONNA CHANGE.
[upbeat pop music]
*
SO WHAT ELSE?
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR DAY.
YOU WENT TO LUNCH.
- BREAKFAST.
ME AND DAD'S VERSION
OF BREAKFAST.
- HOW IS IT BREAKFAST
IF YOU DIDN'T EVEN WAKE UP
TILL 10:30?
- IT'S OUR BREAKFAST.
LOS ANGELES BREAKFAST.
TALKED ABOUT HIS HOT TUB
EXPERIENCE.
- YOUR DAD CRACKS ME UP.
WHEN HE HAS A FEW DRINKS,
HE FEELS LIKE
HE'S 25 AGAIN.
- YUCK.
EW!
- OH, MY [bleep].
- [laughs]
- DID YOU FEED HIM SOMETHING?
- I SWEAR TO GOD,
I DID NOT.
- BUBBA LOVEKINS HAD
A LITTLE ACCIDENT.
- THREE ACCIDENTS.
- THREE BIG ACCIDENTS,
ACTUALLY.
I NEVER SEE YOU GET SICK.
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT, BUB.
I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED, THOUGH?
[squish]
THAT IS THE--
OHHH!
- [laughing]
- YOU DID FEED HIM SOMETHING.
- I DID NOT!
I DIDN'T FEED HIM ANYTHING.
- OH, MY GOD,
I JUST STEPPED IN THAT.
HOW COME I DIDN'T HEAR THAT?
BUB, WHAT THE [bleep]
DID YOU EAT?
[crickets chirping]
- WE'RE DEFINITELY DOING
OUR TOUR TONIGHT
TO THE HOSPITAL?
- YES.
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD,
AS WE'RE DRIVING THERE,
WE PRETEND MY WATER BROKE
SO, LIKE,
WE KNOW, LIKE,
HOW LONG IT'LL TAKE?
LIKE A DRY RUN.
I DEFINITELY WANT JIONNI
TO GO THROUGH THE DRY RUN
JUST BECAUSE
HE'S THE ONE DRIVING.
HE NEEDS TO BE
IN CONTROL
WHILE I'M THE ONE,
YOU KNOW,
THAT'S FREAKING OUT.
I'M GONNA FINISH
GETTING READY,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU
WHEN I'M TESTING YOU.
- OKAY.
- DO SOMETHING.
MOP THE FLOOR OR SOMETHING.
I KIND OF WANT
TO CATCH HIM OFF GUARD
BECAUSE, LIKE, WE DON'T KNOW
WHEN IT'S GONNA HAPPEN,
SO I KIND OF WANT IT
TO BE LIKE,
YOU KNOW, IT'S REAL,
AND HE HAS NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON,
AND THEN IT JUST HAPPENS.
OH, [bleep],
MY WATER JUST BROKE!
[laughing]
OH, MY GOD.
JIONNI, I'M KIDDING.
- [laughs]
YOU HANDLED THAT VERY WELL.
- I KICKED YOU IN THE HEAD?
- YEAH.
DO YOU HAVE TO SHOWER?
- NO.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I WANT TO FREAK JIONNI OUT
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE
ON THIS DRY RUN...
[screaming]
- SHH!
- JUST BECAUSE I KNOW
I'M GONNA BE
LIKE A CRAZY PERSON
WHEN MY WATER DOES BREAK.
IT HURTS!
- [bleep].
- PUTTING MY TIMER ON.
GO!
SERIOUSLY, OKAY? DO IT.
BABY'S GONNA POP OUT.
OKAY, WE'RE LOSING
PRECIOUS MOMENTS RIGHT NOW.
IF THERE'S TRAFFIC
LIKE THIS,
I'M GONNA SHOOT EVERYONE
IN THE FACE.
- I'M CALLING JENNI.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
[honks horn]
[both laughing]
- [kissing]
GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT, BOOGER.
I TRIED IT.
IT'S BROKEN.
- OH.
[line ringing]
- JENNI, HELP ME NOW!
[laughter]
- WHAT? ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- NICOLE'S WATER JUST BROKE.
WHAT DO WE DO?
- HE'S [bleep] WITH YOU.
HE'S LYING.
- OW!
- HE'S LYING.
- ARE YOU LYING TO ME?
- ROGER, JENNI, TELL ME,
WHAT DO I DO?
- OW!
- [laughing]
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU'RE THE MAN
THAT GOT HER PREGNATED.
- I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
[both laughing]
- YOU'RE THE WORST [bleep] LIARS
KNOWN TO HUMAN MANKIND.
- BYE-BYE.
- BYE. SEE YOU LATER.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
- IF JENNI, ON THE REAL DAY,
ANSWERS THE WAY SHE DID
JUST NOW,
I'M GONNA PUNCH HER
IN THE FACE.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE THE HOSPITAL
IS, OR ARE YOU JUST DRIVING?
I DON'T SEE ANY SIGN
FOR A HOSPITAL.
- [gasps shakily]
- WHAT?
- WAS I SUPPOSED TO TURN?
- OH, [bleep].
- I'M LOST ON A DRY RUN
TO A PLACE FOUR MILES AWAY.
WHO GETS LOST TO A PLACE
YOU'VE BEEN TO 500 TIMES?
- WE'RE ON JFK PARKWAY.
- [gasps]
NO, WE'RE NOT.
- YEAH, WE ARE.
THIS IS NOT ACCEPTABLE, JIONNI.
[coughs]
I JUST PEED MY PANTS.
- FOR REAL?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S YOUR WATER RIGHT THERE.
- [coughing and laughing]
I JUST PEED.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- I SWEAR.
- CHECK IT, CHECK IT.
- NO, IT'S PEE.
- BABE--
- I KNOW IT IS.
- BABE, BABE--
- IT'S PEE!
I ENDED UP TINKLING MYSELF.
- EW!
- BUT IT'S NORMAL,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
PREGNANT.
- WHAT IF I FAINT LIKE THAT
WHEN YOU TELL ME?
- YOU CAN'T.
I'LL BE LOST WITHOUT YOU.
- YOU WERE LOST WITH ME.
- STUPID.
CAN YOU STILL
WHEELCHAIR ME OUT?
- OF COURSE I WILL.
- GOING INTO THE DRY RUN,
I THOUGHT IT WAS JUST GONNA BE
A WASTE OF TIME,
LIKE WHATEVER.
BUT ACTUALLY, DOING IT,
WE LEARNED A LOT.
- THERE'S A LOT
TO LEARN, BABY.
- AND WE JUST NEED TO BE
MORE, LIKE, FOCUSED.
- TOOK US SEVEN MINUTES
TO GET HOME.
HOW LONG DID IT TAKE US
TO GET THERE?
- 25 MINUTES AND 8 SECONDS.
SO WE DEFINITELY [bleep] UP
WITH GETTING THERE,
BUT COMING BACK, NOW WE KNOW
THAT IT'S NOT THAT FAR,
AND WE SHOULD GET THERE
IN TIME WHERE, YOU KNOW,
NOTHING WILL GO WRONG.
IF WE DO IT RIGHT.
- WHY IS OUR FRONT DOOR OPEN?
- JIONNI, YOU LEFT
THE DOOR OPEN.
- WHAT?
- ASS[bleep].
[breathing rhythmically]
- EW.
- LAMAZE BREATHING
IS JUST SO STUPID.
IT'S LIKE...
[inhales, exhales]
LIKE, WHO BREATHES LIKE THAT?
I CAN'T BREATHE.
- JUST PICTURE THE BELLY
NOT THERE.
- I KNOW.
- OH, YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW
IT WORKS.
LIKE, WHEN YOU HAVE A BABY,
DOES IT GO DOWN AGAIN?
- I LOVE IT.
THAT'S GOTTA BE IT.
- WHAT IF I HAVE HIM
AND I STILL LOOK LIKE THIS?
- YOU'RE NOT.
- I'LL BE SO PISSED.
- HI.
- I WANT BREAKFAST.
- BREAKFAST. HERE.
- OH, MY GOD,
MY STOMACH HURTS SO BAD.
[huffing and puffing]
- SHOULD I CALL BELLINI
NOW TOO?
- IF YOU WANT.
- RIGHT NOW, OUR NURSERY
IS JUST AN EMPTY ROOM.
NEED TO START, YOU KNOW,
GETTING THIS NURSERY READY.
NICOLE COULD GO ANY TIME NOW.
[line ringing]
- BELLINI. MAY I HELP YOU?
- HI, IS DANIELLE IN?
- UH, DANIELLE.
THERE'S NO DANIELLE HERE.
- OH, MY GOD,
IT'S NOT HER NAME.
- UH, MICHELLE?
- NO.
- IS THIS BELLINI?
- YES, IT IS.
- HI, THIS IS JIONNI LAVALLE.
UM--
- WE ORDERED FURNITURE.
- I WAS JUST, UH, CONFIRMING,
YOU KNOW,
UH, THE PROGRESS
ON OUR FURNITURE.
UM, YOU KNOW,
LIKE A ROUGH ESTIMATE
OF WHEN IT WOULD BE DELIVERED.
- UM, THAT SHOULD BE...
APPROXIMATELY THURSDAY,
THE 30th.
- SOUNDS GOOD.
AND, UM--
- THAT'S LIKE
FIVE YEARS FROM NOW.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT THESE PEOPLE
ARE DOING RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, ARE THEY MAKING IT
FROM SCRATCH?
JUST BECAUSE WE LEGIT ORDERED
THIS FURNITURE
LIKE A YEAR AGO,
AND IT'S TAKING FOREVER
TO GET HERE.
- YOU HAVE THE CRIB...
THE MATTRESS...
THE 58-INCH DRESSER...
THE SLIDE TOP,
AND THE ARMOIRE.
SO IT'S ONE...
- WHAT THE [bleep]'S
AN ARMOIRE?
- TWO...
- "ARM-WAR"?
- "ARE-MORE".
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IT IS.
- AS LONG AS IT'S COMING,
IT'S WHATEVER.
- OKAY.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- HAVE A GREAT DAY.
- YOU TOO. BYE.
- I'M READY.
- ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
- SO TONIGHT I HAVE
A LAMAZE CLASS.
I FEEL LIKE THIS CLASS
MIGHT BE A WASTE OF TIME,
BUT ALSO, WE MIGHT ACTUALLY
LEARN SOMETHING.
[breathing rhythmically]
- EW. PLEASE DO THAT
DURING THE CLASS TONIGHT.
- [laughs]
- I'LL BEG YOU.
- WHEN WE GET
TO LAMAZE CLASS,
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING
IT'S GONNA BE PACKED,
THIS IS GONNA BE LIKE
A CLASSROOM,
AND THERE'S ONLY
ONE COUPLE THERE.
I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY,
A LOT OF PEOPLE
DON'T DO LAMAZE,
BECAUSE NO ONE'S THERE.
- WELCOME, AND CONGRATULATIONS
ON HAVING YOUR FIRST BABIES.
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF BREATHING
I WANTED TO TALK ABOUT,
AT THE START AND END
OF EVERY CONTRACTION,
WHAT WE DO IS SOMETHING CALLED
THE CLEANSING BREATH.
THE CLEANSING BREATH
IS LIKE THIS.
[inhales]
AND OUT.
[exhales]
EVERYBODY WANT TO DO IT
WITH ME?
[all inhale, exhale]
- LAMAZE BREATHING
IS JUST SO STUPID.
YOU HAVE TO, LIKE,
BREATHE FOR FOUR COUNTS,
SO IT'S LIKE...
[inhales, exhales]
LIKE, WHO BREATHES LIKE THAT?
I'M NOT GONNA BREATHE
LIKE THAT.
I'M GONNA BE FREAKING OUT
WHEN I PUSH.
I'M NOT GONNA BE BREATHING
LIKE THAT.
I KNOW IT.
- IF YOU CHOOSE TO GET
AN EPIDURAL,
YOU'RE NUMB FROM HERE DOWN.
THEY'LL TAPE IT UP HERE--
YES?
- I READ STORIES WHERE
THEY GIVE YOU THE EPIDURAL,
BUT THEY MISS IT,
AND THEN YOU'RE NUMB UP.
- NUMB UP?
- YEAH, INSTEAD OF DOWN.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN THAT HAPPEN.
- REALLY?
- SOMEWHERE IN THE WORLD,
I'M SURE IT HAS.
I'VE NEVER--
- I READ IT ON GOOGLE.
I'VE USED GOOGLE A LOT
TO, LIKE, GOOGLE MY QUESTIONS.
LIKE, IT'S SCARY.
LIKE, YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
- POSITIONING FOR LABOR
IS ANYTHING
THAT YOU'RE COMFORTABLE WITH.
STANDING, KNEELING, SITTING...
- [whispers]
IS SHE, LIKE, POOPING?
- ALSO INDUCTION...
- [whispers]
THAT LOOKS NOTHING LIKE POOPING.
- IT IS SO AMAZING HOW...
WHEN YOU FIRST COME IN,
YOU'RE GONNA BE CHECKED,
AND YOUR DOCTOR OR NURSE--
YOU OKAY?
- [laughing]
CAN'T BREATHE.
OH, I'M GIGGLY TODAY.
- THE COUPLE NEXT TO US
RIGHT NOW
ARE TRYING TO LEARN LAMAZE,
AND NICOLE AND I
ARE LIKE JACKASSES,
LAUGHING, RUINING
THIS ENTIRE CLASS.
- IN THE EARLY PHASE OF LABOR,
YOU WANT TO STAY HOME
AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
- [giggling]
- YOU CAN ACTUALLY SHOWER--
YOU CAN ACTUALLY SHOWER
IF YOUR WATER BROKE.
UH, BUT YOU CANNOT TAKE
A BATH.
- I THINK THE OTHER COUPLE
THINKS, YOU KNOW,
ME AND JIONNI
ARE JUST LITTLE KIDS,
AND WE'RE IMMATURE.
WE WERE LAUGHING
THE WHOLE TIME.
- GOOD LUCK.
- GOOD LUCK. SEE YOU LATER.
- SEE YA. GOOD LUCK.
- BUT, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE JUST GONNA BE FUN PARENTS.
SORRY THAT YOU'RE LAME.
- YOU SAID,
"I LIKE THAT POSE.
IT LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S POOPING."
- [laughing]
I KNOW.
- AND SHE WAS BENT OVER
ON ALL FOURS.
WHO POOPS ON ALL FOURS?
- UGH.
THIS IS SO GROSS.
THERE'S, LIKE,
[bleep] COMING OUT OF ME.
IT LOOKS LIKE
A BIG MUCUS BALL.
BABE!
I'M SCARED.
- WHAT?
- I THINK MY WATER BROKE.
- * HOLD ON, HERE WE GO
- NOW WE JUST GOTTA LOOK
FOR MANDEE'S, DUDE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE IT IS.
- TODAY ME AND JENNI,
WE'RE GONNA GO SHOPPING,
BECAUSE I NEED AN OUTFIT
FOR THE HOSPITAL.
- OH, YEAH, THERE IT IS.
- AND RIGHT NOW,
I JUST NEED MY BEST FRIEND
BECAUSE I FEEL GROSS,
AND I FEEL LIKE
I JUST NEED GIRL TIME.
OOH! THIS IS
A REALLY NICE MANDEE'S.
- THIS IS ACTUALLY GOOD,
'CAUSE I NEED TO GO SHOPPING
FOR MAINE.
- UGH, I HATE BEING PREGNANT.
- AH, YOU'RE GONNA GIVE BIRTH
IN, LIKE, A COUPLE WEEKS.
- LOOK AT ALL THESE CLOTHES
I COULD BE WEARING.
[sighs]
I'M IN SO MUCH PAIN.
- I HATE SEEING NICOLE
SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
I WOULD JUST BE UP AND LAYING
IN BED ALL THE TIME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE'S DOING
WHAT SHE'S DOING.
- ME NEITHER.
- [laughs]
WHAT ABOUT THIS GUY?
- THAT'S REALLY PRETTY.
TRY THEM BOTH ON.
- I DON'T WANT TO--
DO I HAVE TO TRY IT ON?
- MM-HMM.
- UGH.
I HATE YOU.
SO I'M TRYING ON
THIS LEOPARD DRESS
THAT I MIGHT WEAR
TO LEAVE THE HOSPITAL.
I CAN'T BREATHE.
- YEAH, BUT IT'S--
JUST PICTURE THE BELLY
NOT THERE.
- I KNOW.
- OH, YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW IT WORKS.
LIKE, WHEN YOU HAVE A BABY,
DOES IT GO DOWN AGAIN?
- YOU'LL AT LEAST LOSE
6 TO 8 POUNDS
BECAUSE OF THE BABY
AND PLACENTA.
- I JUST DEFINITELY HOPE
THAT THESE DRESSES
THAT I'M TRYING ON FIT.
I DON'T LIKE THAT FACE.
- I LOVE IT!
THAT'S GOTTA BE IT.
IF YOU WEREN'T GETTING IT,
I WOULD.
- WHAT IF I HAVE HIM
AND I STILL LOOK LIKE THIS?
- YOU'RE NOT.
- I'LL BE SO PISSED.
- [laughs]
[rustling]
- OOH.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
I AM IN SO MUCH PAIN
RIGHT NOW.
AS I'M CHANGING CLOTHES,
MY STOMACH STARTS
TO HURT.
I'M GETTING CRAMPS AGAIN.
I'M LIKE, "OH, [bleep]."
LIKE, I STILL HAVE TO DRIVE
LIKE TWO HOURS HOME.
WHAT IF I HAVE THIS BABY
IN THE CAR?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- THE NEXT PLACE
IS AN HOUR AND HALF AWAY.
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
- NO.
- I'M JUST SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
THANK YOU.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
- I KNOW.
- SO I FEEL REALLY BAD
BECAUSE I KNOW JENNI
REALLY WANTS TO GO
WEDDING DRESS SHOPPING,
BUT I HONESTLY CAN'T GO.
I HAVE NO ENERGY,
MY STOMACH HURTS,
AND I JUST NEED
TO GET HOME AND REST
BECAUSE I JUST
DON'T FEEL RIGHT.
I HAD A BREAKDOWN
ON SUNDAY.
- WHY?
- I'M OVERWHELMED.
I'M TIRED OF BEING PREGNANT.
IT'S MISERABLE.
JIONNI'S FAMILY WAS OVER,
LIKE 20 PEOPLE.
AND THEN--
- DID YOU START CRYING?
- I JUST WANTED TO BE ALONE.
- YEAH.
- I RAN DOWNSTAIRS
AND CRIED LIKE A TWO-YEAR-OLD.
- AWW.
- I CAN'T MOVE.
I CAN'T DO [bleep].
- DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
I KNOW IT SEEMS
LIKE FOREVER, BUT--
- THIS LAST MONTH
IS KILLING ME.
- UGH, I'M SORRY
TO HEAR THAT.
AT LEAST YOU HAVE
THE PREGNANT EXCUSE.
DON'T KNOW WHAT THE [bleep]
IS WRONG WITH ME.
- I THINK YOU'RE MENOPAUSING.
- [laughs] THANKS.
- IT'S JUST NICE
TO HAVE JENNI THERE
LISTENING TO ME
AND LETTING ME KNOW
THAT I'M GONNA BE OKAY
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I NEED THAT RIGHT NOW.
I NEED MY BEST FRIEND.
[crickets chirping]
POOP!
OH, I'M SO TIRED.
- HEY, BABE.
- I'M SO TIRED.
MY STOMACH IS KILLING ME.
- WANT SOME ICED TEA?
I GOT AN ARNOLD PALMER.
- UGH.
[groans]
[suspenseful music]
*
UGH.
THIS IS SO GROSS.
SO I WAKE UP,
AND I REALIZE
THERE'S, LIKE,
[bleep] COMING OUT OF ME.
IT'S, LIKE,
REALLY DISGUSTING.
IT LOOKS LIKE
A BIG MUCUS BALL,
AND THEN WATER IS COMING OUT.
BABE!
- WHAT?
- SOMETHING'S COMING OUT.
*
I'M SCARED.
- WHAT?
- I THINK MY WATER BROKE.
HEY, BOO.
- HEY, GOOD MORNING.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING,
JUST GOING TO THE GYM.
YOU SOUND TIRED.
- MY WATER BROKE.
- WHAT? YOU'RE LYING.
- I SWEAR TO GOD.
- RIGHT NOW,
YOU'VE BROKE YOUR WATER.
ALL RIGHT, BUT NOW YOU JUST NEED
SOME STRONGER CONTRACTIONS.
- DO YOU THINK
IT'LL TAKE A WHILE?
- YEAH, THIS COULD BE
ANOTHER 24 HOURS.
- I'M TRYING TO KEEP CALM
AND, LIKE,
THINK HAPPY THOUGHTS.
BUT IN THE BACK OF MY HEAD,
I'M HONESTLY TERRIFIED.
- BABE!
BABE!
- WHAT?
- I'M SCARED.
- I THINK MY WATER BROKE.
- THAT JUST CAME OUT?
- IT'S LIKE MUCUS.
- AND I SEE, IN HER HAND,
HER MUCUS PLUG
FELL OUT OF HER VAGINA.
- IT'S MUCUS.
- [bleep].
I'M NOT READY FOR THIS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
SHE SAYS SHE'S
SOMEWHAT LEAKING.
IF THE WATER BREAKS, I HEARD
IT KIND OF LIKE POURS OUT.
SO WE'RE BOTH
KIND OF CONFUSED.
- OH, MY GOD, IT'S COMING OUT.
- BREATHE, BREATHE, BREATHE.
[exhales]
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR...
- I HAVE TISSUE
IN MY CROTCH RIGHT NOW.
- BREATHE.
IT COULD BE YOUR--
YOUR--YOUR...
WATER BREAKING.
- HOLD ME.
- OH, [bleep].
I'M NOT READY FOR THIS.
- MY DUE DATE'S
NOT FOR TWO MORE WEEKS.
WE STILL DON'T HAVE
OUR FURNITURE.
I'M, LIKE, FREAKING OUT
BECAUSE I'M THINKING,
OKAY, MAYBE I'M, LIKE,
GOING INTO LABOR RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, CALL A DOCTOR
BECAUSE I'M SCARED.
- HELLO?
- HEY, DR. RUSSO.
SHE JUST STARTED LEAKING,
AND SHE WENT TO THE BATHROOM
AND, LIKE, WIPED IT,
AND IT WAS, LIKE,
PURE MUCUS.
- THE MUCUS PLUG IS SOMETHING
THAT MAY COME OUT,
YOU KNOW, PRIOR TO HER GOING
INTO LABOR.
UH, DOES SHE HAVE
ANY LABOR PAINS AT ALL, OR NO?
- IT'S JUST TIGHTENING
A LITTLE BIT.
- NO, JUST TIGHTENING UP
- OKAY, SO THEN CALL ME BACK
ONCE HER LABOR PAINS
START COMING ABOUT EVERY
FIVE MINUTES APART,
SO ABOUT AN HOUR OR SO,
OR IF SHE BREAKS WATER,
A LOT OF FLUID
STARTS COMING OUT.
- I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S HAPPENING.
I'M NOT SURE IF WE'RE
HAVING THIS BABY TONIGHT.
NICOLE'S JUST LEAKING.
THE MUCUS PLUG FELL OUT.
WE'RE JUST ALL [bleep]ED UP.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S STILL COMING OUT.
- BETTER BRING ME SOME XANAX
TO THE HOSPITAL.
- WILL YOU SHUT UP?
SERIOUSLY.
- COME ON.
- YOU WANT TO GO UPSTAIRS
IN THE TUB?
- CAN'T GO IN THE BATHTUB.
- IT MIGHT DROWN HIM.
- YEAH.
JESUS.
- [snickers]
UGH, [bleep].
- JUST THINK,
A FEW MORE HOURS...
OUR SON'S GONNA BE HERE.
IT'S BEEN HOURS RIGHT NOW.
IT'S BEEN HOURS AND HOURS.
SHE'S STILL IN PAIN,
AND SHE'S STILL LEAKING.
I-I THINK THIS IS IT.
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- HEY, DOC, NICOLE'S PAIN
IS STILL THERE.
UM, WE'RE TIMING IT.
IT IS EVERY FIVE
TO SEVEN MINUTES.
SHE STILL WAS LEAKING.
- SOUNDS LIKE THIS IS THE--
THIS IS THE REAL THING.
WHY DON'T WE MEET
OVER AT THE OFFICE?
- OKAY, SOUNDS GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT, JIONNI.
- ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, BYE.
- I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M PREPARED.
LIKE, I THOUGHT I WAS, LIKE,
GONNA HAVE TWO MORE WEEKS.
THIS IS NOT WHAT I EXPECTED.
YOU READY FOR THIS?
- NO, I'M NOT READY.
- ME EITHER.
- BUT WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
WE'RE GONNA DO IT
TOGETHER.
[ethereal music]
*
- * I CAN FEEL IT
- BYE, HONEY. GOOD LUCK.
- * CLOSER THAN BEFORE
* IT'S TOO LATE TO STOP
* WHAT CALLS FOR CHANGE
- HELLO.
- THANK GOD MY PARENTS
GOT HERE IN TIME,
SO THEY'RE NOT GONNA MISS
ANYTHING,
AND THEY'RE GONNA BE HERE
FOR ME, YOU KNOW,
THROUGH THE LABOR
AND EVERYTHING.
SO, YOU KNOW,
IT'S GO TIME.
- ALL RIGHT, WE'LL BE
RIGHT BEHIND YOU, HONEY.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ARE YOU--YOU SHIVERING?
- I SHIVER WHEN I GET NERVOUS.
I'M NOT COLD.
- OKAY, WELL, YOU GOTTA RELAX
A LITTLE BIT.
TRY TO BREATHE.
- OH, [bleep],
WHERE'S THAT TOWEL?
OH, MY GOD,
IT'S REALLY COMING OUT.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
JUST DON'T GET NERVOUS.
- I NEED TO CLEAN MYSELF UP.
[suspenseful music]
*
UGH.
CAN'T WALK.
OH, MY GOD,
I'M HURTING SO BAD.
HELP ME.
[laughter]
I JUST LEAKED EVERYWHERE.
I'M REALLY SCARED TO DEATH
RIGHT NOW.
I WANT TO GO
STRAIGHT TO THE HOSPITAL
BECAUSE THESE CRAMPS
ARE KILLING ME.
- YOU STILL ABLE TO TIME THEM
A LITTLE BIT?
- LIKE FIVE TO SEVEN.
IT VARIES.
IT'S WEIRD.
- YOUR WATER IS BROKEN,
SO THIS IS THE GAME PLAN.
RIGHT NOW SHE'S 1 CENTIMETER.
I JUST CALLED OVER
TO THE HOSPITAL,
AND THEY'RE PRETTY PACKED
OVER THERE.
THEY HAVE ONE ROOM RESERVED,
SO HOPEFULLY THEY'LL GET
A COUPLE PEOPLE DELIVERED
BY THE TIME YOU GO OVER THERE,
BUT YOU'RE STILL EARLY
IN THE PROCESS.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE ANYWHERE
NEAR GETTING
AN EPIDURAL JUST YET.
NOW, LET ME JUST DO
AN EXAM FIRST.
- YEAH.
- SO YOU GUYS STEP OUT.
- I JUST LEAKED NOW,
SO YOU'RE GONNA SEE GROSSNESS.
- OKAY.
- ALL I WANT TO DO
IS HAVE THIS BABY.
I'M TRYING TO KEEP CALM
AND, LIKE,
THINK HAPPY THOUGHTS.
BUT IN THE BACK OF MY HEAD,
I'M HONESTLY TERRIFIED.
- YOU ALL RIGHT? LET'S GO.
- [crying]
- SIT DOWN THERE.
- I'M SO SCARED.
- DON'T WORRY, BABE.
I PROMISE I'M HERE, OKAY?
THIS IS IT.
- OKAY, WE'RE GOOD.
- THIS IS IT, LORENZO.
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
[laughter]
OH, [bleep].
THIS IS, LIKE,
THE SCARY PART,
WHERE THEY START PUTTING
I.V.s IN YOU,
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
SO I'M VERY, VERY SCARED,
BUT I'M VERY RELIEVED
TO BE AT THE HOSPITAL.
- HOW YOU FEELING?
- I'M SCARED.
- ALL RIGHT,
THIS IS THE GAME PLAN.
I MEAN, YOU COULD WALK AROUND
AT HOME,
WALK YOURSELF INTO LABOR.
OTHERWISE, WE COULD HAVE YOU GO
TO THE HOSPITAL.
RIGHT NOW,
SHE'S 1 CENTIMETER.
BUT YOU'RE STILL EARLY
IN THE PROCESS.
THIS COULD BE
ANOTHER 24 HOURS, OKAY?
- I DO NOT WANT TO BE IN LABOR
FOR MORE THAN, LIKE,
A DAY,
BECAUSE I'LL FREAK OUT.
LIKE, I CAN'T DEAL
WITH THIS [bleep].
- YOU KNOW, MOST OFTEN,
WHEN YOU GO INTO LABOR,
YOU BREAK YOUR WATER, YOU START
TO CONTRACT RIGHT AWAY.
YOU START TO DILATE.
RIGHT NOW,
YOU BROKE YOUR WATER,
BUT NOW YOU NEED--JUST NEED
SOME STRONGER CONTRACTIONS--
- DO YOU THINK
IT'LL TAKE A WHILE?
- YEAH.
- I WANT THIS TO BE
AS COMFORTABLE FOR NICOLE.
WE'LL JUST GO
BACK TO THE HOUSE,
WAIT IT OUT A LITTLE BIT,
AND SEE WHAT WE CAN DO,
AND THEN WE'LL GO
TO THE HOSPITAL.
- IT'S GONNA BE
A LONG DAY.
GONNA BE IN LABOR
FOR LIKE 24 HOURS.
THIS IS BULL[bleep].
- FALSE ALARM.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
FALSE ALARM MY ASS.
OUCH.
LORENZO'S DEFINITELY
PISSING ME OFF.
I FIGURED HE WOULD WANT
TO COME OUT AND MEET ME,
BUT HE'S STILL, LIKE,
CHILLING IN MY WOMB,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY
HE DOESN'T WANT TO COME OUT.
I'M GONNA CALL JENNI.
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- HEY, BOO.
- HEY, GOOD MORNING.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING,
JUST GOT TO THE GYM.
YOU SOUND TIRED.
- MY WATER BROKE.
- WHAT? YOU'RE LYING.
- I SWEAR TO GOD.
BUT I'M STILL 1 CENTIMETER,
BUT I HAVE CONTRACTIONS,
AND THEY HURT LIKE A BITCH,
AND I'M PROBABLY GONNA GO
TO THE HOSPITAL
IN, LIKE,
A COUPLE HOURS AND...
- GET OUTTA HERE.
- DELIVER THIS BABY.
- HOLY [bleep].
- OH, I'M, LIKE,
IN TEARS RIGHT NOW.
[laughs]
- YEAH.
- I'M SO EXCITED.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
I'M EXCITED FOR YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL TEXT YOU
IN A LITTLE BIT.
- LOVE YOU.
I'M SO EXCITED.
- DON'T POOP.
- LOVE YOU, BYE.
IDIOT.
- BYE.
- THAT IS CRAZY.
THAT'S EARLY.
- C-SECTION.
- SO YOU WANNA JUST SAY
SCREW THE GYM
AND GO GET READY?
- OKAY, LET'S GO.
- SHE'S GONNA POOP, THOUGH.
I KNOW IT.
- [laughing]
STOP.
I'M SO EXCITED
FOR NICOLE RIGHT NOW.
SO ALL I WANT TO DO
IS GET UP THERE.
I WANT TO GET EVERYTHING THAT
WE NEED AND GET ON THE ROAD
TO EAST HANOVER.
- UGH.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW
SHE'S NOT SWINGING AND PUNCHING
EVERYBODY RIGHT NOW.
[laughs]
- MOM, SHUT UP.
- THE WAITING GAME.
- YEP.
- I HAVE TO POOP.
- OH.
- MAKE SURE
THAT'S ALL YOU DO.
[laughs]
- DON'T PUSH TOO HARD.
- EW.
- [laughs]
- YOUR MOTHER AND I
ARE GONNA START DRINKING
HERE PRETTY SOON.
- ME AND YOU BOTH, PAL.
IT'S ALL DOWNHILL
FROM HERE.
- I'M GONNA PICK UP
A BASSINETTE
AND A DIAPER CHANGER
FOR HER.
- AND YOU WANT TO STOP
AND GET CIGARS,
YOU WANT TO STOP
AND GET SWEET FRUIT,
AND YOU WANT A TWO-HOUR RIDE
UP THERE.
PHEW. AWESOME. OKAY.
- WE'RE GONNA GRAB IT.
IT'LL TAKE ME TWO SECONDS
TO RUN IN THERE.
I'M GONNA GRAB
A DIAPER CHANGER.
A BASSINETTE.
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO GO GET SWEETS.
- WE'RE FINE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- SO--
- IF WE'RE NOT FINE,
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ANY BITCHING.
WHATEVER YOU WOULD LIKE.
- THANK YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR.
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- HEY, DOC, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HOW'S SHE DOING?
- GOOD.
- SAME THING, JUST, YOU KNOW,
EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
PAIN'S ABOUT THE SAME.
- YOU GUYS WANT
TO SHOOT OVER?
YOU KNOW, IF SHE'S STILL NOT
DILATED THAT MUCH,
WE'LL PROBABLY DO
THAT BALLOON THING.
- SO DR. RUSSO IS SAYING
HE MIGHT HAVE TO INDUCE ME.
SO BASICALLY, HE MIGHT HAVE
TO PUT A BALLOON
IN MY CERVIX TO EXPAND IT
SO THE BABY CAN COME OUT.
I'M HOPING IT'S NOT, LIKE,
A HUGE, LIKE,
BIRTHDAY PARTY BALLOON.
- IF SHE GETS UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH THAT,
SHE CAN GET HER EPIDURAL.
I'M HERE RIGHT NOW, SO YOU GUYS
CAN COME ON OVER, OKAY?
- AWESOME. THANKS, DR. RUSSO.
I APPRECIATE IT.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I'LL TALK TO YOU SOON.
- ALL RIGHT, BYE.
- BYE-BYE.
- HERE WE GO.
THIS IS IT.
MY BABY'S COMING TONIGHT.
- GIVE ME A HUG...
- WE'RE ALL HERE.
- BEFORE I BECOME GRANDMA,
AND I'M NOT JUST MOMMY.
- I'M EXCITED,
BUT I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
AND--PFFT.
IT'S NERVE-RACKING.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS SOON.
- ALL RIGHT.
- BYE.
- GOOD LUCK.
WE'LL SEE YOUSE THERE.
- * CAN'T IGNORE IT
* IT'S UNDERNEATH YOUR SKIN
* IT'S NOT THE END
* THIS IS WHERE WE BEGIN
- JUST IMAGINE,
OUR KID IS GONNA BE OUT
BY TONIGHT.
- HOPEFULLY.
- HE'LL BE OUT.
- THEN WHAT?
WE JUST GO HOME AND, LIKE,
TAKE CARE OF HIM?
- THAT'S IT.
THEN HE'S OURS.
- * WE CAN'T LOSE
- LET'S DO THIS.
IT'S LIKE WE'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT
FOR MONTHS AND MONTHS
AND MONTHS.
NOW'S THE TIME.
LIKE, IT'S REALLY HAPPENING.
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK.
IT'S HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS IT.
- OKAY.
- THIS IS IT, LORENZO.
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
[laughter]
OH, [bleep].
THIS IS, LIKE,
THE SCARY PART,
WHERE THEY START PUTTING
I.V.s IN YOU.
SO I'M VERY, VERY SCARED,
BUT I'M VERY RELIEVED
TO BE AT THE HOSPITAL.
- HOW YOU FEELING?
ALMOST TIME
FOR THE EPIDURAL.
- I'M SCARED.
- AND THEN OUR SON COMES.
- CAN I SEE THIS?
- WHY?
- LET ME SEE IT.
HI, DAD.
- HI, BUDDY.
- SAY SOMETHING TO HIM.
- I SAID, "HI, BUDDY."
- THAT'S IT?
- I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU.
MOMMY'S DOING GOOD.
- MOMMY HURTS. OUCH.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I'M SCARED.
- THIS DOOR?
- YEAH.
[knock at door]
- HI.
- BOO-BOO.
- AW.
- THANKS FOR COMING, PAL.
- YEAH, MAN.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- OKAY.
- YOUR MAKEUP'S BEAUTIFUL.
THE FIRST THING I NOTICE
IS HOW GLAMORIZED
NICOLE LOOKS.
- I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
- SHE'S IN A LEOPARD GOWN.
HER HAIR AND MAKEUP'S DONE.
I'M LIKE, WHAT, ARE YOU
GOING OUT TO DINNER?
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY
FOR ABOUT TO GIVE BIRTH.
- YOU DO.
I WAS THINKING--
- LIKE--
- YOU LOOK LIKE A MILLION BUCKS.
- GOOD, THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
TO FEEL, TO LOOK LIKE.
- [laughing]
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- SHE DIDN'T POOP YET.
- YOU'RE GONNA POOP,
JUST FOR THE RECORD.
[grunts]
YOU READY FOR THIS, BUDDY?
- OH, YEAH.
- THIS IS CRAZY.
- CAN'T WAIT.
- THIS IS EARLY.
- THIS IS IT.
- THERE'S NO TURNING BACK NOW.
[laughs]
- NO. NO.
- THERE'S A BALLOON
IN MY VAGINA.
- [laughs]
- YOU'VE HAD STRANGER THINGS
IN YOUR VAGINA.
- YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
- [laughs]
YOU GUYS WANT US
TO LEAVE YOU BE, OR--
- YEAH, WE'LL GO OUT
FOR A COUPLE HOURS.
- YEAH.
- GO, UH--
YEAH, GO OUTSIDE.
HANG OUT.
I'LL CALL MY DAD TO TELL HIM
YOU'RE COMING.
- OKAY. COOL, COOL.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THANKS FOR COMING.
- THANK YOU.
- ABSOLUTELY, BRO.
WE'LL GIVE YOU GUYS
SOME PRIVACY.
- APPRECIATE IT.
- I'M NOT GONNA HAVE
LORENZO FOR A WHILE,
SO JUST GO TO
OUR MAN-CAVE/NURSERY
AND JUST CHILL OUT
AND, YOU KNOW,
TAKE A NAP OR SOMETHING.
I'M OVERWHELMED.
- I KNOW.
YOU SHOULD BE.
- THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF
GOING ON.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY...
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- ME AND ROGER GOT NICOLE
A BASSINETTE FOR LORENZO
AND A CHANGING TABLE.
THE LEAST I CAN DO IS PUT
A LITTLE THINGS TOGETHER
TO HELP NICOLE
UNTIL HER OTHER FURNITURE COMES.
- HEY, THERE HE IS.
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW YOU DOING?
- WE BOUGHT, UM,
A CRIB AND A DIAPER CHANGE
TEMPORARILY
FOR HER TO HAVE DOWN THERE
FOR WHEN THEY GET HOME.
- THE CRIB IS COMING.
- OH, I KNOW.
THIS ONE'S FOR THURSDAY.
- YEAH, BUT--
- BUT IT'S A SURPRISE FOR THEM.
- GOOD LUCK. GO AHEAD.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
- THERE YOU GO.
- YOU COULD PUT IT UP,
BUT THEN YOU COULD
TAKE IT DOWN.
- JANIS IS DEFINITELY
A LITTLE SAUCY RIGHT NOW,
BUT THE BABY ROOM YOU CREATED
IS TWO FLOORS UP.
I CANNOT IMAGINE NICOLE
GOING TWO FLOORS
TO CHANGE LORENZO
FOR THE NEXT WEEK.
I'M [bleep] SETTING IT UP.
- WHY DO I GET ROPED
INTO THIS [bleep]?
- [grunts]
[sighs]
WHOA, IF YOU'RE
AT ALL ANNOYED,
I WILL DO THIS MYSELF.
- YOU WON'T DO IT YOURSELF,
'CAUSE YOU COULDN'T DO IT
YOURSELF, AND YOU KNOW--
- I DO ALL THE PROJECTS
IN OUR HOUSE,
ALL THE THINGS BUILDING.
I BUILD ALL THE TIME
IN OUR HOUSE.
- I'M NOT GONNA LIE.
I CAN BE GRUMPY AT TIMES,
YOU KNOW.
ESPECIALLY IF I'M HUNGRY.
UH, OR AWAKE AT ALL.
- IT'S BEEN ABOUT 24 HOURS NOW
SINCE NICOLE'S BEEN IN LABOR,
AND I JUST WANNA [bleep]
MEET LORENZO AT THIS POINT.
- I THINK I HAVE TO POOP.
- OH, GOD.
- THAT MIGHT BE
A CONTRACTION.
THAT MIGHT MEAN YOU'RE IN--
- EW, IT'S IN MY VAGINA.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
WHERE'S THAT BUTTON?
[beeping]
- OH, BOY.
SHE'S NUMBING IT.
- WHAT'S IN YOUR VAGINA?
- PAIN.
- IT JUST FEELS LIKE PRESSURE.
- SO THAT JUST NUMBED IT.
- THAT MIGHT NOT BE POOP.
THAT MIGHT BE THE BABY.
- I KNOW, THAT'S WHY
I JUST PUSHED THE BUTTON.
[laughter]
- YOU GETTING NERVOUS?
- NO.
- NO, SHE--
- PUSH HIM OUT.
LET'S GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
I WANT TO MEET HIM.
- I REALLY HAD TO TAKE
A HUGE [bleep].
- WOW.
- YEAH, LIKE, BIG.
- LIKE A 6.5-POUND [bleep].
- LIKE A [bleep]
THAT DOESN'T BREAK,
AND IT KEEPS TWIRLING.
- UGH.
- THAT TYPE OF [bleep].
- IT'S LIKE THE DAY AFTER
GOING OUT
TO THE CLUB TYPE OF [bleep].
- OH, YEAH,
AFTER-KARMA [bleep].
NOW, HOW AM I GONNA FEEL IT?
LIKE, WHAT'S IT GONNA FEEL LIKE
WITH THE EPIDURAL?
JUST SO I KNOW.
- YOU'RE GONNA FEEL PRESSURE,
LIKE YOU HAVE TO MOVE
YOUR BOWELS.
AND THEN THE BABY--
- SO WHEN HE'S COMING OUT,
LIKE,
DOES IT HURT,
OR IS IT MORE LIKE--
- UM--
- LIKE [bleep]?
- YOU'LL FEEL A STRETCH--
A STRETCHING.
- OH, [bleep].
I'M SCARED.
- DON'T BE.
YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT.
- I MIGHT POOP.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- OKAY.
[bleep], I'M NERVOUS.
- YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
- WE'RE STEPPING OUT.
- IT'S BEEN A LONG NIGHT
FOR EVERYBODY,
ESPECIALLY NICOLE,
AND THIS CHILDBIRTH
IS REALLY KIND OF GOING
INTO THE TENTH HOUR
AT THIS POINT.
AND WE'RE JUST KILLING TIME,
WAITING FOR THIS BABY
TO ARRIVE.
- MY BACK HURTS.
TAKE CARE OF ME.
STOP.
STOP. STOP MAKING ME
UNCOMFORTABLE.
- [laughing]
IT'S A LITTLE ODD
TO DO THIS IN A HOSPITAL,
BUT...
IF YOU'RE GAME, I'M GAME.
I'M GONNA KEEP
THE ROMANCE ALIVE.
HOW'S THAT NIPPLE DOING,
JUST HANGING OUT?
- WHICH ONE IS--
IT'S NOT HANGING OUT.
- [laughing]
YES, IT IS.
- WHY ARE YOU MAKING IT
AWKWARD FOR ME?
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST LOVE ME?
- [laughing and snorting]
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO ALWAYS
[bleep] WITH ME.
SOMETIMES I JUST NEED LOVE.
- I GIVE YOU LOVES, MONKEY.
I GIVE YOU LOVES.
[door creaks]
- HOW YOU DOING?
FEELING SOME PRESSURE?
- THINK I'M GONNA [bleep]
MY PANTS.
- OH, THAT'S NOT TOO GOOD.
OKAY.
- NO, LIKE, FOR REAL.
I DIDN'T GO TODAY.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- LET'S HOPE
IT'S THE BABY'S HEAD, OKAY?
- NO, IT'S, LIKE,
IN MY BUTT HOLE.
- WELL, THE BABY'S RIGHT ON TOP
OF THAT AREA.
- LIKE, NO ONE BELIEVES ME.
I REALLY HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM RIGHT NOW.
BUT DR. RUSSO SAYS
IT'S LORENZO
TRYING TO COME OUT,
BUT I--
IT'S IN MY BUTT.
LIKE, I KNOW IT'S GONNA BE
A TURD.
- WELL, YOU'RE ALMOST
FULLY DILATED.
- [groans]
I'M GONNA POOP, I SWEAR.
- THE BABY'S DOWN
MUCH LOWER NOW,
AND THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE FEELING.
- IT HURTS.
- OKAY?
SO YOU'RE ABOUT AT 9,
9 1/2 CENTIMETERS.
ALL RIGHT, THE HEAD'S STARTING
TO AT LEAST COME DOWN
OVER THE LAST HOUR,
HOUR AND HALF.
YOU HAVING A CONTRACTION NOW?
- YEAH, IT HURTS.
- COULD BE THE BABY.
- IT'S THE BABY'S HEAD.
- JUST THINK, BABE.
HE'S ALMOST HERE.
- NOTHING TO BE SCARED ABOUT.
YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT.
- NEXT TIME YOU SEE ME,
I'LL BE IN SCRUBS, ALL RIGHT?
- I'M JUST SCARED.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO TALK.
PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME TALK.
- YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE, HON.
OKAY?
- [breathing shakily]
YOU'RE MAKING ME SO STRESSED.
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
- I DON'T LIKE IT.
- YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT.
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
- THIS IS NOT NORMAL.
- OKAY, OKAY.
- NICOLE, YOU'RE DOING AWESOME.
YOU'RE DOING AWESOME, OKAY?
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
NICOLE, YOU'RE A PRO.
- THROUGHOUT YOUR LIFE,
YOU DEFINITELY HAVE MOMENTS
YOU'RE NEVER,
EVER GONNA FORGET.
BUT NOTHING, BY FAR,
COMPARES TO THIS.
- MM-HMM.
- NOTHING.
- THERE WE GO.
LITTLE MORE, LITTLE MORE.
- [whimpers]
[baby crying]
- [sobbing]
BABY'S HERE.
[baby crying]
- ROGER WANTS TO DO IT
THE MORE TRADITIONAL WAY,
WHICH IS GET ENGAGED.
- I'M KIND OF GETTING TAG-TEAMED
HERE A LITTLE BIT BY EVERYBODY.
- NOW I JUST NEED A RING.