- HE'S GORGEOUS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS IS MY SON.
IT'S LIKE, I DID THIS.
I CAN'T GIVE YOU A WORD
TO EXPLAIN
THE FIRST TIME YOU SEE
YOUR KID.
SHE LIKES IT.
- OH, [bleep]. SORRY, ROG.
- HE'S ADORABLE. HE'S SHIVERING,
WHICH IS SO CUTE.
- AW!
- AND I'M JUST, LIKE,
IN TEARS,
FALLING IN LOVE WITH HIM.
- THANK YOU.
- BYE, BABY.
- HE'S MY NEW BEST FRIEND.
EVEN HIS FARTS SMELL GOOD.
I LOVE THE SMELL OF HIS FARTS.
IS THAT WEIRD?
- ROGER WANTS TO DO IT
THE MORE TRADITIONAL WAY,
WHICH IS GET ENGAGED.
- I'M KIND OF
GETTING TAG-TEAMED HERE
A LITTLE BIT BY EVERYBODY.
- NOW I JUST NEED A RING.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
*I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
[upbeat music]
- HE'S HOME!
- OH, HE'S SO CUTE!
- HIS OUTFIT'S TOO BIG.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- DON'T FALL DOWN THE STAIRS.
- OH, I PROMISE I WON'T.
- WHAT SHOULD I PUT HIM IN
RIGHT NOW?
- LET ME SEE WHAT YOU HAVE.
OH, WHAT ABOUT THE NIGHTIE?
- BASICALLY, EVERYTHING'S
JUST COMING NATURALLY,
SO IT'S AWESOME.
- I FEEL VERY COMFORTABLE
ABOUT BEING A PARENT RIGHT NOW.
- ME TOO.
- DO WE HAVE ANY FORMULA?
- NO.
- YOU DIDN'T--
THEY GAVE US SOME.
- NO.
- THEY BROUGHT US IN,
LIKE, FOUR BOTTLES.
- YEAH.
- YOU FORGOT THEM.
- NO, THE BOX OF STUFF THEY
GAVE US WAS THE--THE BOTTLES.
- I KNOW, BUT THEY--
RIGHT BEFORE WE LEFT,
THEY CAME IN AND BROUGHT US,
LIKE, SIX BOTTLES.
- I DIDN'T GRAB IT,
'CAUSE I LEFT THE BAGS.
IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
WHEN YOUR FIANCEE SAYS,
"I'M BREAST-FEEDING,
I'M BREAST-FEEDING,"
THAT'S, LIKE,
YOU'RE NOT THINKING FORMULA.
- I'LL JUST SQUEEZE MY [bleep].
- OH, GOD.
[upbeat music]
* *
- BABE?
- YEAH.
- ARE WE TAKING MY TRUCK?
WE GOTTA GO, THOUGH, BABE.
WE'RE RUNNING LATE.
SO TODAY, YOU KNOW, UH,
I JUST WANT TO SPEND SOME TIME
OUT AT THE CABIN
AT THE LAKE, AND, UH,
MAYBE TAKE JENNI FISHING.
DO YOU REALLY NEED
FAKE EYELASHES TODAY?
- YES, I DO.
- WE GOTTA GO.
WE'RE RUNNING LATE.
- WELL, I'LL BE READY
AFTER THE SECOND EYELASH.
- YOUR BOOTS ARE IN THE CAR,
RIGHT?
- YES, SIR.
- ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I'LL BE DOWN THERE.
I'M READY.
- LIKE, DUDE,
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
WE'RE IN MAINE.
THERE'S NO EMERGENCY.
- READY?
- YEP.
[baby cries]
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
[baby passes gas]
OH, MY GOD.
HE JUST [bleep] ON MY LEG.
- [laughs]
IS IT ON YOUR LEG?
[baby passes gas]
- THAT WAS A WET ONE.
I THINK
HE JUST POOPED HIS PANTS.
- [laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
IT SMELLS!
[blowing]
UGH!
STINKY PEW-PEWS.
[baby passes gas]
[laughs]
OH, MY GOD!
HIS FARTS ARE SO LOUD!
[baby passes gas]
HE'S STILL GOING.
I LIKE LORENZO'S FARTS.
EVEN THOUGH
THEY SMELL LIKE ROTTEN EGGS
AND LEGIT [bleep],
I LOVE IT.
- OH, MY GOD,
HE DEFINITELY [bleep].
- I KNOW.
HE'S SUCH A TINY BABY,
BUT HE FARTS LIKE A--
YOU KNOW, LIKE A GROWN MAN.
[kisses]
MY LITTLE BOY.
- HE SMELLS
LIKE PURE [bleep].
- OH, YEAH, LET'S CHANGE HIM.
HE'S PROBABLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
LET'S DO THIS.
- GIVE ME HIM.
- OOH, WATCH MY NIPPLE.
OW.
- OH, COME HERE, DUDE.
HE'S SLEEPING.
I'D RATHER
JUST LET HIM SIT IN IT.
- NO!
- DID YOU DO POOPIES
IN YOUR PANTIES?
[both groan]
- EW!
I THINK ME AND JIONNI ARE DOING
A GREAT JOB AS NEW PARENTS.
- YOU'RE WIPING IT ON MY THUMB.
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
- WHO CARES?
ESPECIALLY ME.
LIKE, I NEVER TOOK CARE
OF A BABY BEFORE
OR A NEWBORN,
AND THE FACT THAT, YOU KNOW,
EVERYTHING JUST SEEMS
SO NATURAL TO ME, I MEAN,
I DEFINITELY HAVE
MATERNAL INSTINCTS.
IS THIS THE RIGHT DIAPER?
- IT'S ON BACKWARDS,
YOU--
- [laughs]
- "IS THIS THE RIGHT DIAPER?"
[baby cries]
- [laughs]
- "IS THIS THE RIGHT DIAPER?"
IT'S JUST ON BACKWARDS.
[baby cries]
IT'S--IT'S OKAY.
- SEE, NOW, I'M A NEW PARENT.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
LIKE, I'M JUST
GETTING USED TO EVERYTHING.
IT HAPPENS.
- OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
[upbeat music]
* *
- THERE IT IS, MONKEY.
- YAY.
- HOME SWEET HOME.
IT'S BEEN A YEAR.
IT LOOKS THE SAME, THOUGH.
- UH-HUH.
YAY.
- HOME SWEET HOME.
I COULD GET USED TO THIS.
COULD YOU?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- YEAH, WELL, YOU WANT
TO GO CATCH A FISH?
- I'LL GO FISHING.
- WELL, LET ME GO SEE IF THERE'S
FISHING RODS IN THE BOAT.
LET'S GO LOOK.
I WANT TO TAKE JENNI
OUT ON THE BOAT.
I WANT TO SEE IF SHE'S REALLY
THIS FISHERMAN
THAT SHE CLAIMS TO BE,
AND, UH--
- "FISHERMAN" AND "FISH"
ARE TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
I'VE FISHED BEFORE.
I COULD NOT TELL YOU
THAT I AM A FISHERMAN.
- [grunts]
- I LIKE THIS ONE
'CAUSE IT HAS A NEON WORM.
[electronic beep]
- ALL RIGHT, YOU CAN THROW IT ON
THERE, BABE, IF YOU'RE READY.
- OKAY.
[upbeat music]
OH, YEAH, BRING IT.
- SEE THIS HERE, BABE?
IT'S REAL SHALLOW OUT HERE,
SO USUALLY THE BASS HANG OUT.
THE IDEA IS TO GET IT AS CLOSE
TO THESE ROCKS AS YOU CAN,
BUT DON'T SNAG THE BOTTOM,
'CAUSE YOU'LL LOSE YOUR LURE.
[whimsical music]
* *
YOU HAVE TO MAKE IT
LOOK ALIVE,
SO YOU HAVE TO
KIND OF JIG IT.
- I'VE FISHED BEFORE.
- JENNI.
- I'M NOT GONNA HIT YOU.
- JESUS.
* *
- [scatting]
COME ON.
OH, OH, OH, OH!
- YOU GOT ONE?
- I GOT IT!
- HANG ON, HANG ON, HANG ON.
- I SEE IT, I SEE IT, I SEE HIM!
BRING HIM IN CLOSER.
- AAH!
WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
AAH!
- BABE, BRING HIM IN CLOSER!
- NO!
I CAN'T BRING IT IN!
[laughs]
- IT'S A BASS.
- [laughs]
- EASY WITH THE ROD TIP!
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- THAT'S THE FIRST CATCH
I'VE EVER HAD!
- MRS. "I GO FISHING
ALL THE TIME."
- I SAID I NEVER CAUGHT
ANYTHING BEFORE.
- OH, MY GOD.
SHE'S LIKE, "THERE'S SOMETHING
ON THE END OF MY LINE."
AND THEN SHE'S--
I THOUGHT SHE WAS GONNA
THROW THE FISHING ROD
IN THE WATER, YOU KNOW?
THAT'S THE POINT.
YES, IT'S--THAT'S A FISH
ON THE END OF YOUR LINE.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE HERE FOR.
- OH, LET HIM GO.
HE'S CUTE.
- I'M GONNA LET HIM GO.
- HI. I GOT YOU!
- HI, BUDDY.
[claps]
- GOOD JOB, BABY.
GOOD JOB.
- THAT WAS FUN.
LET'S DO IT AGAIN.
- [laughs]
CHECK THAT OUT.
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT SPIDER RIGHT THERE.
- [gasps]
- [laughs]
- I'M NOT COMPLAINING.
I'M NOT GONNA
JUMP OUT OF THE BOAT.
- LOOK AT THE SIZE OF IT.
THAT THING IS MONSTROUS.
- WE HAVE TO GIVE LORENZO
A BATH.
- ALL RIGHT.
BATHING YOUR SON
FOR THE FIRST TIME, IT'S SCARY.
- HE LOOKS LIKE
HE'S GONNA PEE.
PLEASE DON'T PEE
ON MOMMY.
- DINNER'S READY.
I MADE YOU BEAR BALLS.
YOU GOTTA TRY 'EM.
- OH, MY GOD,
I'M EATING A BEAR'S TESTICLE.
- TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK.
- WOW. YEAH.
IT TASTES LIKE A BALL.
[upbeat music]
- [laughs]
CHECK THAT OUT.
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT SPIDER RIGHT THERE.
- [gasps]
- [laughs]
- I'M NOT COMPLAINING.
I'M NOT GONNA JUMP
OUT OF THE BOAT.
- LOOK AT THE SIZE OF IT.
THAT THING IS MONSTROUS.
LOOK IT IN THE EYE.
WE'RE GONNA
BEAT YOUR FEAR TODAY.
- NO!
I GOT A SPIDER NEXT TO ME
THAT IS, LIKE, THE GARGANTUAN
OF ALL SPIDERS,
LIKE, STARING AT ME.
IT WANTS TO EAT ME,
BUT I WILL NOT COMPLAIN.
I WILL NOT MAKE HIM
TURN AROUND THE BOAT
AND PROVE THAT I
CANNOT HANDLE THIS,
SO I'M GONNA SUCK IT UP
AND DEAL WITH HIM.
- OH, THE SPIDER'S
ON THE MOVE.
- CHARLOTTE, STOP MOVING.
I'M NAMING THE SPIDER
CHARLOTTE,
'CAUSE SHE HAS A BIG WEB.
EW, EW.
DON'T [bleep] WITH ME.
YOU KNOW, I'M BASICALLY
TELLING CHARLOTTE
TO GO [bleep] HERSELF.
"IF YOU STAY ON YOUR SIDE,
I'LL STAY ON MINE."
BUT EVERY TIME THE BOAT
WOULD VIBRATE,
CHARLOTTE WOULD, LIKE,
CRAWL UP AND DOWN THE WEB
AND BE LIKE,
"WHAT'S GOOD?"
[groans and laughs]
SO, WE'RE, LIKE, INCHES AWAY
FROM EACH OTHER AT THIS POINT,
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF SHE'S GONNA ATTACK.
- IT WAS MORE LIKE FEET,
BUT...
- INCHES, AT ONE POINT.
- MAYBE EVEN YARDS.
- * IN THE FACTORY,
I DREAM *
**
*THIS METALLIC DISEASE *
* *
- YOU THINK THAT
AIR CONDITIONER'S BOTHERING HIM,
BLOWING THIS WAY?
- YEAH.
- JIONNI, YOU NEED HELP?
- NO.
- [bleep]!
- OH, GOD!
- I GO TO TAKE OUT
THE SCREEN,
AND [bleep] DUST
FLIES EVERYWHERE.
LIKE, THE JABRONI THAT I AM,
DIDN'T SHUT THE THING OFF.
THE FIRST THING I THINK OF IS,
COVER LORENZO'S FACE.
- [groans]
ASS[bleep].
JIONNI, OH, MY GOD.
- SORRY, BUDDY.
- HOLY [bleep].
- DON'T--DON'T--DON'T!
WHAT?
- [laughs]
DID YOU SEE THE WEB?
- NO.
- DO YOU SEE
ALL THE, LIKE,
HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS OF DOTS
AROUND IT?
- IS THAT--IS THAT BABIES?
- THOSE ARE LITTLE SPIDERS.
- OH, [bleep] ME
IN THE ASS[bleep] RIGHT NOW.
NO, THIS IS NOT OKAY.
- I THOUGHT YOU LOVED NATURE.
- I [bleep] HATE SPIDERS.
- [laughs]
- I WANT TO FISH.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE ABOUT
CALM, COOL, COLLECTED,
AND MY ANXIETY'S UP THERE,
DUE TO THE FACT
THERE'S ABOUT 1,000 BABIES
AND A 2-INCH WOLF SPIDER.
- SO, WAIT A MINUTE.
FISHING IS CALM,
COOL, AND COLLECTED?
- [screams]
- YOU GOT HIM! REEL HIM IN.
REEL HIM, BABE, REEL HIM.
- [screams]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
IT'S FIGHTING ME!
YOU TAKE IT!
- NO. REEL IT IN.
DON'T DROP THAT ROD.
- I WAS A LITTLE
TAKEN ABACK.
- I THOUGHT
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
CALM, COOL,
AND COLLECTED THOUGH?
- UP UNTIL THE POINT
YOU CATCH A FISH.
- OH. GOT YOU.
- AAH! OOH!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HANDING IT OFF.
KEEP IT AWAY
FROM THE MOTOR.
- [laughs]
[screams]
- THAT'S A GOOD-SIZED ONE.
GOD, YOU'RE SO TERRIFIED.
I MEAN, LIKE,
YOU'RE LIKE, "AAH!"
- OOH, OOH.
STOP FLAPPING, HOMEY.
WE'RE GONNA LET YOU GO.
- IT'S NICE.
- HELLO.
- IT'S A GOOD-SIZED FISH,
BABY.
- BYE, BABE.
- [grunts]
MY BABY'S NAILIN' EM.
YOU DON'T EVEN GIVE ME TIME
TO GET MY FRIGGIN' HOOK
IN THE WATER.
I THINK
IT'S BEGINNER'S LUCK.
- WHAT?
- IT'S ABSOLUTELY
BEGINNER'S LUCK.
- HOW IS
ANYTHING BEGINNER'S LUCK?
DO I HAVE SOMETHING?
- WHAT IS IT?
- DID I CATCH SOMETHING?
OH, IT'S FIGHTING ME!
IT'S PISSED OFF!
- NO, GET IT.
KEEP IT IN THE WATER.
- I'M KEEPING IT DOWN
- IT'S A LITTLE ONE.
IT'S A LITTLE ONE.
- I CAUGHT FISH.
- RIGHT, BUT WHERE'S
THE SKILL SET IN THAT?
BRING YOUR TIP UP SO IT
COMES UP TO THE SURFACE HERE,
NEXT TO ME,
NOT OUT THERE.
- COME ON, YOU [bleep].
DOESN'T HAVE TO BE A SKILL SET.
I CAUGHT FISH.
YAY! I GOT THREE!
ME 3. ROGER 0.
- [laughs]
YOU'RE GONNA
RELEASE THIS ONE.
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE GONNA
RELEASE THIS ONE.
- COME AGAIN?
HOW DO I HOLD IT?
- JUST LIKE I AM.
- EW, I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T.
I'M GONNA THROW UP.
I WANT TO HOLD IT LIKE THAT.
- NO, YOU CAN'T, 'CAUSE
THAT'S NOT THE PROPER WAY.
- OH, GOD, I'M, LIKE,
FREAKING OUT. I REALLY CAN'T.
- YOU POKE WITH YOUR FINGER IN
AND JUST GRAB IT LIKE THIS.
WATCH. JUST THIS SIMPLE.
JUST, BOOM, LIKE THAT.
- THEY HAVE LITTLE TEETH.
THE FISH HAVE LITTLE TEETH,
AND WHEN YOU PUT YOUR HAND
IN THERE, YOU FEEL THEM,
AND IF YOU PRESS TOO HARD,
I FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA HURT IT.
I DON'T LIKE
HURTING ANIMALS.
- GRAB IT.
- LET ME HOLD THE BELLY
FIRST, SO I CAN--
- I'LL PUT IT IN THE NET,
AND YOU PICK IT OUT OF THE NET.
- NO, LET ME--
OH, HI.
- YEAH, WATCH WHEN IT KICKS
WHAT HAPPENS.
IT HASN'T KICKED YET.
- YAY! I THREW IT IN
MY WAY.
- JENNI DEFINITELY BEAT ME.
UM, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN NICE
TO HAVE A LITTLE MORE TIME
TO ACTUALLY FISH
RATHER THAN TAKING
ALL THE FISH OFF HER LINES,
BUT, NO, SHE DID BEAT ME.
SHE DID REALLY WELL.
GOOD JOB, BABY.
- UH-OH.
I'M STUCK.
- I LOVE THE SMELL OF MUD
IN THE MORNING.
- NEW JERSEY AND MAINE
ARE, LEGIT,
TWO DIFFERENT WORLDS.
- OH, THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
SEE HIM?
- EW, EW, SOMETHING
WAS SQUISHY RIGHT THERE.
WHAT IS THAT?
- [laughs]
[guitar music]
* *
- YOU LIKE IT OUT HERE?
- I LOVE IT OUT HERE.
I WANT YOU TO BUILD
A HOUSE OUT HERE.
- I WANT TO BUILD
JENNI, DESPITE THE SCREAMING
AND MAYBE BEING A LITTLE TIRED,
SHE STILL HASN'T COMPLAINED,
AND, YOU KNOW,
I GOTTA TAKE MY HAT OFF
TO HER, YOU KNOW?
I-I DON'T KNOW THAT
I WOULD HAVE SAID THAT
EARLY IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
WE GOTTA LEAVE SOON, BABE.
- I'M GONNA TRY NICOLE.
- COOL.
[phone rings]
- HEY. HOW'S MAINE?
- IT'S AMAZING.
WE'RE OUT AT, UM, ROGER'S CABIN
RIGHT NOW WITH, UH,
NO ELECTRICITY
OR RUNNING WATER,
AND IT RUNS OFF...
- GOD.
- PROPANE AND A GENERATOR,
SO IT'S REALLY COOL.
IT LOOKS LIKE A...
- DOESN'T SOUND COOL.
- YOU KNOW, LIKE A LOG CABIN
OUT ON A MILE-LONG LAKE.
BUT I JUST CAUGHT
THREE BASS FISH.
- WOW.
- WHO ARE YOU?
NO ELECTRICITY.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT SHE'S DOING UP THERE.
SHE'S TOTALLY
OUT OF HER ELEMENT, I FEEL.
- I AM VERY RELAXED RIGHT NOW
AT THIS CABIN.
AND WE'RE ABOUT
TO GO CLAMMING.
- SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
- AT LEAST JIONNI
CAN APPRECIATE IT.
- YEAH, MR. SURVIVOR MAN
OVER THERE.
- HELL YEAH.
- DID ROGER POP THE QUESTION?
- WHAT'D SHE SAY?
- SHE ASKED IF YOU
POPPED THE QUESTION.
- [laughs]
- I WAS REALLY HOPING
THAT NICOLE
WOULD NOT ASK IF ROGER
POPPED THE QUESTION IN MAINE,
BUT I KNEW IT WAS COMING.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH.
I KNOW IT'S NOT
GONNA HAPPEN.
THEREFORE, WHY ASK?
- OKAY.
WHY DO YOU ASK SO MUCH?
- I DON'T ASK.
- OKAY.
GUESS THAT DEPENDS
ON WHAT QUESTION.
- HE GOES,
"DEPENDS ON WHAT QUESTION."
- "WILL YOU MARRY ME?"
- NO.
- YES, I WILL, NICOLE.
- CRICKET.
- UH-HUH.
- JIMINY.
- BYE, ASS[bleep]S.
- BYE.
I THOUGHT I MADE A FUNNY,
AND I DIDN'T.
- YOU'RE REALLY
DOING YOUR MAKEUP RIGHT NOW?
[grunts]
LIKE, REALLY?
TO GO CLAMMING?
- AN EYELASH WAS BLOWING OFF.
- I DON'T THINK
THE CLAMS CARE
IF YOUR EYELASH FALLS OFF.
[upbeat music]
[phone rings]
- HEY, DEENA.
- HELLO?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
- NOTHING. WHAT'S UP?
- NOTHIN'. I JUST WANTED TO CALL
AND SEE HOW YOU WERE FEELING.
- GOOD.
JUST RELAXING RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH, UM, I WANNA KNOW,
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' TOMORROW?
- UM, PROBABLY NOTHING.
- I WANNA COME OVER,
AND I WANNA SEE THE BABY,
AND I WANNA SEE YOU.
- I KNOW.
HE'S SO CUTE.
HE SLEEPS A LOT, THOUGH,
SO HOPEFULLY HE'LL BE UP
WHEN YOU'RE HERE.
- IT'S GONNA BE A LOTTA FUN.
- OKAY, I LOVE YOU.
I'LL TEXT YOU.
- ALL RIGHT.
- OKAY, BYE.
- LOVE YOU TOO. BYE.
- COOL.
WE HAVE TO GIVE
LORENZO A BATH.
CAN'T WAIT
TO WASH HIS HAIR.
- YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO PUT
ANY KIND OF LOTION ON HIM.
- DADDY DOESN'T WANT
TO GIVE YOU A BATH.
- I DIDN'T SAY I DON'T
WANT TO GIVE HIM A BATH.
I'M TELLING YOU
WHAT THE NURSE TOLD ME.
YOU DIDN'T GO TO ONE BATH
THAT SHE GAVE HIM.
- I KNOW, BUT WHY WOULD IT
BE BAD TO GIVE HIM A BATH?
- SHE SAID IT'S NO GOOD
FOR HIS SKIN
TO HAVE A BATH EVERY DAY.
- SO WHY'D SHE DO IT
EVERY DAY?
- BECA--I HAVE NO IDEA.
- I WANT TO GIVE LORENZO
A BATH TODAY
BECAUSE I THINK
HE SMELLS LIKE CHEESE
AND HIS HAIR LOOKS GREASY
AND HE JUST LOOKS
KIND OF DIRTY.
LIKE, I KIND OF WANT TO--
- HE DIDN'T SMELL
LIKE CHEESE.
- YEAH, HE DID.
AND WHEN I WAS A BABY,
I HATED BATHS,
SO THIS MIGHT
BE TORTURE FOR YOU.
- IT'S SCARY, BATHING YOUR SON
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
HE'S SO LITTLE.
I'VE NEVER DONE IT BEFORE.
YOU WANT TO BE SO CAUTIOUS.
HE'S SO FRAGILE,
IT--IT'S SCARY.
- OKAY, MAKE YOU
NICE AND CLEAN.
GET BEHIND YOUR EARS.
HE LOOKS LIKE
HE'S GONNA PEE.
PLEASE DON'T PEE
ON MOMMY.
[baby cries]
YOU'RE CLEAN!
YOU KNOW, NINE MONTHS AGO,
I NEVER THOUGHT THAT I WOULD
BE TAKING CARE OF MY SON.
DOES THAT FEEL GOOD?
HE LOVES IT.
IT JUST MAKES ME
FEEL GOOD ABOUT MYSELF,
AND I KNOW THAT I'M GONNA
BE A GOOD MOM,
AND I DEFINITELY
DON'T DOUBT MYSELF ANYMORE.
[kisses]
YOU DID SUCH A GOOD JOB.
HE'S SUCH A G.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
[kisses]
BEAUTIFUL.
OH, GOD, HE'S HUNGRY.
HE'S LOOKING FOR A [bleep].
- I'M ALL GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- IT'S EARLY.
YOU KNOW, EARLIER THAN JENNI
NORMALLY GETS UP.
UM, IT'S ABOUT 5:00
IN THE MORNING.
- I'M COMPLETELY OUT OF IT
RIGHT NOW.
- BREAK YO' MOTHER[bleep] SELF!
YOU FEEL BETTER?
- [laughs]
STOP.
- ARE YOU AWAKE NOW?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU LIKE OYSTERS?
- OVERCOME YOUR FEARS.
COME ON.
- I'M GONNA EAT A RAW CLAM
RIGHT OUT OF THE OCEAN
RIGHT NOW.
I NEED A LITTLE
SALT AND PEPPER ON IT.
[rock music]
* *
- YOU'RE DOING GOOD,
SO FAR.
I HOPE YOU SEE
A WORM OUT HERE THOUGH.
OH, I REALLY HOPE
YOU SEE A BLOOD WORM.
- ARE BLOOD WORMS REAL?
CAN I GOOGLE THEM?
- I SWEAR BLOOD WORMS
ARE REAL,
AND IT'S NOT GOING
TO ATTACK YOU.
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THEY BITE.
- IF YOU PICK IT UP WITH
YOUR BARE HAND, IT'LL BITE YOU.
IT'S, LIKE,
A CENTIPEDE-LOOKING THING.
- YEEH.
**
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH THOSE?
- KILLING BLOOD WORMS
WITH THEM.
- YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS?
COME ON, JENNI.
- YES.
- WHAT ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
DOING WITH THOSE?
- BRINGING--WHOOPS!
[laughs]
- YOU CAN'T EVEN WALK
IN SNEAKERS,
AND YOU'RE GONNA WALK
IN THOSE?
- [laughs]
ARTHUR!
- HEY!
- YO!
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HI.
- P.J., JESUS.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- IT'S BEEN TOO LONG, MAN.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN, BROTHER?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I'VE BEEN GOOD.
- GOOD.
- THANK YOU.
- HOW WAS THE RIDE?
- IT WAS--UH, WE--WE TOOK
A FEW WRONG TURNS,
BUT WE MADE IT.
- AH, THEY LOOK LIKE GOOD
[bleep]-KICKING BOOTS.
- SHE GOT THESE
OUT OF THE CAR.
I'M LIKE, "WHAT--
WHAT DO YOU NEED THESE FOR?"
- FOR CLAMMING.
- SHE CLAIMS
THAT SHE'S GONNA
BEAT A BLOOD WORM
TO DEATH WITH 'EM.
- HE TOLD ME THERE'S
BLOOD WORMS IN THERE.
- YOU MIGHT SEE A BLOOD WORM.
- EH, THEY'RE PRETTY--
- SPIKING IT.
- THEY'RE PRETTY QUICK, THOUGH.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
- YEAH.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY SHE
WOULD EVEN NEED HEELS IN MAINE,
BUT, FOR WHATEVER REASON,
SHE BROUGHT HEELS
TO GO CLAMMING.
IT MAKES NO SENSE.
- MAY I USE THE RESTROOM...
IN THERE?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- WHICH WAY? RIGHT OR LEFT?
- [laughs]
- OUT BEHIND THAT BUILDING.
- ARE YOU LYING?
AAH! THE OUTHOUSE?
- YEAH. ROLL THAT--
YEAH.
- HE'D BETTER GIVE ME THAT
DAMN RING SOONER THAN LATER.
IT'S GROSS.
I FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA VOMIT.
WELL, IS THERE--?
I NEED SOME SORT
OF TOILET PAPER.
[laughs]
THE OUTHOUSE IS
A LITTLE TOO MUCH FOR ME.
IT'S TOO CONFUSING,
YOU KNOW?
MAY I HAVE PAPER TOWELS?
- WHAT?
- FOR TOILET PAPER?
- IT'S IN THE WHITE
PLASTIC TUB.
- OH, IT IS?
- YEAH.
THAT'S HOW YOU KEEP
THE MICE OUT OF IT.
- THAT'S HOW THE MICE
DON'T EAT IT.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT?
- [laughs]
GOD, STOP.
I'M NOT GONNA FREAK OUT.
I COME TO FIND OUT
THE TOILET PAPER'S IN THE BIN
DUE TO THE FACT THAT MICE
CAN EAT AT IT.
- ALL SET?
- ALL SET.
- [laughs]
- UM, SO I JUST...
[laughs]
OH, MY GOD.
A LITTLE TOO MUCH FOR ME.
A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
I CAN HOLD IT.
NO.
[exhales]
I'M GONNA HOLD IT.
- ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, FINE.
I GOTTA PEE.
[laughs]
- I'M GONNA
GO GET MY BOOTS ON
AND GRAB SOME CLAM HOES
AND ROLLERS AND...
- LET'S GO DO THIS.
THESE ARE THE GOOD ONES,
'CAUSE YOU DIG IT IN
AND THEN YOU FLIP IT OVER.
- THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING?
- IT'S A CLAM HOE,
AND THIS IS A ROLLER,
AND YOUR CLAM
HAS TO NOT FIT THROUGH.
IF A CLAM FALLS
THROUGH THERE, IT'S NO GOOD.
- OKAY.
- TOO SMALL.
- DID YOU GET ALL THAT?
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT.
- DON'T DOUBT ME. OH, THIS IS
GONNA BE A BACK BUSTER.
- WELL, YA AT LEAST GOTTA
GET ENOUGH
TO TAKE HOME
FOR FAMILY DINNER.
- YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
- [laughs]
- NEW JERSEY AND MAINE
ARE, LEGIT,
TWO DIFFERENT WORLDS.
IT'S LIKE GOING
TO A DIFFERENT COUNTRY.
UH-OH.
[exhales]
I'M STUCK.
- I LOVE THE SMELL OF MUD
IN THE MORNING.
- I ACTUALLY THOUGHT ABOUT
BRINGING MY HIGH HEELS OUT HERE.
HUH...
- HOW ARE YOU DOING,
MY LOVE?
- UM, I'M ATTEMPTING,
YOU KNOW?
- I WAS TALKING TO P.J.
- OH.
THERE'S REALLY NOTHING
I WOULDN'T DO FOR ROGER,
BUT CLAMMING
IS LEGIT EXHAUSTING,
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO, LIKE,
STAY ABOVE THE MUD
SO YOU DON'T GET STUCK.
EVERY [bleep] STEP YOU TAKE
IS HARD.
THEN YOU'VE GOT TO FIND
A LITTLE HOLE,
AND THEN YOU'VE GOT TO DIG
AND DIG AND DIG AND DIG,
AND THEN YOU CLAM
THE WRONG WAY--
UGH! IT'S A WORM!
AND YOU MIGHT GET BIT
BY A BLOOD WORM.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
THIS IS A WORKOUT.
IT'S A LOT OF EFFORT
JUST FOR A [bleep] CLAM.
- THERE YOU GO.
OOH, THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
SEE HIM?
SEE HIS HEAD RIGHT THERE?
- OH, NO, IT LOOKS LIKE A WORM!
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DO THIS.
I CAN'T DO IT.
[gasps]
- KEEP GOING.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
- I CAN GET IT!
- NICOLE DIDN'T WHINE THAT MUCH
GIVING BIRTH.
- I'M FREAKING OUT.
YOU GET IT.
- NO.
- [laughs]
- EW, EW, SOMETHING WAS SQUISHY
RIGHT THERE. WHAT IS THAT?
- [laughs]
- OH, WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, COME ON NOW.
- HURRY UP,
BEFORE HE GETS AWAY.
- UH, UH, AAH!
- HURRY UP!
[laughs]
- [whimpers]
- [bleep].
I KEEP SPEARIN' 'EM.
- THAT'S A KEEPER.
- YAY, I GOT ONE.
- OOH, NOW, YOU--
WELL, YOU'RE UP TO TWO.
- OOH, I GOT A WORM!
AAH! WHAT WAS THAT?
- THERE HE IS.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT.
- HOW MANY YOU GOT, BABE?
- NOT DOING WELL AT ALL.
CLAMMING IS--IS PRETTY MUCH
WHAT I REMEMBER IT BEING.
IT'S A LOT OF HARD WORK
FOR A LITTLE REWARD.
BUT IT'S DEFINITELY MORE CLAM
THAN I'VE GOTTEN
IN A LONG TIME RIGHT NOW.
[groans]
EATING ONE RAW?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU EAT 'EM RAW?
- YOU LIKE OYSTERS?
- ARE YOU--ARE YOU
GONNA CLEAN IT FIRST?
- NO, THE OCEAN CLEANS IT.
- YOU TRY IT FIRST.
DO YOU CHEW IT?
- OF COURSE YOU CHEW IT.
- THIS IS...
[whimsical music]
I NEED A LITTLE
SALT AND PEPPER ON IT.
- OH, BUT YOU EAT SUSHI.
- [laughs]
- OVERCOME YOUR FEARS.
COME ON.
- I'LL NEVER LIVE THIS DOWN
IF I DON'T DO IT,
AND I CAN'T COMPLAIN,
SO I'M GONNA EAT A RAW CLAM
RIGHT OUT OF THE OCEAN
RIGHT NOW.
- IT'S A RAW CLAM.
IT'S NOT A SPIDER.
- HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT TEXTURE?
- IT'S NOT VERY GOOD!
- EAT IT, BABY.
- IT'S DOWN.
- GOD LOVE YA.
[laughter]
- SO, THERE'S A TECHNIQUE
WHEN IT COMES TO CLAM EATING.
- OH, IS THERE EVER.
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE A DOWNEASTER.
- GOOD JOB. YOU DID GOOD.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
GOOD JOB.
BEEN EATING CLAM
MY WHOLE LIFE.
NEVER A COMPLAINT
FROM A CLAM YET.
- EW.
- WE'RE GONNA MAKE A CLAM DIGGER
OUT OF YOU YET, DARLIN'.
- RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- JENNI'S TALKING THE TALK
AND WALKING THE WALK, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, SHE'S--
SHE'S GETTING IN THERE.
SHE'S GETTING HER HANDS DIRTY.
I'M PROUD OF HER, YOU KNOW?
SHE'S DOING A GOOD JOB
AND NOT COMPLAINING.
- [belches]
THAT WAS FUN.
I CAN'T BREATHE.
IT'S LIKE SOMETHING
I'VE NEVER SMELLED BEFORE!
- [laughs]
- IT SMELLS LIKE 5,000 FISH
JUST DIED ON THIS BOAT
AND HAVE MARINATING IN THE SUN
FOR, LIKE, A WEEK.
EHH! GOD.
- YOU CAN EAT ONE
IF YOU WANT!
- OH, GOD. EHH!
- AAH!
- WHAT ARE YOU SCREAMING AT?
- HE POOPED ON ME!
I'M GETTING UP AT LEAST
FIVE TIMES A NIGHT.
ARE YOU SLEEPING?
- NO.
WE SHOULD ENTER
THE DIAPER OLYMPICS.
[upbeat music]
- * I JUST CLOSE MY EYES *
- I'M HAVING SUCH A GOOD TIME
OUT HERE.
- GOOD.
- *JUST RAMBLE AWAY *
- EVERYONE'S WAY OF LIVING
IN MAINE AND IN JERSEY
ARE DAY AND NIGHT.
IN JERSEY,
EVERYTHING'S FAST-PACED,
WHEREAS IN MAINE,
EVERYTHING'S SLOW-PACED,
AND, YOU KNOW,
MORE HOME COOKING
AND JUST, LIKE, CHILL,
AND I LIKE THAT.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS?
- THANK YOU.
- HOW ARE YOU, JENNI?
- HEY, HOW'S THE GUY?
- HI! HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- [groans]
- SO, LISTEN, I--I'VE GOT, UH,
BEVERAGES ON THE TABLE HERE.
- OH, EXCELLENT.
- OKAY.
- SO, I TOOK EVERYTHING OUT,
SO I WANT YOU
TO HELP YOURSELVES.
- I'M--YOU KNOW I WILL.
YOU KNOW I WILL.
- AND GLASSES ARE OUT,
AND THERE'S RED AND WHITE WINE
FOR JENNI.
- OH, THANK YOU.
I LOVE ROGER'S
AUNT SUSAN.
SHE'S LIKE, YOU KNOW,
BETTY CROCKER,
SUSIE HOMEMAKER,
AND SHE'S JUST, LIKE,
THE SWEETEST WOMAN EVER.
- JENNI, I KNEW
YOU WOULD LOVE HIM.
- LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT THING.
- YOU'RE MY NEW BEST FRIEND.
- THIS IS MY BUDDY.
- IS THAT A PERSIAN?
- I BRUSHED HIM OUT
REALLY GOOD, BUT HE SHEDS.
- IT'S A PERSIAN?
- IT'S A HIMALAYAN
FLAME POINT.
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL.
- HIS NAME IS CASHMERE.
I COULDN'T WAIT
TO SHOW HIM TO YOU
'CAUSE I KNOW YOU'RE SUCH
AN ANIMAL LOVER.
- MY FAMILY LOVES JENNI.
JENNI LOVES MY FAMILY.
IT'S EXTREMELY SPECIAL FOR ME
BECAUSE THEY ACCEPT HER.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S JUST LIKE
ONE OF THE FAMILY.
- BEAR BALLS.
- JENNI AND ROGER,
DINNER'S READY.
- IS THAT BEAR BALLS?
- I MADE YOU BEAR BALLS.
YOU GOTTA TRY 'EM.
- [laughs]
- YOU KNOW I'M GAME.
ARE YOU GONNA TRY ONE?
- TRY 'EM.
- THEY LOOK DELICIOUS.
- WHEN YOU SAY "BEAR BALLS,"
YOU KNOW,
YOUR FIRST INITIAL REACTION
IS, "OH, MY GOD,
I'M EATING A BEAR'S TESTICLE."
- TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK.
- WOW. YEAH.
IT TASTES LIKE A BALL.
- IT'S NOT.
IT'S BEAR MEATBALLS,
AND THEY'RE ACTUALLY
REALLY GOOD.
- WHAT ARE YOU
DOING TOMORROW?
- WE'RE GONNA GO LOBSTERING.
- GOING LOBSTERING. WOW.
SO, TOMORROW,
YOU'LL PROBABLY BE THE ONE
BAITING THE BAGS,
YOU KNOW?
- OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- SO, BE PREPARED.
- WHAT'S "BAITING THE BAGS"?
- BAITING THE BAGS MEANS
THAT YOU'RE PUTTING THE RAW--
- NO, DON'T RUIN IT!
DON'T RUIN IT!
- THE RAW BAIT THAT'S BEEN
FERMENTING FOR WEEKS...
- THE SUSHI!
- INTO THE BAIT BAGS...
- THAT GO OVERBOARD
IN THE LOBSTER TRAPS.
- [groans]
- WEAR YOUR
VERY WORST CLOTHES.
- DON'T WEAR
ANYTHING YOU LIKE AT ALL.
WEAR ROGER'S CLOTHES
OR SOMETHING.
[laughter]
- THERE YOU GO.
- THANK YOU, EVERYBODY,
FOR TALKING HER OUT OF
GOING LOBSTER FISHING TOMORROW.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
- I THINK JENNI THINKS, LIKE,
YOU BAIT A LOBSTER TRAP
WITH, LIKE, A T-BONE STEAK
OR SOMETHING,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- I JUST THOUGHT YOU JUST
[bleep] PULL UP A LOBSTER
AND YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
- YOU READY, BABE?
- I'M READY.
I DON'T WANT TO GO.
- I DON'T WANT TO GO EITHER,
BUT WE'VE GOT
AN EARLY MORNING TOMORROW.
- [groans]
THANK YOU FOR FILLING MY BELLY
WITH LOVE.
- ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
- THANK YOU.
- MWAH!
- LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU TOO.
LOVE YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING US
THIS EVENING.
[upbeat music]
[baby crying]
- ARE YOU SLEEPING?
- NO.
[baby crying]
SOMEONE'S SUPPOSED
TO HAVE ENERGY,
AND THEN SOMEONE SLEEPS,
AND THEN VICE-VERSA,
AND WE'RE BOTH EXHAUSTED.
TEAMWORK!
- YOU GOTTA GET YOUR SLEEP
OR THIS KID'S GONNA BE
IN BACKWARDS DIAPERS.
- CRAZY RIGHT NOW.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING.
I SAID "BACKWARDS DIAPERS."
IT JUST--I NEED TO SLEEP.
[laughs]
[bottle clatters]
WHAT THE HECK WAS THAT?
AAH!
- WHAT ARE YOU SCREAMING AT?
- HE POOPED ON ME!
ALLS HE DOES
IS [bleep] ON ME.
I'M GETTING UP AT LEAST
FIVE TIMES A NIGHT.
IT'S JUST NON-STOP.
EVERY TIME NICOLE AND I
SAID WE'RE GONNA SWITCH,
WE'RE NOT SWITCHING.
IT'S WE'RE BOTH GETTING UP.
WE'RE BOTH NOT GETTING SLEEP.
THE WHOLE ROTAT--
EVERYTHING BACKFIRED.
YOU SOAKED
MY FRICKIN' SHIRT!
YOU KNOW THAT?
BABIES [bleep]
AS THEY PLEASE.
THEY [bleep] WHEREVER THEY WANT,
RUIN OUTFITS, PEE, POOP.
THEY LIVE THE LIFE.
THEY--SOMEBODY ELSE EVEN
CLEANS 'EM UP.
I'M SO TIRED.
- TEAM DIAPER.
- NO ONE CHANGES DIAPERS
BETTER THAN US!
- WE SHOULD ENTER
THE DIAPER OLYMPICS.
- I GOTTA PEE-PEE.
- YOU GOTTA GO
IN A BUCKET, BABY.
- THERE'S NO BATHROOM
ON HERE, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- [groans]
NOTHING LIKE CARRYING
MY OWN PEE BUCKET.
- HI! HOW ARE YA!
- YAY!
OUR FURNITURE IS HERE.
NOW WE GET TO SET UP
OUR NURSERY.
HOW MUCH SHOULD WE TIP THEM?
- $40 APIECE.
- OR WE COULD GIVE THEM
ICE POPS.
- [laughs]
- WE HAVE A LOT
OF ICE POPS.
[whimsical music]
* *
- [groans]
- I'M ALL GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT.
- WANT A BOWL OF CEREAL?
- NO.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
IT'S EARLY.
YOU KNOW, EARLIER THAN JENNI
NORMALLY GETS UP.
UM, IT'S ABOUT 5:00
IN THE MORNING.
- THIS LOOKS LIKE
I'M GOING TO WORK.
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE CHANGING PROFESSIONS.
YOU GOT LOBSTERS HERE,
AND YOU GOTTA GET UP EVERY
MORNING LIKE THIS, YOU KNOW?
[laughs]
- I LOVE LOBSTER FISHING.
IT'S WHAT I GREW UP DOING,
SO I'M EXCITED.
I'M JUST PUMPED.
THIS WHOLE MAINE TRIP
IS JUST KIND OF
GETTING BACK TO, UH,
MY ROOTS, YOU KNOW?
- OH, MAN, I'M COMPLETELY
OUT OF IT RIGHT NOW.
- BREAK YO' MOTHER[bleep] SELF!
YOU FEEL BETTER?
- [laughs] STOP!
- ARE YOU AWAKE NOW?
- IT'S [bleep] 6:00
IN THE MORNING!
I [bleep] HATE
"BREAK YOURSELF."
- WHEN IT STOPS WORKING,
I'LL SWITCH TO SOMETHING ELSE.
IT'S STILL WORKING PERFECTLY
RIGHT NOW, THOUGH.
- YOU'RE KILLING MY EARS.
- WELL-OILED MACHINE RIGHT NOW.
- MORNING.
- GOOD MORNING.
- LET'S HOPE WE'RE BETTER
LOBSTERMEN
THAN WE WERE CLAMMERS.
WHAT'S UP, BROTHER?
WHAT'S GOING ON? ROGER.
HOW ARE YOU? THERE YOU GO.
THERE'S YOUR BAIT BUCKET.
YOU WANT TO BE POSTED UP
RIGHT NEAR THAT THING.
- TO BE HONEST, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT TO EXPECT
WHEN IT COMES
TO LOBSTER FISHING.
I JUST PICTURE
THE DEADLIEST CATCH,
AND THAT SCARES
THE [bleep] OUT OF ME.
- LET'S DO THIS.
I'M READY.
AM I DRIVING OR--?
- OH, NO. NO.
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
* *
- HOW ARE YOU DOING?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
- [laughs]
- VERY PUNGENT.
- YOU KNOW YOU HAVE TO PUT THAT
IN BAIT BAGS, RIGHT?
- IT'S LIKE SOMETHING
I'VE NEVER SMELLED BEFORE!
- AND YOU'RE NOT EVEN
CLOSE TO IT YET.
WAIT TILL YOU GET UP THERE
CLOSE.
- I DON'T HONESTLY
THINK I CAN!
- [laughs]
- THE LOBSTER BOAT
JUST SMELLS LIKE DEATH.
IT JUST SMELLS LIKE 5,000 FISH
JUST DIED ON THIS BOAT
AND HAVE BEEN MARINATING
IN THE SUN FOR, LIKE, A WEEK.
- BAIT A BAG!
- YOU'VE GOT YOUR GLOVES ON.
- STUFF THAT AS FULL AS YOU CAN
AND THEN CINCH IT UP.
HURRY UP, THOUGH, 'CAUSE WE'VE
GOT TRAPS COMING ON BOARD.
- OH, GOD.
- YOU CAN EAT ONE
IF YOU WANT!
- EHH! GOD.
- DUDE, JOE'S GONNA WANT TO HIRE
YOU SO BAD AFTER SEEING THIS.
- YOU CANNOT GET RID OF
YOUR SENSE OF SMELL,
DUE TO THE FACT
THAT YOU HAVE TO BREATHE,
AND IT WAS JUST, LIKE,
SO [bleep] VILE.
BABE?
- WHAT?
- I GOTTA PEE-PEE.
- YOU GOTTA GO
IN A BUCKET, BABY.
IT'S A LOBSTER BOAT.
THERE'S NO BATHROOM ON HERE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THERE'S YOUR PORTA POTTY.
YOU TAKE A BUCKET,
YOU GO UP IN THE FRONT,
YOU SIT ON IT, YOU PEE,
YOU COME OUT HERE,
YOU THROW IT OVER THE SIDE.
- IS THERE TOILET PAPER?
- UM, A PAPER TOWEL,
PROBABLY.
- I'M NOT GONNA SAY ANYTHING,
EVEN THOUGH, IN MY HEAD,
I'M [bleep] SCREAMING
VIOLENT WORDS.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE DRANK
COFFEE.
UHH! THAT IS NASTY.
AND THEN, THE BOAT'S SWAYING,
AND YOU'VE GOT TO TRY
AND LEVEL YOURSELF
ON A BUCKET TO GO PEE.
THANK GOD IT WASN'T DARK
IN THERE.
[groans]
NOTHING LIKE CARRYING
MY OWN PEE BUCKET.
- MY GOD,
YOU PEED FIVE GALLONS.
DON'T PUT IT
OVER THE BAIT.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO RUIN THE BAIT.
- I HAVE PEED
ON DEENA'S FOOT.
I HAVE PEED
BEHIND KARMA'S BAR.
ON PORCH STEPS.
GO [bleep] FIGURE.
- I HEREBY CHRISTEN
THE SEA.
- THANK YOU.
- GOOD JOB BY YOU.
[seagulls squawking]
- OH. OH, YEAH.
BRING IT.
- YOU WANT TO GET IN HERE,
BABE?
- GRAB 'EM.
- AAH! [bleep],
IT'S HANGING.
- GRAB IT. THROW IT IN THERE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- AAH!
[whimpers]
- GRAB IT.
- AS LONG AS YOU GRAB 'EM
RIGHT THERE, YOU'RE GOOD.
- [whimpers]
[groans]
- LOOK AT THAT ONE, BABY.
LOOK AT THAT ONE.
- AAH!
- LOOK AT THAT SUCKER.
- WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- [laughs]
THAT IS A MONSTER.
- AAH!
- NO, GO AHEAD.
WE'LL LOOK AT HIM AFTER.
FINISH YOUR TRAP.
- [groans]
SO, YEAH,
I'M NOT FEELING THIS.
[whimpers]
LET GO, LET GO, LET GO.
STOP WAILING.
I DON'T LIKE THIS
ANY MORE THAN YOU DO.
- GOOD JOB, BABY,
GOOD JOB.
I'M PRETTY PROUD OF HER,
ALL IN ALL.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S SCARED
OF THE LOBSTERS
LIKE SHE IS SCARED
OF MOST THINGS,
BUT SHE STILL GOT IN THERE
AND SHE STILL DID IT,
SO, YOU KNOW,
WHAT MORE COULD I ASK FOR?
DID YOU HAVE FUN?
WELL, I HAD FUN.
THANK YOU FOR COMING WITH ME.
- OVERALL, LOBSTER FISHING
IS DEFINITELY
FOR A CERTAIN BREED
OF PEOPLE.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE
A CERTAIN THICK SKIN TO DO IT,
SO I GIVE PEOPLE PROPS
FOR BEING LOBSTERMEN.
GOT IT?
- YEP.
- I'M WASHING ALL OUR CLOTHES
WHEN WE GET BACK.
EVERYTHING STINKS.
[pop music]
MY BODY SMELLS LIKE DEATH.
[belches]
- TELL ME THAT'S NOT BEAUTIFUL
OUT THERE, THOUGH,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- IT'S GORGEOUS.
UM, AND THEN--
- BREAK YO' MOTHER[bleep] SELF!
- WILL YOU JUST [bleep]
STOP WITH THAT?
STOP. JUST STOP.
- I HAD A GUN.
- I'M NOT EVEN KIDDING.
- [laughing]
I HAD A GUN THIS TIME.
IT WASN'T EVEN LOADED,
I SWEAR.
BREAK YOURSELF!
- STOP!
- *AH, GO ON *
* YOU'RE CALLING ME
AT HOME *
- OH, THERE'S BUGS.
- YOU'RE OKAY. COME ON.
- PUT YOUR FEETIES UP
SO THE SWELLING GOES DOWN.
- MY LITTLE BURRITO.
[phone rings]
HELLO?
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
- WHOA.
HEY, BOO.
- WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
- I'M JUST LAYING OUTSIDE
WITH LORENZO.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- WE JUST GOT DONE
LOBSTER FISHING
EARLY THIS MORNING.
WE GOT UP AT, LIKE,
5:00 TO GO AND, UM,
I DIDN'T GET
MUCH SLEEP LAST NIGHT
'CAUSE WE WERE AT
HIS AUNT'S HOUSE FOR DINNER,
AND SHE COOKED BEAR BALLS
AND, LIKE--
- WAIT.
DID YOU SAY "BEAR BALLS"?
- YEAH.
- NASTY.
SHE'S EATING BEAR BALLS.
- BEAR TESTICLES?
- LIKE, BEAR TESTICLES.
- ARE THEY GOOD?
- HOW'S ROGER'S FAMILY?
- THEY'RE GOOD.
- SO, YOU'RE, LIKE,
MEETING ALL OF HIS FAMILY,
MAYBE HE'S THINKING
ABOUT PROPOSING.
IT'S ABOUT TIME
ROGER PROPOSES.
AT THIS RATE,
I THINK I'M GONNA GET MARRIED
BEFORE JENNI
EVEN GETS ENGAGED.
- OH, DON'T EVEN GO THERE.
HE'S SITTING RIGHT HERE.
- I'LL GIVE YOU PRIVACY,
IF YOU WANT.
- WELL, I REALLY HOPE,
LIKE, GENUINELY,
I HOPE YOU'RE HAVING FUN
UP THERE.
- YEAH, I AM.
I'M HAVIN' A LOT OF FUN.
I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW
ON OUR WAY BACK.
- ALL RIGHT, BYE.
I LOVE YOU.
- BYE.
I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE
I WANT TO PUNCH NICOLE
RIGHT IN THE [bleep] NOSE
'CAUSE SHE KEEPS ASKING
IF ROGER HAS PROPOSED YET.
HE DID NOT,
AND STOP [bleep] ASKING.
- IT'S SO WEIRD.
- THE BEAR BALLS
WAS ENOUGH FOR ME.
I MEAN, UGH!
- AUNTIE JENNI
ATE BEAR BALLS.
THAT'S FRICKIN' WEIRD.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY...
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- * SO FAR, SO FAST *
* SOME THINGS
AREN'T MEANT TO LAST *
- ARE YOU EXCITED
FOR THE FURNITURE?
I CAN'T WAIT.
IT'S GONNA FINALLY
LOOK LIKE A BABY'S ROOM.
- DOES HE HAVE [bleep]
IN HIS NAILS?
- NO, IT'S DRIED BLOOD.
- IT'S YELLOW.
HAVE YOU BEEN
PICKING YOUR BUTT?
- BELLINI TRUCK'S HERE.
LET'S GO GET
OUR FURNITURE.
- HOW ARE WE GONNA CARRY
ALL THAT [bleep] DOWNSTAIRS?
- THEY ARE.
- OH.
- THINK I'M DOING IT?
- YAY! IT'S HERE.
I AM SO EXCITED
THAT THE FURNITURE IS HERE,
BECAUSE NOW WE GET TO SET UP
OUR NURSERY.
LORENZO'S HERE.
LIKE, PERFECT TIMING.
- HOW DO YOU
WANT THIS SET UP?
- THE CRIB'S
DEFINITELY GONNA GO THERE.
- OKAY.
- UM, THE BOOKCASE--
- HEY, HEY,
I HAVE A [bleep] SAY.
- OH, SORRY. "THE BOSS"
GOTTA LOOK TOO.
- I'M SORRY.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- OKAY. WHAT?
- RIGHT?
- WHAT, YOU WANT THE ARMOIRE
RIGHT THERE?
- WHAT'S AN ARMOIRE?
- THE ARMOIRE'S, YOU KNOW,
THE LARGER DRESSER
WITH THE OTHER DOORS ON IT.
- THE ARMOIRE?
SAY "THE BUREAU'S COMING."
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT THE CRIB.
YOU GOT THE, YOU KNOW,
CHANGING TABLE.
YOU GOT THE BOOKSHELF.
- THE BOOKSHELF.
- THE CHAIR.
- OUR CHAIR.
- IT'S JUST WEIRD.
JUST DON'T SAY "ARMOIRE"
IN MY BASEMENT,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
- HOW MUCH
SHOULD WE TIP THEM?
- $40 APIECE.
- OKAY.
OR WE COULD GIVE THEM
ICE POPS.
- [laughs]
- WE HAVE A LOT
OF ICE POPS.
- HERE YOU GO.
THIS IS FOR YOU GUYS.
TAKE THAT. THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
- THANK YOU.
PEACE BE WITH YOU.
- AFTER THIS FURNITURE'S IN,
YOU LOOK OVER,
IT LOOKS LIKE
AN ACTUAL BABY'S ROOM.
- OH, THAT'S NICE.
- IT'S GONNA LOOK LIKE
A HOME DOWN HERE.
- WOW, LET'S SEE.
- IT'S NICE.
- WOW.
IT LOOKS GOOD.
LORENZO'S ALL SET, MAN.
- THIS IS IT.
NOW WE'RE NOT LEAVING.
- OH. WAIT,
DON'T MAKE IT TOO GOOD.
YOU GUYS COULD STAY
FOREVER.
[upbeat music]
- LET'S DO THIS.
* *
- BETTY, WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO
SHOPPING IN THE WINERY WITH ME?
- CERTAINLY.
I WOULD LOVE TO.
- SO, ROGER'S GONNA
STAY BEHIND
TO HANG OUT WITH HIS DAD,
AND ME AND BETTY
ARE GONNA GO WINE TASTING.
WE'RE "THE PINK TEAM."
I FEEL LIKE THE BOYS
NEED THE BOY TIME
AND THE GIRLS
NEED THE GIRL TIME.
- YEAH, THIS IS WHERE
I ALWAYS LIKED IT.
RIGHT OFF--
RIGHT ALONG IN THERE.
- THAT'S REALLY GOOD
IN THE SPRING.
- THERE'S A LOT OF NESTS
THERE.
- NOT SO GOOD NOW?
- WELL, IT MAY STILL BE.
- I THINK WE'RE, UH,
GONNA HEAD BACK IN THE MORNING,
BUT I'M GLAD WE GOT--
GOT TO COME UP
AND SPEND SOME TIME,
YOU KNOW?
- IT MEANT A LOT TO ME
WHEN YOU GUYS COME UP AND--
- I TRIED
TO PUT JENNI THROUGH
EVERY MAINE THING
THERE IS TO DO
WHILE WE WERE UP HERE,
YOU KNOW?
- YEAH.
MAKE HER A MAINE GIRL.
- DOES SHE GET THE MAINE STAMP
OF APPROVAL?
- SHE'S BEEN--SHE'S BEEN, UH,
APPROVED, YES.
- I GUESS WHAT I'M TRYING
TO SAY IS, THINGS, UH,
THINGS HAVE BEEN GOING
REALLY WELL LATELY, AND...
- GOOD.
- YOU KNOW, UM,
I THINK I'M READY TO
AND I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE IT
TO THAT NEXT STEP,
WHICH OBVIOUSLY IS,
YOU KNOW, GETTING ENGAGED,
AND IT'S SOMETHING
THAT I'VE DEFINITELY
PUT SOME SERIOUS THOUGHT
INTO LATELY,
AND I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE
JENNI'S THE GIRL FOR ME, SO--
- GOOD.
- YOU KNOW?
- I'LL TELL YOU, YOU TWO--
- I WANT TO MAKE SURE MY FAMILY,
UH, AGREES WITH ME.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S ALL.
- I AGREE WITH YOU.
I SEE THE CHANGE IN YOU
THAT NO OTHER GIRL
HAS EVER DONE TO YOU.
- MM-HMM.
- AND YOU CERTAINLY KNOW JENNI
BETTER THAN I DO,
BUT WHAT--WHAT WE KNOW
OF JENNI, WE LOVE HER.
YOU COULDN'T FIND
A NICER GIRL.
- I'M NOT
A SUPER EMOTIONAL GUY,
BUT IT'S ALWAYS GOOD TO HAVE
YOUR DAD'S STAMP OF APPROVAL.
YOU KNOW,
IT MAKES ME FEEL GOOD.
- YOU TWO SEEM TO BE RIGHT
FOR EACH OTHER.
I MAY BE JUMPING THE GUN,
BUT I-I CONSIDER HER
PART OF OUR FAMILY NOW.
I MEAN, SHE'S A SWEETHEART
AND WE LOVE HER,
AND, UH, YOU GUYS ARE GONNA
BE REAL HAPPY TOGETHER.
- *'CAUSE IT'S OUR TURN,
BABE *
* AND WE'RE GONNA LEARN
TO DO THIS RIGHT *
* YEAH, I'M SORRY
THAT IT'S TAKEN YEARS *
* I NEVER WANTED
TO FEEL LIKE THIS *
* READY OR NOT *
* HERE I COME *
- JUST TO THINK,
HE WAS IN YOUR BELLY
THE WHOLE TIME WE WERE
IN THE SHORE HOUSE.
- OH, MY GOD.
HE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS YOUR BABY.
- OH, YEAH.
WE'RE LOBSTER TIME.
- YOU CAUGHT 'EM.
YOU GOTTA PUT 'EM IN.
- WHAT?
GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M NOT LISTENING
TO THEM SCREAM.
- [laughs]
- [sighs]
LOBSTERS DO NOT SCREAM
WHEN BOILED.
- THEY DON'T SCREAM.
- THEY "EEK." EEEEH!
- IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL BETTER NOW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO STAY
WITH YOUR MOMMY, RIGHT?
JUST ME AND YOU?
- YOU LOVE MOMMY, RIGHT?
DADDY'S ANNOYING, RIGHT?
KEEP TALKING TO HIM,
'CAUSE HE'S YOUR BEST FRIEND.