- I'’M SORRY, BUT I CAN'’T SIT
IN A CAR FOR AN HOUR.
I HAVE NO ENERGY.
MY STOMACH HURTS.
AND I JUST NEED
TO GET HOME AND REST
BECAUSE I JUST
DON'’T FEEL RIGHT.
BABE! I'’M SCARED.
- WHAT?
- I THINK MY WATER BROKE.
- I'’M NOT READY FOR THIS.
- MY WATER BROKE.
- WHAT? YOU'’RE LYING.
- I SWEAR TO GOD.
- THAT'’S EARLY.
- I'’M JUST SCARED.
I REALLY DON'’T WANT TO TALK.
[choked up]
PLEASE DON'’T MAKE ME TALK.
- YOU'’RE GONNA BE FINE, HON.
OKAY?
- [crying]
YOU'’RE MAKING ME SO STRESSED.
- HEY, HEY, HEY.
- I DON'’T LIKE IT.
- YOU'’RE GONNA DO GREAT.
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- JUST THINK, BABE,
HE'’S ALMOST HERE.
- NOTHING TO BE SCARED ABOUT.
YOU'’RE GONNA DO GREAT.
- I'’M JUST SCARED.
I REALLY DON'’T WANT TO TALK.
[choked up]
PLEASE DON'’T MAKE ME TALK.
- YOU'’RE GONNA BE FINE, HON.
OKAY?
- [crying]
YOU'’RE MAKING ME SO STRESSED.
- HEY, HEY, HEY.
- I DON'’T LIKE IT.
- YOU'’RE GONNA DO GREAT.
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT,
NOW WHAT WE'’RE GONNA DO
IS WE'’RE GONNA PUT ONE LEG
UP ON HERE
AND ONE LEG UP OVER THERE,
AND YOU JUST TRY YOUR BEST
PUSHING, OKAY?
BUT YOU WANT TO USE
YOUR DIAPHRAGM TO HELP PUSH
THAT BABY DOWN
WITH THE CONTRACTION, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- AND BEAR DOWN.
HARD, HARD, HARD, HARD.
DON'’T LET THE AIR OUT.
- AWESOME, AWESOME.
THAT'’S AWESOME.
TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
LET IT OUT.
NOW TAKE ANOTHER DEEP BREATH.
- ONE MORE TIME.
- YOU'’RE GONNA DO GREAT.
YOU'’RE GONNA DO GREAT.
YOU'’RE DOING GREAT, NICOLE.
- YOU MAY JUST BE
A FEW PUSHES AWAY.
- COUPLE PUSHES AWAY,
THE DOCTOR SAID.
- OH, REALLY?
- NO WAY.
- THAT'’S AWESOME.
- NICOLE, YOU'’RE A PRO!
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH.
- SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE--
YOU'’RE DOING AWESOME.
- [grunts]
- TEN.
- YOU'’RE DOING GREAT.
- LOTS OF PRESSURE.
- NICOLE, YOU'’RE DOING AWESOME.
- EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
- YOU'’RE DOING AWESOME.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOU'’RE DOING AWESOME, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT?
GIVE ME A LITTLE PUSH.
GOOD, HON.
FINISH IT OFF.
- HERE HE COMES.
- [laughs]
- HERE WE GO.
LITTLE MORE, LITTLE MORE.
- [groans]
- YAY!
- [laughing]
- A BOY! THERE YOU GO.
- GREAT JOB.
- OKAY.
[Lorenzo bawling]
- [laughing]
ALL RIGHT.
AWESOME!
- YOU DID IT!
- GREAT JOB.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- HI, LORENZO.
- OH, OH.
- I LOVE YOU.
[Lorenzo crying]
- THROUGHOUT YOUR LIFE,
YOU DEFINITELY HAVE
MOMENTS YOU'’RE NEVER,
EVER GONNA FORGET.
BUT NOTHING, BY FAR,
COMPARES TO THIS.
- MM-HMM.
- NOTHING.
- I'’M PREGNANT.
WILL YOU BE THE GODMOTHER?
- OH, MY GOD!
- WHAT?
- OH, MY GOD.
- YOU'’RE PREGNANT?
- HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
- IS THAT IT?
- YES, IT IS.
- EW!
- YOU CREATED THAT.
- IT'’S A BOY!
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
- I'’M NOT READY.
- ME EITHER.
LOOK HOW SMALL
HE'’S GONNA BE.
[squeals and laughs]
- DID YOU FEEL THAT?
- [gasps]
HE'’S KICKING!
I'’M PROUD OF YOU.
YOUR MOM'’S PROUD.
EVERYONE'’S PROUD OF YOU.
ONCE HE'’S OUT,
I GUARANTEE YOU,
YOU'’RE GONNA BE FEELING
AWESOME.
- PROMISE?
- I PROMISE.
- [laughing tearfully]
THE BABY'’S HERE.
[Lorenzo crying]
- YOU LOOK JUST LIKE DADDY.
- ♪ SO TRUST ME,
AND I'’LL TRUST YOU ♪
- [crying]
I'’M JUST HAPPY...
[sniffles]
BECAUSE...
I'’VE ALWAYS WANTED A KID,
AND HE'’S HERE...
AND IT'’S WITH JIONNI,
AND HE'’S HEALTHY
AND BEAUTIFUL.
AND I LOVE HIM.
HE'’S PERFECT.
- NO WAY.
- HERE HE IS.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- SEE, ROG?
- OH, MY GOOD LORD.
- HEY.
- OH, MY LORD.
- THAT'’S AUNT JENNI
AND UNCLE ROGER.
- I TAKE BACK WHAT I SAID.
[laughter]
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
[Lorenzo cries]
OH, MY GOD.
- ISN'’T HE CUTE?
- HE REALLY IS.
- YEAH, RIGHT?
- AND I WENT ON A WHOLE THING
ABOUT BABIES DON'’T GET CUTE
FOR A COUPLE WEEKS--
HE'’S REALLY CUTE.
- HE'’S CUTE.
- HE IS CUTE.
- GOT A FULL HEAD
OF HAIR, HUH?
- YEAH.
- HURT LIKE A BITCH.
- AW.
- SHE LIKES IT.
SHE LIKES IT.
- OH, [bleep].
SORRY, ROG.
- NO.
- I HAVE TO TAKE
THE BABY INTO THE NURSERY.
THE QUICKER WE GET THE BABY
INTO THE NURSERY,
THE QUICKER NICOLE
CAN GO UP TO HER ROOM.
- WE HAVEN'’T EVEN BEEN PARENTS
FOR FIVE MINUTES,
AND RIGHT AWAY,
THEY'’RE TAKING LORENZO,
AND WE'’RE LIKE, "NO!"
LIKE, "KEEP MY KID HERE."
OUR KID.
I'’M SO TIRED.
- YEAH, GET SOME REST.
- YEAH, WE'’LL LEAVE YOU BE.
I'’M GLAD THAT WE WERE HERE FOR
THIS AND WE WEREN'’T IN MAINE.
THAT'’S AWESOME. WE--
- I CAN'’T BELIEVE IT.
THIS IS MY SON.
IT'’S LIKE, I DID THIS.
I CAN'’T GIVE YOU A WORD
TO EXPLAIN THE FIRST TIME
YOU SEE YOUR KID.
- BEAUTIFUL.
- THERE'’S NO WORD THAT COULD
POSSIBLY--IT'’S JUST LIKE--
- AMAZING.
- THERE'’S NO WORD.
- OH! [laughs]
- OH, MY GOSH.
- OHH.
- LOOK AT THAT HEAD OF HAIR.
- HOW CUTE.
[baby crying]
- HE REALLY HAS
A FULL HEAD OF HAIR.
GOT THE ONE EYE OPEN,
LOOKING AROUND.
- HE'’S SO CUTE.
- WOW.
- YOUR GIRL'’S ALL GROWN UP.
- I KNOW.
LORENZO IS THE MOST PRECIOUS
LITTLE BABY
I'’VE EVER SEEN
IN THE WORLD.
LIKE, HE DOESN'’T LOOK
LIKE AN OLD, SCRUNCHY MAN
OR AN ALIEN BABY
OR A CONEHEAD.
HE'’S, LIKE,
JUST PERFECTLY SHAPED.
HE'’S ADORABLE. HE'’S SHIVERING,
WHICH WAS SO CUTE.
- AW.
- AND HE'’S, LIKE, GOT
HIS LITTLE LIP QUIVER GOING.
AND HE'’S LOOKING AT ME,
AND I'’M JUST, LIKE, IN TEARS,
FALLING IN LOVE WITH HIM.
- THANK YOU.
- BYE, BABY.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[Jenni taps on glass,
smooches]
- [laughing]
HE'’S LIKE, "GET AWAY, GET AWAY.
ENOUGH'’S ENOUGH."
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS, DRIVE SAFE.
- LOVE YOU GUYS.
- YEAH, WE'’LL KEEP
IN TOUCH, OKAY?
- YES.
- DEFINITELY. LOVE YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- KEEP US UPDATED, DEFINITELY.
- YEAH, WE'’LL KEEP IN TOUCH.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, DRIVE SAFE.
- KEEP US POSTED.
- WILL DO.
- THANK YOU.
- GOOD NIGHT, LORENZO.
I LOVE YOU.
- GOOD NIGHT, LITTLE BUDDY.
- GOOD NIGHT, POOP.
- YO, GET THE [bleep] OUT
FROM HERE.
I'’VE SEEN PLENTY OF MICE,
BUT IT'’S DIFFERENT
WHEN THEY'’RE IN YOUR HOUSE.
- [squeaks]
- BET THAT HURT HIS...
- SO YOU GUYS HAVE
ANY OTHER QUESTIONS?
- IF SHE EATS A LOT
OF CHOCOLATE.
CAN SHE MAKE CHOCOLATE MILK?
- [giggles]
- NO.
- OW, DON'’T MAKE ME LAUGH.
MY VAGINA HURTS.
- ♪ I LOVE MAKING LOVE
TO YOU ♪
- ♪ I LOVE MAKING LOVE ♪
- ♪ IT'’S ALL
THAT I WANT TO DO ♪
- ♪ BABY ♪
- ♪ LET ME SAY OOH ♪
- [squeaks]
- WHAT--
YO.
GET THE [bleep] OUT
FROM HERE!
NO [bleep] WAY.
I'’M AN OUTDOORSY GUY.
I GREW UP IN MAINE.
SEEN PLENTY OF MICE,
BUT IT'’S DIFFERENT
WHEN THEY'’RE IN YOUR HOUSE.
NO [bleep] WAY.
WHERE'’D IT GO?
- [squeaks]
- RIGHT THERE.
THERE IT IS.
GOT YA, [bleep].
OH, [bleep]!
I HAD YOU TOO,
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
WELL, WE TRIED, BUBBA.
WE HAD HIM.
IT'’S A LITTLE DISCONCERTING.
IT'’S YOUR HOME, YOU KNOW.
YOU DON'’T WANT CRITTERS
LIVING IN YOUR HOME.
[smooching]
SO I WAS DOWNSTAIRS
HAVING MY BREAKFAST...
- WHAT NOW?
- AND I SAW MR. MOUSE
RUN ACROSS THE FLOOR.
- NO, YOU DID NOT.
- I SWEAR.
- YOU GOT UP HERE.
- I SWEAR TO GOD.
- NO, YOU DIDN'’T.
- I'’M MOVING OUT.
- I ACTUALLY CAUGHT IT.
- NO, YOU DIDN'’T.
- TEMPORARILY.
AND THEN I LOST IT,
LIKE AN IDIOT.
- DUDE, WE CAN'’T LIVE HERE.
- IT'’S A MOUSE, JENNI.
I HIGHLY LIKELY
WOULD'’VE SCARED JENNI WITH IT
IF I HAD CAUGHT IT,
YOU KNOW.
I MEAN,
SHE WAS STILL SLEEPING.
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE CRAWLED
IN BED NEXT TO HER WITH--
- ARE YOU [bleep]
KIDDING ME?
- I WOULDN'’T HAVE PUT IT
IN THE BED BY ITSELF,
BUT WITH THE TUPPERWARE DISH,
YEAH.
- THAT'’S NOT NICE.
YOU DON'’T DO THAT TO PEOPLE.
- WHAT DO I DO TO YOU
THAT'’S EVER NICE?
ALMOST NOTHING.
- IT'’S A NEW HOUSE.
- THEN WE'’LL FIND DEAD MICE
IN OUR PLATES.
- THAT'’S [bleep] DISGUSTING.
I'’VE NEVER HAD THAT HAPPEN
IN MY 27 YEARS OF LIFE.
EVEN THE SHORE HOUSE
WASN'’T THIS FILTHY.
[indistinct chatter]
- HI.
- LOOK, HIS HAIR'’S COMBED.
- WASH ALL YOUR HANDS.
- THANK YOU.
- LOOK HOW DIFFERENT HE LOOKS
FROM LAST NIGHT.
OH, WOW.
- I'’M BREASTFEEDING
REALLY GOOD.
- YOU ARE? OH!
- ARE YOU?
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- DAD.
- LET ME WASH MY HANDS.
- HE ACTUALLY HAS WAY MORE HAIR
THAN MIKEY DOES.
- MORE HAIR.
- I LOVE WHEN HE SMILES.
HE'’S LIKE--
- SMILES?
- THAT'’S GAS.
HE'’S POOPING ON YOU.
- YOU KNOW,
I COULD JUST TELL
FROM MY FAMILY, LIKE,
THEIR LITTLE BROTHER
JUST HAD A BABY.
LIKE, IT MEANT SOMETHING
FOR EVERYBODY.
- WE'’RE IN THE CLUB NOW--
THE KIDS CLUB.
- NICOLE, DID YOU HAVE TO PUSH
FOR A WHILE, OR WAS IT--
- DAVID, DON'’T.
- I PUSHED FOR, LIKE,
15 MINUTES.
- 15 MINUTES?
- IT WAS WEIRD, '’CAUSE I DIDN'’T
REALLY FEEL MY LEGS.
- [laughs]
- THAT'’S HOW I WAS.
- JUST NUMB?
- BUT I WAS JUST LIKE,
"I THINK I'’M DOING IT RIGHT."
- LOOK HOW DARK HE IS.
- YEAH.
- AND I DIDN'’T POOP.
- THAT'’S ALWAYS A PLUS.
- THAT'’S A--
THAT'’S AN ACCOMPLISHMENT.
- THAT'’S MORE
THAN WE NEEDED TO KNOW.
- I HAD SO MUCH GAS,
I REALLY THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO.
- HE WAS DOWN THERE.
HE WAS, UH--
- I FARTED IN HIS FACE.
[laughter]
- HE WAS CHECKING
BEFORE HE STARTED.
SO SHE'’S LIKE, BOOP!
SHE GOES, "JIONNI, I'’M SO SORRY.
POOP, I'’M SO SORRY.
I DIDN'’T MEAN TO DO THAT.
DON'’T HATE ME."
AND, LIKE,
SHE WAS APOLOGIZING TO ME.
AND HE'’S LIKE, "DON'’T WORRY."
- '’CAUSE I THOUGHT
IT EMBARRASSED HIM.
- "THAT'’S ALL NORMAL."
- SO SORRY.
- SO THEN AT THE END,
AT THE WAY END,
HE WAS JUST LIKE--
- HE WAS STITCHING ME.
- STITCHING, DOING EVERYTHING,
AND YOU HEAR, BOOP!
HE GOES, "THAT ONE GOT ME."
[laughter]
AND THEN THE THING--
I SAW THAT THING
COME OUT AT THE END.
- OH, THE PLACENTA?
- THE PLACENTA?
- HE GOES, "ALL RIGHT,
I'’M ABOUT TO PULL IT OUT."
AND HE GOES, "WAIT A SECOND."
HE'’S LIKE, "I DON'’T WANT
TO MAKE A MESS ON YOU."
HE PUTS A SHEET
RIGHT OVER HER THING.
IT JUST POURED.
A GALLON OF BLOOD
POURED INTO THIS THING.
I WAS LIKE--
UH, IT WAS BAD.
IT'’S A STINGRAY.
YOU KNOW, WITH THE FLAPS,
THE TAIL, SLOPPY AND WET.
THAT'’S WHAT I SEE RIGHT NOW,
A STINGRAY...
FLAPPING HIS WINGS
OUT OF THE VAGINA.
IT'’S DISGUSTING.
- I WOULD'’VE STEPPED OUT.
- YEAH.
[laughter]
- I'’LL BE OUTSIDE.
- YEAH.
- I FEEL LIKE
I'’M GONNA PASS OUT NOW.
- I'’LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- SERIOUSLY.
- TAKE YOUR TIME.
DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
[hip-hop music]
♪ ♪
- OH, MY GOD.
MY WHOLE BODY HURTS
FROM YESTERDAY.
- I KNOW.
IT WAS AN EXHAUSTING DAY.
WHO HAS A BABY
FOR 27 HOURS?
- [laughs]
- NICOLE, THAT'’S WHO.
- UH-HUH.
I CAN'’T IMAGINE HOW SHE FEELS.
- YEAH, I'’M GLAD WE WEREN'’T
IN MAINE WHEN THAT HAPPENED.
- [burps]
I JUST CAN'’T BELIEVE
IT HAPPENED TODAY--
THIS MORNING.
- I KNOW.
- LIKE, I'’M EXCITED
TO GO TO MAINE,
BUT IT'’S LIKE, MAN,
I HAVE TO WAIT ANOTHER WEEK
TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
- HE IS A CUTE BABY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'’M JUST GONNA SIT
OUT HERE FOR A MINUTE,
GET SOME COLOR.
IT'’S GOOD VITAMINS
IN THE SUN.
- OH, [bleep].
BIG DRAGONFLY.
- GOD, I HATE ALL [bleep]
LIVING CREATURES.
- THIS IS LIKE A [bleep]
PETTING ZOO AROUND HERE.
- I FEEL LIKE WE'’RE IN MAINE
RIGHT NOW,
WITH ALL THE BUGS
IN OUR BACKYARD.
- I'’M EXCITED.
I HAVEN'’T BEEN UP THERE
SINCE DAD'’S SURGERY.
IT'’LL DEFINITELY BE
A NICE LITTLE NEEDED VACATION.
I WANT TO, UM,
REALLY GET TO SEE
HOW HE'’S DOING TOO,
'’CAUSE HE'’LL NEVER TELL ME
THE TRUTH OVER THE PHONE.
MY DAD, UNFORTUNATELY,
HAD A HEART ATTACK
AND HAD TO HAVE
A QUADRUPLE BYPASS.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
TOTALLY DIFFERENT,
GOING UP THIS TIME
TO ENJOY IT,
SPEND SOME TIME WITH DAD,
SEE HOW HE'’S DOING HEALTH-WISE.
SO I THINK I HAVE
EVERYTHING UP THERE WE NEED.
CAN YOU THINK OF ANYTHING
YOU NEED FOR YOURSELF?
- I'’M GONNA PACK
SHORE STORE SWEATS,
SPANDEX, AND A COUPLE
HOOCHIE OUTFITS.
WE'’RE GOOD TO GO.
- WHAT DO YOU NEED
HOOCHIE OUTFITS FOR?
- I DON'’T KNOW--YOU NEVER KNOW
IF YOU NEED A HOOCHIE OUTFIT.
- THERE'’S NO CLUBS
UP THERE, BABE.
THERE'’S NO--
- NICE DINNER OUTFITS?
- THERE'’S ONE RESTAURANT.
- I DON'’T WANT TO PUT ALL
THE PRESSURE ON BETTY COOKING.
- YOU CAN COOK AT CAMP.
IT'’S NOT GONNA BE
ANYTHING DU JOUR,BUT...
- DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT DU JOURMEANS?
- I BELIEVE IT'’S FRENCH
FOR FANCY...
LIKE DELUXE.
BUT YOU CHECK IT OUT,
AND YOU TELL ME.
IS IT D-U-J...
- DU JOUR.
- O-U-R?
- "AVAILABLE AND BEING SERVED
ON THE DAY."
- YEAH, WHAT'’S UP?
- THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH FANCY.
- I WAS PRETTY [bleep] CLOSE.
- WE ALL KNOW DU JOUR
IS PART OF FOOD.
- YOU DIDN'’T KNOW WHAT IT MEANS,
'’CAUSE YOU HAD TO GOOGLE IT.
SO SHUT THE [bleep] UP.
- YEAH, BUT I WANTED TO MAKE
SURE IT WAS ACCURATE.
SO THAT MEANS "OF THE DAY."
- I DATE YOU FOR YOUR
INTELLIGENCE, CLEARLY...
- NOT FANCY.
- NOT THE SIZE
OF YOUR BREASTS.
[cymbal crashes]
- I CLEARLY DATE YOU
FOR YOUR MUSCLES,
NOT THE SIZE OF YOUR HEAD.
- OH. THAT HEAD.
- [laughs]
[yawns] I THINK I'’M GONNA
GO LAY DOWN AGAIN.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO COME UP THERE
AND MAKE SWEET, SWEET LOVE
TO YOU?
- UGH. NO.
- BABE?
- NO.
- MAKE LOVE?
OKAY.
- THIS IS MY NEW BEST FRIEND.
- HE'’S SO CUTE,
AND I JUST, LIKE--
- EVEN HIS FARTS SMELL GOOD.
I LOVE THE SMELL
OF HIS FARTS.
IS THAT WEIRD?
- ROGER WANTS TO DO IT...
- I JUST THOUGHT
IT MIGHT PUT SOME IDEAS
IN THERE.
- THE MORE TRADITIONAL WAY,
WHICH IS GET ENGAGED,
GET MARRIED.
- I'’M KIND OF GETTING
TAG-TEAMED HERE A LITTLE BIT
BY EVERYBODY, YOU KNOW.
- NOW I JUST NEED A RING.
[line trilling]
- BABE, JENNI'’S CALLING YOU.
- HELLO?
- HEY, BOO.
HOW YOU FEELING?
- TIRED.
- AW.
HOW'’S THE BABY?
- HE'’S GOOD.
HE JUST, UM,
GOT SOME MILK,
SO HE'’S SLEEPING.
- WHEN ARE YOU GONNA LEAVE
THE HOSPITAL?
- TUESDAY.
- AW, ARE YOU EXCITED
TO GO HOME WITH HIM?
- YEAH.
WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO MAINE?
- WE'’RE LEAVING
TUESDAY MORNING.
- ARE YOU EXCITED?
- MM-HMM.
- WHEN I THINK
ABOUT ROGER AND JENNI
GOING UP TO MAINE,
I'’M JUST THINKING
MAYBE HE'’LL POP THE QUESTION.
HE'’S GONNA PROPOSE TO YOU
IN THE WOODS...
- [snickers]
- ON A FOUR-WHEELER.
- IN MAINE.
- GOD, NO.
JIONNI SAID THANK YOU
FOR COMING TO VISIT US.
- OH, OF COURSE.
I CAN'’T WAIT
TO COME BACK UP.
I'’LL CALL YOU BEFORE MAINE.
AND I'’LL CALL YOU
EVERY DAY OUT THERE
TO MAKE SURE YOU'’RE DOING
ALL RIGHT
WITH LORENZO AT HOME.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL, HAVE FUN.
- I WILL.
TELL JIONNI I LOVE HIM,
AND I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU, BYE.
- BYE.
OH, MY GOD,
SHE SOUNDS SO TIRED.
[Cameron Rafati'’s XOX]
- ♪ '’CAUSE I'’M ON MY OWN ♪
♪ TRYING TO BE
WHERE YOU CALL HOME ♪
[Lorenzo cooing]
♪ AND I'’M ALL ON MY OWN ♪
♪ BUT SOMEWHERE WHERE
THE SATELLITES STILL FIND ME ♪
- GOOD JOB TODAY.
- LOVE YOU.
- ♪ IF I LOOK BACK ♪
♪ I CAN SEE YOU ♪
[line trilling]
- HELLO?
- HEY, WHAT'’S UP, BUDDY?
- HEY, ROGER.
- WHAT'’S GOING ON?
- HOW'’S IT GOING?
- NOTHING. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- OUT AT CAMP.
- YOU'’RE OUT AT CAMP, HUH?
- I AM.
- JENNI AND I WERE TALKING,
AND, YOU KNOW,
WE'’D DEFINITELY LIKE
TO STAY WITH YOU GUYS
PROBABLY ONE NIGHT,
AND THEN IF WE HAVE ENOUGH TIME,
I WOULD LOVE TO SPEND
A NIGHT OUT AT CAMP
WITH JENNI.
- GREAT. YOU'’RE ALWAYS WELCOME.
YEAH.
- THANKS.
- THIS IS THE TIME OF YEAR.
IT'’S JUST...
- YEAH, I LOVE IT
THIS TIME OF YEAR UP THERE.
BUT HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
HOW'’S EVERYTHING GOING
WITH YOU?
- I'’M GOOD.
I'’M A LOT BETTER THAN I WAS.
I'’M COMING AROUND.
- RIGHT.
- SO I'’M GETTING BETTER
EVERY DAY.
- THE MOST IMPORTANT PART
OF GOING BACK TO MAINE FOR ME
IS CHECKING ON MY DAD
AND CHECKING ON HIS HEALTH,
YOU KNOW.
THAT'’S MY MAIN CONCERN,
MY DAD'’S GETTING OLDER,
I DON'’T KNOW HOW MUCH MORE TIME
I'’M GONNA HAVE WITH HIM.
AND, UM, LOVE MY DAD,
YOU KNOW.
HE'’S MY BEST FRIEND.
DEFINITELY LOOKING FORWARD
TO IT.
I HAVEN'’T SEEN YOU
IN A WHILE.
WE JUST WANT TO COME UP THERE
AND UNWIND,
RELAX A LITTLE BIT,
AND SPEND A LITTLE TIME
WITH YOU GUYS.
- ANYTIME YOU WANT TO COME,
WE'’RE HAPPY
TO HAVE YOU HERE.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL,
YOU GUYS ENJOY YOUR TIME
OUT AT THE CABIN,
AND I WILL TALK TO YOU SOON.
- ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
- NO MORE ME AND YOU.
GOT A LITTLE BUDDY WITH US
FROM NOW ON.
YOU COOL WITH THAT?
- YEAH.
- ME TOO.
- HE'’S MY NEW BEST FRIEND.
YOU'’RE THE OLD.
- THAT'’S NOT COOL.
THAT'’S NOT--
- JIONNI, I'’M KIDDING.
- YOU'’RE NOT KIDDING.
- EVERY TIME I LOOK
AT LORENZO,
I JUST THINK
HOW AMAZING HE IS,
AND KNOWING THAT, LIKE,
HE'’S OUR CHILD,
IT'’S JUST--
YOU KNOW, IT'’S SPECIAL.
- HE'’S SO CUTE,
AND I JUST, LIKE--
- EVEN HIS FARTS SMELL GOOD.
I LOVE THE SMELL OF HIS FARTS.
IS THAT WEIRD?
I LOVE THE SMELL
OF HIS [bleep].
- HEY, GUYS.
- HEY.
- HOW YOU DOING?
- WHAT'’S UP?
- NOT MUCH.
- WHAT'’S GOING ON?
- HOW WAS YOUR DAY TODAY?
DID YOU GET SOME SLEEP FINALLY?
- NOT YET.
- NOT YET?
HOW'’S THE BABY DOING? ALL RIGHT?
- GOOD.
- HE'’S BREASTFEEDING.
- LATCHING ON?
- YEAH.
- GOOD, GOOD. EXCELLENT.
[Lorenzo coos]
ALL RIGHT, I'’LL DO THE
CIRCUMCISION TOMORROW MORNING.
[Lorenzo cries]
- WILL HE FEEL IT?
- WELL, THE MEDICINE SHOULD HELP
A LITTLE BIT,
BUT HE'’LL FEEL A LITTLE BIT.
HE MAY BE
A LITTLE CRANKY TOMORROW.
- I DON'’T LIKE IT.
I--IT'’S GONNA HURT.
I-I CAN'’T--
HE'’S GONNA BE CRYING.
- DO YOU REMEMBER
YOUR CIRCUMCISION?
- TO THIS DAY.
- NO, YOU DON'’T.
- IT WAS PAINFUL.
- HE'’LL BE FINE.
YOU DON'’T REMEMBER.
- IF YOU TAP MY BALLS,
I CRY.
- [clicks tongue]
- IMAGINE MY WIENER
GETTING CHOPPED UP.
- OKAY, BUT YOU WERE, LIKE,
A DAY OLD.
YOU DON'’T REMEMBER
THOSE THINGS.
- YOU'’RE GONNA FEEL IT.
- CAN WE KEEP THE FORESKIN?
- [chuckles]
ALL RIGHT.
- I'’D BE HUMILIATED
IF MY MOTHER
WAS JUST LIKE,
"HERE'’S JIONNI'’S FORESKIN."
LIKE, "OH, MY SON WON
FIRST PLACE.
"OH, MY SON GOT
AN '’A'’ ON HIS TEST.
HERE'’S HIS FORESKIN."
IT'’S JUST NOT--
IT DOESN'’T FIT.
- BUT I LIKE SCRAPBOOKING.
- NOT FORESKIN.
- I'’LL SEE YOU
IN THE MORNING.
- I DON'’T WANT HIS FORESKIN.
WHAT A WEIRDO.
- I'’M GONNA DO
THE CIRCUMCISION.
- BYE, WIENER.
DON'’T HURT HIM.
- WHAT IF HE CUTS THE TIP
OF THE HEAD OFF?
AW, HIS LITTLE WIENER.
- LOOK AT THIS CRITTER
IN HERE.
THAT A COCKROACH?
WHOA, COME HERE.
- WHAT IS IT? EW.
DON'’T FREAK ME OUT.
AND NOW I'’M GONNA THROW UP
MY [bleep] DINNER.
I DON'’T DO COCKROACHES.
- ♪ STEADY YOUR HEART ♪
♪ LIKE A TRAIN CAR
ROLLING HOME ♪
♪ WHERE WE'’RE GOING,
WE JUST DON'’T KNOW... ♪
- THINK HE DRANK ENOUGH?
SHOULD WE ASK THE NURSE?
[beep]
JUST SAY WE HAVE A QUESTION.
[line rings]
- HI, CAN I HELP YOU?
- HI, WE NEED TO SEE
OUR NURSE.
- OKAY, I'’LL BE RIGHT IN.
- OKAY.
OH, THAT WAS HER.
[knock at door]
YES?
- HI.
- THIS IS ALL HE DRANK.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
ONE OF THE BIGGEST KEYS IN LIFE
TO BEING A GOOD PARENT
IS KNOWING WHAT YOU KNOW
AND KNOWING WHAT YOU DON'’T KNOW.
I KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT A NEWBORN.
NOTHING.
NOW'’S THE TIME TO ASK.
[beep]
[Lorenzo whimpering]
- I THINK HE'’S DONE EATING.
- SHOULD HE FINISH IT?
- HE DOESN'’T HAVE TO,
BUT HE CAN.
[beep]
- SHOULD WE HOLD HIM
LIKE THAT FOR BOTTLES?
- IS THAT SWADDLE OKAY?
[beep]
HE'’S FINE UNDER THIS THING?
LIKE, NOT TOO COLD
OR ANYTHING?
[beep]
WHY WAS HE CHOKING?
'’CAUSE IT WAS COMING OUT
MAYBE A LITTLE FASTER?
[beep]
CAN HE DRINK
IF HE'’S IN THE SWADDLE?
AND CAN I DO IT
FROM IN MY ARMS?
- YEAH.
- HE'’S HIGH ENOUGH?
DOES EVERYBODY ASK YOU
QUESTIONS THAT ARE STUPID?
- NO STUPID QUESTIONS.
CALL ME IF YOU NEED
ANYTHING ELSE, ALL RIGHT?
- THANK YOU.
- YOU'’RE WELCOME.
[Lorenzo fussing]
- HE PEED.
- CHANGE HIM.
- I CAN'’T WAIT
TO CHANGE DIAPERS.
THIS IS THE WHOLE PART
OF HAVING BABIES
IS CHANGING DIAPERS.
ALL PEOPLE TALK ABOUT
- YOU GONNA PEE
IN DADDY'’S FACE?
HE'’S GONNA PEE ON US.
- ON YOU.
- I DON'’T MIND LORENZO
PEEING IN MY FACE
AS LONG AS HIS PEE-PEE
DOESN'’T GET IN MY MOUTH.
[Lorenzo cooing]
- GOT THE HICCUPS?
HE'’S GOT THE HICCUPS.
- REALLY?
- DO YOU PAT HIS BACK
IF HE'’S GOT THE HICCUPS?
- SCARE HIM.
BOO.
- [clicks tongue]
HE STILLS GOT '’EM.
- WE'’LL JUST ASK.
[beep]
SHE'’S GONNA THINK
WE'’RE IDIOTS.
[line rings]
- HI, CAN I HELP YOU?
- CAN HE LAY ON HIS BACK
WITH HICCUPS?
- YES.
- OKAY.
- HE'’S FINE.
- OKAY, THANKS.
- YOU'’RE WELCOME.
- SHE THINKS
WE'’RE ASS[bleep].
- NO, WE JUST DON'’T KNOW.
THERE'’S SO MUCH
THAT WE HAVE TO LEARN.
IT'’S STILL A RESPONSIBILITY
THAT I WAS NEVER, LIKE,
EXPECTING OR AWARE OF.
YOU CAN'’T PRACTICE IT.
THIS IS YOUR SON.
LIKE, HE DEPENDS ON YOU AND I
TO RAISE HIM.
WE GOTTA REALLY
STEP IT UP AND...
AND...
- BE PARENTS.
IT'’S JUST HICCUPS.
I USED TO GET THEM ALL THE TIME
WHEN I DRANK WINE.
[toy squeaks]
IT GOES AWAY.
PROMISE.
[gentle rock music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ WE DON'’T NEED
NO CHUBBY DOGS ♪
♪ WE DON'’T NEED NO-- ♪
LOOK AT THIS CRITTER
IN HERE.
LOOK AT THIS.
IS THAT A COCKROACH?
IF THAT'’S
A [bleep] COCKROACH--
IF THAT'’S A COCKROACH,
I'’M MOVING OUT OF HERE.
[bleep] SNEAKY LITTLE BA--
WHOA, COME HERE.
- WHAT IS IT? EW.
DON'’T FREAK ME OUT,
'’CAUSE I'’M GONNA BE OUT TONIGHT.
I DON'’T DO COCKROACHES.
- I DON'’T KNOW WHAT THIS IS.
IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE A COCKROACH,
BUT IT CAN'’T BE A COCKROACH.
WE LIVE IN A BRAND-NEW HOUSE.
- UGH.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
LOOK AT THIS.
TAKE A PICTURE OF THIS
WITH YOUR PHONE.
IT'’S GONNA RUN LIKE HELL.
YOU GOTTA GET A QUICK PICTURE.
- GAH!
EW, EW, EW.
- GET A PICTURE OF IT.
- I THINK THAT'’S
A COCKROACH, BABE.
WE CAN'’T BE HERE.
SOMEONE'’S GOTTA EXTERMINATE
THIS [bleep].
- THAT IS A COCKROACH.
I DON'’T KNOW.
- ROGER THINKS
IT'’S A COCKROACH,
AND NOW I'’M GONNA THROW UP
MY [bleep] DINNER.
ALL OUR DISHES ARE GONNA
HAVE TO BE WASHED, THEN,
AND EVERYTHING WE JUST ATE
IS CONTAMINATED.
- OH, HE'’S STILL ALIVE.
THAT [bleep] CAN TAKE A HIT.
- THAT MEANS IT'’S A COCKROACH.
THEY DON'’T DIE.
I'’M DEFINITELY CURIOUS
TO KNOW WHERE
THE COCKROACH QUEEN IS,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU SEE ONE,
THERE'’S, LIKE, A BILLION MORE.
SO I WONDER WHERE
THAT BITCH IS.
SHE'’S PROBABLY SOMEWHERE IN
BETWEEN TWO CRACKS IN THE WOOD.
- I'’M NOT SURE THAT'’S TRUE
WITH COCKROACHES.
- IT'’S WHAT THEY DO
IN THE COCKROACH-KILLING
COMMERCIALS.
- OH, THAT'’S WHERE YOU GET
YOUR INFORMATION FROM?
SAY NO MORE.
- CAN WE GO
TO A HOTEL, PLEASE?
I DON'’T WANT TO DO THIS.
I DON'’T LIKE BUGS.
[knock at door]
- COME IN.
- GOOD MORNING, GUYS.
- HEY.
- HOW YOU DOING?
HOW YOU FEELING?
- GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT,
DID YOU HAVE A GOOD NIGHT?
GOOD SLEEP?
- WELL, WE'’RE GETTING THERE.
- YOU GETTING THERE?
- HE WAS REALLY BAD LAST NIGHT.
- I DIDN'’T.
I WAS UP LAST NIGHT.
LIKE, HE WAS CHANGED.
WE TRIED FEEDING HIM.
AND HE WAS JUST SCREAMING,
LIKE--
- RIGHT.
- FOR HOURS.
- NOTHING. IT'’S NORMAL.
- YEAH. NO, I'’M JUST SAYING--
- HOPEFULLY THE BABY DOES ALL
OF ITS SCREAMING AND CRYING
HERE NOW
AND WHEN YOU GO HOME,
THE BABY WILL SLEEP
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
ALL RIGHT?
BUT THAT'’S ALL NORMAL.
ALL RIGHT, SO I'’M GONNA DO
THE CIRCUMCISION,
AND THEN WHEN I COME BACK,
I'’LL GIVE YOU INSTRUCTIONS
AS TO HOW TO TAKE CARE
OF ALL THAT.
- EVEN THOUGH LORENZO'’S
GONNA GO THROUGH
THIS HORRIBLE PAIN RIGHT NOW
WITH THE CIRCUMCISION,
HE'’S GONNA THANK ME.
I DON'’T KNOW IF IT'’S GONNA BE
EIGHTH-GRADE DANCE.
I DON'’T KNOW
IF IT'’S GONNA BE THE PROM.
- OR IN THE LOCKER ROOM
WHEN EVERYONE'’S CHANGING.
[laughing]
NO, YOU KNOW,
WHEN THERE'’S THAT ONE KID
THAT'’S NOT CIRCUMCISED
AND HE GETS MADE FUN OF...
- WHAT?
- OKAY, NEVER MIND.
BYE, WIENER.
- OH, BOY.
- MWAH.
- I'’LL BE BACK
IN A FEW MINUTES, GUYS.
- DON'’T HURT HIM.
- AW.
- [laughs]
- OH, BUMPED IT TWICE.
- YOU JUST HIT HIM.
- SEE YA.
- [laughing]
TAKE IT EASY, GUYS.
- WHAT IF HE CUTS THE TIP
OF THE HEAD OFF?
AW, HIS LITTLE WIENER.
- HE'’S GOT A NICE HEAD
OF HAIR NOW.
- WOULD IT BE BAD IF WE PUT
SOME KIND OF, LIKE,
HAIR GEL OR HAIRSPRAY?
- IS THAT A REAL QUESTION?
- WHAT'’S THE POINT OF HAVING
A BABY WITH THAT MUCH HAIR,
AND YOU CAN'’T STYLE IT?
- SOMETHING STINKS.
- [laughing]
- DID YOU [bleep]?
- NO, WE HIT A SKUNK.
- GOD.
[knock at door]
- IS HE BACK?
OH, NO!
- HE'’S BACK.
HE'’S FINE.
- WHERE'’S HIS FORESKIN?
UGH!
OH, MY GOD.
- LET ME SEE IT.
- LOOKS LIKE A...
- SNAIL.
- SAUSAGE.
- ALL RIGHT,
SO HE'’S ALL DONE.
- [gasps]
- HE'’S FINE.
- A BEAUTIFUL PENIS.
DR. RUSSO DID
AN AMAZING JOB.
- HE WAS BARELY CRYING.
HE'’S NOT CRYING NOW.
- HE'’S NOT GRUMPY.
- WENT GREAT.
THANK YOU, DR. RUSSO.
- MM-HMM.
- HE'’S CUTE, HUH?
- HE'’S GOT A NICE HEAD
OF HAIR NOW.
- WOULD IT BE BAD IF WE PUT
SOME KIND OF, LIKE,
HAIR GEL OR HAIRSPRAY?
- IS THAT A REAL QUESTION?
- YOU'’RE GONNA GEL HIS HAIR
RIGHT NOW?
- WHAT'’S THE POINT
OF HAVING A BABY
WITH THAT MUCH HAIR,
AND YOU CAN'’T STYLE IT?
- I WASN'’T EVEN THINKING
ABOUT THAT.
WHY WOULD YOU?
- [laughs]
NEW PARENTS.
- ♪ WAKE UP, WAKE UP ♪
[alarm beeping]
- GET UP.
- NO.
- WE GOT A ROAD TRIP.
[grunts]
- OW, OW, OW, OW.
- STRETCH IT OUT.
STRETCH IT OUT.
- OW.
- JUST STRETCH IT OUT
A LITTLE BIT RIGHT NOW.
REALLY GET INTO THIS ONE.
- COME ON!
- LET'’S REALLY
STRETCH THIS ONE OUT.
- OW! IT'’S TOO EARLY!
- NOPE, THAT'’S GOOD RIGHT THERE.
IT'’S YOUR
THORACIC MUSCLE HERE.
[grunts]
THERE YOU GO.
YOU READY FOR A ROAD TRIP?
- [laughing]
STOP. YOU'’RE SO SICK.
THAT'’S NOT STRETCHING ME OUT.
IT'’S ABUSE.
- NOW I'’M CERTIFIED.
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
- TOLD YOU WE SHOULD HAVE
PACKED BEFORE.
ME AND ROGER
ARE HEADING TO MAINE, FINALLY.
BUT WE STILL HAVE A TON TO DO.
- NEED TO PACK.
- WELL, WE'’RE GONNA HAVE TO MAKE
[bleep] TWO BIG BAGS WORK,
'’CAUSE I'’M NOT DOWNSIZING.
AS OF RIGHT NOW, I HAVE
THE ESSENTIALS IN ONE BAG
AND THE CLOTHES
IN THE OTHER.
OBVIOUSLY, I NEED
EXTRA EYELASHES.
- YOU NEED THE FURRY BOOTS,
SWEETHEART?
MAINE,
NOT ANTARCTICA.
ONLY THING I BROUGHT
THAT I PROBABLY WON'’T USE
IS SEX LUBE.
- YOU'’LL USE IT.
- [laughing]
NOT ON YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE READY
TO GO.
- I AM.
- WHY DO YOU NEED
SOMETHING CUTE FOR ME?
WE'’RE GOING
INTO THE WILDERNESS.
- JUST IN CASE
WE'’RE NOT IN THE WILDERNESS.
- THE ENTIRE STATE OF MAINE
IS WILDERNESS.
- AND OBVIOUSLY,
I DO HAVE TO PACK
A COUPLE PAIRS OF HEELS,
CLUB OUTFITS,
CERTAIN THINGS JUST IN CASE
THAT WE, YOU KNOW,
TO AND FROM MAINE,
MIGHT STOP OFF
AND GO OUT.
- STOP PICKING OUT
CLUB GEAR.
YOU DON'’T NEED CLUB GEAR.
GOT A 15-HOUR RIDE
AHEAD OF US,
AND WE MIGHT HIT A FEW CLUBS
ON THE WAY.
YOU KNOW, YOU NEVER KNOW.
NEVER KNOW.
- WELL, YOU PICK IT OUT.
- DON'’T EVEN LOOK AT THAT.
- LOOK AT WHAT?
- ANYTHING UP THERE
YOU DON'’T NEED.
LET ME SEE.
THESE WOULD BE GOOD
FOR, YOU KNOW, BEAR DEFENSE.
YOU COULD BEAT A BEAR TO DEATH
AS YOU'’RE WEARING THEM.
- I WANT TO BRING THESE.
- YEP, THAT WOULD WORK
AS A BEAR-BEATER TOO.
SURE, BRING '’EM.
WHY NOT?
- THEY'’RE MY FAVORITE.
- I CAN SEE I'’M NOT GONNA WIN
THIS ARGUMENT.
- YEAH, I'’M GONNA SHOW
YOUR DAD THESE.
- AWESOME. HE'’S GONNA
REALLY LOVE THOSE.
- I KNOW.
I DON'’T COMPLAIN
ABOUT THE HAIR GEL.
HE SHOULD NOT COMPLAIN
ABOUT MY HEELS.
HE'’S A DUDE.
HE DOESN'’T GET IT.
- [sighs deeply]
[upbeat pop music]
- ♪ FOR A NIGHT ♪
♪ OR FOR ANOTHER YEAR ♪
♪ A TICKET FOR A FREE RIDE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING GOES HERE ♪
♪ ♪
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- I'’M NADINE VACCARINO.
I'’M ONE OF THE LACTATION
CONSULTANTS.
- NICE TO MEET YOU. JIONNI.
- NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
FIRST I WANT TO CONGRATULATE YOU
ON YOUR DECISION TO BREASTFEED.
IT REALLY IS THE BEST DECISION
YOU'’VE EVER MADE FOR THIS BABY.
ALSO GOOD FOR YOU.
IT BURNS 500 CALORIES A DAY.
- YEAH.
THE FACT THAT YOU
CAN BURN CALORIES
FROM BREASTFEEDING,
I MEAN, WHY NOT?
OBVIOUSLY,
I WANT MY BODY BACK,
AND PLUS, IT'’S THE HEALTHIEST
FOR LORENZO.
- AND HOW SAFE IS IT
WITH THE WHOLE
PUMP-AND-DUMP THEORY?
LIKE, IF SHE HAS, LIKE,
A DRINK OR TWO ONE DAY,
YOU KNOW, IN THE FUTURE.
- THE AMERICAN ACADEMY
OF PEDIATRICS,
IT SAYS, YES,
IF YOU HAVE MORE THAN ONE DRINK,
YOU NEED TO PUMP AND DUMP
THE NEXT FEEDING.
- WHEN I DRINK
MY FIRST GLASS OF WINE,
I'’M GONNA DRINK
TWO BOTTLES OF IT.
I DON'’T WANT
JUST ONE GLASS.
- EVERYTHING IN MODERATION.
- MM-HMM.
WINE IS LIKE EATING PRINGLES.
LIKE, ONCE YOU POP,
YOU CAN'’T STOP.
- SO YOU GUYS HAVE
ANY OTHER QUESTIONS?
- WE HAVE A QUESTION,
I CAN TELL.
ASK IT.
- [sighs]
IF SHE EATS
A LOT OF CHOCOLATE,
CAN SHE MAKE CHOCOLATE MILK?
- [giggles]
- NO.
- [laughing]
- THAT'’S STUPID.
- HOW IS IT STUPID?
IT MAKES SENSE.
LOGIC.
- '’CAUSE CHOCOLATE MILK
IS NOT GONNA COME OUT
OF MY BOOBS.
- I DON'’T MEAN DARK CHOCOLATE,
HERSHEY.
I JUST MEAN THAT IT COULD HAVE
A LITTLE CHOCOLATE--
CHOCOLATE-MILK TASTE.
- [giggles]
OW, DON'’T MAKE ME LAUGH.
MY VAGINA HURTS.
- YAY!
- MAINE, HERE WE COME!
- [mumbling]
I'’M EXCITED TO SEE YOUR DAD.
- [mocking mumbling]
- I WOULD LOVE
TO GO FOUR-WHEELING IN, LIKE,
THIS TYPE OF LAND UP THERE,
BY CAMP.
- YEAH, NO, WE'’LL GO.
- I'’M NOT GONNA COMPLAIN
THIS WHOLE TRIP.
- I WOULD RUSH YOU
TO THE EMERGENCY ROOM,
'’CAUSE SOMETHING
WOULD BE WRONG.
THERE'’S JUST NO WAY
IT'’S GONNA HAPPEN.
- NO, IT'’S TRUE.
- [yawns]
WELL, IT'’S NICE SPENDING
TIME WITH YOU.
I'’M ENJOYING YOUR THOUGHTS,
OUR CONVERSATION.
I LIKE IT BETTER
WHEN YOU'’RE AWAKE,
SO I CAN ANNOY YOU.
YOU WANT ME
TO RUB YOUR BOOBS?
BABE?
LITTLE BIT?
- I KEEP DOZING OFF,
WHICH KIND OF SUCKS
ON ROGER,
'’CAUSE HE HAS NOBODY
TO MAKE FUN OF OR TALK TO.
- NO, I THINK I STILL TRIED
TO DO IT,
EVEN WITH YOU SLEEPING.
- YEAH.
- DID MY BEST TO ANNOY YOU.
[laughs]
- SOMETHING STINKS.
- [laughing]
- DID YOU [bleep]?
- WE HIT A S--
- CROP-DUST THIS [bleep] CAR?
- BABE, WE HIT A--
NO, WE HIT A SKUNK.
- WE DIDN'’T HIT A SKUNK.
- WE HIT A SKUNK.
I SWERVED.
I MADE EVERY EFFORT
TO MISS IT
AND INADVERTENTLY
RAN OVER A SKUNK.
- CAN YOU DO SOME
CROSS-VENTILATION HERE
AND CRACK YOUR WINDOW?
- [laughing]
IT WAS A SKUNK.
YOU'’RE GONNA GET MAD AT ME
FOR MOTHER NATURE?
- I REALLY JUST THOUGHT
IT SMELLED LIKE A FART.
- NO, IT WAS A SKUNK.
- I THINK IT WAS A FART.
- NO, IT WAS SKUNK.
IT'’S NOT LIKE
I WAVED IT AT YOU.
- I'’M SURE YOU ACTUALLY DID.
- NO.
THAT'’S RUDE.
- THAT'’S GROSS.
- [laughs]
[laughing]
- WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
DID YOU DO IT AGAIN?
- '’CAUSE YOU'’RE SMACKING
YOUR LIPS OVER THERE
LIKE YOU SWALLOWED IT.
- HEY!
- HE'’S HOME!
LORENZO IS FINALLY HOME.
THANK GOD.
NOW WHAT?
- [laughs]
[line trilling]
- HI, THIS IS
CHRISTINA'’S FLOWERS.
- DO YOU RENT OUT
THOSE STORKS
THAT YOU PUT ON THE LAWN
WHEN SOMEBODY HAS A BABY?
- YES. DO YOU WANT
A WOODEN STORK
OR AN INFLATABLE STORK?
- A WOODEN ONE.
AND THE ONLY THING IS,
I WOULD NEED IT FOR TODAY.
- YEAH, I THINK WE CAN DO IT.
- OKAY, THANKS VERY MUCH.
[traditional Italian music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ RUN AWAY ♪
♪ TO A BETTER PLACE ♪
- FINALLY WE ARRIVED.
THEY'’RE PROBABLY IN BED.
- HEY.
- HEY!
- THERE THEY ARE.
- BAXTER!
- ALL RIGHT!
- YO.
- HI, BUDDY!
- IT'’S GREAT TO GET HOME,
'’CAUSE I DON'’T GET
TO GO HOME OFTEN.
SO WHENEVER I GET TO SEE
MY DAD, IT'’S JUST AWESOME.
AND BETTY--
I LOVE HER JUST AS MUCH.
IT JUST FEELS GOOD
TO SEE THEM BOTH
AND HUG THEM BOTH, YOU KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I LOOK A LITTLE BETTER
THAN LAST TIME YOU SAW ME.
- YOU DO.
- YOU LOOK AMAZING.
- LAST TIME WE SAW YOU, YOU HAD
A BIG TUBE DOWN YOUR THROAT.
I CAN TELL
JUST BY LOOKING AT MY DAD
HE'’S DOING MUCH BETTER
AND HE'’S FEELING MUCH BETTER.
IT'’S JUST NICE
TO SEE HIM SMILING, YOU KNOW?
- SO WHAT ELSE IS NEW, JENNI?
WHAT'’S--
- BIGGEST THING NOW IS NICOLE
JUST HAD LORENZO.
- OH.
- AND WE WERE THERE.
- ROG...
- WHAT?
- KEEP IN MIND...
- [laughs]
- I WANT A GRANDBABY.
- OH, I KNOW.
- [laughing]
I TOLD YOU.
I GET THESE TEXTS--
- NOW, YOU'’RE NOT HELPING
THE CAUSE AT ALL.
- I GET THOSE TEXTS
FROM YOUR DAD.
[laughter]
- MY DAD--
HE DROPS SUBTLE HINTS...
- SUBTLE?
- THAT HE WOULD LOVE FOR US
TO HAVE A CHILD
SO THAT HE CAN BE
THE DOTING GRANDFATHER
TO OUR CHILD, YOU KNOW.
- ROGER WANTS TO DO IT...
- I JUST THOUGHT
IT MIGHT PUT SOME IDEAS
IN THERE.
- THE MORE TRADITIONAL WAY,
WHICH IS GET ENGAGED,
GET MARRIED...
- OH.
- THEN HAVE KIDS.
- EXACTLY.
- WELL, THAT'’S FINE.
- I CAN HONESTLY SAY
MY YEARS BEFORE I MET JENNI,
I WAS NEVER ONE
OF THOSE GUYS, NEVER,
WHO EVER WOKE UP BY HIMSELF
AND FELT LIKE SOMETHING
WAS MISSING.
- WOW.
- I LOVED MY INDEPENDENCE.
BUT I GOTTA BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
IF I'’M BEING HONEST...
- YOU'’RE NOT INDEPENDENT NOW.
- IF I DID THAT TOMORROW
AND I WOKE UP BY MYSELF,
I WOULD MISS JENNI.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- AW.
- OH, I BELIEVE THAT
WITH ALL MY HEART,
BECAUSE I'’VE SEEN THE CHANGE.
- ME AND BILL MAKE IT
KIND OF OUR JOKE TO, LIKE,
TAG-TEAM ROGER
AND SEE HOW FAR
WE CAN PUSH HIM,
WHERE ROGER FEELS AWKWARD.
I DON'’T FEEL AWKWARD,
'’CAUSE I'’M READY.
NOW I JUST NEED A RING.
- [laughs] YOU BETTER HURRY UP.
- YEAH.
WHY IS THAT PIECE OF PAPER,
"MARRIAGE,"
SO IMPORTANT?
- I'’M GETTING MUSHY HERE,
BUT, UM, IT--IT--
YOU DON'’T NEED A PIECE OF PAPER
TO LOVE SOMEBODY.
I ALREADY LOVE JENNI.
- OH, THANK YOU.
AND I LOVE YOUR DAD.
- WITHOUT YOU HAVING A P--
IF--IF YOU--
IF YOU TWO--
- YOUR NOSE IS GROWING
A LITTLE BIT.
- NO. NO.
- [laughing]
- YOU COULD SAY TO JENNI,
"YEAH, YEAH,"
YOU KNOW, "I'’M HAPPY WITH YOU,
I LOVE YOU,
AND I WANT TO STAY
THE REST OF MY LIFE WITH YOU,"
BUT IF YOU ACTUALLY DO IT
KIND OF OFFICIALLY--
- IT'’S MORE THAN JUST WORDS.
- UH, LET'’S PUT IT THIS WAY.
THERE'’S ONE PERSON
IN THIS ROOM THAT WOULD--
WOULD BE VERY,
VERY EXCITED TO HEAR
THAT YOU TWO
WERE GONNA GET MARRIED.
- NO, YOU CAN MAKE THAT TWO.
- THAT'’S RIGHT,
BUT I DIDN'’T--
- YOU CAN MAKE IT THREE.
- [laughs]
- SO, UH...
- ANYWAY.
- LET'’S CHANGE THAT SUBJECT.
I THINK WE'’VE--
- HOW DID YOU RAISE HIM?
- [laughs]
ALL RIGHT,
READY TO HIT THE HAY?
I COULD THINK
OF A THOUSAND ARGUMENTS
AGAINST GETTING MARRIED,
BUT MY DAD GAVE ME
TWO OR THREE REALLY GOOD ONES
FOR IT, YOU KNOW.
- SORRY WE GOT HERE
SO LATE.
- NO, WE'’VE BEEN EXCITED
TO SEE BOTH OF YOU.
- YEAH.
WASN'’T JUST MY SON.
- [chuckles]
- MAYBE MY...
MAYBE MY FUTURE
DAUGHTER-IN-LAW.
- YEAH, WELL...
- [laughs]
- MAYBE IN--
MAYBE IN MY LIFETIME.
- OH, NOT IN MINE?
- [laughs]
I'’M JUST KIDDING.
- OH!
I'’M TRYING TO HOLD IN THERE.
- I'’M SURE ONE DAY
DOWN THE ROAD,
I'’M GONNA HAVE KIDS
OR GONNA BE MARRIED,
SO TALKING ABOUT IT
DOESN'’T UPSET ME AT ALL.
I JUST WOULD LIKE IT
TO BE DONE.
I WOULD LIKE MY BIG RING.
- WAIT, WAIT.
- YEAH, REMEMBER WHEN I USED
TO WEAR THESE WHEN I WAS A KID?
- TYPICALLY, AT HOME,
I JUST SLEEP
IN MY SPIDER-MAN UNDEROOS.
BUT, UM, I FEEL LIKE
THAT MIGHT BE
A LITTLE TOO MUCH
FOR BETTY TO HANDLE
AT THIS POINT
IN HER LIFE--
ME WALKING
AROUND THE HOUSE
WITH MY DING-A-LING
HANGING OUT.
- EW.
- WHAT?
IT'’S TOO MUCH FOR YOU
TO HANDLE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU KNOW,
ONESIE CAME IN HANDY.
- [laughs]
- JACKPOT.
- YOU LOOK LIKE A ROBBER.
- I AM A ROBBER.
I'’M GONNA ROB
YOUR VIRGINITY.
[bed squeaking]
- GET OFF ME!
[laughing] STOP.
[crack]
- OH, MY GOD.
DID YOU HEAR IT?
IT JUST BROKE.
WE JUST BROKE THE BED.
- THERE'’S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- I JUST WANT
TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT DR. KENNEDY IS GONNA SEND
THE BABY HOME.
- YAY!
- OKAY?
SO GREAT NEWS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I'’M SO HAPPY FOR YOU GUYS.
- I'’M EXCITED
TO LEAVE THIS PLACE,
BECAUSE I WAS KIND OF ANNOYED
AT THE FACT
THAT THE NURSE WAS CHANGING
HIS DIAPER
AND BATHING HIM,
BECAUSE I WANTED TO LEARN
HOW TO DO THAT STUFF.
SO, GOING HOME, I'’M GONNA BE
DOING ALL OF THAT,
AND THAT'’S WHAT A MOMMY
SHOULD BE DOING.
OKAY, MOM,
CAN YOU PUT THAT DOWN
AND TAKE A PICTURE
OF US REAL QUICK?
[Lorenzo squeals]
WAIT.
- [chuckles]
- DON'’T DO YOUR [bleep].
- JIONNI, WE'’RE GONNA REMEMBER
THIS THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
MOVE.
I'’M NOT EVEN IN IT.
[camera shutter clicks]
- COME HERE.
- I WANT ONE BY MYSELF.
- ONE WITH YOUR SON?
- I'’M GETTING UPSET.
- OKAY, MOMMY,
GRAB THE BABY.
COME ON, I'’LL TAKE ONE
WITH YOU AND--YOU AND--
- DO ONE ON MY CELL.
- [groans]
- EVERYONE'’S GONNA BE
DOING THIS.
- NOT EVERYONE'’S
GONNA BE DOING THIS.
IT'’S NOT A TOY.
- WHY ARE YOU SO GRUMPY?
- '’CAUSE I JUST DON'’T WANT THIS
TO HAPPEN AT MY HOUSE.
- OKAY, WELL,
WE'’RE NOT AT YOUR HOUSE.
THEN LET'’S ENJOY
THE MOMENT.
- WHY ARE YOU ACTING
LIKE THAT?
- WE'’RE GONNA GET DIVORCED
BEFORE WE EVEN GET MARRIED.
[laughter]
- HOW ARE WE GONNA GET DIVORCED
BEFORE WE'’RE MARRIED?
- I'’M JOKING.
- BETTER BE JOKING.
- I THINK.
[giggles]
NO, I LOVE YOU.
STOP.
- WE'’RE GETTING DIVORCED.
- NO, WE'’RE NOT.
- LET'’S GO, BUDDY.
TIME TO GO HOME.
FROM HERE ON OUT,
EVERYTHING IS GONNA BE A FIRST.
HE'’S GONNA HAVE
HIS FIRST CAR RIDE WITH US.
HE'’S GONNA HAVE HIS FIRST TIME
BEING IN THE SUNLIGHT.
- THIS IS CALLED "OUTSIDE."
THE FIRST TIME
LOOKING AT CLOUDS,
BREATHING AIR OUTSIDE.
- OUTSIDE.
- YEAH.
- ♪ I'’LL BUILD YOU A HOUSE ♪
- HI.
- ♪ THAT WON'’T FALL DOWN ♪
- HE'’S MISSING
HIS WHOLE FIRST CAR RIDE.
WANT TO WEAR MY SUNGLASSES?
[giggling]
- ♪ YEAH ♪
- ALMOST HOME, BUDDY.
- ♪ I'’LL BUILD YOU A HOUSE ♪
- YAY!
YAY, MOMMY!
- ♪ THAT WON'’T FALL DOWN ♪
- HEY!
- HE'’S HOME!
LORENZO IS FINALLY HOME.
THANK GOD.
- YOU WANT TO SEE
YOUR NEW HOUSE?
COME ON, WE GOT
A COUPLE SURPRISES FOR YOU.
- OH, MY GOD,
MY VAGINA HURTS.
- OOH.
- OH!
I LOVE IT!
- YOU PUT "LORENZO" UP?
- UH-HUH.
- YOU GOT LETTERS?
- I LIKE THAT.
- OH, MY GOD, I LOVE IT.
JANIS REALLY WENT
BALLS TO THE WALLS
WITH EVERYTHING.
- MY WACK-A-DOO MOTHER, OKAY,
CRAZY AS SHE IS,
SHE DID THE ENTIRE THING
FOR US.
WE WERE GONE TWO DAYS.
- THANK GOD FOR HER.
- HERE'’S YOUR CRADLE.
- [gasps]
OH, MY GOD, IT'’S GORGEOUS.
- WHOA!
- AND OUR FURNITURE'’S
NOT EVEN HERE YET.
- THANKS, MOM.
- JENNI LEFT YOU THAT,
A LITTLE NOTE.
- AW.
[burps]
AW.
SHE GOT HIM
A LITTLE BRACELET.
SHE GOT ME A NECKLACE.
I LOVE JENNI.
LORENZO--
HE'’S FINALLY HERE.
WE'’RE A COMPLETE FAMILY.
- I'’M NOT THINKING
ABOUT PARTYING.
I'’M NOT THINKING
ABOUT NOTHING.
IT'’S AMAZING HOW YOUR MIND-SET
CHANGES SO FAST.
- MM-HMM.
NOW WHAT?
- [laughs]
- LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT SPIDER RIGHT THERE.
- [screams]
- [laughs]
- I'’VE GOT A SPIDER
THAT IS STARING AT ME
AND WANTS TO EAT ME.
JUST GET ME OUT OF THE BOAT.
GET ME OUT OF THE BOAT.
- LOOK AT THE SIZE OF IT.
- GET ME OUT OF THE BOAT.
[Lorenzo farts]
- OH, MY GOD.
HE JUST [bleep] ON MY LEG.
- HA HA!
- HE'’S SUCH A TINY BABY,
BUT HE FARTS LIKE A GROWN MAN.
[Lorenzo farts]
UGH.
- DINNER'’S READY.
- BEAR BALLS.
- I MADE YOU BEAR BALLS.
- THEY LOOK DELICIOUS.
- YOU GOTTA TRY '’EM.
- OH, MY GOD, I'’M EATING
A BEAR'’S TESTICLE.
- TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK.
- DID ROGER POP
THE QUESTION?
- OH, DON'’T EVEN GO THERE.
NICOLE KEEPS ASKING
IF ROGER'’S PROPOSED YET.
HE DID NOT,
AND STOP [bleep] ASKING.