- I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA GET
PREGNANT AT THE SAME TIME.
- CAN'T WAIT FOR NEXT YEAR
TO START MAYBE TRYING.
- I WOULD LOVE
IF JENNI HAD A BOY
AND I HAD A GIRL,
BECAUSE THEN THEY CAN DATE
AND GET MARRIED,
AND THEN THEY CAN MAKE
A SNOOKI-JWOWW BABY.
- I FIGURED WE COULD
MAYBE SKIP THE GYM,
GO TO DINNER.
- FREAKING ME OUT
WITH THIS DINNER.
[laughs]
- IS HE PROPOSING?
[up-tempo rock]
- OH, MY GOD,
THIS IS IT.
LIKE, I'M GONNA BE
PROPOSED TO.
WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- IT MIGHT BE ALL THEY HAD.
- WHY ARE WE GOING
IN A PINK THING?
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
*I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
- * WHEN YOU,
WHEN YOU TOLD ME *
* THAT YOU,
THAT YOU WERE UNHAPPY *
* I ASKED YOU
TO SAY *
- THAT'S ALL THEY HAD
FOR A TAXI.
- WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- MIGHT BE ALL THEY HAVE.
- THEY MIGHT NOT HAVE HAD
ANY LINCOLN TOWN CARS.
- WHY ARE WE GOING
IN THAT?
- * ROMANTIC
ROMANTIC ROMANTIC *
- I'M LOOKING
AT THIS PINK LIMO,
AND I'M LIKE,
"TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT.
IT'S GONNA HAPPEN."
WHY ARE WE GOING
IN A PINK THING?
- AND I LEGIT
ALMOST [bleep] MY PANTS.
MY HEART'S IN MY THROAT
RIGHT NOW.
- YOU DIDN'T WANNA GO EAT?
- [laughs]
I CAN'T EAT RIGHT NOW.
ALL I THINK OF IS
PINK DIAMONDS.
YOU KNOW, WHO GETS A PINK LIMO
WITHOUT PROPOSING?
- YOU'RE GOING ALL THE WAY
IN STYLE, COME ON.
- APPARENTLY, IT'S NOT
WHAT SHE EXPECTED.
I DON'T KNOW.
- NO.
I WAS THINKING OF A CAB.
MY FAVORITE COLOR
IS PINK AND BLACK.
- WE'RE JUST GONG
TO DINNER.
WHY DO YOU HAVE THIS LOOK
OF TERROR?
- JUST CAN'T--
MY HEART'S IN MY THROAT.
- [chuckles]
- ONCE I GET A DRINK IN ME,
I'LL BE GOOD.
I'M IN MY DREAM LIMO.
IT'S PINK AND BLACK,
MY FAVORITE COLORS,
AND THERE'S
DISCO LIGHTS EVERYWHERE.
I FEEL RICH.
- YEAH?
- ARE WE TAKING
THE PINK LIMO HOME?
- SURE ARE.
- THIS IS THE PERFECT INTERIOR
TO DRIVE TO MY PROPOSAL.
I SHOULD HAVE MY HAIR DID
FOR IT
SO I'M NOT LOOKING
LIKE A REGULAR GIRL.
- YOU NEVER LOOK
[up-tempo rock]
- THIS IS NICE.
- [clears throat]
WELCOME TO THE PILOT HOUSE.
YOU HAVE TO SHOW YOUR PILOT'S
LICENSE TO GET IN HERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT?
RELAX.
- ENJOY YOUR DINNER.
- THANK YOU.
THERE'S CHAMPAGNE
AND ROSE PETALS ON THE TABLE.
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHEN HE'S GONNA DO IT,
HOW HE'S GONNA DO IT.
ALL I KNOW IS I'M FREAKING
THE [bleep] OUT
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE ROGER'S
GONNA PROPOSE.
- CHEERS.
- THANK YOU.
- TO ALMOST
2 1/2 YEARS TOGETHER,
- YES.
[laughs]
- WHAT?
- SORRY.
I'M NOT USED TO YOU
BEING ROMANTIC.
- [chuckles]
- DID YOU KILL
ONE OF MY DOGS?
- [chuckles]
- IS THAT WHY WE'RE HERE?
- WE'D ONLY BE AT DINNER
LIKE THIS IF IT WAS BELLA.
IF IT WAS NOEL,
WE'D BE AT HER FUNERAL.
I'M NOT A BIG CHAMPAGNE GUY,
BUT WHY NOT CELEBRATE?
- CELEBRATE WHAT?
- US.
JUST HAVING A NIGHT OUT.
CELEBRATE ME SKIPPING THE GYM.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
- I GUESS SO.
- THAT'S PRETTY BIG.
- YOU'RE NOT VERY TALKATIVE
THIS EVENING.
- MM-HMM.
I'M GONNA BRING UP
THE PRETTY FLOWERS.
I'M SORRY.
- [sighs]
HAPPY?
- YES.
- OKAY.
- NERVOUS?
YES.
EVERYTHING
ABOUT TONIGHT'S PERFECT,
BUT I CAN'T EVEN APPRECIATE IT
AT THIS POINT
BECAUSE LIKE MY EMOTIONS
ARE LIKE--
IT'S, LIKE,
JUST SENSORY OVERLOAD.
- [laughs]
WHY ARE YOU NERVOUS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- YOU'RE MAKING NERVOUS,
SO STOP.
- OH, BABE, GUESS WHAT?
WE GOT SOMETHING IN THE MAIL
FOR LORENZO.
- WHAT?
- LET'S SEE
WHAT IT IS.
IT'S A SOCIAL SECURITY CARD!
- CAN I SEE IT?
- LORENZO DOMINIC LAVALLE.
- LET ME SEE IT.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SENT US
LORENZO'S SOCIAL SECURITY CARD.
LORENZO IS OFFICIALLY
A HUMAN,
HE'S A CITIZEN
OF THE UNITED STATES,
AND HE'S, LIKE, A PERSON.
HOW IS HE SUPPOSED
TO WRITE HIS SIGNATURE?
SO THIS MEANS THAT NOW
HE CAN, LIKE, RUN FOR PRESIDENT
OR BE AN OLYMPIC.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.
- HE'S OFFICIALLY
A HUMAN.
- YOU'RE GONNA RUN
IN THE YEAR 300,000.
- WHAT?
- HE'S GONNA BE PRESIDENT.
- IN 300,000?
- 3,000.
WHAT'S THE YEAR?
IS HE GONNA BE ALIVE IN 3,000?
- HE'LL BE [bleep] 80!
- [laughs]
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- OH.
2020.
HE'LL BE 12.
HOW OLD WILL HE BE
IN 2040?
- 2042, HE'LL BE 20.
- 2042?
THERE'S GONNA BE LIKE
SPACESHIPS AND [bleep].
I KNOW IT.
- 22, 32--HE'LL BE 30.
- HE'S GROWING UP
SO FAST.
- FIRST, THE UMBILICAL CORD...
- AND THEN THE POOP.
- THEN THE POOP.
NOW A SOCIAL SECURITY CARD?
- HE'S GROWING UP.
- WHAT'S NEXT?
- NOT READY FOR THIS.
- HE'LL BE 30 IN '42.
- 30 YEARS OLD!
AW.
- NO ONE EVER ACCUSED ME
OF BEING BRIGHT.
- I'M NOT BRIGHT.
[Lorenzo coos]
- HOW'S THE MARTINI?
- YUMMY.
- GOOD? CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING
ELSE TO DRINK?
- SURE.
- TALKED HER INTO IT.
- [laughs]
- THIS IS GONNA MAKE ME SICK.
BUT IT'S OKAY.
SO, BECAUSE I'M SO NERVOUS,
I CAN'T STOP DRINKING.
BETWEEN THE GLASSES
OF CHAMPAGNE,
THE CHOCOLATE MARTINIS...
MM!
VODKA...
- OH, THAT'S SO YUMMY.
PINEAPPLE MARTINIS...
OOH.
- [chuckles]
- MANGO MARTINIS...
- WOULD YOU LIKE SOMETHING ELSE
TO DRINK?
- [bleep] IT,
I'LL HAVE ANOTHER ONE.
- THERE'S [bleep].
- I'M DRINKING EVERYTHING
AND ANYTHING
THAT I CAN POSSIBLY GET
MY HANDS ON,
BUT THE ONLY THING
I KEEP THINKING OF IS
"WHERE THE [bleep]
IS THIS RING?"
- FILLED IT UP
NICE AND FULL FOR YOU.
- OH, YUMMY.
CHEERS TO THAT.
- [laughs]
- DID YOU TAKE TOMORROW OFF?
- NO, I DIDN'T TAKE
TOMORROW OFF.
- REALLY?
SO IT'S JUST DINNER?
- YEAH, BABE.
YOU'RE MAKING ME FEEL BAD,
LIKE I DIDN'T DO ENOUGH.
- I'M NOT DISAPPOINTED.
I'M JUST A LITTLE DRUNK.
- [laughs]
- I DON'T WANT ANYMORE.
[burps]
- THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
- I'M GETTING
THAT WATERY FEELING
IN THE BACK OF MY THROAT
RIGHT NOW
WHERE I KNOW I HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM
OR IT'S GONNA END UP
ON THE FLOOR.
SEE YOU IN ABOUT 20.
- [chuckles]
- I HAVE TO GO
THROW UP.
[coughs liquid
and groans]
SO NOW WHAT?
- CAN I INTEREST YOU
IN SOME DESSERT?
- I'M SO FULL
AND I'M SO GROSS RIGHT NOW
AND MY STOMACH
IS SUCH IN KNOTS,
BUT DESSERT'S ON ITS WAY,
AND, I'M LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD, YES,
OBVIOUSLY,
THE RING IS IN THERE."
- OH, I'M LEAKING!
- LET ME SEE.
- [shouts]
[laughter]
[upbeat synthesizer]
- HELLO.
- HEY, BABE.
- HOW'D YOU MAKE OUT
IN THERE?
- GOOD, EXCEPT FOR I DIDN'T PUT
ALL MY BOOB STICKY TAPE BACK ON.
- [laughs]
ALL RIGHT.
- SO NOW WHAT?
- CAN I INTEREST YOU
IN SOME DESSERT?
- SURE.
- OR POSSIBLY A 250-POUND
NAKED MAN IN YOUR BED?
- NO.
246 POUND, MAYBE.
- OKAY.
AFTER THAT MEAL,
IT'S PROBABLY 251, SO...
- THAT'S TRUE.
I'M SO FULL
AND I'M SO GROSS RIGHT NOW
AND MY STOMACH
IS SUCH IN KNOTS,
BUT DESSERT'S ON ITS WAY,
AND, I'M, LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD, YES, OBVIOUSLY,
THE RING IS IN THERE."
- THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD
CHEESECAKE RIGHT THERE.
- I KNOW
THE RING'S SOMEWHERE,
SO I HAVE TO EAT
THE WHOLE THING,
OR AT LEAST STAB AT IT
BECAUSE IF IT'S IN THERE,
I NEED TO KNOW.
- NEED HELP WITH THAT,
OR YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
[laughs]
MINUTE BY MINUTE
BY MINUTE BY MINUTE,
I'M LOSING HOPE
THAT THE RING IS IN THERE.
- [chuckles]
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, SPORT.
YOU WANT SOME HELP?
- MM.
THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA DO
SOMETHING NUTS TONIGHT.
- HOW SO?
- THE PINK LIMO THREW ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GONNA DO.
- YEAH, I THINK I KNOW.
I WASN'T SURE,
AND I DIDN'T WANNA SAY IT.
- WELL, I DIDN'T
WANNA SAY IT
IN CASE YOU TOOK OFFENSE
TO IT.
- [clears throat]
I GUESS THEN I FEEL BAD 'CAUSE--
- DON'T FEEL BAD, THAT'S WHY
I DIDN'T WANNA TELL YOU.
- I REALLY JUST INTENDED
A ROMANTIC DINNER
WITH THE TWO OF US, BUT...
- I JUST GOT
REALLY NERVOUS.
I WAS WOUND UP, AND THAT'S WHY
I DRANK LIKE A FISH.
- I FEEL BAD.
NOW YOU MAKE ME FEEL BAD.
I'M SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I STILL LOVE YOU.
I JUST REFERENCED PINK LIMO
WITH PINK DIAMONDS.
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
I'M ALMOST FEELING BAD.
I ALMOST FEEL
LIKE I'M TORTURING HER MORE
THAN I THOUGHT WAS EVEN
GOING TO BE THE CASE, YOU KNOW?
BUT I CAN'T GIVE UP
MY SECRET.
IT'S TOO GOOD.
I FEEL LIKE
THE WORST BOYFRIEND EVER.
- NO, IF YOU'RE NOT READY,
YOU'RE NOT READY.
I'M NOT PRESSURING.
- I LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE THE GIRL
I WANNA BE WITH.
BUT I DO SEE NOW,
LOOKING AT IT,
THAT MAYBE THE PINK LIMO,
IN HINDSIGHT,
WASN'T THE BEST IDEA.
I'LL DO A WHITE LIMO
NEXT TIME...
- MM-HMM.
- OR BLACK, PROBABLY.
MY APOLOGIES.
- I JUST WANT
A BIGGER RING NOW.
BETWEEN MY HEART ATTACK
ON THE WAY TO THE RESTAURANT,
ME THROWING UP
IN THE RESTAURANT,
AND NOW ME BEING
UBERLY DISAPPOINTED...
- LET'S GO BACK
IN OUR PINK LIMO NOW.
- YOU HAVE A GOOD DINNER?
- YES.
- AMAZING DINNER,
AMAZING.
- I FEEL LIKE ROGER
SHOULD FEEL BAD.
BUT THIS MIGHT BE
A GOOD WAY
TO, LIKE, LIGHT A FIRE
IN HIS ASS.
- I FEEL LIKE I DISAPPOINTED YOU
A LITTLE TONIGHT,
AND I FEEL BAD
ABOUT THAT,
BUT I'M SORRY.
- * CRAZY LOVE *
* WHAT I FEEL FOR YOU *
- I'LL JUST KEEP WAITING.
- THAT MUSTANG'S THE SAME YEAR
AS MY DAD'S, I THINK.
- BECAUSE OF TONIGHT,
I'M MAKING ROGER ADD
ANOTHER KARAT OR TWO
TO MY RING.
I'M A SCORNED WOMAN.
BYE, PINK LIMO.
- [chuckles]
WHAT'S THE WORST SHE'S GONNA DO?
NOT GIVE ME ANY SEX?
- YUP.
- PRETTY MUCH USED TO IT.
WHERE'S MY BUBBA?
- YEAH,
I MISS MY CHILDREN.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- CALLING NICOLE.
- JENNI.
SHE'S GONNA CALL ME
AND ASK [bleep].
PLEASE DON'T THROW ME
UNDER THE BUS TOO BAD.
SHE PROBABLY DOESN'T EVEN LIKE
ME AS IT IS.
I'M A DUDE, BABE.
THAT'S WHAT DUDES DO.
- SCREW UP?
- WE SCREW UP FROM TIME TO TIME.
- YELLO?
- HELLO?
- HOW WAS YOUR DINNER?
- SNOOKS, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BELIEVE THIS.
- WHAT?
- I FELT LIKE I WAS
ON AN EPISODE OF PUNK'D.
- WHAT?
[baby fusses]
- YEAH?
- GUESS WHAT PICKS US UP.
- WAIT, WHAT?
- A HOT AIR BALLOON.
- A PINK STRETCH LIMO.
- AND?
- AND GUESS WHAT
I THOUGHT.
- YOU'RE GETTING ENGAGED.
- YES.
DESSERT COMES...
AND STILL NOTHING.
ALL THROUGH DINNER,
I'M LIKE POUNDING DRINKS BACK.
I CAN'T KEEP
MY THOUGHTS TOGETHER.
I GO TO THE BATHROOM.
I END UP THROWING UP.
- [laughs]
- I COME BACK.
I'M COMPLETELY FINE.
- OKAY.
- HE NEVER PROPOSED.
- SO WHY'D HE GET
A PINK LIMO?
- THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
- ROGER, HELLO!
THE GIRL'S WAITING FOR YOU
TO PROPOSE,
AND YOU GET HER
A PINK LIMO?
THAT'S A TOTAL [bleep]TEASE,
AND ROGER DEFINITELY [bleep] UP.
LIKE, I'M GONNA PUNCH HIM.
WHAT AN ASS[bleep].
DID YOU TELL HIM YOU THOUGHT
HE WAS PROPOSING?
- YES, AND THEN
THE MOMENT HE REALIZED
WHAT HE DID, HE FELT
LIKE A COMPLETE ASS[bleep].
HE FEELS SO BAD
RIGHT NOW.
- THAT'S REALLY EMBARRASSING.
- IT, LIKE, KIND OF WAS.
I WAS, LIKE,
"AW, [bleep]."
- SHE'S LAUGHING IT OFF,
BUT, DEEP DOWN INSIDE,
I KNOW JENNI
WANTS TO CRY,
AND I JUST WISH
I WAS THERE FOR HER
TO CRY ON MY SHOULDER.
I LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU.
- OKAY, SORRY, BYE.
- [laughs]
GOOD-BYE.
- HOW EMBARRASSING.
- WHAT A JERK-OFF.
- WHY WOULD YOU GET A PINK LIMO
FOR JUST A NORMAL DATE?
- MAYBE IT'S A DECOY
FOR ANOTHER TIME.
HE'LL DO IT WHEN SHE TOTALLY--
- WHEN SHE LEAST EXPECTS--YEAH.
HE PROBABLY
DID THAT ON PURPOSE.
- HE IS A BIG JOKESTER.
- IT'S NOT FUNNY.
- HE THINKS HE'S FUNNY.
- SHE WAS SO NERVOUS.
- I HAVE AMMO ON ROGER
FOR A GOOD, LONG TIME.
- MM-HMM.
- HE CAN CALL ME SHORT,
FAT, UGLY, WHATEVER HE WANTS.
AFTER THAT MOVE, FORGET IT.
- HE'S A DOUCHE.
- ONE DAY,
WILL YOU PROPOSE?
- YES, YOU ALREADY KNOW THAT.
YOU STILL LOVE ME
EVEN THOUGH I'M A DUM-DUM?
- MM-HMM.
AFTER TONIGHT, I DON'T EVEN
WANNA THINK ABOUT AN ENGAGEMENT.
- ME EITHER.
[laughter]
- [Bleep] YOU.
THANK YOU
FOR A LOVELY DINNER.
- [sighs]
THANK YOU FOR BEING
A LOVELY GIRLFRIEND.
I MIGHT HAVE GONE OVERBOARD
WITH THIS WHOLE THING,
BUT IN JUST A FEW DAYS,
IF SHE CAN HOLD ON THAT LONG,
AND SHE DOESN'T KILL ME
FOR ALL THIS,
THERE'S GOING TO BE
A GREAT ENDING TO THIS STORY.
both: I LOVE YOU.
- SORRY I'M AN IDIOT.
- IT'S ALL FORGIVEN.
I JUST EXPECT IT
SOONER THAN LATER NOW.
- GOOD THINGS HAPPEN
TO THOSE THAT WAIT.
- YOU'RE WAITING 2 1/2 YEARS.
HE'S, LIKE, TALKING ABOUT--
HE WANTS TO [bleep]
GO SKYDIVING,
WHICH I'M, LIKE, SO AGAINST.
- IT'S AWESOME.
WHO GOES RANDOMLY SKYDIVING?
HE'S GONNA PROPOSE.
I THINK
YOU SHOULD DO IT.
- I DON'T LIKE HEIGHTS.
- YOU SURE?
YOU WON'T BE THE FIRST PERSON
THAT [bleep] THEIR PANTS.
I MIGHT [bleep] MY PANTS,
BUT I'M STILL GOING TO DO IT.
- [Bleep].
- LOVING THE PURSE.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHY IT'S SO BIG.
- [laughs]
- SO I'M GOING DOWN
TO GET SOME LUNCH WITH JENNI,
AND SHE TOLD ME THIS STORY
ON THE PHONE
ABOUT THE PINK LIMO DATE,
BUT I NEED TO HEAR IT
IN PERSON.
LIKE, WHAT THE [bleep] HAPPENED?
- CAN WE HAVE IT OUTSIDE?
- SURE!
- OKAY.
- OH, I'M LEAKING!
- CAN I SEE?
- FEEL THAT?
- OH, MY GOD!
- [screams and laughs]
[laughter]
OH, MY GOD.
I NEED A--
- DO YOU WANT TISSUES?
- SEE, I KNEW--
[groans]
THIS IS BULL[bleep].
I SHOULD BE PUMPING
RIGHT NOW.
- DO YOU WANT TISSUES
TO STICK IN THERE?
- YEAH. I SHOULD'VE BROUGHT
MY NIPPLE PADS.
- IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
NICOLE'S A NEW MOM.
MILK'S COMING OUT.
GET SOME NAPKINS,
AND [bleep] STUFF YOUR BRA.
WE DID IT IN HIGH SCHOOL.
- MM-HMM.
ALL RIGHTY.
- HAVE A NICE DAY.
- AWKWARD.
THANKS.
- [laughs]
[up-tempo rock]
[line ringing]
[indistinct greeting]
- HEY, WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- WHAT'S UP, ROGER?
- PLAN IS COMING TOGETHER,
AND I NEED A FAVOR
FROM YOU AND LAURA
IF YOU CAN DO IT.
- ALL RIGHT, WHAT'S UP?
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
NOW THAT I FEEL LIKE
THE HARDEST PART OF THIS
IS, YOU KNOW, OUT OF THE WAY,
BEING, YOU KNOW, SKYDIVING,
AND MEETING WITH THE PEOPLE AT
FREEFALL ADVENTURES, AND NOW
I HAVE TO MAKE EVERYTHING ELSE
HAPPEN, YOU KNOW?
MAINLY, I HAVE TO GET LAURA
AND SEAN TO DECORATE THE HOUSE
WHILE WE'RE GONE,
YOU KNOW?
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU GUYS
COULD MAYBE COME HERE
AND SET UP SOME, YOU KNOW,
LIKE, ROSE PETALS ON THE BED,
SOME--YOU KNOW,
A CHILLED BOTTLE OF CHAMPAGNE...
I'M GONNA SHOW HER
THAT I CAN BE PRINCE CHARMING.
JUST TO KIND OF KEEP THE DAY
GOING, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, EVEN AFTER
WE GET HOME,
I JUST WANT TO KEEP
SURPRISING HER
AND KEEP SURPRISING HER,
YOU KNOW?
- ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
- ALL RIGHT, PRAY FOR ME.
- WITHOUT A DOUBT,
WE GOT YOU.
- [chuckles]
ALL RIGHT, BRO.
- GOOD LUCK.
- I WANT TO HEAR
ABOUT THIS DINNER.
- UGH.
IT DIDN'T PISS ME OFF.
IT JUST--
- THAT WOULD PISS ME OFF.
- NO, 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW--
- [Bleep] TEASE.
- HE'S NOT READY, BUT YEAH.
IT WAS LIKE A [bleep] TEASE.
I WAS EMBARRASSED
THAT I THOUGHT DIFFERENT.
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE?
- YEAH.
THAT IS EMBARRASSING.
I FELT SO BAD FOR YOU.
BIG PINK LIMO.
- WHAT KIND OF RING DO I WANT?
both: PINK DIAMOND.
- THE WHOLE TIME IN THE LIMO,
I'M LIKE THIS.
- JUST WAITING FOR IT?
- JUST WAITING.
AND SO IT DIDN'T HAPPEN
IN THE BEGINNING OF THE NIGHT,
AND THEN IT DIDN'T HAPPEN
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
SO OBVIOUSLY,
WHAT PART OF THE NIGHT
DO YOU THINK I EXPECTED?
- DESSERT.
- SO I PICKED OUT,
LIKE, A CHEESECAKE.
GOT THE CHEESECAKE.
NO RING.
- I HONESTLY WOULD LOVE
TO HAVE BEEN THERE
TO SEE JENNI, LIKE, STABBING
THE WHIPPED CREAM,
TRYING TO FIND THE RING.
LIKE, I FEEL SO BAD
FOR JENNI,
BUT HONESTLY,
THIS IS THE FUNNIEST THING
I'VE EVER HEARD.
- AT THE END,
WHEN I DIDN'T GET A RING,
I WAS LIKE, "DUDE, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GONNA PROPOSE."
AND THEN I EXPLAINED WHY 'CAUSE
HE COULDN'T UNDERSTAND IT.
AND HE'S LIKE, "I FEEL
LIKE A COMPLETE ASS[bleep]."
AND HE'S LIKE,
"PLEASE DON'T TELL NICOLE.
SHE'S GONNA THINK I'M MEAN
OR IT'S A CRUEL JOKE."
I'M LIKE, "WELL, IT KIND OF IS
A CRUEL JOKE,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IT'S WHATEVER."
AND THEN HE'S, LIKE,
TALKING ABOUT--
HE WANTS TO [bleep]
GO SKYDIVING
WHICH I'M, LIKE, SO AGAINST.
- IT'S AWESOME.
I THINK YOU SHOULD DO IT.
WHO GOES RANDOMLY SKYDIVING?
HE'S GONNA PROPOSE.
I DON'T WANT TO SAY ANYTHING
TO JENNI,
SO SHE, LIKE, THINKS OF IT
AND IS LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD.
HE'S GONNA PROPOSE."
SO I'M KEEPING IT IN MY HEAD.
BUT I'M LIKE,
"BITCH, YOU HAVE TO GO."
- JUST THINKING ABOUT IT
MAKES ME NAUSEOUS.
- NAPKIN'S FILLING UP.
YOU'LL KNOW ONE DAY.
[dog barking]
- AHEM.
TODAY, LAYNA FRIEDMAN
IS COMING BACK
TO SHOW ME THE ACTUAL RING.
[doorbell rings]
NICOLE WAS KEEPING JENNI
VERY BUSY.
KEEPING HER AWAY FROM ME,
GIVING ME TIME
TO PLAN ALL THIS.
AND NICOLE DOESN'T
KNOW IT YET,
BUT I DEFINITELY OWE HER
A BIG HUG AND A THANK YOU.
LAYNA!
- BIG SURPRISE.
- IS IT IN THERE?
- [laughing] YES!
- HOW ARE YOU?
VERY GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
COME IN.
- OH, MY GOD, ROGER,
I GOTTA TELL YOU--
- IS IT AMAZING?
I'M NERVOUS.
I'M BASICALLY AT THE POINT
OF NO RETURN NOW.
YOU KNOW, THE RING IS HERE.
- OKAY, YOU READY?
- I THINK SO.
- YOU SURE?
- YEP, I'M READY.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT IS INCREDIBLE.
BIGGER THAN I EVEN THOUGHT.
- YEAH.
- YOU GUYS ABSOLUTELY NAILED
WHAT I WAS LOOKING FOR.
ABSOLUTELY.
- OH, GOOD.
- LET'S HOPE SHE SAYS YES.
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD.
- SHE'S--
WITH A RING LIKE THAT,
- WHY WOULD SHE
TURN YOU DOWN?
- YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THE RING IS AMAZING,
AND IT'S EVEN BETTER
THAN I THOUGHT.
BUT IF SHE WANTS IT,
JENNI HAS TO JUMP
OUT OF THAT PLANE.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH, LAYNA.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- AND I'M GONNA CALL YOU
AND TELL YOU
HOW EVERYTHING WORKED OUT.
- PROMISE ME.
I WANT TO HEAR
ALL THE DETAILS.
- I WILL, I'LL GIVE YOU
- OKAY. BYE.
- LAYNA, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[sighs]
WOW, NOW WHERE DO I PUT THIS?
- YOU PLANNING TO KILL ME?
IS THIS WHAT'S GOING ON?
- YES.
I THINK SHE SHOULD JUST
COME WITH ME
AND BECOME A LAWN DART,
IF THAT'S THE WAY
GOD PLANNED IT.
- I'M FINE WITH THAT.
NO!
- [laughing]
- I'M NOT FINE WITH THAT.
- "I'M FINE WITH THAT"!
[alarm beeping]
- [weakly]
RISE AND SHINE.
- ARE YOU PLANNING
TO KILL ME?
IS THIS WHAT'S GOING ON?
- YES.
- I DON'T MIND.
YOU CAN DO IT AT THIS POINT.
- SO TODAY'S THE BIG DAY.
GOTTA GET MY GIRL READY
TO GO SKYDIVING, THAT'S ALL.
- I'M NOT GOING.
- YOU'RE GOING.
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER
AFTER YOU STRETCH.
- STOP.
- ARMS UP HERE, LIKE THAT.
- YOU'RE BREAKING MY BONES.
- STRETCH 'EM RIGHT HERE.
THEN I'M GONNA DO ACROSS,
LIKE THIS.
- OWW!
YOU'RE ACROSS MY--
- WE'RE GONNA CROSS 'EM
LIKE THAT.
- [laughing] OW,
YOU'RE MAKING ME [mutters].
OUCH!
- STRETCH 'EM A LITTLE.
GOTTA STRETCH 'EM OUT
LIKE THIS. READY?
- [laughing]
OWW!
- TWO...THREE...
- [laughing]
- AND FOUR.
COME ALL THE WAY BACK.
[grunting] LIKE THIS.
- NO!
[overlapping chatter]
- HEY, THAT'S MY WIENER.
- [laughing]
STOP.
- [grunting]
GOOD.
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
YOU'RE GONNA BE REFRESHED.
- [laughing]
YOU HURT MY LEG.
- NOW GET UP.
- OW. DON'T HIT ME.
- TODAY'S KIND OF
MISSION IMPOSSIBLE.
A LOT CAN HAPPEN.
A LOT CAN GO WRONG.
I CAN'T EVEN TELL YOU
IF MY GIRLFRIEND'S
GONNA GET ON THE PLANE.
- IT'S ANYTHING
BUT THE TYPICAL PROPOSAL.
THEY'RE GONNA SET UP
A HUGE BANNER
IN THE FIELD WHERE WE LAND
THAT SAYS, YOU KNOW,
"JENNI, WILL YOU MARRY ME?"
AND THEN I'LL BE ON BENDED KNEE,
HOLDING THE RING,
WAITING FOR HER
TO GET THERE, YOU KNOW?
AND EVERYTHING JUST HAS
TO COME TOGETHER PERFECTLY.
"FEELING YOUR HAND IN MINE
AND LOOKING
AT THOSE GENTLE EYES."
I WOULD NEVER SAY THAT.
[birds chirping]
- I DON'T WANT
TO GO SKYDIVING,
BECAUSE I ACCEPT MY FEARS.
I'M LIKE, ALL RIGHT,
I'M SCARED OF HEIGHTS.
I'M NOT GONNA DO ANYTHING
WITH HEIGHT REQUIREMENTS,
AND I'M GOOD TO GO.
- IS THAT WHY YOU
DATED YOUR EX?
- [laughs]
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN GO,
HONESTLY.
- AH.
ALLS I SAID WAS, "GET THERE,
TAKE THE CLASS."
SEE WHAT YOU THINK.
- I DON'T LIKE HEIGHTS.
- I'M SURE YOU WON'T BE
THE FIRST PERSON
THAT [bleep] THEIR PANTS.
I MIGHT [bleep] MY PANTS,
BUT I'M STILL GONNA DO IT.
I THINK SHE SHOULD
JUST COME WITH ME
AND BECOME A LAWN DART,
IF THAT'S THE WAY
GOD PLANNED IT.
- I'M FINE WITH THAT.
NO.
- [laughing]
- I'M NOT FINE WITH THAT.
- "I'M FINE WITH THAT."
OKAY, WELL...
I CAN'T MAKE YOU GO.
I WANT YOU TO GO.
I THINK--WILL YOU
AT LEAST TAKE THE CLASS?
- I GUESS.
- IT'S LIKE A 10-MINUTE,
15 MINUTE CLASS, I THINK.
I DON'T KNOW.
- OH, THAT'S ALL YOU NEED
TO JUMP TO YOUR DEATH?
- NO, YOU'RE ATTACHED
TO SOMEBODY.
- YOU JUST WANT ME TO DIE.
I KNOW WHAT THIS IS.
- YOU OVER-THINK STUFF.
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
- YOU WANT BABY WIPES?
- YOU'RE NOT FUNNY.
- [laughing]
[imitating airplane engine]
OPEN UP THE HANGAR.
WHY DO I HAVE A FEELING
YOUR BOOBIES ARE GONNA POP OUT?
- I NEVER AGREED TO GO YET.
- I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS
BECAUSE I'M FULLY COMMITTED
TO THIS IDEA OF SKYDIVING
AND MAKING THIS PROPOSAL
HAPPEN THERE.
SO IF I GET HER THERE,
AND SHE BAILS,
YOU KNOW, AND WON'T JUMP,
I REALLY
DON'T WHAT TO DO.
- STILL RECOVERING
FROM THE PINK LIMO.
- YOU JUST HATE MY GUTS,
DON'T YOU?
- LITTLE BIT.
- AH, SHOOT, THIS IS TOO MUCH
FOR ME TO HANDLE.
- I THINK YOU'RE FINE.
- HELLO.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
UH, WE ARE INTERESTED
IN DOING A JUMP.
- ALL RIGHT.
FIRST TIME?
- FIRST TIME FOR BOTH OF US.
- YOU READY?
- I THINK I'M READY.
I DON'T KNOW--
- IS SHE READY?
- I'M NOT SURE
ABOUT MY GIRLFRIEND, BUT...
- ALL RIGHT.
- NO.
- YOU'RE NOT READY?
- YOU HAVE ANY
PRE-COUNSELING CLASSES
SHE COULD SIGN UP FOR OR--
- YOU'RE ACTUALLY GONNA
WATCH A QUICK VIDEO,
GONNA BRIEF YOU A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT WHAT TO EXPECT,
AND THEN YOU'LL FILL OUT
YOUR PAPERWORK AFTER THAT.
- OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT.
SO THIS IS REAL QUICK.
SO YOU READY?
- YEP. SHOOT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- HELLO, AND WELCOME
TO FREEFALL ADVENTURES.
FOLLOWING THIS INTRODUCTION,
YOU WILL BE GIVEN
THE OPPORTUNITY TO READ AND SIGN
AN ASSUMPTION OF RISK,
ALSO CALLED A WAIVER.
- THE--OF THE GUY SAYING,
"YOU COULD POSSIBLY DIE,"
AND YOU SIGN YOUR LIFE AWAY.
- THEY HAVE TO SAY THAT.
YOU COULD LIFE A LITTLE MORE
ON THE EDGE.
- I FEEL LIKE I LIVE
LIFE ON THE EDGE.
- YOU DO? HOW SO?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
- NO, I FEEL LIKE--
IN MY COMFORT ZONE I DO.
- A FULL 2 1/2 MILES
ABOVE THE GROUND.
WHEN YOUR JUMP TIME
HAS ARRIVED...
- THIS, LIKE,
REALLY HAPPENING?
- IT'S HAPPENIN'.
- NOW...LET'S GO
SKYDIVING.
- ALL RIGHT,
YOU GUYS READY?
- I'M IN.
- YOU EXCITED?
- I'M IN!
- YOU KIDDING ME?
- MY GIRLFRIEND'S
A BIT OF A BADASS.
SHE'S GONNA DO THIS.
- NO.
- SHE'S A BIT OF A BADASS.
- I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD
MAKE OUT MY WILL RIGHT NOW.
BUT I'M TELLING YOU,
IT AIN'T [bleep] GOING TO YOU.
IT'S GOING TO MY DAMN DOGS.
- [laughs]
- ALL RIGHT, SO YOU READY
TO FILL OUT YOUR PAPERWORK?
- JUST SIGN, PRINT,
AND FILL OUT THE BOTTOM OF THAT.
THAT'S IT.
YOU GUYS ARE ALL SET.
- COOL.
- SO HAVE FUN.
- I'M GONNA THROW UP.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET GEARED UP
AND LET'S GO.
- [grunts]
DOES IT FIT?
- MY BOOBS ARE...
[zipper zips]
UHH! OKAY.
- THAT'S PRETTY FORM-FITTING
RIGHT THERE, GIRL.
- THERE'S THAT LOOK.
A DEER IN HEADLIGHTS.
- YEAH, WAIT
TILL I'M UP THERE.
- IS IT WEIRD
THAT I JUST WANT TO SING
"HIGHWAY TO THE DANGER ZONE"
RIGHT NOW?
- GO [bleep] YOURSELF.
[speakerphone ringing]
- [Snooki on phone]
HELLO?
- SO I'M ABOUT
TO JUMP OUT OF A PLANE.
- YAY! YOU'RE DOING IT!
- YEAH, WELL, THERE'S STILL
A CHANCE TO TURN AROUND.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW
UNBELIEVABLY HORRIFIED
I FEEL RIGHT NOW.
- I'M PROUD OF YOU.
I WOULD JUMP
OUT OF A PLANE.
- I, UH...
- [chuckles]
- DO YOU WANT TO TAKE
MY POSITION?
I JUST WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
ONE LAST TIME
IN CASE ANYTHING HAPPENS.
- ALL RIGHT, IF YOU DIE,
DON'T HAUNT ME.
- I'M GONNA HAUNT THIS [bleep]
IF I DIE.
HE'S THE ONE THAT CAUSED ME
TO DIE EARLY,
SO I'M GONNA HAUNT YOU,
AND I'M GONNA CUT THE BITCH
THAT YOU'RE WITH AFTER ME.
- GOOD LUCK!
- THANK YOU.
GIVE LORENZO A KISS FOR ME.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
HAVE FUN.
- LOVE YOU TOO.
BYE.
- LET'S DO THIS, BABY.
- I FEEL LIKE I'M EITHER
GONNA PROJECTILE VOMIT
OR FAINT.
- I'M BASICALLY [bleep]
IF JENNI DOESN'T JUMP
OUT OF THIS PLANE.
I DON'T HAVE A BACKUP PLAN.
IT'S REALLY ALL OR NOTHING.
- * GENTLY ROLL YOUR EYES *
* AND MY MIND TAKES OFF
THROUGH THE CLOUDS *
* OF ME AND YOU *
- THEY'RE JUMPING
OUT OF A PLANE?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S ROMANTIC.
- I FEEL LIKE ROGER'S
GONNA PROPOSE.
100 BUCKS SHE CALLS BACK
IN AN HOUR: "I'M ENGAGED."
IF YOU JUMP OUT OF A PLANE,
HE'S GONNA PROPOSE.
- I'M CALLING IT.
- I--NO, I SAID IT!
YOU HAD NO IDEA.
- I'M CALLING IT.
ROGER'S DOING IT.
- THAT'S MY IDEA.
- ROGER'S DOING IT.
LIKE, THAT'S SO RANDOM--
"LET'S GO JUMP OUT OF A PLANE."
- OH, I CALLED THAT.
- JIONNI, I SAID IT FIRST.
[baby babbling]
WE SHOULD GO SKYDIVING.
I WOULD LOVE THAT.
- OUR PROPOSAL SUCKED.
- NO, IT DIDN'T.
IT WAS NICE AND ROMANTIC
AND NORMAL.
- EVERYONE'S JUMPING
OUT OF PLANES,
GETTING DOLPHINS AND [bleep].
- I DON'T NEED THAT.
YOUR PROPOSAL WAS AMAZING,
IT WAS ROMANTIC,
AND I LOVE MY RING,
AND YOU SHOULDN'T
FEEL BAD AT ALL.
'CAUSE YOU'RE AWESOME.
- I WENT THE ROMANTIC ROUTE.
- AND THAT'S HOW I WANTED IT.
I LOVED YOUR PROPOSAL.
AND I WOULDN'T CHANGE IT.
- THANKS.
[engine buzzing]
- HAVING A GOOD TIME.
TAKE SOME SORT OF DRUG.
OH, [bleep].
IS THIS HAPPENING?
- YOU GOT THIS.
- I'M SWEATING THROUGH THIS.
- I'M SWEATING TOO,
BUT IT'S JUST
'CAUSE IT'S HOT.
- HEY, WELCOME
TO FREEFALL ADVENTURES.
HOW WE DOING TODAY?
- EXCELLENT. CAN'T WAIT.
- READY TO GO SKYDIVING?
- NO.
- ANYBODY AT HOME YOU WANT
TO SAY HI TO OR GOOD-BYE TO
BEFORE WE GO JUMPING?
- BYE, LORENZO!
- NICE.
- HOW 'BOUT YOU?
- BYE, LORENZO.
- [laughs] YEAH.
- YOU WANNA SAY GOOD-BYE
TO THE DOGS?
- BELLA AND NOEL,
YOU GET ALL OF MY STUFF.
THIS IS MY WILL
AND TESTAMENT.
I DON'T WANT
TO GO THROUGH WITH THIS.
BUT I FEEL LIKE THERE'S NOTHING
THAT I CAN DO TO STOP IT.
- LET'S GO.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- NO!
- YOUR CHARIOT AWAITS.
WATCH YOUR HEAD WHEN YOU
CLIMB IN, ALL RIGHT?
- I'M 100% FEELING LIKE
I SHOULDN'T BE GOING THROUGH
THIS RIGHT NOW.
DO I JUST, LIKE, CLOSE
MY EYES THE WHOLE TI--
LIKE, WHAT DO I DO?
I'M SO SCARED OF THIS.
I FEEL LIKE I'M HOPING
I PASS OUT
AND JUST WAKE UP
WHEN IT'S OVER.
- JUST JUMP.
IT'S THAT EASY.
- * TONIGHT,
IT'S JUST ME AND YOU *
* TONIGHT, IT'S JUST
ME AND YOU*
* WE'RE GOING OVER THE EDGE *
* WE'RE GOING
OVER THE EDGE *
* DON'T, DON'T, DON'T,
DON'T LOOK DOWN *
- BASICALLY [bleep] IF JENNI
DOESN'T JUMP OUT OF THIS PLANE.
I DON'T HAVE A BACKUP PLAN.
IT'S REALLY ALL OR NOTHING,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
WORST-CASE SCENARIO,
I'LL PAY ONE OF THEM
TO THROW HER
OUT OF THE PLANE.
- * OVER THE EDGE *
* DON'T, DON'T, DON'T,
DON'T LOOK DOWN *
- LET'S DO THIS!
LET'S JUMP OUT OF A PERFECTLY
GOOD AIRPLANE, BABY.
- THIS IS SLIPPERY.
HOLY CRAP.
- YOU READY TO GO SKYDIVING?
- NO.
- MY BOYFRIEND'S GOING.
- WHEN YOU JUMP, YOU CAN SEE
FROM HORIZON TO HORIZON,
YOU CAN JUST SEE, LIKE,
THE ENTIRE EARTH BELOW YOU.
AND YOU'RE LIKE, "WOW."
- * BABY, BABY,
YOU LOOK SO MEAN *
* ON THE COVER OF A MAGAZINE *
* BABY, BABY,
YOU LOOK SO FINE *
- I JUST WANT TO YELL,
"DON'T DO THIS."
AND AS I'M ABOUT TO YELL,
"DON'T DO THIS..."
- * YO' A BAD MOTHER-- *
- WE JUMP.
AND I BLACK OUT.
THAT'S IT.
DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
- [laughing]
- NICE!
- THAT WAS BAD-ASS.
I WOULD DEFINITELY
DO THAT AGAIN.
THE MOMENT THE PARACHUTE
GOES OUT,
EVERYTHING IS, LIKE,
PROCESSING.
LIKE, "HOLY [bleep], I'M LIKE
THOUSANDS OF FEET IN THE AIR."
I'M--I'M SO SCARED.
I'M LOOKING AT THE GROUND.
EVERYTHING'S GOING LIKE,
"WAH, WAH, WAH."
- [laughs]
- I SEE JENNI NOW, AND IT'S
LIKE, "OH, [bleep]," YOU KNOW?
IT'S TIME. THE D-DAY MOMENT
IS HERE AND IT'S HAPPENING,
AND YOU'RE THINKING,
"CAN SHE READ THE SIGN YET?
CAN SHE READ IT NOW?
CAN SHE READ IT NOW?"
- WHOO! WHOO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- COME OVER HERE.
- [chuckling]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[laughing]
OHH!
- I LOVE YOU...
MORE THAN YOU CAN
EVER IMAGINE.
I WANT TO SPEND
THE REST OF MY LIFE WITH YOU.
- OHH.
- WILL YOU MARRY ME?
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD!
OHH!
I'M SO...
[laughing, murmuring]
- IS THAT A YES?
- YES!
- * WITHOUT YOUR LOVE *
- HOLY...
YEAH!
THAT'S MY RING!
- DID I DO GOOD?
CAN I PUT IT ON?
- YEAH.
I'M SORRY, I'M SHAKING.
YOU JUST MADE ME
JUMP OUT OF A PLANE.
[laughing]
IF IT FITS...
- LET'S SEE.
- OHH.
- [laughs]
- [laughing]
THANK YOU!
- THAT'S REALLY IT.
I MEAN, WHEN WE LANDED,
HAD A COUPLE GLASSES
OF CHAMPAGNE
AND WENT HOME.
- THAT'S IT?
I FEEL A LITTLE PISSED
RIGHT NOW
JUST BECAUSE
I'M JUST WAITING FOR HER
TO SAY, "I'M ENGAGED,"
AND SHE DOESN'T.
- YEAH, WHAT ELSE
IS THERE SUPPOSED TO BE?
- OH, I DON'T KNOW.
- [laughing]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- "X" MARKS THE SPOT, BABY.
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD! BABE!
- WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- ARE YOU HAPPY?
- YEAH, WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
[onlookers cheering]
I WANTED TO KILL--
I WANTED TO KILL YOU
UP THERE.
- OH, MY GOD,
THAT WAS CRAZY.
YOU'RE STILL SHAKING.
I WAS LIKE, "I HOPE
SHE CAN READ THE SIGN
AS SHE'S COMING IN."
- I COULDN'T.
I HAD MY EYES CLENCHED.
- I LOVE YOU.
I'M THE HAPPIEST GIRL
IN THE WORLD RIGHT NOW.
- WOULD YOU DO IT AGAIN?
- NO.
- NO?
- NEVER.
- I WOULD.
- NEVER, NEVER, NEVER.
- RIGHT NOW, I FEEL LIKE
THE LUCKIEST GIRL IN THE WORLD.
I HAVE THE PERFECT MAN,
I HAVE THE PERFECT ENGAGEMENT,
THE PERFECT RING.
- WAS IT THE PERFECT ENGAGEMENT,
THOUGH?
'CAUSE IT WAS LIKE--
- YES!
- THERE WAS A LOT OF TERROR
INVOLVED IN IT.
- WELL, THE PERFECT ENGAGEMENT
AFTER I GOT ON MY FEET
AND LANDED.
- I'M A LITTLE RELIEVED.
YOU SAID YES, SO...
THINK THAT'S A GOOD THING.
- MM, THANK YOU.
IT'LL SINK IN
IN ABOUT AN HOUR.
- RIGHT?
IN THE MEANTIME, DO YOU--
COULD I INTEREST YOU
IN A GLASS OF CHAMPAGNE
TO CELEBRATE?
I HAVE A LITTLE SETUP
OVER HERE.
- YOU DO?
- YES.
OHH...
IT'S MUCH BETTER
THAN THE RESTAURANT.
- RIGHT?
- I'LL REMEMBER THIS DAY.
- I'LL REMEMBER
THIS DAY.
CAN I ASK
HOW BIG IT IS?
- BIG.
- IS IT?
- 7.
- 7?
OH HO, MY BABY DID GOOD.
- [laughing]
- YEAH.
I LITERALLY CANNOT STOP
LOOKING AT THIS RING.
THIS THING IS [bleep] CRAZY.
I'VE NEVER OWNED
ANYTHING THIS NICE.
AND I JUST KEEP
LOOKING AT IT LIKE,
MY FAIRY TALE
HAS COME TRUE.
- CHEERS.
- SORRY.
[giggling]
IT'S NICE.
IT'S VERY NICE.
- TO 2 1/2 YEARS TOGETHER.
AND HAVING BEEN THROUGH IT ALL,
I THINK, REALLY.
AND FINALLY, IT'S OUR DAY.
- FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I'M SPEECHLESS.
- THAT IS A FIRST.
- THANK YOU.
- I LOVE YOU.
THAT'S NUTS
WHAT YOU JUST DID.
- [chuckles]
FOR ME, IT'S GONNA BE SOMETHING
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
- FOR ME TOO.
YOU'RE WITH ME
FOR LIFE NOW.
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT.
- MY OVERWHELMING FEELING
RIGHT NOW IS ONE OF RELIEF.
BUT IT'S ALSO ONE
OF EXCITEMENT
THAT, YOU KNOW,
I NOW HAVE A FIANCEE.
- HOW FANCY.
- A FIANCEE.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU WANNA GET OUT
OF THIS GEAR?
- YEAH, I CAN'T STOP
STARING AT MY RING.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY I'M NOT--
I'M JUST SO HAPPY
ABOUT THE RING.
- I DID GOOD, BABY.
- YOU DID.
- I DID GOOD.
EVERYTHING TODAY, I COULDN'T
HAVE PICTURED IT BETTER.
I COULDN'T HAVE
PLANNED IT BETTER.
AND NOW, THE SUN'S SETTING,
AND, UH, IT WAS JUST...
- AMAZING.
- VERY POETIC.
IT WAS--IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
- I REMEMBER YOU.
- REMEMBER ME?
I'M BACK AGAIN.
I MISSED YOU.
- I WAS A LITTLE DISAPPOINTED
THE FIRST TIME.
- OH? WHY IS THAT?
- TODAY WAS AMAZING.
IT WAS PERFECT.
IT WAS VERY SPECIAL.
I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD
BE THIS LUCKY IN LOVE.
ESPECIALLY WITH
A GUIDO FROM THE SHORE.
- NICOLE'S GOING TO BE JEALOUS.
- THAT'S MY BABE!
SO I'M CALLING NICOLE RIGHT NOW
TO TELL HER
ABOUT THE SKYDIVING
TRIP,
BUT NOT TO TELL HER
THAT I'M ENGAGED,
BECAUSE I WANT TO SAVE THAT
FOR WHEN I'M FACE TO FACE
WITH HER.
- HELLO?
- HEY, BOO.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
I JUST GOT BACK FROM THE JUMP.
- HOW WAS IT?
- I WAS LITERALLY SCARED
OUT OF MY [bleep] MIND
FROM THE BEGINNING
TO THE END,
WHEN I LANDED.
- WHAT ELSE HAPPENED?
- WELL, THAT'S--
THAT'S REALLY IT.
I MEAN, WHEN WE LANDED,
HAD A COUPLE GLASSES
OF [bleep] CHAMPAGNE
TO CELEBRATE,
AND WENT HOME.
- THAT'S IT?
I FEEL A LITTLE
PISSED RIGHT NOW,
JUST BECAUSE I'M JUST WAITING
FOR HER TO SAY, "I'M ENGAGED,"
AND SHE DOESN'T.
- YEAH, WHAT ELSE
IS THERE SUPPOSED TO BE?
- OH, I DON'T KNOW.
- [laughing] COME ON, SNOOKS,
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
- I DON'T KNOW,
I'M [bleep] CRAZY.
WHATEVER.
- YEAH. WOW.
I'LL LET YOU GO.
I LOVE YOU.
- OKAY, LOVE YOU.
GLAD YOU HAD FUN. BYE.
- [laughing] BYE.
- BULL[bleep]!
HE DIDN'T PROPOSE.
I FEEL SO BAD FOR JENNI.
I HONESTLY WANT TO KICK
ROGER RIGHT NOW.
- JENNI'S BIOLOGICAL CLOCK
IS TICKING.
- SO IS ROGER'S.
- ROGER MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO GET IT UP SOON.
- [giggles]
IT'S PISSIN' ME OFF.
THEY'RE NEVER
GONNA GET ENGAGED.
- A REAL JERK-OFF.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW!
- HOME SWEET HOME, BABY.
- YAY.
IT'S THE BEST DAY OF MY LIFE.
- YEAH?
- WITH THE EXCEPTION
OF THE JUMP.
- IF I HAD TO PUT
A NUMBER ON TODAY
ON A ONE-TO-TEN SCALE,
I'D GIVE IT A TEN.
BUT EVEN AFTER WE GET HOME,
I'M GONNA HAVE
A LITTLE SURPRISE FOR HER.
I THINK I'M FINALLY
GONNA GET LAID.
- AW, THANK YOU.
- BUBBA!
- MY LOVEKINS!
- WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT ARE THEY IN?
- WHAT IS THAT?
[door closes]
- WALKING INTO THE HOUSE,
AND THE FIRST THING I NOTICE
IS DIESEL'S IN A TUXEDO,
AND NOEL AND BELLA
ARE IN, LIKE,
LITTLE WEDDING DRESSES.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THIS IS.
- HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT IS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT IS, MONKEY.
- [laughing] WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- DID YOU HAVE JOEY
COME HERE WHEN I WAS GONE?
- I DON'T KNOW, MONKEY.
- THERE'S ROSE PETALS
GOING UP THE STAIRS,
AND I'M LIKE,
"OH, DEAR [bleep].
IS THIS LIKE
ANOTHER SURPRISE?
- WHAT IS IT?
- WHAT IS THIS?
[laughing]
COULD HAVE STARTED A FIRE.
MY BEDROOM IS LIT UP
BY, LIKE, THOUSAND,
I FEEL, CANDLES.
THERE'S ROSE PETALS
ON THE BED,
HE HAS CHOCOLATES AND OYSTERS
AND SHRIMP AND CHAMPAGNE.
AND I'M JUST LIKE,
"WHAT THE [bleep] IS GOING ON?"
OH, NO.
- THIS IS TO PUT YOU
IN THE MOOD.
- STILL NOT IN THE MOOD.
- [laughs]
- I'M KIDDING.
- CAN I--CAN I INTEREST YOU
IN AN OYSTER
OR 30, MAYBE?
[both laugh]
NOW, EAT SOME OYSTERS,
DAMN IT.
- [laughing] CAN I JUST
GO TO THE BATHROOM?
- SERIOUSLY, WHEN
YOU GET OUT OF THE BATHROOM,
YOU BETTER START
EATING OYSTERS.
- IT'S BEEN
LIKE TWO HOURS.
THIS IS UNREAL.
[door shuts]
- [chuckling]
I SHOULD SPRAWL OUT ON HERE.
I WISH I HAD A PAIR
OF WHITEY TIGHTIES.
I DON'T THINK I DO.
WELL, THOSE
ARE PRETTY CLOSE.
JUST TO BE SURE THAT TONIGHT
IS GOING TO, UH,
BE A LUCKY ONE FOR ME,
I TAKE SOME OF THE CHOCOLATES
THAT WE HAVE THERE
AND MAKE AN ARROW
SO THAT THERE'S NO DENYING
THE GENERAL REGION
IN WHICH
SHE SHOULD PLAY IN.
[sexy music]
- [laughing]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- "X" MARKS THE SPOT, BABY.
- OH, MY GOD!
BABE!
- JUST COME LOVE ME.
- [laughing]
- I WAS TRYING
TO SET UP AN ARROW.
IT DIDN'T REALLY
WORK OUT TOO GOOD.
[both laughing]
- HE'S BASICALLY SAYING,
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"FOLLOW THE ARROW."
BUT BECAUSE ROGER
COULDN'T MAKE THE ARROW RIGHT,
IT LOOKS LIKE A BIG BLOB
OF CHOCOLATE ON HIS STOMACH.
- [chuckling]
- YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU SHOULD
BE IN TITANIC RIGHT NOW!
- DO YOU WANT TO PAINT ME?
- [laughing]
YOU'RE SO CUTE.
- I LOVE YOU. MM!
- I LOVE YOU.
TODAY HAS BEEN ONE
OF THE BEST DAYS OF MY LIFE.
IT WENT FROM, LIKE,
EXTREME, PURE FEAR
TO THE HAPPIEST MOMENT
THAT I WILL NEVER FORGET,
EVER, EVER, EVER, EVER
FOR THE HISTORY OF MY LIFE.
BEST DAY EVER.
ROGER'S DEFINITELY GONNA
GET SOME [bleep] TONIGHT.
GIVE ME TEN MINUTES.
SO I DRAW THE BATHTUB
AND GET IT READY
WITH CANDLES
AND NICE BUBBLY,
AND I GOTTA BRING
CHAMPAGNE IN THERE.
AND ROGER'S LIKE,
"I'LL BE THERE IN TEN MINUTES,"
OBVIOUSLY TO GET
OUR GROOVE THING ON.
- [snoring]
- BABE!
SO I'M SITTING HERE
WAITING FOR MY FIANCE,
AND I'M IN THE HOT TUB
WAITING FOR 45 MINUTES.
YEAH.
- [snoring]
- BABE!
[snoring continues]
- SERIOUSLY?
all: BACHELOR PARTY!
BACHELOR PARTY!
[all cheering]
- THIS IS GONNA BE
A LONG NIGHT.
[crash, glass breaks]
- OHH! OH, MY GOD!
- BOTTOMS UP, KIDS.
- SO, IN THE LAST NINE MONTHS,
THE ONLY SHOT
THAT I'VE TAKEN
IS MY OWN BREAST MILK.
- ARE YOU GONNA BE GOOD?
- YES.
- OKAY.
- NO KOOKA OR CARTWHEELS.
- NICOLE IS LITERALLY
RAPING EVERYONE.
SHE IS ON LAURA, SHE'S ON DEENA,
SHE'S ON RYDER, SHE'S ON ME.
- SURPRISED I DIDN'T, LIKE,
TEAR MY VAGINA OPEN
WITH MY STITCHES.
- I'M A GOOD MOM!
- AAH!