- I WANNA THROW JENNI
AN ENGAGEMENT PARTY HERE.
- IS IT A SURPRISE?
- A SURPRISE!
- YOU HARD-CORE
MADE OUT WITH RYDER
FOR, LIKE, A MINUTE AND A HALF.
LIKE, SHE WAS STRADDLING YOU.
- WELL, I MIGHT NOT BE
ENGAGED AFTER THIS.
- WHY DID YOU GET ENGAGED
TO ME?
- YOU BEGGED ME.
- NO, YOU'’RE A GROWN MAN.
- YOU DON'’T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
LEAVING?
- I TEXT JIONNI, "LISTEN,
"AT THE CLUB LAST NIGHT,
I DID BLACK OUT,
AND I MADE OUT WITH RYDER."
- HOW MANY MOMS DO YOU KNOW
THAT HOOK UP WITH GIRLS
AT CLUBS?
- SO YOU DON'’T WANNA BE
WITH ME NOW?
- YOU CAN LEAVE NOW.
TELL MY MOM
WE'’RE NOT HAVING
THE PARTY HERE.
- [sniffles]
[I Love Itby Icona Pop]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- [sniffling]
[Lorenzo fussing]
I'’M A GOOD MOM, I THINK.
[Lorenzo crying]
[line ringing]
- HEY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING. ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- NO.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- I TOLD HIM WE MADE OUT
AND I MADE OUT WITH RYDER,
AND HE'’S TELLING ME
I'’M AN UNFIT MOTHER.
HE WANTS ME
TO GO GET HELP, LIKE...
I DON'’T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- YOU SHOULD STICK UP
FOR YOURSELF, HONESTLY.
HE SHOULD NOT BE
TREATING YOU LIKE THIS.
HE SHOULD NOT BE SAYING
THESE THINGS.
- LIKE, RIGHT WHEN I TOLD HIM,
HE WAS LIKE,
"I'’M NOT MARRYING YOU.
YOU'’RE NOT THE WIFE THAT I WANT.
YOU'’RE NOT THE MOM THAT I WANT."
LIKE, ALL THIS HORRIBLE [bleep].
- NICOLE, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
HE CHOSE TO BE WITH YOU.
HE CHOSE TO GET YOU PREGNANT.
HE CHOSE TO PROPOSE TO YOU.
THEN HE HAS TO [bleep] CHOOSE
TO DEAL WITH THE REAL YOU.
- HE DOESN'’T WANT
TO DEAL WITH ME.
HE WANTS ME TO GO GET HELP,
SO I DON'’T DO THAT AGAIN.
- YOU DON'’T NEED HELP, NICOLE.
YOU NEEDED A BREAK.
JIONNI'’S TELLING NICOLE
THAT SHE NEEDS HELP.
WHAT THE [bleep] DOES SHE
NEED HELP OVER,
THE FACT THAT SHE MADE OUT
WITH ME?
DO I NEED HELP?
NO, MOTHER[bleep].
SHE'’S A GREAT MOTHER
AND A GREAT FIANCEE.
[bleep] LET HER LIVE.
WHERE ARE YOU RIGHT NOW?
- I'’M DRIVING AROUND.
I WANTED TO GET
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
- I'’M SORRY. UGH!
WHY IS HE DOING THIS?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- LET ME TELL YOU,
I KNOW
WHAT YOU'’RE GOING THROUGH.
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU.
I'’LL CALL YOU LATER.
- OKAY.
- [sighs]
- ♪ NOW, I GUARD YOUR SECRETS ♪
♪ SO JEALOUSLY ♪
♪ YEAH, THEY EAT ME ALIVE
WHILE I SLEEP ♪
- IT'’S VERY AWKWARD
COMING HOME.
WE'’RE NOT TALKING.
I JUST HATE FEELING
THIS WAY WITH HIM.
IT'’S WEIRD.
- I'’M JUST TRYING TO FIGURE
THINGS OUT RIGHT NOW.
I'’M--I FEEL ALONE,
I FEEL LEFT,
LIKE I REALLY HAVE NOBODY.
HAVING A KID AND A FIANCEE
IS NOT SUPPOSED TO FEEL LIKE
THE WAY I FEEL RIGHT NOW.
[Nicole whispers indistinctly]
- ♪ COME BACK HOME TO ME ♪
♪ BECAUSE MY LIFE
JUST ISN'’T ♪
♪ WHAT IT USED TO BE ♪
- JUST QUIET IN MY BEDROOM
BECAUSE ROGER'’S, YOU KNOW,
250-POUND ASS
ISN'’T THERE TO STOP ME
FROM TOSSING AND TURNING.
I MISS HIM,
AND I MISS MY BUBBA.
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- HEY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING. HOW YOU FEEL?
- GOOD. HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- SAME. JUST, YOU KNOW,
WAITING TO HEAR FROM HIM.
DID YOU AND JIONNI TALK AFTER?
- NO.
- IS HE BETTER, THOUGH?
IS HE, LIKE--DID HE CALM DOWN
AND APOLOGIZE?
- I THINK HE CALMED DOWN, BUT
WE DIDN'’T REALLY TALK YET, SO...
ARE YOU GONNA TALK TO ROGER?
- NO. HE KNOWS HOW I FEEL.
IT'’S JUST WHEN HE'’S GONNA
GET OVER IT, YOU KNOW, IT'’S--
I'’M NOT THE ONE MAD AT HIM.
YOU KNOW,
I'’M NOT EVEN UPSET ABOUT IT.
I'’M JUST WAITING FOR HIM
TO COME BACK.
- SO BASICALLY ME AND JENNI
ARE GOING THROUGH
PROBABLY THE WORST TIMES
IN OUR LIVES
BECAUSE WE'’RE FIGHTING
WITH OUR MEN,
AND I'’M NOT THE ONLY ONE
HEARTBROKEN.
MY BEST FRIEND IS TOO,
AND WE'’RE THERE FOR EACH OTHER.
- WE'’LL CATCH UP TOMORROW.
HOPEFULLY WE'’LL BOTH HAVE
ANSWERS BY THEN.
- ALL RIGHT.
FEEL BETTER.
- YOU TOO.
LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
BYE.
- SO NOW THAT WE
CALMED DOWN A BIT,
THINK WE SHOULD TALK?
- RIGHT NOW?
- YEAH.
- OKAY.
I'’M SCARED RIGHT NOW, I JUST--
I HONESTLY DO NOT WANNA FIGHT.
I JUST WANNA TALK THINGS OUT,
BE REAL WITH EACH OTHER,
AND JUST TRY AND RESOLVE THIS
BECAUSE I [bleep] LOVE HIM.
- SO YOU DID WHAT YOU DID.
I KNEW IT WAS GONNA HAPPEN.
EVERY TIME I LET YOU GO OUT,
IN THE BACK OF MY MIND...
I GOTTA THINK ABOUT IF YOU'’RE
GONNA BLACK OUT AND HURT ME.
THEN YOU SAID TO ME
ABOUT RYDER--
RYDER'’S DISGUSTING.
YOU HAVE A SON, YOU KNOW?
YOU SHOULDN'’T EVEN BE
HANGING OUT WITH HER.
WHATEVER I SAID THROUGH A TEXT
THAT, YOU KNOW,
YOU'’RE AN UNFIT MOTHER,
YOU'’RE A HORRIBLE FIANCEE,
YOU'’RE MEAN,
AND YOU'’RE JUST A BAD PERSON--
THAT WAS MY FIRST REACTION.
- YOU CAN'’T SAY THOSE THINGS,
THOUGH,
AND EXPECT ME
TO BE OKAY WITH IT.
- YOU CAN'’T HOOK UP
WITH TWO GIRLS,
AS A MOM AND A FIANCEE,
AND EXPECT ME TO BE OKAY
WITH IT.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT I DON'’T WANNA BE
WITH SOMEBODY THAT DOES THAT?
IF NICOLE WANTS TO BE A MOM
AND TO BE A FIANCEE
AND GOES OUT TO CLUBS
AND HOOKS UP WITH GIRLS...
I DON'’T SEE A FUTURE
WITH HER AT ALL.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW MUCH YOU [bleep] HURT ME.
I DON'’T WANNA MARRY YOU
IF THAT'’S HOW YOU'’RE GONNA BE.
- ISN'’T IT FUNNY
HOW WE WERE SO EXCITED
TO BE, LIKE, ENGAGED,
AND WE'’RE BOTH FIGHTING?
I DON'’T WANNA HURT HIM,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I'’M STILL WORKING ON THINGS.
- IS IT THAT BAD?
- I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
IF I'’M GETTING MARRIED.
- I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW MUCH YOU [bleep] HURT ME.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND, YOU KNOW,
WHAT YOU DID WAS WRONG.
I DON'’T WANNA MARRY YOU
IF THAT'’S HOW YOU'’RE GONNA BE.
- JIONNI,
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
I WAS PREGNANT FOR TEN MONTHS.
I WENT OUT FOR ONE NIGHT.
IT'’S GONNA GET CRAZY.
- YOU'’RE MAKING OUT WITH GIRLS,
GIVING THEM LAP DANCES.
I DON'’T WANT A FIANCEE
THAT DOES THAT.
- I'’M NOT GONNA DO THAT
EVERY WEEKEND.
- HOW DO I KNOW?
- BECAUSE I'’M TELLING YOU.
- I DON'’T KNOW
IF THIS IS A ONE-TIME THING.
I THOUGHT ITALY
WAS A ONE-TIME THING.
I THOUGHT SEASIDE
YOU'’RE, YOU KNOW,
SCREWING UP.
IT'’S HARD FOR ME.
IF SOMEBODY SAYS,
"WHY DO YOU LOVE HER
AFTER ALL THAT,
WHY ARE YOU WITH HER?"
I LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT '’CAUSE
I DON'’T KNOW HOW TO EXPLAIN IT.
OKAY, LET'’S JUST SAY I CROSSED
A LINE WITH MY WORDS.
- YOU DID.
- OKAY.
A NORMAL MOM GOES OUT
AND HOOKS UP WITH GIRLS?
- OKAY, BUT IT DOESN'’T
MAKE ME A BAD MOM.
- SO YOU DON'’T REGRET
MAKING OUT WITH GIRLS?
- I DO. I REGRET DOING
THAT STUPID STUFF.
BUT I DON'’T REGRET GOING OUT
AND HAVING A GOOD TIME.
DATING ME,
YOU KNEW THAT
I WENT OUT
AND DID CRAZY [bleep].
- I KNOW, AND I--
- AND IT'’S HARD FOR ME
TO CHANGE THAT.
ME BEING A PARTY GIRL BEFORE
AND NOW BEING A WIFE
AND A MOM,
I MEAN, I'’M STILL
WORKING ON THINGS.
I DON'’T WANNA HURT HIM.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IT'’S GONNA TAKE TIME
FOR ME TO, YOU KNOW, BE...
BE THAT.
- IF YOU REALLY LOVE ME,
YOU WOULDN'’T HAVE DONE THAT.
- OKAY, SO BECAUSE I DID THAT,
IT MEANS I DON'’T LOVE YOU?
- THAT MEANS YOU WEREN'’T
THINKING ABOUT YOUR FAMILY
THAT NIGHT, AT LEAST.
- I WAS THINKING ABOUT YOU GUYS.
- HOW WERE YOU
THINKING ABOUT US?
I KNOW YOUR ASS WAS OUT
AND ALL YOUR [bleep] I HATE.
- I WAS WEARING A DIAPER.
- I WENT OUT FOR A PARTY
FOR A GUYS'’ NIGHT OUT
AND DIDN'’T DO WHAT YOU DID.
- OKAY, WE'’RE
TWO DIFFERENT PEOPLE, JIONNI.
AND I'’M SORRY.
I'’M TELLING YOU I'’M SORRY,
I'’M SORRY, I'’M SORRY.
LIKE...WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- ARE YOU SURE
THERE'’S NOTHING ELSE
THAT I'’M GONNA BE
WORRIED ABOUT?
- THAT'’S WHAT JENNI TOLD ME
AND I TOLD YOU.
- ALL RIGHT.
SHE LET ME DOWN.
SO HOW DO I KNOW SHE AIN'’T
GONNA DO IT AGAIN?
I DON'’T KNOW.
IT'’S ABOUT ME GIVING HER
ANOTHER CHANCE
AND FIGURING IT OUT.
[Lorenzo fusses]
- [sighs]
AY YI YI.
ALL RIGHT, BABY,
I GOTTA GO.
TONIGHT I WANNA GET
ME AND JIONNI SUSHI
AS KIND OF, LIKE, A SURPRISE.
I WANT THIS TO BE THE TIME
WHERE I TELL HIM HOW I FEEL
BECAUSE HE TOLD ME
HOW HE FEELS,
AND I JUST WANNA LET HIM KNOW
HOW I FEEL.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- HI.
CAN I ORDER TO GO?
- SURE.
- USUALLY, WHEN I TELL SOMEBODY
MY FEELINGS,
I WRITE IT DOWN,
OR I PUT IT IN AN EMAIL
BECAUSE THINKING ABOUT IT
AND, YOU KNOW,
WRITING IT DOWN JUST
MAKES IT SO MUCH BETTER
THAN TRYING TO SAY IT
AT THAT MOMENT.
THANKS, GUYS.
- BYE-BYE.
- SEE YA.
[alternative music]
♪ ♪
OUCH.
- HEY.
- WHEN I WALK DOWN THE STAIRS,
I SEE HIM SMILE,
AND HE'’S, LIKE, HAPPY.
- AW, YOU GOT ME SUSHI?
THANKS, BABE.
- NOW I KNOW THIS CONVERSATION
IS GONNA BE GOOD,
AND, YOU KNOW, WE'’RE NOT GONNA,
LIKE, FIGHT.
MMM.
- PRETTY GOOD.
SO WHAT'’S IN THE BOOK?
- I WROTE SOME THINGS DOWN
BECAUSE YOU KNOW HOW IT'’S,
LIKE, REALLY HARD FOR ME
TO REMEMBER
MY FEELINGS AND TELL YOU.
- [laughs]
- "THESE ARE, LIKE,
MY CONCERNS.
"WHEN YOU GET ANGRY,
YOU SAY REALLY MEAN THINGS.
"AND I DON'’T WANT YOU
TO DO IT ANYMORE.
"HURTS MY FEELINGS.
"IF WE HAVE FIGHTS,
IT'’S BETWEEN ME AND YOU
"AND NOT LORENZO.
"ALWAYS LOVE ME
EVEN IF I MESS UP,
"LIKE WHAT I DID AT THE CLUB.
I WANT YOU TO STILL LOVE ME
AND NOT HATE ME."
- I DON'’T HATE YOU AT ALL.
I NEVER HATED YOU.
I WAS DISCUSSING WHAT YOU DID
THAT NIGHT
AND THAT NIGHT ONLY.
- "STOP BRINGING UP THE PAST
'’CAUSE WE'’LL NEVER GET
OVER IT."
- I KNOW.
I CAN'’T HELP THAT.
- CAN YOU TRY?
- YES, I'’LL TRY VERY HARD.
- EVERY SINGLE TIME WE FIGHT...
- I KNOW.
- YOU BRING UP ITALY.
- THAT'’S A PROBLEM I HAVE.
- THAT'’S ALL.
- I'’M 100% GONNA WORK ON THAT
IF IT BOTHERED YOU THAT MUCH.
AND IT'’S NOT OKAY
FOR WHAT I DID.
YOU CAN'’T GO BY--
WITH EVERYTHING I SAID
BECAUSE IT'’S NOT TRUE.
AND I DO LOVE YOU
FOR WHO YOU ARE.
AND I WAS WRONG FOR...
SAYING THOSE THINGS.
I WAS JUST PISSED
AT THE TIME.
I SAID SUCH HARSH THINGS
TO NICOLE
BECAUSE THAT WAS
MY FIRST GUT REACTION.
I WAS MAD,
AND THAT'’S A BIG MISTAKE.
I SCREWED UP.
MAYBE I OVERDID IT.
I DEFINITELY REGRET
SOME OF THE WORDS I SAID.
THANKS FOR TELLING ME.
- NO.
I'’M HONESTLY SO HAPPY
THAT, YOU KNOW,
GOING TO BED TONIGHT,
ME AND JIONNI AREN'’T FIGHTING.
YOU KNOW, WE BOTH WANT
TO MAKE IT WORK.
WE'’RE BOTH IN LOVE,
AND WE HAVE LORENZO.
WE WANT THIS FAMILY TO WORK.
- [bleep].
[laughs]
- OOPS.
- WHAT?
- I THOUGHT I DIDN'’T HAVE
UNDERWEAR, BUT I DO.
- [laughs]
I'’M GLAD OUR FAMILY'’S BACK.
- ME TOO.
- DO YOU STILL WEAR DIAPERS?
- NO.
[giggles]
- IT'’S QUIET IN THE HOUSE
WITHOUT ROGER.
I AM REALLY MISSING HIM.
- HELLO?
- HEY.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WANT
TO COME OVER AND TALK.
- UM...
[I Know It'’s Youby Guards]
- ♪ TAKE THE VERY BEST FEELING
THAT YOU EVER HAD ♪
♪ YEAH, THAT'’S THE ONE,
THAT IS WHAT... ♪
[dog barks]
- OKAY.
COME ON.
IT'’S QUIET IN THE HOUSE
WITHOUT ROGER AND DIESEL HERE,
SO I AM REALLY MISSING HIM.
I DO FEEL LIKE A JACKASS.
I DO FEEL LIKE I REALLY
PUSHED HIM TO HIS LIMIT.
[dog barks]
BELLA,
WHY ARE YOU SO CRAZY?
[dog barks]
IF IT'’S GONNA BE
EITHER OF US TO BREAK,
IT HAS TO BE ME.
[line trilling]
- HELLO?
- HEY.
- HOW YOU BEEN?
- [laughs]
I'’M OKAY. HOW ARE YOU?
- I'’M GOOD.
I WAS WONDERING
IF MAYBE LATER
YOU WANTED TO COME OVER
AND TALK,
SO I CAN APOLOGIZE...
- SURE.
- OR WE CAN TALK ABOUT THINGS.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
THANK YOU FOR CALLING.
- MM-HMM.
- ALL RIGHT, BYE.
- BYE.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'’M GONNA TALK TO JENNI
AND SEE IF HER AND ROGER
ARE OKAY.
- YEAH?
- SINCE WE'’VE ALL
BEEN FIGHTING...
- THEY'’VE BEEN FIGHTING?
- LIKE FREAKS.
- YEAH, BUT I DON'’T REALLY
KNOW, LIKE, WHAT ABOUT.
WHAT DO I TELL HER
IF SHE ASKS ABOUT US?
- HOWEVER YOU FEEL.
- THIS MORNING,
I FEEL A LOT BETTER.
IT'’S NOT, LIKE, 100%,
YOU KNOW, GOOD WITH US,
BUT WE'’RE OKAY,
WE'’RE STILL WORKING ON THINGS.
[whispers]
I LOVE YOU.
[normal voice]
SAY IT BACK.
- I LOVE YOU.
- IT'’S NOT--
YOU'’RE SAYING IT LIKE,
[slurring]
"LOVE YOU TOO."
- YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU.
- I DON'’T THINK JIONNI'’S
REALLY OVER OUR FIGHT.
I MEAN, HE DEFINITELY WANTS
TO WORK IT OUT,
BUT I KNOW THAT HE'’S STILL HURT.
HOPEFULLY IN TIME,
EVERYTHING WILL GET BACK
TO WHERE IT WAS.
- BYE. HAVE FUN.
- BYE, LORENZO.
[Lorenzo babbles]
[laughs]
BYE.
[Before You Change Your Mind
by The Vacations]
- ♪ I'’M A CONVICTED WHORE ♪
♪ A PRISONER OF WAR ♪
♪ SO JUST
BEFORE WE CLOSE THE DOOR ♪
[doorbell rings]
- COME IN!
- I'’M GOING TO SEE JENNI TODAY.
AND I JUST WANT TO TALK
ABOUT HOW I'’M FEELING.
AND ALSO I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT THE [bleep] IS GOING ON
WITH HER AND ROGER.
- HOW ARE YOU?
LOVE YOU.
[kisses]
IT'’S THE ONLY TIME
YOU'’LL EVER SEE ME ON MY KNEES,
BY THE WAY.
- I KNOW.
- [laughs]
OKAY, SO--
- WHERE'’S ROGER-PANTS?
- HE'’S AT, UM, WORK
RIGHT NOW,
BUT I DID ASK HIM TO STOP BY.
- CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED?
'’CAUSE I REALLY DON'’T KNOW.
WAS HE MAD BECAUSE YOU WENT OUT?
- NO.
- OH.
- WE HAD THESE PLANS TO GO OUT.
- OH, THE NEXT DAY?
- YEAH, SUNDAY.
- OH.
- THE ONLY THING
THAT HE SAID THE DAY BEFORE
WAS LIKE,
"DON'’T GET TOO DRUNK."
SO--
- YOU GOT WASTED.
- OH, I WAS SO WASTED.
LIKE, I WOKE UP DRUNK.
AND HE'’S LIKE, "YOU KNOW, I--
THIS IS MY ONLY DAY OFF."
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
"CAN YOU JUST GET UP
AND GET MOVING?"
I WAS A [bleep] ROYAL BITCH.
AND WE FLIPPED OUT,
AND WE STARTED, LIKE,
SCREAMING AT EACH OTHER.
AND THEN I WAS LIKE,
"WELL, WHY THE [bleep]
DID YOU EVEN PROPOSE?"
- YOU SAID THAT?
- YEAH.
- OH, GOD.
- YEAH, YEAH.
I TOOK IT TO THAT--
TO THAT LEVEL.
AND HE TOOK DIESEL
AND TOOK OFF.
HAVEN'’T SEEN HIM SINCE.
- HMM, IT'’S NOT THAT BAD.
- SO I CALL HIM THIS MORNING.
HE SEEMS TO BE BUSY AT WORK,
AND HE HAS [bleep] TO DO.
AND I'’M LETTING IT GO.
I'’M GONNA SEE IF HE'’S
GONNA STILL GO TOMORROW.
SPEAKING OF TOMORROW, ARE
YOU STILL HAVING THAT PARTY?
- I DON'’T EVEN KNOW.
'’CAUSE THE LAST TIME
WE TALKED ABOUT IT,
JIONNI SAID, "THE PARTY'’S OFF,
IT'’S NOT HERE," SO--
- DO YOU WANNA MOVE THIS PARTY
TO A RESTAURANT?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- IS IT THAT BAD?
- OKAY, BACK UP.
SO YOU GUYS FOUGHT IT OUT.
- A LOT OF [bleep]--
- LIKE, COMPLETELY, LIKE,
LEGIT FOUGHT IT OUT
OR FAKE FOUGHT IT OUT?
LIKE, WERE YOU BOWING DOWN?
- NO, I SAID MY SIDE.
- AND WHAT DID HE SAY?
- HE'’S ALLOWING ME TO GO OUT,
HAVE FUN,
GET DRUNK, DANCE, WHATEVER,
BUT HE DOESN'’T WANT ME
TO MAKE OUT
WITH GIRLS, SHOW MY KOOKA.
AND, YOU KNOW,
THAT'’S UNDERSTANDABLE BECAUSE--
- THAT'’S FINE.
- YOU KNOW.
- BUT HE DOESN'’T TAKE IT
TO THE EXTREME
LIKE, "GIVE ME MY SON,"
AND, "YOU NEED HELP."
I HONESTLY DON'’T THINK
WHAT YOU DID
IS ANY REASON FOR HIM TO SAY
THOSE THINGS.
- NO, I KNOW.
AND HE AGREED THAT, YOU KNOW,
THAT WAS WRONG FOR HIM TO SAY,
AND HE'’S GONNA WORK ON THAT.
AND I NEED TO WORK ON
WHEN I DRINK.
I CAN'’T BLACK OUT AND MAKE OUT
WITH YOU AND RYDER.
AND, YOU KNOW,
I JUST CAN'’T DO THAT.
- I DON'’T KNOW HOW YOU DO IT.
I DON'’T KNOW
HOW YOU DO ALL OF THIS
AND HAVE A BABY.
YOU STILL LOOK FABULOUS
IN YOUR [bleep] PSYCHOTIC HEELS.
- I LOOK GOOD, BUT I FEEL LIKE
A [bleep] ASS[bleep].
- LISTEN, JUST EAT IT.
WE ALL HAVE TO EAT IT
ONCE IN A WHILE.
I'’M GONNA HAVE TO EAT
MY PRIDE TONIGHT.
- ISN'’T IT FUNNY
HOW WE WERE SO EXCITED
TO BE, LIKE, ENGAGED?
WE'’RE BOTH FIGHTING,
AND I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
IF I'’M GETTING MARRIED.
- I'’M [bleep] BRINGING HIS ASS
DOWN THE AISLE.
I DON'’T GIVE A [bleep]
IF I HAVE
TO SEDATE HIS ASS
OR NOT.
I DIDN'’T GO THROUGH ALL
THIS [bleep] NOT TO GET MARRIED.
I THINK ROGER HAD
A BREAK ENOUGH.
YOU KNOW, WE'’RE GONNA
DO DINNER TONIGHT,
AND HE AIN'’T GOING ANYWHERE
AFTER THIS.
- SO YOU'’RE GONNA BREAK
HIS KNEECAPS.
- IF I HAVE TO,
I'’LL [bleep] BREAK '’EM.
I DON'’T CARE.
- I FEEL LIKE
I SHOULD GET PREGNANT AGAIN,
SO HE'’LL LIKE ME AGAIN.
- SERIOUSLY?
- I'’M JUST KIDDING.
- LIKE, "OOH,
LET ME CAPTURE HIM
"AND CHAIN HIM TO THE BED
'’CAUSE WE HAVE KIDS NOW,
SO HE HAS TO STAY WITH ME."
- I'’M PSYCHO. SORRY.
I HAVE THIS RING ON MY FINGER,
AND IT'’S GONNA STAY HERE
FOREVER.
EVEN IF ME AND JIONNI
FIGHT AND GO CRAZY,
WE'’RE NEVER BREAKING UP.
ALL RIGHT, I'’M GETTING
OUT OF HERE. SEE YA.
I WILL STALK JIONNI
TILL THE DAY HE DIES.
WE ARE GETTING MARRIED.
SEE YA LATER.
GOOD LUCK.
- [laughs] THANKS. LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- YOU THINK
THAT'’S NORMAL BEHAVIOR
TO ACT LIKE THIS A WEEK
AFTER WE'’RE ENGAGED?
IT LEADS ME TO BELIEVE
THAT, YOU KNOW, MAYBE I JUMPED
THE GUN A LITTLE EARLY.
MAYBE, YOU KNOW, LIKE--
- WELL, THAT'’S NICE.
- BABE.
- YEAH?
- WE HAVE TO FIND A PLACE
TO HAVE A PARTY.
- WHERE YOU WANNA DO IT?
WANT TO HAVE THE PARTY,
LIKE, OUT?
- LET ME GOOGLE.
- NICOLE AND I NEED TO MAKE
SOME DESPERATE PHONE CALLS.
WE NEED TO FIND
A LAST-MINUTE PLACE
FOR OUR SURPRISE PARTY
FOR JENNI AND ROGER.
SO WE GOTTA CALL SOME,
YOU KNOW, LOCAL PLACES
AND SEE WHO'’S GONNA TAKE US
LAST-MINUTE
AND, YOU KNOW,
HAVE A PRIVATE PARTY FOR US.
- ALL RIGHT, I'’M GONNA CALL,
AND YOU'’RE GONNA ANSWER FIRST.
- YOU'’RE GONNA CALL,
I'’M GONNA ANSWER IT?
- YOU'’RE GONNA TALK FIRST.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHEN I GET NERVOUS
CALLING PEOPLE,
I USUALLY GET THE GIGGLES,
AND I ACT
LIKE I'’M FOUR YEARS OLD
ON THE PHONE.
[line trilling]
[whispers] BABE.
- THANK YOU FOR CALLING
MEDIEVAL TIMES.
HOW MAY I BE OF SERVICE?
- HI. UM--
[giggles]
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
I'’VE NEVER SEEN SOMEONE SAY HI
AND START GIGGLING
LIKE YOU'’RE EIGHT.
- [laughs]
I GOT NERVOUS.
PLEASE, I'’M NOT KIDDING.
I'’M VERY NERVOUS.
- WHAT IS WR--
- PLEASE?
- CALL HER BACK RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN'’T DO ANY WORSE
THAN THAT.
- HELLO, GODFATHER'’S.
- [laughs]
HELLO?
- OH, MY GOD.
- HI, UM--
HOLD ON,
JIONNI HAS A QUESTION.
- OH, MY GOD.
- [laughs]
- HOW CAN I...
- HELLO?
- CAN WE THROW A PARTY--
[laughs]
DO YOU GUYS THROW PARTIES?
- YES, ABSOLUTELY.
THAT'’S WHAT WE DO THERE.
- OKAY.
UM, WELL...
I WANT TO THROW A SURPRISE PARTY
FOR MY BEST FRIEND.
THANK GOD WE FINALLY FIND
A PLACE,
AND HOPEFULLY JENNI AND ROGER
WILL SHOW UP.
- SO WHO DO WE INVITE?
- I THINK IT'’S JUST GONNA BE
THE ROOMIES.
- I REALLY DON'’T KNOW WHETHER
IT'’S A "MEET LORENZO" PARTY
OR, YOU KNOW,
A SURPRISE ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
SO I'’M JUST GONNA KEEP IT
SIMPLE,
AND I'’M GONNA INVITE
THE SHORE ROOMIES.
- WHAT'’S UP?
- I CALLED
BECAUSE I WANNA INVITE YOU
TO JENNI'’S SURPRISE
ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
SHE JUST GOT ENGAGED.
- OH, COOL.
- BUT IT'’S A SURPRISE,
SO YOU CAN'’T TELL HER.
AND I INVITED
ALL THE SHORE ROOMIES.
SO EVERYONE IS COMING,
I FEEL.
- COOL. IS LORENZO GOING
TO BE THERE?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, I CAN COME.
- COOL.
I'’LL TEXT YOU THE ADDRESS.
- ALL RIGHT,
THANKS FOR THE INVITE.
- OKAY, BYE.
- ALL RIGHT, BYE.
- I DID IT!
- ♪ IF IT WASN'’T FOR YOU ♪
♪ I WOULD GO BACK TOO ♪
♪ IF IT WASN'’T FOR YOU ♪
- COME ON, BUBBA.
I KNOW YOU HAVEN'’T TORMENTED
YOUR SISTER IN A WHILE.
- OH.
[dogs barking]
- YO.
- YOU BROUGHT BUBBA BACK.
- YEAH.
- HI.
- TO TORMENT. HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
ARE YOU STILL ANGRY?
- I'’M KINDA OVER IT.
LET'’S GO IN HERE.
I CAN'’T EVEN HEAR YOU.
- THE FACT THAT ROGER HAS DIESEL
WITH HIM RIGHT NOW MEANS
THAT HE IS OBVIOUSLY WILLING
TO COME HOME.
HE'’S JUST WILLING TO STAY HERE.
I KNOW YOU LIKE YOUR ROLLS
AND I LIKE MY--
- YEAH, YEAH.
NO, THIS IS AWESOME.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WANT TO SIT NOW?
- YEAH.
- YEAH. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW,
IT'’S BEEN A COUPLE DAYS.
I'’VE DEFINITELY COOLED OFF.
AND, YOU KNOW,
I'’M BACK HERE TODAY
TO SEE IF WE CAN GET
EVERYTHING STRAIGHT.
- I JUST WANT TO SAY SORRY
FOR TAKING IT TOO FAR
LIKE I HAVE A HABIT OF DOING.
- [clears throat]
WELL, I CERTAINLY APPRECIATE
THAT.
I THINK IT'’S IMPORTANT, THOUGH,
THAT YOU UNDERSTAND
WHY IT MADE ME MAD.
DO YOU UNDER--
DO YOU EVEN UNDERSTAND THAT?
- MY ATTITUDE?
- IT WAS JUST THAT--
I DON'’T GET A LOT OF TIME
TO HANG OUT WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW, I WORK A LOT,
SO I DON'’T GET MUCH TIME.
I UNDERSTAND YOU WERE HUNG OVER.
I GET THAT.
BUT WE HAD--WE HAD PLANS.
IT WASN'’T LIKE
WE DIDN'’T HAVE PLANS.
YOU ACTUALLY MADE THOSE PLANS,
AND THEY WERE,
YOU KNOW, WELL IN ADVANCE
OF YOU GOING OUT SATURDAY NIGHT.
- I DO FEEL BAD FOR THAT.
- BUT WE SHOULD NOT BE
AT THIS STAGE
IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
I FELT LIKE WE CAME
THROUGH THE WORST OF THIS.
WE USED TO DO THIS A LOT.
AND I REALLY THOUGHT WE WERE
ON PRETTY STABLE GROUND.
I ALWAYS KNOW THAT WE'’RE GONNA
BUTT HEADS HERE AND HERE.
BUT I DIDN'’T THINK
A WEEK AFTER WE WERE,
YOU KNOW, ENGAGED,
I'’M GOING TO BE LEAVING
THE HOUSE
BECAUSE WE'’RE BICKERING SO BAD.
BUT IT LEADS ME TO BELIEVE THAT,
YOU KNOW,
MAYBE I JUMPED THE GUN
A LITTLE EARLY.
MAYBE, YOU KNOW, LIKE--
- WELL, THAT'’S NICE.
- DO YOU THINK
THAT'’S NORMAL BEHAVIOR
TO ACT LIKE THIS A WEEK
AFTER WE'’RE ENGAGED?
- NO.
- I DON'’T THINK
THAT'’S NORMAL BEHAVIOR.
- NORMAL BEHAVIOR IS APOLOGIZING
AND MOVING ON.
- I AGREE,
AND THAT'’S WHY WE'’RE HERE.
AND WE'’RE STILL ENGAGED,
AND WE STILL LOVE EACH OTHER,
AND, YOU KNOW, ALL IS WELL.
BUT I'’M JUST EXPLAINING
MY FEELINGS, YOU KNOW.
- WILL YOU READ YOUR FORTUNE?
I LOST A FORTUNE.
- YES, WILL YOU--
MINE SAYS,
"WHY THE [bleep] DOES JENNI KEEP
DEFLECTING SO MUCH?"
THAT'’S WHAT IT SAYS.
I CAN READ IT.
- [laughs]
- ALL RIGHT, WELL,
YEAH, LET'’S MOVE PAST IT.
YOU KNOW, NO SENSE
IN BEATING IT ANYMORE.
I'’M GLAD I'’M HERE.
I LOVE YOU.
THANK YOU FOR THIS.
- THERE'’S A WEIGHT
LIFTED OFF MY SHOULDERS
BY ROGER ACCEPTING MY APOLOGY.
AND I'’M GLAD '’CAUSE SOMETIMES
YOU NEED TO FIGHT
TO GET BACK TO THE BASICS,
GET BACK
TO WHY WE LOVE EACH OTHER,
WHY WE'’RE TOGETHER,
AND WHY WE WORK THROUGH THINGS.
- "WHAT YOU DESIRE
IS ALWAYS POSSIBLE.
IT WILL COME TO YOU."
WELL, IT JUST DID
IN THE LAST TWO DAYS.
I WAS AT THE STRIP CLUB
EVERY NIGHT.
EASY.
THAT'’LL BREAK--
THE ONLY THING
THAT WILL BREAK A DIAMOND
IS JUST RAW, COLD STEEL.
AND YOU JUST HIT SOME
RIGHT THERE.
[chuckles]
- THANK YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- LET'’S GO TO BED, PLEASE.
- YOU GUYS JUST FIT
SO PERFECTLY TOGETHER.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
WE LOVE HER.
SHE'’S A SISTER,
AND NOW YOU'’RE A BROTHER.
- THANK YOU.
- YAY!
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
DEFINITELY A HEARTFELT MOMENT
FOR SURE.
- THANK YOU, ROGER,
FOR FINALLY PROPOSING
'’CAUSE I WAS GETTING PISSED.
- THANKS, BOO.
- LOVE YOU.
- YAY.
[laid-back music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ OH ♪
[cell phone rings]
♪ OH ♪
- [whispers] JENNI.
SEE THE VERDICT.
HEY, BOO.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED.
- [laughs]
- WELL, I HEAR ROGER,
SO IT SOUNDS GOOD.
- WHERE DO YOU HEAR ROGER?
- I HEARD A GRUNT.
- [laughs]
- [grunts loudly]
- [laughs] EW.
SO I'’M GUESSING
YOU TWO ARE GOOD?
- YEAH.
- WE'’VE ALREADY HAD SEX TWICE.
- HOW WAS THE TALK?
- [laughs]
IT WAS GOOD.
I APOLOGIZED.
I SURPRISED HIM
WITH A CANDLE-LIT SUSHI DINNER.
- YOU COPIER!
LIKE, WAY TO STEAL MY IDEA.
- I, LIKE, MADE IT ROMANTIC
AND, LIKE, DIMMED THE LIGHTS
AND [bleep] NOT REALIZING--
- YOURS WAS PROBABLY BETTER
THAN MINE.
MINE LOOKED REALLY GHETTO.
- MINE LOOKED GHETTO TOO.
- OH, ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH, IT WORKED FOR ME.
IT WORKED FOR YOU.
- SO THEN YOU TWO ARE GONNA COME
TO THE PARTY TOMORROW.
- YEAH, I'’M EXCITED TO SEE YOU.
I'’LL CALL YOU TOMORROW TO LET
YOU KNOW WHAT'’S GOING ON,
AND WHENEVER ROGER
GETS OUT OF WORK,
WE'’LL LET YOU KNOW
WHEN WE'’RE ON OUR WAY.
- ALL RIGHT.
- LOVE YOU.
- OKAY, LOVE YOU.
BYE, GUYS.
- BYE.
- THEY HAVE NO IDEA.
I REALLY THINK THEY THINK
IT'’S A "MEET LORENZO" PARTY.
AND, YOU KNOW, I THINK I'’M GONNA
PULL THIS OFF GREATLY.
EW.
[giggles]
EW. LIKE, I SOUND
LIKE AN OLD PERSON.
EW!
I CAN'’T BELIEVE I SAID THAT.
[muffled]
OH, MY GOD.
I'’M GONNA PULL THIS OFF
REALLY GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
I'’M GONNA GO PUMP MY BREASTS.
- WHERE YOU GOING TODAY?
- I HAVE TO GO GET A CAKE,
GO TO THE LIQUOR STORE,
AND THEN GO DECORATE.
TODAY IS THE SURPRISE
ENGAGEMENT PARTY DAY,
AND I HAVE A LOT OF [bleep]
TO DO
BEFORE THE PARTY EVEN STARTS.
ALL RIGHT, PEACE OUT.
- YOU GOT YOUR LIST?
- NOPE.
- CHRIST.
- CAN I HAVE THE STRAWBERRY?
- DO YOU WANT ANYTHING WRITTEN
ON IT?
- HAPPY ENGAGEMENT?
- OKAY.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- BYE-BYE.
- AY YI YI.
HELLO.
- HELLO.
- I NEED TWO WHITES
AND TWO REDS.
DO YOU HAVE CHAMPAGNE?
- SURE.
- IS THERE A BIGGER BOTTLE?
- YEP.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- YOU'’RE WELCOME.
- BABE?
- YEAH?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THIS ONE?
- I DO LIKE IT,
BUT IT IS A LITTLE ELVIRA-ISH.
- I KNOW.
- YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
BUT YOU PROBABLY COULD SELL
A [bleep] LOAD
OF COORS LIGHT TONIGHT.
- THANKS.
I HAVE NOTHING ELSE.
- [laughs]
- NO, I SAID I LOVE IT.
- NO, YOU JUST MADE FUN OF ME.
- I SA--
I DO LIKE IT.
BUT IT HAS A LITTLE ELVIRA VIBE
TO IT.
[singsong]
ELVIRA!
- ♪ EVERY TIME YOU'’RE LOOKING ♪
♪ YOU DON'’T KNOW
WHAT YOU'’RE LOOKING FOR ♪
♪ SO MAYBE YOU SHOULD BITE
YOUR TONGUE ♪
- READY?
- CAN YOU CARRY THE PRESENTS?
- OF COURSE.
"BABY EINSTEIN."
KID AIN'’T GOT A CHANCE.
♪ ♪
- HEY, NICOLE.
- HI.
- DAVID ALAN.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
HOW ARE YOU? NICE TO MEET YOU.
SO WHERE ARE WE--
- WELL, THIS IS MY SPACE.
THIS IS THE FRONT PART.
BACK HERE IS WHERE
WE'’RE GONNA HAVE YOUR PARTY.
- OKAY.
- COME ON. WALK IN. AFTER YOU.
- THIS PLACE IS COOL, BABE.
EVERYTHING LOOKS GREAT.
THERE'’S A LITTLE PRIVATE ROOM
I CAN DECORATE.
AND, YOU KNOW, IT'’S GONNA BE,
LIKE, JUST FOR US.
AND THAT'’S EXACTLY
WHAT I WANTED.
THIS--
OH, [bleep].
[groans]
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
- THIS SIGN IS NOT WORKING.
CAN'’T [bleep] REACH.
- YOU WANT ME TO DO THAT?
- I CAN'’T REACH.
- IT NEEDS TO BE TIED UP THERE.
WE'’RE SHORT.
SO WE'’RE STANDING ON CHAIRS,
TRYING TO HANG [bleep],
AND IT'’S JUST NOT EASY.
- [bleep].
PULL IT TOWARDS YOU.
BEING 4'’9" AIN'’T EASY.
- NO.
- IS THAT CENTERED OR NOT?
- IT'’S FINE.
- IS IT REMOTELY CLOSE
TO CENTERED?
- YEAH, IT'’S GOOD.
- OKAY.
WANNA MAKE IT A LITTLE HIGHER,
OR IS THIS JUST APPROVED
FOR US?
- THAT'’S--
WHAT?
[laughs]
- WE'’RE THE ONLY ONES
THAT CAN WALK UNDER THAT.
- OH, WELL.
WHATEVER.
AS LONG AS I CAN GO
THROUGH IT,
I MEAN, I DON'’T CARE
ABOUT ANYBODY ELSE.
- NICOLE?
- PAULY!
- CONGRATS, CONGRATS, CONGRATS.
- THANK YOU.
- HI.
- MWAH.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- DO YOU WANT TO SEE HIM?
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER? DO YOU NEED
ME TO H--DO THE HIGHER ONES?
- DO YOU WANT TO SEE
OUR BABY FIRST?
- YES.
- WE CAN'’T REACH THE HIGH STUFF.
- HE'’S SLEEPING.
- OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
LOOK AT THIS LITTLE GUIDO.
- UNCLE PAULY.
WAKE UP.
- LOOK AT THIS LITTLE GUIDO.
THIS IS AMAZING.
I GOTTA GIVE HIM A BLOWOUT.
- YOU CAN. LOOK AT HIS HAIR.
- HE IS ADORABLE.
YOU DID GOOD, SNOOKS.
YOU DID GOOD.
- DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS PLACE IS OR--
- MM-MM.
[belches]
OH.
- GOOD PUSH, BABY.
GOOD PUSH.
- OOH. I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
WHERE THAT CAME FROM.
- HEY, D.
- HI.
SO WHAT ARE WE DOING?
- YOU CAN HELP ME RIGHT NOW
ACTUALLY.
I'’M GONNA THROW HER OFF
WITH A SIGN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- BABY SHOWER.
- OH.
- WHERE SHOULD I PUT IT?
- WE SHOULD PROBABLY DO IT
FROM HERE TO HERE.
- I DON'’T KNOW WHEN JENNI
AND ROGER ARE GONNA GET HERE.
I'’M BASICALLY
JUST THROWING EVERYTHING,
JUST MAKE IT LOOK LEGIT.
IT LOOKS LIKE [bleep],
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHATEVER.
I JUST NEED TO GET
THESE THINGS DONE.
- SURPRISE!
- OH, YOU SHOULDN'’T HAVE, GUYS.
- IT'’S AN ENGAGEMENT PARTY
FOR RONNIE AND SAM!
[laughter]
- AW.
- YOU SHOULDN'’T HAVE.
- WHAT'’S UP, MY DUDE?
WHAT'’S GOOD, WHAT'’S GOOD?
- RONNIE, DOES HE LOOK BIGGER?
- WOW.
- OH, MY GOD.
I DIDN'’T EVEN SEE HIM.
[laughs]
- DOES HE LOOK BIGGER
FROM LAST TIME?
- HE LOOKS SO MUCH DIFFERENT.
- OH, REALLY?
- HIS HEAD'’S BIGGER.
- HE'’S SO TAN.
- I KNOW.
I DIDN'’T EVEN TAN HIM YET.
- SURPRISE!
- HEY.
- YO, THEY JUST PULLED
IN RIGHT BEHIND ME.
- FOR REAL?
- YEAH,
THEY'’RE ABOUT TO BE HERE.
- OH, MY GOD,
PULL THE CURTAIN!
- SHUT THE CURTAIN!
SHUT THE CURTAIN!
- GUYS,
GET THE SILLY STRING READY.
THEY'’RE ABOUT TO WALK IN.
- READY?
- [groans]
GOD.
- THEY'’RE COMING?
CAN YOU SEE THEM?
MY PALMS ARE SWEATY.
- YEAH, SHE'’S WALKING IN.
- BABY SHOWER.
WE'’RE NOT GOING
TO A BABY SHOWER, ARE WE?
- I THOUGHT IT WAS
A "MEET LORENZO" PARTY.
- READY, GUYS?
EVERYBODY READY? READY?
all: SURPRISE!
- [blows horn]
- WE GOT TO DO A TOAST.
- YEAH.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
I'’M VERY PROUD OF BOTH
OF YOU.
THIS GUY--YOU GUYS READY
FOR A BABY.
[laughter]
- YOU'’RE READY FOR A BABY NEXT.
- ROOKIE.
- BABY SHOWER?
WE'’RE NOT GOING
TO A BABY SHOWER, ARE WE?
- I THOUGHT IT WAS
A "MEET LORENZO" PARTY.
- READY, GUYS?
- READY?
- [clears throat]
all: SURPRISE!
- [blows horn]
[all shouting]
- DON'’T DO IT!
DON'’T DO IT!
- IS THIS FOR US?
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- EVERYBODY'’S HERE.
- HOLY [bleep].
IT'’S A PARTY FOR ME.
AND I'’M SPEECHLESS.
- SURPRISE, BITCH.
- THANK YOU.
- I PULLED IT OFF.
- HEY, GUYS.
- AW, THANK YOU.
- WHOO-HOO!
- SEXY DRESS.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- CONGRATS, BRO.
- CONGRATS, AGAIN.
- AW, THANK YOU.
- CONGRATS.
- WERE YOU SURPRISED?
- YEAH, I WAS.
- CONGRATS, JENNI.
- I CAN'’T BELIEVE
ALL YOU GUYS ARE HERE, MAN.
I WAS MOST IMPRESSED
THAT ALL JENNI'’S, YOU KNOW,
SHORE MATES COULD BE THERE.
- LET'’S POP SOME CHAMPAGNE,
YEAH.
- I NEVER EXPECTED IT,
AND I WAS KIND OF
REALLY TOUCHED BY THAT.
AND IT WAS REALLY AWESOME
THAT THEY COULD DO THAT
FOR US.
- SO HOW WAS SKYDIVING?
- HOW DID YOU ASK HER?
- I WENT DOWN THERE,
I MET WITH THE PEOPLE,
I SET IT ALL UP,
HAD THE SIGN MADE, YOU KNOW...
- YEAH.
- THE WHOLE NINE YARDS.
AND I'’M LIKE, "LISTEN."
- WHAT WAS THE SIGN?
- IT JUST SAID,
"WILL YOU MARRY ME, JENNI?"
BUT IT WAS SPREAD OUT
WHERE WE LANDED.
- OH, AND SHE COULD SEE IT
FROM THE SKY.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- THAT'’S GANGSTER.
SO GET IT STRAIGHT.
NICOLE'’S A MOM.
JENNI AND ROGER ARE ENGAGED.
ALL I KNOW IS, HOW THE HELL
ARE YOU GONNA TOP THAT, RONNIE?
[laughter]
- SUCH A [bleep].
I MIGHT AS WELL DO IT NOW,
RIGHT?
YEAH, RIGHT!
- OH, MY GOD!
[all laughing]
- HE PLANNED THAT.
- HE DOES IT EVERY PARTY.
- I KNOW.
HE DOES THAT ALL THE TIME.
- WE GOT TO DO A TOAST.
- YEAH.
WE'’RE GONNA GO AROUND,
AND I'’M GONNA START.
- OKAY.
- JENNI, YOU'’RE MY BEST FRIEND.
AND I HOPE I SURPRISED YOU,
AND I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
AND THANK YOU, ROGER,
FOR FINALLY PROPOSING
'’CAUSE I WAS GETTING PISSED.
- THANKS, BOO.
- THANK YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- YAY.
YOU GUYS JUST FIT
SO PERFECTLY TOGETHER,
AND I'’VE NEVER SEEN
JENNI HAPPIER.
CONGRATS AND, YOU KNOW,
WE LOVE YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- I'’M HAPPY
FOR THE BOTH OF YOU.
EVER SINCE YOU CAME
INTO JENNI'’S LIFE,
SHE'’S BEEN A GREAT PERSON,
A GREAT FRIEND TO BE AROUND.
BEFORE THAT--
- I WAS A [bleep].
YOU CAN ADMIT IT.
- SHE SAID IT.
- JENNI, I'’M VERY HAPPY
FOR YOU GUYS.
I LOVE YOU TWO AS A COUPLE,
AND I WISH YOU THE BEST.
- THANK YOU.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- LET ME PUT ON MY GLASSES.
HOLD ON.
[clears throat]
"ROGER, YOU ARE THE BEST MAN
FOR MY SISTER, JENNI."
- YOU SPELLED "ROGER" WRONG.
- OH. SORRY.
- THERE'’S NO "D" IN IT.
[laughter]
"CONGRATULATIONS,
AND I WISH YOU GUYS THE BEST."
- YAY!
- AW, CUTE.
- WE ALWAYS KID AROUND
ABOUT HOW WE'’RE LIKE
THIS BIG FAMILY AND WE'’VE
BEEN THROUGH SO MUCH TOGETHER.
AND TO SEE YOU GUYS,
YOU COME INTO HER LIFE,
NOW YOU NOW COME
INTO OUR LIFE,
ALL OF OUR LIVES,
SO HAPPY TO HAVE YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS. WE LOVE HER.
SHE'’S A SISTER,
AND NOW YOU'’RE A BROTHER.
- THANK YOU.
- YAY.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
IT'’S SO COOL THAT EVERYBODY
SAID SOMETHING NICE
ABOUT JENNI'’S
AND MY ENGAGEMENT.
I MEAN, THAT MEANS A LOT,
YOU KNOW.
DEFINITELY A HEARTFELT MOMENT
FOR SURE.
- YAY.
- JIONNI!
- THANK YOU, GUYS.
- JIONNI.
- I GO?
- BABE.
- YEAH.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
I'’M VERY PROUD OF BOTH OF YOU.
THIS GUY--YOU GUYS
READY FOR A BABY.
[laughter]
YOU'’RE READY FOR A BABY NEXT.
- ROOKIE.
[laughter]
- [clears throat]
- "ROGER, JENNI, THIS GUY--"
- [laughs]
- [clears throat]
THIS GROUP IS LIKE A BUNCH
OF HYENAS, SOME SAVAGES.
YOU CAN'’T PAUSE
FOR ONE SECOND.
I WAS BUILDING UP,
YOU KNOW.
IT WAS ALONG THE LINES OF,
"LOOK AT THIS GUY,
LOOK AT HIM,
LOOK AT YOU.
THE BABY'’S COMING NEXT."
MY SPEECH SUCKED.
- JUST EXPECT IT SOON.
THAT'’S IT.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
[laughter]
IT'’S THE LAST TIME I MAKE
A SPEECH WITH THESE GUYS.
IF THERE'’S A SPEECH
AT JENNI AND ROGER'’S WEDDING,
MY ASS IS GONNA BE
IN THE BATHROOM.
I AIN'’T SAYING [bleep].
- I WOULD JUST LIKE TO SAY
TO EVERYBODY,
YOU KNOW, I WAS
KIND OF THE OUTSIDER
NOT THAT LONG AGO.
AND, YOU KNOW,
EVERYBODY'’S ALWAYS BEEN
EXTREMELY RESPECTFUL TO ME
AND ALWAYS HAD OUR BACK,
AND THAT MEANS A LOT TO ME.
AND I JUST WANT TO THANK
EVERYBODY FOR BEING HERE TODAY.
I KNOW EVERYBODY'’S
EXTREMELY BUSY.
AND IT MEANS A LOT,
SO THANK YOU.
- YEAH. THANK YOU, GUYS.
[all cheering]
- LET'’S DO A CHEERS
TO JENNI AND ROGER.
- SALUTE.
- THANK YOU, GUYS.
- JENNI AND ROGER!
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- I LOVE ENGAGEMENTS
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
- THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
- CHEERS.
- I'’M SO USED TO HANGING OUT
WITH YOU GUYS IN SEASIDE,
I JUST LITERALLY CHUGGED THAT
LIKE IT WAS A SHOT
LITERALLY.
AND THEN I REALIZED,
THAT'’S CHAMPAGNE.
- IT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME
THAT MY ROOMMATES LOVE ROGER
AS, YOU KNOW, ANOTHER ROOMMATE,
LIKE, OUR NINTH ROOMMATE.
- I FEEL LIKE,
IF I'’M THE NINTH ROOMMATE,
THEN IT'’S ONLY FAIR THAT JIONNI
WOULD BE, YOU KNOW, 9 1/2.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
I'’M GONNA GET OUT OF HERE.
- I GOTTA GET GOING MYSELF.
- BYE.
- MWAH.
- BYE, UNCLE PAULY.
I AM VERY PROUD
THAT I PULLED THIS OFF.
I MEAN, BEING SO STRESSED
AND OVERWHELMED
AND EVERYTHING THAT'’S GOING ON,
THE FACT THAT I GOT
TO SURPRISE MY BEST FRIEND,
I FEEL GOOD.
- READY, BABE?
- LET'’S GO.
I THINK WE DID GOOD.
- I THINK WE DID GREAT.
- WHOO!
- THERE'’S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWWON THE WAY.
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- ♪ WE'’RE GONNA RUN AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE THE LONG WAY ♪
- OH, MY GOD,
I'’M GONNA POOP MY PANTS.
I'’M NOT KIDDING.
- YOU DIDN'’T EVEN EAT YET.
- ME AND JIONNI ARE GOING
OUT TO DINNER
WITH JENNI AND ROGER TONIGHT.
I'’M STARVING, AND I'’M EXCITED
TO GO HAVE A NICE DINNER.
- NO MORE SURPRISES TODAY.
NO MORE SURPRISES.
- HEY.
- I WANNA THANK YOU GUYS
AGAIN SO MUCH
FOR THROWING
THAT ENGAGEMENT PARTY FOR US.
IT REALLY MEANT A LOT.
- HOW CUTE WAS PAULY'’S SPEECH?
- JIONNI PRETTY MUCH NAILED IT.
- "YOU, ME, THE BABY, THIS GUY."
- "THIS GUY."
- "YOU GUYS, THIS GUY."
- [laughs]
- "BABY."
- THERE YOU HAVE IT.
- IT WAS THE BEST THING EVER.
I'’M REALLY HAPPY THAT YOU GUYS
GOT ENGAGED.
- ME TOO.
- THANK GOD.
- IT WAS THE BEST DAY
OF MY LIFE.
- YOU'’RE GONNA REMEMBER IT
FOREVER.
- MM-HMM.
- WHAT'’S MORE MEMORABLE
FOR YOU,
THE DAY THAT JIONNI
PROPOSED TO YOU
OR THE DAY
THAT LORENZO WAS BORN?
- LORENZO.
- OBVIOUSLY.
I WOULD SAY THAT, YEAH.
- NEVER BEAT IT.
- WE'’RE GONNA DO IT
THREE MORE TIMES.
- THREE MORE? WOW.
- I WANT FOUR KIDS.
JENNI SAID SHE WANTS
TO START NEXT YEAR.
- I'’M OKAY WITH THAT.
- [squeals]
- LOOK AT HER.
AW, SHE'’S SO CUTE.
- I'’M EXCITED.
- YOU KNOW, FROM EXPERIENCE,
TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU GUYS ARE YOUNG, YOU KNOW.
- ONE OF US IS, ANYWAY.
- YEAH.
- LET'’S BE HONEST.
I'’M NOT GETTING ANY YOUNGER.
AND, YEAH, I AM READY
TO BE A DAD NOW.
- AW.
- WHEN WOULD YOU GUYS LIKE
TO BE MARRIED BY?
- I SAID NEXT OCTOBER.
- DO YOU REALIZE THAT WHEN YOU
WALK IN THE RECEPTION HALL,
IT'’S GONNA BE
A [bleep] ZOO? SAFARI?
- WE'’RE GONNA LIMIT
A LITTLE BIT.
- NO.
- A LITTLE BIT,
WE'’RE GONNA LIMIT.
- NO.
TABLECLOTHS, THE CARPETS--
EVERYTHING'’S LEOPARD.
- YOU GONNA GO THAT EXTREME?
- YES.
- DON'’T HAVE
TO GO CRAZY.
- THE CEREMONY
IS GONNA BE TRADITIONAL,
BUT THEN THE RECEPTION IS GONNA
BE ANIMAL PRINT GALORE.
- DON'’T GOTTA RUIN IT.
- I'’M NOT GONNA RUIN IT.
- THAT'’S NOT TRADITIONAL.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
WE'’RE WORKING ON IT.
THAT'’S WHY WE--
THAT'’S WHY WE'’RE WAITING.
- I WOULD LIKE TO JUST TAKE
THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO CHEERS EVERYBODY
AT THE TABLE
AND SAY
WHAT A RIDE IT'’S BEEN.
IT REALLY HAS,
THE LAST FEW MONTHS.
[all screaming]
- [screams]
- I SEE IT, I SEE IT,
I SEE HIM!
- MY WATER JUST BROKE!
[cork pops]
[shrieks]
- NO! NO! STOP!
- LET'’S DO THIS.
- HERE WE GO.
A LITTLE MORE, A LITTLE MORE.
- YAY!
A BOY.
- YOU DID IT.
- GREAT JOB.
- ONE DAY, WILL YOU PROPOSE?
- ONE DAY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AW.
- WILL YOU MARRY ME?
- OH, MY GOD.
[laughs]
[gasps]
- IS THIS THE RIGHT DIAPER?
- IT'’S ON BACKWARDS.
- [laughs]
- MWAH.
both: LOVE YOU.
- IT MEANS A LOT THAT,
THROUGH ALL THIS,
THESE TWO HAVE REMAINED
SUCH GREAT FRIENDS,
AND NOW YOU AND I
HAVE BECOME FRIENDS.
- ALWAYS.
- I THINK THEY'’RE ALWAYS...
- THANK GOD YOU GUYS GET ALONG.
- GONNA BE IN EACH OTHER LIVES,
AND NOW WE'’VE KIND OF MADE
OUR OWN FAMILY OUT OF IT.
- WE HAVE BEEN
THROUGH A LOT THIS PAST YEAR,
BUT THINGS TURNED OUT AMAZING.
I MEAN, THIS IS THE HAPPIEST
THAT WE'’VE BOTH EVER BEEN
IN OUR ENTIRE LIVES.
- MM-HMM.
AND IT'’S A NEW CHAPTER
IN OUR LIFE,
AND I CAN'’T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT THE NEXT CHAPTER IS.
- WEDDINGS AND MORE BABIES.
- MM-HMM.
- WE CAME A LONG WAY, HUH?
- WE HAVE COME A LONG WAY.
- THROUGH THICK, THROUGH THIN,
WE'’RE STILL HERE.
IT WAS THICK, AND IT WAS THIN.
- VERY THIN.
- GLAD WE DIDN'’T WAIT YESTERDAY
FOR YOUR SPEECH IF THAT WAS IT.
[laughter]
- AND CHEERS TO OUR WEDDING.
- YES, CHEERS.
- WHOO!
- AND CHEERS TO...
- LORENZO.
- LORENZO. ABSOLUTELY.
- WHOO!
- I DIDN'’T WANT TO RUIN IT
BY SAYING SOMETHING.
[pop music]
♪ ♪
- YOU GUYS READY TO GET OUT
OF HERE?
- YEAH, I'’VE BEEN HOLDING
IN MY POOP FOR A WHILE.
- [laughs]