Reiner!
Eren!
I think the fight's over.
We're out of strength.
At this point,
I can't exactly kill Reiner.
In that case, let's go back home.
See you later, Reiner.
Protect the airship from below!
Use every last shot you've got!
They are retreating.
Does this mean we're safe?
They are running.
Gabi!
Eren Jaeger!
You won't get away!
I'm going to kill you!
Damn, you're a filthy sight.
Did you fall into a pile of shit?
Eren.
Captain.
This brings back memories, Eren.
You have such a kickable face.
After you're all tied up,
we'll have a chat.
That's fine, but I explained
everything in the letters.
Did you not understand it?
That face…
It reminds me of the rotten shits
who lived underground.
I never thought I would see it on you.
Cheer up.
Everything happened like you wanted.
Stop them! Kill every last one you can!
Everybody, get in now!
They have got nothing
to take down an airship!
Jean!
You go! I'll hold the rear!
I'm counting on you, Commander Lobov!
I told you, I'm a recruit!
Nobody needs the Garrison anymore!
Especially not some overpaid geezer!
Jean!
Grab on!
Who's left?
We're still waiting on Squad Lima.
As far as we know,
there are six casualties.
I see. Shit!
That's nothing compared
to the damage we did!
It's a huge victory!
The New Eldian Empire's
first battle ends in victory!
-Yes!
Tonight, we celebrate in honor
of our six fallen heroes!
First battle, huh?
How many more until the fighting ends?
Just how many have to die?
Anyway, I'm just glad we survived again.
It's not very fair to the others,
but you guys are special…
to me.
That hurts, idiot.
Don't hug us while wearing hard-ass gear.
Excuse me, Jean?
You're the idiot for always fussing over
your tiny-ass beard!
What?
That's right!
Why grow a beard if you can't eat it?
What?
Say, are we eating soon?
Not until we reach the island.
What a useless leader you are.
Gabi!
Gabi, wait!
Come on. That's enough.
They are flying away.
Running after them is pointless.
Even you know that.
Zofia…
Zofia's body was crushed under debris.
I was sitting right next to her.
Udo tried to help her,
but he got trampled by the stampede.
Stepped on repeatedly
until his head split open.
And the two gate guards…
They stopped me.
I was trying to run back to the plaza.
I'm an Eldian, but they told me
to turn back because it's dangerous.
Then they were shot by a girl
on the roof and died.
Being an Eldian born in the zone,
people spit at me when I go outside.
I've had a lot of miserable memories,
but that's why I try so hard.
To show the world that Eldians
are good people!
So that someday,
we could be proud of our Eldian armbands!
I worked hard believing it could happen!
But they crushed everything!
This internment zone is my home!
It's where the people I care about live!
Isn't trampling on it unforgivable?
And yet, you're telling me
not to run after them?
When Zeke was killed before our eyes
and we could do nothing?
Not knowing why any of this happened?
Why, Reiner?
Why was my mom eaten by a Titan?
They were trampled on.
What?
The enemy was attacked by Marley Warriors
and lots of people died.
This is revenge.
Did you…
see it happen?
No, I didn't.
Neither did I.
Besides, they are all just island devils
who threaten world peace.
You should know that!
They are cruel devils
who have always deserved to die.
They are nothing like us.
Reiner, I'm the same as you.
Across the sea, within the Walls…
It's the same.
Squad Lima? That means everyone's aboard.
Tell the bridge we're good to ascend!
Roger!
What?
A kid?
It hit!
It's still attached.
Gabi!
What do you think you're doing?
This trigger…
If I pull it…
Gabi…
Don't tell me
you're thinking of boarding it!
I'm going to kill those island devils!
You'll just end up dead, idiot!
Tell my mom and dad.
Let Reiner and the others know.
That I fought until the end.
Even if we don't win today,
you guys will carry on my will.
Falco! Gabi!
What the hell are you guys doing?
My brother…
Goodbye, Falco.
You were one of the good ones.
What?
You have to rescue Gabi
from the dark future that awaits us.
Falco!
Falco?
Why?
The one who should inherit
the Armored Titan is me!
What?
Did you hear a sound just now?
-Hey! Quiet down!
-Make some noise! Victory!
-Yes!
Hey!
Isn't Lobov still out there?
No, I think he came aboard.
Sasha!
MARLEY MILITARY'S OFFICIAL RIFLE
THE OFFICIAL BOLT-ACTION RIFLE
FIRES FIVE SHOTS
CAN BE EQUIPPED WITH
THE STANDARD-ISSUE KNIFE AS A BAYONET
USED REGULARLY BY
THE WARRIOR UNIT, ARMY, AND NAVY
You bastard!
-Sasha! Hey!
-What?
Hang in there! Hey!
You're so damn loud…
Are we… eating soon?
Bandages, now!
We've got to stop the bleeding!
Right!
Sasha! Make it to the island!
Meat…
Jean, they climbed aboard
using Lobov's ODM gear.
What?
I'll toss them outside. All right?
If we toss kids out of an airship,
will the killing ever end?
What happened to Braun and Grice?
They ran off without warning
and never came back.
Pieck.
Commander, I remember…
There was a Marley soldier
who led Galliard and me into a trap.
I remember seeing
that same soldier three years ago.
They were on the first scout fleet
sent to Paradis after Reiner came back.
What?
The missing scout ships?
Yes. I'm sure of it.
They looked so awful with a beard.
Hey. Are you going to wear that forever?
What?
I thought it was well-received.
They are still celebrating?
Don't touch me, you devils!
We haven't lost yet!
The rest of our comrades
will carry on the will of War Chief Zeke!
Gabi, stop!
What do we do with them, Jean?
Us true Eldians
are going to haunt you until you die!
Pass that on to your ringleader
after I'm dead!
I'll take you to him.
You can tell him exactly what you told me.
How did you identify the soldier?
Well, it's someone I had
a particular interest in.
Because she's a devout follower of Zeke.
Gabi? Falco?
Why are you here?
Why…
I could ask you the same.
You're alive?
Why did you let them capture you?
Who are these kids?
They killed Lobov
and used his gear to come aboard.
Sasha was shot by this one here.
I don't think she's going to make it.
I'm leaving the rest to you, Onyankopon.
You got it, Hanji!
Well?
Did everything play out
as you hoped, Zeke Jaeger?
What?
For the most part,
but there were a few miscalculations.
Zeke…
What? Who are these kids?
Miscalculations.
Yelena!
What the hell happened
to trapping the Cart Titan and Jaw Titan?
People died because of you!
I'm sorry.
I assure you they fell down the hole,
but it's still my fault.
And to cover for that slipup,
the Beast Titan chucked more rocks
at us than planned.
That was some clever improv
for a clown like you.
Wouldn't you say, hairball?
Don't glare at me like that, Levi.
What if I piss my pants?
And you're quite the actor yourself,
considering you want to kill me so bad.
I'm the kind of person
who saves the best bite for last.
I like to savor the taste.
We killed the Marley brass
and destroyed their port and fleet.
That should buy us some time.
Until the whole world launches
a joint attack on Paradis?
Every time you're caught by the enemy,
we sacrifice lives to get you back.
No matter how many it takes.
And yet knowing that, you went
so far as to make yourself a hostage.
Just like you hoped,
we didn't have much choice.
You put your trust in us
and we lost our trust in you.
But now we have the Founding Titan
and a Titan with royal blood.
The cost of those sacrifices
will be paid through Eldia's freedom.
Sasha…
is dead.
Conny.
Did Sasha have any last words?
She said…
"Meat."
I brought some meat
from the officers' storehouse!
It'll be fine!
We can just get more cattle and sheep
once we retake our land!
Eren, Sasha only died
because you dragged the Scouts into this.
Could they have taken some other path?
Unable to change the past,
they must continue
down the one before them.
Next episode, "Brave Volunteers."