I'm retaking the Founding Titan!
Eren!
What?
Was that him?
Is that… Ackermann?
You're kidding…
Can't you see I'm a Titan?
These guys are just humans,
yet they are coming to kill me?
These guys…
They are the devils of Paradis!
Behind us! Retreat!
Shit! I can't shake them!
Damn it!
Shit! That's here, too?
The Cart Titan!
Pieck!
I guess I made it in time.
Like I thought, my machine gun gear
is perfect against their soldiers.
That made getting it worthwhile.
Eren!
That's him all right.
The Beast Titan!
Zeke!
I'm going to kill you, Eren Jaeger!
Let no one escape.
Kill them all.
Don't die on me.
Survive!
This is…
Is that…
No way.
Mr. Kruger?
No.
Eren Jaeger!
Damn you!
Vice-Captain Braun!
Vice-Captain!
Vice-Captain, I'm sorry!
It's all my fault!
What?
He's alive, but…
He's unconscious,
but his body should heal itself
with the Power of the Titans.
That is, as long as
he has the will to live, but…
I'm sick of this… of myself!
Just kill me!
Vice-Captain, I'll go get help.
There are more than
just enemies out there.
There's me, Gabi, the others…
We're all on your side.
Just hang in there, Vice-Captain.
Incoming!
That jerk!
Hey, wait!
I'll slaughter him!
Protect the war chief's rear!
-Right!
-Above!
-Bad angle!
Galliard! You're a lifesaver!
-Thanks!
-Pock!
That was close! Thanks!
Be careful!
I'm not sure where Ackermann is!
He's hiding somewhere!
Are you serious?
-Porco! The War Hammer Titan!
-Yes.
She has crystallized like Annie.
My teeth are useless against that.
But you're completely worn out now.
If you had anything left,
you would stab me right through my nape.
You've got no more moves to play.
But I have plenty.
Shit! After all that, the bastard
still has more fight in him?
But if we get him, the Founding Titan…
What are you afraid of, Pock?
What?
There's no need for us to rush.
We're the ones controlling
the battlefield.
They are being driven into a corner.
They came here in ODM gear,
so their weapons and fuel are limited.
In other words, they are stranded
in enemy territory without support.
The Marley army has surrounded
the zone by now, so there's no escape.
For starters, Paradis can't compete
against Marley in a real war anyway.
But if we take out
the Founding Titan right here and now,
they can't do the rumbling!
Their trump card is right in front of us!
All the more reason to move cautiously!
Right now, just focus on protecting
the war chief from Ackermann.
That's Pieck for you!
Precisely!
Eren Jaeger is not my enemy.
Someone else comes first.
Show yourself, Levi.
You're running out of time.
Wow! War Chief Zeke is something else!
Grice?
Commander Magath!
Commander! Back in the venue--
What are you doing?
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm fine!
Then get the hell out of here!
Well, Vice-Captain Braun is underground
behind the stage, and he isn't moving!
What?
It's my fault. He was…
shielding me.
Who did it to him?
Eren…
Jaeger.
Hurry and dock!
We need soldiers at Liberio on the double!
The whole zone's taking heavy damage!
What?
Hey! Get your ship out of here!
Can't you see the fleet?
Hey!
What?
Battleships?
Snap out of it! Get the hell out of here!
But, Commander Magath…
It's the port.
The only one who can do that--
The Colossal Titan!
The Titan they stole from Bertholdt!
Those shits!
I guess they didn't barge in here
without a plan after all!
How about this, you damn devils?
If you lose the Founding Titan,
your plans mean jack shit!
The other Ackermann? Out of my way!
War Chief! Here comes their attack!
-Zeke!
-Get down, Gabi!
-Zeke?
-Pieck! They are coming!
-What's wrong?
-Hey, Carlo!
Say something, man! Carlo!
You will pay for that!
This is for last time.
Now! Fire!
Pieck!
Guys!
NEW ODM GEAR
GEAR USED BY THE PARADIS ISLAND FORCES
WHICH UTILIZES
COMPRESSED GAS AND WIRE HOOKS
FIRED FROM SPECIAL EQUIPMENT TO ALLOW
THEIR SOLDIERS TO NEARLY MIMIC FLIGHT
Are these the sort of sights that you saw?
Bertholdt…
No. Please, don't!
Hurry! Finish it off!
Don't shoot! Please, stop!
It missed?
Was it because of the steam or…
Is it my fault I missed?
Pieck!
It's the Cart Titan!
Run away…
Pieck!
Hurry!
Protect Pieck!
Eat shit, you devils!
Braun! Give Grice a hand!
Yes, sir!
Look out! Stay back!
This way! Hurry!
Not only the war chief, but Pieck, too?
Damn it!
Damn you!
So fast!
Ymir's Jaw Titan was nothing like this.
So this is the Jaw Titan's power?
I see.
It's awful.
Her body can't heal fast enough.
But she's a Titan, so why?
Unlike the Armored Titan,
the Cart Titan
isn't exactly known for its toughness.
Reiner! Where is he?
You said Eren Jaeger got him
and he's not moving!
Can't he fight? Hey!
I don't know!
He's still underground
behind the stage, but I…
I'm thinking
we should leave Reiner out of it!
What are you saying?
What about Udo and Zofia?
What about all the people
Eren Jaeger killed?
Hey, Gabi!
Stay away from the window!
The enemy will see you!
What?
Commander!
Commander! I've spotted the guide lights!
Thank goodness.
So far, the operation is going as planned.
We're counting on you, Onyankopon.
Leave it to me, Hanji!
Sneak through the zone, low and slow.
We'll follow the lights
and pick everyone up.
We've only got one shot,
so any stragglers are out of luck.
If we're not shot down first, that is.
Talk about a reckless plan.
Did you get possessed
by Erwin or something?
I can only hope.
If it means his strength is with me.
Now that it has come to this,
if we can't recover Eren and the others,
there's no future for us.
Jean, it's here.
Yes. Right on time.
You guys think you're escaping on that?
Not happening!
Shoot!
What?
Hey…
You're kidding me!
Stop!
Stop it!
Please, stop!
What happened?
The War Hammer Titan was eaten.
And the Jaw Titan is next.
It can't be…
Not Galliard, too.
No…
-What?
-No!
Reiner!
Help us!
-Hey!
-Galliard is about to get eaten!
Help us!
Reiner!
-Shut up.
-Reiner!
Can you please be quiet?
-Please! Be quiet!
-Reiner!
-Help us!
-Hey! Cut it out, you brats!
-Reiner!
-Hey! Cut it out!
-Help us!
-Why won't you guys…
just let me…
die in peace?
Out of strength, the Armored Titan falls.
Furious to have her hometown trampled,
Gabi picks up a gun and takes off.
Next episode, "Assassin's Bullet."