We were abandoned.
That's why we live in a camp
surrounded by walls.
Because the blood of devils
runs through us.
That's also why your father isn't here.
Your father…
is a Marleyan.
He can't be with us Eldians.
If only we were Marleyans…
Oh, right.
Back then,
I strove to be a Warrior
so we could be Marleyans.
Who said you could walk?
Run, you filthy seed of swine!
Don't you want to be Honorary Marleyans?
Did you guys hear?
We're attacking Paradis Island
in just a few years.
-What?
It's almost time for us to inherit Titans!
Out of the seven of us,
they are picking six!
Yes! I can finally be a Marleyan!
What? Why are you so excited?
If we have to leave
the worst person out, it will be you.
Excuse me?
-What's your strong point?
-What?
Your strength?
Your brain?
Your aim?
Combat ability?
No.
The only value they see in you
is your loyalty to Marley.
"I'll slaughter the island devils
real good for you, sir!"
Are you making fun of our mission?
Or maybe you're a stray Restorationist?
What?
You are, aren't you?
I'll report you to the commander!
Report this, you little shit!
Do you want some more?
Porco, enough!
Hating the island
doesn't make you special!
Have fun waiting for 13 years alone!
-Damn it!
-Porco!
Let's go, Pieck.
Don't cry too long
or the commander will chew me out.
Reiner, I'm sorry.
Stand up, Reiner.
Come on.
I'm going to become a Marleyan
and live with my mom and dad.
I can't wait for 13 years.
But it's like he said.
I'm the worst one here.
Porco doesn't make the decision.
Besides, loyalty is important.
Right, Annie?
What?
I wasn't listening.
-Do you really want that as your goal?
-What?
Thirteen years is all you get.
Thirteen years to be a hero.
If I crush the devils on Paradis,
I'll save the world.
Then my parents will be proud
to have me as a son.
I wish something would happen.
Eren! There you are!
Marvelous.
Even better than we expected.
The Female Titan.
Versatility is its biggest strength.
On top of its mobility and endurance,
its hardened strikes
are incredibly destructive.
The range is limited,
but it can call Pure Titans, too.
Leonhart is perfect.
The Armored Titan
specializes in hardening.
If it charges in at full speed,
the gates of any wall will crumble.
As Marley's shield
that must withstand attacks,
it suits Braun's perseverance.
The Jaw Titan is an assault weapon.
It's as speedy as it is small,
with claws and jaw
that crush nearly everything.
Entrusted to the quick-witted Marcel.
The Beast Titan is as potent as ever.
Though slightly larger
than the other Titans,
its throwing technique
is dreadful on another level.
What's more, his blood
seems to have hidden power.
The Cart Titan has outstanding endurance,
suitable for long missions.
It can be outfitted with different
equipment to extend its usefulness.
Pieck's superior judgment will serve well.
And then, there's the Colossal Titan…
A god of destruction.
Hoover will be able to handle it.
I feel bad for those island devils.
One day, that's going to
show up to kill them.
This new Warrior Unit
may outperform their predecessors,
but I question the military's decision.
Sending children to retake
the Founding Titan sounds insane to me.
You think?
Didn't those children
just crush a nation before our eyes?
This is messed up!
Why was the worst of us chosen?
What did you do?
It seems you're the worst one.
That's all there is to it, Pock.
You little--
Porco! Are you sure
you want to defy the brass?
What?
Reiner.
I'm sorry.
What?
Dad!
It's you, right?
Mom used to work
in these barracks before I was born!
That's where you met her! Karina Braun!
Look at this!
Mom and I are Honorary Marleyans!
-We can all live--
-Bloody hell!
Did that woman send you here?
To get revenge on me?
Shit!
Now her kid is a Warrior?
If they find out where you're from,
my family is screwed!
You're going to get me hanged!
I'm running the hell away!
Away from you and your damn Eldian mother!
Reiner!
I'll be waiting for you!
That's right.
Even without a father,
I'm still the chosen Warrior
of the Armored Titan.
I'll save everyone from the island devils
and be the world's hero.
We didn't cover much ground tonight.
We can't do much about the clouds.
Will the King really not use
the Founding Titan,
even if we break the wall?
What's the use of asking now?
Trust Marley's research.
That's right. We can't turn back.
Tomorrow, we reach the wall and then…
What?
Are you having second thoughts
about killing the devils?
Have you forgotten what they have done?
We're the world's chosen Warriors
sent to punish the island devils!
-I'm sorry.
-What?
Reiner, I'm sorry.
You were never meant to be
chosen as a Warrior.
I talked you up and criticized my brother
to influence their decision.
What?
I…
just wanted to protect my brother.
I'm sorry, Reiner.
I'm sorry!
Why…
are you apologizing?
Bertholdt…
Annie…
Marcel…
They got eaten!
They got eaten because of me!
And I'll be next!
This is where I'm going to die!
Not bad.
This is a first.
You actually beat me…
in a long-distance race.
What?
If we…
took out that Titan,
we wouldn't have lost Jaw.
Shit!
Now Marcel is gone for good.
They said there wouldn't be
Titans this far out!
We've got to go home.
What?
Let's find Jaw and leave.
They would have changed back to human.
Besides, without Marcel to lead,
this mission is doomed.
Wait.
We can't…
We can't!
We can't go home!
We've got to continue the mission!
Oh, right.
If we go back now,
you'll just get eaten by the next Warrior.
Not that I give a shit.
-You think only I will?
-What?
That only I will get the blame
for running away?
You guys are that certain
you won't get eaten, too?
Catching Jaw won't be easy either.
If they used its power and ran,
our Titans could never catch up.
They can't control it
right after becoming--
You had no problem controlling
the Colossal Titan immediately!
Anyway, we're doomed at this rate!
Without the Founding Titan,
there's no going home!
Back there, if you were a fraction
as calm as you are now,
we wouldn't have lost Marcel or Jaw.
But you've got no problem intimidating us
to save your own ass, right?
How about you come clean to Magath?
Tell him, "It's all my fault!"
Honorary Marleyan, my ass!
Chosen Warrior, my ass!
Marleyans! Eldians!
They are all liars!
Everyone only thinks about themselves!
I'm no different!
I've got to get home alive!
If you feel guilty, just die!
Take all the blame and die!
Reiner is dead.
If we need Marcel,
then I'll be Marcel.
Please stop this.
This is the only way
we'll be able to go back home!
Let's go back…
together…
to our hometown!
What?
I wanted to be a Warrior.
I thought I could make my mom's wish
come true and we'd live with my father.
But…
I had a father
who didn't want any part of us.
My mom had a dream
she knew would never come true.
I should never have been chosen.
I should have died today.
Why did he apologize?
Why did he save someone like me?
No! I'm not ready for this to end!
I still don't understand anything!
Where am I?
Inside Wall Rose.
Annie.
Bertholdt.
I'm sorry.
Marcel…
I'll be the Warrior I should have been.
You!
What the hell did you come here for?
To save humanity!
WARRIOR CANDIDATES
A UNIT OF CHILD SOLDIERS
CONSISTING OF ELDIAN "DEVILS"
UNDER THE COMMAND OF THE MARLEY ARMY,
THEY UNDERGO HARSH TRAINING
ONLY ELDIAN "DEVILS"
CAN INHERIT THE NINE TITANS
I lived in Wall Maria,
deep in the southeast mountains.
It happened at dawn.
The animals were all stirred up
and I heard a strange rumbling.
Thinking they were footsteps,
I opened the window.
The rest is a blur,
but I ran away on my horse.
Leaving behind three kids
about the same age as you guys.
Hey, missy.
You've got good taste
in men to tail a geezer like me.
I was born at an inn.
My mom, who works there,
talks about my father so much.
I know that it's you.
Well, that's really touching.
If you want a hug from Daddy,
put your hands up.
How are you sure it's not you?
I made a promise to my sister.
This joke of yours isn't making me laugh.
You're so mean, Dad!
Hey, now.
Having a rebellious phase, are we?
That's a new one.
Are his legs saying
it's going to snow today?
No. That's the clear skies position.
Just call it hail,
or you'll be late for muster.
Wake up, Bertholdt!
While you two snoozed
after playing with your friends,
I was busy crawling around
the capital's sewers.
If he's around, this is my limit.
Your limit…
Let's take what we know back to Marley.
They will be happy to hear anything.
Do you honestly think that?
Not if that's all we have to show
after five years.
Then what do you want us to do?
Destroy Wall Rose.
It's the only way we can
smoke out the Founding Titan.
A lot of your friends are going to die.
I keep telling you.
They are not friends, they are devils.
But gaining their trust can't hurt.
And frankly, your aloof behavior isn't--
I'm going to barf.
Can you move your face away from mine?
I bet you're exhausted.
Sorry for always laying the burden on you.
Let's call it a day.
I keep having the same dream.
I dream about the guy
who hung himself in the fields.
Why did he tell us that story
right before he hung himself?
Eren, take a break.
You're going to die.
Shit!
Reiner, how do you do it?
How can I be more like you and Mikasa?
At this rate,
I'll die without doing a damn thing!
Just do what you've got to do.
Keep moving forward.
That's all we can do.
Yes. You're right.
Aren't you going to
drive out every last Titan?
I know you can do it.
Shit!
I can't let this go on!
That's right.
I still have those guys.
The hospital…
Hey!
Well, I guess you're recovering well.
You're good enough to talk now.
Kind of.
I'm here for emotional trauma,
but it's a lie.
What?
I said I lost my memory and can't go home,
but I just don't want to.
It would be hard to face my family now.
Will you snitch on me?
I wouldn't do that.
You're hurt.
Is it from your Warrior training?
Yes, but I won't become one.
Another candidate is so talented,
I don't even stand a chance.
-That's good to hear.
-What?
You're a good guy.
I hope you live a long life.
But I don't want them to be a Warrior.
Why not?
Is the other candidate a girl?
She's famous around here.
She did incredible things in the war.
Everyone's saying
she should be the next Armored Titan.
But since I'm powerless,
I can't do a damn thing about it.
Every day I'm here, I think,
"Why did it ever come to this?"
Damaged minds and bodies…
Their freedom taken away…
Even losing themselves.
If people knew it would come to this,
nobody would go to war.
But most people are pushed by something,
forced to march into hell.
That "something" wasn't their choice.
Their situation or others made them do it.
But people who push their own backs
see a different kind of hell.
They can see something beyond hell.
It might be hope.
It may even be another hell.
Only those who keep moving forward
will ever know.
Magath sorts out the military
for the Tybur family to tell the truth.
As the festival enlivens the city,
an unexpected surprise awaits Reiner.
Next episode, "From One Hand to Another."