Hey.
It's dangerous here.
Fly away…
somewhere far away.
Falco!
What?
-What is my brother doing here?
-Good!
You're still talking!
Colt!
Time to run! Hold on!
Falco!
Colt? Status report?
It was a direct hit.
The Eldian Unit at the front
got blown away.
And the trench?
It's hopeless! We can't dig any farther!
We can't? You're calling the shots?
An Eldian, giving orders?
Watch your tone with
Commander Magath, you mutt!
But at this rate…
Falco, are you drunk?
He must have hit his head badly.
Do you remember this war
we have been in for four years?
Who are you guys?
Wait. What?
Wasn't I flying around
with a sword just now?
Like, whoosh!
And there were Titans that I--
I guess I'll just have to explain
everything from the start.
Listen up and listen carefully, Falco.
This battle is the climax of a war
that has lasted four years.
If we can take out Fort Slava…
Well, technically,
if we sink the Mid-East Allied Forces
fleet in its port,
it will spell victory for Marley
and end the war.
But unless we take Fort Slava
sitting on the high ground,
it's hopeless to attack the port.
Why can't the Marley fleet just do it?
Seriously, Zofia?
You have faith in the fleet?
It took those imbeciles four years
-to control the seas!
-Oh, god!
-And guess what?
-Oh, my god!
-They lost half their damn ships doing it!
-It hurts!
Now they are telling us
they are too chicken
to attack until we take the fort?
Screw them all! They are pricks!
Udo, you're going to
squeeze Falco's head off.
Oh, my! Sorry!
So what's the deal?
Why did they send us
Warrior candidates to the front lines?
To judge us, obviously.
To pick which one of us
will be the next Warrior.
The time is coming.
Commander Magath chose
the front lines to be our final test.
He knows what's on the horizon.
The plan to conquer Paradis
needs a main player…
The successor of the Armored Titan!
The Armored Titan…
I wonder which one of us it will be.
Really, Gabi?
It sounds to me like you're saying
none of us come close to you.
Because you don't, right?
Well, Gabi does have us beat.
As far as our grades go.
No. There's more to it than grades, Udo.
I keep telling you.
The difference between us
is that I'm prepared.
To shoulder the fate of us Eldians
and to slaughter that island of devils,
who have done nothing but make us suffer!
I'm going to win this battle
and prove that the Eldians left
in this world are good Eldians!
I refuse to lose until I free everyone
from the internment zone!
Well, what exactly are you doing?
Pretty cool, right?
It won't work, Commander Magath!
We can't destroy the railroad without
the machine gun slaughtering us first.
They've got soldiers
along every inch of the trench.
To top it off, the fort can
bombard us whenever they want.
If we stay here too long,
they will just shower us with shells!
Do you have a better idea, Colt?
We should let Jaw and Cart loose.
Galliard and Pieck will get it done.
They will wipe out the trench
and bunker in a flash.
No.
If we play our cards wrong, we lose.
Commander Magath, "that" showed up.
What's "that"?
That.
An armored train.
It's equipped with
four massive cannons in total.
They are the Allied Forces'
new weapon, Anti-Titan Artillery.
If one of those 150mm rounds hits
a Titan, it will kill it in a single hit.
Even one of the Nine.
But both of our Titans
are incredibly fast.
The odds of hitting their nape--
And if they did?
We would lose a Titan and a Warrior,
with no guarantee
that we would get their powers back.
That's right.
Just like our plan nine years ago
to retake the Founding Titan
that resulted in us losing
the Colossal Titan and Female Titan.
The perceived hit to Marley's
military might is what sparked this war,
putting the Paradis Island Operation
on hold.
What is it that makes
our motherland, Marley, so great?
The Power of the Titans.
Correct.
Our nation won't last
if we keep losing them.
The Power of the Titans is absolute,
and it must always remain that way.
Prepare the Eldian Unit for attack!
-Yes, sir!
-Commander Magath! But that's--
What's the matter, Eldian?
Are you not Warriors
who swore loyalty to Marley?
This is a chance for the 800 Eldians here
to serve our motherland with honor.
All creatures drink of joy
at nature's breast…
Everyone, up! Prepare to attack!
Come on! Stand up!
Eldians!
Your mission is to assault
and destroy the enemy railroad!
The suicide squad will rush the bunker
and disable the machine gun!
Listen up!
Let your actions purge
the disgrace of being spawn of the devil!
This is your chance to be honored
by our great motherland, Marley!
Prove yourselves worthy!
-Yes, sir!
You Warrior candidates are to stand by.
The 800-strong Eldian Unit
must destroy the rail at whatever cost.
As long as that armored train
is patrolling the fort,
the Armored Titan and Beast Titan
can't do what they came for.
But…
Colt.
As the chosen successor
of the Beast Titan,
learn what it means to lead already.
Perfect. We can destroy the train, too.
Please, let me take a shot at it.
What?
Surprise!
If you will let me, I can disable
the armored train all on my own!
Hey, Gabi!
How much do you think Marley has spent
training you all these years?
Hell no.
It's true.
I am exceptional
compared to Falco and the others.
There may never be another Warrior
as talented as I am.
Not to mention one this cute.
But if I succeed, we won't lose
the whole unit of 800 Eldians!
And if you fail?
You lose just one promising candidate
and seven hand grenades.
If you think I'm more valuable than
800 Eldian soldiers, I totally understand.
You love me so much
that you would rather sacrifice
the lives of 800 soldiers over me--
Fine.
Go ahead.
-Gabi, don't--
-I swear!
I will prove to you that I'm worthy
of inheriting the Armored Titan!
What are you doing?
For this to succeed,
please allow me to remove my armband.
Very well.
Hey, someone's coming this way.
It's a woman.
Girl, actually.
I think she's surrendering.
No, wait.
She might be an Eldian.
It looks like something's wrong with her.
She's dragging her leg.
What if she is an Eldian?
Shoot her before she turns into a Titan.
Screw that.
If you want to shoot her, you do it!
Shit.
What the…
Wait.
Wait for it!
Wait!
She isn't moving.
Who cares? Shoot her!
Now is my chance!
She really did it!
Galliard! Hurry up!
Damn it! You Marleyan cowards!
This is why you bastards…
all deserve to die!
Gabi!
Falco, don't!
Galliard!
What?
The armored train has been disabled.
We'll now commence the airborne assault.
Remember to stick to the plan.
Zeke will be our spear
and Reiner will be our shield.
MARLEY: A MILITARY DICTATORSHIP
AFTER THE GREAT TITAN WAR,
MARLEY WAS REVIVED
AS A FORMIDABLE MILITARY POWER,
UTILIZING 7 OF THE 9 TITANS AS WARRIORS
Damn, that hurts!
Why did a Marleyan like me get shot at?
-What are you doing, Falco?
-You Eldians are supposed to…
-Can't you tell?
-soak up the bullets!
He's in no shape to fight us anymore.
Udo, give me a tourniquet.
-Here.
-Stupid kids.
Screw the enemy.
Is that supposed to be your selling point?
You really think obeying the laws of war
will earn you the spot of Armored Titan?
It's not going to help, you know.
Like I care?
Weirdo.
He's saying something.
Interpret, Udo.
Say I stopped his bleeding
and that he will be fine--
"Don't touch me."
"I'll be tainted."
"You devil," he says.
Retreat! Hurry up!
Get away from the fort!
Don't get caught in it!
It has begun.
Ahem!
No! Stop!
Truly devils…
Our Marleyan ancestors
were eaten, just like that.
By you Eldians.
Fire!
The kinetic bombardment went well,
but due to the altitude,
roughly half died on impact.
A lot of the Anti-Titan Artillery
are still operational.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-nine.
And now I know their locations.
But still…
More walls?
I'm sick and tired…
of walls.
-It's the Armored Titan!
-Kill it!
Fire!
Anti-Titan shells that
penetrate even my armor?
What the…
What hit me?
An armored train? There's another?
Shit!
Fire--
Galliard!
You son of a whore!
Nice!
They got it under control?
Our defeat brought about this war, Reiner.
Isn't war a terrible thing?
Finally…
With this, the war will be over.
What?
With their fleet destroyed,
the Mid-East Allied Forces signed
a peace treaty with Marley.
The war spanning four years
ended in a Marleyan victory.
But as the world learned that the era
of Titan domination was coming to an end,
Marley was pressed to obtain
the Founding Titan as quickly as possible.
Oh, no…
Thanks to the incredible bravery
of the Marley army,
Fort Slava has fallen at last!
-Unbelievable!
-Hooray!
-That's our Marley army for you!
Hooray!
"Titans are not absolute."
Marley was shown this painful reality.
Victory providing a brief joy,
the Warriors return
to their hometown of Liberio.
Next episode, "Midnight Train."