I doubt this is something
you want to hear,
but just listen.
Three years ago…
Back then, we still might have been
able to change something.
THREE YEARS AGO
Captain!
The team that went ashore
hasn't made contact for two hours!
I see.
Prepare to send teams two and three.
Yes, sir!
This island of devils defeated
the Warrior Unit.
Whatever the cost,
Marley must learn what happened.
Hang on!
It's a devil!
Hello, friends from Marley!
Welcome to Paradis Island!
I'm Hanji!
I'm here to greet our guests
who have come so far across the sea!
Now step this way
and join us for some tea!
By the way, we're already friends
with this guest that arrived before you!
Isn't that right, Niccolo?
Captain! Forget about me
and shoot these devils!
-What are you saying, Niccolo?
-Captain!
He's tired of your shitty skit.
Niccolo!
Understand this, you devils!
Marley doesn't mingle with filthy blood!
Go drink your pig piss
with your filthy friends!
Hey!
Are you sure you want to be rude to us?
Can't you see the Titan behind you?
We'll never yield to you devils!
Say hello to this!
What?
Hands up, Yelena!
Drop your weapons.
What are you…
Do as she says.
Hanji, I would be happy
to accept your invitation.
Let's have tea.
I've longed to meet you…
Eren.
That huge lady of theirs
shot and killed her comrade.
I wonder what her goal is.
Who knows?
Whether a friend or foe,
she's not to be trusted.
No napping, Sasha.
But their willingness to share information
is unbelievably lucky for us.
Yes, we've been really lucky.
We stopped their landing by pure chance.
If Marley comes in force,
we'll be screwed.
We've got to do something.
Well…
Oh, my…
Oh, I see! That's how it shoots a bunch!
That's a standard-issue in Marley.
The Marley army
has 20,000 soldiers per division.
With fifty divisions,
that's one million soldiers.
There's also the navy with 3 fleets,
each comprised of 21 battleships.
They have made tremendous progress
in new weapons and aerial warfare as well.
Aerial?
Damn it!
Don't freak out
or they will think we're weak.
I know!
In other words, vehicles allowing one
to attack the enemy from the sky.
-What? From the sky?
-Hey!
If Marley had such capabilities
this whole time,
why haven't they attacked in over a year?
There are two main reasons.
One being the Pure Titans released here.
Even with the latest weapons,
they would hinder a land assault.
They were used as a tool
to confine Eldians within the Walls,
but in turn,
they have protected Eldia from invasion.
Yes. Well, isn't that funny?
Though dawn is coming soon,
and that's when Titans are active.
But if we're way out here,
sipping on tea outside the Walls,
you must have killed
all the Titans roaming around.
Is that true?
-What?
-And what if it is?
Are you going to report it to Marley?
No, it blows away my expectations.
And the second reason?
Currently, Marley is at war
with multiple nations.
They can't be bothered with Paradis.
You defeated the Warrior Unit,
the pride of Marley,
and captured two of their main weapons,
the Colossal Titan and Female Titan.
Marley's many enemies took notice
and were quick to unite and declare war.
If you guys are secret agents
who infiltrated Marley,
I'm guessing you came
from conquered nations?
Oh, am I right?
If you're going up against Marley,
I bet you've got big backers!
We're not secret agents
or anything of the sort.
We were powerless.
Marley took our homes
and forced us to be soldiers.
We were close to losing hope
at ever striking back.
Until we met him.
A Titan that people of the world feared,
calling it a devil.
But I saw something completely different.
A god.
One that gave hope to the powerless.
Under Zeke Jaeger's command,
we shot our superiors.
We're the Anti-Marleyan Volunteers.
Our goal…
To free the Eldian people.
That concludes Zeke Jaeger's requests.
"For the sake of all Eldians
whose existence is threatened--"
Absurd! I don't even want to hear it!
He's the Beast Titan!
He turned the people of Ragako
into Titans and incited a panic!
This is the same person
who nearly annihilated the Scouts!
His one and only goal
is to retake the Founding Titan.
Since he can't do it by force,
he'll attempt it diplomatically.
He should know that we'll expect that.
Let's hear what else he has to say.
"According to Zeke, he has a secret
plan to solve the Eldian issue."
"To carry it out,
it requires the Founding Titan
and a Titan with royal blood."
"With both, the world can be saved."
"However, he will only reveal the plan
when his conditions are met."
Bullshit!
He must think we're idiots!
Eren?
He's telling the truth. I remember…
The one time I was able to use
the Founding Titan's power
was when I touched
a Titan with royal blood.
That Titan had to be
my father's other wife, Dina Fritz.
Zeke, Dina's son, must have figured out
a way to elude the vow renouncing war.
The one single hope
remaining for us Eldians…
To wake the millions of Titans sleeping
in the Walls and activate the rumbling.
You…
Why did you keep quiet
about this for so long?
I was concerned for Historia's safety.
I couldn't let her get made into a Titan
based on some hunch of mine.
Yes, it was careless of me.
We'll talk about it later.
But if that's really true,
Zeke's secret plan holds up.
Are you nuts? You trust them?
Yes! We can't have all those
soldiers on the island!
We ought to hang them all!
No, we can't do that.
To protect the island
from Marley's scout ships,
we need the volunteers.
Without their wireless radio…
This is the first… scout fleet.
Request… aid.
This is the… first scout fleet.
Second fleet. Go ahead.
What a relief! Our ship ran aground!
We've been waiting for your help.
We're on the way! In the cove, huh?
How many ships? Don't worry!
Two are headed your way!
Hey!
Are you okay? We're coming to get you!
-It's the Colossal Titan!
-How?
Hey! It's the enemy!
Hurry! Jump!
Run!
Jump off!
Welcome to the filthy island
of filthy devils.
You're going to love it.
As long as you like pig piss.
You can leave if you want,
but not on a ship.
Are you good at swimming?
It was fun back then.
Certainly, we Eldians are feared
and hated by the world.
By people across the sea
whose faces we don't know.
But not everyone across the sea
was our enemy.
And we found out the world itself
was complex and full of unknowns.
By the way, why do you have
dark skin, Onyankopon?
Because our creator thought,
"It's more interesting
with a mix of people."
You Subjects of Ymir are the same.
We exist because we were wanted.
Who created us?
The one who gave the Founder Ymir power.
God.
That's what some people believe.
Aren't we free to think what we want?
What the hell is this food?
Is it even edible?
Smells fishy.
You've never had seafood?
Niccolo's a master of Marleyan cooking.
Jerks. If you don't like it, don't eat it.
Eldians like you don't--
So good!
-Hey!
-No fair, Sasha!
Niccolo! You're a food genius!
Stop eating like a pig!
I've never had anything like this!
There's plenty, so take your time.
The port will be finished soon!
Thanks to the Marleyan engineers,
building it has been quick.
They have surely been cooperative.
It went bad at first
since neither side trusted the other.
But given enough time, if we set aside
our labels and see each other as people,
we can understand each other.
Armin, have you seen Bertholdt's memories?
What? Yes.
But there's nothing that seems helpful.
There's not much time.
Zeke has less than three years left.
Yes, about that…
Do we really want to go along
with Yelena's plan?
What's the problem?
Is using the rumbling to threaten
the world the only way to protect Eldians?
Then we will be the devils
that terrorize the world.
Before it comes to that, can't we talk?
If we can fix Marley
and the world's misconception…
"Misconception"?
What "misconception"?
You know, like how we're scary.
The world sees us as monsters
who can turn into Titans.
They are not wrong.
There are Marleyans who like us, too.
How many?
Most of the Marleyans
are sitting in prison cells.
But given enough time…
Yes. We need time.
That's right.
And to buy us that time,
we've got to keep them at bay.
I wonder…
Did we make the right choice?
I can't help but think,
"Could there have been some other path?"
I thought I understood Eren
better than anyone.
Even Mikasa.
But I don't know anymore.
SCOUT FLEET
FORMED TO INVESTIGATE PARADIS ISLAND
AFTER THE OPERATION TO RETAKE
THE FOUNDING TITAN HAD FAILED
THE FIRST FLEET EMBARKED IN 851
Hey! Aren't you a Marleyan?
What the hell are you doing here?
This graveyard is full of people…
-your kind killed!
-Wait!
-Let us take care of this guy!
-Let go!
Sorry. Please.
Marleyans can piss off!
Hey, Niccolo!
Are you okay?
Damn it! Why?
Is Sasha really dead?
Yes.
Why? What the hell were you guys doing?
Shot by a kid who sneaked on the airship?
It's too ridiculous to be true.
It was no ordinary girl.
She had been trained.
A Warrior candidate?
I let my guard down. Sorry.
Why are you apologizing to me?
All I did was cook her food.
Thanks for letting her eat
so much tasty food, Niccolo.
What do you think about this, Conny?
Sasha and I were like twins.
It feels like half of me is gone.
You're…
You all knew my daughter, didn't you?
Excuse me.
I'm just a captive Marleyan,
but I'm allowed to work as a chef.
Your daughter loved eating my food
more than anyone else.
So if you ever want to…
please come and eat my food.
On the house, right?
Of course.
You guys are calling it a victory.
Isn't ignorance a scary thing?
If I send your dead body to Marley
and reveal your little plot,
your gramps and granny are done for.
But if this secret plan of yours is real,
I can wait to chop you up.
Either way works for me.
I appreciate your graciousness.
But don't I get to meet Eren first?
Don't be in such a hurry.
We've got the finest hotel for you.
You can stay there and relax for a while.
Hey. Can you please stop glaring at me?
This is all of the Titan serum
we stole from Marley.
But you'll have trouble reproducing it.
No, we should manage fine with this much.
I only wish we could properly thank you.
We owe you so much already.
We were ignorant, but you gave us hope.
For us to suspect you,
we're truly no better than devils.
For three years, we've done nothing
but show we're friends of the Eldians.
It's unfortunate.
The guns we brought
were meant to give Eldians freedom.
I know it's selfish to ask, but can you
overlook our cautiousness for a while?
We have to keep Zeke on a tight leash.
It's fine, Commander Pyxis.
We'll dine at the same table again soon.
This is my hotel?
You got a problem with it?
It's a forest of giant trees.
I can't think of a better place for you.
Might be lots of fun with ODM gear.
Hey, Captain Levi.
Do you think I could show
Gabi and Falco this natural wonder?
Damn it.
Whether they see the sights
or not depends on you.
Eren Jaeger!
Eren would have done it alone.
Whether we helped him or not,
the worst would have happened anyway.
In any case, we killed a lot of people.
The navy, army, and civilians
got dragged into it.
And just like that, all were lost.
But unless that port was destroyed,
Marley would have retaliated
and attacked the island.
We killed any hope for peace,
but we had no choice.
Just like you guys that day.
Hey, Annie.
Say something, please.
Fight or die.
Win and live.
The only way to win is to fight.
Fight.
Fight!
Without any allies on the outside,
they must kill their enemies to live.
Is that the right choice or not?
There's not a soul who knows.
Next episode: "A Sound Argument."