Ed!
Get Tom Rudd in. Now.
Were offering him Northern
Ireland, the lucky sod.
I think he's expecting
to be offered Transport.
Well, tell him he's taking the bus
to George Best airport, right?
He's making Paul Remmington
a cabinet minister.
Rem-tard Remmington.
I mean the guy is an epic...
Fuck-up.
He's so dense that light
bends around him.
Come on, people!
Let's get going here.
I've got a to-do list
here, that's longer
than a fucking
Leonard Cohen song.
Rem-tard at Energy and Climate change.
Really?
I'm not getting that.
It's not on here. How did you get that?
About Remmington?
Refresh the page!
Yeah... Ah yeah...
Oh, look! Fatty's staying put.
They're not moving Fatty!
Yeah, well, That's because they don't have
five big blokes and a winch.
They couldn't really demote Fatty,
because he knows too much.
He doesn't know where the Ryvita is kept, does he?
I've got this re-shuffle going on.
The Lemmington Spa
by-elections coming up.
I've got more on my plate
than a spinster at a wedding.
That wasn't a reference to your
daughter, by the way, Andrew.
Well. That's Hugh gone then.
- That's so sad, isn't it...Hugh.
- Yeah.
You don't give a shit!
No, I...perhaps I don't.
Northern Ireland office - Tom Rudd.
Who's Tom Rudd? Tom Rudd?
Isn't he in Harry Potter?
Tom Rudd is army slang
for standing up buggery.
Doug, Doug - Douggie!
Look at you - cock the size
of Pink Pather's tail.
Come, have a Kit Kat.
Uhm... I'm afraid I turned it down, Malcolm.
You know that 90% of household dust is
made of dead human skin?
That's what you are.
To me.
Doug Hayes is a massive abortion.
Again, not a reference to your daughter.
We need somebody to plug
this DoSAC hole.
Anybody.
Fucking mammal with a head.
Have you two finished
emptying your desks yet?
Yes, don't worry Terri,
we're all ready to go.
I'm just trying to get
everything organized
for whenever whoever arrives.
They are gonna have
their own people.
It's gonna be very embarassing if your
handcream's still in the drawer.
Handcream?
Yeah, or whatever men have.
I don't know...
Electric nose-hair trimmers...
...Ex-lax...
Awww... Look at Glenn...
Your face.
On the scrapheap
at the tender age of 76
that is no life for you,
is it - Glenn-nes.
Hey, do you want me
to call Dignitas?
I could call Indignitas.
They could come around and shove you out
of the window, dressed as a clown.
Sam, Sam...
Get me uhm...
Nicola Murray.
If she says no, the only other
candidate is my left bollock ...
... with a fucking smiley face
drawn on it.
Ladies and gentlemen...
May I introduce the
new Secretary of State ...
-Hello
-for the Dept. of Social Affairs
... and Citizenship,
Nicola Murray.
- Thank you.
- Hello. Lovely to meet you.
- Hello, hi.
- I'm Glenn.
- Glenn Cullen.
- How lovely to meet you.
-These are just...
Hugh's previous incumbents.
- Ken and Ollie?
- No Glenn...
- Ollie Reeder.
- Right.
- Are you an Ollie or an Oliver?
- I'm whichever you prefer, in fact.
Well okay, Oliver. I like
the name Oliver.
- Well, Ollie. I don't know...
- Oh, you are an Ollie.
... don't know why I said that.
- Thank you.
- Good.
I'm the ideas man.
- Sorry... I've gotta...
Thank you.
Just need a .. one second.
Uhm.. Yes I know.
But they frog-marched me into it.
I didn't know...
I had no idea.
James, be fair! I left
seven fucking messages for you.
Your secretary or whoever
it is, is useless.
I don't think the school thing
is gonna be a problem.
It's not going to be a problem, cause
they have vetted me at Number 10.
And obviously nobody has
soiled themselves ... or shot me.
Great, well I take your warm
congratulations as implied.
Fucking... arsehole.
- You alright?
- Yes, it's all a bit crazy.
just feels like my head is made
entirely of smoke alarms.
It's all just a bit - ugh!
Yes, well it was all a bit of
a shock for us all, you know.
- In a good way, in a good way.
- Good.
Well like twins or tax rebate ...
Yes, let me continue with the tour.
That's such a nice chair...
This was Glenn's office.
Is there a chance of getting
something like that?
Would you like me to have
it moved to your office?
- Great, could you do that?
- Right.. Ollie... ?
- Ollie, that's right.
Glenn and Ollie, what
I need to know from you...
All the stuff that Terri's
not gonna tell me
- the stuff she's gonna keep from me.
- Oh, huge list.
- Where the bodies are buried.
- Exactly.
- Yes, the plate pits.
The big cardboard boxes with
bits of old junior minister.
Just going to sort out
that policy digest.
- Lovely.
Urban renewal is a bit
of a running sore.
- In what way?
Well, it's very woolly and big.
Like a mammoth.
(laughter)
Right... Okay, so uhm...
My big thing... Come in actually.
Come in to my office
with nowhere to sit
or put anything.
My primary focus is
social mobility.
- That's very much my big thing.
- Right.
I'm really telling you that really,
partly to get your take on it
and also so that you can
start spreading the news
and printing the posters.
And, you know.
Fire up the turbo charges,
set the phasers to equality.
- It's Murray time!
- Well, the thing is
and Ollie, please, correct me
here if I'm wrong
-Oh, I will certainly do that.
Social mobility and making people
richer, costs money
Yes, and we don't have
any of that.
If you speak to
Nick at the Treasury
he will tell you the same
with his annoying lisp.
What you're telling me basically is that
I'm going to be a woman
with a computer and some pens.
Well, it's just the pen budget.
I mean I have just as
much real power
as those twats who sit on
either side of Alan Sugar.
Well... Yes.
Secretary of State, we have some
clothes for you to look at
- for a press photograph later.
- Oh.
- We can do this later, maybe?
- Definitely.
- You're size 16?
- I'm 12.
I'm so sorry, I will get those changed.
Right away.
At the moment
I've got nobody at all.
Apart from Hugh's guys
who are just kind of
so fucking patronizing
And cold. Seriously, one of them
looks exactly like
he works at menswear at Selfridges.
I don't know what
the fuck to say to him.
Secretary of State?
- Yes?
- Your fruit salad.
- Thank you.
Oh I've just had a couple
of press calls
Couple of the papers asking about
your husband and the PFI.
Already? My God.
They're so on it.
Could you brief me?
Yes, sorry... It's honestly nothing.
James works for Albany,
which is the company
that was awarded the PFI prison's
contract by this departement.
-Yes, I remember.
I know that sounds bad,
but actually James wasn't at Albany
when the contracts were awarded
and I wasn't here, so
- Yeah, maybe.
- It's not a conflict of interest.
I think you could just run
that by Malcolm.
He's on his way.
Not Malcolm... He's what now?
Coming in?
Yes, he'll be up in 25 seconds.
Okay... Fuck.
Right.
So Malcolm Tucker, Malcolm Tucker,
Malcolm Tucker!
Malcolm.... I'm not nervous,
you know, it's just...
Malcolm's sort of one of those
things that I'm aware of
without ever having really
come into contact
... with. Like a rat.
No, he'd hate that.
He thinks of himself as a sort of
thin white Mugabe.
Do you think?
Because if you are
worried about Malcolm
we have amassed a few tips
how to deal with him,
over the years.
We have worked out when he's
gonna give you a verbal colonic
and some avoidance maneuvers.
Tai-kwon-spin!
Is this the No 1 Ladies Detective Agency?
- Malcolm Tucker!
The real deal.
- Hello.
- The real deal. Good to see you.
You're looking great.
All right, hens and bracket. It's time
to hang up your lady cocks.
Nicola Murray. Here you are.
Secretary of state.
For the Departement of Social Affairs
and Citizenship.
Yep, I now have one the of the longest
job titles in Western politics.
Thank god I don't have to wear
a lapel badge.
It's a pity we couldn't just make
an abbreviation of it, you know
like PFI.
Which I think stands for
Pretty Fucking Embarassing.
If you're a bit sloppy
with the details.
Which clearly your
fucking husband is.
Okay, look.
James works for Albany, fine.
He wasn't even working there when
the contract was awarded.
- Don't worry... That was just me.
- Okay, right. fine.
That's the sort of thing
the press will throw at you.
I mean - you step out of line,
they'll be all over you.
Like a pigeon on a chip.
Is that you chair?
Oh god, yeah. It's cool,
isn't it?
It's got lumbar support.
Bin it.
People don't like their politicians
to be comfortable.
They don't like you having expenses,
they don't like you being paid
they'd rather you lived in
a fucking cave.
Okay, fine. So...
What should I be sitting on?
Should I just get an upturned KFC bucket?
A fucking normal chair.
Right?
Not a fucking massive
vibrating throne
Malcolm must be hating this.
All these bright fresh new
ministers to blood in.
and to plan a by-election.
If it's any consolation to you
a little bit of you will always be
in this departement
because she's got your chair.
Doesn't she? She has got your chair,
and in fact your dandruff.
Hahaha. If I go, that chair
is coming with me.
You know those old men you see
who go to the park to read the paper
That'll be you.
You could go in your chair.
They'll make you king of
all the tramps.
So uh... You have three kids, yeah?
- I've got four.
- Four?
Katie's sixteen, she's the oldest.
She's just left school.
Not going to a college,
to a university ?
Uhm, she's a bit of a rebel.
What sort of a rebel?
What are we talking here
Are we talking a pierced navel
or holidays in Pakistani
training camp?
It's chiefly heroin.
Although she has cut down since
getting pregnant
by that Nigerian people
smuggler, because
the track marks would have
affected her porn carrier.
- I'm sorry to disturb. Uhm.
- Morning Malcolm
- Morning, Terri.
Just wanted to give you
a few things - here
that's change from
the fruit salad
this is this morning's paper
- do excuse me -
I'm surprised that you
hadn't vetted me
I thought you'd know
about the kids.
It's just that you were a sort of
late-ish kind of appointement.
That didn't quite give
me the time to
to fuck the i's and
fist the t's
as Robert Robertson might say.
Sound to me like, she's only bringing
in one other person, so
I wonder whether she might keep
one of us on permanently.
Thank God I'm safe.
Gee! We know you're safe, Terri!
How do we know you're safe?
We know you're safe, because
you keep using the word "safe"
like bloody Jim Bowen.
You've got a dull sack,
that's safe
do you want to go for
the treasury, young lady.
Okay. This is Walton.
What about these other kids.
What ages are they?
They're 11, 9 and 5.
Eleven?
-Uhm.
So that's a secondary school?
No, she's still at a primary -
state primary.
Lovely little school
with terrible SAT results,
but a really good kind of
broad demographic.
and steel band.
She will be going to a secondary school,
what - in September?
Yeah, yeah.
So... uhm...
I can see where
this is going.
Uhm.. it's not
an issue.
Great! If it's not an issue I can
just fucking toddle off then
I will go and have a nice relaxing
wee sleep under my duvet.
Probably will have to tug myself off
cause I'm so fucking relaxed about that.
Cause I know there is
no fucking issue here.
Right?
She's not going to
a comprehensive, Malcolm.
She's going to a local
independent school.
Jesus H... fucking Corbett.
Do you honestly think...
Do you honestly believe that as a minister
you can get away with that?
You are saying that all your
local state schools
ALL the schools that this governement
has drastically improved
are knife-addled
rape sheds
and that's not
a big story?
For fuck's sake!
Sort it, or abort it!
Let's get this clear.
My family is off limits.
Alright? This job is not going to get
anywhere near my husband
and my kids.
Just doesn't.
Of course it fucking does.
as per the wee bar code
and the serial number
under your right armpit
you are now built and owned
by the state
and you're under the spotlight
24 hours a day, darling!
You know what you are?
You're a fucking
human dart-board.
and Eric fucking Bristow's on the oche
throwing a million darts
made of human shit
right at you.
Can you take that?
Can you?
Okay, look. You -
the all-swearing eye -
You didn't even know how
many kids I had
You had to ask me.
So who on Earth in the press is
gonna even know or care?
Do you remember
The Big Breakfast?
- Remember that program?
- Yes!
Remeber how Chris Evans started that?
D'you remember it was a big success?
And then they had that guy
Johnny Vaughan - remember him?
Everybody loved him. Fuck knows why
but they loved him.
Do you know what
this is here?
This here -
is fucking series 10.
of the Big Breakfast.
And you know
what you are?
You're the fucking
dinner lady
that they've asked to come
to present the show.
The reason I didn't know
about you and your children
is you are so low
down
on the list
of candidates for this job
I didn't even have the chance
to look into you.
So low.
Waaaaay waaay waaay way
... low.
You are now being scrutinized for
what you wear, what you say.
For your hair,
your shoes
your fucking earrings,
your fucking cleavage
and your dress - which
by the way
is way too loud.
- Too loud?
- Yeah! I'm getting fucking tinnitus here.
Look.
Your crooked husband -
I can make go away.
But your crooked husband combined
with you being worried about
your underaged daughter coming
home up the duff
from some truanting bastard -
I cannot.
She goes to the comp - okay?
Oh, God.
You Glenn, yes
and or Ollie.
Terri!
Just a quick update really.
- How did it go?
- It was all very positive
we sort of know where
we all stand now
the PFI thing you know about
- not a problem, Malcolm's fine.
Second little thing I've
just apprised Malcolm of
is that my eleven year-old daughter
will be going to a private school.
- Oh, for fuck's sake!
- Sorry...
- It's a personal issue
I'm not Education Secretary, so
Nor will you be!
Secretary of State - with respect -
this is political suicide.
- Thank you very much
for your support, Glenn.
I was hoping there was
another way around it.
Sorry, there is no way around it,
it's horrible,
It's a bit like Dover.
You know, if you wanna
go to France
you've got to go through it.
We don't have to go through
Dover to get to France
you can go through Weymouth,
through Portsmouth, there's plenty ...
I don't want to go to Dover.
I don't want to go to
fucking Dover or France!
I just want my daughter to
be happy at school.
Great, well that's good,
that's excellent.
That's .. you've got principles,
the common thing ...
For fuck's sake Ollie,
there is no point
telling her just what she
wants to hear, is there?
So Terri?
Yes? I'm sorry, but personal
issues are not my brief.
Okay, thank you
for that.
The chair -
the lumbar chair
has to go to skip,
Malcolm insisted.
Oh, okay.
Not now, cause I've got
work to do
but if you could get somebody...
Apparently, if you have a nice chair
it turns you into
Saddam Hussein.
The entire building
smells of cold sores.
Ah, so -
first cabinet meeting.
How do you feel?
Anxious, nervous,
worried?
Well she probably wasn't until you said
"anxious, nervous, worried?"
Now you are an advert
for Tarmazipan.
Going sick all over the Foreign Secretary
- would that look bad?
No - Jeffrey House shat himself on
his first morning.
Ollie, please!
Well I find that kind of tomfoolery
very tiresome.
Sorry - Terri,
what's the driver's name?
It always makes you look more human
if you know their name
I am human, so.
It's Elvis.
Seriously, what's
his name.
No, it's Elvis.
He's from the Ukraine,
you see.
And nobody can pronouce
the real name
So they call him Elvis on
account of the - uhuhuh.
What?
Take a peak.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
You look like you've shat
a lego garage or something.
Jim Lane's daughter is standing as an
independent in Lemmington Spa.
(noises)
This is going to split
our vote.
Do you thing we're
in trouble?
Maybe we should have chosen
her over Liam Bentley.
No - she thinks just because her
dead fat-ass dad was an MP
that gives her the right to be
our candidate.
No no no. This isn't
tsarist Russia.
This isn't fucking Dimblebys.
What do we do?
We'll send everyone up there.
To support Liam Bentley,
including the Prime Minister.
You want to send Tom
up there?
Yeah, fuck it, he'll be alright, as
long as he doesn't do the smile.
You hit the phones, right?
I'll be with you in two shakes
of a crying baby.
Wow.
Black widow.
Malcolm.
Congratulations - first cabinet.
I heard you wowed them.
The meeting's literally just finished,
how would you know that?
PM texted me - he's
very impressed.
You could be nominated for
best newcomer.
Really?
No.
You knew Jim Lynn,
didn't you?
The dead fucker.
God rest him.
Yeah, I did a bit
back home.
Very sad - all those weeks
on life support.
Nice chair.
Sad? Lying on you back, getting fed
nutrients through a tube?
It's my idea of a fucking
holiday.
How would you like to
go to Lemmington?
When?
This morning.
It's never too soon
to go to Lemmington.
I've just taken over a departement,
I have a hell of a ...
You've been asked by the PM
specifically to pop
along to Lemmington
and do some photo-ops
with Liam Bentley.
Supporting him, yeah?
I don't really have any
choice, do I?
Of course you have
a choice.
You can decide exactly
how you say "yes".
You can do it with a voice.
Have fun with it.
Yes.
In my own voice.
I look forward to
toasting your success.
Have a lovely time in
Lemmington, yeah?
Can I go?
Of course you can
fucking go.
Jesus.
Never easy.
Never fucking easy.
- Yeah, hi.
- Hey.
Um, yeah.
- Glenn.
- Glenn ...
What do you think of
Glenn?
Huh. Well it's sort of like asking
what do I think of skirting boards
I mean - I assume that we need them
but I'm not really sure why.
I'm finding him
very old-school.
Well, yes.
He's ancient school, really.
Glenn - he used to get his packed
lunch nicked by Plato
he's an old ...
So I'd like you to come up to
Lemmington with me.
Oh great, yeah.
Well, it's a...
it's my favourite of
the spa towns.
Apart from all
the other, so.
Okay, lovely. So if you could
just get
uhm, Terri in.
Please.
Sure!
- Terri!
- Yeah?
You're on.
What?
What were you and Bravo Two Zero
talking about in there?
- Who?
- Her, you know.
Her in there.
Bravo Two Zero.
Well, I don't know what
that means, Glenn.
Yes you do - no,
I don't mean that, I mean
Juliet Bravo.
You've completely lost me,
Glenn. I really ...
Juliet Bravo! She was a
lady policeman.
A lady policeman? Did the last 30
years not happen to you?
- What?
- Have you been asleep
in a box of straw like a Blue Peter tortoise
Lady policeman.
I've asked Ollie to come up
to Lemmington with me.
- Ollie?
- Yeah.
I can't really connect
with Glenn.
You think I shouldn't have
asked Ollie?
No no - I didn't say that.
You sort of did with
your face.
No no, Ollie has got
plenty of good points.
It's just he's ...
well he's a little bit morally bankrupt
and massively self-centred.
And a tiny bit dangerously
unreliable.
But he has got a lot of good points,
as I say.
Great - well
thank you.
Can you just send
Glenn in for me?
Glenn!
Nicola would like
to see you.
- Hi Glenn, take a seat.
-Thank you.
You ever worked in
retail, Glenn?
No, never have.
Oh, just...
Uhm, so what do you
think of
Terri - do you
trust her?
No.
Right - cause she just told me she
sort of prefers you to Ollie.
When I say I don't
trust her -
What I mean is I don't
trust her around money.
Really?
Blimey, what - she
steals?
No no no no - I'm
not saying anything like that.
Cause actually - I got very little
change from my fruit salad.
No no no - let me just
roll back a little bit here.
Perhaps, uhm...
all the way to the boathouse.
Actually, I do
trust Terri.
Okay.
Your chair's gone.
Oh yes, yeah...
I had to
bin it - Malcolm insisted.
But it was my chair.
Oh right, I...
It was
It was decadent, Glenn.
It was a chair
gone mad.
Do you know where
it's gone?
Skip.
I'm sorry - for your loss.
I paid 600 pounds
for that chair.
How's her hair?
Terri, you'll be delighted to know
that the Secretary of State is now
checking her hair
in my glasses.
You're on TV live.
What now?
You're on now -
apparently.
Why are you
squatting down?
Ah - there she is.
Malcolm - Nicola
will be there in a minute.
No, you're in the shot
actually, Ollie.
Why am I in the shot?
* Nicola Murray! *
Hi everybody,
well - uhm
I'm very pleased
to see
a number of familiar
faces here - Hello!
Isn't see good
with the people?
Yeah, she is.
But then - so is Kate Thornton
and she's wanted
for war crimes.
Ladies and gentlemen
let's take a look at Liam
Bentley's election poster.
Mrs Murray, do you feel
your husband's involvement
in the PFI's prisons contract
compromises your position?
Well, I'm just here to support
Liam Bentley
You don't think there's
a conflict of interest?
No - I really don't.
- Excellent.
- She's handling this very well, Malcolm.
You think?
Will you resign,
minister?
Oh shut up,
you twat!
... and I think they're
interested also in
greater opportunities
for social ...
Looking terrific, Ollie.
What? Sorry?
A little bit edgy.
Can you please make sure
Nicola's right in the middle.
She doesn't look
important enough
could you just -
move her over.
- Could you move for a second. ?
- Right here?
Perfect!
- Perfect, that looks terrific.
- No no no ...
No!
Jesus - Terri!
The letters!
That's great.
What does is say,
Terri?
- It says Liam...
- No it doesn't
- ... Bentley.
- Not there it fucking doesn't!
- Back where you were -
please, stay
This is obviously
the hot spot.
Well okay, if you crop the ...
Well of course if you crop
Malcolm!
You tried.
You really tried.
Did your best,
mate.
Very happy with it.
You both did
your best.
Thanks.
Big smile!
Hi darling! Did you see
mommy on the telly?
I know,
did I look funny?
It did, good boy.
It said "I am bent".
Have you uhm...
Yes.
Yeah, is this now official
news that's calling?
Great - someone's just sent
me a Youtube clip
which is me, in front of
the "I am bent" sign
randomly intercut with
bits from Family Guy.
It's not even funny! Why do people
fucking do that on Youtube!
Look - let's learn and grow
from this experience.
We can make a blacklist
of words
you should never
stand in front of.
In case the press gets
to do something like that.
- Peacock.
- Peacock, of course.
Shuttlecock. Spatchcock.
Anything with cock, really.
You remember that
folk singer - Tim Hardin.
Well you'd be able to get
"I'm hard."
Out of that.
Coarsefishing - that  could be
arsefish if you crop that.
And walkie-talkie could be
cropped to say
alkie - twice.
There are no
walkie-talkie
why would I stand in front
of a walkie-talkie sign?
Malkie-Malkie.
Well you know, Howard,
she's not bent
neither in the sense of
being corrupt or being gay.
And by the way, that's an
incredibly homophobic
headline - you massive puff.
You've got egg on your
face, Howard.
You over-easy
piss-bag.
Oh hey Yoko Ono and
the two remaining Beatles
piss off.
Right - any chance we could just
skip over the usual abuse bit
and move on to the part where
we sort this out.
Yeah.
You need to make
a decision.
Are you still going ahead
with the private school
because if you are, we need
to draft a statement
saying that your husband
is leaving his job.
Are you taking a piss?
You're expecting me
to choose between
fucking up my
daughter's life
and fucking up
my husband's life?
Yeah.
So I just have to choose
between them.
Like they're on some fucking
cosmic dessert trolley.
Listen darling - I can't fight on
two fronts, you know?
If the press run with both
of these stories
you're fucking dead.
You set this up,
didn't you?
What?
To put me in
my place?
Or get back at me
for ignoring your advice?
Or some other weird
perceived slight
that doesn't in any way merit
this massive fucking out-of-proportion
Isreali-style response.
You don't realise - I'm your
fucking fairy godfather - right?
Jesus - God
help me!
I'm your fairy
fucking godfather.
I've got
a magic wand
that I can wave about
but I've got a fucking Blackberry
and a chiff.
You've got a decision to make,
You make it -
talk to you later.
Malcolm!
Sorry - can we just carry on
talking about that thing?
Was it you who positioned
me there?
Do you know what the first
sign of madness is?
Paranoia.
Have you seen that film -
A Beautiful Mind
the one with that
Russell Crowe?
The one with
the maths guy
he thinks the CIA are
working away in a shed
at the bottom of his garden.
That's you.
No. I am not
the mad one here.
You are the mad one.
You're Russell Crowe.
Oh no no no.
You are Russell Crowe.
And you need to fucking
listen to me, Russell
you fucking antipondean, fucking
kangaroo-loving fruitcake.
See this poster stuff
that's fucking
small fry
The really horrible stuff
that's all still about to fucking
happen to you - right?
Right you're coming in here so
we can carry this on?
- Now?
- If you can spare the time!
Uh, no.
I - no. I can't...
I don't use lifts,
I'm claustrophobic.
You're what?
Not hugely -
I can be in rooms
you've seen that - I just
don't do lifts - that's all.
This lift is - I mean it's
fucking huge!
I mean this is bigger
than some rooms
this is bigger than
some people's flats.
It's about not being able
to get out.
Oh, well that's great.
That's fucking great.
That's another fucking thing
right there.
Not only you've got a fucking
bent husband
and a fucking daughter that
gets taken to school
on a fucking sedan chair.
you're also fucking
mental!
Jesus Christ,
see you
you are a fucking omni-shambles
that's what you are.
You're like that coffee machine,
you know
from bean to cup,
you fuck up.
He so is Russell Crowe.
- Who?
Nicola, I did want to tell you
that I
I tried to get a message through
to Ollie ...
- I know.
- I have been doing this
a long time now,
by which a mean, you know
in an experienced - firm hand on
a tiller sort of way.
Not in a clapped hard
over the hill kind of way.
- Yeah I know.
- I've learned to look out
for these sort of things
I have developed a kind of
sonar for them now
like a bat.
Glenn, do you want to...
would you want to maybe
stay on
I could use that sonar.
Batty man.
Right.
Uhm, forgive me...
I think that's
Jamaican slang for
"homosexual".
Yes, I was thinking that
as I said it
I'm really sorry -
I didn't.
No no no no.
I'm on my way down -
see you by
the front door, Elvis.
Have you decided?
Oh, shit.
Yes, Malcolm,
you know I have decided
the minute you told me
I had to decide.
I'm gonna change
Ella's schools.
Good for you.
Listen - I'm gonna try and get
your social mobility thing moving.
I talked to the chancellor
I'm gonna keep banging
away at it - you know
like Charles Haughtry
on a sleeping guardsman.
Okay.
I mean she's ...
She's very bright so
- Yeah?
- They say if you're very bright
then it sort of doesn't matter
what school you go to.
That's true.
That is very true.
Hey!
See you later -
state educator.
It's a highly expensive lumbar
support chair, for God's sake.
Oh don't be ridiculous.
I mean that's paper recycling, it's
not gonna be there - is it?
I'm gonna call you in the morning
and if you're not there
you're in big trouble.
Glenn.
See this...
Dickensian hysteric
who's just gone home?
Here's what you do -
right?
You're made out of great aw's - yeah?
You make a big noise
to impress Nicola.
But secretly, you're wanking
behind the curtain to me all the time.
You want me to
pass information onto you?
Don't kill yourself though -
well, not over this
you know.
I just want you to make
her feel good - you know?
You can be a friend of
Dorothy's - can't ya?
Then we'll all get some fucking
peace around here!
Right!
I'm on my way
to wipe my arse
on pictures
of Nick Robinson.
I'm getting good
at getting my queef.
[subs by .knotie
edited by gilly]