Like you have no [bleep] head
on your shoulders.
Good night.
I just wanted to say thank you.
You really saved my ass
out there.
- I'm jon.
I'm nik's boyfriend.
- Oh.
- You're sneaky.
- I came here for you.
- I didn't even invite you!
- You're mingling
with a bunch of fake people.
- You know what?
You're rude.
Bye.
- ♪ oh, oh ♪
♪ glamorous days,
glamorous nights ♪
♪ in the fast lane,
everything is insane ♪
♪ glamorous days,
glamorous nights ♪
♪ that's how I live my life ♪
[echoing]
♪ live my life ♪
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my god,
it's so good to be home.
- I forgot to tell you.
- What?
- I put in a call
to doreen
To possibly move
into a corporate position.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- I had no idea
that you even wanted to work
Rate.
- I've been flying for, jeez,
really, ten years.
- Wow.
- When you add it all up
together...
- Yeah.
- I'd be going into work
At 9:00.
I would be done
by 4:00 or 5:00.
I could have a dog.
I could have a boyfriend
And then possibly late
have a family.
- That's so exciting.
Corporate--farrah.
- I hven't even heard back
from her yet,
'cause, of course,
I'm obsessing
about the phone call.
- She'll call. Don't wo.
Don't worry.
♪ ♪
[women vocalizing]
♪ get out ♪
- Are they kind of hot?
- [mouths words] oh, my god.
I love that there's
really cute guys at this bar,
But my own boyfriend
won't even talk to me.
- Have you tried calling him?
- I text him a few times.
He didn't answer.
Then I tried to call,
but...
- He didn't answer?
- Because he doesn't want
to talk right now.
Jon and I got
into a huge fight,
And I'm realizing
that long-distance is difficult.
And I don't know
where we stand.
Anyway, let's talk
about something happy.
- Someone's birthday's
coming up.
- No.
What do you normally do
on your birthdays?
- Oh, nothing. I never celebrate
my birthday like that.
Never have, like,
a party or anything, so...
- Really?
- I have a ten-year-old son,
And at this point,
he's my main focus.
It's a sacrifice sometimes,
but it's my choice.
- Honey, I have
a month-long party
For my birthday.
- It's not a big deal.
Yeah.
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ one, two, three ♪
♪ all my friends
keep calling ♪
- Good morning, birthday girl.
- Happy birthday,
birthday girl!
Pack your bags!
- For wha?
- We have a flight booked
in, like, two hours.
- A flight?
- A birthday flight.
- Where are we going?
- Surprise.
- What am I packing?
- Anything you can find
in your closet.
- Flip-flops,
boots,
Bikinis, parka,
Basketball.
- Come on, snow boots?
- Tennis racket.
- So where are we going?
- We're going
to the library, tasha.
- ♪ I like to keep
my suitcase packed ♪
- Come on, party girl.
- All right, listen.
You guys, I'm not taking
another step
Till you guys tell me
where we're going.
It is my birthday.
Can I get some info here?
All:
We're going t vegas!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
All:
Yeah, baby.
- I made a few calls,
worked my magic,
And got us hooked up
with a suite at the palazzo.
- Yeah, vegas.
- And as for getting a flight,
we're flight attendants.
It's not a problem for us.
- All of us together.
- All five of us.
- I'm so excited to go.
When I think
of birthday parties,
I just think of taevon and cake
and kid things.
But vegas for me
anst me in vegas,
Let's do this.
All: Cheers.
- Whoo!
- Welcome to las vegas.
- Ooh!
- A limo.
- Hi.
- Wow.
Wow. Hi.
[ringtone plays]
- Hold on, hold on, hold on.
It's jon.
Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
I was thinking,
since you're off tonight,
You should fly down
to san francisco so we can talk.
- I'm actually in vegas
with the girls.
It's tasha's birthday.
- Why didn't you tell me
that you were going to vegas?
- Uh, we haven't talked.
I haven't had a chance
to tell you.
- We need to deal
with this.
- Right now I'm in vegas.
I'm just here
to have some fun.
So we're gonna have
to talk later, I guess.
- Are you serious?
This is ridiculous.
Nikole, we need to talk
about where we're at.
So I was think--
- Now's not really
the best time.
- You know what?
I'm gonna let you go.
You have fun in vegas.
- Nikole, let's go.
- How'd it go?
Everything okay?
- Jon just hung up on me.
- Screw jon.
It's time to party.
- Jon can wait.
We're in vegas.
- Going to vegas!
Whoo-hoo!
- It's vegas, baby!
- ♪ get ready, go ♪
♪ this is your life ♪
♪ enjoy the ride ♪
♪ ♪
♪ this is your life ♪
♪ enjoy the ride ♪
[echoing]
♪ the ride ♪
- This room
is beautiful.
It's huge.
[all screaming]
There's bedrooms over here
and bedrooms over there.
Everything is perfect.
- Are you guys jumpng--
[all screaming]
- Thank you.
- Cheers to vegas.
- Birthdays.
I mean, have I ever
let you guys down?
[laughter]
- Can you rephrase
that question?
- Have I let you down
so far on this trip?
All: No.
- Cheers.
- Thank you so much.
[laughter]
- That was a good one.
Just thank you, guys, for, like,
going out of your way,
'cause you truly
didn't have to do that.
You guys mean a lot to me,
Although you may not think so,
but you guys really do.
I do have a mushy part
in my heart. It's there.
- Happy birthday, tasha.
- Thank you.
- Happy birthday, honey.
- We have to get ready, though,
'cause I am feeling
a little airplane-y.
- What are you guys wearing?
- Ooh.
That's a good question.
- Hopefully nothing
by the end of the evening.
- Ooh.
- Oh!
- What?
- Let's do it.
[pop music]
♪ ♪
To your birthday.
- Cheers.
- Yeah, right.
- The one time
I spent new year's in vegas,
The guy I was dating
brought viagra with him.
- That's not good.
- So we're in the bed
For, like, 12 hours.
- No.
Shut up.
- From, like, 2:00 a.M. Till
about 2:00 p.M. The next day.
- What?
- I woke up facedown like this.
All: Oh!
- Blech.
- I'm gonna get me some of that.
[laughter]
That's the kind of party
I'm looking for.
- My craziest story was,
I was here in vegas,
Approached
by a beautiful couple.
- You were.
- If I swung that way, maybe.
- I get that all the time,
honey, in grocery stores.
- Grocery stores?
- In the grocery store.
[laughter]
- I should go grocery shopping
more often.
[laughter]
- Vegas has never really ben
a jackpot for m
For, like, finding dudes.
- Yeah.
- I might meet a guy,
and he might be really nice,
But all it's gonna do is make me
thankful that I have jon.
- You're in vegas,
and I'm just down to have fun.
- Yeah, I know.
Atever appens happens.
- No thinking
about jon tonight.
- I'm feeling
like I'm ready to par-tay.
[dance music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I'm in the club, man ♪
♪ I got her body steaming ♪
- I was having myself
a great time.
It's the first time all five
of us have been out together,
And it's time to shake
some stuff up in here.
- ♪ my smoke alarm,
she on fire ♪
♪ my smoke alarm,
she burning up ♪
she on fire ♪
- I was looking around the club
for nik and tasha.
Then I see nikole
on the catwalk,
Heading
toward the stripper pole.
- ♪ going up and down that pole
like a flag ♪
♪ shake that thing
from the front to the back ♪
- Me and tasha
started getting crazy.
Like, having so much fun.
- Then this guy walks up
with a pile of cash,
And she is working for it.
It's like,
"what are you thinking?"
Doesn't even phase her.
- ♪ I'm in the club, man ♪
- I guess when you're in vegas,
You either go big,
or you go home.
- ♪ she on fire, fire ♪
- ♪ bounce, bounce, bounce ♪
- ♪ hey ♪
- There's cowboys everywhere.
- ♪ bounce, bounce ♪
♪ bounce ♪
- ♪ hey ♪
- We were dancing.
We were drinking.
We were laughing.
We were having a good time.
Vegas is crazy.
- I get we all have
to have a good time,
But nikole's acting
like she's single,
Partying up with these guys.
We're just like, "wow."
- ♪ hey ♪
- ♪ bounce, bounce, bounce ♪
♪ bounce, bounce, bounce ♪
- ♪ hey ♪
[dance music]
- Come on, girls.
[girls cheering]
I need you to come up
to the dj booth.
- I love hanging out
in the dj booth
When I'm at a club.
The dj--he was cute.
He looked nice.
He looked like he wanted
to have fun,
And I really just thought,
"that's why they call it
sin city."
♪ ♪
- We're laughing,
having a great time,
And then we see rodney,
Tasha's baby addy.
What is going on?
- Did he not get the memo
this was a girls' weekend?
- Ld rodney
to come to vegas.
We hang out.
We kick it.
I know when he's around,
I'm guaranteed
To get some cake in vegas.
- I'm watching tasha
dance with rodney,
And then tasha leaves.
She didn't say anything.
She just bounced
- I guess she wanted
to make sure
Her birthday night ended
with a bang.
- It's really surprising,
But I guess
it's non my business.
It's tasha's birthday.
- But then we've got nikole
over here...
With the dj?
I-I don't know
what's going on,
But it's starting
to get crazy.
- ♪ let me
you get naked, yeah ♪
- I see nikole eing
Really touchy and feely
with this dj.
- ♪ freak it, girl, we on ♪
- I'm just thinking,
"nik, what are you doing?"
- ♪ you know I got it
freaky girl ♪
♪ my freaky girls ♪
- All me and jon do lately
is fight.
So I'm in vegas.
Like, there's a dude.
He's paying attention to me.
And we'e not fighting.
It was nice.
- ♪ you know I got it ♪
- If jon finds out
about this,
He's not gonna be happy.
- When you're in vegas,
You're just kind of livng
the single life.
Sometimes you forget
you have a boyfrien at home.
I know I did.
- Oh, jeez. Oh, jeez.
Oh, jeez.
- I'm just hungover.
This is how I feel
about last night.
- [laughing]
- Hello?
Yes.
Hi, doreen.
Oh, good.
Yes, I am.
Yeah, yeah, that's okay,
No problem at all.
- Vegas is so ridiculous.
It looked like you were having
a good time.
- You and tasha.
- Dude, what--
tasha, like, she--
- I can be there
no problem, doreen.
- Rodney, just, like,
out of nowhere?
What was that about?
- I just think
that's kind of rude
That rodney would show up
on a girls' weekend.
Hello? We put
this whole thing together.
And then she just bails
for rodney.
- Thanks, doreen.
I'm hungover, dehydrated.
My head is a-poundin'.
But I finally got this interview
that I've wanted.
Doreen from corporate,
Really?
I got to get
my [bleep] together.
[door closes]
- Right, 'cause it was supposed
to be a girls' weekend.
I just don't think
that's cool.
- [whispers]
I think they're finally done.
- Oh, well, well.
- Schwoo.
- Damn.
Tasha did get
a birthday present.
- And there she is.
- Hey, ladies.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Ladies.
- Did you have fun last night?
- I had a lot of fun.
It was my brthday, so...
- What's up with, uh,
you bailing on us, though?
- Rodney showed up,
and...
He showed up.
It's not a big deal.
- It's not a big deal
to bail on your friends?
When you go out with a group of
girlfriends, you stick together.
- Could you even remember
that I left last night?
[laughter]
No answers.
- There was a lot of work
that went into this weekend.
- And I appreciate it greatly.
- Well, it wasn't just
about you.
- It is my birthday.
I do what the hell
I want to do.
- We all collectively
wanted to have a girls' weekend.
- It was the end
of the night.
I didn't know that we needed
to walk out
Holdig hands together.
I don't see the big deal.
- You left us.
That was your choice.
- If that's how you want
to put it,
If that's how you feel.
- It's the truth.
- Not why I left.
- You left the group.
I just think that it's rude
To leave all your friends.
- I think it's rude
for you to kiss a boy
If you have a boyfriend.
- I didn't kiss a boy.
And you're [bleep] rude.
- I'm not [bleep] rude.
- Yes, you are, tasha.
- No, I'm not!
I'm just telling you!
[bleep], you kissed a boy.
I left with rodney--
big deal.
- I didn't kiss a boy
last night.
- Okay, well,
what happened?
- You need to get
out of my face right now.
- Well, I'm not, so...
- I don't want to talk
to you anymore.
- All right,
so we won't talk to her.
- Nik.
Nikole.
- What?
- Come here.
- No, I don't want to be
around rude people.
- Let's talk about this.
- No.
- I ain't rude.
- You are rude, tasha.
- No, I'm not, nikole.
- If I say you're rude,
it means you're rude.
- No, it don't mean
that I'm rude.
You ain't gonna just keep
[bleep] talking [bleep] to me.
I'm not rude.
I'm just stating facts.
[door closes]
Close the door.
That's best.
- Well, I don't know who's gonna
deal with that situation
In there, but I'm going
to gamble,
So is anyone down?
'cause that's wherm going.
- Me.
- Let's go.
I am out.
Sorry, guys. Bye.
- All our money!
- ♪ c-c-c-come on, baby,
give it to me ♪
- Winner, eight easy.
- We won!
[cheers and applause]
- It's fine.
Me and jon will deal
with our problems.
I just think
tasha's always rude.
You know, she only--
she says what she wants
When she wants,
and she doesn't care
About other people's feelings.
She could have easily said,
"I'm sorry
I bailed on you girls."
But instead,
mm, mm.
[girls cheering]
- I'm fine with it.
I love that rodney's here
And it's your birthday.
- I don't want anyone
To feel uncomfortable,
you know.
- In all honesty,
if jon had just shown up...
- She would have done exactly
the same thing.
So honestly speaking,
Ink nkole is bipolar.
One minute the chick
is throwing me a birthday party,
And then the next se's yelling
and screaming at me.
Like, you need to get
some meds, seriously.
Thank you.
I'm glad that you understand.
- I just want you
to be happy.
That's what this whole weekend
was supposed to be.
- My point exactly.
Let's win some money.
Roll that ten.
Roll that ten!
- I don't want to talk
about her anymore.
I'm really upset with tasha
For what she said to me,
But I'm more upset
at myself
For what's gonna happen
between me and jon,
Because I know
he's gonna be mad,
And I-I don't know
where this is gonna put us.
- He knows you love him.
And he adores you.
Like, h--
- Well, I should have not drank
that much.
I shouldn't have put myself
in those situations, right?
I should have just danced
with you guys all night,
And then
that wouldn't have happened.
I need to rethink
the way I have fun.
- I really don't care
about nikole's opinion.
I think what she said in the
room was really uncalled for.
Like, I'm tired of that.
I'm over it now.
I said my piece.
I said wht I have to sy.
I'm grown. I don't have
to explain anything to anyone.
And besides,
it's my brthday.
We're here to have fun.
It's over.
- I feel bad about leaving
the girls behind
After what happened today,
but I got to get out of here.
And a little part of me
doesn't mind
Leaving all the drama behind.
- ♪ everybody gets
a little lost ♪
- After this vegas rip,
I'm tired.
I can't do this
kind of thing anymore.
The timing might be right
to get this corporate job.
- Hello, farrah.
How are you?
- Hey, doreen.
Thank you for taking the time.
I know
you're really busy.
- This is why I'm here.
- You know, I just want to know
what my options are
And what my next step
would be.
- You have to really think
about, um, everything
That's going on
in your life,
Because it's gonna change.
Do you have roommates?
Virgin america roommates?
- Yes, I do.
- Well, supervisor's
a great position
It's a very rewarding position,
but it's very challenging.
There could be a day
where you're going to have
And you're gonna have to be
very, very tough with them.
You know,
you're a role model.
If you get into corporate,
You know,
you have to change.
Some of your images
may have to change.
- I mean, I'm looking
for a lifestyle change.
- Okay.
- I just feel like this
Is the next step,
and I'm ready.
- It might be a good time
and a good move for you.
But that's another thing.
I know you love
being on the promo team,
And you wouldn't be
on it anymore.
You may have
to move out.
This is the time, really,
that you need to decide
What you want to do.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my god,
I'm hurting, nik.
I drank too much
last night for sure.
How you feeling?
- I'm okay.
Just really want
to see jon.
- It was a crazy weekend.
- It's hard being the only one
with a boyfriend,
And then all of us go out,
and there's guys everywhere.
- It shouldn't be hard, though.
You made the choice
to be in a relationshp,
So you should own that.
- Well, it's not like I liked
any of those guys.
It was just--
they're everywhere.
And the guys weren't, like,
touchy-feely,
Kiss-y, grope-y,
come home with me.
- But, you know,
even if they are,
You need to know
how to handle that.
I don't know, nikole.
- I mean, I don't want
to hurt him.
I don't--I let him.
I moved away.
And now I'm running
around vegas and...
Not being a good girlfriend.
And our one-year anniversary's
coming up.
I hope we make it to that.
[indie pop music]
♪ ♪
Sync by Jujuleder
www.addic7ed.com
- Next time on fly girls...
- I was thinking
that I might head
Into the city to see amir.
- You want to put your hert
out there to be smashed?
It's crazy.
- That whole situation, uh-uh,
that doesn't work for me.
- I did the right thing.
I'm out of here.
I know
what the hell I'm doing.
Oh.
You damn snitch.
Why would you tell on me?
- Tasha.
- I know you want
that promotion and all,
But not on my expense.
Snoop dogg
album rlease party--
That is my dog.
- I can't gt my mind
off jon.
- This is not the time or place
to be talking about this.
- I need a friend right now,
and I don't have any here.
- I don't want to say
you're a bitch.