- This chick
is gonna be a handful.
- This is insane.
I don't think
Virgin America's
ever put on
an event this big.
- Mandy, I wanna put you
out on the fire truck
with Richard.
- Is that Nikole out there?
[Crowd cheering]
You show up, and the promo event
is all about Nikole.
- It's not on me, Mandy!
- We were best friends.
And then all of a sudden,
we weren't friends at all.
[Crying]
And if you don't see that,
maybe we
shouldn't live together,
because I can't
handle this anymore.
- Being a flight attendant,
you never know where
a new day can take you.
We jet-set to some of the most
beautiful places in the world,
get invited
to exclusive parties,
and live extraordinary lives.
And the best part about it is
it's our job.
- Ever since
I was a little girl,
I wanted to be
a flight attendant.
They were these independent,
confident, successful women
that were in control
of their lives.
And now that's me.
- I grew up
in a strict community
where my family had a clear
vision for me to become a nurse
until one day I realized...
That wasn't what i wanted.
So I made my own decision
to become a flight attendant.
I haven't looked back since.
- ♪ ticktock on the clock,
but the party don't stop, no ♪
- flying is everything for me.
I've been doing it
for almost nine years now,
and I'm good at what I do.
But when you travel
all the time,
I've learned that sometimes
life on the ground
can pass you by.
- I became a flight attendant
because I love to travel.
I do have a 10-year-old son
that I do need to take care of,
and he is my main focus.
- Back home in Arizona,
I was destined
for the white-picket-fence life
of settling down,
getting married,
and having kids.
But I knew
that wasn't for me.
So I headed to California
and became a flight attendant.
Now I'm in control
of my own destiny.
When we put on our uniform,
the world is our playground,
and anything can happen.
- ♪ oh, glamorous days,
glamorous nights ♪
♪ in the fast lane
everything is insane ♪
♪ glamorous days,
glamorous nights ♪
♪ that's how I live my life ♪
♪ live my life, live my life ♪
- ♪ you make me say
hoo hoo ♪
♪ you make me say
la la la la la ♪
- since Mandy and I had
our fight in Fort Lauderdale,
we've pretty much stayed
out of each other's way.
So I was excited to spend
some quality time
with Tasha and Farrah.
Since I just moved
in the house
and Mandy and I
are on shaky ground,
I definitely want these girls
on my side.
So what about boys?
Have you met any hot boys
on the plane?
- No.
- Yeah, like, I just don't--
- so you're just having
total schmoozing douche bags
pick you up?
- I've had that happen, like--
are you serious right now?
- It's the flight-attendant
fantasy.
- It probably is.
But I don't want a fellow
that's a douche bag.
[Pop music]
- Ladies, you're working rock
the Kasbah promo event, right?
- Yes!
Rock the Kasbah
is Virgin America's
most prestigious promo event.
It is a major
charity fundraiser,
and you're standing
on the red carpet in uniform.
It's pretty big.
It's Tasha's first.
- Yeah,
and I'm kind of, um...
Nervous.
I've never done
a promo event before.
This is a big thing, because
you are in the forefront,
and you are the face
of Virgin America.
So all the big bosses
are watching.
But I just think
that this is so big for me,
'cause it's my job here,
you know.
And I don't wanna get out there
and mess something up,
you know?
- No, it's smart
to feel that way.
[Cell phone rings]
Ooh! Hello.
I will answer.
Hello. Tasha's phone.
House of three
hot drunk girls.
Tasha's gettin' drunk!
- That is my phone.
Excuse me!
Hello?
Hey, honey, how are you?
- Who was it?
- I don't know.
They didn't say anything.
- You're so bad.
- I know.
- No, this bitch didn't
just pick up my phone
and say what the hell she said.
That was one of the girls
that's living in the house.
Don't worry about it, honey.
- Do you know boys in L.A.?
- I know a few. Yeah.
- Was that one of your boos?
- No, it wasn't my boo.
First of all, don't ever answer
my phone again, okay?
What kind of [Bleep] Is that?
- All I said was hello--
- hello and that we were
getting drunk, and it's my son.
You picked up my damn phone
talking to my son
like you don't have no
[Bleep]Damn head
on your shoulders--
that's what I'm talking about.
- Tasha, it was a phone call.
- That was totally
disrespectful, so good night.
- Wow.
That was her son.
- ♪ ooh la la ♪
♪ sing ooh la la la la,
come on, come on ♪
♪ ooh la la ♪
- ladies, I am so excited
for this trip!
- Me too.
- I know.
It's so nice to be able
to go to New York
for a couple of days,
especially 'cause
I have these days off.
- It'll be good to get
out of the house
and away from Nikole
for a minute.
- Yeah.
- Lord.
- Amen with that!
[all giggling]
- Nikole and I
got into a fight
literally a couple days
after she had moved
into our house.
But the good thing
about being a flight attendant
is that I can just
hop on a plane
and go somewhere fun,
and then I'll deal with it
when I come back.
- What are your plans?
- Oh, I'm gonna be seeing
my friend Avir.
Avir's the lead singer
in a band called bamboo shoots,
and he's pretty hot.
We're gonna go see his band,
and I'm kind of looking forward
to seeing if there's maybe
a possibility
of something more happening.
- Ooh!
- Maybe I'll just, like--
you know, we'll see.
We'll feel it out.
- [Giggles]
How exciting.
- Hi, Jarod.
- Hi, how's it going?
- Hello!
[all giggling]
- ♪ one, two, three
turn around ♪
♪ don't watch me now,
just turn around ♪
♪ touch your knees, don't move,
- hey, Tasha,
are you almost ready?
- Yes.
It's the day of the big event,
rock the Kasbah,
and I just hear a voice that
I don't wanna hear right now.
- Did you get your high heels?
I put 'em in your room for you.
- Bitch,
stop talking to me,
because I'm not over
what happened.
- Almost ready.
Need my belt, need my shoes.
Are you ready
to rock the Kasbah?
- ♪ walk right through
that door ♪
- you're mad?
Dude, we're about to work
a huge V.I.P. Event.
- We've gotta lay down
some ground rules here.
One, I don't ever want you
to touch my stuff.
Two, just stay out of
Tasha's zone, and we'll be fine.
- I would love to stay
out of your zone.
But it's a little impossible.
It should be over.
I'm not gonna kiss
the ground she walks on.
- Nevertheless,
those are my ground rules.
Either you like it--
- yeah, 'cause it sounds
really fun working with you
for the next five, six hours.
You have a great attitude
going into it.
- I don't have to be friends
with Nikole.
I just have to work
with Nikole at this point.
[The sounds'
these four songs and a fight]
- ♪ everybody knows
when it's on, here we go ♪
♪ laugh all you want ♪
♪ but it's totally outlawed ♪
♪ there's no control
of its own ♪
- how's it going back here?
- Not bad.
There was one guy who tried
to spit his gum into my hand.
He wanted to get rid of it,
so he was like,
"do you have a place..."
Like, who am I, your mom?
Seriously?
Hey.
Hey!
- Hi. How's it going?
It's a long flight,
and when you're not
working the flight...
- Yeah.
- I'm excited about tonight.
It's gonna be so much fun.
- You're having dinner
with your sister in Brooklyn?
- It's my sister
and her husband.
- And it's your younger sister.
- Yes, my younger sister.
She just turned 28.
- Wow. Okay.
- Yeah.
- Were you, like,
super excited for her
when she
was getting married or...?
- I mean, yeah.
My sister, she is a little
bit further along
as far as the marriage,
the dog.
Sometimes I do think...
"Should that be me?"
- I'll let you guys get back.
- Okay.
- I'll get back to my seat.
- ♪ we gotta get up and go ♪
♪ why don't you
give it a go? ♪
♪ everyone is waitin' ♪
- oh, my gosh.
- This is beautiful.
- I've never done
a promotion this sick.
We're gonna have fun, right?
- We'll see.
- Tasha, you still
cannot be mad at me.
- I understand all that,
but it was really big, so...
- We got a meeting to go to.
You need to come on.
- Yeah, we should
go ahead and do that.
- Thank you all so much
for being here tonight
and helping out.
As you can see,
this is
a ginormous production.
- Jessica is the event planner,
and all of us
have to report to her.
But for me, she's my ticket
to getting invited to more
of these promo events.
So I need to show her
that I know my [Bleep].
- When you guys are done
with the red carpet,
then you guys are gonna
go into the silent auction.
If I see one person
with a drink tonight
or chewing gum,
you're out of here.
This is not your guys' party.
You are here to work
and show me that you're working.
There's eyes
on everyone tonight.
There's gonna be a tremendous
amount of celebrities here.
We have Sharon Stone,
Daisy Fuentes,
Paula Abdul, Lindsay Lohan.
There's every executive
from virgin
across the board here,
so don't mess up.
- Lady, you just made my anxiety
go from 100 to 3,000.
- ♪ gonna be
the party starters ♪
[pop music]
- ♪ New York,
New York City ♪
- in the city.
- Shut up.
- 24 hours ago,
I had no plans
for my days off.
And now I'm in New York
with Mandy and Farrah.
That's the great part
about being a flight attendant.
- Is everybody coming
for a drink?
- Louise and I are headed
to see my friend
Avir's band play, so...
- Okay. Have fun.
- Thank you.
- See you, Louise.
- We're going
to the Empire Hotel, please.
- ♪ New York City ♪
- oh, my gosh, I just got
such a weird butterfly feeling.
Definitely have to figure
some things out this trip.
All I know is that
when I hang out with Avir,
we always have
a ton of fun.
So that's kind of what
I'm gonna have to figure out--
has this always been
in the back of your head
like it has mine,
or am I just alone on this?
- How do you feel
about the fact
that he's going to be on tour,
and--I don't know--
there might be, like,
a lot of girls around
and groupies?
- Um...
I-I don't know yet.
Everything is just kinda
up in the air.
- ♪ said it's a Friday night,
and we 'bout to do it big ♪
♪ I got my girls in the back
'cause we about to ride out ♪
- rock the Kasbah
is a a-list event.
There's no messin' up here.
- ♪ bright like a star,
pullin' up in fancy cars ♪
- bigger the car,
bigger the person.
On the red carpet,
my job is to be
the perfect flight attendant.
I'm basically a walking ad.
I need to stand there
and represent the company
just like I would
if I was placed on a billboard
or in a magazine.
- ♪ I said,
if you wanna be a star ♪
♪ look at me, look at me,
look at me ♪
♪ if you wanna be a part
of the rich and famous ♪
- I don't know
who these people are.
- It is Gavin Rossdale.
- Is it?
- You just said hello
to Gwen Stefani's husband.
- Did I?
[laughing]
- That's a pretty big person.
This is Hollywood.
- I didn't think
it would be this big.
Like, I didn't even fathom
that it would be,
you know, like this.
- Well, we're here, so...
You gotta drop the nerves.
- You know what?
I don't need any guidance.
So thank you, thank you.
- Girls, this is
Richard Branson's speech.
You need to make sure
it gets up to the podium.
- Okay. All right.
- Basically.
It has to be on the podium
before what time?
8:00?
- Before 8:00.
- So about 7:20,
I think you guys should get
to your silent auction spots.
Let's make a lot of money
and get in there.
- And make sure
you deliver that speech.
- ♪ if that's love ♪
♪ I'm giving up ♪
♪ my heart
can't take it anymore ♪
- I'm on my way to dinner
with my sister
and her new husband,
and I'm really excited.
I'm looking forward
to the visit.
So I haven't seen you guys
since the wedding.
- Yeah.
- Is it any different?
- It's weird.
You go from being
an individual to being a team.
- Your partner in crime
for life.
- Yeah.
- I like that.
- So, yeah, Farrah, are you
seeing anyone lately?
- Not...Not really.
- Oh.
- I think as I see
my younger sister
and her relationship
with her husband,
I'm thinking...
"Ticktock, ticktock.
My clock is ticking."
I want that.
I want what they have.
- So living in this situation
with all these girls...
How do you see that
helping you kind of...
Your life in the direction
of settling down,
finding the right person?
- You know, I love what I do,
but, you know, I've done this
for nine years.
I'm interested
in the next step,
and I'm seeing what that
lifestyle is like to be home.
Maybe having
this jet-set lifestyle
has hindered me
in making that connection
to maybe meet
my perfect guy.
- Yeah, this is it--
crash mansion.
- Oh!
[Pop music]
- I finally see Avir,
and I'm like,
"okay, here we go."
Hi, guys.
- What's up?
- Hi.
How are you?
- I'm good.
- When I'm with Avir,
it's such a wonderful feeling,
because, like,
I'm just happy and bubbly,
and I love being
around him.
- Cheers to a great show.
- [Coughs]
Sorry.
[laughter]
- When are you guys going on?
- Whenever they tell us.
- We'll be the groupies
in the front.
- All right, deal.
See you afterwards.
- Okay.
- All right.
- You are so giddy
right now.
[Chuckles]
- All right, so this song's
called shake it (Off).
Just go nuts, all right?
- ♪ shake it, shake it,
shake it off ♪
- ♪ I've been patient,
waiting for my time ♪
- it's so exciting
to see him perform again,
and he's, like, super cute
up there singing,
and I'm so proud of him.
♪ ♪
[continues singing
under music]
♪ ♪
- I know more than ever
that I want to take our
friendship to the next level,
but I have no idea how I'm going
to tell him how I feel.
- ♪ shake it, shake it,
shake it off ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Thank you, guys.
- So we just need to raise
lots of money.
- Right.
- Guys.
- We're trying.
- Try harder.
- When you're assigned
to work the silent auction,
you wanna raise as much money
as you can for the charity.
So you'll say
whatever you need to say
so that they put
their name down
and put a big number
on that check.
Did you wanna look
at the auction pieces?
- Yeah.
- Got some skydiving.
- Do you want skydiving?
- And it goes to charity.
- It's for charity.
Bid it up, it's for charity.
- She says
let's do it naked.
[Laughter]
- Yeah.
- Tasha, are you
taking this serious?
'Cause this is a big event.
- Yeah, of course I am.
- Excuse me, Tasha,
we're gonna need the speech
up to the podium
in five minutes.
- Okay, got you.
Thank you.
So I look down,
and Richard Branson's speech
is gone.
Nikole, have you seen
that folder?
It has to be here.
- That was your responsibility.
- At this point, I'm like,
"oh, my God."
Like, "how can you mess
this up?"
I could lose my job.
And I have a minute or two
to get up there
and put it on the podium.
We need it really fast,
so if you're not gonna help me,
I'm gonna just have to
find it myself, so I gotta go.
- Hi. How are you?
- Good. How about yourself?
- Good. Did you take a look
at some of the bids?
- Excuse me.
Go.
- Oh, thank you!
- Tasha, go.
- Oh, my God, thank you.
I gotta go. Thanks.
- [Exhales deeply]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome to the stage
sir Richard Branson.
[Cheers and applause]
- Hey.
This night has been big, real big.
Hey listen. I just wanted to say,
"thank you, thank you, thank you."
- I hope in the future if
something happens between us,
it doesn't have to be
some big thing.
Like, I just hope that
we can forgive each other...
- Right. Okay, well, just--
I just wanted to make sure
you accept my apology,
'cause you did--
you saved me tonight,
and I really appreciate it.
[Applause]
- ♪ she wants to ride
really low ♪
♪ she wants to take
the top off ♪
- hey. What's up?
Thank you.
What's your name?
- Astrid.
- Avir.
I like your necklace.
- Thank you.
- So the show was super good,
but I was really excited
to finally get to talk to Avir
one-on-one.
- Mandy, Bianca.
- Hi.
- Hi, I'm Bianca.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey.
- Awesome, awesome show tonight.
- Oh, thank you.
- I love you guys.
- Oh.
- Will you sign my cd for me?
- Yeah, totally.
You wanna hold this?
- After the show,
he has to talk to fans
and make sure
that they feel special.
And I get it.
It's part of the deal.
- Give me your number.
We'll meet up.
- There ya go.
- Perfect.
- For Avir to give
a stranger his phone number
in front of Mandy
was just rude.
[Laughing]
I wanna bash his face in.
- You're such a flirt.
- I know.
- Can we talk outside
for a minute,
alone?
- ♪ let me in or let me out ♪
♪ so I can take
a breath of air ♪
- um...
You know
that the whole reason
that I'm excited
to come to New York always
is 'cause of you, right?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- And you know...
You're my friend.
But can you tell that...
I might have feelings
for you, possibly?
- Sure. I mean...
I like you too, you know?
- But, like--
like, like what?
Like is it...
Something more,
or is it all in my head?
- I mean...Yeah.
I mean, I'm really glad
you came, you know,
and it's, like, whenever
I see you, it's cool.
But it's not gonna
go anywhere.
I know it's not gonna
go anywhere, so...
- All right.
- For now, you should probably
just go hang out
with your friends
and have a good time
and don't just be so worried
about everything and...
- I came for you.
That's fine.
I'll go inside.
- All right.
Well, we'll talk more, okay?
- ♪ I never really ever know
what to say ♪
- bye.
- ♪ I'm just trying to get us
on the same page ♪
♪ I always get it better
right afterward ♪
♪ when all the wrong impressions
are said and heard ♪
♪ how come I can never
get the right words ♪
♪ I need to convey ♪
sync by dny238
for www.Addic7ed.Com
- next on fly girls...
- So, ladies,
I'm going to see jon.
I miss him.
- You're gonna move down to L.A.
And visit every once in a while.
That's a pen pal.
- You're not my pen pal.
You're my boyfriend.
I love you.
- Well, I just don't know
if this is working out for me.
- We have this huge
yacht party this weekend.
- Can I invite friends?
- You can only come
if you bring
all your hot friends.
- Deal.
All: Cheers!
- You're mingling
with a bunch of fake people.
- I'm mingling?
- I came here for you.
- I didn't even invite you!
- Why can't you just be
supportive of what I do?
- Because
you're a flight attendant.
Woo!