[ Airplane engine takeoff]
Being a flight attendant,
you never know
where a new day is going to take you.
We jet-set to some of the most beautiful places
in the world,
get invited
to exclusive parties,
and live extraordinary lives.
And the best part
about it is, it's our job.
- Ever since I was
a little girl,
I wanted to be
a flight attendant.
They were these independent,
confident, successful women
that were in control
of their lives.
And now that's me.
- I grew up
in a strict community,
where my family
had a clear vision
for me to become a nurse...
Until one day I realized
that wasn't what I wanted.
So I made my own decision
to become a flight attendant.
I haven't looked back since.
Sync dny238
for www.Addic7ed.Com
- flying is everything for me.
I've been doing it
for almost nine years now,
and I'm good at what I do.
But when you travel
all the time,
I've learned that sometimes
life on the ground
can pass you by.
- I became a flight attendant
because I love to travel.
I do have a ten-year-old son
that I do need to take care of,
and he is my main focus.
- Back home in Arizona,
I was destined
for the white-picket-fence life
of settling down,
getting married,
and having kids.
But I knew that wasn't for me.
So I headed to California
and became a flight attendant.
Now I'm in control
of my own destiny.
- When we put on our uniform,
the world is our playground,
and anything can happen.
- ♪ oh, oh ♪
♪ glamorous days,
glamorous nights ♪
♪ in the fast lane,
everything is insane ♪
♪ glamorous days,
glamorous nights ♪
♪ that's how I live my life ♪
[echoing] ♪ live my life ♪
- ♪ when you wake up
in the morni ♪
♪ do you think of me? ♪
♪ am I the first thing... ♪
- every time you get
on the plane,
there's over a hundred
new personalities,
and you never know
who you're gonna meet
or what's gonna happen.
- Early-morning flights
can be rough,
because you always
have to put on a smile,
even if you're not feeling it.
Hi, good morning.
- - ♪ Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday... ♪
- it always amazes me
that people bring everything
they own on the plane.
That is a big bag.
It's like, "hello?
You can check your bags.
It'll be there when we land."
Big bag?
- [laughs]
- Ladies and gentleman,
welcome aboard.
From the flight deck, sit back,
relax, and enjoy the ride.
- ♪ there's nothing to fear ♪
- can I get you
something to drink?
- I'll take
a club soda, please.
- Sure. And for you?
- How you doing?
- Good.
How are you doing today?
- Awesome.
Enjoying yourself there?
- I am.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Looks like somebody
has an I.F.B.
- Who?
- Did you not see
the guy in 18c?
- An I.F.B.
Is an in-flight boyfriend.
It's a cute guy that you scope
out to help the time fly.
Can I get you a water?
- Yeah, sure.
- How's it going?
- We said it at the same time.
- Jinx.
- You owe me a coke.
- Double jinx.
I just got out
of a four-year relationship.
Things just didn't work out
between us,
and I still feel
very vulnerable.
- My friends and I,
we're having
this cocktail party tonight.
- Yeah?
- You should come down
and check it out.
- Give me a call.
- All right.
- Sounds good.
- I get business cards
from guests all the time
offering to take me out.
But I've never really taken it
too seriously.
- [Laughing]
- I.F.B.
- Hey.
- ♪ home is where
your heart is ♪
- mommy has to go
to work, okay?
Because I travel
a lot for work,
my son, Taevon, lives up north
with his dad.
We're not married,
but we share custody,
so it works out.
Make sure you listen
to your dad.
- Okay.
- And do your schoolwork.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Be good for daddy, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
- You ready to get going?
- ♪ hey ♪
♪ ♪
- another day at work, right?
- I'm excited to go back to L.A.
- yeah.
- But we do have
a little cleaning to do.
Got a new roomie moving in.
Get some new blood,
some new energy
poppin' in the house.
- Yeah, okay.
We have a new roommate
moving in today,
which is great because
less household bills for me.
So I'm excited about that part.
- ♪ bum ba-dum ♪
- is she gonna be there
when we land?
- You're like, "no."
You're like, "please, no."
- Well, I just want to get home
and, like, at least be able
to unpack and maybe have
a glass of wine to prepare.
- Yeah, she's definitely gonna
Spice things up a little bit.
- Spice, yes.
I've known our new roommate,
nikole, since training,
and let's just say
her personality enters the room
five minutes before she does.
- The four of us live
in a house by the beach,
and we're always
in and out of town,
which is typical
for flight attendants.
So we call it the crash pad.
I'm trying to get the place
clean for the new roomie
who's moving in today.
What about the dusting?
[Laughs] Come on.
- All right, I swear,
I'm gonna do it. We are.
Farrah's always trying
to be someone's mom.
When I get off work,
I wanna chill out.
- What's up?
- Hey.
- How are you guys?
- Good.
So what are you guys doing?
- Cleaning.
- You're doing it for us?
- Yeah.
- Dusting?
- Yeah, for nikole.
- We're rushing for nikole?
Who is she?
- Yeah.
- I'm excited about nikole
coming, like, right?
[Laughter]
- ♪ here we go, pick me up ♪
♪ in your
brand-new truck ♪
♪ ♪
- when I found out the girls
were looking for a new roommate,
I found out their place
was right on the beach.
L.A. has
the best party scene.
It's full
of beautiful people...
Perfect for me.
- ♪ crazy, crazy ♪
- I hope when
I turn that doorknob,
that it all goes well.
Sometimes I tend to have
bad luck with girls.
- Nik?
- Hi!
- How are you?
- Good.
- When she pulls up
with those two damn dogs,
I'm like, "oh, hell, no."
- Hey.
- Hi.
How are you?
- I'm good.
- Good.
So all of us are here.
- Nikole and I used to be
best friends and roommates,
but then we had a falling out,
and we stopped talking.
Hopefully, she's grown up.
I know I have.
- Fort Lauderdale,
in the morning.
- I know.
Are you ready?
- Oh, born ready.
As part of the promo team,
we get to go to all
the cool company events.
And tomorrow
we're launching a new city,
Fort Lauderdale,
and it's gonna be big.
- Are you excited?
- ♪ another launch party ♪
♪ ah ♪
- Mandy's gonna be there too.
- Oh, you're going.
- Yeah.
- Ooh, so what are
we doing tonight, hmm?
- I was invited
to a cocktail party...
- Ooh.
- This guy I met on the plane.
- Great.
- Oh.
- I don't date people
I meet on the plane anymore.
"Rotten apples"...
That's what I call them.
- Yeah.
- But I'm gonna wish you
the best of luck.
All right, girls,
where's my room?
- Come, I'll show you.
- Show me where
the magic happens.
♪ can't wait,
can't wait to party ♪
- are they even housebroken?
- Of course not.
Are you kidding?
- This is gonna be a fun ride.
- Yeah, interesting.
- ♪ boy, read the signs
on my body ♪
♪ can't you feel me
getting naughty? ♪
♪ chicka-boom, chicka-boom ♪
♪ that's right,
my boom, chicka-boom ♪
- oh, wow.
I think this is it.
- This is the house?
- Yeah.
- What?
- This house is beautiful.
♪ ♪
- hey, well,
thanks for inviting us.
- Of course, ladies,
my pleasure.
- This is amazing.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
What?
I thought you said
it was a cocktail party.
- Everyone's in tank tops
and flip-flops and bikinis.
Like, what is this?
I wish you
would have said something.
That's okay.
- No, ladies, come on.
You're both stylin'.
You're the life of the party.
I love your earrings.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, totally.
- Why don't you introduce us
to some of your friends?
That way, I can mingle
and become the life of the party
in my cocktail dress.
- Of course.
I was just about to do that.
ESE are the ladies
I was telling you about.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Hi.
- You ladies have
very nice dresses on.
- Thanks.
- I'm not gonna lie.
- Okay, air hostess?
I'm sorry...
- The correct term
is "in-flight team member."
- What about "lady"?
"Hey, lady?"
- Or "hey, you."
What about "hey, you"?
- Don't take offense.
They got the whole classic '60s,
air hostess was, you know...
- Pretty sassy.
- Is that
what virgin's going for?
- I would say
the closest thing...
- 'Cause I heard hooters
is opening an airline.
- Ah...
- Geoff's friends are so rude.
I was pretty sure
after that moment
that the night
was already over.
- Where do I sign up
for that mile-high club?
[Laughter]
- Hey, Tae, how are you?
[Laughs]
- When Taevon stays at his
father's house, we video chat.
Since I'm away days at a time,
it's important
for me to talk
to him every night.
How's school?
Good.
I missed it?
What did you get it for?
- Oh, man.
Well, congratulations.
Good for you.
I might get you a gift.
So I'll actually see you...
I don't know...
In two days, three days.
Take a bath.
- No, no, no, no.
Okay, well,
take one again tonight.
Get your school clothes ready,
so you can get ready to go
to sleep, okay?
Good night.
I love you.
- I love you too.
- Bye.
- Hey, was that Taevon?
- Yeah, we were just skypin',
u know.
- Aw, little man.
- Being away from him so long,
you know, it gets to me.
I'll get over it.
- ♪ she's got the rhythm
that I can't forget ♪
♪ she's got the rhythm ♪
♪ she's got me waking up ♪
- Geoff's friends
were really rude,
but I wanted to give him
a chance,
because we obviously
had such a great connection
on the plane.
- U go overseas lot?
- No, we don't go overseas,
only domestic.
- Only domestic.
- What do you do?
- [Imitating Dr. evil]
The details of my life
are inconsequential.
In the springtime,
we make meat helmets.
[Both chuckle]
- What is that from?
- [Imitating Dr. evil]
My father owned a boulangerie,
with a penchant for buggery.
- Geoff started to do
Austin powers imitations.
- [Imitating Dr. evil]
My childhood was typical...
- It was just so bizarre.
- I hope Mandy's okay.
She's...
- I like to call her
Mandalay Bay.
It has a nice ring to it.
- I was really excited
about getting back into dating,
but if these are the type
of guys that are out there,
no, thank you.
- Smashing party, right?
- Thanks for inviting me.
- Of course.
[Both laugh]
Yeah, so it would be nice
to see you again.
- Ah...
Hmm...
- My philosophy about it is
life is short, you know?
Sometimes you just gotta take
action, make things happen...
Just go with it.
- [Laughs]
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Oh.
- It's time to go.
We've got only 12 hours before
our flight tomorrow, so...
- 12 hours? I mean, you could
still party for a little bit.
- That's, like, the time
they give us to stop drinking,
get some rest, be ready
for the next day, so...
- Mandy saved me.
She got me out of there.
- What was that?
[Girls laughing]
- Okay,
but what's more awkward...
That kiss
or me working
the Fort Lauderdale launch
tomorrow with Nikole?
[Both laugh]
[Cheers and applause]
- It's quite a production, huh?
- One of the best perks
about my job
is being part
of the promo team.
Every time the company
launches a new city,
they throw an inaugural party.
I'm so excited to work
this event.
When you're part of the promo
team, all eyes are on you.
This is insane.
I don't think Virgin America
has ever put on
an event this big
for a new city.
- All right, guys.
You've got
a very busy schedule.
Rachel and Jenna,
I want you to greet everyone
that is coming in.
Let's have Farrah and Nikole
work the v.I.P.,
reserved seating area.
Our two flights
from L.A. and San Francisco
are gonna come in through here.
They're gonna be parked
over here.
So we're gonna just shoot
a big stream of water
right over the planes.
And, Mandy,
I wanna put you out
on the fire truck with Richard.
- When you're on a fire truck
with Richard Branson,
this is the coveted position
at this event.
And I'm so excited.
- You ready?
Let's work the room, people.
Let's work the room.
[Pop music]
- Part of the day was
just working the party,
kind of introducing people
to the airline.
- So, um, quick question.
- Yeah.
- You guys put Mandy
on the fire truck?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Good. She's cute.
- She is.
It's a pretty big event
for someone to do it
for the first time.
- Well, keep an eye
on them, Nikole.
Keep an eye on these guys.
- I will watch
the fort down here.
I'll make sure
it all gets handled.
- Thanks. I appreciate that.
That'd be good.
- Nice.
- Mind if I borrow her
for a second?
Thanks.
- See you in a bit.
- Okay.
- Can you help us out
by putting all the centerpieces
on the tables?
They seem to be missing.
- All of a sudden, Nikole starts
kind of barking orders.
I'm like,
"okay, what are you doing?"
Make sure that all the napkins
have the paperweights on them.
- You know what, Nikole?
I've done this a few times.
Thank you.
- Yeah, wow.
♪ ♪
- we gotta get on the fire truck
with sir Richard.
Where's Mandy?
- Probably working the room.
- I don't see her around here.
All right, you're up.
We gotta go now, come on.
- Dimitrios is my boss.
If he says,
"get on the fire truck,"
I get on the fire truck.
I have to follow
his instructions.
And sometimes it pays
to be in the right place
at the right time.
It's good to see you again.
- Hi, dear.
Great.
So you're coming up?
- I'm coming up with you.
- Great.
- ♪ you must be dreamin' ♪
♪ if you think
you're gonna get with me ♪
- is that Nikole out there?
- Dimitrios
was looking for you.
- And?
- Right, well, this is fun.
- ...Fort Lauderdale welcome.
They've come all the way
from California!
[Cheers and applause]
- ♪ I'll take your picture ♪
- I shouldn't
even be surprised.
This is exactly
something she would do.
- I'm sorry.
- ♪ keep on movin' on ♪
[echoing] ♪ on ♪
- nice little view.
- Don't let
your glasses fall off.
- Or your pants fall down.
- Right.
- What about you and Geoff?
How was the party?
- He was cool at first,
and then all of a sudden,
he just became, like,
this different person.
It just didn't feel right.
- Right.
They're not all like that,
let me tell you,
'cause, you know, I date.
And I do my thing.
- There's plenty more
out there.
Like, he's not the only one.
You just have to be willing.
- You know when you're
with someone in a relationship,
and you get so comfortable,
and, like, you know
everything about them?
I wish dating was like that.
But then it...
It wouldn't be dating, I guess.
- Right.
- You're gonna play?
- No.
- Oh, my God, come on.
- I'll watch you.
- No, come on.
- Oh, my God.
Do you even play volleyball?
- No, but we're gonna
try it today.
- ♪ maybe I'm right,
or maybe I'm wrong ♪
♪ makin' it up as we go along ♪
♪ don't run away... ♪
- [screams]
♪ ♪
[club music]
- The flights came in.
The launch was a hit.
Our work is done.
Now it's time to do
what we do best...
Par-tay.
- ♪ take the number,
step to the back of the line ♪
- I've been
to New York a bunch.
- New York, a little Marrakesh.
- Tyler works really closely
with Virgin America,
and he's at all
of our promo events.
So he's just become
a friend of mine.
- San Diego.
I'm north of San Diego.
I'm throwing a party.
- What? Where?
- Darling!
- Hi.
- I am ready to dance.
- I'm having
a conversation with Tyler,
and Nikole interrupts me
so rudely.
I've had enough with Nikole.
- Can I steal her
just for a second?
I just need to talk to her.
- Steal me? No!
- Can I take her?
♪ ♪
- do you even know, like,
what's going on?
Do you have any idea?
It's, like,
I'm having a conversation
with a friend of mine.
Can you back off for a second?
- Back... no.
I'm not in your space.
It's a party.
- But you are in my space.
- You show up, and it's, like,
the promo event
is all about Nikole.
And surprisingly, like,
I should have known.
I should have known exactly
what to expect from you.
- You have
serious issues with me
that have nothing to do
with tonight.
- You just totally
disrespect me all the time.
- I do not disrespect you.
- We were best friends.
And then all of a sudden,
we weren't friends at all.
- Move on!
- And it's really super hard
for me to get over the past
when you're acting like this,
that's all.
- Acting like what?
Having fun?
People have fun, Mandy!
- I have fun.
- No, you don't have fun.
What happened to you?
- I do have fun.
And my fun does not involve
stepping on someone's toes
to get in the limelight,
like you did this afternoon.
- No!
- Okay, Dimitrios,
I'll go with you.
I'll go with you
wherever you want me to go.
- That's on him!
It's not on me, Mandy!
- I don't believe you.
- You work for this comp...
Then go [Bleep] Talk to him!
- All I want
from this situation
is for something
to be different.
I expect the most out of you,
and I get nothing back.
[Crying]
I get nothing back from you,
and I don't even understand.
I don't have any idea why it is
that you can't move on with me.
And you're like,
"I don't have it in me."
- I have it in me to move on,
but when you tell me
that I'm stuck
in the limelight and that...
- Because you are,
because you can't share,
because you can't just be
a friend
who's happy for another friend
to have a moment.
And if you don't see that,
maybe we
shouldn't live together,
because I can't handle
this anymore.
- I moved in the house
with every intention
of being friends
with Mandalay again.
Party!
I don't think I'm gonna fight
anymore for her.
She's gonna have to win
my friendship over from now on.
- Coming up this season
on fly girls...
- Being a flight attendant,
I get to visit
all over the world.
- I get v.I.P. Hookups
and access to some
of the most glamorous events.
- Like, nobody believes
we get to do this stuff,
but we really do.
- Okay, here we go.
Louise and I
are headed to New York.
- ♪ w-w-w-watch me move ♪
- I want you to be with me.
- You know how I feel.
It's not gonna go anywhere.
- This isn't High School.
- Well, why can't you just be
supportive of what I do?
- Because you're
a flight attendant.
- He grabbed my hand.
He was like,
"what about the Mile-High Club?"
And I said, "what about it?"
- I'm thinking of possibly
going into corporate.
- What?
No more flying?
- I'm interested
in the supervisor position.
- You may have to move out.
- 13b... like, really
getting on my nerves.
- It's the way you walk down
that aisle...
Unbelievable.
- Okay, that's a little
inappropriate, sir.
- You are rude, Tasha.
- You ain't gonna just keep
talking to me like that.
I'm not rude.
- If I say you're rude,
it means you're rude.
- No, this bitch didn't.
- I came here for you.
- I didn't even invite you!
Bye.
- ♪ w-w-w-watch me ♪
- going to Vegas!
- Nikole was hooking up
with the DJ?
What are you doing?
- Our lifestyle
does not make it easy for us
to become friends.
- I'm sorry if I hurt you.
Can we please just start over?
- ♪ w-w-w-watch me ♪
♪ I'll get you in the mood ♪
sync dny238
for www.Addic7ed.Com