Hi. There is a wine glass on the floor
by the elevator. Do you know long
it's been there? Over an hour. You know
how I know that? Cause I put it there.
To test you. Get rid of it.
Hey!
Why don't we get this fireplace up, OK?
Fire is sexy.
And let's get the AC up
because fire is hot.
Nicole, what you doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be off today?
Yes, I am but girls keep wiping out
in these giant heels
that you are making us wear
so I have to cover.
But don't expect much. I'm either
really hungover or still a little drunk.
Let's keep it together today,
RJ is coming in.
Don't worry, I'll be fine. I had
a pack of nicorette for breakfast.
The Times has picked The Inn as one
of New York 10 best places to stay.
They're coming in to interview RJ cause
he's the owner. Even though I'm the one
who did everything around here,
not that he would ever acknowledge that.
Oh, Neal's got daddy issues.
It just kills me when older men
withhold their approval
of younger men
who want to be like them.
He made me general manager
of the hottest hotel in New York.
In fact,
I'm kind of a big deal right now.
If you were hoping
to ride me to the top,
now it might be
a good time to hop on.
Sexual harassment.
Lucky for you I need it today,
otherwise I might call Rhonda on you.
Please, don't even joke,
just the sound of that woman's name
makes everything on me proper.
Not again!
Rhonda, seriously
you look gorgeous today.
Oh, Molly wants something.
What is it?
Remember how you said you'd talk to Neal
about getting me out of reservations
which I hate
and up to the front desk which I'd love.
No, what I remember saying is,
"Please stop asking me about this."
Rhonda, thanks god, help!
Ming is...
She's flipping out. I...
I sent her to clean 410
for an early checking but apparently...
Neal was already there
giving the model from Sweden
an early checking up his own...
- No, he wasn't.
- Yeah, yeah, he was.
And the worst part is
I can't get Ming to stop rocking
to tell me what he looked like naked.
You know, you pick it up.
Excuse me, miss Peet?
Miss Peet?
Jason, that makes me sound
like a teacher.
I'm not old enough to be your teacher.
I'm sorry I can't tell
how old black people are.
Anyway I know you told me to hang
in there with this bellmen thing
but it's been 3 days and I hate it.
And I tried to talk to Neal
about this but he just said,
"Do you realize
where you get to work, op?"
Don't you pay Neal any attention.
Now, is mister Jeffreys upstairs
waiting for his luggage?
No, I put him in a cab to the airport.
What is this?
Nicole, what happened?
Miss catalogue model here
doesn't know how to walk in high heels.
I mean, come on,
suck in your stomach,
squeeze your ass and focus.
I've been doing it since I was 3.
This is the third child
who falls in these things.
What is Neal thinking?
What am I doing? I had lunch.
I'm like an animal.
Larry, baby, give me some ice
for this foot.
This is great news,
if her ankle is broken
then they do need someone upstairs.
Molly...
have some sensitivity,
this child is hurting.
And she stinks like an ashtray.
That's why your bones are so brittle.
And you, no, you're not going upstairs.
- Why?
- Because I need you in reservations.
- Anyone can answer a phone.
- But not like you.
- I'll train some new girl.
- But I like having you down here.
- I'll come visit on my breaks.
- Stop it!
What do you have to get up there so bad?
Do you realize who stays here?
Rockstars, producers, europeans.
They could discover me and make me
an international singing sensation.
That is quite a plan.
You got fair, girl, it's...
Exciting!
Crazy as hell but...
I'm telling you, if these girls
keep falling off their shoes,
you're gonna get yourself sued.
Okay, let me explain why
I'm not taking those girls
out of those shoes.
Because hot chicks and high heels
turn me on, how about that?
Plus there's something
about their discomfort
that makes me feel like a man.
How about you let me do my job
and you take care
of human ressources whatever that is.
I take care of people.
You do know what people are, right?
They are those broken down things
holding up your uniforms.
Okay, I don't know
where all this is coming from...
But let's be clear. The Times is not
writing an article about this hotel
because you breastfeed
the hobbits downstairs.
They're writing it because of me.
I personally chose every piece
of furniture in this lobby,
every piece of art on these walls.
And every piece
of smoking hot ass behind the...
What is that?
How did it get out?
You know, it's totally unfair
that you're so super busy
just because all those other girls
broke their ankles and stuff.
- Do you want me to help?
- I'm not doing anything.
Do you want me to get that?
I don't answer the phones, it just goes
somewhere else, I don't answer.
She's not getting upstairs.
And we both know why.
Alright, in retrospective,
it's probably the wrong week
to go off my anti-anxieties.
RJ is on his way here with The Times,
you're all over me with the "Hey, hey,
"you a real fine woman,
won't you back that thing up", so...
Let's be done. Okay?
You want to get her outta here?
Your downstairs girl is blocking
both of my upstairs girls. Thank you.
I can't believe you put me away
from the front desk
just as a two-time Grammy winner was
checking in and I was helping Nicole.
It would've been a perfect time for you
to ask Neal If I could work upstairs.
Baby girl, mother loves you
enough to tell you the truth.
Neal is not going to let you
work upstairs, okay?
That you are as plump and lovely
as a girl can be. You are.
Alright, but this is not the plump
and lovely Bed and Big Breakfast.
It's the skinny bitch
and high heels hotel, you feel me?
Now...
let's get downstairs and do the jobs
we're being paid to do today.
I'ma catch up with you.
I need the two-time Grammy winner
to give Hello to Rhonda.
Inn Reservations, I hate my life,
can you hold?
Hi, Julie, is my father there?
Will you have him call me
as soon as it gets out of court?
I'm just having a really bad day at work
and I wanted to talk to him about it.
Victor,
get whatever color curtains you want,
you know, I don't care about that stuff.
No, not purple, come on!
No, that's too gay.
Well, I know we're gay,
but now that's just gay on gay.
Victor, I got to go.
God, why can't I be the wife?
Do we still have those normal looking
shoes the girls used to wear?
Yeah, let me look.
- Ms Peet... Rhonda...
- Jason...
Did you come all the way down here to
tell me that you hate being a bellman?
I just don't think
I fit in good upstairs.
It's all these beautiful people
and they are all so smart and classy.
Baby, those people
aren't smart or classy.
And you're just
as beautiful as they are.
No!
Yes, you are.
Can't you just give me
something to do down here?
Baby you don't have any skills.
I can waddle.*
Sit down!
Let me tell you a story.
About a week ago,
I'm walking down Colombius Avenue
and up the street in front of me,
there's this homeless man.
So see, all these people
are making these really wide circles
so they don't have
to walk up next to him.
Well, when I get up there,
I see that the man...
pants are open
and his thing is out.
Jason, it was a monster.
You know
what I thought in that moment?
I'm thinking "Buddy, if you got a thing
like that and you end up homeless,
"you got nobody to blame but yourself."
I don't get it.
Really, I'd like to.
What was the cross street?
People need to know what they got
and then they need to use it.
You fit in fine upstairs, baby.
Trust.
I can't believe
you're making us put these shoes on.
They look like
they cover the prescription.
I'm not letting one more child
get hurt on my watch.
Well, Neal is gonna freak.
He wants us mean and hobbled.
Neal is not even gonna notice. You're
all behind the desk the entire time.
Rhonda did it.
She made us wear the old shoes
and we hate them.
I feel like a lesbian postal worker.
I wish you looked half that hot.
RJ is gonna be here in any seconds
so you all better back up in your toes.
- Don't you dare, get down.
- Get up.
- Down!
- I said get up!
- Up!
- Don't listen to him, down!
- Stop it, down!
- Up!
It's quite a number
you choregraph there.
RJ, welcome!
Neal, how come every time I come here
you're borderline hysterical?
I'm not hysterical. Are those
the people from The Times?
- Should I go introduce myself?
- Definitely not.
You two, come with me.
So Rhonda,
how did the birthday party go?
Mario treated you okay?
Like a queen.
Thanks for making the call.
Call? What call?
He made a call for you?
Now how do you think it made me feel
to get off an airplane
and have my office inform me
that my hotel is being sued?
Oh, I told you you were gonna get sued!
Who is suing us?
Molly Plesky's father.
Apparently
someone here at the hotel told Molly
she was too plump
to work at the front desk.
And apparently,
that is now discrimination.
"I told you you were gonna get sued!"
That's ugly.
I don't like it.
Let me remind you that I did
a little time upstate for a crime
that I may or may not have commited.
And the last thing I need
is for that reporter to change his story
from "Top 10 Best Places to Stay"
to "Ex-con Hates Chubbies."
You should know RJ.
I did not say it, Rhonda did.
Wait a minute. It's your evil policy.
You won't let go and put a girl upstair.
She's not getting upstairs!
- Hold hands.
- What?
- I'm sorry?
- Hold hands.
It's what I did
when my kids must behave.
Do it.
Now, Rhonda, say something nice to Neal.
Nice suit, Neal.
You have amazing cans, Rhonda.
It's true, they're pretty spectacular.
Thank you. Thank you both.
Now, as far as I'm concerned,
you two are one. I want you
to make that law suit go away.
Or I'll make you go away.
Both of you.
Victor, I can't talk right now,
I'm at work.
Well, remember that thing I used to do
before I got health benefit
and you became a playwright?
I'm sorry.
Are you there?
I cannot believe this child.
Getting her daddy to sue this hotel
and putting my job in jeopardy?
I'm gonna rip right into her!
No, you are not.
I'm going to handle this, got it?
- Molly, can we talk for a sec?
- In my office, now.
Molly, why do you think we just
dragged you in here, right now?
My god,
are moving me to the front desk?
- You are not, sweetie.
- Yes, yeah we are.
You are? I'm so exciting!
Sorry, I just need
to get your signature on these.
First of all, I want to apologize.
I was heartbroken to hear you felt
you were being discriminated against.
Obviously you got your feelings hurt
and I feel very bad about that.
- What's happening here?
- And this one.
The truth is it was RJ's idea
for all the girls upstairs to be this
weirdo model types. I told him,
That's not the world we live in anymore
but he didn't want to listen.
- This one.
- You really need me
to do this right now
or you're just in here to eavesdrop.
Eavesdrop.
Okay, then sit down
and stop distracting me with all this.
- Get out!
- Yep!
Personally, I think it's great
that your dad is suing the hotel.
It's gonna light a flame
under RJ's butt
and get rid of this all stupid policy
altogether.
But if you put me upstairs,
he won't sue.
I'll tell him not to.
Hang on!
That hadn't occurred to me.
Had that occur to you Rhonda?
- Let me...
- Why don't you call your daddy
and tell him everything
is gonna be alright now.
Thanks, Neal.
What are you doing?
You're not putting her up there.
No, I'm not.
We'll just put her off a while
and find some reason to fire her.
I'm not going along with that.
Those kids out there
might just be decoration to you
but they mean something to me.
And I'm not going to start lying to this
girl just to make it better for you.
Hey, it's better for you too.
If Molly's daddy shuts down this hotel,
you're gonna loose all these kids
you care so much about.
And what are you gonna do
with yourself then?
Is she behind me?
- No!
- Got her.
You know, it is so offensive
that there's a policy
that heavy people can't work upstairs.
That's like saying I can't work upstairs
because I'm a redhead.
That's why I can't work upstairs,
isn't it?
Jackass, I've just sent guests up to 510
which you marked as clean.
Meanwhile, they're walk in
to find a filthy room
and your chinese woman
crying in the tub.
Ming... She's in the bathtub?
She's feeling much dishonoured.
Listen, if she can't clean the rooms,
I'm sure there are 11 other people
in her apartment who can.
Hey, stick!
Now, *.
You know what this is?
This is food.
We eat it and we're nice.
You don't eat and you're mean.
Mean and thin.
You always leave out
the most important part.
Don't make a black woman
take off her earrings.
It kind of burnt.
I don't know
who I am more mad at right now.
Molly for creating all this drama,
Neal for lying to Molly
or me for letting him get away with it.
When I was a kid,
we were greatful for food,
clothes, a hammy down white baby doll.
These new kids think
they are entitled to everything.
You understand what I'm saying?
I just...
Oh, hell.
Where did you come from?
Neal is not really
gonna put me upstairs?
No, baby, he's not.
Then why did he lie to me?
Because he's a liar.
And because RJ is upstairs
with that reporter from The Times,
he didn't want your little story
getting out.
This si wrong Rhonda, you knwo it is.
What's wrong is having your daddy
trying to fix your problems.
If I had a fight
that I thought was worth fighting,
baby, I'd fight it for myself.
Okay, I'd get right on up,
into whatever face
was looking down on me,
and I'd say,
"Hey, it's Rhonda, deal with me."
"Or I will bring
this whole house down around."
Well... Hold on.
- Where are you going?
- To fight my own fight.
No, no!
Wait a minute!
That's not what I meant.
Oh, damn!
What did I just do?
I think you just sent up upstrairs
to bring the whole house down
around ya.
So why don't we give one of RJ
with the lobby down below?
A king and his castle kind of thing.
I like the sound of that.
- Where should I stand?
- Where you are is fine.
Baby girl, wait.
What exactly
are you planning to do here?
I'm going up to RJ and that reporter
and I'm gonna say, "Hey,
"I'm Molly, you can't hide me downstairs
because I'm plus size."
Hold on, a lot of people's lives
could be affected by this.
Sorry, but it's always been like this
and I'm sick of it.
Besides, if it's a fight worth fighting,
I got to fight it, isn't what you said?
Yeah, I guess I did say that, didn't I?
Look, I get it.
You don't care about me.
But are you really gonna let
Rhonda loose her job over this?
Wait! Are you gonna
loose your job if I do this?
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine, come on.
Rhonda, this is your whole life,
you don't have anything else.
Excuse me, you got one friend
on these stairs. Let's go.
Come on.
I can't.
Oh, god!
Are you okay?
No.
That wine glass
is still by the elevator.
I had no idea how hungry I was.
I mean...
I feel calmer,
my head doesn't hurt, it's like...
Oh my god, the screaming stopped.
You have beautiful eyes,
I've always said that.
When you say stuff like this, it makes
me wish that we're still hang out.
Why don't we?
- Victor bugs me.
- Oh my god, he bugs me too.
- Then why are you with him?
- I don't know.
That was delicious, baby girl.
Saving my job,
knocking Neal down those steps.
You knocked Neal down the steps?
No, I threw myself down the steps
in a heroic gesture to save this hotel.
Are you okay?
Here, sit down, I'll get you some ice.
I know, right? 11 grams of protein
and she's calibraty.*
Why are you looking so sad?
You did a good thing up there.
You're my girl.
Whatever, I'm still your fat girl
who can't work upstairs.
Why do you wanna work upstairs?
The guests are mean,
they're all perfumy,
you can't believe how many of them
answer the door naked.
Women and men.
And they are old,
like thirty and above, it's gross.
But I'm a singer
and I need to be up there
so the people who stay here,
the people who matter can see me.
Why? If you're a singer,
they just need to hear you.
There you go.
What am I supposed to do?
Answer the phone all,
"Reservations, this is Molly."
Do that.
Why are you bossing my balls to get
upstairs when you can sing like that?
That's is the truth right there, diva.
But I can't really
answer the phone like that.
No, you're right. Cause once was great
but I can't hear that all day.
Here's what you could do though.
Just occurred to me
that we got a bar right upstairs.
- Don't.
- Where people sometimes perform.
- That baby did just save your job too.
Fine, you can have one night a week.
- Really.
- But like a tuesday.
Afternoon, and no suntime.
I hate him, never ask me why.
- Okay.
- Oh my god!
This is gonna be so fun.
You are officially
the most talented person I know.
Damn, I should have fed her
months ago.
Reservations,
this is Neal.
Reservations, this is Neal...
Reservations,
this is Rhonda.
That's how you do that.
- Do you want to grab a drink?
- Where do think I'm going?