Petra was
the last one here yesterday.
-She must have left this.
-Not like her.
-No news from her since yesterday?
-She wanted a break.
The sooner I'm married
the sooner I can divorce.
Let's book the registry office.
The other night mustn't be repeated.
I've thought about
our collaboration.
You realise we can't collaborate
with a competitor.
You've withdrawn
substantial amounts.
Sebastian doesn't have access
to this account. Only Petra does.
-Will you help me with something?
-Sure.
-Nothing's happened between you two?
-No, I promise.
I'm staying for your sake.
-How did Egil and your mum meet?
-At the hotel.
-What's her name?
-Jessika.
The person who says
that a Jessika Adolfsson
has worked here is lying.
You didn't see me.
I was never here. No damage done.
EMPLOYMENT AGREEMENT
JESSIKA ADOLFSSON
Sorry, several days have gone by
and Petra is still missing.
When will you do something about it?
It's not that simple.
What do you mean?
That's what the police do, isn't it?
How was she when you last saw her?
Well, it's been
quite messy recently.
In what way?
We've argued a fair bit.
Petra wanted a break,
so I moved out.
So you two argued and you'd
moved out? That doesn't sound...
I don't care what it sounds like.
Yes, we argued,
but she wouldn't just vanish.
Or not answer messages or her phone.
But what caused her to want a break?
Tell me about the argument you had.
That's not all there is to it.
We argued, but she also
told me about a conflict at work
with her brother Sebastian.
Do you know what that was about?
No, you'll have to ask him.
Look, I'm sorry
to have to ask this question,
but considering your differences...
Is there a possibility that
Petra might want to hurt herself?
No. No, she'd never do that.
Are you sure about that?
THE BEACH HOTEL
Have you come
to have a go at me again?
The police are looking for Petra.
This is serious, Werner.
I can't get hold of her.
No one has heard from her for days.
I know why she's staying away.
So go to the police and tell them.
I won't announce publicly that
my child has stolen from the hotel
in order to support
her gambling habit.
Are you sure about that?
Money is missing and she's missing.
What else do you need to know?
What are you going to do about it?
Nothing. This has happened before
and you know it.
Everything always has to happen
on your terms.
Marianne, you shouldn't let her
get you so agitated.
She's in the wrong and there
will be consequences. Simple.
Aren't you worried
about losing them?
They're your children.
What are you on about? What's
Sebastian got to do with this?
Is he doing well
at your beloved hotel?
Or is he about to leave it all
behind and go back to Stockholm?
I don't think so.
You really don't
feel any responsibility.
Are you okay?
It's all a bit much at the moment.
I understand.
Why don't we just
forget about that collaboration?
What do you mean?
-What?
-Your opposition makes it difficult.
Why did you meet with Sebastian
without asking me?
I don't trust him.
I do and
you can't ignore me like this.
Why is everything
always about Sebastian? Hey?
You've taken on
far too much since Egil died.
Let me look after you.
I don't need anyone
to look after me.
I don't know
if Tone has spoken to you.
-She did work here.
-Who?
Jessika Adolfsson.
You assured Julie that
she'd never set foot here.
Here's her employment certificate.
I just wanted to double check.
You don't know
everything about everyone.
Petra has taken money
from the hotel.
You're not going to
report her to the police, are you?
I don't see the point in that.
Do you think she's gambling again?
I don't know.
Maybe she's ashamed of it.
Maybe she's angry.
Let's not mention
that missing money.
It's better if we give her a chance
to come home and explain herself.
So the reason
for not reporting her missing
is not that you're worried
about her reputation?
Okay, I'll leave
the decision to you.
What would you do?
I just want her to come back.
Yeah, me too.
You wanted me to help out?
With this? No, it's fine.
Only until Petra gets back,
of course.
I know you've said
you don't want me interfering, but
you can't do everything yourself,
yours and Petra's job.
That way you would have
a bit more free time as well.
To spend with Shirin.
Okay.
Hey...
I'm sorry.
What's this? We never argue.
You're right. We never argue.
I've been thinking about
your birthday.
-I can't face having a party.
-No.
I know, but wouldn't it be nice
to hang out with a few friends
and just chill out for once?
-Would Gabrielle be up for it?
-I'll check.
She might enjoy the distraction
and having some people around.
Okay, just a small gathering.
I promise.
-Promise.
-Sure, sure.
-Okay?
-Fine.
So nice to see you back.
Thank you.
I really feel at home here.
You're a very sweet couple.
Thank you.
She always says that.
She's trying to
pair me with everyone.
Last year she suggested Britta
of the cold buffet.
-She's retirement age.
-Yes.
-Louise?
-Yes?
There's something
we need to talk about.
Sure.
It can wait. I have to...
Just some stupid advertising.
You need to try to stay calm.
-Like your dad?
-He's more worried than you think.
Julie!
I did find Jessika Adolfsson
in our archives.
Dad obviously
doesn't know everything.
-How long was she there for?
-About a year.
-Isn't that good news?
-I suppose so.
Come and sit down.
The food is getting cold.
Hi, Sebastian speaking.
I see. Today already?
No, I don't see a problem with that.
Okay, see you then.
Who was it?
It was the police.
They wanted me
to come to the police station.
I can't believe
how this has changed.
Any news about Petra?
No.
-Is it nearly finished?
-I think so.
Almost.
-Can I have a closer look?
-Sure.
You don't have to say anything.
Are you worrying about Petra?
You know the dates
for the registry office...
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, I completely forgot.
I just wanted to say
not to worry about that now.
Let's wait for her to come home.
Does it bother you if I...
-If I stay for a bit?
-Not at all.
Right, one step down
and then one more.
Now you can look.
-Where are we going?
-Home.
At least for a few days. I've booked
a hotel, since we can't use the flat
and tomorrow we're going to Astoria.
Robin and Anja are coming
and a few more.
-I can't.
-You need to get away from here.
Me, too. We both need it.
-I can't. Not now.
-Why?
I'm going to the police station.
-It's about Petra.
-Talk to them and then we'll go.
I can't just walk away
from everything, don't you see?
No, I don't see that, since
you wanted to get away yesterday.
I'm home-sick.
Aren't you?
Of course, but...
We don't belong in this backwater.
-What if I do?
-You'll give me right in six months.
Regardless of when Petra gets back,
I'm not sure
if I should hand over the hotel.
-You promised me!
-Can we just leave this?
I only asked for one thing
and now you're ignoring that.
I'm trying to manage this chaos.
Do you have to
complicate things further?
Here you go.
It looks like your mum
worked at the Beach Hotel after all.
Do you have
all the proof you need now?
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologise.
I was just worried
that she'd lied to me.
What would I do then? What if
she said things that weren't true?
There are still some things
that I need to know.
Sure, ask away.
Can I just ask you something?
Sure.
Being on the board
is really exciting.
I tend to find it really boring.
If there's anything else I can do
at the hotel, please let me know.
Did you have
anything in particular in mind?
I'm not sure.
I just want to help out.
I don't mind working my way up.
I need to learn the basics.
I'll have a think about it.
POLICE STATION
Are you making progress?
Do you think
she's choosing to stay away
or do you suspect
a crime has been committed?
Sebastian, I suggest
I ask the questions.
Of course. Apologies.
Don't worry.
How would you describe
your relationship with Petra?
We have a good relationship
most of the time.
-Are you close?
-I'd say so.
Petra can be
a bit reserved sometimes.
I've only got one sister and want to
have a good relationship with her.
Do you argue a lot?
No, certainly not.
Did you have an argument
before she disappeared?
Who told you that?
I'm sorry. You ask the questions.
Yes, we did actually.
And what did you argue about?
Petra thought that I was
about to break our agreement.
-What kind of agreement?
-A work thing.
-And were you?
-No, I don't know...
Maybe she perceived it that way.
She can be a bit highly strung.
I just want her to come back
so that we can sort everything out.
Your fight never became physical,
did it?
Most definitely not.
Is there anything we should know
that would help us find her?
No.
Hi, what are you doing here?
-I'm in a hurry.
-Hey...
Why did you
need to access the office?
Why do you ask?
-I was just wondering.
-Did you mention it to anyone?
-No.
-Good.
Because if you do
you're in real trouble.
But I helped you.
Who's going to believe you?
You know what? Just forget it.
Okay, what's happened?
It's just that Lojsan called
to swap to work the evening shift.
My, Svante,
you've really fallen for her.
What do I do?
What do you want to do?
Is there any point anymore?
I've already ruined it with all my
ranting about rules and regulations.
Aren't you going to Stockholm?
No, it didn't work out. Have you got
some dishes I can get stuck into?
They're waiting for you.
Okay.
If there's something you really
want you need to go for it now.
Promise you'll do that.
-Hi, what's up?
-Hi.
It's Julie's birthday and I wanted
to organise a party for her.
You know the grand hall
at the town hall.
-You want me to stay away, yeah?
-On the contrary.
I really want you to come.
I'm inviting all of her old friends.
You really should be there.
It's not a big party, is it?
-She hates that kind of thing.
-It'll be just the way she likes it.
And a little surprise.
-Okay, I'll see if I can make it.
-Sure.
-And bring your girlfriend.
-Thanks for the invite.
No worries.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I needed to get away for a bit.
I bet Svante would go insane
if he found me here.
I won't say anything.
Has someone been nasty to you?
No, not exactly.
But still totally inconsiderate.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't burden you with this.
That's fine.
You're also new in this town, yeah?
Yeah.
People are so strange around here.
I know. Or coming here
makes them strange.
You're going out with Sebastian,
aren't you?
The guy who kind of owns this place.
Yeah.
Please,
don't tell anyone about this.
Okay.
But he mustn't be nasty to you.
He's not nasty.
Maybe he just doesn't love me
as much as I love him.
In that case he's crazy.
-Lunch is ready.
-Oh, great.
-I didn't realise the time.
-I know. I've been in meetings.
Is this our laid-back life?
Rushed lunches
and long working days?
-I like it this way.
-Me, too.
-I know. Get used to it.
-It might be gone by tomorrow.
I don't know if there's time
for you to buy a new dress.
Why?
The registry office is booked for
tomorrow at two p.m.
-You haven't changed your mind?
-Are you joking?
You were indecisive.
We can postpone it if you want to
invite people and have a reception.
Definitely not.
Don't even go there!
Do you need help?
You could say that.
Werner was never like this, I bet.
I've seen it all.
And much worse than this.
This, for example.
Petra just left this.
I don't know who's meant to
deal with it. Maybe Gabrielle?
I'll look into it.
Have a seat.
We haven't had time to chat
since I took over.
You've been busy.
I need to catch up. You arrived
here when I moved to Stockholm.
I was fresh out of university.
Werner seemed to see potential in me
and I'm forever grateful for that.
You were very close to him,
I believe.
You saw that withdrawals had been
made. Why didn't you come to me?
Old habits simply.
It won't happen again.
Not even if Werner asks you?
He's not likely to do that, though.
Your loyalty to Dad
makes my life difficult.
I understand.
As the new CEO you want to
put your stamp on the hotel.
-Yeah.
-I can see that.
I'm happy to stay
and help you with that transition.
Then we can see how it goes.
What do you think?
Well, that sounds terrific.
Super. Thank you.
You should know that
I know this business inside out.
It might sound ridiculous,
but this is my dream job.
I've always wanted to
work for a family business.
I'm not convinced
it's the best combination.
Family and business, I mean.
I have to disagree with you.
If Werner is moving on,
maybe I'll do the same.
But until then
I'll be supporting you.
I would be silly to let you go.
But could you help me let Dad know
who's in charge now?
We can try.
Thank you.
I thought she liked me.
At least a little bit.
But recently she's been really off.
-How do you mean?
-One moment she's sweet to me.
-The next she asks me to piss off.
-Stay away from her.
-Lilja says the same.
-Who's that?
A friend. She's cool.
I just don't want any
misunderstandings between us.
Just be upfront with her.
That's the most important thing.
Should I be upfront
about being unsure?
Haven't you finished for today?
Lukas is off home to ponder whether
he's in love with his friend or not.
Oh, stop it.
Have you been baby-sitting today?
No, I think it was actually
the other way round.
It was good to have someone
who'd listen to me.
Why didn't you speak to me?
I mean, I would have
been fine with that.
Okay. Thanks for letting me know.
I wish you a pleasant afternoon
in Saltsjövik.
Okay, now what's wrong?
Nothing at all.
I've been thinking.
And I think I might as well
be honest with you.
Hi, Lojsan.
What are you doing here?
-I've called, but you don't pick up.
-Leave me alone.
-But...
-Just leave.
Or I'll have Svante escort you out.
I've got a room booked here.
You can't stay here.
If he's got a booking, then...
Yep. Room 314 booked and paid for.
-Is Lukas here?
-No, he's gone home.
-Would he like dinner with me?
-You'll have to ask him that.
The lifts are over there. Floor 3.
Breakfast is served 6:30-10:00.
Check out is before midday.
Very professional.
The thing is,
he doesn't know that I'm here.
You want to see your son?
Sort it out yourself.
Will do.
Floor 3.
-Sorry. Torbjörn, Lojsan's...
-I understand.
Svante. Front desk manager.
See you.
Are you okay?
Sure. Fine.
-Sebastian wanted...
-Wait.
Sure, sorry.
It's fine.
It's just the way I want it.
Do you think she'll agree to it?
I think so.
Great work.
As usual.
What did you
have to say about Sebastian?
I want to talk about
yours and mine collaboration.
And about my future at the hotel.
Rest assured that I won't let him
get rid of you. I guarantee that.
I don't want any trouble
between you two or for the hotel.
You're not causing trouble.
On the contrary.
-I can talk to him, if you like.
-No need.
We've sorted it out.
Okay.
Did he want to discuss
anything else... regarding us?
I've not said anything about us.
And no one here suspects that we...
No.
That was a one off.
A mistake.
We both agree on that, don't we?
I really put a lot of trust in you.
-Good luck with your wedding.
-Thank you.
So Torbjörn is your...
Yeah, I don't want to talk about it.
No, I understand.
Do you want me to stay?
If you don't
want to deal with him I can.
Thank you.
That's nice, but it's not necessary.
What was it
you wanted to talk about before?
Oh, nothing.
It's not important.
Okay...
Is Petra back?
-No.
-Sebastian needs her signature.
I thought...
Sorry, I wasn't thinking at all.
-I won't bother you.
-No, I can take them.
Have you still not heard from her?
Sorry, I'll leave you in peace now.
I'm sorry I just vanished. Please
understand I need to be alone.
I am so worried.
Just tell me where you are.
Hi, you've reached Petra. Please,
leave a message after the tone.
Petra, please just
tell me where you are.
Seeing each other before the wedding
brings bad luck.
You never told me
you were superstitious.
What was it you wanted?
If you could just
read and sign this.
-A prenuptial agreement.
-I cleared it with Tone.
But not with me.
Look at it as a means
to silence the prophets of doom.
I didn't realise people think that
I'm marrying you for your money.
Then I'll leave this
with the tax authorities.
I'll do it.
Okay.
-Kiss.
-You'll smear everything.
I'll get changed. See you outside.
What's that? Perfume?
-For the guests.
-For Dad, you mean?
No.
-What shall I do with my hair?
-Ask the guests.
Did you
have dinner with him yesterday?
No.
-Will you see him tonight?
-I don't have time.
You don't have to ignore him, Lukas.
Isn't that what you're going to do?
This is better than
the registry office.
Do you wish Petra was here?
I do, but...
This is about us.
Marriage is built on love and trust.
By entering into marriage
you promise to respect
and support one another.
Do you, Vendela Kraghenberg,
take Werner Gyllenmark
as your wedded husband, to love,
for better, for worse?
I do.
Do you, Werner Gyllenmark,
take Vendela Kraghenberg,
as your wife, to love,
for better, for worse?
I do.
You are now husband and wife.
Congratulations, Dad!
She's just so cool.
And clever.
But her boyfriend
treats her like shit.
Is this Rebecca?
Have you not been listening?
I'm talking about Shirin.
Okay. Sorry.
I can't keep track of
all the ladies you fall for.
Do you think I fancy her?
It sounds like it.
Would you like to meet up...
later?
-Hang out and do something?
-Sure.
You decide what we're doing.
No superhero films.
Okay.
Thanks for being our witnesses
at such short notice.
Of course.
I'm sure it'll be you two next.
What do you make of
the message Petra sent?
I suppose it's good news.
We just need to
convince her to come home.
-She should have been here today.
-Yeah.
This was so nice,
but we need to get a move on.
Julie's birthday party.
Well, I'm not going.
But I promised we'd be there.
Go without me
if it's that important.
-We'll also be going now.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
-Once again, congratulations.
-It was really lovely.
-It's so nice to have you here.
A toast for Julie!
Cheers!
How did you have time
to organise this?
It wasn't that hard. You're popular.
Thank you, darling.
I'm so happy you're here.
Any news?
-Not yet.
-Are the police still involved?
Yes, but...
Happy birthday.
Oh, you shouldn't have.
That's so sweet of you.
I do hope they fit you.
Open it.
-Did you leave the door unlocked?
-No.
Ta-da! Here I am.
-Come and arrest me.
-Mum!
You know how I feel
about that word.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm just so happy.
-I didn't know you were coming.
-No.
-How did you get in.
-The cleaner dragged me in.
You have a beautiful home, Werner.
Thank you. You think so?
-This is really you.
-Yeah?
So what have you been up to today?
Well, Inez...
Secrets? Oh!
You were in a rush.
You didn't want to wait? Wonderful.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
If we'd known you were coming
we would of course have waited.
Why? I'm right on time to celebrate.
There's only one thing missing.
A chilled bottle of Champagne.
Best brand.
Eh... I see. Champagne.
Well done.
I can't believe
Aksel asked you to come.
I can leave if you like.
Shall we sneak out?
Or maybe you love big parties?
Stop it. You know that this isn't...
I will now give a pining speech
and you'll be crying.
Stop it.
Could I have
everybody's attention, please?
Julie, would you mind coming over?
What are you up to?
First I'd like to thank you all
for being here at such short notice.
I really appreciate it.
I also have something
to say to you, Julie.
We've been through so much recently
and there's no one I'd rather
share my life with than you.
Julie...
Elisabeth Grip.
Will you do me the honour
and marry me?
He's kind of sweet, like...
"Get your best Champagne.
Lovely and expensive."
And he brings us this.
You should have been there
at the wedding.
It was truly beautiful
out there by the rocks.
Could you bear
staying here for a whole year?
Well...
My little sweetheart.
I'm going to ask him
to let you go to France
for a few months.
A bit of distance
will speed things along.
What do you think?
I'm alright.
Let's just stick to the plan.
If we'd stuck to the plan
that house in Brittany
would have been ours by now.
I wasn't able to
push him any further.
He would have grown suspicious.
He's not stupid.
He's presented me
with a prenuptial agreement.
Which I don't expect
you have signed?
-No.
We'll have to give it some thought.
Okay, as long as you don't sign it.
I hope you haven't got
any other surprises in store for me?
No.
Vanilla? Honestly.
What did you pick? Pistachio?
Are you 70, or what?
I've never had a boyfriend before.
Okay.
I'm not sure why I said that.
It probably sounded weird.
No, I'm just surprised.
What's that?
Subtitles: Anna Townend
plint.com