SALTSJÖVIK BEACH HOTEL
- This is so typical of Werner.
- Details were never his thing.
- It's only a party.
- It beggars belief he invited dad.
- And that dad accepted.
- They mustn't get into a fight.
That's why we've also been invited.
- And half the town.
- He's got such a massive ego.
- We'll stay one hour max.
- Sure.
- Are you okay?
- I rue all the questions.
From dad and mum.
And definitely from my brother.
You don't have to
answer any of them.
- You know what my family is like.
- Lucky you have me then.
Cheers.
So this is where you're hiding.
Several of the guests have arrived.
- Is Sebastian here?
- No, not yet.
We'll wait a bit longer then.
There is champagne, right?
Sure, lots.
Are you really sure about this?
You go, I'll be right there.
There is one more thing.
Egil is here.
Was he not invited?
We always invite him.
That doesn't mean he's welcome.
THE BEACH HOTEL
- Stop it.
- Come on, sister.
- You know I don't like it.
- Relax.
So you've deigned to visit
us from Stockholm.
Where's you chic little girlfriend?
She'll kill you
if you call her that.
She's over there
talking to dad's chic girlfriend.
- She has a name.
- Right. Vanja?
- Vendela.
- Sure. I've only met her once.
You'll just have to
visit us a bit more often.
I never hear from you.
Dad said you were...
That was more like...
Thanks. More as a kind of therapy.
Okay. And what about the debt?
Gabrielle and I have
a repayment plan now.
We've put it behind us.
Where is Gabrielle by the way?
Okay.
Martin's still going strong.
- Amazing that he's still around.
- I know.
- Dad doesn't change anything.
- No.
Is working for him still...
wonderful?
I wanted to check something with you
before I mention it to dad.
Some ideas regarding hotel PR.
You said "dad" and "new ideas"
in the same sentence.
Hi.
You wanted to accept the invitation,
so please make an effort now.
I remember when
we had the deck made
and Werner hired some cheap,
crappy labour in Poland.
We had to tear it down
and start from scratch.
Werner...
- I was there, right?
- That's right.
I still can't believe you were
married to someone like him.
Don't remind me.
If it hadn't been
for the children...
I don't understand
why Sebastian stays.
If you see him tell him
I want to see him. Alone.
- Hi.
- Where's Julie?
- Powdering her nose, I think.
- She doesn't like these gatherings.
- You're so sensitive.
I'll get something to drink.
I have to ask you a favour.
Make sure Julie is safe.
What do you mean?
I know someone broke in.
Huh? When?
Is that why you installed
the CCTV cameras?
Just keep an eye on her.
Can I trust you?
Of course.
- Must you really leave?
- Yes.
There's an issue with the register
in the spa department.
- I can take care of it.
- No, stay here and have fun. Okay?
- You deserve it.
- Let me know if you can't solve it.
Promise.
I'm on my way.
Hi. He was in a rush to leave.
There's an issue at Mistral.
Where's Petra?
I better make sure
she doesn't stray.
You do that.
- Sebastian! Hi!
- Hi, mum.
I've missed you so much.
- Hi, Sebastian.
- Hi.
I'm so happy you made it.
Excuse me.
That sounds very interesting.
Please proceed.
Sure. Wait.
No, sorry, it's no bother.
That same old trick?
Fake phone call.
Boring party.
Here you go.
I don't know if I should drink more.
I feel a bit tipsy already.
- Hi.
Shirin. Sebastian's girlfriend.
Julie.
We're childhood friends.
Okay. Should we go in?
They're about to start.
Go ahead. I'll catch up.
You can make money as an artist
even before you die.
- As long as you are enterprising.
- And have the requisite talent.
It's the birthday boy.
Isn't it time for your speech?
- I'm waiting for Sebastian.
- He's here.
- Is he?
- I just saw him.
Tone! I'm so sorry,
I didn't see that was you.
Tone, we need to speak later.
Come, let's say hi to Sebastian.
So...
- Hi.
Don't you want to watch the show?
Why are you here, dad?
You and Werner in the same room
is never a good idea, right?
No, but I have to do this.
I've postponed it for too long.
What do you have to do?
- Can we meet tomorrow?
- Sure.
- Great.
- Want to have lunch?
I'll...
I think I'm going to disappoint you.
What is it? Should I be worried?
Don't worry about it now.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Sebastian is back.
Yes.
He's here because of the party.
- Hi. Do you have a moment?
- I'm busy.
- Let's talk in your office. Now.
- Egil...
- Werner, it's time for your speech.
- Don't get involved in this.
Egil,
you've had an eternity to apologise.
Apologise?
You're bloody amazing.
I'm here to help you.
Despite everything.
I don't need your help,
so just leave.
Alright, take it easy now.
The both of you.
Dear guests.
We're here to celebrate
Werner's 60th birthday.
I...
I have had the honour
of working with Werner
for around 20 years.
And every day has been a pleasure.
But I won't bore you with that.
I'll hand over to the man,
we're here to celebrate,
Werner Gyllenmark.
Thank you for the kind words,
Svante.
When we first broke ground...
I remember all the snide remarks.
Not many believed in
a big beach hotel in Saltsjövik.
But I knew we'd...
That I...
had made the right decision.
And see where we are today.
This is what I call
a real beach hotel.
Thanks.
But I wouldn't be here
without my family.
Their support has been crucial.
Sebastian, my son...
You have fought harder
than anyone else I know.
We weren't sure if you'd be able to
walk again after the accident.
Look at you now.
A wonderful young man.
Successful advertising executive
in Stockholm.
That's how it is. Nobody's perfect.
Petra. My first born.
Who works at the hotel
and does a brilliant job.
Without love and family
life is worth nothing.
Vendela, come up here.
I am very happy to announce
that Vendela has agreed to
become my wife.
That being the case I will step down
as the hotel director.
There are some big changes coming.
I'd also like...
Dad!
- Egil!
- Dad!
- Call an ambulance.
- Dad?
Egil!
Is your car here? I'll drive you.
Hi. My dad was rushed here
in an ambulance.
- What's your dad's name?
- Egil Grip.
- I'll handle this.
- Okay.
- Egil is under observation.
- Is he awake? Can I see him?
No. Your mum is with him right now.
She is not my mum,
she's my dad's partner.
- What's happened with him?
- Indications are it an overdose.
I noticed you dad has
a Tramadol prescription.
Do you know
if he takes that every day?
He has an old knee injury.
It's possible.
This party he was at...
Do you know how much he'd drunk?
One glass, possibly two.
I don't know.
Tramadol and alcohol can be
a dangerous combination.
My dad would never take something
that was dangerous.
Has he been stressed lately?
He runs a hotel.
Being stressed comes with the job.
Wait here. I'll come and get you.
- Thanks for coming with me.
- Would you like me to stay?
I'LL STAY FOR A BIT
Here by yourself?
It's on the house.
Thanks. I should hope so.
It's my father-in-law's party.
Of course.
Sebastian's girlfriend. Wow!
- Where's Sebastian now?
- He gave Julie a lift to hospital.
Right. That was scary.
I hope it works out.
Who is this Julie?
Sebastian said
they're childhood friends.
- Okay. More than friends, then.
- Perhaps. But it's a long time ago.
Thanks for the wine. It was nice.
I must eat something
before I get dizzy.
It'll work out, right?
Of course.
- You still have it.
- I can't take it off.
- I lost mine.
- Really?
In Switzerland.
I tried to find it in the snow.
My friends had to drag me away.
I almost got frostbite.
Okay. Wow.
Was it good there?
It wasn't what I expected,
but it worked out in the end.
I wanted to visit, but it didn't
seem like you wanted that.
You never asked.
You got so angry when I
didn't move there with you.
- Let's not talk about this now.
- Right.
But I want you to know
that I really wanted to.
It was difficult since mum got me
both a flat and a job in Stockholm.
- Have you seen Sebastian?
- He went to the hospital with Julie.
So, "big changes", huh?
I love her, Petra.
I know it might seem odd
hearing that from your old dad.
I was referring to the other thing.
Of course you did.
I think you're absolutely right.
The hotel needs a new direction.
What was the problem
with the old one?
I didn't mean it that way.
Have you decided
who will take over from you?
You'll be told the same time
as everyone else affected.
Tone will be told first, I presume.
Petra.
I know you'll be happy
with my decision.
Two glasses. Thanks.
Cheers.
He'll be fine. You know that, right?
I'm very sorry, but...
Egil developed difficulty breathing.
We did what we could, but...
Unfortunately...
his heart couldn't
cope with the strain.
This can't be true.
I was in there just now.
Do you hear me? It can't be true!
He was fine.
Calm down.
- I just saw him.
- Mum...
Good thing you only turn 60 once.
- I thought you'd packed my things.
- I packed what I wanted to bring.
You can't be serious that you
care about any of these things.
- Maybe I do.
- Only how much they are.
In a week, Werner,
we've left all this behind us.
Sure. Maybe I should
have told them in my speech.
Don't spring too many surprises
all at once. Talk to the family.
In private.
You know I love you, right?
So... how tired are you?
How tired am I?
Does the old man need his 10 hours
of sleep or...
- ...is there a bit of wiggle room?
- That depends.
- I'm so sorry.
- How did you get in?
- You don't answer your phone.
- What do you want?
Egil is dead.
What? What are you saying?
Werner?
The office. Now!
What's going on?
Here you go. They'll help you sleep.
Okay.
I can't believe Egil is dead.
- You must be Sebastian.
- I'm sorry. Remind me of your name.
Aksel. Didn't Julie mention that?
Great that you could help
this evening.
I just wanted to say hi to Julie
before I leave.
She... She's sleeping.
Okay.
Morning. Did you sleep well?
I'd fallen asleep
when you finally came to bed.
I'm sorry, but...
Egil's death changes things.
What things?
Julie is very likely
going to take over at Mistral,
but she's not ready yet.
That gives us a bit of wiggle room
which we should take advantage of.
Okay.
But what difference
does it make for us?
We're leaving everything behind.
Julie.
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
I didn't know he was that ill.
That it was so serious.
Why are you here?
I'll make breakfast for mum.
She can't handle getting out of bed.
I'll come along. I have to ask her
about dad's medicine.
Can't that wait?
She's not doing well.
Neither are you.
Going somewhere?
I'm going back to Mistral
to talk to the staff
about what's happened.
Hello?
What are you thinking about?
I'm sorry. I...
Yesterday was all about
handling the chaos.
It's beginning to sink in.
Of course.
He'd been in your life
for a long time.
I was so angry with him
when he and mum became a couple.
I blamed him for the divorce.
I just took dad's side.
- That's understandable.
- But...
Egil and dad were best friends.
They opened the beach hotel together
when we were children.
When they fell out Egil took over
some of the land and built Mistral.
What do you mean by "took over"?
I try to stay out of it,
but dad claimed he'd been cheated.
Nobody wants to dig deeper.
Okay.
I'm sorry, but I have to ask...
So Julie is Egil's daughter?
- Your half-sister?
- No.
Mum and Egil got together
when we were teenagers.
When you and Julie were together?
- Okay.
- Sorry. I should have told you.
She'd probably agree with that.
SALTSJÖVIK BEACH HOTEL
- Please don't touch.
- Okay. It's valuable. I understand.
- Is it the hotel's founder?
- Yes, on the right it's...
Werner Gyllenmark,
who ran the hotel for 20 years.
The other one is Egil Grip.
He's sadly no longer with us.
So... Welcome to
Saltsjövik Beach Hotel.
Are you the receptionist?
No, I've been the front desk manager
for many years.
- Where's the receptionist then?
- Mum, stop it.
I'll check you in.
No problem at all.
Shouldn't the receptionist
be here on her first day?
I'm sure there's
a very good reason for that.
Louise Wickström.
Everybody calls me Lojsan.
Svante Jakobsson.
Front desk manager.
- You're really fond of that title.
- Right. Then you must be Lukas.
Our new cleaner. Welcome.
I suppose I might as well
give you a tour of the place.
You show the way, Svante!
How is Marianne?
- I got her to eat a little bit.
- That's good.
You know... I thought...
Do you have to...
It might be work.
- When you become the new CEO...
- He hasn't promised anything.
Who else would it be?
It's always been your goal.
No one knows the hotel better.
He can't choose anyone else.
Thank you. For always supporting me.
We support each other.
We're family. And now we should
become a family for real, I think.
If we want this to happen
we need to start now.
- You do want this, right?
- Sure, absolutely.
The whole process is just so...
It involves so many people.
It feels too private for that.
Then we'll just have to find
a donor we know.
- You've found someone, right?
- I have.
MISTRAL
When check-out is completed
you list the room for cleaning.
Welcome to Saltsjövik.
Is this your first visit?
- Yes.
- Same here. I just moved here.
I hope you'll like it here
as much as I do. Your name?
- Henriksson.
- That's my maiden name.
Maybe we're related.
Where are you from?
- Gothenburg.
- The diamond of the west coast.
Unfortunately, I have no relatives
there as far as I'm aware.
- Room 219.
- Thanks.
The lift is right there.
- Welcome.
- Thanks.
Did I do well?
Don't be too personal
with the guests.
So... the check-out process.
Hi, Petra.
- Am I disturbing?
- Yes, a bit, actually.
I just wanted to tell you I spoke
with Gabrielle at the party.
I'd be honoured to help you.
As your donor.
Considering how long
we've worked together...
Absolutely. Let's go through
the details in due course.
- I'm a little busy right now.
- Sure. Of course.
See you.
MOVING BOX
Life takes some unexpected turns.
Six months ago I'd have
never thought we'd end up here.
You didn't know dad was
sleeping with your best friend then.
Svante is just too funny.
What a character.
I'll go crazy if I have to clean up
after everyone every day.
- Then it's back to school.
- Forget it.
Make up your mind!
You can't loaf around at home.
This is not my home!
- Where are you going?
- Out!
A coffee for sir!
You seem happy.
Have you met someone new?
No, I haven't met someone.
Quite the opposite, actually.
What do you think of the new one?
Lojsan, right?
"Lojsan". She wanted her nickname
on her name tag.
- Totally unacceptable.
- She sounds like fun.
She is fun.
Happy and nice towards everyone.
- That's terrible!
- She's just a bit... too much.
- She likes you.
- What do you mean?
I saw you showing her around.
The way she looked at you.
I've been a bartender long enough
to know that look.
No... She's just good at listening.
And that's important.
It's important.
Hi.
You can have an awesome sandwich
that I've made myself.
- Or you can have a roll.
- I'll take the roll, thanks.
- Roll. Great. And a coffee as well?
- Sure.
- You're not from here, right?
- No. Thank God!
- Staying long?
- I hope not.
This is actually a fun place.
Just last night...
...Werner Gyllenmark's biggest
competitor died at his party.
Are you almost done?
- His name's Egil.
- What's that?
The man you were blabbering on about
who died.
- He had a name.
- I'm sorry.
Her name is Rebecka.
Cleaner at The Beach Hotel.
MISTRAL
- Hi.
What are you doing?
Why didn't dad say anything
if his heart was that weak?
What is it?
Read it.
What is this?
"I have tried to reason with you,
but it's obvious you won't yield
until you've ruined it for us all.
I'm coming to the party.
I'm going to tell the truth.
This has to stop."
Subtitles: Jakob Jensen
plint.com