Let me welcome you
to Saltsjövik's Beach Hotel.
Classic Werner.
Egil is here.
What are you doing here, Dad?
You and Werner in the same room
is not a good idea.
I came here to help you.
I don't need help, so you can leave.
Who is that Julie, really?
Still using that old trick?
Sebastian said
they're childhood friends.
So, more than friends?
And with that, I'm leaving the CEO
position at The Beach Hotel...
Dad!
Unfortunately his heart
couldn't handle the stress.
It can't be true,
I was just in there!
There, Mum.
I've tried reasoning with you,
but you clearly won't give up.
I'll come to the party,
this has to end.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry, I just had to check
something, quickly.
You have no right
to barge into my bedroom like this.
I know.
I know that. I just have to...
Did Dad take Tramadol often?
Definitely not.
And be careful with those.
So you don't think
he could have taken too many?
Why would he do that?
The doctor thought
that might be the reason.
The doctor?
The doctor should have saved him.
One moment he's fine...
the next he isn't breathing.
I'm going to sue them!
Would you say that...
Dad had enemies?
What do you mean?
I've found really strange,
threatening emails.
From who?
I don't know. They're from an
unknown email address.
Egil had no enemies.
He was a bigger man than that.
You know who wished him harm.
THE BEACH HOTEL
There's coffee.
We have to leave in ten minutes.
Yesterday you barely wanted
to go back.
I'm just a little curious
about my colleagues.
Ah. Any cute girls?
Stop it.
Who's that?
No one important.
Is it Dad?
That's good, right?
That he's getting in touch.
-Isn't it?
-One text, in two weeks.
-Maybe it isn't easy for him.
-Why do you defend him?
I don't.
I think everything
will work out in the end.
You think he'll come back?
Why are we here then?
Not everything
is that black and white.
No, let's make the best
of this situation.
Right, honey?
We might even have fun today,
who knows?
I've tried looking up the email
addresses the blackmailer used...
but there's no way to trace them.
Whoever did it
knew what they were doing.
It's a good thing Egil
printed everything.
Otherwise we never would have known.
Maybe that's what he wanted?
What...
What do you want to do now?
Do you want to take this
to the police, or?
Yes, I think so.
Congratulations on your engagement.
I don't think I said it
the other day.
Thanks, yes, well,
some other things happened...
"Some other things."
Yeah, it's so horribly tragic.
Do they know the cause of death yet?
Yeah, the doctor thinks it might
have to do with his medicine.
That's right,
you drove Julie to the hospital.
Yeah, he was nice enough
to volunteer.
But maybe we should talk...
about something else.
We didn't have time to tell you
everything at the party.
Oh my God... you're not?
No, no. Petra!
-Petra.
-You're not getting a sibling.
I'm suddenly sweating.
But listen guys, as you know,
or maybe you don't,
Vendela's mum, Inez lives,
since a while back, in Bretagne.
I had no idea.
An amazing house,
right by the ocean. It's so nice.
But, unfortunately, it's starting
to get a bit hard for Mum
to take care of it by herself.
-So...
-Yes, so we thought we'd help her.
By moving there.
We'll simply buy the big house
and she'll live in the guest house.
I don't really understand...
I think you do.
Guys, that sounds amazing.
No, it sounds insane.
Oh, Petra.
Dad, you haven't taken a week
of vacation your whole life.
What are you gonna do over there?
I've had an art studio there
for a long time.
Right, and while she's painting,
what will you do? Pose?
Maybe I will.
No, I'll think of something, we'll
think of something, don't worry.
Yeah, well,
I have to propose a toast.
Vendela...
you've succeeded in doing something
none of us has managed...
To get Dad to want to take it easy.
That's worth toasting.
-Congratulations.
-Thanks.
-Cheers.
Does this look good?
Yeah, but Svante usually goes around
and checks everything.
-Svante?
-Yeah, our boss.
He's really pedantic
so he always does the last bits.
And he doesn't get annoyed?
People are so disgusting.
-What is it?
-I have to get out of here.
Now? We have several rooms left.
Yeah but maybe we could just
grab a quick coffee?
No one will notice.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, come on.
So, when are you moving?
As soon as possible.
We've already started
sending things down.
There's no reason to wait,
we can sort out
the practicalities from there.
But what about the house here?
Are you selling it?
No I think we'll keep it. Unless
you're interested? Or you, Petra?
So you must have already decided.
Who's taking over.
Yeah, that's true.
What are you waiting for?
Will you tell us at the airport?
Mum.
Hi.
Hi, can we offer you anything?
I'm sorry for your loss, Marianne.
-Are you?
-Yes.
It's your fault.
Excuse me?
I think we should leave.
You couldn't drop it, could you?
You just couldn't let us be.
Mum, you're just being unfair.
Petra, he doesn't need
you to defend him.
He's never needed anyone
but himself.
You're in shock, Marianne, you don't
really know what you're saying.
You can't belittle me anymore,
Werner.
I want to know how it feels?
To have another life
on your conscience.
If you're here to spread lies
and be rude, you can leave.
Come on, Mum.
He cannot love anyone but himself,
you'll find that out.
Come on.
Yeah, well...
Well, what can you say?
-Do you feel better?
-Yeah, a little.
That job makes me panic sometimes.
What are you doing on the weekend?
What is there even to do
in Saltsjövik?
How old are you?
Eighteen.
-In a few weeks.
-So, 17.
Then you can't miss the club.
-The club?
-Yeah.
The youth club.
Julie!
-Hi!
-Hi.
I'm Rebecca.
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
I just wanted to say that.
I'm so sorry.
RIght, I have to go.
Who was that?
Julie Grip.
She's the manager of Hotel Mistral.
So it was her dad who died?
Shit. And you know her?
No. I probably wouldn't say
I know her, but...
Everyone knows who she is.
You can't be suggesting Dad had
something to do with Egil's death.
Right?
His heart just couldn't keep going.
I know you admire him
and everything he does.
I didn't know things were
that bad between you.
He's sabotaged Egil all these years.
Yes, but wasn't it fairly...
mutual?
That old conflict.
You don't know everything
about your father.
And what he's capable of.
No, so tell me.
My sweet son,
you think the best of everyone.
Mum, if you have something to say,
I want to know.
I'm so tired, Sebastian,
I can't do this.
That's it... Come here.
How much can do I have to take
during one single family gathering?
Werner didn't deal with that so
well, but he's probably right.
Marianne is in shock.
And then France?
France?!
I mean, Dad doesn't speak
a word of French.
That will make him popular.
-You don't think...?
-What?
That she's a gold digger?
Maybe you should talk to him
if you're worried, Petra.
Yeah, I will.
Or I'll let Tone do it.
And you feel ready?
To take over?
Yes, of course.
It's happening.
Everything we've longed for.
Speaking of, Martin will be coming
over to us soon.
Oh, is that necessary?
Yes, we should talk to him
before we take his sperm, right?
What are you doing here?
I came home with Mum.
She's asleep.
How are you feeling?
Fine.
Julie...
Your dad has just died,
you're not fine.
No.
Have you even sat down
since it happened?
I will later.
When?
I don't know.
Maybe after the funeral.
There are a thousand things
that need to be done now.
Hey, I know you want to be strong.
You can't just carry on like normal.
You know that, right?
Come on, let's go for a walk.
Hi.
-Nice top.
-Thanks.
-Do you like Marvel?
-The latest Batman was okay.
Are you completely uneducated?
I saw Rebecca.
Are you on a date?
No, we just took a break from work.
I think she's a bit down.
Isn't this your first day?
Yes, why?
You're already slacking off.
Rebecca said it was okay.
Is she your boss?
Don't worry, I'm on top of it.
It doesn't seem that way.
Knock knock,
is this where you're hiding?
-Where are Lukas and Rebecca?
-I have no idea.
I'll call them.
Guests will be
in this room in an hour.
I'll help you.
I can't get in touch
with Dad's doctor.
And I have to go to Mistral and talk
to the staff about the future.
Hey.
Can't we just forget
about all that for a moment?
Shall we go down to the beach?
I haven't been there for ages.
It hasn't changed.
Nice to hear.
-The shortcut?
-Of course.
What the hell are you doing?
-That was fucking close. Idiot.
-What the hell.
Okay. It's okay.
Maybe we shouldn't have
crossed like that.
-I wasn't thinking.
-It's okay.
Hey, come on.
It's okay.
You're fast.
This is where I started
once upon a time.
As a cleaner.
Is it just as neat and tidy
at your place?
-What do you mean?
-How do you divide housework?
You and your wife?
I don't have one... I'm single.
Really? Are you separated too?
No, nothing like that.
It... just hasn't worked out
that way.
I'm just surprised.
So, what do you do
when you're not working?
There are often things to do
at home too.
Make the rosters
and that sort of thing.
Fun.
And then I help out with the soup
lunches down at the Sailors' Home.
Lunch for the lonely.
Mostly pensioners, you know.
They never get out to meet people...
so we organise lunch
and some entertainment.
Something to brighten up their day.
It's nothing big, but it feels nice
to give something back.
Throw?
I'm just babbling on.
I haven't asked you about yourself.
How long have you danced bugg?
You wrote about it on your CV.
I think there's a group
down in Town Hall.
You should look them up.
I'll do that. Thanks for the tip.
It feels like I was here
just the other day.
Hello?
Sorry. On the road back there,
it was terrifying.
Hey, come on. It wasn't a big deal.
I feel grateful sometimes.
I know how fast everything can be
taken away.
Might as well enjoy life
as much as possible.
What? Was that a bit too much?
Maybe just a bit.
Are you fully recovered?
Yeah, well...
I take painkillers sometimes
when my back gives me trouble.
-How often is that?
-I'm okay.
I have to get back to the office.
I'm going back to Stockholm soon.
I know.
Maybe it's just as well.
You've got a lot of questions.
Do you mind us asking
about your family?
Of course. Both my parents are
in the restaurant industry.
So it's in my blood.
That's not what I meant.
I was thinking illnesses
and that kind of thing.
Is there anything hereditary?
Well, my dad was crazy.
But not in that way.
I mean just that he had crazy ideas.
Especially during the holidays.
One summer,
we'd go on luxury cruise,
the next, we'd camp
in the middle of the forest,
in the driving rain, naturally.
So no illnesses?
No.
MISTRAL HOTEL AND SPA
-Hi.
Where have you been?
I've been trying to get hold of you.
Sorry.
I thought the doctor had been
in touch or something.
No, we just went for a walk.
Ah, you and Gabrielle?
No, by myself.
Oh, okay. You said "we".
Then I misspoke.
Where have you been?
-We took a break.
-For two hours?
This is completely unacceptable.
Don't you know how much trouble
you caused us all?
Was it your idea?
We needed a break, okay?
I've had a terrible day,
and I hope it never happens again.
Okay? I'm warning you.
-If this happens again...
-That's enough.
You're not responsible
for the staff here.
-I know that.
-And I deal with any warnings.
Excuse me for helping.
Next time,
you don't need to help at all.
If everything is so terrible here.
I promise.
This mistake will not be repeated.
Back to work. Now.
What's your problem?
Nothing.
We need to have a talk
before we take the next step.
There's something I want
to bring up first.
-It's important.
-Go on.
This child you'll help us have,
you won't be their parent.
No... But that's okay.
Are you sure about that?
Yes... I've never wanted to
be a father.
Okay, then why volunteer for this?
Why help us?
There are two reasons, really.
The first is that I like you.
Okay, and the other reason?
I've always been carefree in life.
It's time to do
something meaningful.
Something significant.
So maybe it's worth going into that
booth with some overused magazine
and do the deed, so to speak,
and hand the jar over to a nurse.
I have to apologise
for the other night.
I interrupted just as
you and Vendela...
Right, no, gosh...
You couldn't have known.
And you had important news.
Marianne blames me.
What do you mean?
For Egil's death.
But that just happened. He must
have been sicker than we thought.
Yes.
The most important thing now
is that it doesn't look like
we're benefiting from this.
-If you get what I mean.
-Do what you think is best.
You or your successor.
I was actually wondering what
your thoughts were on that.
One thing first...
We're moving, Vendela and I.
Yes, to France. Petra told me.
Welcome.
What do you think about that?
I don't know what to say.
I haven't known Vendela that long.
What do you want to know?
Or is it Petra who's wondering?
Tone, we've known one another
for awhile now.
Do you think I'm someone who can be
seduced by one dazzling smile?
Come on.
She's not after anything.
In reality, she's the one with
money. Well, her mother, anyway.
Right, who you're buying
the house from.
Can I at least take a look
at that contract?
Of course,
if that make you feel better.
Petra, in future,
you don't have to go through Tone
when it comes to family matters.
Okay?
POKER
Hey, how was your bath?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Darling... have you had a stroke?
Just tell me what you were doing.
Okay. I was just talking to Dad.
It wasn't pleasant.
I need a glass of wine.
Do you want one?
Where are my scissors?
No idea.
-Hey, Marianne?
-Yes?
Have you thought at all about...
about the future?
Where you'll live,
and that kind of thing?
What do you mean?
This is mine and Egil's home.
Yes, and mine.
I grew up in this house.
Aksel and I planned to start
a family here.
My husband has just died...
and you want to kick me out?
No, I didn't say that.
Just that this isn't going to work
long term.
You're the coldest person
I've ever met.
Have you no heart?
Here. Can you leave, now?
Egil didn't want to see it,
but I saw it from the start...
how bad you are.
But I'm the one
who has to do it all
while you whine
about fucking scissors.
Can you leave now?
So?
What do you say?
It feels familiar.
That means positive,
in advertising language?
-I knew it.
-It's definitely not bad, but...
isn't it very similar
to previous campaigns?
Mm. Just how Dad wants it.
-And that's the main thing.
-You know how it is.
He's never been disappointed in you.
Sure he has. Many times.
He says if I gamble again,
I'll never take over.
So make sure you don't.
That's great!
There's the solution.
Petra...
I'm fucking done
if he thinks I've started again.
-No...
-Hey...
It'll be okay.
You make everything sound
so fucking simple.
I know. That's my superpower.
Listen.
I'll help you.
Okay?
Okay.
With this too. If I may.
Do you want to?
No, don't think that way.
It's good you called to tell me.
So... thank you for that.
Great. Good. Bye.
I've called the removalists.
Already?
Mm. They're going to move your
things all the way to Bretagne.
The booking needs to be made early.
If you want to be helpful,
you can take these with you.
I'm getting used to them.
Or I can set fire to them.
With you in them.
What do you think?
Fine.
Hello?
Where are you?
Sorry, Vendela. Sorry.
No, I'm just... thinking about
who should take over the hotel.
I thought that was decided.
No.
It's not that simple.
That's not how it sounded
when we made that decision.
Together.
I'm moving, Werner.
I'm ready for this change.
The question is, are you stuck...
in that armchair?
You know what you want.
Yeah, should I not?
TONE
-It looks great.
-Thanks.
Hey, do you have a minute?
I'm actually on my way out.
-What is it?
-I just talked to Mum.
She's freaking out.
I know, it didn't go well. But it
needs to be dealt with eventually.
Where we're going to live.
Why?
You've lived under the same roof
for years, it's been fine.
Are you kidding?
Marianne hates me.
-She always has.
-Of course she doesn't.
-She does.
-You're just different.
She's just lost...
I know.
You've also lost Egil.
But... can't you just try
to talk to one another?
Do you know how often I've tried?
It hasn't worked once.
She's never wanted anything to do
with me. That's just how it is.
I didn't know it was that bad.
How could you have missed that?
She sent you to Stockholm
just to separate us.
I don't mean you didn't go
of your own free will.
Maybe she's right,
that I'm cold and heartless,
and it's just as well that you left.
Hey, Julie?
-I have to...
-Wait.
I've always regretted it.
That I didn't go with you.
I have to go.
I hope we see you again soon.
So...
I'm ready for your apology.
Are you serious?
You exceeded your authority.
Will you act normal again
if I say sorry?
I don't understand.
We had a really nice time yesterday,
we got quite close, right?
Yes.
Yes, but you thought it was
completely terrible.
That's what you told Lukas
and Rebecca.
How awful it was to work with me.
No, I said it was terrible
that you and I had to do their job.
Working with you was fun.
Alright.
So I was wrong?
Yeah, like 100% wrong.
Happens to the best of us.
Even you.
By the way, I signed up
for bugg course. Thanks for the tip.
You're welcome.
Darling...
Are we celebrating something?
-Thank you.
-It's your favorite, right?
You're so sweet.
What did you do today?
Um... not so much.
I thought about trying out that yoga
in town but it didn't work out.
I'm just a bit stressed.
Saltsjövik feels so small.
Everyone seems so involved
with one another.
You're right.
It's just a lot of old shit.
Let's go home.
As soon as possible.
Yes, please.
SVANTE GAVE ME THREE EXTRA ROOMS
TOMORROW. I THINK I'LL BE "SICK".
Excuse me!
I thought you were at work.
I was going there now, actually.
-No, I'm done for the day.
-Oh, where are you going?
Home. I've got a studio apartment
around the corner.
Do you live alone?
Yes, when you work, you get paid,
and you can pay for things.
Like rent... Part of your education.
Right.
See you.
I CAN HELP YOU.
YOU'RE THE BEST!
As I said, the autopsy is complete.
We found large amounts
of Tramadol in Egil's body.
I have to ask, did you see
any signs that Egil was depressed?
No, Dad had his problems but I don't
think he wanted to kill himself.
No, but the Tramadol
he was prescribed
was 50mg for temporary pain.
We found signs he'd taken
at least three times that.
And during a short time.
He should have known better.
He did.
What Julie might not have
the same awareness of is that...
Egil was very stressed.
I had to help him keep control of...
most things, actually.
It doesn't surprise me at all
that he would miss his medication.
Petra came to me with a suggestion
for the hotel's marketing.
What did you think?
Interesting.
Lots of new ideas.
I have to say,
it looked unexpectedly professional.
She just asked for some input,
but she did it mostly herself.
Do you think Petra would be
a good CEO?
Absolutely.
I don't want you to answer
as a loyal younger brother.
I mean it.
This job demands
everything you have.
If you lose focus,
it could go under.
Petra couldn't be more focused
and keen for this.
She's dedicated her life
to the hotel.
Just like you.
She stayed here
when I went to Stockholm.
If she needs help, marketing
or whatever, I'll help her.
I'll always be there for the family
when you need me.
Good.
You were there for me.
After the accident.
You know I'm proud of you.
Hmm?
What are you doing?
First you say Dad was on top of his
medication, and now the opposite.
I don't know what
you're going on about.
Why did you change your story?
Leave me alone!
-Are we waiting for someone?
-One more.
Did you want me, Werner?
Absolutely. Come in. Sit down.
I know my move might seem to have
come up suddenly.
For some.
I know you know,
but I'll say it anyway.
I've dedicated my life
to this place.
And I can honestly say,
I never thought I'd be...
handing over the baton
to someone else.
You've decided.
This work demands loyalty...
devotion... clarity.
The decision hasn't been easy.
But I'm counting on you
to accept it.
Taking over as CEO, is...
Sebastian.
Subtitles: Lily Ray
plint.com