As you know, Vendela's mother has
been living in Brittany for awhile.
Unfortunately, it's getting hard for
Mum to look after all this alone.
So we thought we'd help her
by moving there.
Do you feel ready to take over?
Of course.
-What are you doing?
-Hey.
The autopsy is finished.
We found large amounts of Tramadol
in Egil's body.
-Would you say Dad had enemies?
-What do you mean?
I found really weird,
threatening emails.
Call me Lojsan, everyone does.
How do you divide the housework,
you and your wife?
-I'm single.
-Really?
The child you help us have,
you won't be their parent.
I've always regretted
not going with you.
The new CEO will be...
Sebastian.
Thank you for your time.
No problem.
You've read the autopsy report,
right?
-Yes, I've read it.
-Good.
Marianne, you know Klara Söderbom
from the police?
Hi, Marianne,
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Can you and I have a little chat?
About what?
I thought you could show me
where Egil kept his medicines.
Sure. Come with me.
THE BEACH HOTEL
You said no, right?
I said I'd think about it.
But that means no, right?
Darling, you've never said
you wanted to take over
your dad's old hotel.
It's not that old.
Don't laugh this off.
No, okay. I haven't.
-It's always been Petra's dream.
-Exactly.
You can't give up everything
you've built for this.
Your last campaign went so well.
You'll be able to take over
any client you want, soon.
Our life is there.
Not here in Saltsjövik.
I've worked here
almost my entire adult life.
Jesus, Sebastian was lucky
to have worked here over summer.
Sure, but you can't
really think about it that way.
How can that not play a role?
I don't want to fight,
but I think you've made a mistake.
I know you've made a mistake.
We've been plodding along too long,
we need a new perspective.
Yes, it wouldn't have been
a problem for me.
Petra, you are
an excellent hotel manager.
And I'd love to see you continue.
What if I don't want to?
It doesn't matter what I want
because you always prefer Sebastian.
Okay. This isn't about that.
-No?
-When did you last gamble?
-Ages ago.
-How long?
If I look at your phone's search
history, apps... what will I find?
It's under control.
Okay, one mistake,
after an extremely stressful day,
that can't be such a big deal.
Who told you?
You weren't going to tell me,
were you?
Don't you see
this is just like last time?
I can't trust you. It's that simple.
It's not about my gambling, is it?
I never really had a chance.
You've always wanted Sebastian
to take over. Jesus!
-Is this group bookings?
-That's up here.
Right.
Did you do any rostering yesterday?
I did a bit of rostering, yes.
You're on it.
-Hey.
-The stairwell light's fixed.
Thanks! Well done.
-It was just a loose plug.
-I appreciate that.
Initiative.
You're the one who asked me
to look at it.
Yes, but still. Thanks.
While you're at it, look at the
lobby, I think it was flickering.
-Okay.
-Great!
-Hey?
-Yeah?
Trying to win points with me
through my son?
No, that would never occur to me!
I wouldn't mind.
-Hey! Welcome to Saltsjövik!
-Thanks!
Thank you so much for your help.
So, what happens now?
I'll confirm a few details,
and then...
I think we're done here.
-Again, I'm so sorry for your loss.
-What about the high dose?
Dad would never have made
that mistake.
It was a stressful day, Julie.
He must have mixed up his pills.
But you told me
he had total control.
Well, we'll test these.
It's a routine measure.
Wait! Look at this.
Someone was trying to blackmail Dad.
Okay. I'll take a look at this.
That's enough, Julie.
We won't take up any more
of your time, Klara. Thanks a lot.
Thank you.
Isn't it enough for you
that he's gone?
Do you have to let your paranoia
cause all this unpleasantness?
-Hello.
-Hey.
Have you had a nice morning?
Pleasant and peaceful?
I don't know what's worse,
Swedish or French bureaucracy.
I think I've got what we need to
register the car when we get there.
How about you?
I'm trying to get hold of Sebastian.
I see.
Maybe he needs some time to think.
You thought he'd say yes?
Do you know what I think?
-No.
-It's time for your kids to grow up.
Realise they have you and the hotel
to thank for their comfortable life.
Do you think he doesn't want this?
He probably does.
But his girlfriend might not be
as keen to live in Saltsjövik.
But I'm not either, actually.
-No?
-No.
But you know, girlfriends,
they come and go.
They do not.
It felt totally natural, to give
them the family they dream of.
It's so generous off you.
They've waited long enough.
Excuse me, can you give me a moment?
Of course.
Nice to see you're still here.
Who knows?
I might be stuck here forever.
Sebastian has been offered
the CEO position.
And... I don't even know
why I told you.
I don't even know you, but...
I don't know
what's going on right now.
Maybe it's fate.
It's probably best not to flirt
with more than one woman at a time.
The police are taking it seriously.
That there's something odd
about Dad's death.
I know how I sound, but I...
I really don't think Dad would have
mixed up his medication.
Sometimes accidents happen.
It's that simple.
But why didn't he say
he was being blackmailed?
I don't know.
But I don't want you to drown
in this.
At risk of sounding
like I'm at work,
I think this is part
of your grieving process.
You're looking for something else
to focus on,
other than the grief.
You need space to be sad too.
Hey? Don't you?
Yeah, maybe.
So, will you send me
an invoice later?
The first conversation is free.
Sorry, I'm just going on
about myself.
No, it's fine.
How are you?
Well... we're struggling on.
Or, I guess it's mostly me.
I think it would be easier to be
a single mother right now.
I don't think so.
You and Aksel will probably have
quadruplets before we even have one.
ENTRANCE
First-class service around here,
hey?
I thought I'd have a coffee.
I think my boss has got a crush
on my mum.
Gross, right?
What does she say?
We haven't really discussed it.
-Is he harassing her?
-No, no.
It's more the way
they laugh together and...
No, I don't want to talk about it.
Do you know much about
connecting speakers?
A bit. Why?
I want to connect my TV
to my wireless speaker,
so the whole apartment is like
a cinema.
Nice.
I think I could try to help.
-Really?
-The day after tomorrow.
I'm free in the afternoon.
Perfect!
Hey.
-Did you plan this all by yourself?
-Yes.
Why didn't you talk to me?
You've been so busy with the police.
Not too busy to plan
my own father's funeral.
This song you want played
at the end, for example.
Yes?
I just don't see my father
in any of this.
Have you ever considered your father
might have changed when he met me?
If you had your way, Julie,
you'd erase mine and Egil's life
together.
-Like it never happened.
-Not everything is about you.
-Julie speaking.
-Hi, Julie. It's Klara.
Hi.
We found nothing out of the ordinary
in Egil's medication,
so we consider this case closed.
But what about the emails?
The blackmail?
We can't trace them.
And I'm sure if Egil had been really
worried, he'd have contacted us.
So you're not going to do anything?
We have no reason to take
this investigation further.
We can't even prove
there's been a crime.
I'm sorry, Julie.
Right. Thank you.
Nice of you to come so quickly.
I just needed to move a meeting.
Werner said you had some questions
about the house in Brittany.
-I wanted to see if I could help.
-So nice of you.
Have I understood right
that Werner will buy the house,
but it will be under your name?
Yes, that's the plan.
French tax laws, apparently.
I don't know much about
that sort of thing.
-You like helping Werner, don't you?
-It's my job.
And he really appreciates it,
I know he does.
Are you disappointed he's leaving?
It was a bit unexpected,
it's not like Werner.
Would you rather he stayed here...
with you?
No, that's not... We've never...
We work together.
Calm down, I'm just joking.
Something's missing.
I don't think so.
There's land as well, right?
-Yes.
-This is just building designation.
Right. I must have left it in there.
Wait here, I'll be right back.
Hey! Hello there. Do you have time
for a little coffee?
Not here!
It wouldn't look good to the guests.
Okay, a little one.
It could taste better.
I'm used to it.
Come over and try my coffee.
You'll know what I mean.
There's a policy here at the hotel
that I haven't mentioned yet.
-It's important.
-Okay?
Employees aren't allowed to have
relationships with one another.
Who came up with that idiotic rule?
Werner.
I don't think it's idiotic.
It's there to help avoid conflicts
at work.
Right. And you've always followed
that rule?
Yes... It's Werner's oldest rule.
Werner's oldest rule,
it must be important.
Fun guy, that Werner.
I thought I'd steal some sheets
from you.
Sure, but you'll have to get me
some more later.
Yes, boss.
I wanted to ask you something.
-What's that?
-Could you take my rooms later?
Are you going to sneak away again?
-I'm going to a funeral.
-Egil's?
Yeah.
-Did you know him?
-Please, Lukas.
It's important.
It would mean so much to me.
You'll have to ask Svante too.
If it's okay.
Of course.
Okay.
See you later, then.
Dad liked these.
This is wrong.
I shouldn't go to his funeral.
What is it?
The police are closing
the investigation.
Marianne claims I'm paranoid
because I don't think
Dad's death was an accident.
Sometimes we see patterns
because it's easier to accept.
So you don't believe me either?
Darling, I'll support you
no matter what.
Hey? You know that.
But right now,
it's about your father's funeral.
Okay?
Hey.
I had a nice time yesterday.
I can only agree.
-There you go.
-Thanks.
But today's the last day
of the conference.
Of course.
But is it your last night
at the hotel?
That's very tempting.
-But I should go...
-To your family.
Exactly.
But who knows? Maybe I'll see you
again at the next conference.
Yeah, you know where to find me.
Have a nice evening.
-What are you doing here?
-Everything's ready.
Do you want Thai or pizza later?
My shout.
-You forgot.
-No... I just...
-I thought we...
-It's fine.
No, I have work in the afternoon.
-Okay.
-You don't like when I skip work.
No, that's true.
I can come by tomorrow
and do it then.
It's fine. I'll sort it out.
-Lilja...
-See you.
Come on! Lilja!
-Where's Shirin?
-She's got a headache.
She didn't really know Egil so...
She's angry with me.
As well.
You told Dad I gambled again, right?
I haven't said a word.
-You have to believe me.
-Nobody else knows.
I don't know why he did this.
I didn't ask to be CEO.
No, of course not!
Everything lands in your lap,
even what you don't want.
What do you want me to do?
Say no, obviously.
Hey, listen.
I'm accepting the job...
Look at me.
Then we can work together.
After six months, I'll move back
home and you take over.
Why would that make a difference?
If Dad sees us working together,
he'll let go more easily.
He'll notice you know
the hotel better than me.
So you're prepared to stay
in Saltsjövik half a year?
Why?
Stockholm will always be there.
I like it here.
Is that you're only reason to stay?
Dad will never agree to it.
He doesn't have to know.
Until it's time.
Okay? Let's go.
Come on.
Would you have liked to go?
Maybe.
But he wouldn't have
wanted me there.
Would you have forgiven him?
For tricking you out of the land
to build Mistral?
And stealing your wife?
He's gone now.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Okay.
Are you okay?
-Don't touch me or I'll break down.
-Okay.
What happened the other day...
It was wrong.
Wasn't it?
It absolutely can't happen again.
I know.
It's probably good that
you're going back to Stockholm soon.
How's the headache?
Better.
I'm sure you know I've asked
Sebastian to take over the hotel.
He mentioned it.
I don't know if this interests you,
but things are going really well
for Sebastian in Stockholm.
Very well.
When do you think he'll get
an chance like this there?
To run a big company?
In 10, 20 years, maybe?
You haven't thought ahead that far,
right?
But you should.
I see you and Sebastian are serious.
And this will benefit you
in the end too.
You won't have the struggle we did
when the kids were small.
You can have kids right away
and still have a comfortable life.
We certainly haven't discussed
children yet, so...
I'm aware that Saltsjövik can seem a
bit paltry compared with Stockholm,
but this is Sebastian's home.
I think you should understand that.
I think it would be very nice
for Sebastian
to feel supported by you.
You think it's a bad idea?
It's not up to me, but...
I'm going to be a father!
But... is that how Petra
and Gabrielle see it?
Not yet. But I'm sure we can
come to an understanding.
This is my chance
to have a family too!
But you've never wanted one.
-You've been satisfied with your...
-My...?
More temporary connections.
Have you never wanted children?
Yes, I might have wanted that but
that's not how things worked out.
Imagine a little kid,
running around here, "Pappa!"
Yeah, it sounds pretty nice,
actually.
Julie, hi.
Sorry if I'm interrupting.
Hi. Rebecca, right?
Yes. I just wanted to thank you
for the lovely funeral.
It felt really personal.
How nice that you thought so.
And you're beautiful.
Your dress is lovely... nice dress.
Thank you.
I just wanted to ask if...
it might be okay
if we could meet sometime?
Yeah, I guess so.
Right, okay, great!
-Then we'll talk later!
-Sure.
Bye!
-Who was that?
-I barely know her.
Shall we go?
Shirin's waiting for me.
-I saw you were talking to Julie.
-And?
Nothing. That's your business.
Good.
Six months?
-Hey.
How was it?
Nice.
But...
You know.
-Yeah.
-How are you?
Better.
Hey, I talked to Petra.
About the CEO position at the hotel.
You're thinking of accepting?
I have to.
Just for six months,
then we'll go home.
Six months?!
Darling, we can do this.
Okay?
-Together.
-Okay.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Wait a moment.
I don't need to ask
where you've been, do I?
Is it a problem?
Lukas covered for me.
Of course it's a problem when you do
the opposite of what I tell you.
Right, it won't happen again.
It does happen, all the time.
Can you tell me what was
so important about this funeral?
-It's none of your business.
-Honestly, Rebecca.
I don't know what to do with you.
You've had so many chances.
-If showed me I can trust you.
-Chances to do what?
I started as a cleaner here.
Just like you.
Do you really think everyone goes
around dreaming of being like you?
I think they see what rewarding
workplace they have, yes.
It's like any other shit job.
Then I really don't know why
you stay.
No, me neither.
I quit.
Julie.
Everyone seemed very satisfied
with the funeral.
But not you.
I just wish we'd have been able
to plan it together.
Dad was good at keeping us friends.
He was fantastic.
I want to try.
For his sake.
What can I do to improve things
between us?
Easy. Stay away from Sebastian.
-What?
-I saw you outside the church.
I don't know what you're playing at,
Julie.
But I won't
let you ruin his life again.
You know what I'm talking about.
If you hadn't dragged him out that
night, he'd not have been run over.
He's still in pain, you know.
He'll probably be in pain forever.
It was an accident.
It never would have happened
if it weren't for you.
He didn't take risks
before he met you.
Leave him alone.
He has Shirin now.
Hey. You're finished working.
Come with me!
Let's celebrate!
Shouldn't we wait?
How long?
Six months?
In six months, I'll be
far too pregnant to drink this.
Hopefully.
What if Sebastian doesn't
do what he says?
Stop it. Why wouldn't he?
He says I should trust him
but I don't know.
Someone told Dad
I've started gambling again.
Is that true? Have you?
No, of course not.
You're unbelievable.
-What?
-Then I know I did the right thing.
-You told him?
-I saw you!
And I gave you a chance to explain
and you didn't.
And now you're doing it again!
I was afraid of what the stress of
this CEO position would do to you.
How the fuck could you?!
There, I've emptied my locker.
-Anything else?
-I've written a reference for you.
It might be useful.
I don't think so.
Tell me you don't get like this
whenever someone quits?
It feels like a failure of sorts.
My boss at my old job was afraid
of conflict.
She wasn't like you at all. She was
happy to leave this stuff to me.
If you've got advice,
I'd be happy to hear it.
Maybe we could talk
over dinner tonight?
Like a work meeting? Nothing more?
Yes, boss. No rule-breaking, I know.
-Have you got a minute?
-Of course.
-I'd actually wanted to call.
-We've reconsidered.
Good, I've also had time to think.
I don't think you really understand.
I want to be part of
this child's life.
It's actually one of my demands
if I'm to help out.
We're not going through with it.
-What?
-We're not having a child.
You can't do this!
You have to at least explain
what I did wrong!
This has never been about you.
What about Gabrielle?
Does she feel the same?
Hi.
How do you know
you're being ghosted?
After a day, something like that.
Who are you texting?
Rebecca. She quit today.
I didn't even get to say goodbye.
-What will she do now?
-That's what I'm trying to find out.
Do you need help with the speaker?
It's fine. I sorted it out.
It wasn't that hard.
What are you doing tonight?
Not going home.
Mum's taken the boss home.
Seriously?
Want to watch a movie at my place?
Absolutely.
Good. Deal.
Darling, about the hotel?
I'm not doing a long-distance
relationship, so you know.
But Bea from work has just separated
from her boyfriend.
I think she'd rent our apartment
for six months.
What? Did you think
I wanted to break up?
No, I thought it was unimaginable
for you to live in Saltsjövik.
Come on, I love you, Sebastian.
I want to live where you live.
Thank you.
But I refuse to live here.
It's not going to happen.
-We need a place of our own.
-Okay.
Good.
-Where are you going?
-Julies.
Ah, mature.
I can't be near you right now.
You're the one who betrayed me.
You sabotaged my chances of getting
what I've always wanted.
What's that? Having a child,
or a fucking CEO job?
You and Martin can have a kid
together if that's all you want.
You don't get what you've done.
So you're really going to leave?
I can't deal with this any longer.
My last job was like an exercise
in chaos theory.
A colleague thought the hotel would
work better
without a bunch of guests
living there all the time.
What do you like most
about your job?
The people.
The guests,
and those who work there.
You don't like surprises, do you?
That depends. This morning, I had no
idea we'd be having dinner together.
I thought this was a meeting.
I'm really glad you've started
working at the hotel, Lojsan.
Me too.
And rules are just rules, right?
Thank you for a fantastic dinner.
Have you forgotten something?
Yes.
-Hey.
-Are you waiting for me?
-Yes. Here.
Still addicted to lattes?
What is it?
I thought you'd have left by now.
Well... It didn't work out that way,
despite everything.
Dad's asked me to take over as CEO
at the hotel.
And you've accepted?
So you're staying here?
-Yes.
-That's...
Sorry, I'm... shocked.
Do you want to be here?
Yes... I think it could be fun.
-Fun?
-Yes, fun.
That might sound absurd to you,
but you can have fun at work.
You have no idea what you're doing.
Don't say that.
I know one thing, at any rate.
All these old conflicts
with the hotel and all that...
They're finished.
Okay? I want them gone.
Shall we have a breakfast meeting
right now?
Talk it through?
I don't have time.
I'm meeting the lawyer.
Dad's will, you know.
Right. I get it.
Another time.
Okay?
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Welcome, have a seat.
Thank you.
I'll get to the point.
Egil changed his will in Marianne's
favour recently,
since de facto laws don't give great
protection for unmarried couples.
That's why he left the villa
to both of you.
So you're saying we're to continue
sharing the house?
Yes, but you can always choose to
sell your share to the other party.
And what about the hotel?
I have a letter here from Egil.
The last paragraph.
Julie, I understand if you never
forgive me for not telling you this.
I have another daughter from a short
relationship outside my marriage.
A daughter I chose to have
no contact with
to protect you and your mother.
I've lived my life in debt
to this child,
which is why I've decided
to give half of Hotel Mistral
to my daughter Julie Grip,
and the other half to my other
daughter, Rebecca Adolfsson.
Subtitles: Lily Ray
plint.com