What's that?
-It's Petra.
-We can't keep doing this.
We'll just hurt one another.
-And other people.
-I know.
-Don't you know any jokes?
-No...
There's something I want to say.
Okay, go.
I'm in love with you.
Haven't you noticed?
No, go to hell!
-Did you forget something?
-Yes.
-Hey, Lojsan.
-What are you doing here?
Can't you give me one more chance?
For Lukas' sake?
-I should probably go home.
-You can sleep here if you want.
We should probably sleep.
If you can see it's him
in the pictures,
the money will come
when I see the material.
-How much did you hear?
-No idea.
They're the things Petra had
when they found her.
This is Sebastian's.
You have to see this, from security
footage, check the time.
He said he came straight
from the train to the party.
He lied to you.
Are you ready?
We have to go to the police, now.
I want to see
the security footage again.
It is him.
I understand it's hard for you.
I know a lot points to him,
right now.
Don't you see this becomes more
dangerous the longer we stay silent?
Okay, I'll go to the police.
-Good.
-But I want to go alone.
Okay.
THE BEACH HOTEL
What are you looking at?
The papers have started writing
about Petra.
What are they saying?
You don't want to know.
Of course I do.
I want to know what you're thinking.
Shirin, I...
Don't say "we need to talk".
We can't be like this.
How? What's happened?
Don't you think things have changed
with us?
Don't put that on me.
What do you want?
-I love you.
-Stop it!
-I want to have a break.
-To do what?
Get with Julie?
No... I need to think.
What about me? Should I move out?
-Where?
-I don't know, we...
-We'll have to work it out.
-You mean I'll have to.
Without a rich family who conjures
up a job and house when I want?
-Hey...
-I can't deal with this right now.
You've gotten strong!
-Did you let me win?
-Never, I'd never do that.
But seriously,
have you started working out?
No, I just work.
Okay.
How long are you staying?
I've said two nights.
Come on, Mum.
-Then we'll see, okay?
-Okay.
I'm grateful for each second
I get with you two.
You're so strong.
I'm so happy you're here.
I have to ask,
have you found any...
messages from Petra yet?
You can say goodbye note.
Okay.
No, I haven't.
And I don't think I will.
But where is this coming from?
Doesn't Sebastian's necklace matter
anymore?
I'm not totally sure it is his.
Okay. Do you want to see it again?
It's in the box.
Petra wasn't well.
Anyone could see that.
Sure, maybe, but she'd never
have left me like this.
-Even if she was gambling again?
-Can you stop?
What? I'm just trying to help you
get an answer.
It feels more like you're trying to
help yourself.
I don't know what
to believe anymore.
You say you're after the truth.
But whatever doesn't fit
your worldview, you remove.
Do you really think he'd hurt
his own sister?
I think it's best if you leave now.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
-I can come back later.
-Wait a minute.
-What you're doing at my house?
-I need to talk to Julie.
Listen to me carefully,
don't go near her again, understand?
-What did she say?
-She wants to be left alone, okay?
I know that's not true.
You're a fucking psychopath.
-Why did you come back?
-You know...
-Poser.
-Sometimes, I wonder the same thing.
If you leave now, you might be okay.
Julie would have come with me.
-Are you okay?
-Leave!
-Sorry!
-Get out!
It feels like before.
-Not quite.
-What do you mean?
The old Torbjörn wouldn't have
let his son win an arm-wrestle.
I saw it was important to him.
And for you.
He's happy you're here.
What about you?
Did I destroy everything between us?
You got very close.
And I'll never forgive myself
for that.
You're the best thing
that happened to me.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
Damn you.
Do you know how long I've waited
for you to say those words?
Hey.
I thought I'd...
-I just wanted to...
-Yes?
I messed up the other night.
I shouldn't have picked
a horror movie.
I know you don't like them.
Good we've got that sorted.
I'll get a coffee at work
since I'm there anyway.
See you.
Right.
Look, a delivery of wines directly
imported from Château Neuf du Pape.
Look. I'd completely forgotten
I'd ordered them.
And to think you could be so proud
of a cardboard box of wine.
Yes. If you have a nice hotel,
you need nice wines.
But they're dear.
I'll put them away.
I like them too.
-New money wine.
-Behave yourself.
Me? Behave myself?
Him, showing those off,
"Look what I ordered."
What is it? Ten bottles?
-Come on.
-Anyone could order those.
Like some kind of new money habits
he wants to...
No, when are you going to start
talking to him?
About the divorce?
It's too soon.
-What are you talking about?
-It will never work.
Rubbish! At your age, I'd managed to
get divorced four times!
Angelo, he was number four,
we hadn't even moved in together.
-Sure...
-You can do anything.
-Werner has just lost his daughter.
-What does that have to do with us?
I can't throw it in his face now.
Vendela, you know
what you have to do.
Until then, I have nothing more
to say to you.
Shirin, what's wrong?
Listen to me,
you need to breathe more deeply.
Breathe with me, in...
and out.
Come on, once more, calm and still.
And out. Good.
Does that feel a bit better?
Can you stand up?
All right.
I don't know what happened.
I came here
and everything went black.
I couldn't see anything.
-Want me to get Sebastian?
-No.
He wouldn't come anyway.
And I really don't want to hear,
"What did I tell you?"
I'd tear the place down.
Then maybe you should go home.
No, please let me stay.
I promise I won't lose it again.
Lose it as much as you like.
And hey, if you want to talk,
I'm happy to listen.
He attacked me when I asked him
to leave.
Mm, but you know we only have
your word to go on?
Do you think Sebastian's story will
sound the same?
No, probably not.
And it's not him who's here
making a police report, is it?
Okay...
So he shows up unannounced
to your place.
Did he say what he wanted?
He wanted to see Julie.
Well, they're old friends, right?
They were together as teenagers.
Since Sebastian came back
to Saltsjövik,
he's been obsessed with her.
He shows up at her work,
in our home...
Now his sister and stepfather
are dead, and I don't know,
I think it's strange how much
has happened...
Wait, stop, hello.
Wait a minute,
I'm not following at all.
What do you really want
to talk about?
I'm here for Julie's sake.
She doesn't see how dangerous he is.
She's the one who should be sitting
here now.
Why? What do you think
she'd have to say?
Klara, I wish I was wrong.
Okay?
But right before Egil died,
he asked me to keep Julie safe.
If I don't act
and something else were to happen...
I'd never be able to forgive myself.
I didn't notice you here.
I thought I might as well come in.
-But I keep thinking she'll turn up.
-Me too.
It might be insensitive,
but what now?
Will you stay in Petra's position?
What else would I do?
Tone...
Sebastian. He means well, but he's
not really there yet, right?
You have different leadership
styles.
Come on, it's just us.
-You might be right.
-I usually am.
Does he trust you?
I'm working on it.
Can you watch him for me?
We've discussed it.
What, aren't you going to
keep working here?
It's for his sake. And the hotel's.
We need to make sure
he makes no big mistakes.
-And we never had this talk?
-Which talk?
I'm so sorry if the towels
were too soft.
We'll do what we can to improve.
Thank you.
Hey, what do you say?
Shall we go down to the harbour
and dip them in some salt water?
That should do the trick.
To think you can have so much fun
at work.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Nothing can separate me
from you now.
I don't know if you've heard,
Lojsan and I are together again.
No, I didn't know. Congratulations.
Thank you.
So you won't be seeing much of her
for awhile.
I'm taking her on a romantic trip.
Don't say anything. It's a secret.
I'm standing right here.
I can't just leave work
and go on holiday.
Of course you can.
Sixten will get a replacement,
right?
Sure, I'll work it out,
if that's what you want.
I'd prefer to be asked first.
Would the lady like some lunch?
Sure.
See you.
Hey, how are you?
Damn, what have you done?
Have you been in a fight?
Don't worry about it.
I am worried.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Everything's chaos right now.
Is there anything I can do to help?
What do you want in exchange?
Nothing.
Unlike everyone else, you've only
been nice to me from the start.
I care about you.
It's probably best that you know
as little as possible.
So it's nothing to do
with that phone call?
Not at all, you...
You didn't tell Julie?
Of course not.
If...
If you see Julie and Sebastian
together, can you message me?
Of course. I promise.
Thank you.
Mum?
Are you really ignoring me?
Maybe it's just as well.
That you just listen quietly.
I really want to do all I can
so you can keep the house.
But I'm not getting divorced.
I love him.
It wasn't the idea, I know.
You found someone
who was perfect for our plans
but also someone
who was perfect for me.
You must have seen that, deep down.
Can't you be happy for me?
That was the most pathetic thing
I've ever heard.
Do you think it's love you feel
for him?
You don't have it in you,
little girl.
You don't even know what it is.
It'll sting a bit at the start,
sure.
But you're the one
complicating this.
Things will turn out best for you
if you do as I say.
And best for me.
-See this?
-No. What is it?
It's a prenuptial agreement.
Signed and sent to the tax agency.
What have you done?
I don't get a cent if we divorce.
Neither do you, obviously.
Hey?
I'm very happy here, with work too.
Okay...
Yeah, so...
I don't want to move back
to Jönköping.
Then we'll stay.
-We'll stay here.
-Are you sure?
Absolutely. I'm ready. For you.
What about your job?
I'll figure something out.
It'll work out.
Why is Anna-Karin calling?
It's best I just leave her be.
Why?
She didn't take it so well
when I broke up with her.
But hey, we're over. Okay?
It's over.
A toast.
To you, to me, to Saltsjövik.
And for Lukas.
-You're beautiful.
-Stop it.
You are.
How are things?
-You look a bit down.
-I'm good.
Lojsan's going back
to her ex-husband.
What, that jerk who hangs out
in reception all day?
-Does she want that?
-Lojsan can't be made to do things.
Listen...
I'm so sorry I called you a coward.
-Sorry.
-It's true enough.
No, it's really not.
Not in the least.
And Lojsan knows that too.
Did she say she wants
to be with you?
-Yes.
-Then you can't give up yet. Okay?
Okay.
I thought we could have
a little talk about Sebastian.
Okay.
As you probably know,
a report has been made against him.
No, I didn't know that.
-Suspected assault and stalking.
-What are you talking about?
How does your relationship
with Sebastian look?
Is it Aksel who's reported him?
Or Gabrielle?
Julie, I just want to hear this
from you.
Answer the question: have you ever
felt threatened by Sebastian?
No.
Absolutely not.
Why does it feel like there's
something you don't want to tell me?
It's not like you've listened to me
very closely before, right?
Do you still believe your father
died under suspicious circumstances?
Do you suspect anyone?
I'm not really qualified
to do police work.
Am I?
Okay. You don't see grounds for the
report against Sebastian Gyllenmark?
-No, I don't.
-Okay.
Listen, if there's anything you want
to talk to me about, get in touch.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Congratulations to you and Torbjörn.
You already said that.
You can't say it too many times.
Thanks so much.
Call me an idiot if you want to.
No, why would I want to do that?
Lukas is really happy,
and I think this is best
for the family in the long run.
Lukas is almost an adult
and will move out soon.
You're the one who has to live with
Torbjörn for the rest of your life.
ANNA-KARIN
Why hasn't she reached out?
Why don't you?
I don't know what to say.
Well, what do you want to say?
Pretend I'm her and tell me.
I'd say...
Sorry... for things going wrong
the other night.
And... you're cool and smart and...
I don't know why you even want
to be my friend.
-That's basically what I'd say.
-Good! That was great.
Write that.
Friendship can become more.
Are you Lilja or yourself right now?
Just write what you just said to me.
To lilja
Want to meet up?
"Want to meet up?"
Was that too forward?
It's her.
"Absolutely. Training a new person
at work but I can meet later."
You're the best!
I'm sure you'll be together forever.
Like everyone else in this town.
Thank you so much.
TO SEBASTIAN
I LOVE YOU, DESPITE EVERYTHING.
I LOVE YOU DESPITE EVERYTHING
How can you just leave these out?
They're not secret, are they?
Has Sebastian been here?
Why ask about that?
Take these with you.
So I won't have to be reminded
of your conspiracy theories.
Nothing here has anything to do
with me.
I didn't write it.
Just read it.
And come to your own conclusion.
Hey, we have to look at
these streaming services.
We've got no sports channels.
I hate sport and so does Lukas.
Come on! How hard can it be?
Anna-Karin says hi.
She says if you don't get your stuff
by tomorrow, it goes to the tip.
That woman's crazy.
Seriously. She scares me.
So it's not true that she's the one
who kicked you out?
Of course she'd say that.
And that you were fired,
did she make that up?
I really wanted to believe that,
so I called your boss.
You called me boss?
-I can explain.
-Explain this instead:
Why did you come back?
Because you and Lukas are
the most important thing to me.
That's what you wanted to hear,
right?
Did you really think I'd buy that?
You've got this all wrong.
We've got a fresh start, you and I.
I don't need a fresh start.
I've sorted out my life on my own.
You won't cope without me.
How did you get so pathetic?
And you're such a catch?
I'm the best you could hope for.
I'm going back to work now.
You won't be here when I get home.
Were you really going to leave
without saying anything?
How are you getting to the airport?
Don't worry about it.
Let me know when you get there.
Why would I do that?
Because you're my mother.
You know what I've said
about that word.
You're right.
You hardly deserve it.
-Drama queen.
-What's all this?
Inez has decided to go home.
Already?
Hold on, there must be something
we can do to get her to stay.
Respect her decision.
Oh dear.
Just how things go sometimes.
Her mood can change quickly.
Let me drive you to the airport
at least. I'm going out anyway.
Never say no
to a bit of friendliness.
I'll take these.
Wow, what a lot of luggage.
Seriously, aren't you going home?
Never. That's even worse than here.
Please, you have to go home
sometime, right?
I can't deal with it.
What are you going to do?
I don't know. It'll work out.
Maybe I can sort something out.
Oh? What do you have in mind?
Unfortunately, I can't reveal more,
but let's just say I have contacts.
Wow! That sound dangerous.
I'll sort something out.
It'll work out.
Hey.
I talked to the police.
Oh? What do you think?
Do they have enough to arrest him?
How can she believe anything you say
if you make up accusations?
Sebastian has never stalked me.
You might not think so,
but believe me, everyone else does.
This isn't like you.
You don't usually lie.
Neither do you.
See? You don't even deny it.
You'd never hide anything from me,
right?
Have you slept with Sebastian?
Sorry, I...
See this?! He did this
when I told him to stay away!
Tell me, what exactly did he do?
Are you kidding me?
What will make you see?
Does he need to attack you too?
He hurt you, but you can't
make him out to be someone he's not!
Wow. Let me guess.
You didn't tell the police
about the security footage, right?
-Were you ever going to?
-You already destroyed it.
No. You destroyed everything.
What does Torbjörn have to say
about you working night?
He can say what he likes.
I won't have to hear it.
He's gone. I threw him out.
Not because of what I said?
No. He did it all himself.
Oh. That's nice to hear.
I just mean I don't want to be
involved in your decision-making.
-Please, Lojsan, listen to me.
-Isn't it best we just do our jobs
and not get involved in
one another's lives?
Lojsan, I love you.
I've probably loved you
from the moment you walked in.
Please. Can you forgive me for all
my little peculiarities?
Oh my God, I'm useless at this.
What would Werner say?
He can say what he likes.
Vendela, I have a little surprise.
Have you? What is it?
Ta-da!
-Did you forget something?
-I'm so sorry about all that.
We had a good conversation
in the car, Inez and I.
What a husband you have.
He won't let us part as enemies.
No, how would it look?
I convinced her to stay
awhile longer.
So we can become good friends again.
You and I.
We need to celebrate with a glass of
Château Neuf du Pape.
I'll pour.
What are you playing at?
I know you love your husband Werner
very much.
But are you sure his feelings
for you are the same?
This has been a difficult day.
A glass of wine will do nicely.
You keep chopping,
Werner and I will get a head start.
-What's new since the other night?
-Dad moved in.
And moved out again.
I want to hear all about that.
I don't know...
I think there's something
we need to talk about.
I... just wanted to...
What I want to say is...
Sorry, I messed up
another cappuccino.
Can you show me again?
Lukas, this is Jens.
He's just started here.
-What did you want to say?
-Ah, you're Lukas!
I've heard so much about you.
Um, cappuccino, please?
-Yes, see you.
-Nice to meet you.
Really?
Oh, yes.
Just don't say anything to Svante.
He tends to get really grumpy
when staff stay at the hotel.
-Okay.
-To say the least.
How have you managed it
with all your hook-ups?
With my...?
-The thing is...
-Relax.
Wow, what service!
Yes, I thought you deserved it.
You're lovely.
Thank you.
I should...
-I should go.
-Come on.
I can't drink this by myself.
Okay.
Ready?
Well, cheers.
Cheers.
Thank you.
-You could have called first.
-I didn't want to.
-What do you want?
-Come sit.
You know how Julie questioned
Egil's cause of death?
What if Petra didn't kill herself?
Wait, Marianne...
Sure, she was angry at the world,
mostly at you.
But there's no note.
Not even to Gabrielle.
What are you trying to say?
Who would want to kill Petra?
And Egil?
Why does it feel like
someone's after us?
I think it's got something to do
with Fredrik.
-Marianne?
-Yes?
Listen to me.
We agreed, remember?
This is something
we'll never talk about.
You're not doing well,
none of us are,
but stop torturing yourself
with these thoughts.
Go home
and forget this conversation, okay?
Don't treat me
like some hysterical woman.
Listen to me for once.
Why haven't you been in touch?
What do you think?
I know things got out of hand
with Aksel.
It probably sounds really stupid,
but... he attacked me.
Why did you never tell me
you take tramadol?
What's that got to do with anything?
Don't you think I'd want to know
that you...
take the same tablets...
that Dad died from?
-Jesus, Julie...
-When did you come to Saltsjövik?
I came straight to the party.
We saw each other.
-Who can back you up?
-Do you want to call Shirin?
-Where's your necklace?
-Can you calm down?
Julie, please...
It's me.
-What's going on?
-I need answers.
Yes, I take tramadol.
You knew I need painkillers.
And I lost the necklace weeks ago.
I've looked everywhere.
Listen, I...
I stayed away from Saltsjövik
far too long.
And I came here for Dad's birthday.
Mostly to see you again.
Is there anything else?
Do you really think I've got
something to do with Egil's death?
Please... tell me in that case.
I wouldn't be able to handle knowing
you suspect me.
Do you want to leave with me?
I just need to...
get away for awhile.
And think.
Figure out what to do now.
I can leave right now.
To mum:
Mistral is total chaos.
Aksel and Julie have big problems.
I think she's going to leave him.
BUT HE DEFINITELY TRUSTS ME NOW.
Great. You're doing so well.
The whole hotel will be yours soon!
Thanks mum!
I can't wait to see you again!
Are you sure about this?
What exit is it?
Wait, I just need to find my phone.
Are you kidding?
-You know nothing of this area?
-Yes!
You know that.
-Where's my phone?
-I don't know.
I just had it.
Can you see my phone?
No, it was here.
-Where?
-Here.
-I can't see it.
-I saw it down there. Here.
Here, down here.
What's that?!
Subtitles: Lily Ray
plint.com