The new CEO will be... Sebastian.
So you're living here?
Mm. I need to find something to do.
Do you need help here?
Okay, you can have a go.
-I just want to...
-Okay, you want to and you will.
It's always on your terms.
You know what? Leave, then.
Forget me and focus on yourself.
That's what you're good at.
I've always regretted
not going with you.
Egil left 50 per cent of the shares
to Mistral Holding to you.
Do you know how
Egil and your mum met?
She worked at the hotel one summer
when Egil and Werner shared it.
-Can you help me with something?
-What?
Can you check if a Jessika Adolfsson
has worked at the hotel?
Have we had a break in?
Petra was here last yesterday.
-She must have left it like this.
-That's not like her.
Where is she? We were meant to have
a meeting now.
-I'll take the meeting.
-I report to Petra.
Can I be honest with you, Svante?
Petra and I aren't exactly
best friends right now.
I think she's staying away
to punish me.
I'm sure she'll calm down soon,
but...
We'll just have to carry on
until she decides to show up.
-Are you okay with that?
-Absolutely.
-Would you like help tidying this?
-Yes, please.
I'll try calling her again.
THE BEACH HOTEL
The garage will be perfect.
-For what?
-A studio.
Oh, right. But, listen,
that can't sit outside.
No, but I can't exactly paint
in the living room, right?
Is this absolutely necessary
for you?
If we'd moved to Brittany,
I'd have had a whole studio.
This is my job, Werner.
I understand.
We can convert the garage to a
workspace.
There's always a tax break
to claim there.
-I knew you'd understand.
-Talk to Tone about it.
Okay. I'll find a new place
for your little sweetheart here.
-Okay?
-Okay, thank you.
I'll find you something
more fun to do.
Available dates at Town Hall.
Choose the date
you think works best.
These are soon.
That's no problem, right?
No, I just thought you'd want
a proper celebration.
No. Most important for me is that
we become us, that it happens.
-I'll take a look.
-Don't take too long.
Bye.
I need to look at this computer.
You'll have to move me, then.
Jesus, it was a joke!
Has Werner forbidden those too?
-No...
-Svante, you old fox.
Welcome, Börje. How was your trip?
-The Champagne's in the room.
-Thank you.
We can always trust you guys.
Say hi to Werner.
There will be more, trust me.
That's our most generous guest.
How often do they come here?
Börje's here
around three times a year.
His company varies.
Keep him in a good mood
and don't ask questions.
There, ladies first.
-Hi.
-Sit down.
-Stop it.
What? I'm a hotel director now.
Okay... right, so...
I've thought about
our collaboration.
I don't think we should stop
at the travel expo.
No? Were you thinking of something
in particular, or...?
Aksel is right, we have
very different kinds of guests.
But that doesn't mean our guests
wouldn't be interested
in your spa treatments.
Or that a guest from Mistral
wouldn't come here for a drink.
No, that's true. We could have
an offer at check-in.
-Exactly.
-Or even on our website.
Yeah, even better.
-Hi.
-Something to drink?
-No, thank you, I'm fine.
We have to provide something.
How does Julie like her coffee?
She has a tiny splash of coffee
which she drowns in hot milk,
and has the nerve to call it coffee.
Great! I'll get it.
Thank you.
What?
I don't know if this is
such a good idea.
But you just said the opposite.
But doing it together, you and I.
I should maybe do it
with Petra instead.
To start with, she's not even here.
No, where is she?
Off sick due to being offended,
as far as I know.
And secondly, you know it's just you
and I that I trust here.
There. We're out of milk,
unfortunately.
No problem.
Great!
Don't, you're embarrassing me!
-She said yes!
-Who?
Rebecca.
We're meeting here tomorrow.
-It's not the first time.
-It'll be different. I know.
-How long did she take to reply?
-A day or so.
Three.
And you answered in three seconds
again? Right?
-She knows where she has you.
-She does not.
She doesn't know
that you and I are together.
Now you've totally lost it.
When we come, act like my
girlfriend, and she'll get jealous.
-No!
-You're a great actress!
-Never.
-Please.
-Please?
-This is the worst idea ever.
So you'll do it?
You're the best! Thank you so much!
You haven't heard from her today.
Are you worried?
She wanted a break,
so I'm giving her one.
If you hear from her,
can you ask her to call me?
She said she'd help
with Rebecca's mother.
Okay, I know
this is important to you,
but Petra and I have enough
of our own shit to deal with.
I know. I'm sorry.
-I was thinking about Shirin...
-Yes?
she drew a line with you.
-Yes, you could say that.
-It was very childish.
-Yeah, we'll let it go.
-Did she overreact?
Yeah, truly.
A wall for stock, at least,
or I'll go mad.
-MEET TOMORROW AT THE HOTEL?
-YOURS OR MINE?
The landlady she said
we can repaint.
As long as we paint it back later.
Sure, we can return it to the
world's grossest house.
YOURS
-Hello?
-Yeah, sorry.
Did you have to mess
with Julie today?
-It was a joke.
-She didn't think it was funny.
Oh, poor her.
You're not usually like this.
Am I being difficult?
I did move here for you.
Are you going to use that
every time I say anything?
Do you have to work with Julie?
Of course I don't have to.
But I want to.
Why?
I thought you wanted to work
in the bar, not management.
Promise nothing's happened
between you?
I don't want to be humiliated.
You won't be humiliated.
I promise.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Now, let's see...
Let's get this done.
-Yes?
-That one.
-Hey.
-Hi.
I really appreciate this.
I can't wait any longer for Petra.
You could have asked me first.
You know that.
Shirin asked yesterday if anything
had happened between us.
I said no.
Have you told Aksel?
No. I haven't.
It didn't mean anything. Right?
No, it didn't.
Wait a moment.
-I hope breakfast was good.
-It was perfect.
Great.
My wife might call.
But if she does, I'm unreachable
right now. Okay?
-Your wife?
-Yes.
Of course. What's her name?
Elisabeth.
-Do you have the same last name?
-Yes, of course.
-What if it's important?
-Just do as I say.
Save your cash.
You never know when you'll need it.
This is The Beach Hotel's data.
Our cloud, you could say.
So weird, but when I got in this
morning, the cupboard was open.
What? Was anything missing?
No, not that I could see.
Okay. When would this Jessica
have worked here?
Around 2000, I think.
-Okay.
-There, yes.
What's going on here?
I didn't know you were
coming around.
No, I didn't think I needed
an invitation.
I've heard you two are planning
a collaboration between the hotels.
Yes, that's why Julie's here.
I can tell you that Egil would
never have agreed.
Nor you. Right?
Good. So we know
where we have one another.
And you understand it's unthinkable.
I haven't said that.
Excuse me, Sebastian.
This information is not
for your eyes.
Regardless what Sebastian has
promised you.
I'm just looking for a person who
has been employed by you.
-Right.
-Come on, Dad.
-Okay, what's their name.
-She worked here quite awhile ago.
Jessika Adolfsson.
No, no one of that name
has worked here.
You wouldn't consider
double checking?
No need. I know exactly who has
worked here since the beginning.
Right, Sebastian?
It's crazy, but it's true.
Please, I really need to know.
You've got the information we have.
Whoever says Jessika Adolfsson has
worked here is lying.
-Hey, what are you doing here?
-Werner said you need help.
What could that be?
I think he wanted to know
about tax breaks for the studio.
-Was that it?
-Yeah.
-That's fairly easy.
-Super! Then it won't take you long.
So you've got your own company?
Of course. My last yearly financial
statement is in the office.
But I'm a bit busy right now.
You'll find it easily.
We'll give her a chance
to explain. Right?
Sorry, I didn't know it was
a board meeting.
-It isn't.
-No?
Have you thought of more I can do
for the hotel?
Why did you lie? A Jessika Adolfsson
has never worked at The Beach Hotel.
-Why do you say that?
-I checked with Werner.
Did you check up on what I said?
Yes. Did you trick my dad too?
How did you make him believe
you were his daughter?
Come on, have you totally lost it?
Is there even a Jessika?
Of course.
Werner will have to check again.
It's not necessary.
He has no memory of her.
No memory? Didn't he check
an archive or something?
No, he remembers all his employees.
That actually sounds a bit weird.
-Sebastian confirmed it.
-What's he got to with it?
It's not me who has to explain.
So you'd rather believe an old man
who always hated your dad?
Werner didn't just inherit
half my hotel.
I have no reason to believe you.
Of course.
Because you're so superior.
You have no evidence!
Your dad lied for you,
and you're making me the villain!
-Why lie about your mum?
-I'm not!
She said she worked at the hotel,
now she's dead! What should I do?
Can we just calm down? Hmm?
Julie, I have to agree with Rebecca.
We can't trust what Werner
has said.
Okay... But we have to get
to the bottom of this.
Did you know he was married?
His wife's name is Elisabeth.
-That's private.
-That he's sleeping around?
Börje is a regular.
It's not our business.
So if his wife calls, we lie?
Call me old-fashioned,
but I want the guests trust us.
-I think it's weird too.
-You defended her.
No, I didn't.
You didn't have enough proof.
Werner said
she'd never worked for him.
Why would Werner,
of all people, lie?
Or Sebastian, for that matter.
Do you think Egil would have
put Rebecca in his will
if he wasn't convinced
she was his daughter?
There's still too much
she's not telling us.
Wonderful, right?
I baked it for you
to say thank you for the advice.
-Thanks.
Aksel has been thoughtful enough to
ask about my plans for the future.
Now I know.
I'm going to really dive into
my passion.
-Great.
-And that is...
Cooking, of course.
I've always dreamt
of a little cookbook.
How nice that you've started
giving career advice.
I think I'll go photograph it
outside.
I was just trying to help.
WELCOME. WAIT TO BE SEATED.
She'll be here any minute.
You have to practice!
Isn't it enough that I'm here?
Are you really going to wear
that jumper?
It's my favourite!
What will we do?
What's the plan?
No clue. It was your idea.
How do you usually act
with boyfriends?
-That's none of your business.
-You should act quite jealous.
Show that you're mine, you know.
Sit on my lap!
-Am I five years old?
-We have to at least touch.
Like this. Give me your hand.
Come on.
REBECCA: SOMETHING'S COME UP.
LET'S MEET ANOTHER DAY.
You know what? Forget it.
Good.
I did these two last spring.
Eh... What are they?
What do you think?
What do I think?
It wouldn't be hard to get
an exhibition together soon.
Have you contacted a gallery?
I've got a better idea.
The hotel.
-I don't understand.
-Have you ever had an exhibition?
No. There's already
art on the walls.
I don't know if I'd call it art.
I already know where this would
hang. It would be sold in no time.
Not to our guests, I don't think.
Why not? All big hotels collaborate
with artists.
-You don't like them.
-I do! If it's up to me, then sure.
Okay, then we'll do it.
But it's Sebastian
who has to make the decision.
So you'll have to ask him.
Okay. I'll do that.
Mm... Good.
Do you like married men?
The hotel will make sure your visit
isn't coloured by this.
We'll provide room service.
I did it in solidarity
with your poor wife.
Thanks, that's enough.
The whole stay is complimentary.
I'll never come back here.
I'll tell all my friends
not to set foot here again!
Good, we'll avoid even more
unfaithful swine.
It's time for you to go to lunch.
I'll handle this.
Börje, I'm truly sorry.
I like it. Beautiful composition.
It isn't of anything. The guests
will be confused and Vendela upset.
I'm sure she's had critique before.
Of course.
In galleries with their audiences.
Our guests want to swim
and have fun.
This will make them
scratch their heads.
-Okay, well...
-No, do as I say.
I don't want Vendela to be hurt.
-You need to give me something too.
-Sure. What?
Collaboration with Mistral.
-Unthinkable.
-You can choose.
Vendela's paintings in the lobby
or let me explore something
that could help the hotel.
Don't you see you're being used?
What will it be?
Say no to Vendela,
but not too harshly.
Hey.
Why didn't you reply to me?
Something came up for me too.
Are you mad?
Okay, sorry. But it was important.
Okay, if you say so.
Come for a swim tomorrow after work?
-Okay.
-Good.
See you then.
-There you go.
-Thank you.
Werner said I should contact you.
I couldn't wait.
So what do you think
of my suggestion.
I'm sorry, Vendela, but...
I have to say no, unfortunately.
Why?
I just don't think it would be
a good look.
The founder's wife-to-be exhibiting
at the hotel.
Isn't the idea
that it's a family hotel?
I won't force guests
to buy anything.
Aren't you as tired as I am of
the coastal landscapes in the lobby?
You know what?
Come with me to the studio.
I've already seen it.
When?
With Werner?
Okay, I really like your art.
I mean it.
But I don't think
the hotel is really ready.
Werner isn't ready, you mean?
I don't think we're helping anyone
by letting him decide everything.
You're probably right.
It's nice you dropped by,
but I'm a bit busy.
I understand. See you.
There you go. Hope it's delicious.
I hope so too.
It's good. You know your stuff.
Yeah, maybe.
I guess you're good at more
than just mixing drinks.
Excuse me.
-Do you need help?
-Yes.
But you seem pretty busy over there.
-No.
-You sure? Seems to be going well.
It's cool.
-How kind.
-No problem.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What do you think of Julie?
Pretty annoying.
Thank you. I really needed that.
-Take it easy.
-I'm fine!
-I've got it!
-Okay...
-See you tomorrow.
-Hey, wait a minute.
-I hope you're joking.
-What do you mean?
You're going to fire me
over that idiot.
No, of course not.
-Is he gone?
-No, he got an extra night.
With his wife or lover?
-Alone.
-Good.
That suits him.
Why did you ring her?
Because I know someone like him
will never change.
So it's better to know now instead
of being oblivious to the signs.
I wish that feeling on no one.
So, you have...
I'm so sorry, Lojsan.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Hi, you've reached Petra.
Leave a message after the tone
and I'll ring back as soon as I can.
Hey. My wife...
partner has disappeared.
Two days.
We're not really living together
right at the moment.
But apparently she hasn't been at
work either and isn't picking up.
Can't you do something right now?
Okay, I understand. Thanks anyway.
It feels a bit unusual to meet
outside the office.
But now it's Sebastian's domain.
How do you think it's going for him?
He's got more left to learn
than I thought.
It's important he understands
what the hotel is.
What it represents.
Just like you do.
That's why I want him
to turn to you.
So you can help him into the role.
You want me to train him?
No one can do it better than you.
Should I do it before or after
Vendela's bookkeeping?
I haven't asked you to
do her bookkeeping.
I meant for you to keep an eye on
tax offsets and that kind of thing.
Werner, I have to ask you something.
Yes?
Was I ever considered as CEO?
You would have been a wonderful CEO.
I'm not so sure
Sebastian would listen to me.
What are you thinking?
Large withdrawals
have been made this week.
I don't know, Sebastian might have
just made a mistake.
Sebastian doesn't have access
to this account.
Only Petra does.
Is Julie on her way?
She's got a bit too much to do right
now so you'll have to settle for me.
How much has Julie told you
about our plans?
What's this?
You'd think he might be happy to
just talk about The Beach Hotel.
"We've always catered to
the needs of tourists,
unlike other organisations
in the area,
who desperately try to mimic..."
This is the old CEO talking,
not the new one.
But you understand we can't work
with a competitor
who talks about us like that.
We'll look like idiots.
Has Julie seen this?
What do you think?
-Hey!
-Shall we go?
Yeah. But would you be able to
help me with something first?
-Of course.
-I feel so clumsy,
but I left something at the hotel.
I quit in a bit of a hurry.
And you don't want to ask Svante?
Exactly.
-Of course I'll help you.
-You're the best.
That was fine, wasn't it?
Why didn't you say anything?
About the interview?
It was so long ago.
It only comes out once a year.
You didn't think to add
a word or two about Egil's death?
No, I didn't.
Do you think it's appropriate
for your fiance to work in the bar?
It's her choice.
I support her in it.
Yes, but you're CEO.
It's not really fitting.
-It's hard to see myself as CEO.
-What do you mean?
Are you ever going to let me do
this job the way I want?
Of course, as long as you have
the hotel's best at heart.
Reject Vendela's paintings,
that was for the hotel?
Yes, and for her.
I think this was a mistake.
You're trying to get out of this.
You accepted the job, now do it.
I'd love to.
But in my own way, or not at all.
This isn't working.
I don't know what to do.
He works against me in everything.
Then quit, if it doesn't feel right.
-You think so?
-Yes, I think so.
I could move back to Stockholm
tomorrow, you know that.
What are you going to do in here?
You didn't see me, I wasn't here,
no harm done.
-Someone could come.
-Then keep watch.
Go!
-Why haven't you gone home?
-I... forgot something.
-What are you doing?
-I just... They just fell.
Fell?
EMPLOYMENT CONTRACT
SALTSJÖVIKS HOTEL JESSIKA ADOLFSSON
-Are you almost done?
-Quiet!
-Thank you so much.
-Are you sure they're ok like that?
No problem. I'll take them
straight to the hotel.
I read the article.
It was... interesting.
-This is great.
-It is! Just say if you want more.
-I definitely will.
-Super.
Two paintings sold on one day.
I think that's worth celebrating.
To Aksel?
Sebastian said no.
But then I thought... Mistral.
They're probably a bit more open.
-They're going to hang in the lobby.
-Okay.
Darling, can't you laugh at this?
I think we should open
some bubbly,
and look at dates at Town Hall.
I've got a bit of a headache
so I think I'll have a rest.
I'm really sorry.
I had no idea about this.
Who even reads this?
Rubbish magazine.
When did you know you wanted
to take over the hotel?
I've always known,
since I was little.
And how does it feel now?
It wasn't meant to be like this.
I thought Dad would be here
to help me.
I usually have no idea
what I'm doing.
It really doesn't seem like it.
Every day I have moments when
I'm angry at him for being gone.
Let go of it all.
My dad won't let go.
He doesn't trust me.
And I definitely can't trust him.
When will I learn to stop
throwing myself into things?
That's what I love about you.
Dad's angry, Petra's angry.
Shirin doesn't like it here.
Maybe I should leave
before everything goes to hell.
Is there anyone who wants me here?
You know there is.
Are you talking about Mum?
If I stayed for you...?
-We weren't meant to be here again.
-But we are. All the time.
Tell me why you want me to stay.
I can't.
-It will ruin everything.
-Let it, then.
-No.
-Julie...
Subtitles: Lily Ray
plint.com