It's been days. Petra's still gone.
She wouldn't just disappear.
Do you take Werner Gyllenmark
to be your lawfully wedded husband?
I do.
-Well done.
-Why did you meet with Sebastian,
without checking with me first?
Does everything have to be
about Sebastian?
Stop it.
-Hey, Lojsan.
-What are you doing here?
-Where are we going?
-Home!
I can't just leave everything,
you know that!
You promised me!
-Don't let him be mean.
-He's not mean.
He might just not be as in love
with me as I am with him.
If really want something,
you need to go for it, now.
It's Julie's birthday and I thought
I'd throw her a bit of a party.
I'd really like you to come.
Julie Elisabeth Grip, will you do me
the honour of marrying me?
What's that?
Where is she?
We said ten o'clock.
I'll call and check with her.
Do that.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm not blind,
I can see something's wrong.
Are you having second thoughts?
Did you consider my feelings when
you proposed in front of everyone?
Right... So you don't want to get
married anymore, or what?
-That's not it.
-No?
What else could I say
while everyone was staring at me?
Well, I didn't mean for you
to feel like this, at any rate.
I just wanted to share
with everyone.
I know.
I'm just saying I'd rather have been
part of the decision.
It was wrong of me. Okay?
But you and I want to be together,
and...
that's all that matters, right?
I'll call her.
-Yes, hello?
-Hi, Rebecca.
Why aren't you
at the board meeting?
Oh, sorry. I just thought
you'd want to cancel it.
Why?
Because of Petra.
What do you mean?
They found her.
I'm sorry, Julie. But she's dead.
What is it?
THE BEACH HOTEL
It's Petra.
No...
I'll be back in a moment.
My little darling.
Well...
We've lost someone who meant a lot
to this hotel.
As you all do.
I see the Beach Hotel
a bit like a family.
We work together,
we laugh together...
Sometimes, we cry together.
Because we care about one another.
All of us.
How are you?
I don't know...
It's hard to take in.
I'm so sorry.
The police are here.
Do you think you can talk to her?
Hey...
-Stop. Leave me alone.
-Do you want something?
-No.
-You didn't eat breakfast.
-I don't want breakfast.
-What can I do then?
You can leave me alone.
Ding-dong.
Hey, what's your name again?
Svante, Front Desk Manager.
It's on your badge. Smart.
Could you arrange a towel for me?
The hotel towels are so small.
I'll send someone.
Maybe you could send Lojsan.
Maybe you can ask her yourself.
Hey!
I heard. How awful.
How's Lukas?
-He's okay, I think.
-Are you sure?
He could be in shock. It's not
always obvious from the outside.
-Right?
-I don't know anything about it.
What he needs now is comfort
and peace around him, okay?
Are you giving me parenting advice?
No, it's not that.
I just want to see him.
Then do it,
that's why you're here, right?
He gives me excuses all the time.
This Lilja, do you know her?
Is she his girlfriend?
She's a friend.
I can't force him.
No...
I think the best way would be
to invite me over.
Think about it.
So, what happens now?
We wait for the autopsy.
Do you have any idea
where she might have been?
Where she stayed the night?
What do you think you'll find?
She might have left something there,
a message, perhaps.
Petra wasn't suicidal.
Yes, she was angry
and disappointed...
in me and her family,
but she'd never have done that.
Have you found her phone? She might
have messaged other people.
Um... I'll contact you
as soon as I hear anything.
She's not even listening to me.
Try to trust she's doing her job.
Just like with Egil?
Because it's the same thing here.
Something doesn't add up.
Try not to think that way.
But why not?
Don't you believe me either?
What do you think
might have happened.
Someone might have...
I can't bear even thinking about it.
I think you should try
to get some sleep.
You haven't stopped
since she disappeared.
I can't.
It would feel like giving up.
Like I didn't care anymore.
That's not true.
And you know it.
Please, Marianne,
do you have to do that now?
I have to do something
or I'll lose my mind.
I understand, but you have to eat.
But not with you two.
I thought it might be good for you
so you don't have to be alone.
It's just as well I get used to it.
I think Werner would appreciate it.
Has he said that?
He's not talking to me much
right now.
That's how Werner is.
He never says anything
unless it's criticism.
I thought you two
might be able to talk.
He pushed Petra so hard.
Nothing she did was...
enough in his eyes.
Never good enough.
Don't you think
you need one another now?
Can't you come with me
to our place now?
You look after Werner,
I'll look after myself.
I'm sorry, I'm just trying to help.
Go home to your studio, sweetheart.
I don't think you're cut out
for real life.
Sebastian?
Where are you going?
Work, I guess.
How... How are you?
I don't know.
I can't believe she's gone.
I'm sorry, I need to go to work,
but can we talk later?
I guess I should congratulate you.
On what?
Oh, thanks.
Were you surprised?
A bit.
I thought you hated that.
Popping the question
in front of everyone like that.
You hate that.
You don't know me
as well as you think.
Okay. I know now
why Aksel invited me anyway.
I thought you wanted to come.
He wanted me to witness it,
can't you see that?
So he only proposed to me
to get at you?
He just wants to fuck with me!
Did my saying yes have something to
do with you as well?
Not everything is about you
all the time!
Wait, Sebastian!
Room 305, first room to the right
after you get out of the lift.
Okay, thanks a lot.
What is it?
Look what Torbjörn has written here.
"Petra, you were a great person
who touched people's hearts."
Well, wasn't she?
He couldn't know that.
No, Torbjörn can be
quite spontaneous.
Yes, you can tell.
Is that a bad thing? That he doesn't
take himself too seriously?
It didn't work out so well.
I just mean it wasn't so hard
to fall for him.
He's confident,
he jokes with people,
he's interested in sports and stuff,
not just his job.
Then we saw it was... her.
Jesus, how scary.
I've never seen
a dead person before.
Have you?
No, I hope I don't have to.
I have to go work.
Okay. Tell me if you need to talk.
I promise.
Poor thing. That can't be easy.
What?
Have I spilt something on myself?
No.
Okay...
Can you really guarantee that?
I need to know
it won't look manipulated.
You don't need to worry about that,
I'll deal with the consequences.
If you can tell it's him
in the images,
you'll be paid
when I see the material.
No, I'll be in touch.
Yes, bye.
-How much did you hear?
-No idea.
Don't play dumb.
If I said anything,
no one would believe me anyway.
Especially not Julie.
I'd be very grateful.
So grateful you'd help me?
-With...?
-Julie.
Get her to like me a bit more.
She's still suspicious, I can tell.
-Sure.
-Thanks.
-Can I trust you then?
-What choice do I have?
I'm sure you'll get inspired
down in France, don't you think?
I've actually sold several
paintings lately.
Wouldn't it be nice to get away
for a bit?
From this house?
It's like a tomb here.
I know it's a tragedy, boo hoo,
I know that.
But, Vendela,
it really has nothing to do with us.
Nothing I do helps anyway.
No, exactly.
He'll pick himself up, you'll see.
Out of his grieving.
Hey, a few weeks on the Riviera.
That would be so good for you,
don't you think?
Yeah, but I can't
just leave him now.
Why drag it out?
-Name?
-Fredrika Karlsson.
-Fredrika Karlsson, welcome!
-Thank you!
Hey! Welcome, everyone.
You'll be in Conference Room Two,
it's through the doors to the left.
-Thank you.
-No need to thank me.
Mi casa es su casa!
If you get sick of talking about
work with each other,
there's a TV in the conference room
and the match is on channel 47.
You've got to have some fun too,
right?
But not too much fun,
or you'll get a hangover!
Welcome!
What are you doing?
What?
Can't I be a bit spontaneous
and fun?
"Mi casa es su casa"?
Yes, of course.
Hi, there!
Hello, there!
Vendela says
you've been here all day.
We have to start talking
about the funeral.
With Mum and Gabrielle.
Do you think I pushed her too hard?
-We don't have to talk about it now.
-Why not?
If you think so,
I'd like you to say.
-No.
-What do you mean, "No"?
No, you think so, or no, you don't
want to talk and tell me the truth?
The money Petra took,
the bank has asked me several times,
and I have to tell them
what happened.
Maybe we should tell the police.
-That's not an option.
-We have to do something.
-It won't look good if it comes out.
-I won't drag Petra through the mud!
Do you understand?
-There you go.
-Thank you.
There you go!
When's Shirin's break?
She's working all evening.
-Anything in particular?
-No, I want to tell her something.
Why don't you just give up?
I get it, she's beautiful and smart,
funny, wonderful, but...
there will never be anything
between you.
She's nice to you
because that's who she is.
But she's with your boss.
I'm not interested in Shirin.
Are you trying to convince me
you're not in love with her?
Okay, I'll tell her another day.
Have you had an okay night?
As good as it could be.
I know this is a bit of
an uncomfortable question, but...
How were yours and Petra's finances?
We got by.
We're saving again.
Or, we were, I mean.
Do you have joint accounts
and all that?
I look after most of it, why?
A large withdrawal was made
from the hotel.
Right before Petra disappeared.
Are you sure it was her?
She told me she was gambling again.
I'm sorry.
We need to find out
what happened, right?
Okay, here are last year's books,
balance sheet.
-And revPAR month for month...
-Sorry, revPAR?
Average revenue per room,
you could say.
-Okay.
-Try to read it by tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Running a hotel involves a bit more
than smiling at guests.
-Right. No problem.
-Good.
-There.
-Thanks.
Just call if you have any questions.
I really want this to work.
Me too.
Aksel says hi.
Right, well... tell him hi back.
Breakfast was really good.
Nothing beats your scrambled eggs.
So, what can I do in Saltsjövik
now I just have one afternoon left?
Okay.
-Okay?
-You can come for dinner.
Lovely. I can cook.
Steak, just how you like it.
Do you have a barbecue?
No, and you'll come at seven
and leave at nine.
Okay, can I bring a bottle of wine?
No, because we won't drink it.
A real family dinner.
Hey, don't call it that.
I'm grateful.
Truly.
I thought you'd stopped
with that nonsense.
Never.
Check out the steam boat harbour,
it's worth seeing.
Okay. I'll do that.
See you.
Ah, there you are.
Nice to see you up.
So sweet.
-Yeah.
-Was it taken here?
No, down by the dock.
Petra was ten.
Whenever I made the hotel's order at
the fishmonger, Petra came with me.
And when we were done,
she'd nag me until I bought two...
prawn sandwiches and we sat
by the dock and...
It was our thing.
Hey, bartender?
Can't you be sweet
and pour me a glass of wine?
-No.
-Um, yes.
What?
I'm not going to let you get drunk
now before an evening shift!
I'm kidding.
I'm going to go eat. See you later.
Yes.
Will that work out?
Shirin's temporary,
will she get to stay?
She's fantastic. She works hard,
she's lovely with the guests...
Great.
-Considering who she's with.
-Sebastian...
Have you seen how he pines
after Julie Grip?
Huh? It's ridiculous.
I almost caught them
in the office once.
Are you sure about that?
-Shirin deserves something better.
-Oh, like what?
Remember what you promised me
you'd never become?
Probably a lot of things.
You said you'd never be one of those
pathetic men hitting on young girls.
-You've misunderstood.
-Have I?
Yes, and I don't need your advice.
Take care of your own
sorry situation instead.
I don't understand.
Svante, do you know why
you'll never get Lojsan?
Because you're a coward.
Who's never dared to risk
a single thing your whole life.
I'll skip the coffee today.
I went by the hotel.
I couldn't face it today.
I was a jerk to you yesterday.
I don't know how
I could say those things. I...
-I'm sorry.
-You've just lost your sister.
It's no excuse.
I hate fighting with you.
If you want to be with Aksel,
I have to accept it.
Why did you come?
This, between us...
We can't keep this up.
We're hurting each other,
and other people.
I know.
So this is the hole you hang out in,
these days?
I like it.
I'm usually tired after work so
I like taking it easy here.
Right, but is cleaning really a job?
I'm kidding.
Mum looks good.
Maybe...
Do you know if she's met someone?
It's fine, you can tell me.
I don't know.
It's a shame for her to live alone
in that house.
-It can't be easy.
-Are you and Mum...?
We'll see. I'm working on it.
That's what you want too, I guess?
To be a family again?
I was thinking about this dinner...
It might not be much fun for her.
It's fine with me if you skip it.
Mum and I have some important stuff
to talk about.
You'd rather hang out with your...
friend, right?
What's her name?
-Lilja.
-Lilja...
Cute.
What are we doing now?
I don't know.
Do you think this was wrong?
No.
I'm just so...
scared to hurt anyone.
Me too.
But I don't regret this.
-I have to go.
-Why?
What if Shirin turns up?
She's working late.
I know, but it feels...
I know, but...
You're here now
and I don't want to let you go.
I'll...
-I'll call you.
-Okay...
Julie?
Are you sure everything's fine?
Yeah.
My God, what a boring evening.
Yeah, it's really dead here.
It hasn't been this dead for ages.
You have to cheer me up.
Say something funny.
Don't you know any jokes?
No...
But there's something
I'd like to say.
Okay, go.
I'm in love with you.
Okay...
That was actually quite good.
It wasn't a joke.
What are you doing?
-I had to tell you...
-Stop talking now!
Shirin... haven't you noticed?
No, go to hell!
My dad is so embarrassing.
I bet your parents are really cool.
Not really.
-Do they live in Saltsjövik?
-Yep.
We don't have much contact.
It's better that way.
Well, I should go home now.
I'm sure they're done eating.
You can sleep here if you like.
We can watch a movie.
Let me.
That was delicious.
As usual.
I don't know why Lukas didn't come.
You're doing a great job with him.
But I think he needs his father.
Someone to set boundaries.
He misses me.
He misses being a family.
-He said so.
-Did he?
I know I made a mistake, but...
Forgetting the washing,
that's a mistake.
Sleeping with my best friend,
that's something else.
I really want to show you I'm sorry.
But it's a bit hard
now that we live so far apart.
I'm not moving back to Jönköping,
you can forget that.
No, I see that you like it here.
I'd love to stay a few more days.
But it's so expensive at the hotel.
Can't you give me one more chance?
For Lukas' sake.
Please.
Two nights. On the sofa.
I'll take it.
CAUSE OF DEATH: EGIL GRIP
TRAMADOL OVERDOSE
Aren't you coming to bed soon?
I'll be right there.
You can't sit up all night.
What are you even working on?
Nothing.
I just wanted to check something.
Okay.
I CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT YOU.
WHEN CAN I SEE YOU?
Now she'll be murdered.
Don't go down there.
Of course she'll go down there.
Ha! See? She didn't die.
-Shit, did you see that?
-Yes.
Tell me when it's over!
Now.
Damn you!
-Should I do that to you?
-No!
No, Lukas! It's not funny!
We should probably go to sleep now.
Sebastian was here.
He said Petra had taken money
from the hotel.
What?
Do you think it's true?
I don't know.
But it wouldn't surprise me.
No... it wouldn't be the first time.
How could she disappear
with so many questions?
Do you think she...?
I don't know anymore.
Is that..?
They're Petra's things.
She had them when they found her.
Don't you want to open it?
I don't know if I can.
We'll do it together.
God... Okay.
That's not hers.
No.
It's Sebastian's.
What did you want?
I went down to the fishmonger.
I know this is your memory of Petra.
I didn't get to know her that well,
but...
I thought we could
sit here together.
Oh, Vendela.
It's horrible you never got to know
one another.
Yes, though I did a little.
I think you two were alike.
You think she was like me?
A bit sharp...
with a big heart.
You didn't think you'd be here
with an old crying man
when you married me.
An old crying man whom I love.
WHY DON'T YOU REPLY?
HAS SOMETHING HAPPENED?
WHEN CAN I SEE YOU TODAY?
WHENEVER!
-Yes?
-Can you come to Mistral right away?
-You have to see something.
-Well, I...
-I...
-It's important.
Okay, I'm on my way.
I know you're angry.
So just stay away.
Listen, nothing needs to change,
I won't...
Are you going to quit
because of this?
Should I quit every time
a colleague tries to pick me up?
I wouldn't be able to keep a job.
That's not what I did.
No, right. You're in love with me.
Why did you think
I even needed to know?
Are you going to tell Sebastian?
Have you lost it? He'd go crazy!
-You don't know him.
-It's just that I...
Yeah, I know you've seen him
grow up here and all that.
But you know nothing
about he and I, okay?
Shirin, I'd do anything for you.
You shouldn't settle for less.
-What is it?
-You have to see this.
It's from a security camera.
-When did you get these?
-From Marianne.
But they didn't seem to work
for some reason.
So I asked the security company
to email them directly to me.
Right, okay.
-That could be anyone.
-Don't you recognise the jacket?
It's the same one he had on
at Werner's party.
I can zoom in a bit.
Here, look at the time.
He said he came straight
from the train to the party?
How could he have been here then?
And why would lie
about not having been here?
Look, there.
See? It's him.
He lied to you, Julie.
Subtitles: Lily Ray
plint.com