The person who
will be taking over is Sebastian.
-I know you're making a mistake.
-I'll accept. We'll work together.
After six months
I go back home and you take over.
You're prepared to stay
in Saltsjövik for six months. Why?
I don't know what you're up to.
Just don't ruin his life again.
Had you not
dragged him out that night,
he would not have been hit by a car.
How about dinner?
Like a work thing, nothing else?
Julie, hi.
-You're Rebecca?
-Yeah.
-Who was that?
-I hardly know her.
-Egil made changes to his will.
-Here's a letter.
I understand
if you never forgive me.
But I have another daughter,
born outside my marriage.
I have decided to leave
half of Hotel Mistral to my
other daughter, Rebecca Adolfsson.
Hello.
Great that you're able to come.
Have a seat.
We now have access to
the details of Egil's will.
That means you know now?
Why didn't you say anything?
You and Dad knew all along.
There's quite a lot to take in,
for everyone.
But maybe we should
focus on the practicalities?
-In his will...
-Sorry, I can't do this.
-Julie...
-Not just now.
Julie, wait.
Egil stated in his will
that he wanted you to
have 50% of the shares in Mistral.
You own half of the hotel.
Are you joking?
No.
I think I'd better
go and find Julie.
THE BEACH HOTEL
Where are my ties, darling?
You never wear a tie.
Please, just help me look.
-Have you seen my necklace?
-No.
How many
client meetings have you had?
You never wear a tie.
I think
people would appreciate it here.
-Are you excited?
-I am.
Don't exhaust yourself.
You're only here for six months.
That doesn't mean
I'll just be twiddling my thumbs.
Here you go.
If we try,
we should get most of it unpacked.
I want things to be bearable
until we move back.
Okay, but I think I'll be back late.
Right. I love you.
-Nothing from the mini bar?
-No, nothing.
-Thank you very much then.
-Thank you.
I don't understand why people can't
put things back where they belong.
There we go.
-Hello.
-Hi.
How are you doing?
Oh, I'm fine. This thing with
having children happened a bit fast.
-Do you want to talk about it?
-No, thanks.
Do you know what? I feel fine.
It's probably all for the best.
You look all flushed.
Has something happened?
No.
Like what?
I'll see you soon.
I'll take some pictures.
The light is good.
Hang on.
Tone has gone through
the purchase agreement.
Okay. Were there any problems?
No, she didn't spot anything,
but I did.
You might know
what I'm talking about.
No idea.
Will you give me a clue?
-The deposit.
-What about it?
It was
half a million more than you said.
Well, I suppose I accidentally
gave you the wrong figure.
What are you trying to say?
Hey? Do you think
I'm trying to trick you?
No. But I don't like
surprises in business.
Sure, but I'm not an expert.
-We're talking half a million.
-Okay.
I hear what you're saying.
As you can see
there's minimal wear and tear.
No need to redecorate for years.
Not sure about curtains...
-And the throws.
-Werner always loved those.
I believe
he got a good deal on them.
I'd like to see something
a bit more personal.
Imagine giving each room
its own character.
All different?
That sounds a bit messy to me.
Not at all. Look at The Mistral.
We can't copy our competitor.
Just for some inspiration.
What will Werner say about this?
You and Werner
have created this place.
I don't want to change things
for the sake of it.
I just feel it needs a fresh look.
Right. I will make some suggestions.
Thank you.
You're a rock.
She's never said a word
in the time she's lived here.
-It's insane.
-Sure.
Hey...
Have you spoken to Petra?
No, not since I left.
She has been in touch,
but I don't know what to say to her.
If you're feeling a bit unsure,
maybe you should wait.
You don't think I'm being nasty?
I'm your friend.
I'm on your side. You know that.
You can stay with me
for as long as you like.
Thanks.
Right, back to work.
-See you this evening.
-Yeah.
Removals boxes...
-So you live here now?
-I do.
But I need to find something to do.
I'll go mental rattling around the
house like some little housewife.
Do you need help?
Have you got any experience?
Sure. Two seasons at a ski resort.
-Working the bar?
-No, but drinking there.
Of course. Okay then...
What's in a Manhattan?
A Manhattan... Let's see.
Two parts whisky, one part vermouth,
a little Angostura.
Stir, strain and a cherry on top.
Ask me another one.
Okay. Espresso martini.
Espresso martini, okay.
One part vodka,
one part coffee liqueur,
two parts espresso.
Shake everything
until cold and frothy,
sprinkle some
dark chocolate over - done.
Well... Okay, then.
You can try a shift
and see how you get on.
So what are we doing here?
I think we ought to cooperate.
Our hotels
have different clienteles.
I don't see us suddenly
turning into a big happy family.
I just think we can work smarter.
How?
The tourism fair
in Stockholm is coming up
and I suggest we go together
in order to market Saltsjövik.
Double exposure at half the cost.
-Why not think about it?
-I'll give you an answer now.
No.
This is a waste of time.
We'll think about it.
Julie, hold on.
Would you mind
asking Gabrielle to call me?
She'll be in touch when she's ready.
-Has she said anything?
-No.
It was your idea.
Everyone's not always against you.
Gabrielle isn't well.
Don't you see that?
Just tell her... that I miss her.
I really believe in
doing the fair together.
Let's meet and discuss some figures.
Enjoy your coffee.
It's on the house.
Just don't tell anyone. I'm going
out with the CEO and do what I like.
Martin needed help in the bar
and I needed a job.
I could have got you a job
in the marketing department.
Do you find it embarrassing
that I work in the bar?
No, of course not.
Enjoy your coffee.
Hey. Hey...
Have you seen Sebastian?
I'm sure he's around somewhere
doing something revolutionary.
What did you want to talk about?
I'd rather speak to him first.
Don't worry.
We'll be as close as you and Dad.
So Sebastian has a lot of ideas?
Not much will come of them,
but new curtains will be nice.
I understand you're
disappointed you weren't chosen.
Yes, I expect you feel the same.
It's hard to understand
his way of thinking.
It'll be fine.
Sebastian won't stay for long.
Are you sure?
Six months.
After that I'll be taking over.
Sebastian and I agreed that.
In total we save 50,000 each.
And we only
have to do half the work.
Well, that sounds great.
Are you alright? Are you in pain?
-We can carry on another day.
-No, I'm fine.
-It feels like it's my fault.
-What?
-The fact that you're in pain.
-No, stop it.
It's nobody's fault.
It was an accident.
-Well, you know...
-Julie!
Don't.
I've never blamed you.
Where did you get that idea?
Has Mum said something?
-I'll talk to her.
-No, please don't.
Let's just forget about it.
I saw Petra yesterday.
Maybe you should talk to her.
No.
Do you have to do that right now?
Should I leave it
to become totally overgrown?
Maybe you could wait
until we've gone to work?
And how long
will she be staying here?
I'll be going now.
Gabrielle is my friend.
She'll be staying in my part
of the house as long as she likes.
Shouldn't she be back with Petra?
She's distraught.
I'll finish my breakfast inside
and leave you in peace.
Are you meeting that daughter today?
Yes, we have a board meeting.
I will never,
never see her as part of our family.
What family?
There's some omelette
on the cooker for you.
I'm in a rush.
See you later.
-Vendela said I'd find you here.
-Are you on your way to the hotel?
Are you missing it already?
What's on your mind?
Sebastian wants
to do things his way.
But I'm worried that
he won't come to me
even regarding things that
I might be able to resolve.
I don't want it to sound like
I want you to spy on him...
-I don't want any trouble.
-Sure.
If ever there is trouble,
I'll deal with it.
Are you still happy
not to have chosen Petra?
The best role for Petra
is as hotel manager.
I think she knows that deep down.
-What about the agreement?
-What agreement?
Sebastian will be CEO for a year and
then Petra will take over, right?
You didn't know?
Egil left half of the shares
in Mistral Holdings to you.
That incorporates Mistral Spa Hotel
and Mistral Foods and Beverages.
Is this the value of the entire
company or is it my part of it?
Right, let's see. That's your share.
I understand if
this feels overwhelming.
But I'm prepared to buy you out,
here and now, if you like.
No.
Why not?
Isn't this a bit of
a headache for you?
Do you know anything about
how to run a hotel?
No, maybe not, but I want to learn.
Have you always known
that Egil was your dad?
-I've only known for a few years.
-You didn't grow up around here?
I really wanted to tell you,
but I didn't know how to.
Instead you snuck around
here anonymously.
And where's your mum?
Julie, calm down.
We don't need to cross-examine her.
Let's just focus on the business.
Yesterday we met with Petra
and Sebastian from The Beach Hotel.
Why is it all my fault?
Egil knew all along,
but never got in touch with me.
And you never got in touch with him?
-You never emailed him?
-No...
Here are the log in details
for the business department.
I have set up
a mail account for you.
Before you log in we need to check
your phone and computer for viruses.
That's standard security procedure.
You want to go through
my phone and my computer?
Julie...
Here you go.
Check as much as you like.
Do you need my bank log in
and the keys for my flat as well?
-That's the way to the beach.
-And that's where the beach café is?
-Exactly.
-Thank you very much.
What are you up today?
-I can't.
-Have you got plans?
What happened the other night
was incredible.
Sure.
But we can't let it happen again.
I hope you understand.
Well, if you don't want to...
The Beach Hotel. Lojsan speaking.
Lovely. I'll see
if we have any rooms free.
Is it that one?
Hi, Dad.
Sorry, did we arrange a meeting?
Nope.
We are more booked up next week.
Do you like it here, Sebastian?
Yes, all good.
I think it's all going fine.
And you're looking forward to
the next six months?
-Did you tell him?
-Bloody Tone.
She assumed you'd told me.
This is actually a good solution.
And Svante told me you'll be giving
all the rooms individual makeovers.
I can imagine he wasn't
over the moon about it,
but I can explain my reasoning.
If this isn't finished in six
months, will you carry on, Petra?
Oh, come on. What the hell?
Not all of your ideas
are full of magic.
Like I don't believe in
cooperating with Mistral.
-Cooperating how?
-Why always compete?
-So my leadership was foolish?
-No, I'm not saying that.
But if I'm going to do this
it has to be done my way.
So your way is to hand over
everything after six months?
Do you consider that responsible?
You'd better forget
this little plan.
Sebastian is the CEO. End of.
-Here you go. One Sunshine.
-Thank you.
You're a natural.
-Sure.
-No, I mean it.
I'm so happy to have you here.
I hope you feel the same.
Well, I needed something to do.
So what did Sebastian say
about you working here?
Nothing.
Martin, you need
some fresh ideas here.
-Get people to come.
-Really?
This place is so nineties.
Just look around.
-Isn't that back in fashion?
-Was it ever in fashion?
I'm sorry this place doesn't meet
your Stockholm standards.
But Svante and I
built this up from scratch.
Thank you.
So have you found anything?
No, nothing on Rebecca's computer
matches the extortion mails.
Maybe she wasn't behind it.
Or she used another computer.
How the hell could he do this?
First he's unfaithful
and has another child
and then he doesn't mention it.
I understand he didn't want to
admit it at the time, but later?
Years went by.
Maybe he felt ashamed.
And who did he meet?
I'm sure he wanted to tell you.
We don't know the whole story.
No, you're right.
He probably thought
it was for the best.
He always did what was best for you,
you know that.
That's not how it feels.
Maybe this is what Egil wanted.
For you two to work together
and get to know each other.
At the end of the day
she owns half of the hotel.
It will make my job easier
and yours.
-Hey?
-Okay, I'll think about it.
Good.
I'll cook this evening, okay?
Thank you.
Carbonara?
What do we do now?
I don't know.
You can't pay any attention to
what Dad says.
You and I have an agreement.
You always do exactly
what Dad tells you to.
You can't do this to me, Sebastian.
Why didn't you defend my ideas?
You come in here
and think you can run a hotel.
You get on everybody's nerves.
Did you think
I'd let you run everything?
-Why not?
-But the hotel is in trouble.
I had a solution to the problems.
Dad just didn't want to listen
and you let me down.
It's always somebody else's fault.
Can you hear yourself?
And you sound like Julie.
You talk down to people. Shirin
ought to know the real reason...
-You have no idea.
-You play hotel director.
You force your girlfriend
to move here only to get Julie back.
-You're pathetic.
-And what about your gambling habit?
-Dad's right. You can't run a hotel.
-Fuck off.
What's this?
Has the money arrived?
I don't understand.
That is the deposit for the house.
The half million
you got so upset about.
What did you think? That you'd
have to pay for all of it?
We can sign the contract tomorrow.
There's nothing stopping us.
No, I agree.
Good.
Hello?
What's the matter?
You've hardly said a word all night.
-Is it Rebecca?
-No.
Or maybe... I don't know.
It will be alright.
Would you mind asking Marianne about
the surveillance camera Dad put up?
I'd like to look at the footage.
She'd say no if I asked.
Are we back there again?
What do you think
you're going to find?
Somebody was blackmailing him.
We need to find out who it was
and why they did it.
What if they come after us now?
Please, ask her.
Sure, I promise.
Would you like anything
from the kitchen?
-No, I'm fine, thanks.
-Okay.
-Are you in pain?
-Just a long day.
Me, too. Can I ask you something?
Nothing important.
What would you say about
updating the bar a bit?
One more idea from me
and I'll be shot.
So tell them it's my idea.
I'd take a bullet for you...
Do you realise how happy I am
that you're here with me?
I'm happy to be here, too.
Darling, you stink.
Okay, I know. I'll have a shower.
Thank you.
Thanks for today.
It means a lot.
Hello.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for asking...
but do you know
how Egil and your mum met?
At the hotel.
Where is she now?
I'd love to meet her.
My mum is dead.
God, sorry. I didn't realise.
No, how would you know?
It's been a while.
-What was her name?
-Jessica.
She worked at the Beach Hotel when
Egil and Werner owned it together.
How did she die?
She got ill.
It was over pretty quickly.
My behaviour last time
really wasn't okay.
No...
Aksel said that maybe
Dad did this for us two
to get to know each other.
Just the sort of thing he would do.
-Why?
-He found it easy to talk to people.
And find a connection. He didn't
get why others weren't like him.
What was he like as a father?
He worked nearly all the time.
When he was at home, he might not
have played with me or read to me,
but I always felt that
he was there for me the whole time.
Once, as a student in Switzerland,
when I was feeling really low,
I was in my dorm and just
wanted to give up and go home.
Suddenly, there he was.
He'd flown down,
just to see how I was.
We went out for a meal.
That's on the way back to the hotel,
like ten beers later.
Look at the state of us.
So he wanted you, but not me.
I don't know why
he never mentioned you.
But I'm sure he did think of you.
But he never showed that he did.
Busy day?
No, not too bad.
All that's missing
is your signature.
I really want this, Werner.
A new life together with you.
I know.
But you're not ready yet.
You can't bear the thought
of leaving the hotel.
You're so full of energy,
passion, adventure.
I wish I was the same, but I'm not.
I'm sorry.
You have your adventure here.
At Saltsjövik.
We don't need to do this now.
We can carry on as we are.
You're not angry?
No.
You're amazing.
Hang on!
Please, don't think
I have any regrets.
-But?
-I find you very... special.
Special? Like really hard work?
No, the complete opposite.
I can't break the rules
that I make my staff adhere to.
What would people think?
They'd think that
you're listening to yourself.
See you tomorrow. Or this evening.
It's up to you.
Conscientious.
What are you doing here?
How are you?
Well, what do you think?
You never call me back.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm glad you're here.
I fought with Sebastian yesterday.
You're not surprised?
Why do I keep hurting
the people close to me?
We've hurt each other.
Would you like me to come home?
You go back.
I'm going to Stockholm tomorrow.
We'll see what we do
when I get back.
What do you mean "we'll see"?
You're right.
We need some time apart.
So that's just your decision?
Do I not get a say?
-Look, I just want to...
-"You want to."
And "you're going to..."
It's all on your terms!
Your family
is always more important than us.
And your feelings
are always more important than mine.
Just piss off, forget about me
and focus on yourself.
That's what you do best, after all.
I asked her to come over.
You have to sort this out.
Petra.
Look, I'm sorry. I didn't think...
No, I know.
See you.
Hold on.
Could you help me with something?
What?
Could you check if Jessica Adolfsson
has worked at your hotel?
Who's that?
Rebecca's mum.
What do you want from her?
Okay, I'll check.
I'll be in touch
if I find something.
Thank you.
No, we can forget about France.
That's my savings gone.
Unfortunately.
But listen,
it might all be for the best.
It would have taken a long time.
Focus on the wedding instead.
The sooner I get married,
the sooner I can get divorced.
No, I know.
I miss you, too.
A lot.
But I'll see you soon.
Love you.
-Marianne?
-Hello.
I haven't been here since...
His diary.
I do like this hotel.
I'd love to
make myself useful somehow.
Did you have
anything in particular in mind?
-No, I don't know.
-Okay.
You have a think
and I'll see what I can do.
-You promise me that?
-Sure.
I could use your help
with something.
What?
The surveillance camera.
From the days
leading up to Egil's death.
Hasn't Julie
forgotten about that yet?
Okay.
I will see to it.
For your sake.
Thank you.
There you go. Nice to see you again.
The nineties weren't all bad.
-No?
-No, that's when I was born.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I shouldn't have dissed your bar.
Don't worry.
And maybe we could do
with a bit of a makeover.
-Exactly.
-I'm just not sure what it needs.
I'd suggest
you do something with mirrors.
To get some depth into the room.
It would make it so bright.
Blue as a base colour
is kind of safe at a coastal hotel,
but if you look at these stripes...
-Excuse me.
-Can I help you?
Is Sebastian still at the hotel
or has he gone home?
When will you realise
that Sebastian isn't yours anymore?
-Look where the picture is...
-See you.
Subtitles: Anna Townend
plint.com