Previously on Breaking Bad...
I can't help you get through this
if you wont me what it is Walt did.
Two men are coming to kill you.
Come again.
Two men ambushed Hank.
There tattoos indicate an affiliation
with the drug cartel.
You knew my brother when
I was with the DEA.
I investigate everyone I do business.
I am sleeping with my boss
and I don't know why.
What's up partner?
This is my replacement?
In the litlle village
where I was born,
life moved
at a slower pace...
yet felt all the richer
for it.
There, my two uncles
were known far and wide
for their delicious cooking.
They seasoned
their zesty chicken
using only the freshest herbs
and spices.
People called them
"Los Pollos Hermanos"--
the Chicken Brothers.
Today, we carry on
their tradition
in a manner that would make
my uncleproud.
The finest ingredients
are brought together
with loving care...
then slow-cooked
to perfection.
Yes, the old ways
are still best
at Los Pollos Hermanos.
But don't take
my word for it.
One taste and you'll know.
♪ [theme]
♫ Breaking Bad 3x09 ♫
Kafkaesque
Original Air Date on May 16, 2010
-- sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.Com --
[beeping]
[Jesse]
201.6.
Jesus, seriously.
Better over than under.
Over by a pound
and a half.
I thought you were all,
like, precise.
Whatever. We'll just
save it out till next week.
No. We ship it as-is.
What are we,
running a charity?
Come on, man,
we're gonna take it out.
Leave it.
One batch, one ship.
Stop complicating things.
Why are you purposely
giving him free meth?
These bitches are
bleeding us enough already.
You are paid
extraordinarily well.
Why can't you just
appreciate that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, hey.
Hey, I been crunching numbers,
all right?
Oh, you've been
crunching numbers?
Yeah, I've been
crunching numbers,
and I don't gotta be
a mathematician to figure out
that this deal you made
is bullshit.
We both earn--
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know...
a million and a half each.
Whoop-de-doo.
What's he getting?
Huh?
Say he's wholesaling
at 40 large a pound.
That's probably high.
High. Uh, what,
for our stuff?
That's what I was getting.
All right, look,
say he's getting 40 a pound.
All right?
200 pounds a week
for three months.
And, like, what happens
at the end of the three months?
Look, what-- whatever.
200 pounds a week
for three months.
That's 2400 pounds.
2400 times 40,000 is--
and I swear to God,
I double-checked this,
like, 10 times--
96 million dollars.
[zips]
All right?
96 million.
96 to our three.
That is messed up, yo.
That is so messed up.
Fairness-wise, I can't even--
Jesse, you are now
a millionaire,
and you're complaining?
What world do you live in?
One where the dudes who are
actually doing all the work
ain't getting fisted.
What is going on
with you lately?
What's happened to you?
Hang on, can't we just--
Hey, we got to hash this out.
Hey, what's more important
than money?
[door slams]
[monitor beeping]
These things
they laughingly call pillows,
I would not give them
to prison inmates.
You want me to go ask
for another?
No. Just remind me
to bring his from home.
They're not moving
his legs enough.
[knock on door]
[Gomez]
Hey, everybody.
Oh...
Hi, Marie.
Is it okay if--
if I visit?
Yeah.
His color looks good.
[whispering]
Gomie, is that you?
Hey, buddy.
Yeah, it's me.
That's you, Gomie?
Yeah, Hank.
I'm right here.
Come here. Closer.
What is it?
Closer.
Asshole.
[laughs]
Man, he got you good.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm glad to see you still have
your twisted sense of humor.
[chuckles]
[coughs]
Hey, check this out.
I got something that'll
make you feel better.
I've been keeping an eye
on that blue meth of yours.
Six, seven weeks, nothing.
Then all of a sudden, boom.
It's popping up everywhere.
Look at the new locations.
Texas, Nevada,
up in Farmington.
Even right here in town.
A teener here and there,
you know,
strictly street-level amounts.
Man, it's crazy.
How exactly is that
supposed to make me
feel better?
Beuse you were right.
You're the only one
that saw this coming.
Well, three cheers for me.
[beeps]
[exhales]
This thing doesn't do
a damned thing.
Hank, it's probably
still on lock-out.
It's been an hour, right?
I'm hurting here.
I could use some meds.
Okay. I'll go find somebody.
Hey, no more shop talk.
Sorry.
I didn't see it coming.
What?
Damn right you did.
No, I didn't see shit.
Day late and a dollar short,
as usual.
The only reason I'm...
even breathing...
is I got a warning call.
A warning call?
What do you mean?
One minute before
they attacked me,
somebody called my cell
and told me to expect it.
A voice scrambler.
It could have been anybody.
Marie's got
my phone somewhere,
if you want to run
the incoming.
Not that you're going to learn
anything worth knowing.
I don't get it.
Cartel hit?
Who would have called
to warn you?
I don't know.
[winces]
Aw, Jesus.
Come on already.
[groans]
Hang on.
Skyler, I had
nothing to do--
Are we safe?
Yes.
Are you safe?
Absolutely.
Jesse?
What about you?
Face looks better.
How's it all going?
Anything you want
to tell us about?
What, like
my interesting life?
One day pretty much
bleeds into the next.
Been working a lot.
I got a job.
[Group Leader]
Job is good.
It's in a Laundromat.
It's totally corporate.
Corporate Laundromat.
[Jesse]
It's, like, rigid.
All kinds of red tape.
My boss is a dick.
The owner? Super dick.
I'm not worthy or whatever
to meet him,
but I guess everybody's
scared of the dude.
The place is full of
dead-eyed douche-bags,
the hours suck,
and nobody knows
what's going on,
so...
Sounds kind of Kafkaesque.
Yeah.
Totally Kafkaesque.
Majorly.
Ooh, from the U.S. attorney
in Santa Fe.
Very nice.
We've got
all these nice tulips
and baby's breath.
This is chrysanthemum.
That looks like chrysanthemum.
Look at these Hank.
Aren't they beautiful?
Beautiful.
Wow, look at the size
of this basket.
It's got so many
goodies in it.
Look, chocolate-covered pretzels
and cheese sticks
and some some fancy
designer olives.
You had me
at cheese sticks.
Mmm, you're going to have
to fight me for those, Hank.
"Get well, and best wishes
from Ted Beneke
and all the folks
at Beneke Fabricators."
Wow, he gives you
all this time off,
and now this?
Get me a job there.
I know. He's great.
Boss hall of fame.
I don't see anything
here from Kleinman.
They're going to have
to get on the stick.
[knocking on door]
How's everybody doing today?
Good. We're good.
How are you?
I'm very good.
Hi, Hank.
Just going to do a quick
peripheral response,
all right?
See where we're at.
Moment of truth, huh?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
I wouldn't call it that.
All right, let's just
take a look here.
All right.
All right,
I want you to tell me
if you can feel this.
All right.
How about this?
Okay.
How about now?
Do that one again,
would you?
Right there?
Yeah, yeah, I feel it.
A tingle.
Okay, on a scale
of one to ten,
ten being your normal
level of feeling
and one bein
no feeling at all.
Oh, I don't know.
A four?
Okay, four. Okay.
And how about there?
Yeah. Um, a six.
Okay, good.
And here?
Yeah, still there.
A little less.
A three.
Okay.
All right, good.
Thank you very much, Hank.
Good, good.
So this is good news,
right?
Oh, yeah,
definitely.
It looks like
some nerve function
is returning.
Oh, thank God.
All right, so when do we
get him walking again?
Marie, it's important that
we manage our expectations.
We're talking about
months of very hard work,
and even then the odds,
they're not great.
But you can't know
for sure.
No.
When does he start
physical therapy?
We've sent the paperwork
to your insurance.
It's high priority.
We should have
pre-authorization
the next few days.
Certainly by early next week.
[Marie]
Next week?
No, that's not
going to do it.
I've looked into this.
The sooner
physical therapy begins,
the better his chances are.
He needs daily sessions.
Isn't that right?
Well--
Actually,
your plan's treatment program
covers four sessions a week.
Actually,
she asked the doctor.
Plan-wise,
four sessions a week
is fairly typical.
And the therapists
in your network
are mostly fine.
Mostly fine? Okay.
There's a ringing endorsement.
Look, if Hank had
more physical therapy,
with better therapists,
wouldn't it be more likely
he would walk?
It's very hard to say, Marie.
Is the health plan's way
medically justifiable? Sure.
Is it absolutely optimal?
Yo5 know, screw it.
I'm going to make sure
he gets what he needs,
and they can just
reimburse me later.
Mrs. Schrader,
I get your frustration.
Really, I do.
But my best advice
is stay in the network.
Don't go out of pocket.
Physical therapy
is just the beginning.
We're talking nursing care,
modifications to your home,
occupational therapy,
medical equipment.
It could run into
the hundreds of thousands
of dollars.
So what?
We're just supposed
to compromise on his care?
Well, if you don't follow
the insurance company's
procedures,
they may never
pay you back.
I've seen patients
and their families
go bankrupt,
waiting to be reimbursed.
Who is the best
physical therapist
that you know?
I can give you some names.
But they're not likely
to be on your plan.
To hell with the plan.
[door chime dings]
Yeah, there he is.
Finally. I went ahead
and started without you.
Ladies, this is Jesse-san.
He's in for the full treatment.
Kick off your shoes.
Lay back. Exfoliate.
Maybe later.
So, where's the maestro?
Out parking the mini-van?
What do I look like,
his shadow?
Who cares where he's at?
What am I doing here?
Well, I was going
to have you two flip a coin,
but since the genius
can't be bothered,
today's your lucky day.
Look around, kiddo.
It's all yours.
What? This?
Yeah. You are now the owner
of this fine establishment.
For free?
Free?
Ladies, cover your ears.
No, not free.
Look, hey,
this is a squeaky-clean,
highly profitable--
at least potentially--
local institution,
looked upon with favor
by the Chamber of Commerce.
Better Business Bureau.
At $312,000, it's a steal.
312,000?
Don't you get it?
On the outside,
it's a nail salon, right?
On the inside,
it's the best money laundry
a growing boy could ask for.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
Ladies, thank you.
Thank you. Good job.
Come back here.
Sit. Come on.
Humor me here for a second.
Now, you know you need
to launder your money,
right?
Do you understand
the basics of it?
Placement, layering,
integration?
I ain't buying
no damn nail salon,
so just forget it.
You want to stay
out of jail, don't you?
You want to keep
your money and your freedom.
Because I got three
little letters for you.
IRS.
If they can get Capone,
they can get you.
Hey, look.
Here's you, right?
Pink, Pinkman. Get it?
Okay, here's your cash.
You're out on the town.
You're partying hearty.
You're knocking boots
with the chickie babes.
Oh, who's this?
It's the tax man.
And he's looking at you.
What does he see?
He sees a young fellow
with a big, fancy house,
unlimited cash supply,
and no job.
Now what is the conclusion
the tax man makes?
I'm a drug dealer.
[imitates buzzer]
Wrong.
Million times worse.
You're a tax cheat.
What do they do?
They take every penny,
and you go in the can
for felony tax evasion.
Ouch.
What was your mistake?
You didn't launder
your money.
Now, you give me
That's called placement.
Hand me that
little thinGod bin.
This is the nail salon,
right?
I take your dirty money
and I slip it into the salon's
nice, clean cash flow.
That's called layering.
Final step, integration.
The revenues from the salon
go to the owner.
That's you.
Your filthy drug money
has been transformed
into nice, clean,
taxable income,
brought to you by
a savvy investment
in a thriving business.
So you want me
to buy this place
so I can pay taxes.
I'm a criminal, yo.
Yeah, and if you want
to stay a criminal
and not become,
say, a convict,
then maybe you should grow up
and listen to your lawyer.
Right, so you can get
your 5%.
No, that's 17%.
I heard you say 5.
You said it
right in front of me.
Yeah. That was
for your partner.
It's privileges
of seniority and all.
But for you, it's the usual.
17%, and that's a bargain.
Hey, what, you--
Hey, listen to--
Come on, I'm talking to you
about your future here.
Listen to reason.
How is your
brother-in-law?
He'll live.
Good. I'm glad.
Walter, you seem troubled.
How can I help you?
I asked to see you
in order to...
clear the air.
There are some issues
that could cause
a misunderstanding between us,
and I think it's
in our best interest
to lay the cards
on the table.
That's the best way
to do business.
My brother-in-law,
moments before
he was attacked--
someone called to warn him.
I believe that same person
was protecting me.
Those two men, the assassins--
I believe
I was their prime target,
but that somehow
they were steered away from me
to my brother-in-law.
Because of this intervention,
I am alive.
And yet I think
that this person
was playing
a much deeper game.
He made that phone call
because he wanted a shootout,
not a silent assassination.
In one stroke
he bloodied both sides,
set the American
and Mexican governments
against the cartel,
and cut off the supply
of methamphetamine
to the Southwest.
If this man had
his own source of product
on this side of the border...
he would have the market
to himself.
The rewards would be...
enormous.
We're both adults.
I can't pretend I don't know
that person is you.
I want there to be
no confusion.
I know I owe you my life.
And more than that,
I respect the strategy.
In your position,
I wouldn't done the same.
One issue which troubles me--
I don't know what happens
when our three-month
contract ends.
What would you like
to happen?
You know why I do this.
I want security
for my family.
Then you have it.
Three million
for three month.
That was our agreement.
Extended annually,
twelve million a year.
Call it fifteen.
Open-ended.
Would that be agreeable?
[motor accelerating]
[truck horn blares]
[tires screeching]
[gasps]
[exhales]
Part of the reason we talk
about what gets us riled up,
in our daily lives
is to help each other
put a finger
on what our relapse triggers
might be,
head off our disease
before it comes back.
So... anyone?
Free license
to bitch and moan.
How often do you get that?
Jesse, last time
you seemed pretty down
about your job
at the Laundromat.
Let me ask you something.
If you had the chance
to do anything you wanted,
what would you do?
Make more green, man,
a lot more.
Forget about money.
Assume you have all you want.
Um...
I don't know.
I guess I would make something.
Like what?
Not that it even matters,
but...
work with my hands,
I guess.
Building things,
like...
carpentry or brick laying
or something?
I took this vo-tech class
in high school,
wood working.
because it was just
a big Jesus--,
but this one time
I had this teacher
name of, uh...
Mr. Pike.
I guess he was, like,
a Marine or something
before he got old.
He was hard of hearing.
My project for his class
was to make this wooden box,
you know, like a small--
just like a-- like a box,
you know, to put stuff in.
So I wanted to get the thing
done just as fast as possible.
I figured I could cut classes
for the rest of the semester,
and he couldn't flunk me
as long as I, you know,
made the thing.
So I finished it
in a couple days.
It looked pretty lame,
but it worked,
you know, for putting stuff in
or whatnot.
So when I showed it
to Mr. Pike
for my grade,
he looked at it
and said,
"Is that the best you can do?"
At first I thought to myself,
"Hell, yeah, bitch.
"Now give me a D and shut up
so I can go blaze one
with my boys."
[group chuckles]
I don't know.
Maybe it was the way
he said it, but...
it was, like, he w--
he wasn't exactly saying
it sucked.
He was just asking me
honestly,
"Is that all you got?"
And for some reason
I thought to myself,
"Yeah, man, I can do better,"
so I started from scratch.
I made another,
then another,
and by the end of the semester,
by, like, box number five,
I had built this thing.
You should've seen it.
It was insane.
I mean, I built it out of
Peruvian Walnut
with inlaid Zebrawood.
It was fitted with pegs,
no screws.
I sanded it for days
until it was smooth as glass.
Then I rubbed all the wood
with tung oil so it was
rich and dark.
It even smelled good.
You know, you put nose in it
and breathed in,
it was--
It was perfect.
What happened to the box?
I, um--
I gave it to my mom.
Nice.
You know what I'm going to say,
don't you?
It's never too late.
They have art co-ops
that offer classes,
adult extension program
at the university.
You know, I didn't give
the box to my mom.
I traded it
for an ounce of weed.
He's a hero.
You don't deny coverage
to a hero.
They'll say
they're not denying coverage.
No, no,
I'm agreeing with you,
but I went through all this
with Walt.
You'll burn
through your savings,
and then what?
Well, you two managed, right?
You said yourself
that Elliot and Gretchen's
money didn't cover everything.
[sighs]
Jesus, I've got to get back.
What? No.
No, no, no,
you should rest.
Look, why don't you go in
and take a long bath
I put some fresh sheets
on the bed.
I want to be there
in case he wakes up.
With all they're giving him,
he'll sleep till morning.
[doorbell chimes]
Hey, Sky.
Hey.
Wha--
What are you doing here?
Well, I just thought
I'd stop by
to see how
you're holding up.
Is this a bad time, or...
Um--
Hi.
Uh, Marie, this is Ted,
my boss.
Oh, you're Ted.
I've heard so much about you.
Thank you
for your gift basket.
That was really thoughtful.
It was. It was really nice.
Thank you, Ted.
Cheese sticks.
Well, you're welcome.
You know,
we care about Skyler so much
that naturally that extends
to the whole family.
Are you coming in?
Oh, yeah, you should.
[chuckles]
I'm sorry.
Come on in, Ted.
Thanks. Okay.
[clears throat]
We were just having some wine.
Would you like a glass?
No. No, thanks.
I'm just on my way home.
I just thought I'd--
You know, I--
I am really beat.
I think I'm going
to take that bath.
It was nice
to meet you, Ted,
and thank you again.
Nice to meet you, too, Marie.
Please give my best wishes
to your husband.
I will.
Thanks for stopping by,
but it's actually not a--
not the best time
for a visit, so--
Can we just talk
for a minute?
I know you need to be
with your family,
but I haven't heard
from you in days
I left messages--
I'm so sorry.
You gave me all that time off,
and I really should've--
That's not my point.
I-- I care about you.
That's all.
Ted, I--
It's just this whole thing
with Hank
has been one non-stop
horror show,
you know, so...
Well, I--
I just want you to know
that I'm here for you.
Thank you.
Um, but I really do need
you to...
Okay.
Okay?
Skyler, I've got to say
your sister seeing me here--
I mean--
So what?
I'm divorced.
You're divorced.
So what?
Okay, let's talk about it
later, Ted, okay?
Is there some reasonfor sec?
Because--
Later. Ted, not now.
Skyler, just tell me--
You really want
to do this now?
Are you really going to make me
do this right now?
[sighs]
Wow.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm--
Bad idea
to come here.
Ted, I'm--
I'll see you in a day or two.
Back at the office.
Take as much time
as you want.
[Badger]
I can't believe
you had to crush the RV.
Must've been, like...
depressing.
[Skinny Pete]
For real. That's a stone loss.
[Jesse]
No one misses it
more than me.
Free to cook anytime, anywhere.
No quotas, no one to answer to.
What's the point
of being an outlaw
when you've got
responsibilities?
Darth Vader
had responsibilities.
He was responsible
for the Death Star.
True that.
Two of them bitches.
Just saying.
Devil's advocate.
I've got to pay taxes now?
What the hell's up with that?
That's messed up, yo.
That's Kafkaesque.
Church.
Right.
Let's kick it back into gear.
Let's start slinging again.
Boo-yah!
Shh.
Let's dot.
Life's too short.
That's what I say.
Hell, yeah, bitches.
We don't need no RV.
Alls we need is a bicycle,
some Drano, soda bottles,
Nah, nah, nah,
no shake 'n bake.
Where's your self-respect?
Come on.
Yo, maybe it ain't top shelf,
but we could at least move it.
Still kind of dry out there.
Let's-- It'll sell
on the street.
Who says we sell
on the street?
Maybe I know
a whole new market.
Maybe alls we need
is the meth.
[exhales]
[scale beeps]
What's the yield?
Hey.
The yield.
Come on.
Uh... 201.8.
[Group Leader]
I see a couple new faces.
Anybody want to introduce
themselves?
Don't all speak at once.
Yeah.
So my name's Brandon.
Okay, Brandon.
You want to tell us
something about yourself?
Well, why I'm here--
it's just one thing.
It's meth.
It's bad.
Thought I had it kicked
a couple times, you know,
but then... Jesus.
This new version of it
hit the streets and...
wow.
Not that blue stuff.
Oh, sorry,
I didn't raise my hand.
No, go ahead.
This is what we do.
Yeah, exactly, the blue stuff.
You had it, to
Yeah, bro.
I wish I never even
heard of it.
It was like lighting
my whole head on fire.
[Badger]
Yeah, stuff
will burn you down.
Only reason I have
a hope in hell
is because it's long gone.
That's the shame of it.
Nah, come on, man.
Don't tell me that.
I hear it's back in town.
Stay strong, brother.
Stay strong.
It's gonna be okay.
[monitor beeping]
[Marie]
I swear to God, I'll do it.
I will go to the press.
I will go to 48 Hours.
I will go to Nightline.
I don't even know if there is
a Nightline anymore.
It doesn't matter.
They will all take it,
and they will run with it
because he is a hero,
and he is not going to be
in a wheelchair at 43.
Jesus.
Marie, I know Skyler's
already told you this,
but if there's every
anything that you need,
anything at all...
It's good to have you here.
Both of you.
I just wish there was...
something more
that we could do.
Walt?
We can always pay
their bills.
[Marie]
Please, it's tens
of thousands of dollars.
We have the money,
more than enough.
Walt earned it.
Skyler.
I think Marie
should know the truth.
Skyler, I really don't think
this is a good idea.
I think that--
He earned it gambling.
Walt and I, uh--
We've had our problems lately.
You know that.
And, uh...
what it all came down to
really was... money.
Pure and simple.
When Walt was diagnosed,
it, um--
It changed him.
Looking back, I don't think
I ever really understood
what it was
that he was going through.
It was more than facing death.
It was knowing that
he was going to leave behind...
nothing.
And so that's how
this all started.
For better or worse,
he wanted to provide,
and so...
he paid his medical bills
the only way he knew how.
I thought
that Elliot and Gretchen
paid for your treatment.
Yeah, I thought so, too,
but the truth is
he never took their money,
not a dime.
He was too proud to take
what he considered
to be charity.
Isn't that right?
So he put his mindo it
and--
Well, you know how Walt is.
He's-- He's a problem solver,
and he read books,
and he did
a whole bunch of research,
and he came up with...
this system.
A system?
A system for counting cards
in Blackjack.
W-What do you mean,
like Rain Man?
Well, I don't pretend
to understand, you know,
all the details,
but he was convinced
that if you put
enough money into it,
he'd have a, um, uh--
God, what is it?
A statistical edge?
Yes, statistical--
So-- right.
...um, yeah.
So he-- Every spare minute,
Walt was at some card table
somewhere,
and at first he went
to the casinos,
but then he realized that--
[low]
...but then he realized
that the casinos report
your winnings to the IRS,
and if it gets reported,
your family might find out,
and if you do not want
your family to find out,
then you find
another place to gamble,
like an illegal,
backroom game.
You remember
all those long walks
that Walt used to take,
all that time
he used to spend
away from home?
I guess for a couple months
there you were...
sort of leading a double life,
weren't you?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, your--
your fugue state,
was that some sort of cover?
No. No.
He did not fake that, Marie.
The night
that Walt disappeared...
he los$14,000.
[sighs]
It was his pension fund,
our savings,
basically every last dime
we had to our name, gone.
He couldn't live with it.
He was suicidal.
But you have to try
to understand
that as soon as he got
out of the hospital,
he went right back
to gambling.
I mean, that's how deep
this went.
How could you
do that to her, Walt?
I, um--
Anyway, this system of his...
he finally got it to work.
So all this is to say
we have the money.
No more gambling.
But we have the money.
How... much money?
Walt?
Uh--
Well, uh--
It's in the seven figures.
Oh, God.
Holy Mary, Mother of God.
What can I say?
I did very well.
Marie...
you will take our money.
Use it to take care of Hank.
Please.
Marie, let us help.
Does Walt, Jr. know
about this?
Absolutely not,
and I need to keep it th way,
and Hank-- okay--
Hank's got enough
on his mind right now,
so can we just please keep
this between us?
Yeah. Yeah, I--
Yeah, I--
I just-- I need to--
Yeah, okay.
We'll talk about it later.
How did you come up
with that?
I mean, where--
where did you possibly--
I learned from the best.
Somehow something tells me
that Hank is here
because of you.
And I'm not forgetting that.
-- sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.Com --