Mmm.
Sync by honeybunny
www. addic7ed. com
Hey, you got nothing on me, yo.
All right, you can call
my lawyer, Saul Goodman.
Talk to my lawyer, all right?
Hey, you hear me.
I got nothing to say.
I told you.
You can call my-
Ah, Christ! God!
You had my cell phone number!
You had my wife's name!
How'd you do it?
Huh? Who you working with?
If you're, uh, ready to talk,
they want to get a statement.
Your side
of what happened here.
Or we can hold him off
till another time.
Maybe you'll want
to talk to a lawyer.
There it is.
Yo, Adrian.
Rocky called.
He wants his face back.
Come on.
I got to cheer you up.
You see that? That's your
Get Out of Jail Free card.
You understand Get Out of
Jail Free card, right?
I mean, just blink once
if you're following.
The D.A.'s worst nightmare
is that face out in public.
They're going to have
to steer a wide berth
of young Master Pinkman
for fear of the P.R.
poop storm
that will rain down on them
if this story ever gets out.
I mean, this- this beating?
Best thing for you.
You're home free.
Good, right?
Right.
Oh, my God.
You're now officially
the cute one of the group.
Paul, meet Ringo.
Ringo, Paul.
This is- I-
Jesse, I'm-
I am so sorry for this.
This should not have happened.
But it did.
No thanks to you.
But the plan did work.
We would have been
locked up right now
if we didn't lure him away.
But this-
this- I just-
I never saw this coming.
So...
What, uh...
W- what happens now?
What happens now?
I'll tell you what happens now.
Yo scumbag brother-in-law
is finished,
done.
You understand?
I will own him
when this is over.
Every cent he earns,
every cent his wife earns,
is mine.
Anyplace he goes,
anywhere he turns,
I'm going to be there,
grabbing my share.
He'll be scrubbing toilets
in Tijuana for pennies,
and I'll be standing over him
to get my cut.
He'll see me when he wakes up
in the morning
and when he crawls to sleep
in whatever rat hole's
left for him
after I shred his house down,
I will haunt his crusty ass
forever
until the day
he sticks a gun up his mouth
and pulls the trigger
just to get me out of his head.
That's what happens next.
Uh, my advice-
that's probably not
a good strategy.
I mean, they're scared
of you right now.
They want nothing
to do with you.
But if you hit them,
they're forced
to hit back hard.
I mean, they will
turn over every rock
hither, thither, and yon
until someone spills
the beans on you
and anyone associated with you,
uh, present company included.
Yeah, I think what Saul is
saying makes a lot of sense.
Jesse, move on with your life.
Leave it behind, all of it.
Nothing changes.
Once I walk out of here,
I get myself a new RV
and go start cooking again.
How exactly do you think
you're going to get
away with that?
They will catch you.
So what?
What?
I have a Get Out of Jail
Free card.
Hey, I may have overstated
the, uh, power of your face.
Not this.
If the cops catch me...
I give them
what they want the most.
You.
They nab me,
I make a deal
to give up the great Heisenberg
and his million-dollar
drug ring.
You're my free pass, bitch.
You're so sure.
Look, if he didn't
give up my name
while Hank was beating him
senseless,
he's never going to talk.
What do you think that was
in there, a bluff?
He wants your brother-in-law.
And there's going to be
a parade of lawyers
creaming their Underoos
for a case like that.
I mean, I'd take it myself
if it wouldn't cause
so much collateral damage.
And him cooking again.
Hey, when, not if,
he gets caught,
and he's facing 20 years,
what'll he do then?
Believe me, there's
no honor among thieves.
Except for us, of course.
No, he'll-
he'll come around.
And if he doesn't,
there may come a time
to talk options.
Options?
I'm convinced that Mr. Pinkman
was involved
in the manufacture
and distribution
of phenyl-2
methamphetamine,
specifically what we're
calling the blue meth.
I tracked him to a scrap yard
where he stored
an early '80s camper,
an RV.
While waiting for a warrant
to search this vehicle,
which I believed to be
a rolling meth lab,
I received a telephone call
telling me my wife Marie had
been injured in an accident.
Upon hearing the news,
I left Mr. Pinkman
and his vehicle
to tend to my wife.
After arriving at the hospital,
I learned the emergency
call was a hoax.
My wife, fortunately,
was unharmed.
So I immediately went
back to the salvage yard,
but the RV was gone.
Most likely destroyed on site.
And it was at this point
that you drove to the home
of Jesse Pinkman?
I think we're done here.
Agent Schrader
needs to get home,
get some rest.
That's fine.
But just to confirm,
you're taking the Fifth here?
Yeah. That's correct.
Okay. Well, we just want
to GI you all a heads up.
Mr. Pinkman is pressing
charges in this matter.
He's given a detailed version
of events as he sees them.
The word of a meth head.
We know all about his history.
We're well aware,
but toxicology on Pinkman-
his blood is clean,
he's not using.
The kid is even refusing his
doctor-ordered pain meds,
as far as we can tell.
So, um...
...where do we go from here?
A couple of gentlemen
from OPR will come down,
probably tomorrow morning.
Janice will give us
an exact time on that.
And you men will be
continuing your investigation,
so...
Thanks for your time.
Right. We just-
We need one more thing.
Photo of Agent Schrader's
hands, for the record.
Yes, of course.
Bandage off, if you would.
Um, on the table is fine.
Flat on the table is fine.
It's all going to work out.
You've been too good to them
for too many years.
I hope it goes without saying
that we're not talking
to anybody about this, okay?
Okay.
Marie, who?
Hi.
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
I guess crime does pay.
I don't suppose you just
came by to insult me.
No. We need to talk.
You heard about Hank?
About what happened
with this, um, Jesse Pinkman?
Yes, I know.
Whatever Hank
was investigating,
him trying to find an RV,
is there any danger
that could lead back to you?
No. Why would it?
Is this why you're here?
I'm here to talk about Hank.
Mm-hmm.
You know what's
going to happen to him
if this Pinkman
presses charges?
Hank could lose everything.
I thought maybe, um...
There's a way
you could help him.
How?
Contact Pinkman.
Get him to drop the charges.
Look, Skyler, I don't know
what kind of relationship
you picture me having
with this person.
I'm not asking.
He was- He's-
He's not my friend.
I mean,
it's not as if we-
I'm-
... were even close.
I'm not asking.
But there must be
something you could say.
Isn't it even worth a try?
Hank is your family.
Not currently.
What?
I said not currently.
I'm late. I have to go.
Hello. I was starting
to get worried.
Car trouble.
Oh. That's a bummer.
You should call me next time.
I'll pick you up.
Uh-huh.
No, uh, no sandals today?
I just thought-
a bit more professional.
Well,
everything is on track.
We got our distillate.
Just waiting to-
Let's get our trays ready.
Clean, no moisture.
Done.
Is our, uh...
Our solvent filtered?
I thought you might ask that.
Done.
That's good.
Hand in glove.
That's what we strive for.
Yo5 know,
this might be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
So, you the gentlemen?
Lucky you boys called me.
I got a load to pick up.
I'm taking the 40
straight through to Memphis.
I could hammer it out
in about 15,
but there's a girl down there
named Lainie or Lolly
or something. Maybe Fran.
She's got one
of these fetish things-
wants to get peed on.
I was hoping
to see her tonight,
so I want to wrap it up
here ASAP
because traffic
can be a wild card,
you know,
rubbernecking and such.
The surprising thing is
women who like to get peed on
always tend to be
from the warmer climates.
You'd think the ones
in the colder zones
would be more inclined.
Maybe it's a shock
to the system
if the body's
not properly acclimated,
but, you know, I leave that
for smart minds than me.
Science is a mystery.
Well, take a gander.
Prices are negotiable.
Buying in bulk
gets you a discount.
I'm running a special
on these little honeys.
JHPs. Hollow-point bullets,
known by the natives
as Black Death.
Check it out.
Huh. You like that?
So sweet, you want to lick it.
Nickel-plated brass casing,
Lubalox coat for panache.
Sucker has six razor claws
that expand upon impact.
Whew.
Shred your mama's head
like a cabbage.
Hmm.
Keep it. On the house?
Anyhow, I've been
windjamming long enough.
Why don't you boys tell me
what you're looking for?
What can I do you for?
Vests.
Vests? Hell, yeah,
we got vests.
Right here.
Sleek, comfortable,
thermally bonded
non-interwoven Kevlar fiber.
Stop a bullet like a soft wank
against a Quaker girl.
Just ain't getting through.
And lightweight?
Damn, so lightweight,
you'll forget
you're wearing it.
They work?
Sure as shit, they do.
I don't leave home without it.
Ohh!
What the hell?
You broke my freakin' rib,
you maniac son of a bitch.
You're welcome!
Gale.
What temperature
did you set here?
There? That's...
Station Five- 75 C.
I said 85.
8-5.
No.
I, uh-
I wrote it down.
You said 75.
I- I wrote it.
Well, then you wrote it wrong.
That's not what I said.
I said 85.
It's always been 85-
not 75, not 95.
85.
This is chemistry.
Degrees matter.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Great. You're sorry.
Meanwhile, you've just brewed
50 gallons of useless sludge.
Congratulations.
Just dump it. Dump it all.
This batch is ruined.
You look nice.
I look like a TV weatherman.
You want a coffee?
Nah.
I squeezed some orange juice.
You want to glass
of orange juice?
I'm all right.
What are you
going to tell them?
Here's what you're
going to tell them.
He attacked you.
He attacked me?
He- He swung at you
with something.
He-
Swung at me....
attacked you with a pipe.
With a pipe?
It happened fast.
He resisted arrest,
and muscle memory kicked in,
and you had to disarm him.
Muscle memory.
Yes.
It happens all the time.
Years of training, and your body
acted faster than your brain.
You had no choice
but to hit him.
You had to fight back.
Marie, Marie, Marie.
No.
I'm not going to go
in there and lie.
It's some lowlife degenerate
versus you...
Doing the job
you're supposed to.
Why should you be
the one who pays
for doing the right thing?
Oh, baby,
it wasn't the right thing.
It's not what the job is.
I'm supposed to be
better than that.
And you made one mistake.
No, it wasn't one mistake.
I've been-
I've been...
...unraveling,
you know?
I don't sleep at night anymore.
I freeze.
I freeze up.
My chest gets all tight.
I- I can't breathe.
Just-
I panic.
Ever since
that Salamanca thing.
I mean, Tuco Salamanca.
If ever a scumbag deserved
a bullet between the eyes.
It changed me.
And I can't seem to control it.
I tried to fight it.
But then El Paso.
And it's just gotten worse.
What I did to Pinkman...
...that's not who
I'm supposed to be.
That's not me.
All this-
everything
that's happened, I-
I swear to God, Marie,
I think the universe is
trying to tell me something,
and I'm finally...
Ready to listen.
I'm just not the man
I thought I was.
I think I'm done as a cop.
Now, this is-
is not an easy decision,
but it is one
that I have to make.
I'm sorry.
This whole...
Gale situation-
he's- he's just
not working out.
Yes. Now.
It- It may sound unorthodox,
but I think our first-
best option...
Is Jesse Pinkman.
Hello?
It-
No, look. Th-There's-
There's a- a shorthand
that exists between us-
experience together
at a level that, quite frankly,
I- I'm just never going
to reach with Gale.
Look, Mr. Fring,
when I accepted your offer,
I was told the lab is mine.
And I know best how to run it.
Thank you.
Yes, I will. I will.
Okay. Good-bye.
Listen, something's come up.
And, uh, I think
it's a good opportunity.
There's been a job opening.
I need a new lab assistant.
I already did my time.
Why don't you just go
get yourself a monkey?
I don't want a monkey.
I want you.
Oh, gee, thanks.
Well, not interested.
I got my own thing going on.
Nice try saving your
a- head brother-in-law.
That's not why I'm here, Jesse.
There's more.
It's more than an assistant.
Partners.
We'll be partners again.
Split everything 50-50,
just like before.
$1.5 million each.
No.
I don't think you heard-
I've heard you fine.
I said no.
Let me understand this.
You're turning down
$11/2 million.
I am not turning down
the money.
I am turning down you.
You get it?
I want nothing to do with you.
Ever since I met you,
everything
I have ever cared about
is gone...
Ruined, turned to shit,
dead, ever since I hooked up
with the great Heisenberg.
I have never been more alone.
I have nothing!
No one!
All right?
It's all gone!
Get it?
No. No, no.
Why-
Why would you get it?
What do you even care
as long as you get
what you want?
Right?
You don't give a shit
about me.
You said I was no good.
I'm nothing!
Why would you want me?
Huh?
You said my meth
is inferior, right?
Right?
Hey! You said my cook
was garbage!
Hey, screw you, man!
Your meth is good, Jesse.
As good as mine.
Yeah.
50-50.
Yes. 50-50.
Okay.
Partners.
Good.
This is the statement
you want to give?
Yes, sir.
Hank, you don't
have to do this.
No, I-
I do.
I'm good.
So we understand
if we write it up like that,
you'll sign it.
That's the way it happened.
I accept the consequences.
In the light of these facts...
As of this moment,
you're suspended without pay.
I have to ask you to hand over
your badge and your gun.
Yes, sir.
Schrader.
Hold up.
Yes, sir?
I just want
to tell you something.
And to be clear,
you didn't hear it from me.
I don't want you
to get your hopes up,
but the word in the pipeline is
Pinkman isn't pressing charges.
Why not?
Who the hell knows?
Maybe you have
a guardian angel.
It went fine.
Well, fine means what-
means what it means. Yeah.
I'll, uh...
I'll tell you all about it
when I get home, okay?
Yeah. It's-
Yeah, it's just-
I don't know, baby.
I just think-
I think we may be okay.
Yeah.
Okay. I love you, too.
Schrader.
I need you
to listen
very carefully.
Two men are coming
to kill you.
Come again?
They're approaching
your car.
You have one minute.
I don't get the gag,
jerk off. Who is this?
They're coming.
Hello.
Hey, Li-
Hey, Gomie, this is Hank.
I don't know what that
call's supposed to be,
but it's dumb
even by your standards,
so call me when you get this.
Aah!
No.
Sync by honeybunny
www. addic7ed. com