[sighs]
Yo, I thought I was going
to see some, like, vaginas.
I didn't say she actually
painted vaginas.
I said
some of her paintings
looked like vaginas.
Uh, seriously?
[whispers] Not even close.
[chuckles]
Georgia O'Keeffe painted
all kinds of stuff.
Huh. Everyday items,
her surroundings.
Some of it evoked
an erotic nature.
[snickers]
It's who she was.
Not like any vagina I ever saw.
This chick have medical issues?
This particular painting--
Mmm.
...is of a door.
Any other doors
we can check out?
Like, real ones or...
[groans]
You know,
I-I-I don't get it.
Why would anyone paint
a picture of a door
over and over again,
like, dozens of times?
But it wasn't the same.
Uh, yeah, it was.
It was the same subject, but
it was different every time.
The light was different.
Her mood was different.
She saw something new
every time she painted it.
And that's not psycho to you?
Well, then, why should we
do anything more than once?
Should I just smoke
this one cigarette?
Maybe we should only have sex
once if it's the same thing.
Whoa, no--
Should we just watch
one sunset?
Or live just one day.
Because it's new every time.
Each time, it's
a different experience.
Okay, fine.
I guess the cow skull
pictures were cool,
but a door?
I will say it again.
[chuckles] A door.
[snores] [chuckles]
Why not a door?
Sometimes you get fixated
on something,
and you might not even get why.
You open yourself up
and go with the flow,
wherever the universe
takes you.
[snickers]
Okay, so the universe
took her to a door,
and she got all obsessed
with it
and just had to paint it
20 times until it was perfect.
No, I wouldn't say that.
Nothing's perfect.
Yeah?
Well...
Oh, yeah.
Some things.
[giggles]
Oh, that was so sweet,
I think I threw up
in my mouth a little bit.
[laughs]
You can't admit just
for once that I'm right.
Come on.
That O'Keeffe lady
kept trying over and over
until that stupid door
was perfect.
No. That door was her home,
and she loved it.
To me, that's about making
that feeling last.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
[machine whirring]
All right, here we go.
You ready?
[labored breathing]
Come on, give me a step.
Give me one step.
[exhales]
Nope.
Nope, that's it.
Take me up.
You can do this, Hank.
Come on, it's supposed to hurt.
Pain is weakness
leaving your body.
Pain is my foot
in your ass, Marie.
Hey, if you can get your leg
up that high, I say go for it.
Take me up. Take me up.
All right, coffee break.
We're gonna let you rest for a minute,
and then we're gonna try it again.
Never mind about your coffee break.
Take me up.
I'm done. I'm done.
[grunts] [machine whirrs]
Come on, Uncle Hank.
You can do it.
How else are you going
to get out of here?
Don't you have any friends?
I mean Jesus, find
something better to do.
I don't need everyone
staring at me
hanging here
like a camel's ball sack.
Hank, he just wants
to be supportive.
It's all right.
All right, I'll be right back.
Okay?
I'll be right back.
You gonna get me out
of here sometime today?
[machine whirring]
Honey--
We got our first bill,
and, you know,
if you're still insistent--
I am.
Prepare yourself.
[whispers] Yeah.
They're gonna start coming in
weekly like that, so...
Okay.
You're sure you can do this?
Yeah.
[scale beeps]
I'll do that.
What the hell, man?
What, I can't work a scale now?
This is bullshit.
Just say it.
Just say the words.
You think I'm stealing.
Shh.
[Group leader]
Walk with who you are.
That was a phrase my sponsor
used to use with me
back when I first started
coming to meetings.
It's probably just a different
way of saying "Be yourself."
Right?
But this idea of "walk"
also tells me
that I have to move forward.
Always good advice,
at least for me.
I see we have some
new people here at group,
a couple new faces.
Let's see some hands.
First time?
Great. Welcome.
Maybe we can go around,
introduce ourselves.
Say whatever's on your mind.
How about you?
You want to start us off?
[clears throat]
Yeah. My name is Andrea...
and, uh...
We don't bite.
No judgments.
You can be as open and honest
as you want to be.
Honestly, I don't
want to be here.
All right.
Fair enough.
Who else had their hand up?
Hey. 'Sup?
My name's Jesse.
Why, hello.
My name is Brandon.
And this is, I believe, Peter?
Right. I'm Peter.
How are you?
Look, I just wanted
to give you a heads up.
It's gonna get a little
slower smuggling product
with Grandpa Anus
watching every move I make.
But don't worry.
I'll keep it flowing.
Great. Right on.
Yeah.
So how's it selling?
Mad volume?
Yeah. It's, uh...
You know, it's, um...
It's not so good.
What do you mean?
How much have you sold?
I sold a teenth.
One teenth?
That's it?
Yeah.
To who?
To him.
Look, it's not so easy
selling to these people.
They're here trying
to better themselves.
Yeah, there's, like,
positivity and stuff
going on here.
I'm out risking my ass
to get product for you two,
and you're too pussy to sell?
You're pathetic.
You know what?
I want it back. All of it.
I'll sell it myself.
Come on, man.
Don't be like that.
Selling to these people, it's
like shooting a baby in the face.
It's not natural.
Yeah, Jesse,
it's not easy like you think.
I'll show you exactly
how easy it is.
Oh, hey. Sorry.
No. Go ahead.
It's Andrea, right?
Yeah.
Hey, um, my name's Jesse,
and, uh, I don't really
want to be here, either.
Oh, um--
Sorry.
[chuckles]
Thanks.
Aunt Marie's coming to dinner?
No.
Your dad is.
[Walter, Jr.
] How'd you get her to sleep so quick?
Are you that boring?
I'm comforting.
I'm a comforting presence.
[whispers] There we go.
Shh, shh.
Hey, so check it out.
Huh?
See what that means?
Check out the date.
Next Thursday
is officially six months
that I have had my learner's,
which means I can
get my provisional
and start driving by myself.
Since when? You don't
turn 16 for two more months.
It doesn't matter.
It's a provisional.
Look it up. They changed
the law, like, 10 years ago.
Oh, yeah? Well,
I didn't vote for that.
Doesn't matter
if you voted for it.
It's the law.
So both of you start thinking
about what kind of car
you want to buy me.
Mmm.
I think I'd be good with either
an old IROC or a 'Stang.
Ah, a 'Stang.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
How about something with
playing cards in the spokes?
Makes a nice
motor-y sound, you know?
[imitates motor clicking]
[chuckles]
[both laughing]
Yeah, yeah. You're not
gonna get off that easy.
Well, I-- I think
that this is, um--
We should probably table
this discussion for later.
Your dad and I have
a couple things
we need to talk about, so--
Okay.
A 1971 Mach 1 fastback
in Grabber Lime
with a shaker hood.
Mmm.
'Stang.
I want to write that down
so I don't forget.
Oh, darn it. No pencil!
[groans] [laughing]
What is Ice Station Zebra
Associates?
It's a loan-out.
It's fine.
Whose loan-out?
It's fine. Really.
I...have a guy.
Okay.
Um, does your guy know
the tax code and regulations
in New Mexico?
'Cause there's very
specific paperwork
that has to be submitted
quarterly on this.
Yes. My guy is a top...
guy.
Who is he?
Uh.
What's his name?
What are his qualifications?
Walt, this money has
to be unimpeachable
when it reaches Hank and Marie.
And it is. It will be.
But how do I know that?
I mean, apparently, you can't
even tell me the man's name.
Oh. Jesus.
Skyler, do you
really want to know?
I mean, do you really
want to know?
Really?
[man coughing]
[coughing continues]
[door closes]
[Saul]
Hello. Welcome.
What a pleasure it is
to have you.
I'm just gonna call you
Skyler, if that's okay.
It's a lovely name.
Reminds me
of a big beautiful sky.
Walt never told me
how lucky he was--
prior to recent
unfortunate events.
Clearly, his taste in women
is the same as his taste
in lawyers--
only the very best
with just the right
amount of dirty.
[laughs] That's a joke.
That's a joke.
It's funny because you are
so clearly very classy.
Here. Please, sit down.
So Walt tells me that you have
some concerns I can alleviate.
Uh, yes, I do.
I have...
concerns.
If we're going
to go down this road,
and clearly we are
for the sake of
my brother-in-law.
I've heard about him.
He's an American hero.
At any rate,
I need some assurances
that we're gonna go
about this in a manner
that is extremely safe
and cautious.
Fair enough. I'll walk you
through the process.
First step is something
we like to call
money laundering, all right?
Take your money, represented
by, say, these jelly beans.
You know, I'm a bookkeeper-- Then I--
...so I actually know
what money laundering is.
Uh-huh.
Well...
Yeah.
And, as with most things,
the devil is in the details.
So to begin with,
what are we saying is
the source of this money?
That's simple.
Walt here actually
came up with a great story
about gambling winnings.
Blackjack, right?
Some card counting?
Well, actually,
that was Skyler's idea.
[clears throat] Well,
you grow more gorgeous
by the minute.
Well, there you have it.
I'll generate
false currency
transaction reports
out the wazoo.
As well as
the necessary W-2Gs.
I know a couple casino managers
who will jump at the chance
to report false losses.
It's a win-win for everyone.
Yeah, but you can't
sell that for very long.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Way ahead of you.
We declare just enough
so as not to arouse suspicion,
then Walt's one-time winnings
become seed money
for an investment.
Investment in what?
Drum roll please.
Wait for it.
Laser tag.
7,000 square feet
of rollicking fun
in the heart of northern
Bernlillo County.
Laser tag?
Yeah. There's guns
and glow lights and--
Kids wear the vests,
and they have to
split into teams--
Right. No, actually,
I know what it is.
It's just that in relation to Walt, it's--
I mean, it doesn't
make any sense.
It makes more sense
than you two being together.
I'm still trying to figure out
how that happened.
Do you even know Walt?
I mean...
how would he of all people
buy a laser tag business?
It doesn't add up.
It adds up perfectly.
Walt's a scientist.
Scientists love lasers.
Plus they got
bumper boats, so--
Hey, everybody.
Walt suddenly decided
to invest in laser tag.
Just out of the blue.
Really? That's what we're
supposed to tell people,
our family, our friends,
the government?
Let me bottom line
this for you.
You don't need to be involved.
Because I've been doing this
for a lot of years--
successfully,
believe it or not--
without your help.
So thank you for stopping by.
You want a beer or something?
Or something.
What do you mean?
[laughs]
Like beer.
I'm clean out of anything else.
Even if I wasn't,
we're not supposed to.
Yeah.
I've heard it over
and over
and over again.
You know, don't you think
it's ridiculous
that society says beer is okay
and a little hit
of something sweet is wrong?
I mean...
what's the point of shutting
yourself off completely
from something that
lifts you off the ground?
I spend so much energy
fighting the urge not to use,
and I feel like crap
because of it.
I know. It's just...
What?
I can't get caught using again.
See, the thing is...
[whispering] not to get caught.
You ever try that blue stuff
that's going around?
[exhales]
Just a little gas in the tank,
and suddenly...
everything is interesting.
Man, I wish I can make
that feeling last.
Like I said,
I got nothing here.
What if I could get some?
[door opens]
Mommy! Mommy!
Hey, B!
Oh, your Nana
brought you home early.
Grandma, I thought
you were keeping Brock today.
I was.
Then I saw your car.
I thought you had a meeting.
I did, but we changed the time.
Grandma, this is Jesse.
He's from the meeting.
He's like a sponsor.
Jesse, this is Grandma.
[speaks Spanish]
[speaking Spanish]
Jesse, this is Brock.
So, you, uh--
You have a kid, huh?
What's up?
Brock, huh?
That's a cool name.
Here.
Give it up.
Brock is almost 6.
You okay with kids?
What? Yeah, he's cool.
Okay, Brock is gonna
go play in his room
while the big people talk.
He's gonna go play with his
Legos and his cars
Say "Bye, Jesse."
Bye, Jesse.
Safe and cautious,
that's all I'm asking,
and that man is neither.
I'll admit, he comes across
like a circus clown.
But he actually knows
what he's doing.
Safe and cautious is you
not being involved
in this at all.
Well, it's a little
late on that.
This is what happens when you decide
to pay our bills with drug money.
Skyler, this isn't just about
what happened before.
My involvement
in this is ongoing.
Understand?
I can't just quit.
I have something of a contract.
It's all very safe
and professional
and structured.
I can't simply quit.
Where are you going?
If you're gonna launder money,
Walt, at least do it right.
You worked here four years.
It's a business you understand.
It's a story
people will believe.
Not laser tag. This.
This is what we buy.
You.
This is what you buy.
[muttering]
Hey, uh, Jesse, right?
Brandon. Peter.
How goes it?
Hanging in there?
Please, just--
Dumb ass.
Sorry, man. I was trying
to keep it on the DL.
So you and that girl,
you do the deed yet?
Do what?
You know, sell to her.
What are you two
even doing here?
What do you mean?
You can't get
your nut up to sell.
What's the point
of even coming?
Homie, I'm on, like, step 5.
Deuce, yo.
I'm catching up.
Whatever.
Later.
Dude needs to come
into the fold.
[Badger] Yep.
Oh, you know,
I have magical powers.
You want to see?
Ready?
That's not real.
[laughs] [whispers] It is real.
All right, do you want
to see something that's real?
Look at this.
Watch this.
Ready?
You like that?
That's science and stuff.
Makes it do that.
Do it again.
Let Jesse eat
his dinner, Brock.
It's okay.
Want to see it again?
Could you do a trick
with firecrackers?
Firecrackers.
You know, I don't have
any firecrackers on me.
Who does tricks
with firecrackers?
Tomás.
Tomás does tricks
with firecrackers, huh?
Who's Tomás?
He's my kid brother.
Yeah?
And we don't talk about him.
Come on.
Eat your food, Brock.
[Jesse] Can I have a chip?
I'm gonna steal your chip.
[Brock] Hey, that's mine.
[Saul] That's it?
That's what you want to buy?
[Walt] People will
believe it at least.
[chuckles]
I worked here for four years.
Wax on, wax off.
Was that you?
Hey, how come you guys always get
with the air freshener, huh?
I explicitly say
I want no air freshener,
and every time I drive away
smelling like an Alpine w3-- house.
All due respect, I don't see it.
So I vote no.
Makes a better story
than your laser tag.
Is that you talking
or Yoko Ono?
She has a point.
It makes more sense
that I invest right here.
Based on her years
of experience
in money laundering, I suppose.
Let me tell you something.
If you're committed enough,
you can make any story work.
I once convinced a woman
that I was Kevin Costner.
And it worked
because I believed it.
It has nothing to do
with the story.
Besides, this dump
isn't gonna work
because it doesn't have
a Danny.
Okay?
There's no Danny here.
What in God's name is a Danny?
Danny runs the laser tag.
Danny is the guy
who had a vision.
Where others saw a dirt lot,
he saw black lights,
rubber aliens,
teenagers running around
with ray guns, right?
It was like Bugsy Siegel
in the desert.
And when the stock market
took a shit
and Danny got into trouble,
he went searching for exactly
the type of situation
that we're offering.
Danny will look the other way
to keep his dream afloat.
In other words, Danny
can be trusted completely.
That guy-- the guy with the
eyebrows that won't quit--
is he a Danny?
[no audible dialogue]
You buy this place,
all you got is a big building
that squirts water.
You got no Danny here.
You want to stay for dinner?
Yeah.
Thanks.
What time is it?
Early still.
So...
[chuckles] What?
I thought maybe,
if you're holding,
we can do something.
What?
You know, that blue stuff
you were talking about?
Maybe you had a line on some.
Wait. Whoa. What?
I thought you said
the kid is coming home.
Yeah, in a few hours.
And you seriously
want to get high?
I don't know what you're
getting so pissed about.
You're the one who
brought it up the other day.
Yeah, that was before
I found out you got a kid.
What kind of mother are you?
What?
You heard me.
What kind of mom gets wasted
with a little kid
to take care of?
Nobody can say
I don't take care of my son.
You gonna come
in my house and judge me?
Like you got no responsibility,
so it's okay
for you to get high.
Look, I-- What do you know about me?
I take care of my baby.
I'll do anything for him.
The day Brock was born,
I swore...
I won't let what happened
to Tomás happen to my son.
I'll die first.
Sorry. I--
I just--
Look, I'll get out
of here if you want.
That's what you want
to do, then go.
It's not what I want.
Look, I was out of line
talking about that stuff.
We both were.
You're right.
I don't know what
you've been through.
You can tell me if you want.
This whole neighborhood
is run by gangs.
They run the drugs,
control the streets.
And they sort of took Tomás in.
No dad around.
8 years old,
they got Tomás slinging.
Part of some crew.
Then, when he was 10...
for some initiation
or something...
they made him kill somebody.
I heard the rumors.
I didn't believe it at first.
[exhales]
But then I saw him,
like, a weekater.
He told me, yeah, he did it.
They gave Tomás a gun.
Gave him a choice.
Him or some dude.
So he did it.
Told me all about it
like it was nothing.
Who did he say he killed?
Some dealer...
[smacks lips]
from some outside crew.
Right around the corner
from here,
over off the Central.
Just rode up on his bike
and shot him.
Off the Central?
Like, over by the train tracks?
When was this?
A few months back.
What else did he tell you?
He shot the guy
right through the neck.
Shot him dead.
Just because he was
working the wrong corner.
It won't happen again.
Not to my son.
[monitor beeping]
Guess what.
People who say "Guess what"
and then actually
expect you to guess--
I hate those people.
Well, I just heard
about a certain patient
named Schrader-comma-Hank
who is going to be released
at the end of this week.
Isn't that fantastic?
Are they planning on rolling me
out the front door at least,
or they'll put me
on a greased plank
and, uh, slide me
out the window?
Hey.
Listen, I don't care
what any damned
insurance company thinks.
I'm not leaving here
until I'm well.
Hank, this isn't
about insurance.
I've talked to everybody,
and they all say
that you are healthy
enough to go home.
Oh, I'm healthy
enough, huh? Yeah.
Hank, you get stronger
every day.
You don't need to be
in a hospital.
In this condition, yeah, I do.
You'll be just as comfortable at home
as you are here.
You'll have all the same equipment--
All the same equipment?
What--
The equipment--
...does that mean?
...that you have here
that you need.
Short term.
You'll do your PT at home,
and it'll be great
because you'll be home.
Wait till you see the bedroom.
I had them move the plasma in.
I know that's how
you always wanted it,
and you only had to get shot
to get it, right?
I got you a new bed.
A hospital bed?
Well--
You put a hospital bed
in my bedroom?
Hank, you'll be home.
You get that out of my house.
You hear me, Marie?
Today.
Hank--
I leave this hospital
when I walk out of here,
you understand?
And not before.
[Skyler scoffs] What's a Danny?
Danny is an accomplice,
someone who's in on the scheme,
who knows about laundering,
who's paid to look
the other way.
Now, while I agree with you
that laser tag is a hard sell,
without a Danny,
the car wash
isn't really an option.
And he can't get you
another Danny
to run the car wash?
Easier said than done,
if we're looking
for someone trustworthy.
What about me?
What about you?
Me.
I'll be the Danny.
No. No. No, Skyler.
That is not a good idea.
I'm perfectly capable
of managing a small business.
A legal business, not this.
Who else could we trust?
No.
Walt.
I'm in this.
And if I'm in it,
I'm going to do it right.
You are not in this.
You are not--
We're married.
How am I not in this?
We are not married,
Skyler. We're divorced.
Right?
I never actually got around
to filing the papers.
Married couples
can't be compelled
to testify against one another.
So there's that.
Jesse!
Jesse.
Respirator.
Right.
[phone rings]
[ring]
Yes?
Uh-huh.
Yes. All right.
Okay.
I'll be there.
What was that?
An invitation.
[doorbell rings]
Ah. Walter.
You're right on time.
Please, come in.
I hope you like paila marina.
It's a fancy name
for fish stew.
It sounds like a cliché,
but indeed, it's just like
my mother used to make it.
Come on.
You can help me cook.
This is a Chilean dish
that I love,
but I never get to make it.
The kids won't eat it.
But, uh...
you know how that is.
Sure.
Do you mind?
Would you slice the garlic?
Oh.
Very thin.
Why did you invite me here?
We're working together.
Why not break bread together?
Now the garlic.
Mm.
Mmm.
It always amazes me
the way the senses work
in connection to memory.
I mean, this stew is simply
an amalgam of ingredients.
Taken separately,
these ingredients alone
don't remind me of anything.
Hmm.
[chuckling]
Not very much at all.
But, in this
precise combination,
the smell of this meal instantly--
it brings me back to my childhood.
How is that possible?
Basically, it all takes place
in the hippocampus.
Neural connections are formed.
The senses make the neurons
express signals
that go right back to
the same part of the brain
as before,
where memory is stored.
That's, uh, something
called relational memory.
Uh...
don't quote me on that.
I-- I'm rusty on my biology.
That's very interesting.
Walter,
I would like to help you,
if I could.
Help me how?
Well, when I first started out,
I made a lot of mistakes.
[sigh]
More than I care to admit.
I wish I'd had
someone to advise me--
[chuckle]
because this life of ours,
it can overwhelm.
You are a wealthy man now.
And one must learn to be rich.
To be poor anyone can manage.
What advice do you have for me?
Never make
the same mistake twice.
Hey.
What's up?
You, uh, you Tomás?
Heard you were the man.
Yeah? What you want?
Crystal.
You think you could hook me up?
300.
For a teenth?
Shit, come on, yo.
300.
Tch.
Hey, what's up?
Hey.
[whistles]
Bounce.
[breathing heavily]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com