Last time my friend,
Chelsea, set me up
with one of her friends,
I had to get a tetanus shot.
But Molly
is different.
Hey, you know
what would be fun?
Call Chelsea,
tell her I stood you up
and... pretend
you're crying.
Spencer,
I couldn't do that.
Oh, come on.
I can't.
I've never done a practical
joke in my entire life.
Get out.
You've never
called up a store
and asked for, uh,
Oliver Clothesoff?
Make Apeepee?
Never.
Ever, ever.
Come on.
What are you
doing?
No guts, no glory.
No, no, no, no-
Here we go.
What are you
doing?
It's ringing.
I'm nervous,
I'm gonna pee.
Hello?
Chelsea,
it's Molly.
Listen, I am,
I am so sorry
that I set you up
with him, okay?
But my intentions
were good
and you need to think
of Spenny as a trial run
and a way of getting
you back out there.
Okay, do you
forgive me?
I can't fib,
I'm sorry!
Chelsea!
Yeah?
We're having
a great time!
What?
Yeah!
He's, um, kind
and sweet
and funny.
Ask to see his ID.
Do you want
to speak to him?
No, not really.
Chelsea!
Spenny, what
did you do to her?
Did you spike
her tea?
I knew I shouldn't have
told you she doesn't drink!
Molly is a sweet
and vulnerable girl,
do not hurt her!
Chels, relax,
everything's going great.
You might have made
a match in heaven here.
Oh, I wanna
believe you, I do,
I really do, but like,
she's my only friend
other than you.
so I swear to fu-
What'd she say?
Over the moon.
So am I.
Me too.
Ugh!!!
I wonder if we'll like
the same appetizers.
I bet we do.
You know what?
Okay, on the count of 3
we're both gonna say
what we're gonna
order, out loud...
If we pick the same
thing, I am gonna die.
Um-
Can you excuse
me for just a sec?
Okay!
You can think
about it.
Huh.
If it isn't
the devil's spawn.
Last time I heard that voice
it was begging for mercy.
Hello, Spencer.
What did you order
for dinner?
Entrails from
your last victim?
Run along.
This is
my social time.
You know, if I had a
sledgehammer, I'd smash
that rotten divorce
lawyer skull of yours.
I'll give you five
minutes in the hallway,
then I file
a restraining order.
Where do you get off
ruining my dinner date?
Your dinner date?
Where do you get off
ruining my life?
You said things about me
that were unconscionable!
You lied about me
in court!
I was hired by your
wife to do a job!
Do you have a fetish
for watching me sob?
Truthfully, crushing you
in court gave me
a power rush
so intense,
I actually had
an orgasm.
You did?
♪
What's
happening?
♪
You destroyed
me in court!
I hate you,
divorce lawyer!
Ahhhhhhh!
I hate you!
That feels good!
CRASH!
Oh, my god!
Oh, I picked
my appetizer!
Did you
pick yours?
Uh...
Are you okay?
Yeah, great.
Good!
You look rosy.
My name is Spenny.
I've been accused of being
an "Emotionally Stunted Manchild".
incapable of having
a functional relationship.
And it's all because
I want to find love.
Is that such a crime?
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Chelsea, I had dirty sex with my
ex-wife's lawyer, in a bathroom.
You're my best friend.
Try not to be
judgemental.
Are you an animal?
In human form?
I don't know
what happened.
I hate that lawyer.
I hate that lawyer with
every fiber of my being!
When Molly was left
at the altar ten months ago,
I'm the one who pushed
her into dating again.
You know, to build
her self-esteem.
She didn't want to,
I insisted!
It was like being
caught up in a hurricane.
I was powerless!
Did the hurricane blow
your fly down too?
You can't tell Molly.
Don't tell Molly.
Ugh!
Well, I, I can't
tell her!
I'm implicated
in this!
Chelsea!
I have to go
into hiding.
Spencer I'm going
to need a DNA sample,
a hair will do.
You know,
just to make sure
once and for all that
you're really mine.
I don't want to have this
conversation again, please.
Don't you want to
put your mind at ease?
I found a new lab.
I have real
problems right now.
I need to get in
to see Schneiderman.
Oh, honey.
You can't just
walk in off the street
and see Schneiderman.
Tell me about it.
I'm not gonna tell
you about it,
you're not
a psychiatrist.
I may not even
be your mother.
Okay, I'll tell ya
what happened.
The other night I was
at a restaurant on a date
with this girl, Molly,
who I absolutely adore.
I look across the room
and I see another woman
who I despise,
I hate her guts.
The next thing I know,
I'm in the washroom
having sex
with her
and the sex was
unbelievable.
I feel terrible.
You had
revenge sex.
If having great sex
with someone you loathe
is revenge sex,
I had it all right.
Yeah, and you're
dying to do it again.
Blah, blah, blah.
What are you?
Schneiderman's secretary?
This girl, Molly,
she's the real deal.
I could marry this girl,
have children with her.
I really think you should
be more supportive,
so please, get me into
see Schneiderman!
Are you kidding?
I brought him revenge
sex twenty years ago.
Now maybe if the girl
was you sister.
Isn't
snuggling good?
It's terrific.
People jump
right into sex
and overlook the joy
of intimate snuggling.
Yeah, they do that
quite a bit.
When we do
finally have sex,
it'll have so much
more meaning.
There's no rush,
right?
No, there's
no rush.
Sex is just a... teeny part
of a relationship.
Sometimes I don't
think about it at all.
Me too.
Say it again!
You embarrassed
me in court, you dirty lawyer!
Ugh...
Well, if it isn't the
quivering little man-child.
You back for more
punishment?
Look, this has to stop,
whatever this is.
What's wrong?
You scared?
I'm not scared;
I just want you to know
I'm in a relationship that
actually means something!
So why
are you here?
I'm here to
tell you something,
let me be
clear about this,
I hate your guts!
That's what I was trying
to tell you the night
we had the best
sex of our lives.
Your life maybe.
What?
Could have
been better.
Really?
Oh, I know what
you're trying to do.
Well it's not
gonna happen.
You're looking at
a sexual brick wall.
Sex should be
about love, not hate.
It's awful.
That's why they
call it making love.
Don't you think?
Oh, what the hell.
I hate you!
I'm going to show you
just how much I hate you!
You know,
ruined my life!
Spencer, I am in heaven
when I am with you.
Oh-
I'm in heaven when
I'm with you too, Molly.
You know, I thought
when I was stood up
at the altar, that all
men were bastards.
But not you.
Ha, not me-
Say it again!
Sick lawyer,
I hate you!
I know,
I know! Say it again!
Hi!!!
Aw, look at this!
You look terrible.
Oh, I haven't been
sleeping thanks to you.
So...
You guys
are still together?
Chelsea, Spenny
is a great big
hunk of goodness
and he's all mine.
Thanks to you.
Oh, don't
pin it on me.
Aw, she's
so selfless.
So you gonna
tell her?
We've got
good news.
You have news?
We're getting
married!
Oh, my god!
I'm so excited,
I'm gonna go call
mom and tell her.
Oh, go call
your mom-
Say hi to her
for me, please.
I am crazy
about her!
Have you flipped
your lid?
You asked her
to marry you?
You've known her
for a few days
and in that time
you had sex
with your
ex-wife's lawyer!
Only two times.
Twice!
Twiceish.
Maybe it was 3 times,
but it doesn't matter.
Important thing
is I've worked it out
of my system,
like a head cold.
Since when did you
take up smoking?
Since I started
over-eating!
Oh gosh!
Mom is so excited!
Hi, Midge-Midge!
It's your future
son-in-law!
He's so cute.
Oh, Chels!
You're so happy
for us you're crying!
I am.
And more
exciting news.
Mom is so excited,
she said she wants
this wedding to be even
bigger than the last one.
She's gonna re-mortgage
her house again!
You think you can
end it just like that,
you spineless
gape-jaw?
You don't have the
power to end this.
You're too weak,
you haven't got the guts!
I'm doing the right thing.
I know everything
about you.
I'm engaged to be married
to an angel,
and I don't need this
she-beast in my life.
And how you hid
underneath the bed
during lightening
storms,
I humiliated you
in court!
I want to tear
your testicles off
and eat them!
You're wet.
And crinkly.
Don't over boil them.
They get mushy.
Now this...
Is gonna look beautiful
on your big day.
You know tan
is the new white?
Is it really?
Okay.
So am I gonna get an
intatation to the wedding?
Um-
We're thinking of putting
you in charge of parking.
Yeah-
Well, you know,
I'd be honored.
Are ya gonna miss Spenny
when he moves out, Phil?
Well-
Maybe just
a little bit.
Oh, dear...
He's really upset.
He's an idiot.
Oh, Spencer,
go check on him.
Phil, are you
crying?
It was so
sudden!
I mean, you didn't give
me any, any warning.
Why would I
give you warning?
You're my neighbor.
Is there any way
you could get a house
with a, with a
finished basement?
No!
Do you wanna maybe,
want to pencil in
weekly BBQ's
or something?
Phil, I'm starting
a new chapter
in my life
with Molly.
So you're all finished
with the revenge se-
Sssshhh!
Quiet!
l l right.
Ya slayed
the beast?
Yes, the beast
is dead.
Okay, it's,
it's all about Molly,
and, and not about the
beast anymore, no-
No more-
All those beasts
out there.
What other beasts?
If you think about it,
we all get slighted
by lots and lots
of people
in our lives.
And there are
so many instances
where we just
want to get even.
You know?
But, hey,
you don't need
anymore of that
crazy, wild sex stuff.
Ssshh!
Quiet!
Spenny, I love you!
Other beasts!
Yeah, well you know where
you can shove your shirt.
Spenny!
Look, I can't get your
refund from the lady
at the dry cleaner,
she says that the stain
was on the shirt when
you dropped it off-
Jessica, I'm doing inventory,
I don't have time for this.
It's just a shirt,
who cares?
Just a shirt?
You're gonna let her
treat you like that?
treat you like dirt?
She's treating me
like dirt?
Hell yeah she's
treating you like dirt!
She took your money,
she ruined your shirt
and then she acts like
she's doing you a favour?
She took my money.
She took your money!
She ruined my shirt.
She ruined your shirt!
And she won't let you
park out in front,
not even on a Sunday!
That's it!
Yeah!
You get that refund!
Dry cleaner: No refund,
store credit only!
You ruined
my shirt!
I want
a refund!!!
Spen, I'm sorry I'm late,
but I had a faaabulous session
with Dr. Schniederman.
He's not a clock-watcher
like the others.
Did you talk to him
about my problem?
Yeah...
Didn't grab him.
Oh, come on.
Didn't grab him?
Revenge sex
is killing me!
I'll tell ya what
I'm gonna do for you,
my dentist,
Dr. Brickman,
loves a
good story.
You want me to get
psychiatric help
from a dentist?!
Well, he's more
easily impressed
than Dr. Schniederman
and you end up with
a nice toothbrush.
My jeweler,
Rakov!
Yeah, but you have
to buy a watch...
Ow, ow, ow!
So where are
you at right now?
Still with
the lawyer?
Uh uh, I'm done
with the lawyer.
I've moved onto
fair-weather friends,
broken promises
and people
who said they'd help
me move and didn't.
Interesting.
So, is there any
hope for me?
Yeah, there's
always hope.
This impending marriage
with Molly though...
That's really
bumpin' me.
Hey!
Breaking up with Molly
isn't an option, okay?
Okay, okay-
Just let me
think this over.
Wider.
Relax your jaw.
You're gonna have to
hold off on that wedding.
Why?
Revenge sex is
like an abscess,
you have to let the
anger drain from you.
And the only way
to do that is-
You know what.
Have sex with every
woman that crossed me?
It's the only way.
You're lookin' good for
someone who never flosses.
Make an appointment
on the way out.
Pick a colour.
Yellow.
Interesting.
Spenny on phone: Hello?
Arlene Sheposnik?
It's Spenny.
Hey, yeah.
No, I'm good.
Um, do you remember
in high school
when you poured milk
all over my head
in the cafeteria?
I'd like to get together
and talk about that.
Okay, great.
I'll call you later.
Great lead, Jessica,
way to go.
Hey, I got
somethin', Spenny.
Here's a girl you
went to college with
who dumped you
for the football player.
Sarah Listerman
is married with kids.
What's wrong
with you, Phil?!
Sorry, Spenny.
Do I have to go over
the ground rules again?
We're here to get even
with these people,
not ruin their lives!
Okay, but, like,
what if they don't
want you
to bang them?
They're gonna
wanna bang me.
Revenge sex is a ride
you don't pass up.
Do you want both women
and men on the list?
That is so dumb!
I'm not even gonna
entertain that question!
I know it looks bad,
but I'm not having sex
with multiple partners
for my own pleasure!
I'm doing it to save my
relationship with Molly.
Yeah, Molly's really
lucky to have you.
I know, she is.
Yeah, yeah-
You're both pervs.
Good luck!
Are you the Sarah Lynn
who published
my love letters in the
school newspaper,
earning me the nickname
of Prince Wanker?
I think you know
why I'm here.
May I come in?
Thank you.
Sarah Lynn-
Excellent, Sarah Lynn...
Are you the Patsy Beaker
who convinced me
that my economics
professor wanted me
to sneak into her
bedroom at night,
getting me expelled
from college?
I think you know why
I'm here, may I come in?
Thank you.
Ah, Pasty Beaker, got.
Okay, Pauline...
Sarah, Sarah,
Sarah, Sarah-
Ah, oh.
knock-knock-knock
Are you Harriet Woodsley,
the lunch lady
from Crestview High
who accused me
of pinching her ass
when the reverse was true?
I think you know
why I'm here.
May I come in?
I got the DNA results.
What DNA?
I had Brickman
do a cheek swab.
You set me up
with your dentist
to steal a
DNA sample?!
I couldn't help it,
I really had to know!
And apparently
you're mine.
Really shouldn't
have gotten rid
of all those
childhood photographs.
It doesn't
make sense.
I'm still feeling
the pull.
I went through
everybody on this list.
Is it possible that
I'm missing someone?
Does the name
Lisa Ungerman ring a bell?
Should it?
Think back
to that moment
in every boy's life,
your first time.
♪
You've got
a weenis!
What a horrible
memory.
She called it
a weenis.
I have to find
Lisa Ungerman.
You're not gonna get past it
until you even the score.
What if she
laughs again?
Yeah, see that's what
stimeys me about that.
Your father had a
good-sized bologna.
And the men on
my side of the family
pack some
major pipe.
It just
doesn't add up.
Here-
Try a new lab.
Uh huh...
♪
knock-knock-knock
Can I help you?
I think I have the
wrong place, uh-
Spenny?
Lisa?
I knew this day
would come.
♪
Molly, here I come.
Ah!
Lisa Ungerman,
very good.
♪
I've got some great news.
I like good news.
I made a list of all the
people I have to have
revenge sex with.
All I have to do
is get Chelsea on side now
and put this behind me.
ea: By the time
he started having
revenge sex, the train
had left the station.
There was nothing
I could do to stop him.
Well, that's not
exactly what happened.
You. Say. Nothing.
So, my fiancé,
who you set
me up with,
was having sex
with half the city
while I was buying
wedding invitations?
I know, I should have
told you sooner,
I'm sorry,
but you know,
now you know the
truth and your mom
doesn't have to
re-mortgage the house.
Way to go,
Chelsea.
She had to know.
I've given it some
Molly thought-
And I've decided-
I forgive Spencer.
What?
Lisa Ungerman
laughed at his penis
and he needed to work
through that pain for me.
His heart was in
the right place.
I told you she'd
understand.
She was left
at the altar.
Only people that know
pain can understand
the dark bliss
of revenge sex.
Everyone was
staring at me.
I felt like the biggest
loser in the world.
It was like I just
won first prize
in a not wanted
contest.
Don't go there, Molly,
please, don't go there.
I have to, Spencer.
I can't marry you
until I have sex
with my ex-fiancé,
Mr. Big Jerk.
Sounds fair to me.
And the best manb who didn't
drive him to the church,
And that priest
that snickered.
No, don't!
And that photographer
who kept taking pictures,
and that bridesmaid
who showed a little
too much thigh.
Please!
Button it, Spencer!
It's Molly time.
And so, I lost my
sweet, sweet Molly
to the beast
of revenge sex.
Last I heard she was
revenge-sexing
the balloon twister
who ignored her
on her tenth
birthday.
I guess in the end
it's my fate
to my spend my life
loveless.
You still have me, Spen!
And I'm SO happy!
I think I'm gonna
kill myself.
Yeah...
Hey, Chels!
♪