(SQPRANOS THEME SONG)
Hey, no speeding.
This is a party zone!
( RGVVDY CHATTER )
Come on! \/Ve can do it!
Hey, Janet Jackson
Hi, |\/Ir, Soprano!
V\/here's Meadow’?
-Tony_
Billy, thanks for calling
As soon as I found out
it was your mom's place
C)_D_ Friend says
Special K and ecstasy
You fucking kidding me?
-Your kid's all right_
She's a little drunk
321, repeat,
you're breaking up
529, are you in pursuit
of vehicle on 75 North?
ln your grandmother's house
-lt wasn't my fault,
If I had a quarter
every time I heard that
_l'd have a private jet
on 24-hour standby_
Get in the car
(vo|v||T|No )
In your grandmother's house
-Now he's repeating himself_
Just lucky I knew that cop
So he cut me a favor.
Let me guess, he owes you money?
(CAR APPRGACHING )
\/\/hat did she do?
-Go upstairs,
-No, I want to see the fight,
Get your Iittle ass up those stairs!
lVleadow!
We can talk about it in the morning
-Get down here!
Let her go to bed
I want her to answer for herself!
She's drunk! Was she driving?
I couId've taken ecstasy but I didn't!
Don't puke on the floor!
You still up? Go to bed!
She's on ecstasy and you yeII at me?
-Get up there!
\/\/hat did she say for herself?
The usual shit_ "Wasn't my fault
There was designer drugs there, Tony
So, what did you say?
I don't know_ I yelled_
\/\/hat the fuck else am I gonna do?
You sure you're gonna
be all right, Uncle Rich?
I want to walk
See if I run into any
of the old crowd,
Thanks, doII
lVIotherfucker
There has to be consequences
\/\/hat kind of parents would we be
if we Iet her get away with this?
Typical?
Plenty of parents
still crack the whip
Yeah, that's what they tell you
I cannot wait until
she goes off to college
Gh, right, so you can get
Empty Nest Syndrome___
and go on Wellbutrin
like your sister,
As a parent today, you are over
a barrel no matter what you do_
You take the car, you're a chauffeur
Ground her, you stay in
and be a prison guard.
Throw her out,
social services returns her
and we face a judge
She's not 18 yet_
All I'm saying, with the laws today,
you can't restrain your kid physically
She could sue you for child abuse
There has to be consequences
And there will be
|hearyou,okay?
Let's not overpIay our hand, If she
knows we're powerless, we're fucked
He
That guy wants to talk to you
Jesus_ lVIother of Christ! Richie
So when did you get out?
How come nobody told me?
That's funny, Paulie Walnuts
told me he ran into you this morning
Honest to fucking God
nobody said a word.
Cn what?
You ever meditate?
-lVIe? lVIeditate?
-Are you crazy?
Not as crazy as I used to be
But still crazy enough
to take an eye out,
What's going on here, Rich?
Ten years, And not even a pleasant
"Go fuck yourseIf" from you I get,
You know, I always asked
how you were doing,
Hold on there, You
How could you Iet my dear friend
sit here with an empty cup?
-I'm sorry,
That's all right
Bring this gentleman
a veal-parm sandwich
The other two stores
doing as good as this?
Come on, you know, it's a grind
Rich, I know you're a made guy
so I Iose either way,
But I always respected you
and your brother, Jackie,
I'm no victim here
I'm not some greasebaII storeowner
I'm sorry, Richie,
I will not be shaken down
This sucking up to Tony Soprano
has done wonders for you,
I go away for a while, I come back
you're a tough guy,
Don't do this
-Do what?
Take what's owed to me?
-What's owed to you?
I put you in action, Beansie
You got a bad memory, Beansie
Veal parmigiana sandwich
Fuck you
I'II be back every Saturday, partner
I don't fucking believe this
I'm being shaken down, for what?
Tell me, what did I do?
This is not right
I'm not gonna fucking lay down
Won't Iay down, huh? You don't want
to Iay dawn? You piece of shit!
All right, Iet's get her down here
Iguess
Where is the Bride of Frankenstein?
-She's still sleeping,
Yeah, right, Go wake her up
-I wake her up?
I want to get this shit
out of the way before I go out
You guys are making too much of this
-I don't think we're making enough,
She was drunk
Her choice, There's a Zuni saying
"For every 20 wrongs
a child does, ignore 19
There's an old Italian saying:
You fuck up once, you Iose two teeth
That's what aII this is about
Ego and control,
No, I want to understand this
Go ahead, tell me,
You want to hold on to control
over a young woman,,,
,,,whose entire
biological determinism
is to achieve independent
thought and behavior,
,,,but you want to penalize her
because you don't Iike her choices
Go get a fucking permanent
I'm trying to watch TV!
Good morning,
I'm sorry, is it afternoon?
lVIom, please,
Please what?
You'd better have some answers
-(TGNY) Yeah, That's right!
-Fine, You're punished,
For what? I didn't do anything!
You did nothing?
-It wasn't my fault!
It's never your fault, lVIeadow
It was gonna be me,
Hunter and the lVIacaIuso twins
Then Steve shows up with Adam
and people from Boonton!
So Steve's just trying doorknobs
tiII he hits the jackpot?
-No, Hunter tells him,
Now with the Hunter
And she's at home, blaming it on you
It's an old game,
You try studying day and night
to get into coIIege,
We work hard, We deserved a night!
-Take it easy,
Take it easy
I'm sorry you're under a Iot of
pressure, It's still no excuse,
So who was this ecstasy guy?
-I just told you, Adam,
I don't know him,
He came with Steve
The Steve I know?
The school kid you're always with?
He's a flake, Why do you think
I stopped hanging with him?
That's news to me you don't
hang out with Steve,
It's painful to talk about, okay?
You're gonna get punished
Look, you guys,
I know what I did was not okay
I've been thinking about it a Iot and
really not feeling good about myself
You should take away my Discover card
You better believe it!
-That's right!
For two weeks
Three!
How do I buy gas?
Your allowance
I spent my allowance,
And I already owe lVIom
The Pashmina
No more
Till you get your card back
For gas!
Come here
Look at you,
You Iook great, You're sinew
You sack of shit, If you Iost that
baby fat, you'd disappoint me,
Hey, fuck you
You been Iaid yet?
God, what's wrong? I'm trying
Hey, I said 4:00
I Ieave before
the stock market closes
you yeII for not watching
the phone guys,
lVleet Richie Aprile
Your brother, Jackie,
was Iike a fucking god
A great Ieader,
And I heard a Iot about you
Yeah, well, I heard a Iot about you
That's why I'm here
Gut of respect for our friend here
I'm gonna talk nice,
I ever hear you raise your hands
to my niece again,,,
next time you won't see my face
You understand?
Who told you I put my hand on her?
ls this kid getting jerky with me?
Look, kid, I shouldn't
have to explain myself
I'm from the old school
You want to raise your hands
give her your Iast name,
Then it's not my business
Until then, keep your hands
in your pockets,
We understand each other?
Now get out of here
I want to talk to Tony
Go ahead
He's a good kid
Capable
Look, Ton, this is the thing
I want to get my shy business back
I keep getting caIIs
from Jackie's customers
Where the fuck are you going?
-I'II talk to you Iater, Richie,
What just happened?
No more business talk
with him directly,
You fucking with me?
You can talk to him
But not now
And never here
Can you believe we drank
a whole bottle of wine?
Thank God!
Cheers
We're out of here
-Gkay,
Richie broke a chair over his head
You shitting me?
Hit him with a coffeepot too
Broke his cheekbone,
Prick, I talked to him yesterday
He's aII sweetness and lights,
Already this shit's getting old
Yo, bright eyes
-Where you going?
This isn't the Bing, huh?
Fuck did I say?
Hey, how have you been?
Can't complain
-You Iook good,
Where did your friends go?
Tell them to come back, join us
-No, they're leaving,
First time here, Excellent veal
We making small talk now?
Nice to see you
Yeah, you too
ToodIe-oo
-Bye-bye,
Not a bad ass
She had nice pipe-fitter Iips
No disrespect,
Hey, what do I give a fuck?
I hardly know her,
You mean, you would take
the Iips over the tits?
Trust me, my boy,
There's two things I'm good at
It's pulling dents
and spotting good blowjobs
And that sweetie had
world-class blowjob Iips
Am I right, skipper? Good or no?
What the fuck do I know?
It was a Iong time ago,
All right, she was good, AII right?
Cr great?
Why you busting my baIIs?
It was a Iong time ago,
Hey, I remember
every blowjob I ever got
You remember your first blowjob?
How Iong did it take
for the guy to come?
I said, "You remember
your first bIowjob?"
Yeah," "How long did it take
for the guy to come?"
ToodIe-fucking-oo"?
What the fuck was that?
I couIdn't sleep
from the embarrassment
What was so wrong?
It's an accepted form of goodbye
That's not the way
I talk with patients,
It was Jennifer
What did you see at that table
that made you want to hide "Doctor"?
Who were you hiding from?
That's who I was hiding from
A patient,
When you say "see
do you mean professionally
orjust plain "see"?
-What's the difference?
There's a big difference
If it was just a matter
ofjust plain old "see",,
,,,the cordial doctor
wouId've said, "Good night
,,you abandoned the doctor facade
and adopted the Jennifer posture,
Hence, "ToodIe-oo
You're almost there
Elliot, but not quite,
Young girls are not accountable
for their behavior,
I think "ToodIe-oo" was the action
of a ditsy young girl,
And I regressed into the girl thing
to escape responsibiIity,,,
Look, I need you as a colleague
to tell me that I did the right thing
You gotta ask yourself
why you became a psychiatrist
If it was to help people stop
smoking or biting nails,,,
,,,then so be it,
There's nothing wrong with that
Another patient committed suicide
because I was treating this man,
Treating patients from a motel room
isn't optimum,,,
but you were there for her
in phone contact,
It would have been the same
if you'd been on vacation,
Did you say "Iam"?
(YCGA INSTRUCTCR )
And lifting up into Cobra,
And now rising up
into Downward Facing Dog
Richie
Janice, You know,
I thought that was you
Parvati
I changed my name to Parvati in '78
I thought you lived in California now
Seattle, actually, Iast couple years
So, how Iong you been,,,?
-Gut ofjail?
Cne week, That's where
I picked up this yoga shit,
It's working, You seem very supple
I'm doing a Iot of stretching
-So you back now?
l\/Iy mom's at St, Erasmus, A stroke
Guess we're aII getting a Iittle old
-Cnly if that's our choice,
Drag me aII the way out here
I walk through the food court,
this kid spills fried rice on me
Take it easy,
Keep your voice down, Let's talk
I don't talk business,
Don't take it personal
I'm a government target
Why do you think we're meeting
in a fucking mall?
It feels disrespectful,
You know, that's aII I'm saying
When? When did you ever
step in for me?
You forget?
You and my brother stuck up
Feech LalVIanna's card game?
Feech was a made man
If it wasn't for me, you wouId've got
a vicious beating, to say the Ieast,
You know I Iove you
What was yours before you Ieft
will be yours again,
You just gotta give us some time
Jeez, Anthony, you'd do that for me?
Hey, fuck you
What's mine is not yours to give me
Hey, prick, you reached out to me
-I said what I wanted to say,
Well, we got a problem, kid?
I'm trying to get you to slow down
Things are different now,
You gotta be extra, extra careful
When do you know me not to be careful?
VVhen?
You been out of the can 10 minutes,
you shake down Beansie for a piece
Do me a favor, back off
He's a good earner,
Yeah, for you
That's none of your fucking cazzi
Those joints are a cash business
They come in handy,
He's a sneaky cocksucker
-Whatever, back off,
You taking the side
of a civilian over me?
Christ, I'm asking you
to do me a favor,
Do it if you want to,
If you don't, go fuck yourself
Ch, yeah?
-Yeah,
There's no need for that talk
-What?
l\/ly sister
Janice, How's she doing?
Ch, I thought you were baiting me
You know ,,,,
How's your sister?
Fuck your mother,
See what she did?
-Who?
lVIeadow
That house is fucked!
-Thought you didn't swear,
What are you talking about?
I'm outraged,
No, I am beyond outraged
Talk about disgrace? Disrespect for
other peopIe's property?
It's like a freaking
shooting gallery,
It smeIIs of urine, there's puke
aII over the hardwood floors--
Sounds Iike your place in Venice
-She's been punished,
Three weeks without a card
Ch, Madonna,
that's some heavy shit there!
-Janice ,,,,
If that was my child
You got a Iot of fucking baIIs
you know that?
Don't talk to me Iike that
-Let's clear the air here,
You're a Vishnu-come-lately
playing concerned,
Who the fuck are you kidding?
You're here to pick
the frigging bones,
A Iot of baIIs
Temper tantrums
You're passing judgment on him, Janice
Cn us as parents,
How we discipline our children
is none of anybody's business,
You Iet that girl walk aII over you
you'll regret it,
lVIother of God, Janice!
Are aII of you Sopranos the same?
lVIaybe you'II hear this
lVIind your fucking business, Keep your
mouth shut when it comes to my kids!
Alright ?!
lVIaybe I've stayed here too Iong
The fall in the shower didn't affect
your pre-existing heart condition,
But you already knew that
-It never hurts to be sure,
What next does the lVIan Upstairs
have in store for me?
You're lucky it was a sprain
The thing is, doc, I've been feeling
these, like, little fibrillations,
Psychosomatic,
You got out ofjail on a medical
(KNCCKING )
Hey!
There's my boy!
I was afraid you didn't
get the message,
Put a shirt on,
I'm getting a chubby
Doc, this is one of my dearest friends
Richie, this is the best heart man
in the world, Doug Schreck,
l\/Ir, Soprano oversoId me,
I'm only the best in the Western world
Fucking ball-breaker
Doc, do me a favor?
lVle and Richie
Yeah, no problem
He's good, Lets me use his doctor-
patient privilege to meet people here
Fucking house arrest
Federal marshals so far up my ass
I can taste Brylcreem,
Jesus, you Iook good
How you feeling?
I gotta meet Tony at a maII, you here
What the fuck is happening?
Like the man said,
lVIay you Iive in interesting times
You met with Tony?
It's more Iike a fucking audience
with the pope,
What are you gonna do?
Whatever you tell me
You and your brother
were always good boys
You tell me othen/vise
I'm yours, Junior
Whatever, whoever
You just say it
Cnce again, a big welcome home
to our guest of honor,
Richie was surprised by
the changes in 10 years
New Jersey has a hockey team
It's interesting,
lVIeadowIands is the only NHL arena
,where the penalty box
is maximum-security,
lVIaximum-security penalty box
Help me
What the fuck?
I was talking to Paulie Walnuts
who thought that Richie
had been in Bosnia,,,
,,,where there's also
a large lVIusIim population
That's it, Cut of here
-Enough,
And now for aII you youngsters with
visions of tit-fucking in your head,,,
(APPLAUSE )
He
Welcome home
Wait tiII you open it, It's aII ones
I'm a grandfather now, Rich
Imagine that?
Please, no pictures
Exploiting medical curiosities
is against the law,
That why they canceled
your mom's audition?
What did you say?
It's a homecoming
-Cocksucker,
Take a walk
-Is Beansie here?
Haven't seen him
Richie, how's your balls?
They're hanging
Ready and waiting
What?
Go with Silvio
Who?
-Go!
|'|| hold this
Don't worry about it
-Come on,
This guy
Trust me!
He's got a real
fucking attitude problem
-Careful,
Come on
He just did 10 fucking years,
He has a right to be a bit fucked up
Richie will be all right
(|v|oAN|No)
Yeah, Yeah
I see you Iike the dark
Silvio says we can't take it
Whose joint did you just cop
mine or his?
Did we do something wrong?
-You were fine,
(APPLAUSE )
Hey, buddy!
What the fuck are you doing?
What'd you think Tony Soprano
was gonna do for you?
Come here!
-No,
Come here! Come here!
How come you weren't at the party?
I moved a Iot of H for you
and you made the Iion's share
You're just bitter because I invested
my money smart and you didn't,
I spent mine on lawyers
you slippery fuck!
You want to talk Iike a tough guy?
Tough guy, here!
Hey, come on, Please, no guns
What happened to
I'm no greasebaII storeowner"?
Tell me again how
you won't Iay down, huh?
(ouNsHoT)
(HoRNHoNmNo)
Asshole!
(LCUD |v|us|c)
I'm sorry, is the music too Ioud?
-Ch, no, it's fine,
I just wanted to apologize
You know, about earlier,
No, I should be apologizing to you
I was out of Iine
You're right
I never raised a child
I was robbed of that when Eugene
took him back to lVIontreaI,
,but they have me on their
enemy radicals list, so ,,,,
When was the Iast time you saw Harpo?
He changed his name to Hal
I'm sorry, Carm,
can we not talk about him?
Look, I just want you to know
that I was way out of Iine,
Well, I'm sorry too,
Really, I just feel terrible
You know, you're family
And family means a Iot
I just don't feel right
about you leaving here
I don't know
I don't think Tony wants me here
Where will you go? The house is in no
condition to move into, especially now,
l'll be all right
No, I'm sorry,
I really can't Iet you Ieave
Ckay
Ch, maybe just a Iittle bit
The music,
Ch, all right
(HCNWNG)
Richie, no! Richie, no!
Jesus!
(PCP soNo |=>|_AY|No)
Do I put the chocolate in now?
-Put it in, l'll pour the milk,
What did your parents
say about Saturday?
The usual, Nothing,
They're afraid l'll go bulimic again
Purge and they won't say anything
When will they realize we're adults
responsible for ourselves?
So we had a party
at your grandmother's
Would they prefer we go to Limelight?
Hello!
It's because they have no Iife
They focus on bullshit,
So, what did yours do?
They took my Discover card
for three weeks,
-That's nothing,
I know, it was my idea
-Dicks,
So hypocritical too
When you think how my dad
makes a living,
Ch, jeez! What is this?
Why don't you ring for the nurse?
-Never you mind!
That's theirjob
I don't need them
l\/Iy daughter came
aII the way from Seattle
(TV s|_AR|No )
Ch, Jesus!
(KNCCKING )
Hello?
She rang for you
-I did not,
lVIrs, Soprano
Richie Aprile
But I thought you were dead
No, hon, that was my brother, Jackie
Ch, I'm sorry
How did he die, the poor baby?
He had cancer
l\/Ie too
Shut that curtain, will ya?
lVly Johnny would roll over
in his grave if he saw this,
Ch, they wheel people in and out
in and out, Ch, go on!
So isn't Parvati supposed to be here?
I don't know who that is
Your daughter, Parvati, Janice
Ch, yeah, please,
Don't start with that name business
She did it to shame me
( JANICE )You'II have to have your
tea without Iemon,
Richie
You see the beautiful flowers
he brought me?
Yeah, see? Yourfather
has friends with class,
Not Iike some people
lVIa, he's not one of Dad's friends
He's my friend,
You mean, he's your boyfriend?
,,,for beeping my horn
when I came to pick up Janice
Pimps beep!
You know, someday somebody's gonna
wash out your mouth with soap, hon,
Ch, yeah, who? You?
Ch, I wish the Lord would take me
Chh, lVIa, Statazeet
The man's come to visit you
-Take it easy!
You Iay the same trip
on everybody who comes
Don't you have any shame?
-Shame?
Ch, I got plenty of shame
Believe me
Go ahead, lVIa, Shoot your best shot
Never you mind
Just remember what
we talked about Iast week
lVIa, I'm gonna go to
the cafeteria for some coffee
Are you coming back?
-Yes,
I bet you're very good to your mother
She'II be better when I get her home
Does that mean you're sticking around?
If I don't, who'II take care of her?
-What about Tony?
Long story,
You haven't heard what happened?
Tony blames everyone else
for anything bad in life
including lVla,
Tony? No
Trust me, Nothing's ever his fault
I couIdn't visit her empty-handed
-You weren't at yoga,
I'm very busy with my mother
We weren't good together
20 years ago,
Why do you think
it's any different now?
Let's get to the point
I am so not that person anymore
You know, I don't think l'd be
interested in the same Jan I knew
So, what, you've grown?
-Well, you tell me,
Did you ever think you'd
see Richie Aprile doing,,
Downward Facing Dog?
Can she put more gook shit in here?
-It's not that much,
Soy milk, tofu, I hate aII that shit!
(A,J, )Yeah, me too
Shut up, you said you liked soy milk
I Iied, She was taking me
to the video store,
I'm happy Aunt Parvati's staying
The one who thinks you're spoiled?
-Hey!
Whoa!
Don't Iook Iike you're gonna cry
You made your bed,
I need $15
Excuse me?
A Cole Porter CD, It's for lVIadrigaIs
We're doing three of his songs,
You took my card, remember?
Here
What's your problem?
Nothing
Thank you, by the way!
Janice should be home by now
l\/Iy sister was almost out
and you fall for her con?
She can't afford a motel
How about she goes back
to where she was for 20 years
while I took care of our mother?
I thought we couIdn't
mention Grandma in this house
You tell her to Ieave,
I won't, It's not Christian
See? This shit works out
She's a Buddhist,
( JANICE )
Hello!
We're in here, Par
They're beautiful
-Aren't they?
Richie?
Richie Aprile?
He went to visit her,
You know he always Ioved l\/Ia
AII right, I gotta go
You better water them,
I think I hear them crying
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WIZARD GF GZ MUSIC PLAYING )
(TRUCK HoRN HCNKING )
(CRASHING SCUNDS)
(FEMALE soB|3|No )
Aw, Jesus Christ!
Peter, you're scaring your mother
Leave me the fuck alone
Hey, is that a way to talk?
Tony?
Can you pick up the BBC
on that thing, or what?
No jokes please, Tony
(NURSE ) Cnly family
Let him stay
How you doing, pal?
Jesus
They said I might not walk
( FEl\/IALE ) Come on, lVIom, Let's go
downstairs for a Iittle while,
You gonna Iet that animal
get away with this?
I'II Iet you talk to your "friend
Don't listen to these fucking doctors
When it comes to spinal injuries
it's aII a mystery to them,
PauIie's cousin got run over
by a forklift, Broke his back,
(SCBBING)
AII right, here
Here
I can't do it
Ah, ah
Come on
Thanks
Thanks, Tony
I might not be able to wipe
my own ass, you know that?
Your nose is as far
as I'm willing to go,
(LAUGHING)
Listen
Beans
You 1000% sure it was
Richie Aprile driving?
A thousand percent? No
A fucking miIIion percent
And Iet me tell you something
He's lucky I ain't no rat fuck
Because the Iaw knows
that was no random hit-and-run
Don't start talking foolish
We wash our own dirty Iaundry
Hey, am I right, Beans?
Yeah, yeah, CId school
Ckay, good
So you here to see your ma?
I hear she's upstairs,
No, I came here to see you, you prick
That's okay
Go do what you gotta do
I told you to back off Beansie
-I did, Then I put it in drive,
This is funny?
He might never walk again
Did you know that? And for what?
He didn't duke you enough?
He didn't visit you in the can?
When did you visit anybody in the can?
When's the Iast time you gave a fuck
about anybody but yourself?
You remember one thing
and listen good,
You want to talk this old school shit?
Here's a rule you might remember:
I'm the motherfucking fucking one
who caIIs the shots,
You pay me the respect I gave your
brother or we're gonna have a problem
A bad one
Now get the fuck out of here
All right, Tony
Yeah, All right
-Hey,
How you doing?
I'II open it, you change the locks
(RCCK soNo PLAYING )