(SQPRANOS THEME SONG)
( Si|vio ) Get out of the way
Remember
to say please
This is the DVD,
This is the advanced bootleg
These are
the alternate takes
\/\/hat, are you gonna oall Coppola
with ideas on how to fix it?
I do not
believe this
O
Ch, o'mon
You know what soene
I love most?
it was you, Fredo
Ton', you gonna
go see your uncle first
if you decide
to go over there?
Yeah
That would be smart
Fucking disc!
Somebody should tell
Paramount Pictures
to get their
shit together
\/\/e're gonna be stealing
thousands more of these things
So, how was junior
last time you saw him?
His life is about
IVlotrin these days
Ton', what's your
favorite scene?
I can't have this
conversation again
Hit eject!
Don Ciccio's villa
when Vito goes
back to Sicily_
The crickets,
the great old house
IVIaybe 'cause I'm going
over there, you know?
I was in the Army
Signal Corp,
\/\/hat this thing needs is what we call
a "brogan adjustment_"
What's that,
you know how?
Ye
(BIG PUSSY LAUGHING)
( Radio announcer)
This is "1010 wins".
You give us 22 minutes
we 'll give you the world.
( IVIaIe ) Temperatures are expected
to drop tomorrow
after another scorching
day in the city.
Right now it's 96 degrees
at Caldwell,
LaGuardia 's 94
and it's 98 in Central Park
and on the Upper East Side.
Great
lt's like this
every Sunday
and every Sunday
you say "Great,"
like it's
the first time
Could we please Iower
the air conditioning?
I'm doing it
for godsake!
I just got this car
I'm not familiar
with the instrument panel
( IVIaIe ) Get up out
the fucking car!
Take the car
take the car!
Get the fuck
out the car!
You nasty bitch,
get the fuck out of here!
Smack the shit
out of you.
U!
Gkay, okay, okay!
Dammit, man
Sic 'em,
Churchill!
Evan,no!
Sic 'em,
Churchill!
Churchill
Barry!
Who else, huh?
Who eIse?!
(PHoNE R|No|No)
( Female ) West Essex
Crthopedic Group.
I\/Ir. Soprano?
Ckay if
my nephew comes in?
He's got some questions for the doc
about my hip and all.
The doctor will be
right with you.
Perhaps your nephew can
help you with your clothes.
until I know this prick
is gonna X-ray me again
Hurts Iike the fucking
Pit and the Pendulum
just to
wipe myself
So what do you
want to talk about?
Going over
to the other side
See that friend of ours
over there.
I\/Iy car operation
Lose the miserable puss
it's mine now.
Cur friend, what's
he Iike to deal with?
What's he Iike?
Yeah
I only met him
one time.
He came over on
The IVIicheIangelo, 1961
Now, that
was traveling
The fucking
Italian line.
The food, the service
are you kidding me?
He's a serious man
Zi Vittorio.
Serious how?
You know
what I mean
He don't listen to opera
Vittorio,
which is
a fucking break
lsn't he like
a distant cousin of ours?
It's so far removed by now,
Tonto's a closer cousin to you
We deal with him through
a guy named Furio Giunta
he speaks English
Going to Italy, huh?
Yeah
Nice,
I never went
It's not over yet
And we don't
get to go?
You got school
What about mom?
She knows
it's a business trip
just the
two of you?
Right now
Not my idea to have me
set the table.
Carm, you want me
to help with the roast?
( CarmeIa ) it's right there
on the counter.
Carm, it's
a business trip
Did I
say anything?
God!
Naples
Ischia and Capri
And, oh
the food
(SILVERWARE oRoPs)
Look, I know Iast year, Tom and Barb
the trip to the Bahamas,
I said I didn't
have time.
You didn't
It was football season
IVleadow, can you tell
your brother dinner's ready?
It's our
busiest months
Junior's Iast shipment went
to Naples two months ago.
Thirty containers,
two cars to a container
Junior had to give the operation
over to who, specifically?
Ray Curto
Ckay,
good work, Sal
There's something else
you should know.
They're talking like the lVloltisanti
kid might get his button.
Tony, where's he at
with Junior these days?
They ain't
spoke in months
Are you bein'
straight with me?
Ch, Pussy!
What the fuck?
How's it going
colonel?
How you doing
Jimmy?
What'd I hear,
you were in Puerto Rico?
I was playing there once
during the hurricanes,
never again
I said.
Jimmy, Iet me introduce you
to a friend of ours.
This is Joey
from Dover,
Delaware
No shit!
I live in Dover
here, Jersey.
That's right
I forgot.
Joey, know where they got
the name Dover from?
The cliffs,
I'm assuming
That's right
very good.
Jimmy, does it
fucking matter?
Joey, I knew this guy
when he had social graces
It's for IVlarisa's oldest's
sixth birthday.
The kids are aII grown, aren't they, Puss
what are ya doin' here?
It's my daughter's
birthday.
I'm picking up some shit
for a bachelor party.
I'm trying to think
Did I ever meet any connected guys
from Delaware?
That fucking box
Iooks heavy.
The answer is
No,no,no
Alright Iook,
I got to go, fellows
Joey
Nice to meet you
You, I\/Ir. Rude Cocksucker
see you around, baby.
IVIotherfucker,
motherfucker!
Take it easy,
that went fine
He saw me with you
You come aII the way
to a fucking party store
and still somebody's
got to see you?
Sal, listen,
that went fine
Just know this,
you're doing a good job
(ANDREA BGCELLI PLAYING )
You must be so relieved
Pussy is back.
Was a Iong time
Did he ever tell you
where he was?
Ch, he don't Iike
to worry me.
Not even
a card?
That's got
to be a worry
lt's horrible
Anyway, you must
be so happy.
Ah, I love
this song.
lVlmm
Ch honey, I know
your Jackie.
Listen to me, going on about
how happy I am and you a widow
Que sera sera
God, he's so handsome
this guy too.
He's blind
you know
Jesus Christ!
Angie
I'm not happy
Sal is back.
Angie!
I'm sad
and depressed
|'ve thought
of killing myself
Fucking nosy?
Eat your monigott
When he did come home that day
I was upstairs,
I heard the door
and then his voice, "l'm home
I fucking wanted
to vomit.
After all that worrying
he might be dead,
praying
he was okay
I\/Iy heart just sank
and I wished--
he had died
To just come and go
year after year Iike that
Have you reached
out to him?
That's a good one
Listen
and I don't want
my kids to know this
They found a Iump
under my arm.
Ch my god
They biopsed it, I get
the results in a couple days
Anyway,
I told Sal
he said, "Jesus Christ"
kind of alarmed a Iittle
Then he went back to doin'
whatever the fuck he was doin
Spraying WD-40
on his pocket knife
Touch my face, or something
when he comes in.
So Angie, what
are you gonna do?
Benign, malignant,
I'm getting a divorce
(ITALIAN oPERA |v|us|c
coNT|NuEs)
Look at this place
The mother country
Here, they
make it real
Vesuvius, Jesus, who's gonna tell Artie
that mural he spent that money on
Iooks Iike a used Trojan
compared to this?
You notice
the women?
Know what I realized
on the plane?
Even the skanks
are worth fucking!
Those were
my feelings too
Paison, tutto gli
whaddya call it...
Are all the women
good-looking Iike this?
(|_/-\uoH|No)
Hey, you
did alright
Two definite agendas I got
hit the topless beaches
and see
that fucking crater
I don't care what
anybody says, I'm there
Look at
this fucking place
It's been here
a thousand years
Hey T, check out the bank
(Mme)
Anthony Soprano
Yeah
|’m Furio Giunta
Hey, how are you?
Pleased to meet you
This is the friend of ours
SiI and me been talking to
This is Paulie,
this is Christopher
This is Tanno
Welcome
I\/Iy boss Nino say
you can fresh up,
maybe Iittle sleep
then we will
pick you up at eight
And he will meet us
for fare la business.
Whoa, whoa,
wait a minute
Nino? I mean,
I never heard of-
I'm sure he's a nice guy
and everything.
But Vittorio
will be there, right?
IVIaybe no
Commendatori, you are
already checked in.
Commendatori,
Iike a commander
I like that,
that's respect
So did you hear?
You're talking about
the Bonpenseiros, right?
Hang on, Gab, call waiting
It may be Tony from Italy.
Hello?
I didn't sleep
a wink last night
my QOGI,
isn't this awful?
Did you tell
Franny Altieri?
Coh no, she's gonna shit
when she hears this.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
What time Christopher
say he'd get here?
Any time now
He was just going down
to Corso to buy a gift for Adrianna
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
but he was
no supplier.
That why
I'm here.
Tell him we can
fiII any orders.
And also mention
no offense,
we were hoping
Zi Vittorio would be here
Anything you want to talk to Vittorio
about that I don't know?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
Nino is a Iittle disappointed
in your attitude of him.
l’m sorry Nino
I'm sure that l'll learn much,
doing business with a man Iike you
He said--
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
Why is he busting my baIIs?
Tell him to get to the fucking point
Nino is happy to be
at your disposal.
I\/Iy uncIe's problem was he went
to the Russians in Brooklyn,
too much
for the cars
shipped it off
to St. Petersburg
Slovenia
and IVIontenegro
they got people over there that
profited from those conflicts.
You got contacts
in the markets over there
Ton', you try
this octopus yet?
I'm talking
here.
You're like
a fucking child
With the food and the pussy,
what's going on here, Paulie?
This is a big
thing to me, T
I was never
over here, okay?
I\/Iy brother was and my other
brother the doctor was,
with all
his bullshit
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
How mucha you
charge-a un car?
IVIercedes I\/IL series
very popular.
In Eastern Europe
you can sell this car for 110
120 thousand
I\/ly price to you
90 grand.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
It's manufactured
in America.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
(SILVERVVARE DRCPPING)
That's Don Vittorio
You didn’t have to Ieave
your house tonight.
Annalisa, sweetheart
how are you?
Don Vittorio, allow me to
present our friend from America
Anthony Soprano
Don Vittorio, it's an honor
Wheelchair,
aboolebarda !
Think-- something's wrong
with the wheelchair.
He say
Wilshire boulevard
I am his daughter
Piacere
Piacere, Tony
George-a Washington-a
Bridge-a.
Right, very good,
George Washington Bridge
Let’s talk about something else,
and later we’II talk about the streets
Ton', you give
this guy a golf club
he'II probably
try to fuck it.
I come three thousand
fucking miles,
you never said nothing
about this guy Nino,
aII of a sudden
he's my blind date?
Nino was in hide from the
police until two day ago.
Who the fuck
is IVIauro Zucca?
IVIauro Zucca
run this family
Cbviousiy
Zi Vittorio
Then I should be talking
to IVIauro Zucca.
Yes, signore
Can I just get some
macaroni and gravy?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
Paulo, he doesn't
know what you says
you mean grapes?
Uva ?
Gravy, gravy,
tomato sauce
He wants spaghetti and tomato sauce
He doesn’t Iike this.
And you thought the Germans
were ciassless pieces of shit.
Nino,
he's insecure
It effects everything
he says, capice ?
I will talk on the side
to the ear of Annalisa
What the fuck good
is that gonna do?
She is the wife
of IVIauro Zucca
CamiIIo, where's
the pisciadood ?
Down the stairs
go Ieft.
IVIa-jor-digan
expressa-way
Right, IVIajor Deegan
Expressway.
I'm sorry
if he's hassle you
You spend a Iot
of time in the states?
Papa went, I never been
English from school,
e filmsa
When could we get
a chance to talk?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
Come to our house
stay a while.
Where your
family's from
I don't want
to put you out
No, you should have
been guest to our house
But with my father
condition now.
I send you
the car at nine?
Fine
Ton
I Iook fon/vard to it
excuse me.
I'm gonna hoof it back
to the excelsior.
Can you stop fucking
interrupting me?
We've been offered
a ride here,
you know how these people
are about formalities,
why didn't you use
the one in there?
I didn't have
to go then.
(FIRECRACKERS some oFF)
He’s all right
It’s only firecrackers
No, please, he’s my son!
Please don’t hurt him!
The kid only got
firecrackers on him
I want to work with you guys!
Who told you this was the
way to go about it?
Don’t worry
This is Naples University
( Carmeia ) We're gettin
ready to eat.
Ch yeah, forgot
it was dinner time for you
How's Italy?
The time change
and everything, I forgot, sorry
How's Italy?
Got to be honest
with you.
Pretty freaking good
We'll have
to come back here
Sounds Iike you're
working too hard.
Why don't you
take the kids
You know Tony, don't tell me
how to spend my time.
If I want the excitement
of Chinese food,
I don't need
your permission
You know what?
Fine, l'll hang up.
Well if the trip is as bland
as this phone caII.
There's nothing
going on.
What do you want me
to say to you, seriously?
You better not say
what you saw, Jimmy
l'll shove that Elvis shit
right up your ass.
l'II shove a rutabaga
in your mouth Jimmy
Keep you quiet
aI!
(YELLING IN ITALIAN )
I think it was the fuckin' shrimp
hors d'oeuvres on the plane.
Get some Immodium
You want to get made
this is no fucking way.
Tony wants us
to hang with Nino
work out
the dock facilities
I hope we get
some spare time
I'm gonna see
that fuckin' volcano
(RAP |v|us|c PLAY|No)
Ch, ho, gratzie
(WCIVIAN )
Vincenzo, turn off that radio!
(souNo CF KIDS PLAYING)
( ITALIAN CPERA PLAYING )
He
(ANDREA BCCELLI PLAYING )
This song, Jesus
Listen, I've been
to Italy many times
and really, you're not
missing aII that much.
The amount of sexual harassment
that I was subjected to.
I went one time
with my friend Zane
Her, they
didn't bother
me, they couIdn't keep
their hands to themselves
IVIuch Iess the whistling
and the fucking hooting
It’s not Italy
Do you remember
Angie Bonpensiero?
Angie Belfiore
married Sal Bonpensiero
Right, she's thinking
of divorcing him.
Halle-fucking-lujeh!
No I don't know them, but to be
married to a man Iike that.
A man like what?
He is such an adoring
father though.
Three beautiful kids
they raised,
who are now from
a broken home.
we don't need
He's very macho
IVlacho, no, try
swaggering mama's boy
fucking hypocrites
shall we?
Hypocrites?
Carm, come on stop
Just stop.
Is that how you
see your brother?
I thought we were
talking about Angie
with their goomahs and their
prostitutes, emotional cripples
And they expect
their wives to live
like the fucking nuns
at I\/It. Carmel college
It's not
that simple
Cf course not
IVIadonna/whores is the full
equation I believe.
Clothes,
appliances, houses
You are
talking about me
CarmeIIa, no
I don't know
That a woman
of your intelligence
is content to ask so Iittle
from life and from herself
I don't know, it's none
of my business.
IVIarriage is
a holy sacrament
Ckay
Family is
a sacred institution
Roger
And you trying
to fan the flames
with Richie Aprile
of aII people?
Carm, Richie, because of his
life experience in prison,
Ch my god!
But you had me going
for a while there, you really did
Ch Janice honey
I got to Iove ya.
(cARMELA L/_\uoH|No )
(CPERA MUSIC PLAYING)
Collect the toenails
(THWACK CF A GCLF BALL )
Nice shot
It’s a man's club
I'II send you
one your size
Whole set
So Tony, you don't mind
me calling you Tony?
What can
I do for you?
Well you can introduce
me to the boss.
A fuckin'
woman boss?
So what
do you want?
Never happen
in the States.
Never
Cur men kill
each other.
AII my brothers, for example
they aII got murdered.
Cr they go
to prison.
Rome has a war
against us.
But our men are
in Iove to their mama
So being a woman is not
come se dic',
comes natural
We'|| |'||
be dipped in shit
You go around Iike your
father's nursemaid.
Well if an old man carries
the respect of troops,
you keep
him around
I did something
like that myself.
We're cousins
You hungry?
I could eat
Can I ask
you a question?
We not gonna pay
the price on the IVIercedes
VVhy,you
want them?
If your enemy comes
into possession of your nail
or your hair clippings,
they can make the evil on you
I'm flattered you wouIdn't
trust me with your toenaiis
but can I pass without
ruining the moment?
I already
burned them
Nobody gets them
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
Commendatori
Bon giorno
Cocksuckers
A Iot of guys today, they become
soft living in America.
You can't find anybody over there
that believes in the old ways,
keeping silent,
putting the family first
So you want
Naples guys.
Fucking clairvoyant
over here.
they belong only to me
110 percent.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
What?
What do I get?
Well, you get an obvious advantage
to havin' your guys in that end.
How much you
pay me for this man?
Pay you?
Your profitability
is gonna go way up
What are
you thinking?
Funo!
(YELLING IN ITALIAN )
Back up, take it easy
I'm going to give you
one of my best men.
And aII I get is a bunch
of numbers in air.
With all due
respect, hon
I think you're being
a Iittle short-sighted on this
He's my cousin,
he's one of my best men
Forget about it,
it's not going to happen
I'm asking
you nice.
Cr what?
Hey Iook, I don't even
think you understand.
I want you to talk
to your husband about this
I\/Iy husband, fuck you!
He is never coming back
So you have to fucking
deal with me!
Up your ass
( FooTsTEPs )
Where's my other belt?
Did you Iook
under the bed?
Fuck,yeah
I just came from
the doctor's office
Yeah
The biopsy
came back negative
Yeah good, l'||
be back Iater.
(GENTLE soBB|No)
(BACKGRCUND IVIUSIC)
( IVIaIe ): The 3:32 to Mt. Vesuvius
is now leaving at the side entrance.
(KNCCKING )
Pussy
Yeah
What the fuck
you doing here?
I was
in the neighborhood
That bachelor party, they're looking
for some entertainment.
A sett',
you want coffee?
Nah,
I'm good
C'mon, it's
on the boil.
(TEAPCT wH|sT|_|No )
(KNCCKING )
Yeah
Boss say to tell you one hour
manigamo, dinner.
Manigamo, I want to get
the fuck out of here.
You drive me to the city?
Sure, absolutely
I have to ask
What's it like,
working for a woman?
VVhaddya
gonna do?
In America
you don't have?
What?
Tony!
Yeah, come
down to eat.
Jesus Christ, is that
aII your people do?
The Iunch we had
would jam a wood chipper
We need to finish
our business.
I said all
I'm gonna say
(DooR s|_/-\|v||v||No)
( Female )
Vincenzo!
(BARKING )
Have some Amaro
lndigestion, right?
Cheers
So what is this place?
Later we make
the new one.
You're born here, and your
kids are raised next door.
That's a nice thing
You take good care
of your father.
What are
you going do
send him
to a ospizio ?
Hey, listen
(YELLING IN ITALIAN )
This one has to stay
with until he goes to sleep
I'II take you
back in the morning
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
Goodnight
I might as well
have fucking cancer
So what did
the Iawyer say today?
He said I have a good case
we're filing Tuesday.
So your gonna take IVIonday
to think, that's good.
I'm finished thinking
Hell, I thought myself
into fuckin' nonexistence
Well, you are
not nonexistent
and Pussy doesn't
see you that way.
Fuck what he sees!
Not anymore,
it's what I see
God gave me
more years, Carmela
This very morning
God gave me a gift
and I will
use that gift
I won't
waste it
like I wasted 24 fucking
years with this man.
You know what the church
says about divorce.
Ch please, Iet
the Pope live with him
Well, what about
the kids?
They're 19, 21, and 24
it's time we all grew up
Kevin is just starting his
sophomore year at college
Aren't you worried
he's gonna realize
the two stayed together
waiting for him to leave?
Long as he don't
Ioose his privileges
at our house down
the shore,
that's aII Kevin
cares about.
He's so fond of his father
that's aII I'm saying.
And Terry and Scott
with the money problems
and the pregnancy
this is really the example
you want to set,
when your daughter
is struggling very hard
to keep her new marriage
in one piece?
Why you workin'
this hard, Carmela?
For aII of the reasons
I just said.
Because you're my friend
I'm not even sayin' don't.
I'm just sayin'
at the very Ieast
you got to ask
yourself these questions
Terri, they're not even sure
she's gonna be able
Sal began to cry
when he heard that
Ch, honey
In the end, I know
you're not gonna Ieave him
I know you
won't do that
(SINGING IN ITALIAN)
Who are you?
Are you with NATC?
You cut our ski-lift cable
Hey Cara IVlia,
on the way back
bring me one of those plums
from the breakfast tray.
Cosa ?
Never mind
I got to hand
it to ya.
Che bella fruti
None of them
fucking steroids
Come se dic', steroids?
Steroide
There ya go
Who said you're not
a great conversationalist?
Ya fuckin' twat
There's my Iittle
fragolin'.
Ah-ah
Hey, the customer
is always right.
Did I say you
should Ieave?
You know my grandfather was
Napoletan', gran-pappa mio.
He went to America
in 1910.
Three thousand miles
Just a Iittle boy
All by himself
Yep, I'm Napoletan
I\/Ie and Tony both
Sigilian', se
Hard-headed bastards
am I right?
So, what part
of Naples you from?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
It’s right over there
Ariani el pino ?
Your shitting me!
That's where
my grandfather's from!
It’s right over there
We come from
the same town.
Cur families probably
knew each other.
The island back there
is called Progeda.
Madonn', Iook at this
Got to bring
my kids back here
Show 'em aII this
In the olden time
the Sibylla of Cumae
was the second most
important oracle after Delphi
I thought Delphi was in Greece
The Greeks were here
Way before the Romans
and before the Greeks
there were somebody else,
and before them somebody else
"to hear the Sibyl's
predictions of their future
She would sit inside
the cave inhaling gases
I think
I dated this broad
"PossibIy volcanic
though no longer active
delivering unto them
their fates."
Let’s go into the cave
The SibyI sat way back there
see that shaft of Iight?
Some fucking trip
Ch yeah, got
a premonition for me?
You, you're no
problem to read
You are your
own worst enemy
Ch, is that right?
Tell you right now
you remind me
of somebody
from back home
Not your wife,
your girlfriend?
Ch, I got one,
to answer your question
But no, not her
But, she's someone
you want to fuck.
I can tell
Ch really
You know, everybody's
their own worst enemy.
So maybe your psychic power
has been overrated a Iittle bit.
You don't want
to fuck her?
to fuck me?
Yeah, I do
But I don't shit
where I eat.
Que cosa?
Non fare la merdo dove
It’s bad business,
we're in business
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
Not at those price
Alright
You give me Furio
and l'll work down
the price of the cars to 85
Posto, okay
I get more guys
on my timetable
(SPEAKING ITALIAN )
75 thousand
Ckay
Hey, thanks!
So, how the
fuck was it?
Fabulous, I felt
right at home.
Real good
business-wise
I feel sorry for anyone
who hasn't been.
Someday
Where the fuck
is Christopher?
He's in the duty free
buying a gift for Ade.
Four days, he's a block away from
the greatest shopping district in the world
Why the fuck didn't
he think of it then?
( Paulie )
A broad.
He found out who got eight great
tomatoes in that Iittle bitty can.
Go, let's drive
What's the matter, Tony?
Nothin
I tell you we do
real good business-wise?
I got fuckin'
double on those cars
Here he comes
Hey, c'mon!
(ANDREA BCCELLI PLAYING )
Hello, I'm home!
(SINGING IN ITALIAN)