Last season on "Batwoman"...
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Kate, don't leave me! Don't leave me.
ALICE: I want her very, very dead!
If you want Kate dead so badly,
why don't you just shoot her?
No. Her betrayal deserves a reckoning!
LUKE: Where did you get that?
A friend gave it to me for safekeeping
in case she ever lost her way.
ALICE: Oh, goody. It's Tommy Elliot.
TOMMY: What about me?
I'm the guy that taught Bruce
Wayne everything he knows,
so where's my recognition, Doc?
ALICE: I must admit, Tommy.
I made all your dreams come true.
You made me Bruce Wayne.
I need you to strut through
the doors of Wayne Tower
and get me that shard of Kryptonite
from your dear cousin Kate.
[FOGHORN BLOWING]
WOMAN: I think you'll like it here.
There's plenty of room for your stuff,
and your plants will
have their own balcony.
Yes, I said balcony, and look!
Only two locks. We are a
two-lock household now, Mom.
Ooh. Aren't we fancy?
And your little girlfriends will have
an easier time sneaking in and out now.
Okay. Can we not? You are my mama.
You're not supposed to
know about that stuff.
Rent's due on the first.
My office is next to the laundry.
- Are you ready for our new life?
- Mm-hmm.
[DOOR OPENS]
[EXPLOSION]
I did not just see that!
[JET FLYING]
Holy...
MARY: Okay. This is freaky.
Apparently Gotham's raining jet parts.
- Already on it.
- Is Kate there?
She hasn't checked in since she landed
in National City yesterday.
Batcave to Batwoman. You online?
WOMAN: Hello? Can
anybody hear me? Hello?
Hello?
Can anybody moan or something?
Oh. Ohh!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
The suit's GPS is off.
So is her phone.
What about calling her
old-school, Bat-Signal?
Can we flip it on remotely?
We could till the Crows
pulled it offline in their
war with Batwoman.
Now anyone who touches
the thing loses a hand.
- Want to try the hold-up?
- Already calling.
Wake up!
Come on. Live!
Live!
[SOBBING]
Come on! Wake up! Live, please!
Come on!
[GASPING]
MARY: Why isn't she answering?
Maybe she's already at the scene.
With her comms off?
You sure she flew in from
National City this morning?
Checking.
- [MAN COUGHING]
- Hey, hey.
You're gonna be okay, okay?
You're gonna be okay.
[COUGHS]
LUKE: Wayne Enterprises
tail number GC9K23
was set to depart at 10 A.M.
from National City.
Delayed for weather.
So maybe she's still in Nat. City.
Tail number GC9K23
actual departure time...
9:35 P.M.
So she's en route.
Explains why she hasn't
gotten any of our calls.
Except she was set to
land 20 minutes ago.
[SIRENS]
Hello?
LUKE: Okay. GC9K23 departed at 9:35 P.M.
At 10:15, 10,000 feet, 400 knots.
At 10:45, 450 knots, 8,500 feet.
At 10:50...
What?
10:50 what?
What, Luke?
Luke?
Where is Kate's plane?
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
Oh, my God.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[SIRENS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
MAN: Why don't you guys start there?
Okay. Kane's here. Uh, listen.
Go now that way and
check in with me later.
What have you found?
Sir, I don't think you should be
anywhere around here right now.
This was my daughter's airplane.
Tell me what you have.
Have you recovered anyone?
Not yet, but trust me, Kane, go home.
We'll call you if we find anything.
I am not leaving here
without my daughter.
SOPHIE: Sir.
We'll look together.
Come on.
MAN: You two, with me.
MARY: What do you mean Julia
couldn't find the Batsuit?
Julia said she was one of the
first to arrive at the crash site,
searched everywhere,
meaning if Kate was wearing
it she could've survived.
No, but Kate would
have called us, though.
Not if she's unconscious,
so when the suit wakes
up, we'll find her.
I get that it's a supersuit,
but 10,000 feet is still
a hell of a freefall.
Yeah, but the cape's nanotech
is more advanced
than a NASA parachute,
and the suit's shock-absorbing
properties are unlike anything...
MARY: No way.
- Bruce.
- I came as soon as I heard.
It's been 4 years, Bruce.
Where have you been?
If only the answer was as simple
as the question, Mini Fox.
Complicated's fine. We're smart.
I know. Let's find Kate,
and then I'll tell you 3 all about it.
- [CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
- It's my dad.
I should check in, but I
really don't want to leave.
No. He needs you, Mary.
You should go. We'll stay in touch.
If anyone can help us, it's you.
Barely changed the place.
Heh. Uh, you should
probably see the Batcave.
Yeah, I probably should.
Want the honors?
Not sure we have time
for a Proust read-along.
Hilarious. You can go right ahead.
You okay?
Ahem. You've been the man of
the castle for sometime now.
Lead on.
Oh. Okay.
Just like old times, right?
So, Ryan. What's new?
Anything I should I know about?
Actually, um,
I stumbled on something pretty sick,
kind of a game changer.
- Interesting.
- Yeah.
Was it housing?
No. Um, it was not housing.
Okay. What about employment?
All those years teaching martial arts,
surely there's a dojo
that will hire you.
Still looking.
Tell me you paid your court fines.
You make it sound like
these are all my choices.
They are your choices, Ryan.
You have the power to turn this around.
You want to know why
I haven't paid my fines?
Because I can't find a job
because I don't have a home
because no landlord wants
to rent to an ex-con
on post-release.
You see how this works?
No one cares that the dope wasn't mine
or... or that the Crows were dirty
or that I'm actually a decent human.
I am a file in your cabinet.
That is not having power.
That is the very definition
of powerless.
Mind if I join you?
I'd prefer it.
Any news?
Nothing.
- How you holding up?
- I'm not.
The basement vending machine can attest.
[SIGHS]
We're not finding her alive, are we?
Oh, I'm not giving up yet.
Investigators said the plane was flying
with a recalled engine part.
I heard the same thing.
Do you believe that?
Clear skies, the pilot's
psych eval checks out.
Because a few days ago,
you showed me photographs of us
being tailed by some mysterious
woman named Safiyah.
You two had drama, and I
ended up in her crosshairs.
What are you saying?
I'm saying you and Kate were close, too.
Who's to say she didn't have
the same photographs of her?
Julia, if you know something
about Kate's plane being targeted...
I know what you know.
JACOB: But, sir, we've
barely started our search.
I can send more men.
This is my daughter, Commissioner.
I am not giving up.
[SIGHS]
That sounded awful.
They I.D.ed the pilot.
His hand washed up in the harbor.
They think Kate's in the river.
But they're guessing. They
don't... know anything.
They've shifted the search
from rescue to recovery.
Who? The same people who convinced you
to stop looking for Beth
when she went missing?
Dad, we can't listen to them.
How is this happening all over again?
Hey.
You and I, we both know
that crazier things have happened.
I'm not gonna lose hope,
and I'm not gonna let
you lose it either.
LUKE: Okay. For the record,
Kate found it all on her own,
and Batwoman was her idea.
Well, Kate's not the type to sit idle
while her sister's upending Gotham.
Wait. Hold up. You know Alice is Beth?
Of course. They are my cousins.
Red accents are a choice.
Bruce, come on.
Why didn't you call or... or write
or answer one of my 3,000 texts?
Because for every Alice
Kate had, I had 20,
all trying to find a way to kill me
and everyone I cared about.
Protecting you meant not letting you in.
Sticky bomb launcher.
Ohh.
Oh. Your old man knew what he was doing,
although I would have preferred
the suit stay fully impenetrable.
Trust me. That makes two of us.
In fact, this is why Kate
flew to National City,
to ask Kara Danvers if we could destroy
one stupid piece of Kryptonite
before it got into the wrong hands.
The only material on earth strong enough
to penetrate the Batsuit.
I should probably hold onto this.
Look. I wanted it gone, okay?
I... I... I thought I could protect her.
Hey, hey, hey.
We'll find her, okay?
Wait. Where's the suit?
WOMAN: ♪ Can't you feel it coming? ♪
Never again.
- MAN: Unh!
- RYAN: Ugh!
MAN: Huh!
WOMAN: ♪ I can feel it coming ♪
♪ Are you ready for the breakthrough? ♪
♪ Can't you feel it coming? ♪
[VOCALIZING]
Time to be powerful.
WOMAN: ♪ Are you ready
for the breakthrough? ♪
♪ Are you ready for the brand-new? ♪
♪ Are you ready for the real thing? ♪
♪ Because it's coming for you ♪
Hey! Show yourself!
Boo!
Unh!
I did not think that through.
[GRUNTING]
Whoo-hoo!
Hoo hoo! Ha ha!
I'm bulletproof, bitches!
Wait. What the?
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Kate.
Ha ha! What is this, some wannabe?
Agh! Agh! Ohh!
[VOICE MODULATED] Sorry.
Legit didn't mean that.
Sorry? You freaking shot me!
Look. I'm looking for someone.
Figure the False Face
Society knows things.
So who's gonna point me
in the right direction?
I have no idea what this button does.
You want to figure it out together,
or you want to help?
WOMAN: ♪ So now ♪
♪ I'm taking what I want ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm-a calling payback ♪
♪ Treat you like a street rat ♪
Blech.
♪ You thought you played with fire ♪
- ♪ But I'mma trip the wire ♪
- _
Not for long.
ALICE: I got to hand it to you, Tommy.
What the hell are you doing here?
I gave you the face,
but you nailed the voice,
and now Gotham's most
eligible bachelor's
playing find the tan lines
while I... flail... aimlessly.
Can't say I didn't hold up
my end of the deal, hmm?
The only thing stronger
than the Batsuit,
which Mini Fox is in the
process of retrieving,
and very soon, the world
will call me Batman.
Oh. Do you want a parade?
Because I'm pretty sure my sister
is in the large intestine
of a great white.
Oh, is that what this is?
Are you in mourning?
You wanted her dead.
Wanted to kill her myself!
Not to say, "I told you so",
to a... belligerent psychopath.
You could have shot her months ago
when she was out of the suit.
Heh heh. When did I say
I was going to shoot her?
I said I wanted her dead.
Ehh. You..."Cousin Bruce"...
procured the Kryptonite.
I was going to ensure
Commander Kane found it.
A scene would bring them together.
Batty would get caught
in his crosshairs.
Then bang! As she went down,
he would pull off her cowl,
to discover in sinking horror
that he had killed his own daughter.
Alas... mechanical failure.
WOMAN: Hey, Bruce. There's no steam
coming out of the steam shower.
What the hell did you do that for?
No reason at all because
reason doesn't matter.
She's got a friend upstairs.
You want her to call the cops?
I tried being reasonable once.
I... was tethered to reason.
I was calculated, precise, planned,
and look where that got me.
Sharing a roof with Bruce lame.
On what planet do I agree
to live with a woman
who just told me her plan
to have her father kill her twin
like it was some kind
of April Fool's joke.
On my planet
because on my planet
you are still Tommy Elliot,
and if I so much as breathe a word,
Bruce Wayne goes from being the meat
in a top model sandwich
to the guy with a steak for a face!
Trust me, Tom-Tom.
An Alice with a goal is so much sweeter
than an Alice unmoored.
[SIGHS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Fancy seeing you here.
Figured I'd look around to see
if Kate had been getting
any death threats.
And what did we deduce from that jumper?
Is it dangerous?
What are you doing here?
Before she left, Kate said that
if anything ever happened to her
that I should check her safe.
Okay. Where is it?
She also asked that I not tell anyone.
Pretty sure she didn't mean me.
Why? Some sort of unrequited
soul mate clause?
Because I think Kate has been
targeted for some reason,
and she knows I won't stop
until I find the truth.
[BEEPING]
Uh, GPS says it's this way.
[BEEPING ACCELERATING]
MARY: Kate? Kate!
You're alive!
LUKE: No.
Guess you're in on it, too.
I saw her plane go down,
put two and two together.
I'm really sorry.
[SIGHS]
Well, the suit has GPS,
so you might as well just
give it back now, Miss...
Wilder, Ryan, and I'm
not done with it yet.
That suit is meant for a hero,
not the lost and found.
You tell that to the bored billionaire
who found it in Batman's lost box?
LUKE: You don't know the
first thing about Kate Kane,
and you sure as hell don't know
anything about that symbol.
Trust me, I know I'm not a symbol
or a name or a legacy.
Exactly, so why do you think
you're worthy of wearing it?
Because I'm a number.
I am the 327th baby of a black woman
who died during childbirth that year.
I'm a $20 a day check to a group home.
I'm inmate 4075, serving 18 months
for a crime I didn't commit,
but I can live with all those numbers
because the mama who adopted me,
I was her number one,
but it turns out she's just one
of a quarter million
murders in this country
who have not seen justice,
and that is a number I can't live with,
so you can have this damn suit back
when her killer is dead.
Uh...
Ha!
Bruce Wayne.
I take it they're out
of cocaine in Belize.
Missed you, too, Uncle Jake.
You know, believe it or not,
I came home to help
find my favorite cousin.
You want to help?
You stay out of my way
and let me do my job.
That's why I'm here...
to eliminate distractions.
I have a lead on Gotham's
most elusive terrorist.
Batwoman? I scared her away.
I'm referring to Alice.
How? You just got home.
Exactly. She's squatting in my house.
She must have figured
I was gone for good.
Now look. Before you barge in there
and start mucking up all my furniture,
I'd prefer not to end
up on her kill list.
You didn't hear this from me.
[DOOR SHUTS]
Bruce?
- Oh!
- Julia Pennyworth.
Oh! Luke told me you were back.
Yeah. I meant to call, but, um...
No. We've all been so worried about you.
I'm here, I'm healthy,
and I'm late for a
meeting actually, so...
did you ring The Eagle?
Eagle?
The Eagle. Daddy practically raised you.
I think he thinks you're dead.
Good point. Um, yeah,
I'll clear that up.
Well, he's at home in Glasgow,
same little cottage in the woods.
I'll buzz him ASAP.
Good seeing you, Jules.
LUKE: Look, Mary, there's no point.
Okay. She figured out
how to turn off the GPS.
I know, but if I learn more
about this Ryan Wilder chick,
maybe I can narrow down her circles
and figure out where she lives.
RYAN: "The Kane family has
turned their 56th-floor
riverside penthouse into a
search party headquarters".
Hmm. That would be nice. 56 floors up.
Talk about optimal sunlight.
Don't look at me like that.
MARY: Her mom died in childbirth,
father died before she was born.
RYAN: "Following her father's footsteps,
Kate attended Point Rock Academy".
MARY: In and out of group homes,
teen runaway, high-school dropout.
Oh. Wait a minute. This is juicy.
"Kate was dishonorably discharged
weeks before graduation.
In her statement, Kate said,
'It's paradoxical to fight on behalf
of an institution that sees...
my sexual orientation as the enemy.'"
Okay. That's kind of badass.
MARY: Arrested for
possession and intent.
Insisted the drugs weren't hers
and served 18 months.
"Under Pride Real Estate,
she donated millions
to inner city housing projects.
Most recently, she opened The Hold-Up,
a gay bar that she called a safe haven
for anyone looking for their family".
At her sentencing, the judge said that
Ryan had been on the right track
thanks to the woman who adopted her.
Ryan graduated high
school, she found a job.
Everything fell apart after.
Oh, my God.
[RYAN GRUNTING]
Apparently when Ryan and
her adoptive mom walked
into their new apartment,
they startled a bunch of squatters,
and a fight broke out.
The building's landlord
and Ryan's mom were killed.
What the hell is this?
Who are these people?
MAN: I don't know. They just showed up.
ALICE: We need to get out of here now!
MARY: The squatters were linked
to the Alice in Wonderland gang.
[DOOR SHUTS]
That's why she wants the suit,
to go after Alice
because Alice's gang killed her mom.
3, 4, 5, 6! Come on, Mommy! Live!
Wake up! Please!
[SOBS]
Wake up, please, Mama!
Kate's a hero...
in the suit...
[SOBS]
I'm sorry, Mama.
and out of the suit.
[SIGHS]
They're right, Mama.
What am I doing wearing
the suit of a hero
when I couldn't even save you?
MARY: I mean, I get it.
Her mom died in her arms.
She wants justice.
Hey.
We're gonna find Kate.
She needed the suit to survive.
Miracles happen. I mean...
It's my fault.
I was the one hell-bent on
destroying the Kryptonite.
She didn't even want
to do it, and I pushed.
Luke, that is not what happened.
I'm the reason she got on that plane.
Kate's dead...
because of me.
Luke.
You didn't do anything wrong, okay?
Yeah.
Look at me.
What would Kate say if she knew
you were blaming yourself?
I don't know. Things
are usually her fault.
She'd tell you that there'd be
no Batwoman without Luke Fox
and to put your pain into
something worth changing.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
[BEEPING]
Come get your suit back.
He didn't remember our
codename for my father.
The Eagle? He made it up.
Yes. I told him to ring Daddy at home
at his cottage in Glasgow.
Bruce didn't blink an eye.
Alfred lives in a flat in London.
I smelled alcohol on his breath.
I saw he had a drink in
the commander's office,
ran the glass for prints.
Please do not say what I
think you're about to say.
I'm really sorry, Luke.
_
I think Alice made him a new face.
No. No. They carried Tommy Elliot
out of Arkham in a body bag.
Or they wanted us to believe as much,
and who better to masquerade
as Bruce Wayne
than the person who's been
obsessed with him his entire life?
- [BEEPING]
- _
How did I not see this?
Bruce is my friend, and Tommy...
Tommy Elliot killed my dad!
MARY: Luke, you wanted Kate back,
and if the miracle arrival
of Bruce Wayne
could help find her,
then why question it?
I showed him the Batcave.
Where is it, Brucey boy?
I know it's here somewhere.
There she is.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BEEPING]
- He's going after Ryan.
- Ryan? Why?
For the suit
so he can be Batman.
[PIANO PLAYING]
ALICE: ♪ I know something
you don't know ♪
You know where Kate is?
Alice, if you know where she is,
you tell me right now!
[PLAYS GLISSANDO]
What do I know? What do I know?
I know what a watermelon looks like
when it falls from a great height.
That's your sister you're talking about.
And now she's gone,
which is probably your cue
to move on with your life,
maybe remarry, find a new
daughter to replace her with.
I'm not making the same
mistakes I made with you.
I will not stop looking
until she's found.
It's over, Alice...
Kate Kane is Batwoman!
And I'm the Joker. Arkham's waiting.
Use your brain, Commander.
A lesbian superhero
who could have killed me
a dozen times but didn't?
Hmm. I wonder who that could be.
That's preposterous.
Kate would have told me.
You rejected her
over and over to the world, to her face.
Hee hee! You wanted her dead.
- You're wrong.
- Am I,
or did you spend your last
precious moments together
firing a gun at her?
You got your wish, Daddy.
Batwoman is dead,
and she died knowing
that her father hated her.
If you don't believe me,
turn on the Bat-Signal,
see if she comes.
LUKE, ON COMMS: Uh, Batcave to R-Ryan.
Batcave to Ryan. Batcave to Ryan.
You've got someone coming for you.
WOMAN: ♪ No, this
ain't no time to rest ♪
♪ No, this ain't no time to stop ♪
♪ 'Cause you know I'm headed up ♪
♪ 'Bout to turn my level up ♪
♪ Yeah, you know I talked enough ♪
Hello. I'm... I'm here.
Is Batman actually chasing me right now?
♪ I'm about to go to work ♪
LUKE: It's not Batman.
It's Tommy Elliot.
He looks like Bruce Wayne,
but he's actually a psychotic
Arkham escapee
who will kill anyone in his path.
Yeah. You're not making it any better.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
TOMMY: ♪ Jingle bells, Batman smells ♪
♪ Robin laid an egg ♪
Come on!
WOMAN: ♪ 'Bout to turn my level up ♪
♪ Yeah, you know I'm tough enough ♪
♪ Coming back no matter what ♪
♪ From the back to the front ♪
Are you kidding me? What was that?
He wants the suit.
He can have it. I'll
toss it out the window!
- No!
- No! If he gets that suit,
he becomes the most
dangerous person in Gotham.
- You need to outrun him.
- Outrun him?
Look at his car. I don't
even have hubcaps!
WOMAN: ♪ Just about, yeah ♪
♪ I'm about to go to work ♪
Here's a sentence
I've never said before.
Can you hack the Batmobile?
I'll try. Until 10 minutes ago,
I didn't even know it was in here.
WOMAN: ♪ I've worked
at the highest levels ♪
[TIRES SQUEALING]
♪ Work, work, work ♪
♪ I just work ♪
I'm in.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
♪ I'm about to make some noise ♪
[EXPLOSION]
Come on!
Well, that bought her some time.
Yeah. Time maybe, but she
needs to buy her own survival.
♪ Hello? ♪
♪ I want my Batsuit ♪
Oh, crap.
What?
- What?!
- Tommy has the Kryptonite.
You're not Bruce Wayne.
And you're not Batwoman.
Unh!
LUKE: Batcave to Ryan. Hello? Ryan?
Batcave to Ryan. Talk to me.
[DOROTHY'S "AIN'T OUR
TIME TO DIE" PLAYING]
♪ So I hang on ♪
♪ Hang on, oh, whoa ♪
♪ It ain't our time to die ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh, whoa ♪
♪ It ain't our time die ♪
Unh!
No!
[GRUNTING]
LUKE ON COMMS: Batcave to Ryan. Come in.
Come in.
Batcave to Ryan. Come in. Ryan.
Batcave to Ryan. Come in.
We're good.
It's done. It's over.
Sophie called.
Divers still haven't found
anything in the harbor.
Well, as long as my dad's in
charge, no one's giving up.
In the meantime, Tommy Elliot's
on his way back to Arkham.
I know we're in no mood
to pop a bottle of bub,
but at least Ryan stopped
Tommy from getting the suit.
Hey. We're just lucky
we got the Batmobile back
before the cops showed up.
My point is we may
have been a little judgy
when we first met her.
She did a good job filling in today.
Kate is Batwoman, Mary.
I know. Uh...
[THUD]
It's not bulletproof, FYI.
Is this from the Kryptonite?
You mean this? Yeah.
Hurt like a bitch, too.
This was supposed to kill you.
Yeah. Well, it didn't.
Are you okay? Can I see the wound?
Heh. I'm good.
Look. I'm sorry about Kate's suit.
I hope you find her.
Uh...
Wait.
What about everything that you said?
What... what about your mom?
That suit, it's bigger than me.
It's one thing to put it on,
and it's another thing to wear it.
Like you said, Kate was a hero.
I'm not.
Are you still in love with Kate?
Where did that come from?
Because I know how you used to feel,
that if you could do it all over again
you would have jumped on her bike
and left Point Rock in your dust.
How do you even know that?
The question is...
did you still feel that
way two days ago?
I don't know.
This is what Kate left in her safe.
I didn't read it,
but I have a feeling
I know what it says.
WOMAN: ♪ It's the setting of the sun ♪
- ♪ The reckoning ♪
- _
♪ It's the ages come undone ♪
♪ It's the beating of the drum ♪
♪ The reckoning ♪
SOPHIE, VOICE-OVER: "Hey, Sophie,
if you're reading this,
it means I'm not here to
tell you this in person.
I'm Batwoman.
Though part of me thinks you always knew
even when I did a damn good
job of convincing you otherwise,
I'm telling you this because I know
you'll figure it out eventually,
and I want you to know that lying to you
was the hardest thing I've ever done,
but I lied because I love you,
because I wanted to protect you,
and because I was scared
that you would push me away,
so that's the truth.
I hope you think I did
a good job for our city,
and I hope you'll always remember me".
WOMAN: ♪ To feel, we live ♪
♪ We breathe ♪
♪ We need ♪
♪ S.O.S. ♪
_
[SIGHS]
Good news, my dear Mouse.
I have purpose once again.
It was Safiyah
who ruined everything,
and now I'm going to ruin her.
It's lucky you're dead already,
my dear brother,
because there's a war coming to Gotham,
and now there's no Batwoman to stop it.
Heh heh heh.
I did the right thing today, Mama,
and I will try to do the
right thing tomorrow
and the next day,
and sooner or later, I promise,
I'll be your number one girl again.
What the hell was that?
MAN: Greg, move your head!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -