Good evening,
fair citizens of Gotham City.
Black Mask here.
I ask you to look past
this ghoulish veil
and realize it is not the
affectation of a madman
but rather the necessary concealment
of an altruist, so...
This isn't America's Funniest Pets.
How does one fix...
- It's on every channel.
- A broken city?
Well, I've heard the phrase "defund
the police" bandied about. Please.
The GCPD can't afford
the hole in its doughnut.
Well, what about Arkham Asylum,
that house of horrors
that you fund with your tax dollars,
or Blackgate Prison
too violent for Jacob Kane
loving father of lunatic at large
Alice of Wonderland?
Well, how about Gotham City Hall then
or the judges or the D.A.
or the banks,
all chock full of predatory
degenerates
so, crooked they've got to screw
their pants on in the morning?
And don't even get me
started on Batwoman
operating without checks or balances
leaving the collateral damage
of an untold number
of innocents in her wake.
Why are we allowing
these self-serving bandits
to dictate to us what the
terms fair and just mean?
We should be dictating
these terms to them
so I'm asking you to join me
for an evening of anarchy.
Help me raze every single one
of these moldering institutions
to their foundations.
I've dropped masks
at a dozen street corners.
Stand up, strap one on,
become your own vigilante
and when the dust finally settles
over our failed system
well, Black Mask
will still be standing
ready to lead you to your liberation
because you know what
they say about power?
Use it...
Or lose it.
Dear Gotham,
I loved being Batwoman
and I want you to know I never took
wearing the symbol for granted...
Because I know how badly this
city needed a protector...
Someone to inspire hope
someone to prove that there's
something better for us out there.
You've always needed a hero, Gotham
but in this moment,
maybe that's not me.
But I ask you to
look past this ghoulish veil
and realize it is not the
affectation...
Okay. Bat team mission to-do list.
Number one, find Circe.
Number two, get Kate back.
Number three, apprehend Black Mask.
Number four, stop a possible faction
of very angry people
from overthrowing the government.
- Am I missing anything?
- Yeah, how?
So it was my job to make the list.
Okay.
Even if we did find Kate
without the internet, without
Wayne satellites, without phones
and then I somehow managed
to take out
a homicidal sadist
and his armed gang
and then I kidnapped
Circe without my Batsuit
it still doesn't mean
we'll be able to pull Kate out.
Enigma is dead, trinkets didn't work.
Her own family barely made a dent.
There has to be something
that we're not thinking of.
Yeah, but first, we need to find her.
First, we find Black Mask,
then we find Circe.
Whatever, here's the list.
Renumber it however you'd like.
Sophie is on her way with supplies.
I need to head back to the clinic
and prep for a very busy night.
When you guys come up
with a game plan
call me or send a raven or whatever.
Oh, that reminds me.
They max out after five miles,
but they're better than nothing.
So click the button
on the side to talk.
Yes, thank you. We all know
how walkie-talkies work.
Be safe. I love you guys.
I've watched this stream 50 times,
I'm at 5% battery
and I have no idea where
Black Mask is broadcasting from.
Wait, hang on.
I think I got something.
Now Batman, there's a classic hero.
Great voice, no shame.
I mean, he built abdominals
directly into his suit, right?
And he kept trophies
from every single nut job
he dumped at Arkham.
Keeping them off the streets my ass.
He wanted to relish in
the feeling of being powerful.
Who can blame him?
In my day,
Venom turned Bane
into a hulking terror.
Guy could rip the tooth
out of your smile
while shrugging off a
pipe wrench, you know?
Don't worry, Mr. Tavaroff.
I wouldn't do that to you.
And you convinced your lab rat
that the tranquilizing properties
of the Snakebite's vapor
would counteract
the Venom's roid rage.
Well, let's face it. Everybody wants
a bulletproof army,
but nobody wants to deal
with Bane's tantrums all day.
So you're building an
indestructible army.
Was Black Mask not scary enough?
I don't want to be feared,
sweetheart.
I want to be loved.
By dawn tomorrow,
the GCPD will have collapsed
under the weight of
its own depravity,
and Mayor Akins will have been,
shall we say, removed from office
and they by noon,
well, the good people of Gotham
and there's millions
of them, believe it or not...
will be quaking with fear.
"Who will save us now?"
And that's
when Roman Sionis swoops in
and puts a bullet right through
Black Mask's shiny skull.
This of course after
I've offered a raise
to whoever volunteers
to wear my mask that day.
And with Black Mask dead,
Gotham crowns Roman Sionis
as their white knight.
City is mine.
I'm the establishment.
I'm the system.
I'm the invulnerable ruler,
and anyone who tries to stop me
gets to meet you.
And they wonder why we test
our products on animals first!
Get rid of him.
Still...
Begs the question...
How does one become invincible?
It's the Channel 64
Gotham Live logo. Over.
Wait, how did you get online?
"How'd you get online? Over".
We can't talk on top of each other.
Whatever. Over.
Turns out I should have explored
my dad's old workshop sooner.
I found a bunch of old city almanacs
and I matched the letters you found
in Black Mask's reflection
to the old Gotham Live logo.
5566 Olive.
Hope you can read a map. Over.
We'll radio when we get there.
Didn't realize this was a date.
Bitch shot me with a crossbow
while I was trapped in an elevator.
Yeah, and she beat my
ass twice and I wasn't.
Sophie, Circe is stronger
and she's ruthless.
And you're Batwoman.
Am I?
Without the suit,
the gadgets, the symbol,
- I'm just Ryan Wilder.
- Damn right you're Ryan Wilder
and this chick's about
to learn that the hard way.
Where's Kate?
What are you doing in my loft?
I'm sorry, your loft?
You took her bedroom, too?
Kate's not Kate, Circe played us.
- I know, Safiyah told me.
- Wait Safiyah's still in Gotham.
She's not gonna be a problem
unless of course
you're rooting around
the east side scrapyard looking
to strip an '86 Firebird for parts.
Ryan, you take the guy in the car.
It's Mayor Akins.
Hey. Hey, Mayor. Stay with me.
- Stay with me, come on.
- You can't let them take our city.
You got to hold on, okay?
Here, emergencies are channel nine.
Keep trying till you get through.
- Wait, where the hell are you going?
- I know how to beat Circe.
- Ryan, I need to go with you.
- He needs you here now.
Remember when you
needed someone to stand behind
so False Face's
bullets didn't hit you?
Time to return the favor.
We infiltrate Black Mask's hideout
and we pull Kate out together.
Let me guess.
You don't feel confident
fighting without your supersuit
and don't want to risk Soph's life,
so I'm her crash test dummy?
Take the mask, Alice.
Just say the magic words.
I need you, okay?
I know.
Dad...
What were you up to?
We need oxygen!
Let's get that door open hurry up.
You've got to be kidding me.
- You know him?
- Unfortunately.
Someone found him in a dumpster.
Checked his heart in the alley.
No idea how he's not dead.
I can't believe we're wasting
oxygen on this guy.
I don't remember him being this huge.
That might have something
to do with whatever he mixed
with the Snakebite in his arm.
How'd he get Snakebite?
Batwoman shut down the manufacturer.
There shouldn't be
any left in the city.
Apparently he knows someone
who knows someone.
Looks custom.
It's being atomized
through the respirator.
The vapors must be lessening the hit.
A longer high without ODing?
Don't want to leave.
Makes the memories last forever.
I got to go.
That makes sense now.
Are you talking?
I just realized why your mail's
in my sister's loft.
You "live there" now.
You read my mail.
Relax.
It's just a super sexy power bill
postcard from Angelique
she sends her XOs...
Oh, and don't forget you have
a parole board
hearing tomorrow at 9.15am
They really let anyone be a superhero
these days, don't they?
Trust me, you're not
the only one in the car
shocked I've served
more time than you.
Oh, I'm serving my time, dear
just not in the traditional sense.
Remind me to get
the name of your lawyer.
Safiyah's punishment is worse
than a stint at Blackgate.
By killing Ocean, she made
sure I would spend
the rest of my life
in agonizing grief.
She didn't let me say goodbye.
Okay. We're here.
I'm saying I get it.
I get why you hate me.
Hey!
Hey! I said I'm sorry.
What do you want,
forgiveness
because you know what it feels like
to have the one person who cared
about you ripped from your life?
Get this through your head.
You don't deserve my forgiveness.
Why? Because you're the hero
and I'm the villain?
You're not a hero, Ryan,
but you already know that
which is why I'm here,
which is why you're so desperate
to get Kate back,
because your city is falling apart
- and you can't save it.
- Put on your mask.
What kind of hero kills
the first woman they've ever met?
What are you talking about?
Your biological mother
died in childbirth, right?
See, when a girl leaves me
at the whims
of a madman
with a fingernail extractor
my first task upon escaping is
to learn everything about her
and I know that your
first act on this earth
resulted in Mommy's death,
so if you want to point fingers
at who killed
the moms in your life...
We are gonna find Kate.
Then I'm gonna do
everything in my power
to dump your ass behind bars.
Mary to Luke.
I have a crazy idea, over.
- You need to lie down.
- Where is it?
- I don't know!
I get that this is a hail Mary,
but we've exhausted every other idea
and an atomized dose of Snakebite
is way less dangerous
than the injectable
so we expose Kate to some vapors
it triggers a core memory
and we bring her back.
- That is...
- Insane? Over.
Luke? Did I lose you?
Luke, can you hear me?
- Mary, do you copy?
- Yes, yes, copy.
- So Snakebite yes or no?
- I think it's brilliant.
Oh, my god. Over.
... for an evening of anarchy.
Help me raze every single one
of these moldering institutions
to their foundations.
I've dropped masks at
a dozen street corners.
Stand up, strap one on
become your own vigilante
and when the dust finally settles
over our failed system,
well, Black Mask
will still be standing
ready to lead you to your liberation...
Well, this looks
like it's gonna end well.
He's experimenting.
Okay, we need
to get these out of here.
Heads up!
You're gonna use my
own staff against me?
Is it really yours, though?
You were really gonna stab
your own sister in the back?
It's kind of our thing.
Thanks for once.
Get that stuff home and lock it up.
Follow her, I'll distract him.
- I can't beat her.
- And I can't drive the Batmobile.
Save my sister.
The letter dropped off at multiple
news outlets around the city.
The letter from Batwoman
went on to say,
"Someone to prove
that there's something better
for us out there".
The crusader ended her
handwritten note with this...
"You've always needed a hero, Gotham
but in this moment,
maybe that's not me.
Maybe it's a job for all of you now
to trust what you know in your heart
to be right and good
and to find the courage
to use that feeling as
a uniting force against hate".
- Guys, look.
- We're listening to Vesper.
No, seriously, look.
Is that one of those skull masks?
Why is that in this house?
Our neighbors put one
up in their window can we?
Well, I'll be damned.
You! Where's my Snakebite?
Come here! Where is it?
Give me your bag!
I'll give you the Snakebite.
Here.
Back away, or neither of us get it.
Now you're just being an idiot.
Still working out the kinks.
What, what is happening?
This acts like an aerosol,
but it's still Snakebite,
so make sure you get
close but not so close
that you accidentally spray yourself.
Okay, you need to go.
I can't stop Circe.
- Ryan, yes, you can.
- I tried, Mary.
I can't, not without the suit.
They improvise so can you.
Damn.
You don't need the suit
to be Batwoman.
She's already in you.
What the hell are you?
Justice.
You want to know
why you failed as a villain?
Yeah.
Please.
How did you know?
You can't be bad and have feelings.
You can't hate Batwoman
and protect her identity.
You can't hate your sister
and risk your life for her.
See, it's confusing. You can't
sell a confusing message.
Says the freak with two names.
Two names, one goal.
Black Mask terrifies the city.
Roman Sionis rescues it.
You know who was a great villain?
The Joker!
No!
- It won't come off!
- Good luck with your messaging.
The Sionises
live at 2325 Finger Hill
at least according to the Gotham
White Pages from five years ago.
Okay, I'm on 5th and Gray.
Copy. Trigate's the only
bridge out of the city
in that direction,
so if you turn left on Adams
and take riverside,
you might be able to cut her off.
I got eyes, thanks.
Good luck.
Okay, so that's how you want to play?
Damn you can ride a bike.
All right, this bitch is crazy.
- Time to give up, Ryan.
- Call me Batwoman.
Snakebite!
No!
What are you doing?
Tatiana's on her way here
to kill you. Get up!
I'd love to.
Unfortunately, I'm very distracted
renting us a camper at the moment.
I'm sorry.
Tatiana got the jump on you
because you were booking us
a vacation?
Not a vacation, Alice,
a new life
so you and I could disappear together
on the other side of the globe
get away from...
All of this.
Safiyah was right.
I was always gonna have
to choose one of you.
Since you wouldn't choose
Safiyah chose for you.
I thought this Snakebite high
was supposed to be fun.
I think you're missing the point.
This is my goodbye
but I don't... I don't want
to say good-bye to you.
Do me a favor, Alice.
You know this feeling that you feel?
and now that you know
you're capable of feeling it
chase it again.
So, you gonna say
goodbye to me or what?
Beth?
- Kate. Kate, wake up!
- Move, move, move.
One, two, three, four, five.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- Tilt her head back. Help me.
- What?
- She needs air.
What do I need to do?
So you're gonna use one
hand to pinch her nose
and the other to stabilize her head.
Start breathing.
- Nothing's happening.
- Again.
Don't die! Please don't die.
Hey. We got this, okay? Do it again.
Okay.
Don't leave me.
Beth?
Over here! Found some people.
That's Alice from
the Wonderland Gang.
No! No! No! Can't leave!
No, no! No!
Batwoman, if you're listening,
we got your memo
and challenge crushed.
Gotham rejected Black Mask's call
to overthrow
the government last night
and despite the citywide
power outage, sanity prevailed.
Word is leaders of both
the False Face Society
and the Wonderland Gang
are en route to Arkham
which just leaves one
last thing to reject...
your resignation letter, B-woman.
Come back to us, sister.
Gotham needs you
and more importantly
Gotham loves you.
So, Ms. Wilder,
I see that you've been
out of Blackgate for 14 months
and that your P.O. has requested
that you be released
from restrictions early
so two questions for you.
Have you changed and how?
Have I changed?
Honest answer...
No, I haven't changed.
I am still the good, caring,
intelligent human being
I was the day
I was wrongly arrested
and the day I met my cellmate
and the day I was dumped
before this board
and told I had a 75% chance
of being a repeat offender
but since I know this committee
wants to do the right thing today
allow me to give you
the answer you need.
Yes...
I've changed.
I've changed because
I stopped seeing myself
the way you see me
and started seeing myself
for who I am
a woman who has found her power.
All in favor, raise your hand.
On behalf of the power invested in me
by the City of Gotham, I hereby deem
the supervision of the
parolee Ryan Wilder
unnecessary.
Ms. Wilder, you're hereby
released from parole.
Best of luck to you.
Okay. So then me
and Ryan are standing
on this pressure plate in the middle
of Quiz Bowlstudios
having to answer all
of Cluemaster's questions
like we didn't have anything better
to do on a Friday night.
So, where were you?
Nerd flirting with a ginger cutie!
No, we were deciphering
a labyrinthine cryptogram
- to save your ass.
- Deciphering.
Anyway, Ryan zip lines us out
of there like a boss
and saves the day per usual.
Well, I'm glad to hear that
nothing's changed in Gotham
although a little birdy told me
that we have a plus-one
in the hero department.
Where did you find a supersuit?
Okay. So... when I was a kid
I drew pictures of how I imagined
a black Batman would look.
It turns out that my dad was secretly
turning those pictures into reality
but, like, today's not about me,
okay?
Kate, you're home
and you're safe and you're healthy
and Mary and I talked
about your future plans
and we support you.
Thank you.
But million-dollar question.
How does Alice fit into those plans?
You know, I spent so long thinking
that it was up to me
to bring Beth out of Alice.
Turns out Alice brought
Kate out of me.
She's my twin.
She'll always be a part of me
but until Alice wants to be Beth
I can't help her.
Hey.
- Am I interrupting?
- Not at all.
We saved you vegan pizza.
Apparently you
and I have the same taste.
Understatement of the year.
- You guys mind if we have a minute?
- Yeah. Of course, of course.
Kate.
It's really good to see you.
It's good to see you guys, too.
When did we get a Batmobile?
Sick, right? And just so you know
that was actually me
taking it easy on you, so...
- This is probably...
- So this is...
- Wait.
- You first.
- Okay.
I just want to say thank you.
That suit changed my life
in more ways than one
and it has been an honor
to be able to wear your symbol.
I put that suit on
to give back to my city.
You put it on to survive.
You know better than anyone
what that symbol means
to people who have no hope left.
Batwoman's yours, Ryan.
As for Mary and Luke...
They are my family
and I'm going to take care of them.
Thank you.
I hear you're not gonna
try to kill me this time.
True. I'm not gonna kill you,
but I can't promise that you're
not gonna want to kill me.
You're leaving Gotham.
Of course you are.
First to see my dad
and then a friend in National City.
Then I'm off to find Bruce.
Why Bruce?
My sister spent 11 years
waiting for me to find her
and I didn't.
If Bruce is alive
and trapped somewhere
maybe finding him is
the only way for me
to forgive myself
for not finding Beth.
None of that is your fault, Kate.
I wish that made me feel better.
So, you and me and timing?
Maybe in another universe,
we were meant to be together.
But in this one?
In this one
I think we both deserve
something a little easier.
Well, whoever that is for you,
I really hope for your sake...
that she can compete with this.
Well, last night proved
we made an impact on this city.
We're not just taking
bad off the streets.
- We're putting good back in.
- So what's next, Batwoman?
We find that case
of Batman trophies
before anyone else does
and from the sounds of it,
I am gonna have backup!
And now that your clinic is legit,
I was thinking what if
we build our community center
above it, make it an all-in-one
medical, mental health,
hangout for teens and you take point?
I'm so down with that.
Good, we start today.
And where are you going?
Just tying up a loose end.
Janus! Janus!
Janus!
Kane, visitor.
- Make it quick.
- Not a problem.
Damn.
Security's worse than I thought.
I only gave him 40 bucks.
Well, here you have it...
Alice behind bars
the jumpsuit,
embarrassing lack of shoelaces
a neighbor who's crazier than me.
Is it everything you'd hoped for?
I just wanted the system
to work for once.
Right.
It finally did.
This is justice for my mom.
Just happy I got
to see it with my own eyes.
I hope we never see
each other again.
Funny you should mention
mothers actually.
You remind me almost daily
that your adoptive mother is dead
but maybe there's a little
wiggle room for bio mom.
What?
You don't know.
Well, maybe
it's time someone told you.
Your mother didn't die
in childbirth, Ry-Ry.
Mommy dearest
is still very much alive.