Previously on Batwoman...
Quite frankly,
the makeover this city needs
comes from an ugly
I've never seen before.
I love you so m...
Oh, no!
We are going to get Ang back, okay?
I killed Ocean
and I felt...
nothing.
I'm alive
and very pissed off.
Angelique, where is she?
Wave hello
to your fans, Angelique.
I need you to watch
as these two let me go.
You teaming up with Sophie like
this? It's a bad idea.
Okay? She's gonna figure
out who you are. She's smart.
Ryan, on I'm really
missing my batsuit right now.
Oh, my God.
Masks have taken on...
various meanings over time.
Deceit...
disguise...
cheap entertainment.
But as Jung once said...
we all wear masks...
both to...
create an impression upon others...
but also to hide
our own true natures.
Good evening, Mr. Sionis.
It's absolutely beautiful.
Though making people look
their best is my specialty
I think this just so happens
to be my masterpiece.
For generations, every Sionis...
Has had a replica mask
decorating their casket.
I exhumed this one
from the coffin of my dearly
departed daughter.
Once dead...
now, on the verge of rebirth.
My name
is Kate Kane.
No. No.
Dr. Rhyme, if you would.
Ms. Kane...
our therapy has come
to an end-point.
On my cue...
you will remember nothing
of your life before today.
Your only memories
will be those of
Circe...
Sionis.
No.
No...
No!
I must warn you, Roman.
While psychologically
and behaviorally
she is your daughter...
There was nothing I could
do about her voice.
Her larynx was damaged
by your man
during the kidnapping
and subsequent torture.
What the hell, Dad?
why am I wearing this mask?
Now, don't you remember, sweetheart?
You were in a terrible fire
when you broke out of Arkham.
It still feels a little fuzzy.
Well, things will become
more and more clear
as the days pass.
The important thing is,
now that you have this mask...
no one will ever hurt you again.
You're a little late
for turndown service.
Where is he?
Agent Tavaroff.
Heard a rumor you got
a DNA sample from the bat?
I'll verify your rumor
if you verify mine.
Word is you were pretty tight
with the last one.
What's your point, Russell?
Oh, that you could save
the lab a lot of trouble
if you could give us
the name of this one.
How many rape kits have
to go to the back of the line
so you can make a big splash
to boost your career?
The commander know about you
squandering resources like this?
He's the one
who signed off on it, actually.
Commander?
Moore, what can I do for you?
I know how you feel
about vigilantes, sir.
But instead of wasting
our time with Batwoman
shouldn't we be trying
to figure out who Black Mask is?
Well, we were...
but Batwoman got in the way of that
ruined our undercover operation
and cost us a chance
to take down Black Mask.
She's on our side, Commander.
Well, if that were true, she wouldn't
mind being on a first-name basis.
Is that the real reason
you're doing this?
Trust?
Or is it because every time
you see her, you think of Kate?
Get out of my office, Moore.
- Excuse me?
- You think a little fling
with my daughter five years ago
gives you permission
to tell me how to do my job?
Sir, I...
I didn't mean to overstep.
Get out of my office now.
Yes, sir.
Why are you making me relive this?
Black Mask kept tabs on his
cookhouses with a video feed...
allowed him an eye on the cookie jar
without actually getting
his hand caught in it.
Smart, right? Wrong.
Because that allows me to
track the Internet traffic...
So we can track it back to the
camera's IP address
to get the location of the cookhouse
where Angelique is being held.
Not just a pretty face here, people.
Send those cookhouse coordinates
to the Batmobile.
I'm not sure that's
gonna be your first stop.
Somebody turned on the batsignal.
Hi.
It's not a pager.
A little busy here.
Well, unless you want to
give me your name and number...
What do you want?
First off...
lose the 'tude?
I'm doing you a favor.
I thought you should know
the Crows are in the process
of extracting your DNA profile
from blood spatter found
at the Snakebite facility.
Once they have that,
they're gonna upload it
to the National DNA Registry.
Of course...
they'll need something
to match it against
so you should be good.
Unless, of course,
you've ever been in the system.
Anything you want to tell me?
Other than you need
to destroy that sample?
It's already being processed.
They'll have the profile in a few hours.
Arrest warrant won't be
long after that.
I better use what time I have left
to save the one person
who had the guts to testify
against Black Mask.
Remember her?
The one the Crows were
supposed to protect?
Wait.
I can't make any promises about the
sample, but I'll do my best.
Let's hope that's enough.
Am I close?
We don't have a lot of time.
Batwoman, we took a group vote
and you need to come home.
What are you talking about?
Angelique is being held
somewhere in this dump.
And while we appreciate that
she's a former flame...
Sophie just dropped an A-bomb.
We need to figure out how
to preserve your identity.
We will once I find Angelique.
Didn't Sophie just say that we only
had a couple more hours?
Yeah. So I got to be quick.
Okay. I'm just gonna say it.
Finding Angelique is not
worth throwing
The Bat legacy down the drain.
Excuse me?
Look. I'm just saying
you can't have both.
Black Mask is using Angelique
to cook Snakebite
right? So he went through
a lot of trouble for her.
So, I highly doubt he'd just kill off
his golden goose right off-the-bat.
Priority number one
should be saving the future
of the symbol for your sake
and the city's and then...
How about this?
You two call Sophie, you all put your
heads together and save my future.
I'll be here kicking
some False Face ass,
saving my past.
I'll check in later.
Oh! Stop!
What the hell is this?
Barbeque for one?
Batty!
What brings you here?
Was it the odor?
Honestly, I've been at this so long
I can hardly smell it.
Why are you here?
The False Face kidnapped a friend...
so I've been popping
by their known hideouts,
seeing if someone would be willing
to spill his possible location.
I'm looking for someone
they kidnapped, too.
Really?
Her name wouldn't happen
to be...
I don't know...
Angelique, by chance?
How do you know that?
Well...
according to Mr. Extra-Crispy
over here...
when Angelique couldn't
conjure up the special sauce
that gives Snakebite its...
bite...
Black Mask took her phone and used it
to track down the actual chef
who does know all
11 herbs and spices.
You're talking about Ocean.
I thought you killed him?
Well, that's completely
besides the point.
Which is?
Angelique and Ocean are
apparently being held at a place
that is more fortified than this one
and quite frankly, I need backup...
by which, I mean
someone to stand behind
so that the bullets
don't hit my visage.
Damn.
You're crazier than
everyone already thinks.
Well, enemy of my enemy,
doesn't that mean...
That you're still the bitch
who murdered my mom.
Touché...
but I'm also the bitch
who knows where our
beloved cooks are.
The only one who knows,
as of now.
And as much as our...
dearly departed was forthcoming
about their location...
he wasn't as clear about
how long they'd stay alive.
Apparently, Black Mask
just wants them
to spill the recipe, so the clock
is tick, tick, ticking.
What do you say?
Partners?
That silence sounds like
a firm "yes".
You cross me...
and you don't have to worry
about bullets killing you.
Okay.
Oh, goody! I've always wanted
to ride in the Batmobile!
What does this button do?
Pisses me off. Don't make
me hit the ejector seat.
That exists?
You want to find out?
Kind of.
Initiate self-destruct?
Cool.
Hey!
This is a rescue mission,
not a school field trip.
- Stop!
- You agreed to this
little team-up pretty quickly,
which tells me that this Angelique
must be very near
and dear to your heart.
You want to tell me
where I should turn?
Keep going straight...
which I'm guessing you
didn't do with Angelique.
Come on. You can tell me everything.
Who emojied who first?
I'm dying to know how a drug chef
stole Batwoman's heart.
We are not doing this.
We are not getting
to know each other.
Everything I need to know about you
is written on my mama's grave.
Okay.
Can I help you?
Commander Kane just wanted
an update on the Batwoman sample.
Yeah?
He's not the only one.
Agent Tavaroff was
just here checking on it.
Don't worry. I'm gonna babysit
this thing the whole way.
How long until it's ready?
Not much longer.
You know we're gonna have to
deep clean the batmobile now.
Oh, I am well aware.
Based on the trajectory,
they're headed
somewhere along the waterfront.
I get the appeal of Angelique
or whatever, but how
desperate are we?
I mean, Alice?
Alice? Really?
Do we even know this isn't a trap?
Nope.
Tell me you destroyed it.
I can't. Too many eyes.
we need a plan B.
What? Sophie? No.
Every plan involves you
destroying the damn sample!
Look. My entire office is acting like
they're sitting on the nuclear codes.
I'd have an easier time
swiping records out of Area 51.
There are only 78 more minutes
till they get her profile.
Then, they're gonna upload it
to the National DNA database and...
And if she's ever been entered in
there for any reason ever...
such as an arrest...
they're gonna get a match
and the whole world will
know Batwoman's identity.
I got to go. Bye.
How do you know False Face
was telling you the truth?
Well, it's hard to lie
through your teeth
when they've all been yanked out.
Everybody ready for their closeup?
"An idiot's guide to
making Snakebite"...
take one.
And...
Action.
Take two.
There will not be a take three.
One sentry.
Looks like they're trying
to keep a low profile.
I want to see.
Why don't I get any bat toys?
Can I least have a batarang?
Okay. You draw him out...
I'll take him out.
Think you can handle that?
Sure.
What the hell are you doing?
- What you asked.
- I told you to draw him out...
not draw him to us.
And I delivered.
Your move, lover girl.
See? That worked out splendidly.
Might want to
give me that batarang now.
Hey.
Got you a prezzie.
Mary, kind of busy right now.
- I can't really do...
- It's not from me.
It's from someone who knows
how hard you are to shop for
and he...
got you this.
It's a targeted kill drive.
Your lab is turning
Batwoman's DNA evidence
Into a bunch of ones and zeroes
and that guy will rearrange
those ones and zeroes...
making it unreadable.
Didn't know you were
on Batwoman's payroll, as well.
No. Luke just asked me as a favor...
because we hang out
casually as friends.
Yeah.
So according to the Bat team...
if I use this device,
then when the file
is transmitted to the DNA registry,
it won't match anything?
- Yeah.
- That's pretty clever.
So, did Luke include
an instruction manual?
No, but he is available
for tech support.
You just have to plug
that little cutie
into any computer in the building
with tier one access.
Tier one access?
There's only one person with that.
Your dad's been holed up
in there for hours.
How the hell do you expect me
to get him to leave?
Why do you think I'm here?
We make a shockingly good team
and by we, I mean your car and I.
Where are the cooks
being held on the boat?
Because I'm gonna tell you?
Your bad.
She was the nice one.
Where are the cooks?
Upper deck. Upper deck.
If they were harmed in any way,
I swear to you on my
headless mother's grave...
He just passed out.
Oh, my God.
You love him.
I just kicked him for no reason.
- Not him. Ocean.
- Ocean? What?
No.
Is that your boyfriend?
I drove a knife through his heart.
Well, for you, that's not a no.
Oh. That's true.
I had a bit of a breakthrough
at yesterday's therapy session.
Although, it would appear
all the unresolved feelings
I have for him that
I thought I resolved
In killing him are...
as of yet, unfortunately
still on the table.
Last night's...
steamy tryst made it all
the more confusing.
That's why you needed my help.
To make sure he makes
it out of this alive.
Follow me. Stay close.
Almost through with the cook, sir.
I have to admit,
I'm quite pleased
with the performances.
Nuance is everything these days.
Slow down.
Buy ourselves as much time
as possible.
Got a perimeter breach
- at the North docks.
- What is it?
Apparently, we got company.
Looks like Batwoman.
What?
And she's with that bitch, Alice.
We need backup
at the north dock now.
How will we pass the time?
Quietly would be my first choice.
I like you.
You're fun...
but mean.
You sure this Angelique chick is
good enough for you?
She is. Thank you for your concern.
Is she, though? I mean...
city hero, drug dealer.
Doesn't exactly scream Royal wedding.
You asking for a friend...
or...
are you asking
because you accidentally
have feelings for someone
and it terrifies you?
Because...
how could anyone ever
love a monster who watched
her gang kill a woman
and not even wonder her name?
Obviously, asking for a friend.
Angelique was the only
person in our group home
who ever had my back.
I see.
So you were plucked away like
the little orphan Annie
while she was left behind.
That's why you're so determined
to save her now, isn't it?
Guilt.
Where have I heard that before?
Your predecessor was obsessed
with saving me.
She couldn't accept
reality and move on.
Poor thing didn't
realize until it was too late...
And then she died.
Just a little piece of advice...
from an antihero to a hero.
You can't save everyone...
not without losing who you are.
Go! Let's go!
They're at the North docks.
If you really want to know who I am,
you should know this about me.
I am someone who never forgets.
What are you doing?
Oh, don't worry.
I'm gonna save Ocean...
from you.
I am going to make sure
he knows exactly what you are.
And...
Cut.
That's a wrap.
Batwoman to batcave.
I'm in, but...
kind of got
a maze situation going here.
Head to the left.
There should be a stairwell in
the Northeast corner.
Copy.
- Hey.
- Hey. So the lab's
about to upload Batwoman's
DNA to the mainframe.
Talk me through this.
As soon as the file's uploaded...
click on Batwoman's profile.
It'll shred that baby
to high- tech ribbons.
- That's it?
- That's it.
Let's hope this was worth the wait.
And...
They're starting the upload now.
Okay. Here it comes.
- Oh, no.
- What? What happened?
It's not just Batwoman's file.
They're uploading
DNA profiles from dozens
of Crows investigations.
You can't single hers out?
That's the problem.
They made the file labels
numbers for anonymity.
There are no names.
Meaning, there's no way
to tell them apart.
The only way to get Batwoman's
would be to corrupt them all.
How serious are these cases?
This being Gotham, we can be
damn sure it's not for jaywalking.
If we did this...
we wouldn't just be
protecting Batwoman.
We would be protecting
rapists and murderers.
We can't do it, Luke.
What about Batwoman, Sophie?
The results will be back
in a matter of minutes.
What are we supposed to do?
I might have an idea.
What is this?
Guess who passed
the health inspection with
flying colors.
Last time we spoke,
I got the distinct impression
you had no interest In
legitimizing this place.
I didn't, but I do care
about staying open
and you keeping your guys
out of my hair
so consider this...
a compromise.
I'm impressed.
We've got up-to-code storage
certified nurses and doctors.
Sad to say, that leaves me inside
most days doing paperwork.
You okay?
You're sweating. Here.
Yeah. No. I'm...
I'm fine.
So, what happens if someone
walks in with a gunshot wound
that you're supposed
to report to GCPD?
Well...
I do what the regulations say.
I fill out this
thingy and I fax it to the GCPD using
this ridiculous monstrosity...
which, I'm pretty sure,
is twice as old as I am.
This an oversight?
Well...
no one ever taught me how
to send a telegraph
or a fax or whatever they are
and there's n... nothing
in the regulations that
requires me to hire an I.T. guy.
So you figured out your workaround.
Compromise works both ways.
Well, then as far as I'm concerned,
you're clear to open shop.
- I need to get going.
- Wh...
Wait, wait, wait. Seriously...
you do get that we're basically
treating and harboring
potential criminals here.
Well, if it means you'll
start taking my calls again,
I don't need to know
that that thing is not plugged in.
I'll... I'll talk to you later.
Well, that worked.
Where's Batwoman?
Finally, a member of this lame
society who's actually trying.
Love this.
You can find her on the deck.
I'll be back for you.
Looking forward to it.
Okay.
A few more minutes and the world
will know the name behind the Bat.
Dibs on arresting her ass,
by the way.
Come on, come on.
Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
All righty. Who's ready for this?
Betting windows are closed.
The identity of Batwoman 2.0
is...
None found?
What... This is B.S.
How could she not be
in the system?
Did someone send out
Invites to a party
before they found out
If there was a party?
What are you looking at?
Back to work.
Tell Batwoman she's good.
What did you do?
It's handled.
That's all that matters.
Now, I got to delete
my digital footprint
so the commander never
finds out about this.
Look, dude.
You don't have to kill us.
We can make as many
batches as you want.
She's right, man.
Watching a how-to video
isn't the real thing.
There's a million variables.
Potency of the fear toxin,
mushroom oil...
What the hell, man?
Stop.
Wait. You don't want to do that.
What? This?
How did you find us?
Your girl Ryan sends her love.
- Can you walk?
- Go without me.
Dude, no. You're coming with us.
Come on, come on!
Hey. You're gonna get out of here.
You're gonna find that girl you
won't shut up about, okay?
Yeah.
Go find your girl.
You guys take the back...
keep your eyes up. There's
False Face everywhere.
Hey.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
They're not leaving here.
Yes, they are...
unless you can get through me.
- Thank you.
- Never
leave a woman
who's been in captivity
half her life alone
with a hairpin.
Help me!
Good luck with that.
I remember your mom.
Cora. I remember her.
Short hair, purple sweater.
I lied about forgetting her.
Now, help me...
please.
Like you said...
can't save everyone.
What?
Oh, my God.
Hey! Check it!
It's amazing what a little paint
and six figures worth of permits and
doctor's salaries will do, right?
Yeah. It's...
nice.
Hey. Have you noticed anything
strange about your dad lately?
What do you mean?
I mean his demeanor.
Any mood swings, health issues?
He seemed fine when I saw him today.
I mean, he signed off on the place.
He even saw the fax machine.
- What fax machine?
- The one that's...
not plugged in that
keeps us from having to
report our patients
to the authorities.
He signed off on that?
Your dad?
Yeah.
Why are you asking me
all these questions?
I found this in his office.
He probably seized it on a bust.
Wouldn't it be in evidence, then?
What are you saying?
It's his?
Your dad blew up at me
today out of nowhere.
He kicked me out of his office.
Then I found this a few hours later.
It sort of just sounds like my dad.
Soph, you can't be serious.
You should talk to him, Mary.
My dad is not
doing Snakebite.
Then it should be a short
conversation.
But I really think
you need to have it.
I thought you'd never
want to see me again.
Ryan, don't.
Don't what?
Apologize.
I told you...
that you'd be protected
If you ratted out Black Mask.
You almost died because of me.
No. I almost died because
that's what I signed up for.
To make a lot of money...
to feel like I matter
and to know that everything
could be ripped away at any
moment, including my life
and all the people I care about.
It's my fault.
Then let's start over...
putting all of this behind us.
Come into witness
protection with me.
- What?
- I made a deal with the feds.
Everything I know about False Face
In return for my protection.
It's real.
I trust them.
Where are you gonna go?
Come with me and find out.
There's nothing holding us back now.
Say something.
My life is here.
Here?
Gotham sucks.
It swallowed us whole
and spit us out, Ry.
But, what if it could suck less?
How? This city's a cesspool.
Look out the freaking window.
There are ways to fix it.
Like the community center
I'm working on.
Ang...
what if kids like us didn't have to
grow up in the same city we did?
I never deserved you, did I?
Are you kidding me?
You changed my life.
I'm gonna miss you, Ry.
Me, too.
Pretty swanky place you got here
for a guy who slings dope
in the streets.
Alice...
delusional leader of the defunct and
failed Wonderland gang.
Charmed, I'm sure.
I'm not.
Why is she getting
fleas on my furniture?
She was with Batwoman
during tonight's siege.
Figured you'd appreciate
a face-to-face.
Just kill her.
I didn't even do anything. I was
chained to a pipe most of the night.
Actually, there is one thing she has
that could be of interest.
Dump her in the cellar.
I'll deal with her tomorrow.