Do you know
why it's called beginner's luck?
I'll give you a clue.
It's because it's unexpected
and because it doesn't last.
As far as I'm concerned,
it'll last for 13 life sentences.
I love puzzles
but yours, rookie Crow,
is missing a few pieces.
How did you solve
clue master's riddle?
I know it's just my first day,
but a little advice...
Don't advertise the crime
you're about to commit
if you don't want to get caught.
But that's how I showcase
the sheer stupidity of mankind.
I provide the authorities
with all the clues
and then watch
as they screw it all up, anyway.
I'm sorry your view of mankind
is so bleak.
Get well.
No one has ever matched wits
with the master.
Tell me how you did it.
Moore, please. I must know.
You have the rest of your life
in here to figure it out.
Sun's up, fun's up, Brown. Get up.
Brown.
What then?
So, not to backseat hero,
but maybe leave one conscious
- To plant the tracker.
- Takes all the fun out of it.
Where's Black Mask?
Let me guess.
You're more scared of him
than you are of me.
You have a code.
He doesn't. Do the math.
I love math. Here's some.
There are three bones in your ankle.
If I break two, how many are lef...
Freeze.
Hands in the air.
You got to be kidding me.
He's ours. Back the hell away.
Kind of in the middle of something.
Kind of gonna shoot you in the face.
Hands in the air.
- Now.
- You hearing this?
I know it's tempting, but don't.
- You want to know why you guys suck?
- And here we go.
It's not just
because you don't care
about 99% of the people
in this city
or just because you lie
and you cheat
and you cover up murders.
It's because you legit
suck at your job.
Five seconds until we shoot.
I put a tracker on his boot, moron.
Guy had no idea.
He would have led me back
to Black Mask
I would have had the upper hand
and the most dangerous man in Gotham
would have been behind bars.
Instead,
your alpha asses show up late
acting like I was the enemy,
and they gave me time to do this.
I've seen my fair share
of torture toys.
If you know what I mean.
I think she knows what I mean,
but what the hell is that?
Oh, you don't need to worry
about this.
I'd rather you use your energy
conjuring up a name.
Gladly.
When you crashed my Snakebite
cookout last night
you brought a friend.
Batwoman.
Friend?
No. That conniving,
pointy-eared manipulator.
Led me down the garden path
of partnership and trust
only to stab me in the back.
But you know what?
It's my fault. I should have known.
You put on the suit, you're not happy
until Alice is behind bars
- but you know what Really irks me...
- Shut up!
I'm the one doing
the torturing here, not you.
Give me her name,
so I can destroy her life.
The way she destroyed my business.
It eludes me.
You're lying.
Black Mask enjoys people making
it difficult for themselves.
Well, then I'm your girl.
Now, if that doesn't pry something
out of you.
Well, we got nine more tries.
I'm ordering from
that bomb vegan wing place.
You want me
to order you something?
Ryan, hey.
Why is there a Crow in our loft?
I thought you were working late.
I was, but then drama showed up
and ruined my night,
so I cut out early.
Why is Crowphie here?
We were just hanging out.
I didn't realize
I had to run guests by you.
You don't. It's just... her?
Okay, look.
I'm not here to add to your drama.
The guys at work sent me tequila
for my five-year anniversary
and I wanted to share it
with someone.
You're welcome to join us.
And honestly, based on the vibage
that you just walked in here with
it kind of seems like you could use
some ultra-expensive tequila
right now.
So, am I supposed to just act like
I'm cool with her being here?
As a lesbian who was married
to a man for three years
I will say drinking is
the key to denial.
I thought you were bi.
Yeah. There's a lot we don't know
about each other yet, Ryan.
One drink.
Never have I ever had sex
on an airplane.
Everyone, relax. It was private.
Never have I ever sexted
the wrong person.
- Ryan, drink.
- Wait. What?
Oh, oh, my bad.
My bad.
Yeah, your bad.
So, whatever you have going on
with Imani
just FYI, consider me
an unwilling third.
- Oh! Who is Imani?
- I got one.
Never have I ever
compromised my values
to support a white
supremacist organization.
- Drink.
- Oh.
This is not working.
No, no, no, no. Hang on, hang on.
I got one. Okay.
Never have I ever kissed Batwoman.
Yeah.
Never have I ever been saved
by Batwoman.
When did Batwoman save you?
Last Halloween.
Oh, the O.G. makes more sense.
Why does it make more sense?
I don't know, Ryan,
why would it make absolutely no sense
for the new Batwoman
to have saved you?
It's okay.
Refills.
They say the worm is lucky.
No. No, no, no. This...
That ain't a worm.
This is why you don't drink hooch
from the Crows.
I think it's a puss caterpillar.
The southern flannel moth,
genus, Megaloypyge.
It's one of the most
venomous caterpillars
in the world.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- No.
Okay, but according to the Internet
a single caterpillar isn't lethal.
So, we're good, right?
Wait. I don't think we're the target
and I don't think this bottle came
from your boys.
What?
A girl's been poisoned.
Not you. That's no fun.
Can you save her before midnight?
I'll give you a clue, hot shot,
probably not. Love...
Clue Master.
Okay. Who the hell is
Clue Master again?
Ever watch Quiz Bowl
back in the day?
Is that the Jeopardy! rip-off?
Not on purpose.
The host Arthur Brown got fired
and went on a murdering spree.
Along the way, he laid out clues
for law enforcement
to figure out
where his next kill would be.
It stumped everyone for weeks.
Called himself Clue Master.
Guys, Arthur Brown
escaped Black Gate today.
Oh, fine. I'll call my dad,
tell him we made contact.
No, you can't.
This is all a part
of clue master's game.
If we involve the authorities,
he's gonna see it as cheating.
He's toying with me.
Getting his revenge.
- For what?
- He thinks
he's the most brilliant mind
in Gotham.
He believes I'm the only person
who's ever solved one of his puzzles,
and it's driving him crazy.
Okay. Well, it's time
to solve another one.
Yeah, "a girl's been poisoned.
Not you. That's no fun.
Can you save her before midnight?
I'll give you a clue, hot shot,
probably not.
Thanks. That's not a clue.
It's got to be, he's very specific
about the words he uses.
Has he ever called you "hot shot"
before?
Not that I know of. Why?
What are you doing?
I'm making hot shots.
Okay. That's kind of sexy.
Anybody recognize this symbol?
I do. I know where to go.
Kane.
Hi, I know I'm probably
the last person you expected to call.
Who is this?
It's Alice. Beth.
Hello?
I don't...
I... I don't understand.
I need you to trace this call,
and come rescue me.
I'm being held by Black Mask,
and the fact
that I am S.O.S.ingthe man
who had several shoot-to-kill
orders on me
should underscore my desire to get
the hell out of here.
Jacob Kane?
Hello?
You have the wrong number.
Daddy.
Daddy?
So, wait.
Clue Master knew you'd recognize
some random-ass logo
in the middle of nowhere?
It's locked.
Give me a boost.
After I put him away,
he became obsessed with me.
Where I went to school,
where I trained
what kind of tequila I drink.
He couldn't figure out
how some rookie Crow
could solve a puzzle
that no one else could.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait. What?
I don't need a boost?
You'll be fine.
First fence?
It'll come as a shock to you,
but B&E doesn't come naturally.
Start looking for our vic,
keep your guard up.
What was this puzzle about?
Quiz Bowlwas throwing a party
to honor the game show's top winners.
Arthur always thought
the writers dumbed down the questions
to appeal to a wider audience, so...
He put a riddle in the gazette
said he was gonna bomb the party.
So, how did you solve it?
The truth... I didn't.
All rookies spend a year
on the tip line
and on my very first day,
a girl called in frantic
told me about the puzzle,
then told me what it meant.
I was promoted to field agent
the very next day.
Because you lied and took credit
for something you didn't do.
You don't think it haunted me
Every time I strapped on a gun
my first year
that maybe I didn't deserve
to be there?
So, whose glory did you steal?
Someone who begged me
to keep her identity a secret
so I did.
This will come as a shock to you,
but I can be trusted.
Guys.
"Just a nip should do the trick."
It's an antihistamine.
It'll counteract the poison.
Help! Help! Help me! Help!
What did he do to her?
Oh, my god. It's Stephanie Brown,
- Clue Master's daughter.
- Help! Help me!
- Agent Moore!
- Stephanie
- we're gonna get you out of there.
- How? There's no lock, no door.
What is this?
Did... did he poison me?
Are you kidding me?
Just relax, okay?
My dad poisoned me
and locked me in a box!
- You relax!
- Hang tight.
Well, thanks. Yeah.
Where else am I gonna go?
And your brilliant plan will be?
We're at a firing range.
We shoot it open.
With the girl inside?
Would you guys shut up?
What are those?
I found these
under the railing chained
to that gun.
- It's one of his puzzles.
- Exactly.
So, if you two would just release
each other's throats for two seconds,
maybe we could actually figure
this thing out.
- Four targets.
- Yeah.
- Four bullets.
- That's how we get her out.
Look. We hit each of those targets
in this specific color order.
Too easy.
The blocks detach from the chain,
which means
they're probably not in order.
Besides, those symbols
have to mean something.
Okay. Alphabetical by animal then?
Okay. So, bird bobcat, fly,
and then spider.
Bobcat? That's a Puma,
which means it comes after fly.
It's a bobcat,
which means it comes before.
You want to bet her life on it?
Hey! There's a girl
dying in a box. Think.
If they're not in the right order,
why chain them together
- in the first place?
- Food chain.
They are in pecking order.
Okay, bobcat, Puma eats bird,
bird eats spider,
and spider eats fly.
- Let's find out.
- Who said you were shooting?
Pretty sure I just did.
Anyone want to discuss
the five shots of tequila
- you downed tonight?
- Mary.
- Yeah?
- Pick.
Someone who probably holds
a high score in duck hunt
or a military marksman?
Unless you have
some sharpshooter skills
you'd like to disclose.
- Go for it.
- Thank you. Now, back up.
Any questions?
Nope.
Hey. Drink this, drink this.
It's gonna be okay.
No. It's not.
I don't think he's done.
Word of advice.
The last person
who tried to one-up me
ended up
with his eyes gouged out
like two olives on a toothpick.
Now, that makes me want a martini.
Well, just tell Black Mask
who Batwoman is
and you'll be drinking one soon.
Here's the thing. I could
but then,
I wouldn't have the satisfaction
of killing her myself.
It's personal,
but I've had limited success
with my vengeance games as of late,
and quite frankly
it's left me feeling
rather unfulfilled.
Feelings. How awful.
I hope it's worth your life.
One eyeball at a time.
Funny story.
You remind me
of an inmate I heard of at Arkham.
Sweet Circe Sionis.
Poked the baby blues out
of some corporate bigwig.
My Mouse and I used to
call her "can't CEO killer."
Memories.
He deserved it.
Who, dear?
The corporate bigwig.
He crossed a line,
and I had to make sure
he never found his way back.
You. You gouged his eyeballs out.
Why, if it isn't Circe Sionis.
I heard that you were trampled
to death.
In the Arkham breakout.
On the contrary,
I was rescued by my father.
And did you get
those horrific burns before
or after daddy saved you?
Touchy subject?
Enough about me.
It's time to talk about Batwoman.
Bring me Black Mask.
I'll tell him exactly
what he wants to hear.
So, you woke up to discover
you were covered in
some coded message?
You say that like your dad
doesn't write cryptograms on you
while you're unconscious.
Got to be a clue to his next move.
Spoiler alert his next move
is killing you, Agent Moore.
I swear,
when I asked you to cover for me,
I had no idea he'd become
so obsessed with you.
It's not your fault.
Hold up.
You were the one who solved
Clue Master's puzzle back in the day?
Agent Moore took the bullet.
There's got to be a key built in.
If I can find the key,
I can crack the message
and stop him before he makes
his move on you.
Why would your dad do this to you?
I grew up trying
to solve his puzzles.
As I got better,
he used me as a barometer.
If I couldn't solve them,
they were good,
so this morning
after he flew the coop
he paid me a visit.
He thought I'd be his partner
in crime
tried to enlist me
in his little revenge scheme.
He said
that it took Einstein 10 years
to crack general relativity
so he wanted his masterpiece
to take half that time.
Five years
hence the fifth anniversary of me
arresting him.
He said now he can finally finish
what he started.
And let me guess,
we won't know what that is
until you crack that thing,
which is when?
Just me? I don't know.
It could take hours,
it could take days.
What if there were two of you?
It's a cryptogram.
Well, thanks from last year.
Thought you guys said
he was a human computer.
Where's the ram?
I'm sorry. Who are you exactly?
See if you can figure it out.
I'm smarter than my king.
My technology protects Wakanda.
Your name is Shuri?
You think it'd be as easy
as kissing a frog.
What is happening?
- No idea.
- I think it's how nerds flirt.
I woke a monster by reading
from the book of the dead.
I helped lay an iron giant to rest.
As smart as I'm mighty,
the chosen one
still gets all the credit.
Stephanie.
I have to admit.
I was not expecting you to get that.
The first letter of every answer
to her clues of badass ladies
spelled out her name.
Clever. Shuri, Tiana,
Evie, pepper, Hermione...
Great, yeah.
So if we are through
the foreplay section of the night,
can you two geek out
on how to figure out that thing?
- "You're stumped"?
- I see exactly what's going on
here.
"You're stumped."
That was Quiz Bowl'scatchphrase
whenever a contestant lost.
He wrote it here among a bunch
of random letters.
It's a substitution cipher.
So, we have to encrypt
which units of plain text
have been replaced with cipher text.
How long is that gonna take?
Depends.
Units can be a single letter,
- double letters, mixed.
- Monoalphabetic, Polyalphabetic...
Where do you think
your dad is now?
I figure if we can figure that out
then we don't have to deal with this.
He said he wants to finish
what he started.
Quiz Bowl's the last place
he tried bombing.
Before a stopped him,
so keep working this angle.
We'll go see if he's there.
I can't believe this is still here.
This show always creeped me out.
What the hell did we just step on?
It's Quiz Bowl time!
Hey! Show yourself!
Welcome to a special edition
of Quiz Bowl, Agent Moore!
- It's got to be a recording.
- I'm your host, Clue Master
Arthur Brown,
- and you...
- We got to get out of here.
are standing
on an explosive pressure plate.
No. It's weight-sensitive.
You step off, it blows.
Have I got your attention?
Good! Don't blow up!
We'll be right back
after a word from our sponsors.
C4 is wired to the plate.
- Any ideas?
- That whatever we do we do it quick?
He's not here. It is a recording
probably to distract me
from the puzzle he put on Stephanie.
Welcome back to Quiz Bowl.
Can you figure out a way off in time?
I'll give you a clue.
In the end, you'll solve it.
Until then, are you ready
to win yourself more time?
Yes. Give us more time.
But if you're stumped,
it's instantly game over.
- Great.
- Let's get to the Quiz Bowl.
Today's theme is Gotham villainy.
First clue.
A poor man's version Clue Master,
this questionable wordsmith
turns green with envy
when compared to me,
the premier enigmatic.
Is it, A. The Joker,
B. Poison Ivy, or, C. The Riddler?
- Riddler.
I'm not seeing it.
You?
I thought the "y"
if you're was a substitute for "s"
and that would make the "o" a "y,"
and that's when my eyes
started crossing.
Tried the Caesar cipher?
- That's way too boring for him.
- Yeah. I figured.
What's this? Play fair?
Clever.
You know the play fair cipher?
Part of MIT's mystery hunt
my freshman year.
You went to MIT.
Class of '16.
Skipped a few grades.
Why did you?
I was planning on it, but...
Not smart enough?
- Long story.
- Puzzles were how I earned
my dad's affection.
Called me his little pointer.
Turns out he was just training me
to be
his puzzle-breaking lab rat
so that he could Terrorize Goth...
Did you crack it?
Quiz Bowl was a decoy.
Okay. So, where is he?
I'm really sorry, Luke.
We are ready.
Hit me with it! Let's go!
This frosty foe gave the dark knight
a run for his money.
Is it A. Mr. Freeze B. The Penguin,
or, C. Captain Cold?
A. Mr. Freeze.
Victor Fries. When his wife got sick,
he tried to freeze her
till the found a cure.
"A run for his money."
The penguin owns Iceberg lounge,
which has a backroom casino.
Angelique used to work there.
I stand corrected.
Your final clue.
Batwoman thwarted
this tally-totaling hitman
just after donning her new do.
- Is it A. Victor Zsasz, B...
- A!
- Pretty confident.
- I read about it in the paper.
That's all for this episode
of Quiz Bowl!
Forty-five minutes on the clock,
and remember, Agent Moore,
in the end,
you'll solve it.
What does that even mean?
We should call Batwoman.
She could get us out of this.
Yeah. Because that's a possibility.
How would we even get ahold of her?
- Bat-signal.
- So you just beckon her
and she what, grapples on over?
She's shown up
every time I've turned it on.
Well, it's Friday at 2.00am,
I'm sure she's busy.
You're probably right, Ryan,
and what is your idea again
that we can accomplish in 45 minutes?
We need to replace our weight
on the pressure plate
- with an exact counterweight.
- And how do we do that?
We call Luke.
The once-powerful queen pin of Gotham
now protecting the city's hero.
It's pathetic.
I've had enough of this.
Give me Batwoman's name,
or end up all over my Malbec.
What's in a name?
Circe, Black Mask...
Roman Sionis.
What did you do?
Circe told me her father rescued her
from the Arkham breakout,
so I got to thinking
how would dear, old dad feel
about his precious daughter
hanging out with a guy who wears
a kinky skullcap?
Unless dear, old dad is the guy
in the kinky skullcap.
You just gave me three reasons
to kill you.
Relax. This is a good thing.
You happened to kidnap Gotham's
most illustrious skin seamstress.
I... I make faces, human faces.
If you want your daughter
to stop hiding
behind that cheeseboard,
Then, let me help you.
I can give you
your beautiful daughter back.
Tell me how.
Oh, I'll do one better.
I'll show you.
Sophie's right. We need Batwoman.
Unfortunately, Batwoman
is standing on a bomb at the moment.
Doesn't have to be.
What are you saying?
You want me to tell Sophie?
Maybe it's not the worst thing
in the world.
What?
Still no answer. Tried 10 times.
Okay. It's a puzzle, guys.
Clue Master said,
"in the end, you'll solve it."
We just need to figure out
what that means.
I already have.
The answer is there is no answer.
In the end, meaning end of my life,
I'll figure that out.
The way out is to die.
Ryan, we need to do something.
Easy to say from the cheap seats.
You know this pressure plate
was meant for you, right?
You know there's a terrorist
roaming somewhere
in Gotham who needs to
be stopped, right?
Hey. Okay.
The arguing is not helping.
She is the one refusing to trust me.
Why would a I trust you?
Because not trusting me means
you both die.
I will never trust a Crow,
especially you.
I know you're Batwoman, Ryan!
What?
That's crazy.
Mary, please tell her
that sounds crazy.
It's...
Insane? That's insane.
We can keep
this little charade going.
While you're both standing on a bomb
or you can tell me
what to do to save you.
Go to Kate's office at Wayne.
There's a necklace on the shelf.
You turn it,
and it'll open up an elevator.
If you take it all the way down
you'll end up in a cave
with a bunch of gadgets.
Grab the red-and-black baton.
Smart choice.
I'll be back.
It explains why Sophie came over
with that big-ass bottle of tequila.
What are you even talking about?
She was trying to liquor you up,
because we both know you can talk,
to get you to confirm her suspicions
about me.
She would never do that.
Really? Why?
Because she's your friend?
You and Luke were on my ass
for putting Angelique's life
before protecting my identity.
Where's your concern for it now?
I don't think
that this is about protecting
- your identity.
- Really? Then what is this about?
That you hate the Crows so much
you can't think rationally.
I know your history with them,
and I know how awful
they were to you,
but we're standing on a bomb, Ryan
and you would rather
watch it tick down
with me on it
than trust
a legitimately good person,
so thank god
Sophie knew you were Batwoman
because now we might actually
have a chance at not dying.
My childhood home?
I'll give you a clue.
Your puzzles are getting easier.
On the contrary, pointer.
You're getting smarter,
maybe even smarter than me.
You know it's a dog, right?
Why are you wearing
that creepy outfit?
For years,
I held a grudge against a quiz show
For dumbing down their answers.
My world was so tiny back then.
Oh, but there's nothing
like five years in prison
to expose you to all the ignorance
and stupidity on this planet.
Let's weed them out together.
What, because you're such a genius?
Your fight's not with agent Moore.
No rookie cop's smart enough
to outwit the master.
You don't get it.
She didn't outwit you.
Then, why did I spend
the last five years behind bars?
Because I put you there.
I saw your puzzle in the gazette,
I solved it.
I spoiled your plans
by calling the Crows.
Agent Moore answered.
I begged her to say that it was her
So, that you wouldn't do to me
what you were gonna do
to all those innocent
quiz bowl winners.
I taught you, I nurtured you,
I... I made you in my image.
Why would you betray me?
We're the same.
One difference, dad.
You're going back to prison.
What?
What are you doing, Dad?
What, you're gonna kill us both?
Life is a puzzle, Stephanie.
This is the only piece that fits.
No. No! Dad, unlock the door!
Unlock the door!
Stephanie, get down! Get down!
Hey. You okay?
How did you find me?
Just because I didn't go to MIT
doesn't mean I didn't get in.
I'm sorry, Mary. You're right.
I don't trust her,
and now it's gonna get us killed.
It's just...
When I walked in tonight
and interrupted girl talk
between you and Sophie...
If you want to talk, Mary,
talk to me.
She thinks my dad's on Snakebite.
What? You're no way.
Yeah. That's what I said,
but she found
a used syringe in his office, and...
It does.
It matches some strange behavior
and if you think about everything
that he's lost...
Both wives, Beth, Kate.
I mean,
after he closed down the clinic
he pretty much lost me too.
Can you blame him
for wanting to escape all this?
Sophie just wanted to check in on me.
She just wants to see me happy.
Well, let's just hope she wants
to see you alive.
Pretty sure she does.
I got it! What's the plan?
Go up to the big stage door,
open it all the way, and take cover!
- What are you gonna do?
- Go!
What... What the...?
You okay?
That was awesome.
Like I said, you can trust me.
He couldn't stand to live in a world
where I was smarter than him.
Well, according to the EMT,
he's gonna make a full recovery,
so I guess his consequence
will be having to.
You know you're nothing like him,
right?
Genetically, I'm 50 percent him,
which basically means a coin flip
will determine
if I eventually go full Vader.
Okay. It's not gonna happen.
Took you out pretty effortlessly.
Okay. A. it was a cheap shot,
and, B. you were protecting me.
- I was protecting you?
- Yeah.
You knew he'd be here,
and you knew he was dangerous.
Only thing you didn't know
is that I'd be able
to apply your keyword.
It took me a minute
to find an Arthur Brown
who once lived
on Sycamore Ave, though.
Grew up in this house.
I spent my entire childhood trying
to impress a miserable egomaniac,
and for what?
For him to try and kill me?
I don't want anything to do with him.
And you don't have to.
You will find your own people.
I did.
I'd give you my number,
but I have a feeling
you're smart enough to figure it out.
Hey, Dad.
Stopped by the penthouse
and the doorman
said he hadn't seen you in days.
Where are you? I'm worried, okay?
Call me back.
Mary, need you stat!
Oh, my god. What happened?
Couple homeless guys found him
in burn side park.
Snakebite injector still in his leg.
Dad, Dad.
Get the paddles! He's coding.
Dad, stay with me, okay? Dad!
Dad!
So, maybe Clue Master
was right all along.
You are good at puzzles.
How did you put the pieces together
that I was Batwoman?
When we infiltrated False Face.
I found the drive assist bat tech
under the steering console.
I had it analyzed and replaced
before you even noticed
it was missing.
It contained recorded audio
of you telling Luke
you wished
you were in the bat mobile.
Damn. I'm not your enemy, Ryan.
You mean you're not Batwoman's enemy
because we both know a few days ago
you thought Ryan Wilder was an ex-con
without a future.
And I'm here to say I was wrong
And I'm sorry.
Prove it.
Keep this from the Crows.
I already have.
The other day when Agent Tavaroff
was running Batwoman's DNA
for an I.D.
I erased the one casefile
it could be traced back to...
Ryan Wilder.
I know what it's like to be outed.
I didn't want to force you
to trust me.
I wanted to earn it.
I hope this is a start.
How do I know you won't kill me
the second I put this on her?
You don't. It's called suspense.
The correct answer
is because a mask like this
requires touchups.
You may have made your millions
selling overpriced wrinkle cream,
but human flesh is my department.
Put on the damn face!
I assume you have a concealer
in her skin tone.
Well, unless you want her looking
like Michael Meyers.
Are you sure this is...
Really what you want Circe?
I want to be me again.
That's all well and good,
but the real Circe died in Arkham.
I know
because I was one of the inmates
who stepped over her dead body
on my way out the door.
My name is Circe Sionis.
If you say so.
Now, this will be close
but it won't be perfect.
That wasn't the agreement.
Oh. No. I'm sorry.
My work is exquisite
but the girl in this photo
has brown eyes
and yours, my dear, are blue.
But eyes
and their adorable, little sockets.
Are your specialty...
You.
How are you...
Your eyes.
You have our father's eyes.
Kate.