Dear Kate, today's the day.
I'm supposed to die.
Truth is I'm not scared of dying.
I'm scared I didn't live.
My mama always told me
I was put on this earth for a reason,
and now I finally know what that is.
Today is the day I kill you, Kate.
I spent 11 years waiting
for you to find me
but instead, I found you.
Then, I waited for you to save me
but instead, I saved you.
I turned you into a hero.
You helped me find my inner warrior
my voice, my power.
While I played
the part of your villain
the girl who reminded you
how right and noble
and courageous you were.
You made me feel brave.
So I told you my greatest fear
was being locked away again,
and on that very day,
what did you do?
You helped me break
out of the system
that was trapping me.
You lured me into a box,
and you locked the door.
- I've come so far...
To get my revenge.
To inspire others
and I've survived much worse.
Cartwright, the queen of hearts...
Foster care, the candy lady.
If I could do that...
- I can do anything.
I can push off death another day
if it means saving you.
- I can even kill my sister.
- Hide it
I'm the one who practices
without a medical license
around here.
- What are you doing?
- It is a combination
of adrenaline and cortisone.
It will give me a jolt of energy
- and it will kill some of this pain.
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- How did you even learn
- how to do this?
- YouTube.
What?
Did the YouTube medical expert
also explain to you
that this combination
will accelerate the speed
of cell decay by 300%?
Without the shot,
you have days, and with it
you're lucky to have 24 hours.
24 hours is all I need.
I put the tracker on Alice
she probably made it
to Coryana by now.
I will follow her route.
I will find Kate
and I will get the Desert Rose
to heal myself.
And if something goes wrong, you die.
Mary, look at me.
I'm dead already.
- Oh, my god.
- Oh, god.
Fine. Team vote.
Where's Luke?
Actually...
Mary, where's Luke?
I have an active APB
and three field teams looking
for Alice
yet you not only managed to locate her
but tagged her
with a high-powered tracking device?
How?
I'm sure you're familiar
with the concept
don't ask, don't tell.
Then I won't ask. I will state.
You're working with Batwoman.
So, why doesn't she track Alice?
- Because she's sick.
- What do you mean sick?
She's dying.
Long story short, Tommy Elliot
shot her with a poison bullet
and there's no antidote.
So we need you
to bring back a stem
of the Desert Rose to heal her.
Sorry to interrupt.
Our APB for Alice and all
known associates turned up this.
Her friend Ocean boarded
a flight to Rome last night.
Thanks.
The deal Alice made with Safiyah
was that she had to kill Ocean
to get Kate back.
I doubt she showed up
to Coryana without him.
But she is crazy enough
to show up with a fake him.
It wouldn't be the first time
she slapped a face
on somebody else's body.
God knows she fooled me
with the Bruce Wayne wannabe.
If that's true and Safiyah
believes the imposter,
then she hands Kate over to Alice,
and Alice kills her.
Which means you need
to get going now.
The tracker shows that Alice left
the Olsson airstrip and flew east.
Sophie low-key slipped me the feed.
So, we're gonna gloss
over you telling
a Crow you're working with Batwoman?
It was preferable
to losing both batwomen
in one fell swoop.
Sophie said she would get a flower.
And you believe her?
Can we stay positive, please?
We land, find my daughter, get out.
- And I am screwed.
- One more thing.
We need to grab a Desert Rose
while we're there.
- What are you talking about?
- And I rest my case.
I'll explain en route,
but we're not leaving
that island without it.
- No!
- Commander!
- Wait. What the hell happened?
- They're Safiyah's men.
That would mean that Safiyah
knew they were coming.
Oh, my god.
What just happened?
They're taking them somewhere.
Looks like they're heading
toward Olsson airstrip.
It's the same airfield
that Alice left from.
So, they're going
to Coryana?
I have no idea what they're doing.
Ryan, no!
You inject that, you die today.
We literally just watched
our last hope fizzle before our eyes.
Unless anyone else
has any more brilliant ideas.
Start the clock.
I am going to Coryana,
I am saving them, I am saving Kate,
and I'm saving my damn self.
I feel good. I'm sorry.
I haven't felt this good in months.
Okay. Easy there, tiger.
The faster you work the adrenaline
through your system,
the faster it returns
to self-destruct mode.
24 hours was a guess, not a promise.
- Okay.
- Alice's transponder died
over this tiny section
of the mediterranean.
But I don't see an island.
Yeah. That's the point.
It's rigged
to avoid satellite detection.
So if I had the only serum
on the planet
that could cure cancer
and wanted to cloak it
so nobody else could have it,
I would use anti-radar
electromagnetic waves.
So the cowl's lenses can detect
the electromagnetic field.
Consider it your bullseye.
- Bullseye for what?
- These are emp grenades.
So according to Sophie,
the only electricity
that she saw on the island was used
for electric wrist restraints.
So a few of these will knock out
the power for a few hours
and free anyone wearing them,
presumably Mary's dad,
Sophie, and Kate.
Okay. You didn't answer my question
about the bullseye.
I got to find you a ride.
Okay.
Can I address
the elephant in the room?
You are not going to die.
Actually...
The elephant is if I live.
Say I find Kate
and I bring her back here.
Then what?
She's Batwoman, right?
What does that make me?
That's not gonna...
Kate would never push you out
like that.
So, then there's two Batwomen?
Because that's not confusing.
Look, I don't know
what happens
when Kate comes back.
All I know is that I...
I really, really want her back.
I know.
But...
If I do die...
You're in charge of my baby.
No, no, no.
That's not me.
Yes.
Angelique gave her to me,
and I was gonna give her to my mom
when we moved into our place.
She's all I have left of her.
Well, then it's official.
You definitely have to make it back
because I couldn't even keep
my tamagotchi alive for five minutes,
so...
I think I just found you a ride.
Okay. And?
Let's just say I couldn't order you
the vegan option.
You couldn't even afford coach?
We're just lucky this mail carrier's
gonna fly within five minutes
of Coryana's airspace.
- Clock's ticking.
- Yeah. 18 hours to live.
- I got it.
- No. I mean,
you're about 25 minutes
from the drop.
The what now?
I can override the door sensor
and buy you a 30-second window
for the halo jump.
What, what the hell is a halo jump?
High altitude, low opening.
You asked about the bullseye.
You need to hit a tiny target
from 33,000 feet.
Yeah, yeah.
This would be a lot easier
if we had a batplane.
That's what I've been saying.
Okay. I'll get right on
that after I work out
the kinks in the batsub.
Don't deploy your cute
until your heads-up display
reads 3,500 feet
so you avoid detection.
Oh, and use your pressure mask.
Otherwise, you'll die instantly.
Is this a bad time to say
I have never been on a plane before?
Tatiana informed me the two of you
had a little chat.
Of course she did.
That she told you how you
and Ocean fell in love
how he stole a Desert Rose
and how he convinced
you to leave Coryana with him.
That was the gist of it
less a few juicy details
about how he wasn't
the only islander who loved me.
I want to be clear about something.
I considered Ocean a brother.
I had you both erased
from each other because I...
Believed you were
a bad influence on him.
Got it.
A ruler doesn't get to play
by the whims of her emotions, Alice.
Nor can she afford to be blind
to what's right in front of her.
You've disappointed me.
I brought you your brother
with your fancy knife
through his chest.
Now, give me my sister
so I can put one through hers.
You foolish girl.
My men found a tracker on your boot.
You were being followed.
You okay?
I think so.
Where the hell are we?
Exactly where you wanted to be.
Not how you saw this going?
Are you kidding me right now?
There's nothing down there!
Yes, there is,
and you're gonna miss it.
- You need to jump.
- Well, that's easy for you to say.
What if my chute doesn't open?
It will! Ryan, hurry up!
If you miss your window,
you're gonna end up
in the middle of the Ocean,
and there's no shark repellant
on the utility belt.
- Well, why not?
- Because that's stupid. Now, go!
Okay. Okay. You got this.
You got this! Come on!
Let's go!
- There it is.
- I can't watch.
You're breaking through
the electromagnetic shield.
Okay.
I see two unique heat signatures.
They could be restraints.
Deploy your chute and the EMPs.
Why are we here?
You're here
because Alice wants you to have
a front row seat
to watch her kill Kate.
She's here at Safiyah's request.
Me? What did I do?
It's not what you did.
It's what Safiyah
thinks you're capable of.
You're skilled, strong,
and most of all, loyal.
She wants you to join her army.
Why the hell would I join
an army of ruthless killers?
Because you're already a part of one.
His.
Both groups are organized, armed,
and dangerous,
but we are committed
to protecting our people
while you oppress yours.
Touchdown. I made it.
Sort of.
See? That wasn't so bad.
Oh, yeah.
You owe me a spa day.
Just remember
to conserve your energy
or your vitals will drop again.
You seeing this?
That must be the Desert Rose.
I've never seen anything
more beautiful in my life.
Ryan?
- Crap.
- Ryan?
Hello? Can you hear me?
The EMPs must have
knocked out the comms.
Hey. I'm Batwoman.
Is your queen chick available?
We're really doing this?
Oh, boy.
I expected this to feel different.
I'm sure
you can ask your gal pal enigma
to root around your head
and fix it for you.
Now, give me Kate.
You don't even know
why you want to kill her.
She betrayed me.
That's what you keep
telling yourself,
but maybe deep down
in the dangerous musings of your ID
there's a compulsion to kill her
because she's more loved than you
and if you kill her
as irrational as it sounds
you think that love
will transfer to you.
But that's not how it works
so the conscious part
of you uses feelings
like pain and hurt
and betrayal to justify it
but what happens
to all those messy feelings
when Kate's dead
and everyone still hates you?
You are not changing my mind.
I have fantasized
about killing my sister
since she locked me in Arkham.
I know
we've had our differences, Alice
but I do care about you.
I just need to know
this is what you want more
than anything.
More than the air I breathe.
As you wish.
I will take you to her.
If I had a nickel
for every bad penny.
Batwoman?
What brings you here?
We believe she was trying
to help our prisoners escape.
They're gone.
Is everything all right?
It will be...
Because you're gonna help me
and in return,
I'm gonna tell you something
you're gonna want to hear.
I see.
Unfortunately, I don't barter
with uninvited guests.
So if you'll excuse us
we were in the middle of something.
You sure that's your boy over there?
You might want
to look a little harder.
Enough with all these distractions.
I gave you Ocean,
and now you can give me Kate.
My queen
I had no idea.
That was clearly her intention.
Who is this?
A nobody.
Well, a, a body.
Just one the morgue wouldn't miss.
You still have feelings for him
don't you?
Put her with the bat
and find me Ocean.
- What the hell's this?
- Batwoman.
Looks like an emp blocker.
Probably how the cuffs disarmed.
I thought she was sick.
Didn't know you had
an in with Batwoman's doctor.
That Desert Rose
I need to snag, it's for her.
You working with her?
I'm not working with her.
I'm just not working against her.
Who is she?
Honestly, I have no idea.
I don't, sir, but she's been trying
to help us to find Kate
who obviously inspired her to risk
her life for total strangers.
I don't see the harm
in us teaming up.
Except the Crows and Batwoman abide
by two very different ideologies.
Because we're held accountable
for our actions
and she's not?
If that were actually true,
those agents
who plowed down wolf spider
on that tarmac the other night
wouldn't have just been fired.
They'd be in jail.
Now, you sound like one
of Safiyah's lackeys.
You know I love my job, sir,
but I think it's time
we stop pretending
we're not above the law.
What's that smell?
Ammonium nitrate.
As in the bomb-making chemical?
That's one use for it.
Also makes
a very effective fertilizer.
- To grow the Desert Rose.
- Come on.
Kate's got to be around
her somewhere.
I was wondering
how this place could suck harder.
Why are you even here?
To stop you from killing Kate.
I don't know what this obsession
is with my sister,
but you're not part
of our family soap, okay?
I see.
You're on your way out.
You've got a few hours left to live,
and you need Kate to tap back in
because god forbid
the bat ears go unoccupied
for five minutes.
So, people like you
can roam free and kill
their own siblings?
Not to play Monday morning
quarterback
but if you didn't want me
to kill Kate
you should have stopped me
when you had the chance.
Then I wouldn't have been able
to follow your dumb ass
to this godforsaken island.
The tracker was you.
Clever girl.
That's it?
I just royally screwed up a move
you've been planning for months.
You could end me right now,
but you just hit me with a loud sigh.
You're already on death's door.
- Let's let nature run its course.
- Or maybe you're terrified.
- Of killing a sky rat?
- Of killing your sister.
You've been throwing
the same tantrum for months
poisoning bats,
attacking Gotham square
killing, god knows, how many people
because if Kate was gonna die
she was gonna die your way
and here you are moments away
from getting what you want
except, it's not actually
what you want, is it?
You don't want Kate back to kill her.
You just want her back.
Well, someone has spent
an awful lot of time thinking
about the girl they blame
for their mom's death.
You remember what you said
to me on your way out?
You said...
"It's not my fault,"
but you weren't talking
about killing my mom.
You were talking about why you are
the way you are
because as dark
and screwed up as you are
at the end of the day
you're a victim of somebody too.
And that tiny sliver of humanity
won't let you kill your sister
because then it is your fault.
If you want Kate, she's yours.
You've traveled too far
to leave empty-handed.
When someone does me a favor
I always react in kind.
What would you like
in return for helping me?
I've been poisoned.
I want enough Desert Rose
to cure myself.
So be it.
And I want to take Kate Kane
back to Gotham...
Alive.
You gave me one thing.
In fairness,
I'm offering you the same.
The flower or the girl...
Choose one.
The flower.
Done.
I suppose that leaves Kate for you.
Enough with the games.
Where is she?
I will bring you to her...
once you've fulfilled
your end of the deal.
What is this?
It's your second chance.
If you want Kate,
you're going to kill him
the real him.
Did you do this?
I didn't tell her anything.
She didn't have to.
We confiscated her phone
found a search for a charming,
little Shantytown
in Portofino, and there you were.
Isn't that precious?
She was going to come find you.
I always wanted to see
their piazzetta.
Such a sweet, little love story
that ends today.
I gave Batwoman a choice,
and now I'll do the same for you.
You can have one...
Ocean or Kate.
You're supposed to be watching
for the feed to come back online.
I am. It's not.
Mary, it's a plant.
It's Ryan's plant
something she's managed
to keep alive
through her mother's death
through a prison sentence
she doesn't deserve
through a fake Bruce Wayne
trying to kill her
and now she's off saving
Kate just so we can do what
- show her the door?
- Getting both Kate and Ryan back
would be a great problem to have
mostly because it would mean
they survived
this Hail Mary of a plan.
Then keeping this alive is literally
the least I can do.
Oh, my god.
You're one of Safiyah's many arms.
Our queen doesn't like
to be followed.
Hey!
Okay. Okay.
The elevator to the cave is out,
so we got to take the stairs.
- Wait, wait, wait. Ryan's plant.
- What about it?
I can't leave it.
We can grab it later.
Hey. You want
to send her a picture,
ask her if she thinks
we're doing a good job?
Ryan would want us to run away
from a trained assassin.
She asked me for one thing, Luke.
Okay. Okay. Fine, Mary.
Just grab the damn thing.
Fine!
Want to rock, paper, scissors it?
No!
What is this even about?
Some B.S. Frame job?
You made her believe
I killed off her little gang
and blew up her sister's plane.
Why would I stir things
up between you two?
Your little brain wipe worked.
I didn't even know Alice existed
until a few weeks ago.
Tell her.
Tell her, Alice. It was someone else.
I didn't frame Safiyah.
Give me the knife.
This was never
about someone setting you up.
This was about Alice caring about me
more than she cared about you
and your inability to live with it.
Kill him,
and you can have your sister.
Is it worth it,
killing me just to kill Kate?
If you really want to punish her,
leave her here to rot.
I'm sorry, Ocean...
But I don't want to kill her anymore.
Now, bring me to Kate...
Before anyone else
on this island dies.
- What are you doing?
- She's bleeding all over
the damn plant.
Hey. Mary!
You lift, I grab.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Okay. Grab it, grab it.
- Run!
Oi, oi.What's the rush?
- Julia, when did you get back?
- Who the bloody hell is that?
Okay.
Where's Safiyah?
She said
she would bring me a Desert Rose.
She will...
Once she's finished with Alice.
It's finally time for Alice
to be reunited with her sister.
Someone care to explain
why I had to dagger
one of Safiyah's minions?
The many arms found out
we tracked Alice to Coryana.
Courtesy of Batwoman,
who followed her there
to find Kate.
Got it.
That's actually why I'm here.
I have to applaud you
for picking your own survival
over Kate's.
Take it from an island lifer...
Self-sacrifice is overrated.
That's not why I did it.
Alice isn't going to kill her sister.
I'm curious how you know that.
I saw it in her face.
Revenge,
hate, anger, the...
Those are the only emotions
she knows,
so she hides behind them.
Well, you're right about one thing.
Alice
isn't going to kill her sister today.
Kate?
Where's Kate?
What is this?
What did you do?
I hired a team to run down some leads
from the tip line.
We found...
Body parts
off the coast of Bludhaven.
Must have got caught
in the currents.
What do...
what do you mean body parts?
They ran the DNA.
No.
- No.
- Where is she?
Where is my sister?
I never had your sister, Alice.
The DNA was hers. It was Kate's.
I'm so sorry.
Kate's dead.
No! No!
Get her out of here.
No! Kate! No! No!
Let me go!
You blew up her plane!
You killed her,
you stupid, lying bitch!
I had nothing to do with her plane
but when someone tried to frame me
for killing your sister
I saw an opportunity
to get what I wanted
to make you
and Ocean pay for your betrayal.
- You are a monster!
- And I created you
so what does that make you?
- Get her off my island.
- No. No! No!
Are you seeing this?
This is gonna get us out of here.
- You know, how to fly?
- Used to.
I'll get this running.
I'll keep looking for Kate.
Give me an hour. Just...
- If we're not back...
- I'll find you. Go.
Well done, my queen.
This should serve
as a lesson to anyone
who decides to betray you.
What the hell is happening?
He was dead.
When the blade was molded
its molten was imbued
with the Desert Rose.
Its curative properties
sealed Ocean's arteries
upon its entrance.
Welcome back, brother.
That breath in your chest
is only there because of me.
I gave you your life back.
Why would you do this to me?
When push comes to shove,
Alice doesn't actually have feelings
for you.
I wanted you to see that.
You're sick.
I'm not the one who just put a knife
through your heart.
Alice's loyalty will always lie
with her sister
just as yours should lie with me
because loyalty is everything to me.
Isn't that right, Tatiana?
It is, my queen.
Then why test it?
Why after I gave you power
and freedom and health
would you pick a fight with Alice
on my behalf?
- Safiyah, I don't know what...
- You slaughtered Alice's gang.
You sent her a note
saying I killed Kate.
You reeled her back into my life.
Why when you know
how hard I worked to forget her?
But you never forgot her.
That's the problem.
You couldn't.
You were in love.
I was trying to get rid
of that toxic an...
Enough!
You always hated Alice and tried
to drive a wedge between us.
That's how I knew it was you.
No.
-No.
-You wanted to see her lose
and now you have.
Congratulations, Tatiana.
I hope you were entertained.
Keep that in her.
I'll pull it out
when I decide to forgive her.
Now, we both have nothing.
What's happening?
My roses!
Oh, my god.
It's too late.
You are here.
Are you okay?
Did you get a Desert Rose?
I was wondering
why my guard left his post.
Looks like it wasn't meant to be.
We need to find Kate
and get the hell out of here.
Kate's not here.
What do you mean Kate's not here?
I mean,
Safiyah lied.
Tatiana told me Kate
was never on this island.
Kate died in the plane crash.
This can't be real.
I don't want to believe it either.
The feed's back on.
Is that the Desert Rose?
Bloody hell. It's ashes.
Oh, this isn't happening.
We needed that.
Ryan needed that to live.
Oh, my god.
The commander thinks
he can hotwire the plane.
We need to go.
I'm not gonna make it.
You don't know that.
I've only got a few hours.
There's nothing there for me.
Will you sit with me?
Please.
I don't want to die alone.
I'm sorry we got off
on the wrong foot.
You didn't deserve that.
It's because I wasn't Kate.
Hello?
Sophie, can you hear me?
How is my phone suddenly working?
The EMPs that knocked out
the power must have expired,
but I couldn't flag Batwoman
on the comms.
I'm with her now.
You need to get her back to Gotham.
She doesn't want to leave.
Tell her to get her ass
back here now.
I have a cure.
It's our birthstone.
Red is a very symbolic color.
Let's take a picture, Beth.
Make sure our necklaces are in it.
Ready? Cheese.