This is Dana Dewitt reporting
live on the scene
with breaking news!
And breaking bones as Batwoman
has taken the fight
to the False Face society,
disrupting their supply chain
of the highly addictive
street drug, Snakebite.
This is the third
distribution center this week
that Batwoman has targeted
in her mission
to rid Gotham's streets
of this scourge.
Who is Black Mask?
- I want the name!
- I don't know!
Look. That's why we
all wear masks.
You hear me, Black Mask?
You can hide your face,
but you can't hide from me.
I am coming for you!
In a Channel Eight exclusive,
Batwoman laid down the law
and declared war on Black Mask
and citizens of Gotham have
high hopes
that she can succeed where the GCPD.
and the Crows have failed.
You stay here.
- Where is she?
- Mr. Kane, there's been
- a terrible misunderstanding.
- Where is my daughter?
Sir, please allow me to explain.
My daughter, Beth, called me
not one hour ago from this house.
She said, "help," clear as can be.
It was all an insensitive prank.
I'm... I'm...
I'm so embarrassed. I...
Mr. Kane, your daughter
is not in there.
Beth! Beth!
Beth, are you in here?
Beth?
- Beth?
- Daddy?
You came for me.
I knew you would.
I'd never stop looking for you.
Never.
You pretty much broke the internet
with this latest False Face takedown.
Only thing that would have
gotten you more likes
is if you'd done it holding a kitten
but I do have to point out
that you were literally
holding a microphone
and didn't go for the mic drop.
Thought about it.
Wanted to stay on message.
Well, I think Black Mask
heard it loud and clear.
If you're still calling him that,
I'm assuming
you haven't figured out
his real name.
He told me Batwoman
killed his daughter.
Seriously, that doesn't
shorten the list?
There is no list.
Kate never killed anybody's daughter.
Don't forget he also
blames the Crows.
I assume next week
it'll be Aquaman.
Damn.
Wait, wait, wait.
- Is your watch fast?
- Have you met me?
- Then I'm already late.
- For what?
Visiting hours.
Thanks for coming.
Hadn't heard from you in a bit.
Commissary account's down to nada.
Ten-minute phone call
costs 22 bones and change.
Damn. It was 11.50
when I was inside.
Welcome to the Edgewater
private prison system
and seven cents an hour
pressing blue jeans
doesn't go as far as it used to
but I... know you didn't come here
because you miss being on the inside.
Tell me what am I
missing on the outside.
I'm helping to get
a community center off the ground
kind of place you
and I would have loved,
you know, gives kids
a safe space to go to
instead of going into the system.
Open house is tonight.
Sounds nice.
I wish I could get to see it.
You could.
You could walk right out of here
if you just give up the ones
who actually pulled the trigger
on Commissioner Forbes.
Look.
I know you took the fall
to keep me safe from False Face
but I can protect myself.
Sure it's not Batwoman
protecting you?
Is she your girlfriend now?
are guys like super friends
with benefits?
Trust me it is not like that.
It never is till it is.
I'm late for my seven cents an hour.
Thank you all for coming.
As you look around
and see all we have to offer,
know that none of it
would have been possible
without the relentless
dedication of our volunteers.
And I know they wanted
to remain anonymous
so I'll just say
to Mary Hamilton and Ryan Wilder
your secret's safe with me.
You women are superheroes.
- Keep smiling.
- That's what I'm doing.
Please feel free
to look around and see
all the activities we have to offer.
You'll find we've got everything here
from intramural sports
to after-school tutoring
- and we als...
- What about security?
Horten Spence, Gotham Gazette.
Well, Mr. Spence, don't you think
the kids around here already
have enough armed men
watching their every move?
Look.
Don't get me wrong.
I like what you're doing,
but this is a rough neighborhood.
The stats don't lie.
If you want numbers, Mr. Spence,
how about a 10% drop in crime
or a 15% increase
in graduation rates?
Those are the numbers
that neighborhoods see
when community centers
like this open their doors.
You aren't worried
about this place being a target?
for budget cuts, maybe.
You know, despite doing so much,
places like this are always
first on the chopping block.
Maybe the gazette could
do a story about that.
- Good turnout.
- Oh, my god. Tell me about it.
I already have
to refresh the refreshments.
Wilder, I want you to meet Imani,
Director of our tutoring program.
Oh. Well, you certainly schooled
that reporter back there.
- I'm Ryan.
- I know.
I hear you're gonna be teaching
a martial arts class.
I actually hadn't gotten around
to roping her into that yet...
Until now.
Saturday morning.
Think about it.
Look who needs a refill. Me!
I'm hoping you're gonna say
yes to that
because if you don't teach
martial arts, that means I have to
and my roundhouse kick is a disaster.
Well, I figure
it's the least I can do.
Crazy. I...
I can't help but think how much
a place like this would have
really made a difference
for my friends and I growing up.
Yeah. These places are so important,
especially for at-risk kids.
It's so easy for them to
fall through the cracks.
Yeah, I know.
I have a friend who's still falling.
Everybody, down!
For those of you not keeping up
on current events
how's this
for a shocking development?
A community center in Sheldon Park
just got barbequed by a man wielding
what can only be described
as a lightning gun.
The media has dubbed him Kilovolt.
I don't know about you, Gotham
but I'm hoping lightning
doesn't strike twice.
Kilovolt? based on the energy needed
to do that kind of damage,
they're only off
by about a billion volts.
That's your takeaway?
the nickname dropped a few zeroes?
My point being a weapon
with that kind of firepower
costs a hell of a lot more than
the building it was used to destroy.
It was more than a building.
That place was gonna
make a difference.
I don't get it. Why take it out?
It's not like there
was any money in it.
It's about to have
even less money now.
Donors running for their lives
isn't exactly the press
we were looking for.
But it was the story
the press was looking for.
Don't you think it was a little weird
that reporter asking
about the place being a target
right before it became a target?
- What was the guy's name?
- Horten Spence.
He writes for the gazette.
Not anymore he doesn't.
He was fired six months ago
for undisclosed reasons.
Okay. Then I get
why he'd have a grudge
against the gazette,
but what does that
have to do with the community center?
Only one way to find out.
I don't get it.
Yeah. Well, that makes two of us.
These are expense report records
from when I was chasing down leads
on Kate's whereabouts.
Two nights in Monaco,
a layover in Valencia,
a car rental in Madrid.
So, what's the problem?
I have no memory
of being in any of those places.
No judgment here, but...
Were you drinking?
Well, I was searching for one ex,
having just been dumped by another.
So, yeah, alcohol was consumed
but not that much.
But if you don't remember,
how do you remember
it wasn't that much.
So, it would appear that the obvious
explanation is the correct one.
Hey. Don't beat yourself up.
Agent Pennyworth.
Just got an anonymous tip
about a break-in at a farm.
The address matches a property
that once belonged
to an August Cartwright.
What else did this tipster say?
nothing other than to pass
the message on to you and only you.
At least, I think it's you.
Tipster said to pass the message on
to an Agent Penny Dreadful.
Does that mean anything to you?
Unfortunately, it does.
I see you got my message.
Oh, the sad desperation
came through loud and clear.
Gotham's most deranged diva reduced
to making prank phone calls.
What's next?
Ding-dong-ditch?
How about ghost in the graveyard?
Oh, you're not gonna kill me.
You'd just be lonely again.
I mean,...
that's why I'm here, isn't it?
With Kate gone...
because no one really cares
about your every move.
I mean,
the new Batwoman doesn't
give a damn about you anymore
and that must drive
you absolutely crazy.
Crazier.
What will Alice become now
that her sister is dead?
I mean, it's the age-old
question, isn't it?
If a lunatic throws
a tantrum in a forest
will anyone hear?
Guess Gotham's not much
of a playground without a playmate.
I don't need a playmate.
I need a partner.
Well, your last overture at partners
ended with a knife in my gut, so...
Oh, I really need to work
on my negotiating skills.
How about this?
You help me and I'll leave Gotham...
Forever.
Go on. Why would I believe you?
Because you would help me
in ridding myself
of any reason to stay.
See, I need to find
a particular associate
of our mutual friend Safiyah.
She goes by the catchy,
little pseudonym of Enigma.
Never heard of her,
but if you want her dead,
she can't be all bad.
Actually, she's quite good...
At a certain skill that I require.
What would that be?
Hypnotism, specifically the ability
to erase memories, alter others.
Looking to purge
our guilty conscience, are we,
leave Gotham with a clean slate?
Something like that.
Well, how do you even know
that this Enigma can do all that?
Because she's done it to me before.
It was a fluke
that I found out really.
Enigma erased any trace
that she'd ever been there.
I suppose you could say
that I forgot to remember
what she made me forget.
How is that even possible?
You can ask her
when we find her.
Well, that's just it.
I think I already have.
You wanted to see me, Commander?
Yeah. Come in, Dr. Rhyme come in.
Evelyn, please.
I...
I just wanted to thank you
for taking time away
from your practice
to lend your expertise
to our Snakebite taskforce.
- My pleasure.
- I read your report
on what makes Snakebite
so incredibly addictive
though I admit I got a little bit
lost in the medical jargon.
Could you just...
Could you just break
it down for a guy
who doesn't have a Ph.D.
in criminal psychiatry?
The drug attacks the hippocampus,
where the brain stores
memories and emotions.
It targets the memories most
associated with regret and remorse,
which result in a hallucination
that allows the user to alter
the circumstances of those memories.
To get a do-over.
And what could be
more addictive than that,
the chance to right
our worst mistakes,
to erase our gravest sins
even for a moment?
How long have you been
using Snakebite, Commander?
What are you talking about?
Commander Kane,
if we're not honest with each other,
then...
this is just a waste of...
both of our time.
Some...
False Face bastard jumped me
in my car, chloroformed me.
I woke up with an injector in my arm.
I guess since I've been railing
against Snakebite
in the press they wanted
to send me a message.
How could you tell?
Because I'm very good at my job
and even if you've had just one dose,
you're gonna need my help.
Sneaking out the backdoor?
I'm just glad it's you.
Said no suspicious dude ever.
- Expecting someone else?
- Yeah.
A guy packing
a handheld lightning storm.
I'm sure you've heard of him.
Yeah. So, who is he?
- I don't know.
- But you know his schedule.
How did you know he was gonna attack
the community center?
Because it's happened before.
Not by Kilovolt.
He's just the latest player
in a game that's been going
on for a while.
- I'm not following.
- Nobody is.
That's the problem. Community centers
are being terrorized.
The narrows midnight basketball
gets torched by an arsonist.
Diamond district tutoring center
gets shot up.
Anything that was
a refuge for kids...
Taken off the board.
Not seeing a connection.
They're all different M.O.s.
I'm telling you
the Sheldon Park attack
wasn't the first
and it won't be the last.
We're talking about
at-risk youth programs,
not exactly the most
threatening institutions in Gotham.
What's the motive?
That's exactly the question
I as asking
when I was suddenly
fired from the gazette.
Do you have any proof?
As a matter of fact, I do.
After last night's attack, my
editor's agreed to take another look.
Put him on here.
Okay. Up.
Okay.
Third-degree electrical burns.
See if the Crows left us
any mafenide acetate cream.
Cabinet middle shelf.
I'm gonna have to sedate him.
- But he'll make it?
- I think so.
Looks like his laptop
took the brunt of it.
Someone went to a lot
of trouble to destroy the evidence
on this computer,
which means there must be some truth
to the story he was trying to tell.
Figure out where that
thing came from?
Well, it matches
some tech being sold
by a shady Russian
defense contractor.
I'm guessing the kind that
doesn't give up their client list.
We may not need it.
Got a partial print here.
The rest is...
hidden under the battery.
At least, I think it's the battery.
Are you sure you should
be messing with that?
Relax.
Okay.
See? Nothing to worry about.
Let's find out who you are, kilovolt.
Michael Kastrinos, a.k.a Mickey K.
Got an address?
Yes. Cell block J
at Edgewater prison,
where he's been locked up
for the last two years.
So, you were in boring Madrid
filing boring paperwork before taking
a boring flight back to Gotham.
And from there, I followed
the trail to Bludhaven,
where I eventually found
Kate's remains.
Not according to your boarding pass,
which you apparently
used as an itinerary.
Before heading off to Bludhaven,
you had a meeting
with a Dr. Evelyn Rhyme.
You don't remember that?
No.
Dr. Rhyme is a consultant
with the Crows' Snakebite task force.
Why would I want to talk to her?
what say you fly to the nest
and ask Dr. Rhyme.
What about you?
She has a private practice
on sixth and...
I'm feeling nosy.
See? We make a great team.
Oh, come on.
We aren't so different
You and I.
All we have in common
is that we both miss Kate.
Well, there is one other thing.
No matter how much
we both loved Kate,
she always chose someone else.
Is that what you
want Enigma to erase,
all those hurt feelings?
No.
I want her to erase...
The person who caused them.
That was my life's biggest regret,
my greatest failure,
not saving Beth.
Not an hour goes by
that I don't think about it
leaving my daughter
to suffer in that cell.
That's why I can't
shake off this urge
for another hit of Snakebite
because for another
few fleeting moments
i get to be the father I should
have been to her all those years ago.
Who else have you told about this?
- No one.
- Not even family?
My daughter Mary's
the only family I have left.
We're not exactly speaking.
Unfortunately,...
there's nothing I can give you
to blunt the withdrawal,
but there is a way
you can blunt the pain
of the daughter you lost.
How?
by focusing on repairing
the relationship
with the daughter you have left.
Garcia, housed on A block.
You my new lawyer?
I wanted to ask
about the recent attack
on the Sheldon Park
community center.
Who are you?
And the attempted murder
of Horten Spence.
I don't have to answer any
of your questions, bitch.
You already have.
- He did it. Mickey K's Kilovolt.
- He can't be.
The guy has a laceration right
where I sliced him
in the alley. It's him.
Not according to the prison
surveillance footage.
I'm currently looking at footage
from the nights
of both Kilovolt attacks.
Mickey K Is locked up
tight in his cell.
Two visits in one week?
Aren't I the belle of the block?
I was wondering if maybe
you can help me with something.
Grapevine buzzing
about any recent prison escapes,
any rumors of a secret way
in or out of here?
You think if I knew a way out
I'd still be sitting here?
Why do you ask?
Thinking of busting me out?
you know, I would do
anything for you,
but the one thing I can't do is
convince you to punch
your ticket out of here.
Come on, Ang.
The shooters were wearing
a hockey mask and a gas mask.
Give me the names
of the guys underneath.
If I tell you their names,
I'll be the next one
Black Mask puts a bullet in.
Batwoman can't be around
to protect me 24 hours a day.
But I can.
It's just you and me...
against the world...
like always.
I will never let
Black Mask hurt you.
You're forgiven.
Does anyone else want to apologize
for the fact that
for the last two weeks
not a single viable dose
of Snakebite has been produced?
Anyone?
I got plenty of bullets
to go around.
Sir.
You can kill
as many of us as you want.
It won't change the fact
that you wanted to keep
the Snakebite recipe a secret.
And now, we've lost the only
two people who knew it.
Ocean disappeared weeks ago
and his little helper's
locked away in prison.
You got to get her out.
You can't let Angelique
rot in there.
I sent you the names of the men
who gunned down Forbes.
I know. I got
all six of your voicemails.
I'll look into the names she gave me.
I already did, ok?
They manage the Gotham gun club.
Is it that hard to imagine
guys who work
at a shooting range
pulling the trigger?
- Okay. I'll run it down.
- And?
And if the story checks out,
I'll talk to the DA
about getting your girl sprung.
Hey.
So, this is from the night of
the attack on the community center.
And this...
is from two weeks ago.
Now check out
the two hands of solitaire.
They're identical...
Just like these surveillance tapes.
It's the same footage.
They just slapped
a new time stamp on it and
instant alibi.
So, is the prison trying
to cover up the fact
that he escaped and destroyed
the community center?
Worse. I think they let him out.
Our friend, Mickey K,here
wasn't gonna be eligible
for parole for another decade.
And then suddenly, the day after
the community center attack
he was granted
a hearing for early release.
So...
I took the schedule
for recent parole hearings
and I matched it
against spence's list
of attacks on community programs.
Guess what happened after the narrows
midnight basketball was torched.
They paroled a serial arsonist.
And here's another big, wet kiss
from Edgewater's parole board.
This one an armed
robbery enthusiast
conveniently scheduled...
the day after the Diamond
District Tutoring Center got shot up.
Okay, okay. So, someone
from the prison
is letting out criminals
for one night
to target community programs
in exchange for early parole.
And that someone...
Is edgewater correctional
CEO Ellis O'Brien.
He personally intervened
and signed off
on each early release,
all under the guise
of "time off for good behavior"
and he sits on the board
of the Gotham Gazette.
which puts him in the position
to get Horten fired
before he can find out
who's behind the attacks.
Yeah, but I still don't get why.
Why would a prison company
want to destroy community programs?
It's exactly what imani said.
These programs keep kids
from falling through the cracks
but you know who profits
from the kids who do?
Prisons.
Jake. Hey, buddy.
Listen. I'm sorry
to barge in like this,
waving my Crows platinum client card
but I just needed to speak
to somebody I knew I could trust.
What's wrong, roman?
Well, I was doing a routine check
on one of my cosmetics stores.
Long story short, a search of one
of my employees' lockers
turned up this.
That's Snakebite, right?
i didn't want to make a big thing
about it without knowing for sure.
I mean, I've heard of the stuff,
but i've never actually seen it.
Is that the real deal?
Yeah. Yeah. It's the real deal.
Well, it's good
I brought it to you then.
I know how hard you've
been pushing to get
this stuff off the streets.
I just can't believe
my own staff would...
You know, I mean,
I bought it was a kid drug
but this stuff must
really be making the rounds?
Listen. I've got
things, covered on my end.
Can you dispose of this,
make sure it doesn't get
into the wrong hands?
I mean, if it's as bad as you say
this stuff could really
ruin someone's life.
Yeah.
I'll take care of it.
You're the best, Jake.
Dr. Rhyme.
Agent Pennyworth, how are you?
Stumped, actually.
I was hoping you could
clear something up.
Last month when I'd
just returned to Gotham
you asked to see me.
This is gonna sound strange
but...
Do you mind
if I ask what we discussed?
It was a matter of some sensitivity.
Perhaps we should
discuss it in private.
Have a seat, Dr. Rhyme.
Or would you prefer Enigma?
What did you do to me?
Same thing I'm about to do.
Make you forget.
I got a lock on the CEO's phone.
He seems to be working late
at the sight
of Edgewater's latest lockup.
Surveying your latest money maker?
Who's there?
I need a security team down...
Tell me how much money does
the city pay you per prisoner?
One-hundred fifty a day.
So, you're raking in
a couple hundred million a year
to warehouse people?
there's nothing illegal about it.
That's the problem.
All that money means
you'll be willing to do anything
to keep your cells filled.
That's why you sent Kilovolt
to fry the community center.
Any programs that kept at-risk kids
from ending up in one of your prisons
cut into your bottom line,
so you took them out.
All right, all right. You got me.
No need to get physical.
So, you're confessing?
More like stalling.
Are you seeing this?
You got three guards approaching
from the west
and I'm reading a big energy signal.
That suit will protect her, right?
not against three of those
lightning guns it won't.
Nobody's home.
Looks like Black Mask
is tying up some loose ends.
I miss the electric chair,
but a firing squad should do.
Ready. Aim.
Fire!
You've been holding out on me, Fox?
Couldn't let you have all the fun.
- You know I had that, right?
- Yeah. Never had a doubt.
Do you like irony, Gotham?
I think Batwoman does.
For-profit prison CEO, Ellis O'Brien,
allegedly engineered a conspiracy
to sabotage
community outreach programs
in a bid to increase
incarceration rates
among the city's most at-risk
and it seems O'Brien did
increase the prison population
by one himself.
Batwoman spilled the tea
and journalist Horten Spence
spilled the ink.
Talk to me, Gotham.
Has Batwoman found her Lois Lane?
Daddy?
What brought you to
the good doctor rhyme's office?
That's why I can't shake this urge
for another hit of Snakebite
because at least for a few...
What did you do?
That was my life's biggest regret
my greatest failure, not saving beth.
Not an hour goes by
when I don't think about it,
leaving my daughter
to suffer in that cell.
That's why I can't shake this urge
for another hit of Snakebite
because at least
for a few fleeting moments
I can be the father
I should have been to her
all those years ago.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
As much as I want to forgive you...
Forgetting's easier.
Apply the antibiotic twice a day
and change the bandages
as needed.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
My insurance doesn't kick in
for another few weeks.
Yeah. I'm just glad
you got your job back
and I hear a big promotion.
All I have to toast
with are lollipops
but cheers.
- Bye.
Stopped by the med school
your apartment, the hold-up.
Then it hit me
where I could find you.
- Busted. You got me.
- Mary.
Look. I don't care
what you have to say
I'm opening the place back up,
So, if you want to stop me,
you'll have to arrest me.
I don't want to stop you.
I want to help you.
Make this place a real clinic.
Hire real doctors.
I'll even pay for it.
You know that there
are some things that you can't fix
by writing a big check.
What possible objection
could you have
to making this place legit?
Because it goes against the very
reason I started the clinic, okay?
I don't ask for I.D.,
I don't require insurance,
I don't report O.D.s
or non-violent criminal behavior.
I opened up this place
to serve the people
that you don't see as legit.
Come on. You haven't
even finished med school.
And yet yesterday,
I saved a guy's life.
You know,
for the first time since Kate died
I don't feel hollow.
I feel like what I did mattered
that I can make a difference
in this crappy city
and you want to take
that away from me
and for that,
I will never forgive you.
Hey.
So, I heard you put
in for a transfer to Berlin.
That I did.
- Seems sudden.
- I know.
I just, I just woke up this morning
and knew that's
what I wanted to do.
It just feels right, you now?
too many memories here in Gotham.
Take care, love.
Just wanted to make sure
you had a copy of this.
I'm glad the place
is getting some good press.
Yeah. The phones have
been lighting up
with donations and volunteers.
That means I'm off the hook
for teaching martial arts?
i hope not because I already signed
up for your class.
Excuse me.
So, this is all
happening very quickly,
but the D.A. signed off
on Angelique's deal.
A Witsec team is moving her
into protective custody as we speak.
- Thank you.
- No. Thank you
for getting her to talk.
Now until we can
take down Black Mask
Angelique's gonna be
off the grid for bit.
It might be a while
before you can talk to her again.
You came for me!
I knew you would.
Crows treating you okay?
They're definitely more agreeable
chauffeuring me around.
Thanks for getting me out.
You got yourself out.
With a little push.
I don't know how you
did 18 months inside, Ry.
I thought I understood how much
you sacrificed for me by going in.
Not even close,
but now that I do,
I want to say thank you
and that I love you so...
Ang?
- No, no!
- What's going on? Angelique?
- No, no, no!
- What's going on?
Angelique?
Angelique, Angelique!
Angelique, talk to me! Angelique!
No! no, no, no!
Angelique? Angelique!