RYAN: DEAR KATE,
TODAY'S THE DAY
I'M SUPPOSED TO DIE.
TRUTH IS I'M NOT SCARED
OF DYING.
I'M SCARED I DIDN'T LIVE.
MY MAMA ALWAYS TOLD ME I WAS
PUT ON THIS EARTH FOR A REASON,
AND NOW I FINALLY KNOW
WHAT THAT IS.
[FREYA RIDINGS'
"ULTRAVIOLET" PLAYING"]
ALICE: TODAY IS THE DAY
I KILL YOU, KATE.
I SPENT 11 YEARS WAITING
FOR YOU TO FIND ME,
BUT INSTEAD, I FOUND YOU.
THEN, I WAITED FOR YOU
TO SAVE ME,
BUT INSTEAD,
I SAVED YOU,
I TURNED YOU INTO A HERO.
RYAN: YOU HELPED ME FIND
MY INNER WARRIOR,
MY VOICE, MY POWER.
ALICE: WHILE I PLAYED
THE PART OF YOUR VILLAIN,
THE GIRL WHO REMINDED YOU
HOW RIGHT AND NOBLE
AND COURAGEOUS YOU WERE.
RYAN: YOU MADE ME FEEL BRAVE.
ALICE: SO I TOLD YOU
MY GREATEST FEAR
WAS BEING LOCKED AWAY AGAIN,
AND ON THAT VERY DAY,
WHAT DID YOU DO?
RYAN: YOU HELPED ME BREAK
OUT OF THE SYSTEM
THAT WAS TRAPPING ME.
ALICE: YOU LURED ME INTO A BOX,
AND YOU LOCKED THE DOOR.
RYAN AND ALICE:
I'VE COME SO FAR...
ALICE: TO GET MY REVENGE.
RYAN: TO INSPIRE OTHERS,
AND I'VE SURVIVED MUCH WORSE.
ALICE: CARTWRIGHT,
THE QUEEN OF HEARTS...
RYAN: FOSTER CARE,
THE CANDY LADY.
IF I COULD DO THAT...
BOTH: I CAN DO ANYTHING.
RYAN: I CAN PUSH OFF DEATH
ANOTHER DAY
IF IT MEANS SAVING YOU.
ALICE: I CAN EVEN KILL
MY SISTER.
RIDINGS: ♪ HIDE IT
♪ WHEN YOU'RE ULTRAVIOLET
[ELEVATOR DOOR SLIDING]
MARY: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
I'M THE ONE WHO PRACTICES
WITHOUT A MEDICAL LICENSE
AROUND HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT IS...
A COMBINATION
OF ADRENALINE
AND CORTISONE.
IT WILL GIVE ME
A JOLT OF ENERGY,
AND IT WILL KILL
SOME OF THIS PAIN.
-YEAH.
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HOW DID YOU EVEN LEARN
HOW TO DO THIS?
YOUTUBE. WHAT?!
OH! DID THE YOUTUBE
MEDICAL EXPERT
ALSO EXPLAIN TO YOU
THAT THIS COMBINATION
WILL ACCELERATE THE SPEED
OF CELL DECAY BY 300%?
WITHOUT THE SHOT,
YOU HAVE DAYS,
AND WITH IT, YOU'RE
LUCKY TO HAVE 24 HOURS.
24 HOURS IS
ALL I NEED.
I PUT THE TRACKER
ON ALICE,
SHE PROBABLY MADE IT
TO CORYANA BY NOW.
I WILL FOLLOW
HER ROUTE.
I WILL FIND KATE,
AND I WILL GET
THE DESERT ROSE
TO HEAL MYSELF.
AND IF SOMETHING
GOES WRONG, YOU DIE.
MARY, LOOK AT ME.
I'M DEAD ALREADY.
-OH, MY GOD.
-OH, GOD.
FINE. TEAM VOTE.
WHERE'S LUKE?
ACTUALLY...
MARY, WHERE'S LUKE?
I HAVE AN ACTIVE APB
AND 3 FIELD TEAMS LOOKING
FOR ALICE,
YET YOU NOT ONLY MANAGED
TO LOCATE HER
BUT TAGGED HER
WITH A HIGH-POWERED
TRACKING DEVICE?
HOW?
I'M SURE YOU'RE
FAMILIAR WITH THE CONCEPT
DON'T ASK, DON'T TELL.
THEN I WON'T ASK.
I WILL STATE.
YOU'RE WORKING
WITH BATWOMAN.
MM-HMM. SO WHY
DOESN'T SHE TRACK ALICE?
-BECAUSE SHE'S SICK.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN SICK?
SHE'S DYING.
LONG STORY SHORT,
TOMMY ELLIOT SHOT HER
WITH A POISON BULLET,
AND THERE'S NO ANTIDOTE,
SO WE NEED YOU TO
BRING BACK A STEM
OF THE DESERT ROSE
TO HEAL HER.
WHELAN: SORRY
TO INTERRUPT.
OUR APB FOR ALICE
AND ALL KNOWN ASSOCIATES
TURNED UP THIS.
HER FRIEND OCEAN BOARDED
A FLIGHT TO ROME LAST NIGHT.
THANKS.
THE DEAL ALICE MADE
WITH SAFIYAH
WAS THAT SHE HAD TO
KILL OCEAN TO GET
KATE BACK.
I DOUBT SHE SHOWED UP
TO CORYANA WITHOUT HIM.
BUT SHE IS CRAZY
ENOUGH TO SHOW UP
WITH A FAKE HIM.
IT WOULDN'T BE
THE FIRST TIME
SHE SLAPPED A FACE
ON SOMEBODY ELSE'S
BODY.
GOD KNOWS
SHE FOOLED ME
WITH THE BRUCE WAYNE
WANNABE.
IF THAT'S TRUE
AND SAFIYAH BELIEVES
THE IMPOSTER,
THEN SHE HANDS KATE
OVER TO ALICE,
AND ALICE KILLS HER.
WHICH MEANS YOU NEED
TO GET GOING NOW.
JACOB: THE TRACKER SHOWS
THAT ALICE LEFT
THE OLSSON AIRSTRIP
AND FLEW EAST.
SOPHIE LOW-KEY SLIPPED
ME THE FEED.
RYAN: SO WE'RE GONNA
GLOSS OVER YOU TELLING
A CROW YOU'RE WORKING
WITH BATWOMAN?
IT WAS PREFERABLE
TO LOSING BOTH BATWOMEN
IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
SOPHIE SAID SHE WOULD
GET A FLOWER.
AND YOU BELIEVE HER?
CAN WE STAY
POSITIVE, PLEASE?
JACOB: WE LAND,
FIND MY DAUGHTER,
GET OUT.
AND I AM SCREWED.
SOPHIE: ONE MORE THING.
WE NEED TO GRAB
A DESERT ROSE
WHILE WE'RE THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
AND I REST MY CASE.
SOPHIE: I'LL EXPLAIN
EN ROUTE,
BUT WE'RE NOT LEAVING
THAT ISLAND WITHOUT IT.
[CLATTER]
RAH!
MARY: NO!
SOPHIE: COMMANDER!
-WAIT. WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
-THEY'RE SAFIYAH'S MEN.
THAT WOULD MEAN
THAT SAFIYAH KNEW
THEY WERE COMING.
[JACOB GRUNTS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
MARY: OH, MY GOD.
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
THEY'RE TAKING THEM
SOMEWHERE.
LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE HEADING
TOWARD OLSSON AIRSTRIP.
IT'S THE SAME AIRFIELD
THAT ALICE LEFT FROM.
MARY: SO THEY'RE GOING
TO CORYANA?
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
RYAN, NO!
YOU INJECT THAT,
YOU DIE TODAY!
WE LITERALLY JUST
WATCHED
OUR LAST HOPE FIZZLE
BEFORE OUR EYES.
UNLESS ANYONE ELSE
HAS ANY MORE
BRILLIANT IDEAS.
[SIGHS]
START THE CLOCK.
I AM GOING
TO CORYANA,
I AM SAVING THEM,
I AM SAVING KATE,
AND I'M SAVING
MY DAMN SELF.
HUH! HUH! HA!
I FEEL GOOD. I'M SORRY.
I HAVEN'T FELT
THIS GOOD IN MONTHS.
OK. EASY THERE,
TIGER.
THE FASTER YOU WORK
THE ADRENALINE
THROUGH YOUR SYSTEM,
THE FASTER IT RETURNS
TO SELF-DESTRUCT MODE.
24 HOURS WAS A GUESS,
NOT A PROMISE.
OK.
LUKE: ALICE'S
TRANSPONDER DIED
OVER THIS TINY SECTION
OF THE MEDITERRANEAN.
BUT I DON'T SEE
AN ISLAND.
YEAH. THAT'S THE POINT.
IT'S RIGGED TO AVOID
SATELLITE DETECTION,
SO IF I HAD THE ONLY
SERUM ON THE PLANET
THAT COULD CURE CANCER
AND WANTED TO CLOAK IT
SO NOBODY ELSE
COULD HAVE IT,
I WOULD USE ANTI-RADAR
ELECTROMAGNETIC WAVES.
SO THE COWL'S LENSES
CAN DETECT
THE ELECTROMAGNETIC FIELD.
CONSIDER IT
YOUR BULL'S-EYE.
-BULL'S-EYE FOR WHAT?
-THESE ARE EMP GRENADES.
SO ACCORDING TO SOPHIE,
THE ONLY ELECTRICITY
THAT SHE SAW
ON THE ISLAND WAS USED
FOR ELECTRIC
WRIST RESTRAINTS.
SO A FEW OF THESE
WILL KNOCK OUT THE POWER
FOR A FEW HOURS
AND FREE ANYONE
WEARING THEM,
PRESUMABLY MARY'S DAD,
SOPHIE, AND KATE.
OK. YOU DIDN'T
ANSWER MY QUESTION
ABOUT THE BULL'S-EYE.
I GOT TO FIND YOU A RIDE.
OK. UM, CAN I ADDRESS
THE ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM?
YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO DIE.
ACTUALLY...THE ELEPHANT
IS IF I LIVE.
SAY I FIND KATE
AND I BRING HER BACK HERE.
THEN WHAT?
SHE'S BATWOMAN, RIGHT?
WHAT DOES THAT MAKE ME?
THAT'S NOT GONNA--
KATE WOULD NEVER PUSH
YOU OUT LIKE THAT.
SO THEN THERE'S
TWO BATWOMEN?
BECAUSE THAT'S NOT CONFUSING.
LOOK. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN KATE COMES BACK.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
I...
I REALLY, REALLY
WANT HER BACK.
I KNOW.
BUT...
IF I DO DIE...
YOU'RE IN CHARGE
OF MY BABY.
OH. NO, NO, NO.
NOPE.
THAT'S NOT...ME.
YES.
ANGELIQUE GAVE HER
TO ME,
AND I WAS GONNA GIVE HER
TO MY MOM
WHEN WE MOVED
INTO OUR PLACE.
SHE'S ALL I HAVE LEFT
OF HER.
[SIGHS]
WELL, THEN IT'S
OFFICIAL.
YOU DEFINITELY
HAVE TO MAKE IT BACK
BECAUSE...I COULDN'T
EVEN KEEP
MY TAMAGOTCHI ALIVE
FOR 5 MINUTES,
SO...
LUKE: I THINK I JUST
FOUND YOU A RIDE.
OK. AND?
UH...LET'S JUST SAY
I COULDN'T ORDER YOU
THE VEGAN OPTION.
RYAN: YOU COULDN'T
EVEN AFFORD COACH?
LUKE: WE'RE JUST LUCKY
THIS MAIL CARRIER'S
GONNA FLY WITHIN
5 MINUTES OF CORYANA'S
AIRSPACE.
-CLOCK'S TICKING.
-YEAH. 18 HOURS TO LIVE.
I GOT IT!
NO. I MEAN, YOU'RE
ABOUT 25 MINUTES
FROM THE DROP.
THE WHAT NOW?
I CAN OVERRIDE THE DOOR
SENSOR AND BUY YOU
A 30-SECOND WINDOW
FOR THE HALO JUMP.
WHAT--WHAT THE HELL
IS A HALO JUMP?
HIGH ALTITUDE,
LOW OPENING.
YOU ASKED
ABOUT THE BULL'S-EYE.
YOU NEED TO HIT
A TINY TARGET
FROM 33,00 FEET.
YEAH, YEAH. THIS
WOULD BE A LOT EASIER
IF WE HAD A BATPLANE.
THAT'S WHAT I'VE
BEEN SAYING.
OK. I'LL GET RIGHT ON THAT
AFTER I WORK OUT
THE KINKS IN THE BATSUB.
DON'T DEPLOY YOUR CUTE
UNTIL YOUR HEADS-UP DISPLAY
READS 3,500 FEET
SO YOU AVOID DETECTION.
OH, AND USE
YOUR PRESSURE MASK.
OTHERWISE, YOU'LL
DIE INSTANTLY.
IS THIS A BAD TIME
TO SAY I HAVE N-N-NEVER
BEEN ON A PLANE BEFORE?
TATIANA INFORMED ME
THE TWO OF YOU HAD
A LITTLE CHAT.
OF COURSE SHE DID.
THAT SHE TOLD YOU
HOW YOU AND OCEAN
FELL IN LOVE,
HOW HE STOLE
A DESERT ROSE,
AND HOW HE CONVINCED YOU
TO LEAVE CORYANA WITH HIM.
THAT WAS
THE GIST OF IT
LESS A FEW JUICY DETAILS
ABOUT HOW HE WASN'T
THE ONLY ISLANDER
WHO LOVED ME.
I WANT TO BE CLEAR
ABOUT SOMETHING.
I CONSIDERED OCEAN
A BROTHER.
I HAD YOU BOTH ERASED
FROM EACH OTHER
BECAUSE I...
BELIEVED YOU WERE
A BAD INFLUENCE ON HIM.
GOT IT.
A RULER DOESN'T GET TO
PLAY BY THE WHIMS
OF HER EMOTIONS, ALICE.
NOR CAN SHE AFFORD
TO BE BLIND TO WHAT'S
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER.
YOU'VE DISAPPOINTED ME.
I BROUGHT YOU
YOUR BROTHER
WITH YOUR FANCY KNIFE
THROUGH HIS CHEST.
NOW GIVE ME MY SISTER
SO I CAN PUT ONE
THROUGH HERS.
YOU FOOLISH GIRL.
[WOMAN VOCALIZING]
MY MEN FOUND A TRACKER
ON YOUR BOOT.
YOU WERE BEING FOLLOWED.
YOU OK?
I THINK SO.
WHERE THE HELL ARE WE?
[FOOTSTEPS, KEYS JINGLING]
[DOOR OPENS]
EXACTLY WHERE YOU WANTED TO BE.
NOT HOW YOU SAW THIS GOING?
RYAN: ARE YOU
KIDDING ME RIGHT NOW?!
THERE'S NOTHING
DOWN THERE!
LUKE: YES, THERE IS,
AND YOU'RE GONNA MISS IT.
YOU NEED TO JUMP.
WELL, THAT'S EASY
FOR YOU TO SAY.
WHAT IF MY CHUTE
DOESN'T OPEN?
IT WILL! RYAN, HURRY UP!
IF YOU MISS YOUR WINDOW,
YOU'RE GONNA END UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE OCEAN,
AND THERE'S NO SHARK REPELLANT
ON THE UTILITY BELT.
-WELL, WHY NOT?
-BECAUSE THAT'S STUPID.
NOW GO!
OHH! OK. OK.
YOU GOT THIS.
YOU GOT THIS!
COME ON!
LET'S GO!
KATIE GARFIELD: ♪ HERE COME
THE SKELETONS ♪
♪ CRAWLING OUT YOUR CLOSET
♪ THEY GRAB YOUR ANKLES
WHEN YOU'RE RUNNING ♪
♪ TRY TO LOCK IT
♪ OPEN YOUR MOUTH,
BUT YOU CAN'T MAKE A SOUND ♪
♪ THE WALLS TUMBLE DOWN,
TRY TO BREATHE ♪
-THERE IT IS.
-WHOA, WHOA. I CAN'T WATCH.
YOU'RE BREAKING THROUGH
THE ELECTROMAGNETIC SHIELD.
[BEEPING]
OK. I SEE TWO
UNIQUE HEAT SIGNATURES.
THEY COULD BE RESTRAINTS.
DEPLOY YOUR CHUTE
AND THE EMPs.
[CHIMES]
[LOW HUMMING]
JACOB: WHY ARE WE HERE?
YOU'RE HERE BECAUSE ALICE
WANTS YOU TO HAVE
A FRONT ROW SEAT
TO WATCH HER KILL KATE.
SHE'S HERE
AT SAFIYAH'S REQUEST.
ME? WHAT DID I DO?
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU DID.
IT'S WHAT SAFIYAH THINKS
YOU'RE CAPABLE OF.
YOU'RE SKILLED, STRONG,
AND MOST OF ALL, LOYAL.
SHE WANTS YOU TO JOIN
HER ARMY.
HA HA HA!
WHY THE HELL
WOULD I JOIN AN ARMY
OF RUTHLESS KILLERS?
BECAUSE YOU'RE ALREADY
A PART OF ONE.
HIS. BOTH GROUPS
ARE ORGANIZED, ARMED,
AND...DANGEROUS,
BUT WE ARE COMMITTED
TO PROTECTING OUR PEOPLE
WHILE YOU OPPRESS YOURS.
WHOA! OHH!
TOUCHDOWN. I MADE IT.
OH. OH. SORT OF.
SEE? THAT WASN'T
SO BAD.
OH, YEAH.
YOU OWE ME A SPA DAY.
JUST REMEMBER TO
CONSERVE YOUR ENERGY,
OR YOUR VITALS
WILL DROP AGAIN.
WHOA!
YOU SEEING THIS?
OHH! THAT MUST BE
THE DESERT ROSE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
MORE BEAUTIFUL IN MY LIFE.
-RYAN?
-CRAP.
RYAN?
HELLO? CAN YOU HEAR ME?
THE EMPs MUST HAVE
KNOCKED OUT THE COMMS.
[RUSTLING]
OH.
HEY. I'M BATWOMAN.
UM...
IS YOUR QUEEN CHICK
AVAILABLE?
WE'RE REALLY
DOING THIS, HUH?
OH, BOY. HYAH!
SAFIYAH: I EXPECTED THIS
TO FEEL DIFFERENT.
ALICE: I'M SURE YOU
CAN ASK YOUR GAL PAL
ENIGMA
TO ROOT AROUND YOUR
HEAD AND FIX IT FOR YOU.
NOW GIVE ME KATE.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY YOU WANT TO KILL HER.
SHE BETRAYED ME.
THAT'S WHAT YOU KEEP
TELLING YOURSELF,
BUT MAYBE DEEP DOWN
IN THE DANGEROUS MUSINGS
OF YOUR ID,
THERE'S A COMPULSION
TO KILL HER
BECAUSE SHE'S
MORE LOVED THAN YOU,
AND IF YOU KILL HER,
AS IRRATIONAL AS IT SOUNDS,
YOU THINK THAT LOVE
WILL TRANSFER TO YOU.
BUT THAT'S NOT
HOW IT WORKS,
SO THE CONSCIOUS PART
OF YOU USES FEELINGS
LIKE PAIN AND HURT
AND BETRAYAL TO JUSTIFY IT,
BUT WHAT HAPPENS
TO ALL THOSE MESSY FEELINGS
WHEN KATE'S DEAD
AND EVERYONE STILL
HATES YOU?
YOU ARE NOT CHANGING
MY MIND.
I HAVE FANTASIZED
ABOUT KILLING
MY SISTER
SINCE SHE LOCKED ME
IN ARKHAM.
I KNOW WE'VE HAD
OUR DIFFERENCES, ALICE,
BUT I DO CARE ABOUT YOU.
I JUST NEED TO KNOW
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
MORE THAN THE AIR
I BREATHE.
AS YOU WISH.
I WILL TAKE YOU TO HER.
[RYAN BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
IF I HAD A NICKEL
FOR EVERY BAD PENNY.
SAFIYAH: BATWOMAN?
[RYAN GRUNTS]
WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE?
TATIANA: WE BELIEVE
SHE WAS TRYING TO HELP
OUR PRISONERS ESCAPE.
THEY'RE GONE.
IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT?
IT WILL BE...
BECAUSE YOU'RE
GONNA HELP ME,
AND IN RETURN,
I'M GONNA TELL
YOU SOMETHING
YOU'RE GONNA
WANT TO HEAR.
I SEE. UNFORTUNATELY,
I DON'T BARTER
WITH UNINVITED GUESTS,
SO IF YOU'LL EXCUSE US,
WE WERE IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOMETHING.
[RYAN GRUNTS]
YOU SURE THAT'S
YOUR BOY OVER THERE?
YOU MIGHT WANT TO LOOK
A LITTLE HARDER.
[GRUNTING]
ENOUGH WITH ALL
THESE DISTRACTIONS.
I GAVE YOU OCEAN,
AND, UM, NOW
YOU CAN GIVE ME
KATE.
TATIANA: MY QUEEN,
I HAD NO IDEA.
THAT WAS CLEARLY
HER INTENTION.
WHO IS THIS?
A NOBODY.
WELL, A--A BODY.
UM, JUST ONE THE MORGUE
WOULDN'T MISS.
YOU STILL HAVE FEELINGS
FOR HIM, DON'T YOU?
PUT HER WITH THE BAT
AND FIND ME OCEAN.
WHAT THE HELL'S THIS?
BATWOMAN.
LOOKS LIKE
AN EMP BLOCKER.
PROBABLY HOW THE CUFFS
DISARMED.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS SICK.
DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD
AN IN WITH BATWOMAN'S
DOCTOR.
SOPHIE: THAT DESERT ROSE
I NEED TO SNAG,
IT'S FOR HER.
YOU WORKING WITH HER?
I'M NOT WORKING
WITH HER.
I'M JUST NOT
WORKING AGAINST HER.
WHO IS SHE?
HONESTLY, I HAVE
NO IDEA.
I DON'T, SIR,
BUT SHE'S BEEN TRYING
TO HELP US TO FIND KATE,
WHO OBVIOUSLY
INSPIRED HER TO RISK
HER LIFE
FOR TOTAL STRANGERS.
I DON'T SEE THE HARM
IN US TEAMING UP.
EXCEPT THE CROWS
AND BATWOMAN ABIDE
BY TWO VERY DIFFERENT
IDEOLOGIES.
BECAUSE WE'RE HELD
ACCOUNTABLE FOR
OUR ACTIONS
AND SHE'S NOT?
IF THAT WERE
ACTUALLY TRUE,
THOSE AGENTS WHO PLOWED
DOWN WOLF SPIDER
ON THAT TARMAC
THE OTHER NIGHT
WOULDN'T HAVE JUST
BEEN FIRED.
THEY'D BE IN JAIL.
NOW YOU SOUND LIKE ONE
OF SAFIYAH'S LACKEYS.
YOU KNOW I LOVE
MY JOB, SIR,
BUT I THINK IT'S TIME
WE STOP PRETENDING
WE'RE NOT
ABOVE THE LAW.
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
AMMONIUM NITRATE.
AS IN THE BOMB-MAKING
CHEMICAL?
THAT'S ONE USE FOR IT.
ALSO MAKES A VERY EFFECTIVE
FERTILIZER.
TO GROW THE DESERT ROSE.
COME ON. KATE'S GOT TO
BE AROUND HER SOMEWHERE.
ERR!
RYAN: I WAS WONDERING
HOW THIS PLACE COULD
SUCK HARDER.
WHY ARE YOU EVEN
HERE?
TO STOP YOU
FROM KILLING KATE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THIS OBSESSION IS
WITH MY SISTER,
BUT YOU'RE NOT PART
OF OUR FAMILY SOAP, 'KAY?
[COUGHING]
OH. I SEE.
YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY OUT.
YOU'VE GOT A FEW HOURS
LEFT TO LIVE,
AND YOU NEED KATE
TO TAP BACK IN
BECAUSE GOD FORBID
THE BAT EARS GO
UNOCCUPIED
FOR 5 MINUTES!
SO PEOPLE LIKE YOU
CAN ROAM FREE AND KILL
THEIR OWN SIBLINGS?
NOT TO PLAY MONDAY
MORNING QUARTERBACK,
BUT IF YOU DIDN'T
WANT ME TO KILL KATE,
YOU SHOULD HAVE
STOPPED ME WHEN
YOU HAD THE CHANCE.
HEH HEH.
THEN I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO FOLLOW
YOUR DUMB ASS
TO THIS GODFORSAKEN ISLAND.
THE TRACKER WAS YOU.
HEH HEH.
[SIGHS]
CLEVER GIRL.
THAT'S IT?
I JUST ROYALLY
SCREWED UP A MOVE
YOU'VE BEEN PLANNING
FOR MONTHS.
YOU COULD END ME RIGHT NOW,
BUT YOU JUST HIT ME
WITH A LOUD SIGH.
YOU'RE ALREADY
ON DEATH'S DOOR.
LET'S LET NATURE RUN
ITS COURSE.
OR MAYBE YOU'RE
TERRIFIED.
OF KILLING
A SKY RAT?
OF KILLING YOUR SISTER.
YOU'VE BEEN THROWING
THE SAME TANTRUM FOR MONTHS,
POISONING BATS,
ATTACKING GOTHAM SQUARE,
KILLING GOD KNOWS
HOW MANY PEOPLE
BECAUSE IF KATE
WAS GONNA DIE
SHE WAS GONNA DIE
YOUR WAY,
AND HERE YOU ARE
MOMENTS AWAY
FROM GETTING WHAT YOU WANT
EXCEPT...IT'S NOT ACTUALLY
WHAT YOU WANT, IS IT?
YOU DON'T WANT KATE BACK
TO KILL HER.
YOU JUST WANT HER BACK.
HEH. WELL, SOMEONE
HAS SPENT AN AWFUL
LOT OF TIME THINKING
ABOUT THE GIRL THEY
BLAME FOR THEIR
MOM'S DEATH.
YOU REMEMBER WHAT YOU SAID
TO ME ON YOUR WAY OUT?
YOU SAID...
"IT'S NOT MY FAULT,"
BUT YOU WEREN'T TALKING
ABOUT KILLING MY MOM.
YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT WHY YOU ARE
THE WAY YOU ARE
BECAUSE AS DARK
AND SCREWED UP AS YOU ARE,
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
YOU'RE A VICTIM
OF SOMEBODY, TOO...
AND THAT TINY SLIVER
OF HUMANITY
WON'T LET YOU KILL
YOUR SISTER
BECAUSE THEN IT IS
YOUR FAULT.
[FOOTSTEPS]
SAFIYAH: IF YOU WANT
KATE, SHE'S YOURS.
YOU'VE TRAVELED
TOO FAR TO LEAVE
EMPTY-HANDED.
WHEN SOMEONE
DOES ME A FAVOR,
I ALWAYS REACT
IN KIND.
WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE IN RETURN
FOR HELPING ME?
I'VE BEEN POISONED.
I WANT ENOUGH DESERT ROSE
TO CURE MYSELF.
-SO BE IT.
-AND I WANT TO TAKE KATE KANE
BACK TO GOTHAM...
ALIVE.
YOU GAVE ME ONE THING.
IN FAIRNESS, I'M
OFFERING YOU THE SAME.
THE FLOWER OR THE GIRL--
CHOOSE ONE.
THE FLOWER.
DONE.
I SUPPOSE THAT LEAVES
KATE FOR YOU.
[DOOR SHUTS]
ENOUGH WITH THE GAMES.
WHERE IS SHE?
I WILL BRING YOU
TO HER
ONCE YOU'VE FULFILLED
YOUR END OF THE DEAL.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S YOUR
SECOND CHANCE.
IF YOU WANT KATE,
YOU'RE GOING TO
KILL HIM,
THE REAL HIM.
DID YOU DO THIS?
I DIDN'T TELL HER
ANYTHING.
SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO.
WE CONFISCATED
HER PHONE,
FOUND A SEARCH
FOR A CHARMING,
LITTLE SHANTYTOWN
IN PORTOFINO,
AND THERE YOU WERE.
ISN'T THAT PRECIOUS?
SHE WAS GOING TO
COME FIND YOU.
I ALWAYS WANTED TO SEE
THEIR PIAZZETTA.
SUCH A SWEET,
LITTLE LOVE STORY
THAT ENDS TODAY.
[WOMAN VOCALIZING]
I GAVE BATWOMAN
A CHOICE,
AND NOW I'LL DO
THE SAME FOR YOU.
YOU CAN HAVE ONE--
OCEAN OR KATE.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
WATCHING FOR THE FEED
TO COME BACK ONLINE.
I AM. IT'S NOT.
MARY, IT'S A PLANT.
IT'S RYAN'S PLANT,
SOMETHING SHE'S
MANAGED TO KEEP ALIVE
THROUGH HER MOTHER'S
DEATH,
THROUGH A PRISON SENTENCE
SHE DOESN'T DESERVE,
THROUGH A FAKE BRUCE WAYNE
TRYING TO KILL HER,
AND NOW SHE'S OFF
SAVING KATE JUST SO
WE CAN DO WHAT,
SHOW HER THE DOOR?
GETTING BOTH KATE
AND RYAN BACK WOULD BE
A GREAT PROBLEM TO HAVE,
MOSTLY BECAUSE IT WOULD MEAN
THEY SURVIVED
THIS HAIL MARY OF A PLAN.
THEN KEEPING THIS
ALIVE IS LITERALLY
THE LEAST I CAN DO.
OH, MY GOD!
[CHAINS RATTLING]
YOU'RE ONE OF SAFIYAH'S
MANY ARMS.
OUR QUEEN DOESN'T LIKE
TO BE FOLLOWED.
UHH-AAH!
LUKE: HEY!
MARY: HYAH!
OK. OK. OH.
THE ELEVATOR
TO THE CAVE IS OUT,
-SO WE GOT TO TAKE THE STAIRS.
-WAIT.
-WAIT, WAIT, WAIT. RYAN'S PLANT.
-WHAT ABOUT IT?
I CAN'T LEAVE IT.
WE CAN GRAB IT LATER.
HEY. YOU WANT TO
SEND HER A PICTURE,
ASK HER IF SHE THINKS
WE'RE DOING A GOOD JOB?
RYAN WOULD WANT US
TO RUN AWAY FROM
A TRAINED ASSASSIN.
SHE ASKED ME
FOR ONE THING, LUKE.
OK. OK. FINE, MARY.
JUST GRAB THE DAMN THING.
FINE!
WANT TO ROCK, PAPER,
SCISSORS IT?
NO!
OCEAN: WHAT IS THIS
EVEN ABOUT?
SOME B.S. FRAME JOB?
YOU MADE HER BELIEVE
I KILLED OFF
HER LITTLE GANG
AND BLEW UP
HER SISTER'S PLANE.
WHY WOULD I STIR THINGS
UP BETWEEN YOU TWO?
YOUR LITTLE
BRAIN WIPE WORKED.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW ALICE
EXISTED UNTIL A FEW WEEKS AGO.
TELL HER!
TELL HER, ALICE.
IT WAS SOMEONE ELSE.
I DIDN'T FRAME SAFIYAH.
GIVE ME THE KNIFE.
THIS WAS NEVER
ABOUT SOMEONE SETTING YOU UP.
THIS WAS ABOUT ALICE
CARING ABOUT ME
MORE THAN SHE CARED
ABOUT YOU
AND YOUR INABILITY
TO LIVE WITH IT.
KILL HIM, AND YOU CAN
HAVE YOUR SISTER.
OCEAN: IS IT WORTH IT,
KILLING ME JUST
TO KILL KATE?
IF YOU REALLY WANT
TO PUNISH HER,
LEAVE HER HERE
TO ROT.
[WOMAN VOCALIZING]
I'M SORRY, OCEAN...
BUT I DON'T WANT TO
KILL HER ANYMORE.
[GASPS]
NOW BRING ME TO KATE...
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE
ON THIS ISLAND DIES.
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
SHE'S BLEEDING ALL
OVER THE DAMN PLANT.
HEY. MARY!
YOU LIFT, I GRAB.
-COME ON.
-OK.
OK. GRAB IT,
GRAB IT.
[WOMAN MOANS]
-RUN!
JULIA: OI, OI.
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
JULIA, WHEN DID YOU
GET BACK?
WHO THE BLOODY HELL
IS THAT?
UNH!
OH. OK.
WHERE'S SAFIYAH?
SHE SAID SHE WOULD
BRING ME A DESERT ROSE.
SHE WILL...
ONCE SHE'S FINISHED
WITH ALICE.
IT'S FINALLY TIME
FOR ALICE TO BE REUNITED
WITH HER SISTER.
JULIA: SOMEONE CARE TO
EXPLAIN WHY I HAD TO DAGGER
ONE OF SAFIYAH'S MINIONS?
THE MANY ARMS FOUND OUT
WE TRACKED ALICE
TO CORYANA.
COURTESY OF BATWOMAN,
WHO FOLLOWED HER THERE
TO FIND KATE.
GOT IT.
UM, THAT'S ACTUALLY
WHY I'M HERE.
TATIANA: I HAVE TO
APPLAUD YOU
FOR PICKING YOUR OWN
SURVIVAL OVER KATE'S.
TAKE IT
FROM AN ISLAND LIFER--
SELF-SACRIFICE
IS OVERRATED.
HEH.
THAT'S NOT
WHY I DID IT.
ALICE ISN'T GOING
TO KILL HER SISTER.
I'M CURIOUS
HOW YOU KNOW THAT.
I SAW IT
IN HER FACE.
REVENGE, HATE,
ANGER, TH...
THOSE ARE THE ONLY
EMOTIONS SHE KNOWS,
SO SHE HIDES
BEHIND THEM.
WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT ONE THING.
ALICE ISN'T GOING TO
KILL HER SISTER TODAY.
KATE?
WHERE'S KATE?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
JULIA: I HIRED A TEAM
TO RUN DOWN SOME LEADS
FROM THE TIP LINE.
WE FOUND...
BODY PARTS OFF
THE COAST
OF BLUDHAVEN.
MUST HAVE GOT CAUGHT
IN THE CURRENTS. UM...
WHAT DO--WHAT DO
YOU MEAN BODY PARTS?
THEY RAN THE DNA.
NO. NO!
ALICE: WHERE IS SHE?
WHERE IS MY SISTER?
I NEVER HAD
YOUR SISTER, ALICE.
THE DNA WAS HERS.
IT WAS KATE'S.
I'M SO SORRY.
KATE'S DEAD.
ENN! NO! NO!
NO! NO!
GET HER OUT OF HERE.
NO! KATE! NO! NO!
LET ME GO!
OHH! YOU BLEW UP
HER PLANE!
YOU KILLED HER,
YOU STUPID, LYING BITCH!
I HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH HER PLANE,
BUT WHEN SOMEONE
TRIED TO FRAME ME FOR
KILLING YOUR SISTER,
I SAW AN OPPORTUNITY
TO GET WHAT I WANTED,
TO MAKE YOU AND OCEAN
PAY FOR YOUR BETRAYAL.
YOU ARE A MONSTER!
AND I CREATED YOU,
SO WHAT DOES THAT
MAKE YOU?
GET HER OFF MY ISLAND.
NO. NO! NO! NO!
AAH! AAH!
ARE YOU SEEING THIS?
THIS IS GONNA GET US
OUT OF HERE.
-YOU KNOW HOW TO FLY?
-USED TO.
I'LL GET THIS RUNNING.
I'LL KEEP LOOKING
FOR KATE.
GIVE ME AN HOUR.
JUST...
-IF WE'RE NOT BACK--
-I'LL FIND YOU. GO.
WELL DONE, MY QUEEN.
THIS SHOULD SERVE
AS A LESSON TO ANYONE
WHO DECIDES TO
BETRAY YOU.
[GASPS]
[COUGHING]
WHAT THE HELL
IS HAPPENING?
HE WAS DEAD.
WHEN THE BLADE
WAS MOLDED,
ITS MOLTEN WAS IMBUED
WITH THE DESERT ROSE.
ITS CURATIVE PROPERTIES
SEALED OCEAN'S ARTERIES
UPON ITS ENTRANCE.
[COUGHING]
WELCOME BACK, BROTHER.
THAT BREATH IN YOUR CHEST
IS ONLY THERE BECAUSE OF ME.
I GAVE YOU YOUR LIFE BACK.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
WHY WOULD YOU DO
THIS TO ME?
WHEN PUSH COMES TO SHOVE,
ALICE DOESN'T ACTUALLY
HAVE FEELINGS FOR YOU.
I WANTED YOU TO
SEE THAT.
YOU'RE SICK.
I'M NOT THE ONE WHO
JUST PUT A KNIFE
THROUGH YOUR HEART.
ALICE'S LOYALTY WILL ALWAYS
LIE WITH HER SISTER
JUST AS YOURS SHOULD LIE
WITH ME
BECAUSE LOYALTY IS
EVERYTHING TO ME.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
TATIANA?
IT IS, MY QUEEN.
THEN WHY TEST IT?
WHY AFTER I GAVE YOU
POWER AND FREEDOM
AND HEALTH
WOULD YOU PICK A FIGHT
WITH ALICE ON MY BEHALF?
SAFIYAH, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT--
YOU SLAUGHTERED
ALICE'S GANG.
YOU SENT HER A NOTE
SAYING I KILLED KATE.
YOU REELED HER BACK
INTO MY LIFE.
WHY WHEN YOU KNOW
HOW HARD I WORKED
TO FORGET HER?
BUT YOU NEVER
FORGOT HER.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
YOU COULDN'T.
YOU WERE IN LOVE.
I WAS...TRYING
TO GET RID OF THAT
TOXIC AN--
ENOUGH!
YOU ALWAYS HATED ALICE
AND TRIED TO DRIVE
A WEDGE BETWEEN US.
-THAT'S HOW I KNEW IT WAS YOU.
-NO. NO.
YOU WANTED TO SEE
HER LOSE,
AND NOW YOU HAVE.
CONGRATULATIONS, TATIANA.
I HOPE YOU WERE
ENTERTAINED!
[GASPS]
KEEP THAT IN HER.
I'LL PULL IT OUT
WHEN I DECIDE TO FORGIVE HER.
[ALICE GRUNTING]
AGH!
GABRIELLE APLIN:
♪ THE HOUSE IS BURNING
♪ BETTER RUN FOR COVER
♪ RUN FOR COVER
♪ THE HOUSE IS BURNING
♪ BETTER RUN FOR COVER
AHH.
APLIN: ♪ RUN FOR COVER
♪ WHEELS KEEP TURNING,
AND I'M... ♪
NOW WE BOTH HAVE NOTHING.
APLIN: ♪ GOING UNDER
♪ THE HOUSE IS BURNING
♪ BETTER RUN FOR COVER
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
APLIN: ♪ RUN FOR COVER
MY ROSES!
APLIN: ♪ THE HOUSE IS BURNING
OH, MY GOD.
RYAN: IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU ARE HERE.
ARE YOU OK?
DID YOU GET
A DESERT ROSE?
I WAS WONDERING WHY
MY GUARD LEFT HIS POST.
LOOKS LIKE IT WASN'T
MEANT TO BE.
WE NEED TO FIND KATE
AND GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
KATE'S NOT HERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
KATE'S NOT HERE?
I MEAN...
SAFIYAH LIED.
TATIANA TOLD ME
KATE WAS NEVER
ON THIS ISLAND.
[LENSES CLICK]
KATE DIED
IN THE PLANE CRASH.
THIS CAN'T BE REAL.
I DON'T WANT TO
BELIEVE IT EITHER.
[COMMS CRACKLING]
THE FEED'S BACK ON.
IS THAT THE DESERT ROSE?
JULIA: BLOODY HELL.
IT'S ASHES.
MARY: OH, THIS
ISN'T HAPPENING.
WE NEEDED THAT.
RYAN NEEDED THAT TO LIVE.
[SIGHS]
OH. OH, MY GOD.
THE COMMANDER THINKS HE
CAN HOTWIRE THE PLANE.
WE NEED TO GO.
[GAGGING]
[COUGHING]
I'M NOT GONNA MAKE IT.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
I'VE ONLY GOT
A FEW HOURS.
THERE'S NOTHING
THERE FOR ME.
WILL YOU SIT
WITH ME?
PLEASE.
I DON'T WANT TO
DIE ALONE.
I'M SORRY WE GOT OFF
ON THE WRONG FOOT.
YOU DIDN'T DESERVE THAT.
IT'S BECAUSE
I WASN'T KATE.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
HELLO?
SOPHIE,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
HOW IS MY PHONE
SUDDENLY WORKING?
LUKE: THE EMPs THAT
KNOCKED OUT THE POWER
MUST HAVE EXPIRED,
BUT I COULDN'T FLAG
BATWOMAN ON THE COMMS.
I'M WITH HER NOW.
YOU NEED TO GET HER
BACK TO GOTHAM.
SHE DOESN'T
WANT TO LEAVE.
TELL HER TO GET
HER ASS BACK HERE NOW!
I HAVE A CURE!
[BUZZING]
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
YOUNG KATE: IT'S OUR
BIRTHSTONE.
GABI KANE: RED IS
A VERY SYMBOLIC COLOR.
YOUNG KATE: LET'S
TAKE A PICTURE, BETH.
MAKE SURE OUR NECKLACES
ARE IN IT.
READY? CHEESE!
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!