Oh, God.
Ohh!
Huh!
Hey!
Ugh! Oof!
Batwoman to batcave.
We need medics to the
rooftop lot above Harper's Plaza.
Batwoman to batcave.
Do you copy?
I need medics now.
Batwoman to batcave!
You never told me
the 911 operator
was a batwoman fangirl.
Dude's gonna live.
I should have told you
not to work tonight.
You know, I might just
need a little time.
Of course.
Mary and I can
cover bat duties,
try to I.D.
The stabby chick
making lawyer kabobs.
I mean...
I need time alone.
Copy.
You know I'm here
if you need me, right?
*BATWOMAN*
Season 02  Episode 16
Episode Title: "Rebirth"
Aired on: June 13, 2021.
Special agent
Russell Tavaroff
has just been released
on bond.
He'll be a free man
as he awaits trial,
accused of falsifying
evidence to justify
the shooting
of an unarmed Gotham citizen.
The uproar
over crows misconduct
has been ignored
by Gotham officials
until one hero spoke up,
former crows commander
Jacob Kane.
Two crows agents shot...
Heh.
I expose Kane as the godfather
of a fraudulent security racket,
and now these cloying half-wits
in the fake news
are crowning him
a hero.
Haven't you
done enough, Roman?
You imprisoned
the man's daughter,
then brainwashed her
into your own.
He murdered my Circe.
So toying with Kane's
daughter is your way
of... feeling better
about him killing yours?
I apologize,
your royal highness,
but when you gave me
the details
of Kate Kane's flight
out of national city,
you knew exactly what
I had in mind for her.
Speaking of you owing
me a favor,
I was hoping to employ
your daughter's services
to settle my affairs
in Gotham.
I have reason to believe
that Circe's
unique attributes could
benefit us both.
Whatever it is,
I don't want her involved.
She's finally got
her life back.
Last I heard, she was
running around
with a tree stapled
to her face.
Oh, she's ready to
make her grand reentry
into Gotham's
influencer life.
After all, my p.R. Team
covered up the incident
that landed her
in Arkham to begin with
and her death,
yada yada.
They've put together a
very millennial cover story
to explain
her disappearance.
3 words...
Malibu, rehab, retreat.
This is the crown Jewel.
A life
lived but once
is a life lived not at all.
The newest line
from janus cosmetics
has arrived...
Rebirth.
It wasn't enough
that she believed
she was my Circe.
Between the new face
and a strict regimen
of janus restorative
burn cream,
she now looks like
her, too.
I know enigma gave her
Circe's memories,
but who
gave her Circe's face?
If you can believe it,
that rambling
sewer rat Alice.
You brought Kate Kane
and Alice together?
When was this?
Two days ago. Why?
Alice is Beth Kane,
you idiot.
Ugh!
You're coming
with us, kiddo.
If you're wearing
yoga pants,
this is so much worse
than I thought.
Now tell me what
I'm walking into.
This is a government
safe house.
Bidets in the bathroom.
They wouldn't even give us
hand soap
for the community center.
Turns out the lawyer
whose computer was stolen
by "kill Bill" superfan
was working with judges
to place people
into witness relocation.
And all that top-secret
location information
- was on his computer.
- Exactly,
so sword lady's
looking for somebody
in witness relocation,
so I placed a trace
on all of his
outgoing calls,
assuming that he'd reach out
to the witnesses,
give them a heads-up.
And you figured
all that out?
Oh. You know, I may
have outsourced
the fancy parts
to Sophie.
Anyway, we are starting
with this guy
because the lawyer called
him first, called him a lot,
but he never picked up.
Starting to know why.
Found our Vic.
Same perp left
a sword in him.
Definitely trying
to make a statement.
Oh, man. Poor guy
was blind.
This isn't your fight,
batwoman.
Why is that? Because
I can actually fight back?
Tatiana?
Unh!
DNA match complete.
Heh.
My god.
It really is you.
You've got me confused
with a dead girl.
Alice: No. You've got you
confused with a dead girl.
Two dozen inmates used
Circe Sionis as a doormat
on their way out
of Arkham.
Listen.
I know this is a lot
to handle.
Oof!
Hey!
Sorry, but did you
want her to escape?
How do we get Kate back?
There's a secret keyword
to unlock her memories
except the woman
who did that to her
is dead.
The other option is we jog
her memory piece by piece
using personal objects.
Ocean: That's where
these come in.
Everything that's left
of Kate's childhood.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
O... cean, meet daddy.
Daddy, meet ocean.
Good to meet you,
Mr. Kane.
Right. What do we
do now?
Alice: When enigma locked
me out of my memories,
I forced my way back
in with a photograph.
Her work is formidable,
but... as soon as the
first crack appears,
she'll go mad wanting to
know the truth about her life.
Enigma worked
on you, too?
Daddy, you don't get
this extra
without
a little shove.
I thought the shove
was Cartwright.
No. He didn't
fully break me.
I was too strong.
I can attest to that.
Alice may have been
angry
and reckless
and ornery,
but... she could
still love.
What are you saying,
that... Enigma
took away your ability
to love?
I'll let you
get on with it.
Nice to meet you,
Mr. Kane.
Yeah. This Mr. Kane thing
is definitely weird for me.
I want the guy
to like me.
Call me old-fashioned.
If you told me I'd be
in the crows headquarters
with my father,
my sister,
and my... Boy toy
and I wouldn't be
the one in cuffs...
No one ever accused you
of being predictable.
Call you later.
Good.
Ezra castellanos.
Never heard of him.
Probably because up
until a few days ago,
he was being protected by crows
security in witness protection.
5 years ago, Ezra's eyes
were gouged out
with a soup spoon
by a woman named
Circe Sionis.
So this case
was sealed,
but Luke has
a thingy
that unseals seals.
- Ok. Then.
- Ha!
Circe's the daughter of janus
cosmetics founder Roman Sionis.
Former model claimed
self-defense
after Ezra assaulted
her at a party,
and after she went
to Arkham,
Ezra was afraid the Sionis
family would come after him,
so he went
into WITSEC.
Didn't Alice stop by
the other day
asking if someone named
Circe showed up to you?
Yeah, and now I'm
just confused.
Yeah. I'm gonna check
on Luke.
Well, we could try
and track him down
with his fancy
hacker tools.
Assuming you know
which buttons to press.
Ok.
Huh?
Diamond Dust's "Sising stars"
playing...
♪ We are stolen pennies
from the wishing well ♪
♪ We are...
You stalking
me, fox?
It's law enforcement
only.
They let you in,
and last I checked,
your new occupation
is unemployed haircut.
Two whiskeys neat.
Look. I understand
the problem here, ok?
- Oh.
- Yeah. I'm free on bail,
my charges are
gonna be dropped,
and as far as the law
is concerned,
well, we're back to
you being a car thief
who pulled a gun,
so...
I'm not throwing
my career away
because your daddy
didn't teach you
how to stay out of the
wrong place at the wrong time.
Ooh. See, if I were you,
I would not talk
about my father.
♪ Yeah, we are
♪ Yeah, we are...
You come here
looking for a fight?
You looking for another
fake excuse to shoot me?
So how do you propose
we settle this?
Now I heard you won the
crows' hold 'em tournament
two years in a row.
You are a stalker.
Really hope you have
a plan, kid.
You know, some of us
are just here to play cards.
I like punk rock.
How edgy.
You should remember
this bag.
I found a joint
in this pocket,
grounded you
for the entire summer.
Harsh. It wasn't
even coke.
You think he would
try memories
I would actually
want to remember.
You said it ended up being
the best summer you ever had.
I am not Kate Kane,
and even if I was,
what makes you think
I would want to come
back to a father
who stopped looking
for both daughters
and a literal
evil twin, hmm?
What am I missing?
This.
When we were kids,
you had a big crush
on Jenny goldberg.
You only liked her
because she skateboarded,
but you were so excited
because she liked you back
except you weren't
out yet.
You wanted to tell me
you were gay,
but you kept
chickening out.
You knew I had to be
the first to know,
but I was also
the hardest
because I mattered
the most to you,
me... Beth...
Your twin who spent
9 months in the womb with you,
and you were scared
of pushing me away,
so I made you
that stupid mug
to say I already knew
and I loved you.
I'm locked
in a room.
What room?
A... a basement,
a cell.
I... I can smell
formaldehyde.
Cartwright's.
I can't get out.
Why am I here?
Who's there?
Beth?
Beth, is that you?
That's the basement
I spent my childhood in.
You've been there.
Do you remember?
It's... it's more
of a feeling.
I'm... I'm screaming, but
I can't get your attention.
That... that's not
what happened.
Maybe it's a metaphor.
Circe's subconscious
is a cell,
and Kate needs me
to free her.
How can you be sure?
Because it's all
I ever wanted.
Ok. I'm gonna
take your hands,
so just, um...
Don't break mine.
Beth?
Are you there?
Kate, it's me.
I'm here.
I'm not gonna
leave you.
I remember now.
You found me,
but I couldn't
find you.
It's ok.
There's still time.
Poker? Really?
We need you home.
We think Safiyah's
in Gotham.
Thought you
and Safiyah were good.
We are, but the guys
who her lackey
ran her sword through can't
really say the same thing.
Ok. Well, you said
you and Mary got this,
and I'm in the middle of
a game right now, so...
Look. We will give you
the space to do your thing,
but we need a hand.
In this family, we take care
of each other first, right?
Every doctor in that hospital
thought I was gonna die
in that bed,
but you and Mary
slipped me the desert Rose,
and I woke right up.
Ok. If there was a thank
you somewhere in there, I...
I didn't want to
wake up.
How can you say that?
When I was under,
I saw my dad,
and, I mean, he was
right there.
Why the hell
would I want to live
in a world where we
get shot for no reason,
where the gunmen get
out of jail free
so it's not
a matter of if
there's another
bullet coming,
it's when?
Why would I go
through it
when I can be
with my dad again?
I got to get back
to my game.
What? What do you
mean Kate's alive?
She was declared dead.
Julia I.D.
Her parietal skull bone.
Her DNA checks out.
I ran her prints myself.
Look. Everything's a little
bit complicated just now.
The only thing you
need to know
is that Kate is alive
and safe with me at crows,
where no one can hurt her.
Ok.
I'm on my way.
Just give us a little
bit more time.
She's not quite herself.
Someone brainwashed her
into thinking that
she was someone else.
- Who?
- Turns out black mask
is cosmetics guru
Roman Sionis.
He hypnotized Kate
into thinking
that she was his
daughter Circe.
Kate is Circe Sionis.
Dad, you need to be
careful.
We have reason to believe
that Circe's connected to Safiyah.
What? How?
Dad?
Daddy?
- Run!
- Where?
Anywhere. I'll find you.
Err! Ohh!
Unh!
Ugh!
Miss me?
He was saying
that the DNA checks out,
but Kate thinks
she's Circe Sionis,
and she's been alive
this entire time,
which doesn't actually
make sense
because Julia wouldn't
lie to us and say
that she found Kate's skull
because everybody knows
that you can't survive
without a skull!
- Mary.
- Sorry. Just freaking out
- right now.
- Me, too.
Pulling up
to the crows.
Luke needs to know
that Kate's alive.
I know we did the right
thing saving his life,
and I knew he'd have a
lot to work through, but...
Right now, it feels like
we just added to his pain.
It sucks.
I'm glad to have you
on the comms, batcave.
I'll call you back.
Are you Kate Kane?
Can I get back
to you on that?
Need a ride?
- ♪ Outside the castle wall
- Call.
- ♪ The battle call
- Raise.
- ♪ In the air,
- I'm out.
♪ The reckoning is near ♪
Reraise.
- - ♪ Until sides are recognized ♪
- Ohh!
All-in.
♪ All they ever gave
♪ Two sides to describe...
Oh. Sorry.
Do I have you covered?
Yeah. I have a lot
more chips than you.
Uh, look. If you
got me beat
and you want to start
a little collection
with your buddies here
so you can match my chips,
I'll just hang out.
You want to let me in
on the grudge... with this?
What? Grudge?
This is just a friendly game.
Ok.
♪ I know,
I know, I know ♪♪
Why haven't I seen
you around here before?
Name's John Diggle.
I'm from Star City.
I'm in town on a contract
with A.R.G.U.S.
Well, hey. Welcome.
Please. Allow me to remove
this little... distraction,
who's been playing
with us.
Buddy, Gotham city is
our town,
and the house
always wins.
♪ Live in this world
whoo!
I mean, people
do say that.
It's true. The house
does win a lot
because it cheats.
♪ And I know,
I know... ♪
But then sometimes,
I mean, the house
is just
so damn stupid
that it can cheat
and still manage
to lose.
Heh. The man made
a straight.
What no applause
for that... for that
gut-shot straight draw?
I mean, and the speech?
No style points for that?
Ok. Whatever.
Ahem.
I've been running
from this fight my whole life...
And it has gotten me
nowhere.
Hmm. First you're up,
then you're down.
I don't know if you're
gonna take any comfort
from this, Jake,
but, uh, now,
you're down
and out for good.
True for both of us,
black mask,
unless you think Gotham's
gonna buy its zit cream
from a psychotic
gang leader.
Tough call.
It's a good zit cream.
On the topic of
hereditary diseases,
Gotham is about
to find out
that your daughter,
uh, Beth Kane
is none other than
the knife-slinging,
nursery-rhyme-named
Alice.
My people will make sure
gcpd is on your doorstep
before you can clear
this up.
Gcpd on my doorstep?
You know what?
That's a fantastic idea.
Gentlemen.
If you try to blow
the whistle
on the Sionis family,
not only will the public
think you're as crazy
as your daughter,
but the gcpd will, uh,
misplace any evidence
you happen to dig up,
and I will personally make sure
that any family
you have left
suffers immensely.
Jacob Kane, you're
under arrest
for aiding and abetting the
criminal at large known as Alice.
Come on. Is this what
you really wanted?
Unh!
I'm taking
my money back.
That's enough!
Easy, star city.
It's not your fight.
- He won.
- You saw the blatant disrespect
at the table.
In Gotham city,
we hold the line
against punks
like this.
Ohh! Ergh!
I hear you shot him
the other day,
and now you're upset that
he's not showing you respect?
Ohh!
Um...
I never thought
I'd see you again.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
I think she's still
trying to figure things out.
Oh. Yeah.
Of course. Right.
Just any questions
you have, I'm here
or not, you know.
I'm not trying
to smother you.
- I need a drink.
- I...
Did you find my dad?
No. She said a bunch
of false face goons
raided the joint.
Then she described someone
wearing a hair chain
and holding two
big-ass swords.
- Tatiana.
- She thinks Tatiana
wanted Alice.
Alice was
at the crows
with... with my dad?
Literally, what
is happening?
Kate?
Ok. Don't get too excited.
There's still a lot
she doesn't remember.
Sophie.
Whoa.
So Alice just told
you about some mug,
and that was it, really?
Alice? Really?
Uhh. Where is
my father?
Ok. Let's chill.
Just give her a minute.
Hey.
We know it's a lot.
Maybe you should
sit down.
Yeah.
That sounds good.
Agh!
Beth?
Where are you?
Where did you go?
I think you've caused
quite enough trouble.
Hey, Kate.
You're good. You're safe, ok?
No!
Agh!
Ohh!
Wow. You just carry
one of those around?
Oh, yeah. Syringe
chock full of benzos?
Comes in handy
in Gotham.
- Everyone ok?
- Everyone but Kate.
What the hell
happened?
I think Kate and Circe
are duking it out in her head,
and Circe's winning
right now.
So if Alice is
the lynchpin
to jogging more
of Kate's memories
- and Safiyah has her...
- no, no, no.
Even if I could stomach
the idea
of saving Alice's life
right now,
Safiyah came all the way
from Coryana
for the pyro who torched
her entire kingdom,
so what could we possibly
offer her
that would be better
than that, hmm?
Gotham steakhouse
gift card or...
She could rebuild
that kingdom...
If I give her
the desert Rose.
Ryan... no.
It's your last
connection to your mom.
You're really willing
to do that?
Willing is pushing it.
More like we don't have
anything else to bargain with.
Even if you're willing
to make the trade,
how do we even
find her?
Maybe this is a good excuse
to show Luke
just how badly
his friends need him.
Hey. You good?
Yeah.
Your old man's
Lucius fox, right?
Put together some details
when you were having
that friendly game
of hold 'em. Heh heh heh.
You lost your
old man young.
That's... that's
hard, man.
That's real hard.
My old man was a
marine deployed overseas
when I was a boy,
killed in action.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- It's all right.
But it left me
with a lot of questions
about him and me,
so I get it when those
questions become more important
than anything else
in the world, man.
Believe me, I get it.
What you have to
remember is that
we all end up in the same
place eventually, man,
and you'll see
your father soon enough.
What changes with time is
what you get to tell him
you did while you were
on the earth.
Ok. So... I'm just
supposed to ignore the fact
that I'm still
angry as hell?
No, brother.
Don't ignore it. Use it.
You carry the torch
for the great fox family.
You
stand for justice.
You're gonna need anger
to win that fight.
- You ok?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Just some, um,
fogginess, dizziness.
Something's not right.
Lifetime of anger has its side
effects, you know what I mean?
You know we have a
world-renowned neurology department
at Gotham general?
I can get you
a connect if you want.
That's actually
why I'm here.
Have an appointment
in the morning.
Is it supposed
to do that?
No. That's
highly unusual.
In fact, I think
it's...
It's morse code.
- Need...
- Fox...
Help.
I should go.
You know, you seem
pretty important for a man
who's trying to get his
ass kicked in an alley.
Good thing
you're alive.
Thanks.
Take care of yourself,
Luke fox.
Hello. This is
Dana DeWitt,
and I'm coming to you live
from grand street downtown
outside of gcpd headquarters.
Earlier today, we got word
of the shocking arrest
of former crows commander
Jacob Kane,
who is rumored to be...
There he is.
Mr. Kane, is it true
you're the father
of one of Gotham's
most notorious monsters?
It's not like
that, Dana.
Yes, she's my daughter,
and her name is Beth.
She's not a monster.
She's a victim
of evil men and women
who stole her childhood
and manipulated her mind,
of a father who... who
didn't come through for her
when she needed him.
Beth has had
the hardest life
of anyone
I've ever known,
and yet... She has
this humanity inside of her.
I can't imagine
ever having that strength,
so if Gotham is angry
at me, then so be it.
I ask only this of them
as a father.
When you judge Alice
for her crimes,
remember Beth.
She's in here,
my queen.
My dear...
I believe you owe
me an island.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ugh! Ow!
Ooh. This is deep.
How many times
you get hit?
You should've
saw him, ok?
Didn't realize poker
was a contact sport.
Wasn't there
an emergency?
Safiyah's holding Alice
somewhere in Gotham,
so we need your
brilliant decoder brain
to figure out
how to find her...
And save her.
Ok. I give up.
What are you
not telling me?
Kate's still alive.
There's nothing left
of Coryana.
Your scorching
was thorough and complete.
9 villagers perished
in the Blaze,
so if you have managed
to maintain a list
after all these years,
do include them
in your grand total.
You told me you had
my sister.
What did you expect?
If I'm honest,
that,
a tantrum
because at the end
of the day, Alice,
you're just
a spoiled child
who believes she deserves
more than she's earned.
What is this?
Chill. I come in peace.
Let her in.
What are you
doing here?
I've had this plant
a long time.
I didn't even know what
it was or what it could do
until recently,
but even before I knew,
it was my favorite
thing in the whole world.
And why is that?
A woman I counted
as my mother,
she died a while back,
and this plant was
my last connection
to her.
And yet you brought it
to offer
in what I presume
is a trade for Alice?
Your enemy.
Alice is the key
to getting
her sister's
memories back.
The choice is easy.
Revenge is short-lived,
but rebuilding
your island,
it's a no-brainer.
What I don't understand
is what's in this for you.
I see someone giving up
her most valued possession
to save a woman she hates
to unlock the memories
of another woman
she doesn't even know.
It's either remarkable
or remarkably stupid.
I know what Kate Kane
stands for,
and I owe a debt to
the symbol she created.
Found my second chance
at a life because of her.
I've never met her,
but... I believe
you'd make
Kate Kane proud.
I accept your offer.
If I can't have you,
at least I can
have my kingdom.
Thank you...
My queen.
I'll make sure to tell
ocean you send your regards.
Alice, let's go.
It's funny.
Here you are
a literal queen,
and yet I have my
boyfriend and my sister,
and all you have
is a little flower.
Oh, there you go
again,
believing you deserve more
than you've earned.
What did you do?
Where's Tatiana?
Don't play dumb, Alice.
You always knew deep down
a girl like you
could never be worthy
of having it all.
Hey. Easy.
We brought you to a place we
thought you'd be more comfortable.
You kind of lashed out
at Mary.
I did? Is she ok?
She's fine.
She's worried about you.
Who am I?
Whose face is this?
We'll get to that.
Do you remember anything
you've been put through
all these months?
- Why are you here?
- Because you don't seem
to want to stay
in there like a good girl,
so now we're gonna have
to do things the messy way.
Hey.
Are you ok?
Can I get you a glass
of water or something?
I'm gonna need something
stronger than that.
There's an amazing
bottle of tasteless vodka
in my office desk,
bottom drawer.
Would you mind?
- I'll go check.
- Thank you.
Ocean isn't answering
his phone.
I don't care.
You heard
what Safiyah said.
And I didn't give up
my plant
so you could run off
to your boyfriend.
- Get in the car!
- Or what?
You'll kill me,
drag against my will?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
You need me alive and cooperative.
I don't need you.
Your sister needs you.
If she really is back
to being Kate Kane,
then my disappointing her
will come as no surprise.
Ocean?
Oh.
So Safiyah took
her little magic knife
out of you so you could
stick it in me.
That's sweet.
You can keep it.
Oops.
This isn't the magic one.
Ocean?
No. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
You're safe?
How is that even possible?
Blackgate's worst offenders
are all people that you put there.
Judge granted
my petition
for change of venue.
I'm... being transferred
to Metropolis.
Ok. That's a start.
I'll start making calls,
line up character
witnesses, and...
Mary, we're not gonna
beat these charges,
not with Roman Sionis
pulling the strings
and Alice's reputation
hanging over me.
She earned that reputation,
not you,
so you don't deserve
to take the fall
for the things that
she did.
Mary, I want you to
promise me something.
Seeing Kate and Alice
together gave me hope.
When I saw how Kate
was buried
under this grotesque
stranger named Circe,
I understood the same thing
must have happened to... to Beth.
If Circe and Alice
go away,
we can get Kate
and Beth back.
There's only one person
who can make that happen.
Dad...
I understood she
took a lot from you,
took a lot
from all of us,
but... I just wish you
could have seen Beth
before the accident.
Hoping one day
you get the chance to.
That's why I'm counting
on you to save
both your sisters.
No pressure!
Never had to worry
about you before.
Not gonna start now.
I love you, Mary.
I love you, too.
Remind me to never
do a serial killer a favor again.
I'm sorry
you lost your plant.
I know it meant
a lot to you,
seeing as I
babysat it.
Ok. The plant does not
matter to me right now.
I know you want
to see Kate,
but I got something
to say.
I am so sorry
for what happened to you.
I have no idea what it's
like to walk in your shoes,
but let me make
something very clear.
I am not sorry
I made sure you lived,
so screw your choice.
You're not leaving me.
Hey. Did you see Kate
down there?
No. We thought
she was up here.
I left for two seconds
to get her something,
and when I came back,
she was gone.
When did you get in?
I've been calling everybody,
looking for you.
Am I Kate Kane?
Kate Kane? Who? No.
No, no, sweetheart.
You're my baby girl.
Why am I having
her memories?
Why do I have
her fingerprints,
and why do I know
where she keeps
her fricking alcohol
in her office?
You're having an episode.
Let's practice
our grounding techniques.
Agh!
Tell me
what's happening.
You're having an episode,
sweetheart. Please.
Tell her, Roman,
or I will.
I've always held the belief
that a woman
has a right to decide
exactly who
she wants to be.
Subtitles
Synchronized by srjanapala
Greg, move your head!