As if there were
a shortage of syringes
in Gotham's gutters,
a new party drug just hit the streets
that apparently
makes an amphetamine high
feel like your Earl Gray
has steeped for too long.
It seems the gang known
as the False Face Society
is showing
their entrepreneurial side
by making
and distributing snakebite,
known for its dual-pronged
injector needles,
which are said to give
a double whammy dose
of fantasy and fright,
so more fang for your buck.
This trippy two-for-one
is part psychedelic mushroom oil,
part concentrated fear toxin.
It's already sunk its teeth
into the city,
becoming the most sought-after high
on the street.
Users are calling it
the ultimate escapism,
but doctors warn that snakebite
is as lethal as it is addictive.
Talk to me, Gotham.
Am I the only one
who's feeling rattled?
Are you...
Are you real?
You're throwing your life away.
That crap will kill you.
Certainly get you close.
That's the point.
Fear, fantasy,
whatever makes your blood pump.
Who sold you this stuff?
Sorry. Can't give a plug.
I will ask you this
just one more time.
Who is your dealer?
Target acquired.
You're not actually gonna run him
over, right?
And ruin my new paint job?
What the...?
You're not Batwoman!
What was that?
I don't know.
Steering got a little stiff.
You get off on ruining lives?
I don't tell my clients
what to do.
Well, I'm gonna tell
you what to do.
Stop destroying lives.
who's your boss?
You tell him I will find
the head of the snake,
and I will cut it off.
I couldn't get the bat-light,
so I yanked the door.
You set this off?
My brother left for school,
and he never showed up.
He's been gone for three months,
and nobody cares.
Do you care, Batwoman?
I have received intelligence
suggesting that my daughter
Kate Kane is alive.
I believe that she survived the crash
or perhaps wasn't even
on the aircraft to begin with.
I also believe that my daughter
is collateral damage
between two warring parties
and I am personally offering
a million-dollar cash reward
to anyone who can provide
information into who took her
or how that happened.
What do you tell critics who think
this is a futile attempt to rectify
your failed search for Beth Kane?
Well, I... I tell them
that I am a father
who needs your help
to find his daughter
and this search will not fail.
Thank you.
With the largest cash reward
in Gotham history
crows commander Jacob Kane
has galvanized the city
to help find his daughter Kate Kane,
now publicly declared missing.
Are you seeing this?
All this press combined
with a one million dollar reward?
We're gonna find Kate.
- What?
- Nothing.
Sophie just told us
that Kate is alive on an island
in the Mediterranean.
Yeah, and the person who told Sophie
that Kate's alive is named Alice
and Alice heard it
from some mystery woman
named Safiyah
who just hired a hitman
to try and kill me
so we are playing a game of telephone
with a bunch of homicidal women.
Or Alice is telling the truth,
and Kate needs us to find her.
Or she's not, and we're getting
our hopes up for nothing.
See, Alice can't get my hopes up
because I never lost hope
to begin with.
Where are you going?
To work with someone
who wants to find Kate
as badly as I do.
Local firemen rushed
to the scene of a...
Hey. Team meeting. Where's Luke?
Burrowing down a rabbit hole.
Well, clearly, you're free today.
We've got ourselves a bat mission.
Black, male, foster kid, juvie.
In case you're wondering
why GCPD isn't looking for him,
those five words.
They probably just wrote him off
as a runaway.
How long has he been missing?
Couple of months.
Oh, wait. I once lived
in the neighborhood he's from
Wayside heights, aka wasteside.
Is that where you lived with Corah?
No. Wasteside was years
before Mama found me.
This was one of the group homes,
but there was nothing homey about it.
Check it. New girl.
Hi. I'm Ryan. I'm 12.
My favorite animal's
the snow leopard.
My favorite color's yellow.
My last foster parents
said I watch too much tv.
Did your last foster mama
tell you that you
talk too damn much?
Yo. Open up.
I know you hear me.
Thanks.
Gonna get your ass busted.
Gonna be boring your whole life.
Am I on your bed or something?
No. I'm just nosy.
"Ghost kid"? he ain't a superhero.
Says who?
All he can do is be invisible.
Maybe people
who feel invisible think he's dope.
Who? Like you?
For the record, I see you.
New rule.
You keep opening that window for me,
and I've got your back
when you need someone.
So, do you remember the area?
Ryan?
The police report says he disappeared
between home and school.
Well, worth checking out his route.
Field trip? I'll drive.
The Batmobile?
I actually love vintage vans.
Well, uh, my carburetor chokes,
fuel leaks,
and I don't have any air bags,
but, yeah,
if you want to take a selfie
in my living room for Insta,
be my guest.
Wait. You, like, live here live here.
Like, full-time?
Who else would keep my plant company?
Wait. Hold up.
What are we doing here?
Give me a sec.
Crap.
Garbage.
Yes.
What you doing, sweetie?
I'm not stealing. These are free.
Oh, don't worry. I'm not police.
Around here, I'm known
as the neighborhood Candy Lady.
Jelly bean?
No.
So, my son...
Just left for boarding school
and now, I got a minivan
full of comic books.
I was just about to donate them
but, maybe you might want
to pick through them first.
Depends. What's he all got?
Too many,
and by the looks of your stash
I'm guessing your mom
has the same problem I do?
I'm good. Thanks.
No worries, sweetie. Just an offer.
Well, I'll just get these inside.
Happy hunting.
Wait.
Maybe I'll take a peek.
Why are we here?
Because I think Kevin was grabbed
from here to be brainwashed
and sold to a gang.
And you got all that from a janky
comic book storefront?
I got all that
because the same damn thing
happened to me.
Oh. Let me guess.
You're not a morning person.
What the hell are you doing
in my condo?
Sampling the products
in your guest bath.
Of course, your theme is lavender.
Alice.
Fine. Allow me to remind you
what happened less than 48 hours ago
when I explained to you I made
a deal with Safiyah for Kate.
She gives me Kate, and in return,
you and I help her find someone.
I don't need to partner with you
to find Kate.
Well, now that I think about it,
you do have double locks
on all your doors,
no fashionable attire
I looked and not a single thing
past its expiration date
in your fridge.
Risk terrifies you,
and I'm a risk,
and it's quite obvious
that you're not willing
to risk anything for my sister,
so I'm sure you'll find Kate
the safe, regimented,
by-the-books way.
Seems to have gotten you pretty far.
Cute press conference by the way.
A million-dollar reward
is sure to get the woman
who owns an island
to spill the beans.
Stop.
What do we need to do?
You need to power up your computer
and use that "all-access" crows
pass of yours
to find a guy named Ocean,
and I...
Need some more milk for my tea...
Partner.
Whelan,
get art an antiquities started
on finding the original.
This is the mysterious
Jack Napier piece.
- Yeah.
- It's hideous.
Who's Safiyah?
the woman
who has my daughter apparently.
We can't locate her,
but since this was the last thing
on Kate's phone,
we think it will help.
It was stolen apparently
from an active crime scene
and is now rumored
to be bouncing around
the black market.
On it, sir.
The clerk remembered seeing
a minivan lurking around
the comic book store.
That means it's possible
she's still stalking that place
all these years later.
You're telling me
a woman's been lurking
in the shadows,
plucking kids off the street
- for the last decade and a half?
- that's the point.
She doesn't need shadows.
She's a blue-eyed
suburban housewife
who targets kids no one cares about.
She figures out who has
a family, who doesn't,
and then she makes her move.
She sprayed something in my face.
I was so disoriented
by the time I woke up,
i couldn't figure out
where the hell I was.
Does Wayne have cameras
in wayside?
I don't know.
What'd this monster
do to you, Ryan?
What did she do?
She preyed
on every foster kid's greatest fear,
that we don't matter
because we're invisible.
Let me go.
You can't keep me here.
Well, when someone comes
to claim you, you can leave,
but until then,
I'm just a good Samaritan
who found a lost child
wandering the streets.
There's nothing good about you.
That's not true.
Look.
There are 60 jelly beans in this jar,
and every day that you're here,
i'll remove one,
and by the time
there are no more jelly beans left,
you'll realize I am the only one
who's here for you.
Me the sweet
neighborhood Candy Lady.
Why are you doing this?
I'm gonna help you find
your new family,
one who appreciates you,
one who sees you
for your true potential.
Someone will come for me
and kick your ass.
You're not gonna break me.
Do you really believe that?
Think about it.
In all those comic books
that you love so much,
have you ever read
about one of those heroes
saving a kid like you?
The sad truth is she was right.
Heroes didn't save kids like me.
I'm so sorry.
Honestly, so much crap
has happened since,
I hadn't thought
about it much till now,
but the thing I remember is
by the time Kevin
gets to the bottom of this candy jar,
the Candy Lady will have him believe
he has no other choice.
Don't stop on my behalf.
It's normal to want to leave.
Strange place, strange people.
But soon it won't seem so strange.
I'm here for my jelly bean.
Someone will notice I'm missing.
Wouldn't that be
a nice change of pace?
That's when our little game started.
She had 60 days to break me,
and I had 60 days to prove her wrong.
Good morning, sweetie.
Still no inquiries.
Batman stopped the Joker last night.
It's all over the news.
Unfortunately...
You're not.
What are you doing?
Don't you make a sound.
Good morning, ma'am.
We're wondering if you can help us
with a missing persons case.
We're volunteers from Gotham-U
looking for this girl last seen
a couple weeks ago.
Got a lot of people worried.
I never saw her nervous,
never saw her sweat
but when I heard those voices
outside the window
I knew why.
I'm here.
I saw that search party outside,
and I thought I'd done it
thought I'd won.
I thought I had proved to that bitch
that I was worth something
to someone.
Help me. I'm here!
That is so upsetting.
What does the little girl look like?
She's 13, fair skin, blue eyes.
Fair skin, blue eyes.
She was last seen wearing
a necklace with a red stone.
Oh, my gosh. That is just awful.
I will definitely keep
my eyes peeled.
But they weren't looking for me.
They were looking for some white girl
because when white girls go missing
people get off their asses,
and they do something about it.
Hang on.
A search team was looking
for a 13-year-old white girl
wearing a red stone necklace?
I know how to find the Candy Lady.
How?
That girl was Beth Kane.
You mind?
I really thought
you'd be better at this.
We're looking for a man named Ocean.
I'm happy to tell you
everything you want to know
about the seven seas,
but there's only so far I can get
without a last name.
Yeah. Coryana doesn't
really do last names.
Safiyah, Ocean, Tatiana.
It's all very biblical.
Then we need another angle.
In hindsight, I don't know why
I thought you could help me
figure out who this person is
considering you didn't even know
you were swapping spit
with your former flame.
I think it's time for you to go.
And I think you're haunted.
Kate disappeared with so much
left unsaid
between you two,
and it's killing you
which is precisely why I want
to work with you.
Because you'll stop
at nothing to find her.
Is that what you are? haunted?
What do you want me to say, Soph,
that I miss my sister
more than anything
that I regret spending the last year
terrorizing her
now that she's gone I realize
how much she meant to me?
If it's the truth.
Yo, Sophie. It's Luke Fox.
I can't be seen working with you.
I totally understand.
Alice, don't.
- What the hell?
- I didn't order takeout,
but I'll take you out anyway.
Kate was obsessed with finding Beth.
She collected every piece
of documentation
having to do with the search,
including logs of who searched where.
Now, we just have to find them.
Oh. I do not think
I was supposed to see this.
Oh, my god. thank you.
This is mine.
Please don't tell me
Kate was borrowing those.
No.
I've just kind of started moving in.
Wait. You went from the 56th floor
of a riverside penthouse to a loft
- above a loud gay bar?
- A gay bar that I now run.
Figured it would save me
the commute.
Bingo.
I get it.
You move into her place,
you take over her bar.
If I lost my sister,
I'd want to hang on
to every piece of her, too.
You know, speaking
of shorter commutes to work
you should totally live here.
- With you?
- I'm serious.
I mean, it's already paid for.
There's an extra bedroom.
The bathroom is huge, and no offense
your plant was looking
kind of sad in your van.
This has corner sunlight,
and there's a cute...
You don't have to sell my ass
on moving out of my van.
Yes, I'd love to live here.
- Okay.
- Good.
Kate collected all of this as a kid?
Yeah.
The GCPD stopped looking for Beth.
Search parties
stopped looking for Beth.
Eventually, even our dad
stopped looking for her
but Kate never did.
She reminds me of someone.
My ex.
She never stopped looking
for me either.
No. She got you, too?
That's what she thinks.
Told you I got your back.
She allowed herself to get caught
to help break me out.
It was the first time
I remember ever feeling like
I actually mattered to someone.
Well, if Angelique was there,
then maybe she remembers
where the house is.
- You got to call her.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I can't. Things took a turn.
We don't even speak anymore.
Listen.
As a person with season tickets
to crazy lesbian drama,
I can appreciate that,
but on behalf of Kevin Johnson,
you got to make an exception.
See?
Took a turn.
Must have changed her number.
Wait, wait. Maybe this will help.
Point rock,
Gotham hope search group,
Gotham U's youth volunteers.
According to this,
on Saturday, October 1,
they went door to door.
This is a map of their route.
This must be
where the Candy Lady lives.
- Yeah.
- I'm coming for you, Kevin.
Wait. Aren't you gonna suit up?
No. She needs to see my face.
Well, how can I help?
You can clear out my bedroom,
which you're currently using
as your walk-in closet.
I need to do this alone.
Go get Kevin back roomie.
Alice, put the gun down.
Sorry, soph, but threesomes
aren't my thing,
especially when one-third
worked with Kate
to lock me in at Arkham.
- He can help us.
- Us?
Are you not being held hostage
right now?
What the hell is happening?
Oh. Soph and I
have been tasked by Safiyah
to find a man, and once we do
and I kill him,
we get Kate back.
Wait. What?
You never said anything
about killing him.
Didn't I?
Well, this one comes
with special instructions.
Abracadabra. I kill him with this.
Don't even think about it.
There's been a hundred tips
since the announcement,
but the one on wayside
sounds half legit.
I'll swing by, check it out,
let you know what I find.
Never touch my gun again.
So should I stay, or...
We can use your help.
Can I help you, sweetie?
I'm here to claim Kevin Johnson.
Who?
Fifteen, male, African-American,
last seen with you.
- And who might you be?
- Someone who cares.
I have seen him,
and he's found a family
who loves him.
Get her inside.
How exactly am I
supposed to find a guy
with no last name on a laptop?
Do you have anything
with actual calories in here?
There's rat poison under the sink.
Look. I appreciate that the crows
Can get past most encryption fields,
but that doesn't do us
any favors here.
This island must have
the most advanced tech in the world
because it's not showing
up on any satellites.
You can see for yourself.
It's a dead end.
Wait. What is...
Any chance there's something
at Wayne with more firepower?
One hundred percent.
Let me do a deep dive,
and I'll see what I can find.
Behold the only carbs
in this hellhole.
Baguette?
I'm good.
Then I guess we wait.
Tell me you recorded
90-Day Fiancée.
I'm gonna find your dad
and see if his lead
amounted to anything.
If you want to avoid being arrested,
I'd stay put.
Can you pick me up
a six-pack when you're out?
I can't believe
you let yourself get caught.
I heard about this lady creeping
around galaxy hero comics,
so I went there and made sure
she saw me.
Why didn't anyone come for me?
Everyone thought you ran away,
but I knew you'd never leave
your "ghost kid" collection behind.
No!
This is exactly why nobody wants you.
Come on, Ryan.
We got to go before she wakes.
Ryan! Ryan, you got to fight this.
Ryan, fight!
Fight like ghost kid would fight.
Remember when he lost
his lame-ass invisibility
and everyone kept throwing crap
at him but he kept fighting anyway?
Ryan, get up!
You read "ghost kid"?
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Come on.
Oh. Right there.
You don't remember me,
huh, bitch?
I'm the girl you couldn't break.
Where is Kevin?
Kevin ran out of jelly beans.
Who did you sell him to?
No one ever really knew his face,
and now
that it's hidden behind a mask...
No one ever will.
You Rudy?
Kane, right?
What do you know?
Like I said on the phone,
before the plane took off,
I was working the tarmac
as a marshal,
you know, the guy
with the orange batons...
Yeah. I know what, what that is.
So, right before the plane takes off,
I notice a suspicious SUV
pull up to the aircraft,
and I'm thinking to myself,
"what the hell's going on?"
Because only catering
and emergency vehicles
are allowed that far out.
Damn, Kevin.
You smooth.
Now, let's go
and earn you your mask.
I'm here.
What makes you think Ocean is?
Because while you
and Alice were bickering
over what temp
to keep your thermostat
I was texting the only person
we know who knows Safiyah.
Julia?
Yeah.
Turns out Julia
had heard Ocean left the island
a few years back
so she went looking
for him herself
hoping to get more intel on Safiyah.
So, where's he?
Well, she was waylaid,
but she did narrow down
his hideout
to four possible locations.
It looks like two were demolished
one is now an ice cream parlor,
and...
I'm sitting in front of the fourth.
Be careful.
Copy that.
You break it, you bought it.
Do I know you?
If you did, you would
have seen that coming.
Let her go.
- Where's Ocean?
- Who?
Look. I just came here
looking to bag the place
and clearly, it's not worth it,
so you two can have it.
Just when I thought we were bonding.
Did you really think I'd trust you?
I want to find Kate just like you.
The question is why?
To make things right, to apologize,
to promise you'll change your ways?
i think we both know the answer
to that question.
I'm gonna find my sister,
and I'm gonna kill her.
Yo, Kevin.
Candy Lady says you're ripe.
Prove it.
Kill a crow.
But he didn't do nothing.
He's not on trial. You are.
You want to be in the family, right?
Prove it.
You don't have to do this.
You know, I do have a legit
tip for you, commander.
Don't come down
to False Face Society's hood solo.
He didn't.
And that's for making me
sweat out my edges.
Kevin, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
I want a family, and they want me.
Kid, put the gun down.
Kevin, listen to me.
You do this and you throw
your entire life away.
You don't know
anything about me.
Kevin, hey. Wait.
I do, though.
I know you have a brother.
I know that you think
no one cares about you
and I know
that if you pull that trigger
you'll become exactly what
the Candy Lady says you are...
invisible.
How do you know so much about me?
because I set out to find you
because you matter.
I see you
and you are meant
for so much more than this.
Protect him.
This is a False Face Society
hot spot.
There's bound to be more creeping.
How'd you know he was here?
Easy.
I looked.
Candice Long, aka the Candy Lady
was captured tonight
after Batwoman uncovered
a 20-year conspiracy involving
the False Face Society
and child trafficking.
This street-to-gang pipeline
includes Kevin Johnson
who credits both Batwoman and
crows commander Jacob Kane
for his rescue earlier tonight,
which begs the obvious question...
is there a bat-crow partnership
on the horizon?
At least one of us
did something right today.
Half right.
You know,
I never thought I'd say this,
but if Batwoman hadn't been there,
I probably wouldn't be here.
What happened?
Alice happened, sir.
She wants to find Kate
and it's imperative
that we find her first.
I'm totally stealing
this jacket, FYI.
So, you're already
raiding my closet.
She never stopped looking,
even when all the evidence said
that she was crazy.
You know, I can live in her place
and take over her bar
and hold on to all
the little pieces of her
but none of it will bring me closure
if I don't actually look.
I don't want to believe Alice,
but I, I don't want to believe
that Kate's dead either.
Then maybe it's time
we start thinking a little crazy.
Yeah.
Hey. I got to go.
- Everything ok?
- Yeah. I'll let you know.
Look who might have found
the key to the Ocean.
Hi.
What the hell was that?
Wrong number? seriously?
You didn't take my calls
for two years.
I had to play hard to get
for a minute.
Why am I here, Ryan?
Batwoman caught the Candy Lady.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
Damn.
Next question.
Why couldn't you just tell me
that over text?
because maybe I miss the girl
who always had my back.
Truce?