It's all there.
Tell me where I can find
the Jack Napier painting.
Your painting is being held
by the collective...
private club of connoisseurs
of outlawed artwork
and antiquities.
You want to tie the room together
with a vintage canvas that takes you
inside the mind
of psychotic criminality?
These are the people
you need to know.
I want an introduction.
The top crow?
Your biggest clients
are in the collective.
They pay your bills.
You walk up to their doorstep
trying to grab that Napier?
They're gonna ask you for a refund.
You're from Coryana.
You're gonna tell Safiyah
to give my daughter back.
I got a report of a guy
lurking around east end
with a spiky pole.
It doesn't concern you, Batwoman.
That so?
Because he's hanging off my line.
So, why don't you tell me
what kind of fish I caught?
There's an item I'm looking for.
It's gonna help me find my daughter.
The woman holding her captive
doesn't want me to find it.
Safiyah? She sent this guy?
Weapon fits the M.O.
of her assassins.
But I'll confirm
after you hand him over now.
I don't take orders from Crows...
and I got a better shot
at finding Kate Kane before you do.
"All Crows are bastards."
Morning, Gotham.
Guess the early bird
gives us the bird.
Acrobatic Art Prankster Wolf Spider
was at it again,
rolling his eyes at the entire city
from the top
of the Gotham century skyscraper
with an iridescent emoji.
Millennial hacktivism at its finest
and almost enough to distract us
from an even juicier bat story.
Another sighting of Batwoman 2.0
and top crow Jacob Kane together.
This time, working in
the east-end crime scene.
Are we looking at Gotham's
newest power couple
No. Jeez.
I thought Batwoman was cool.
Hey. We don't know
what they were doing.
Maybe Batwoman was saving his ass.
Thought you might be hungry
after last night's reconnecting.
Still sleepy.
I wish you could do something
about that.
You can take the day off.
I can't.
As cute as I look
in your ridiculous robe...
I should get home and change first.
You "walk of shaming" for me?
Like the old days.
Speaking of the old days...
it's time you got
that apology I owe you.
My partying was out of control
and you took my stash
thinking it would help me.
And instead,
it got your ass thrown in jail.
And I get why you don't
want me to visit you.
You served 18 months for me, Ryan...
and it's time
I start paying you back.
One for you, one for me?
I love it...
but we're good.
You got your life together.
That's all I wanted.
Hey. What is this?
- It's a work injury.
- You fall on a corkscrew?
Ryan, you need to get
that looked at.
Yeah. I just got this job.
I don't need my boss
thinking I can't hack it.
You tend bar. She'll understand.
All these years later,
still worrying about me.
It's kind of cute.
You know, what's kind of cute?
You...
Without that nastiness
on your shoulder.
You take care of everyone else.
Take care of yourself for once.
- Giving you an antibiotic.
- So, it's just an infection?
Well, it might have turned necrotic
if you had waited any longer.
Are you sure you're not
having any other symptoms
that you're not telling me about?
No. I...
maybe a little more tired
than normal.
- Okay.
Kate would pop two of these
and she'd be back in fighting shape.
- Okay. Cool.
- But if you're hurt...
you should sit out a few days.
Right. Did Kate ever sit out?
Kate was never shot with anything
that pierced through the batsuit...
and, you shouldn't
compare yourself to her.
What's my choice?
Everybody else is.
I know you don't have a Twitter,
so I assume you mean Luke.
Just don't tell him about this, okay?
I don't need another reason
for him not to trust me.
He's been questioning
every decision I make.
Not to backseat drive,
but aren't you
proficient in six different
forms of martial arts?
What's the point of
just leaving him here?
I told him we wanted
the location of Coryana.
He'll give it up.
Take it from a foster kid.
It is amazing how well you behave
when you are literally starving.
We don't have time to wait him out.
If Alice finds Ocean
before we find Coryana,
Safiyah's gonna give Kate to her,
and Alice is going to kill her.
Okay.
So, do your hacker thing
and get some info
on the spiky pole guy
to speed this up.
I already tried.
I tracked his movements
and confirmed
that he wasn't after Jacob Kane.
He was stalking the guy
that he killed in the alley.
But, the victim
was an investment analyst
at Gotham capital with no record.
What's he got to do with Coryana?
Sir, I'm not defending her actions
but my guess
is, she's after what we're after...
Kate's location.
Let her keep Safiyah's thug.
We got a new lead on the Napier...
Evan Blake, old friend of Kate's
and a fixture
on the Gotham art scene.
Just flew back from a trip to Berlin.
He was caught a couple of years ago
with plundered artifact
and forced to pay restitution.
In other words,
a likely member of the collective
who might cooperate.
Commander, you're underselling
our entire origin story.
Katie Kane saved my life.
- Really?
- Gotham prep.
It's eighth grade,
and the winter formal
is a multiverse shattering crisis
because I'm "straight".
Kate was way out by then,
I had this tragic crush...
and I asked her to the dance.
I'm sure she wanted
to roll her eyes so hard...
but with the grace of a saint...
she said yes.
The only time
you'll ever hear teenage Kate
described as a saint.
My parents take me to pick her up
and Kate is jaw-dropping
in this tailored velvet suit,
just radiating queer confidence.
I, on the other hand dissolve
into a monsoon of tears.
Kate races me up
to her bedroom,
and we go through
the whole thing.
"I'm gay." "I know."
We make it to the dance,
and I came out by default
because I wore
Kate's alexander McQueen
off-the-shoulder mini...
which begged a lot of questions.
But I wasn't afraid anymore.
I was glowing...
and then Kate ditched me
to make out with Maggie Watson.
Sounds like our girl.
So you need my help
with Kate's disappearance.
I'm here for you.
Kate was looking
for a piece of artwork...
something that may have gotten her
on the wrong side of
someone very dangerous.
Our theory is if we find the item
it will lead us to her captor.
Well, you've come
to the right art snob.
I was senior editor
at the Gotham Museum of Antiquities.
I curate my own private collections.
I've got my hands
in a bit of everything.
Yeah. We know. Agent Moore.
Kate was looking for a canvas
painted by Jack Napier
alias the Joker.
You're aware of it, yes?
I know the legend.
Psychotic evildoer breaks into home.
Splashes homeowner's guts
all over some old painting
in the foyer and calls it modern art.
It's a bit on the nose if you ask me.
Not to mention illegal to buy, sell,
or possess
since it was stolen
from an active crime scene.
I'm sorry.
Should there be a harsh light
shining in my eyes right now?
Because the Kate I knew
never gave a crap about art...
and I haven't spoken
with her in years.
We have reason to believe
that you're affiliated
with the collective.
We'll work to get you full immunity
if you help us make contact.
Immunity from what, Ms. Moore?
I'm a perfect angel.
I thought you were here friend.
I love Katie,
but this feels like entrapment.
If you need to contact me again,
I'll refer you to my lawyers.
I want all our tech inside
every device Evan owns,
round-the-clock revolving tails.
Yes, sir, but there could be
an easier way to locate Coryana
with Batwoman's help.
Let me ask her
for access to her prisoner.
Batwoman or whoever it is
who stepped in for my daughter,
I am not gonna grovel at her feet.
Then let me do it,
or at least ask nicely
because Alice will do
a lot worse than grovel
to find Kate before we do.
Ocean.
Hi.
What do you call it when you're sure
you've met someone...
You're sure you've never met?
A stay of execution.
Vodka on the rocks.
Visiting from Gotham?
Why?
Do I look depressed?
You've got the sophistication
of a city mouse.
Mouse.
Touchy subject.
Don't you think mice are cute?
I had a mouse in my life.
I loved him like a brother...
and when he started
holding me back
from my dreams, I killed him.
Shoot.
I think it's my turn to...
That is the fastest
I've ever seen him take the hint.
Can I join you...
in case he decides to try it again?
Pretty sure he's in the next county
by now
but, by all means.
Last time I came here
to meet a Batwoman.
The vibes...
were different.
Please say this isn't a booty call.
Look. I don't know
where you got this idea
that all Crows are bastards
but some of us are trying
to make a difference.
Well, in my experience,
when the Crows fly together,
they call it a murder for a reason.
I want to offer you a deal.
You get everything we know
about Safiyah and Coryana,
and we get access to your prisoner.
So you can beat him
within an inch of his life?
He's a murderer who knows
where Kate's being held.
I'll think about it.
You should be doing everything
in your power to help Kate.
I don't need a crow
telling me how to do my job.
I'm not speaking to you as a crow.
Kate's the love of my life...
and I need your help to get her back.
Hell to the no. No.
Working with the Crows
makes my skin crawl.
- Screw that. No.
- It's not like we're hosting them
a fundraiser.
Trust me.
We make a deal that sounds good,
they'll break it.
Not if we're dealing with Sophie.
Sophie has hauled my ass
in for questioning
so many times, she knows
my damn coffee order. No.
Will you talk some sense into her,
please?
We're at a dead end, Ryan.
Look. I'm sorry...
but you're outvoted.
I get it. You want Kate back.
But the Crows have tried
to ruin my life for fun.
I'm not helping them.
Okay.
So.
Crows horror stories.
You want me to go, or...
Do you want to do yours first?
My girl Angelique had a drug habit.
And on a very ugly night...
she was gone,
like a different person.
So I found her stash,
and I took it thinking
I could somehow straighten her out...
bring her back.
I'm on the street, crying...
no question what kind
of night I'm having
and I pass these two Crows,
and one of them yells out,
"you'd be cuter
with a smile on your face."
And my mama told me
what to do about it.
I pay them no mind and keep moving.
But they, they wouldn't let me go.
So my hand went out,
my finger went up, and boom,
those Crows had what they wanted.
They found the drugs
and thought they were yours.
Sorry that happened to you.
What was yours?
The Crows...
killed my father.
Wait. What?
Really?
Really.
It's not a story for today, but...
It's the worst thing
that ever happened to me.
I should have let you go first.
Look. I will never forgive them...
and I don't want
to help the Crows either...
but we need them to help us.
Remember, this isn't punishment
just for the sake of it.
Given this murderer
every opportunity to talk.
So, unless you have any other ideas,
it's time to take this
to the next level.
You've got some choices.
You can give us the location
of Coryana...
You can get us in touch with Safiyah
or the man known as Ocean.
Help us find the Napier painting.
Listen to me. It is not worth
what they're gonna do to you.
The many arms will kill whoever
lays hands on that painting.
You'll never find Coryana.
I never said the two were related.
The painting gets us to Coryana?
Is it a map?
Cyanide capsule.
- Let's get him down.
- It's too late. It's too late.
Kane pushed him too hard,
and now we're at a dead end.
Maybe not.
We've been surveilling
a suspect we linked to the Napier
and we just got a hit
on its location.
A group called the Collective
is having
a special exhibition tomorrow night
to auction the painting off.
Why now?
Word must have gotten
back to the owner
about the body that dropped
the other night.
Too much heat.
You doing anything tomorrow night?
You looking for a date to this thing?
We don't have an insider.
But we need someone
with no connection to the Crows
who can infiltrate the event
and grab the Napier
without getting caught.
I go alone.
No Crows at the location,
no surveillance.
and I want you directly in charge
of any Crows assigned
to this mission.
This is a one-off.
We're not partners.
So, Ocean...
What do you do?
I bore people to death
by telling them
I'm a soil technician.
That sounds like a fancy name
for dirt nerd.
but you smiled when you said it,
so...
you must like your work.
I grew up in nature.
My family cultivated
everything we ever needed
from the land.
In a place like Gotham,
where everything is concrete...
isn't that incredible?
So tell me...
where is this magical
place you hail from?
I'm meeting an associate.
Should splash some water on my face.
Five shots...
No, regrets.
Hey. Can I ask you something?
Have we met somewhere before?
Think I'd remember you.
Probably just thinking
about somebody else.
Oh, well.
Do you mind...
Shutting the shade?
You slept through half the day.
Five shots, no regrets.
Shall I explain?
I do wish you would.
Some lunatic on a far-away island
is holding my sister hostage
and she won't hand her over
until I got you
and air mail the evidence.
This woman got a name?
Enough women want you dead.
I need to be specific?
Just answer the damn question.
Safiyah.
Although her obedient
island followers call her queen.
Not me.
I called her sister.
I have three words.
Who is she?
Look.
Wait. Are you sure art collectors
are supposed to have this much swag?
Well, first of all,
they're not art collectors.
They're outlaws.
And if Evan Blake
is the style guide...
this party's about to look
like The Hunger Games.
What's Evan Blake's deal?
He and I were always angling
for Kate's affection.
No.
He was way more competitive
and had...
A lot more flair than me.
Now, he's overeducated,
and apparently...
he's addicted to mischief.
The Crows say that he runs
the door for the Collective.
No.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, I think I can make this work.
I'd say so.
H... Hey. I, I brought the plan...
I... I brought the game plan.
The event is inside a private hangar
at Gotham international.
It's actually a pretty clever way
of doing this.
So, the Collective flies in,
they unload their pieces...
they buy, sell, party...
then they load back up, fly away.
No, customs, no TSA,
maximum security.
How are we sneaking the batsuit
through that security?
See, we just happen
to have VIP access
to every square inch
of that terminal.
Yeah. Between Wayne enterprises
and Hamilton dynamics...
we burn more private jet fuel
than the Hadids, Kardashians
- and the Air Force combined.
- Yeah.
So with our resources,
Crows's intelligence,
and a secret agent
that no one's going
to suspect, Ryan Wilder.
Wait. I'm just supposed
to talk my way inside?
Oh, no.
Did you think Mary
had all the accessories?
Look at this precision metalwork.
The weight is perfectly balanced.
What's the provenance?
- Which bat did it belong to?
- Woman.
- 1.0 or...
- Current model.
The Batarang is a stunning piece.
We'll make an exception
and allow it into the exhibition.
Okay. I'm really loving that dress.
- Didn't it debut in London?
- Nailed it.
Actually, it was New York,
winter '18.
Well, I heard there was a dress code
so I borrowed it from a friend.
Heard from who, exactly?
Of course, I'm a big believer
in the first amendment
except when it comes
to the shenanigans that go on
behind the Collective's closed doors.
Evan baby...
what are you doing to my girl here?
You beat me here.
Ang, big night.
Patrons need their party favors.
And this one's yours?
Yeah.
I totally spaced on the heads up.
It's fine. You're forgiven.
Any questions?
Pronouns?
He, him, they, them.
I go with the flow.
Now, you two, go forth and do crimes.
- Ang, what are you doing here?
- Saving your ass at the door.
You can't just slide into the DM.
You need a referral.
What party favors
was he talking about?
Ang, no.
What do you want me to say?
That you weren't
lying through your teeth
when you told me
you'd pulled your life together.
For your information,
I'm clean.
Four months, but do you know
what people need
to pull their lives together?
Money.
If you get caught,
distribution is eight-10
at Blackgate.
Says the girl turning
Batwoman's missing hardware
into an Etsy shop.
We know what I'm doing here.
What are you doing here?
Save it.
You are the only one here
who's judging.
- Is this thing on?
- Loud and clear.
Want to try channel two?
No, not really.
- Batwoman to Moore.
- Copy. You're late.
Thought maybe you got cold feet.
Believe it or not, I ran into an ex.
Okay.
Well, I hope he's not gonna be drama.
She, and always.
Let you know
when I find the painting.
Stand by.
Luke, got the target.
Okay. Great.
Give me a good look.
Okay.
Moving on to the next phase.
A lot of interest in this one.
Yeah.
It's kind of gimmicky, isn't it?
Oh, it's dreadful, zero technique.
But, you know, celebrity artists.
Help me to understand the appeal
in owning something like this.
Some of the people here?
Total sickos.
And you?
I don't like being told
what I can and can't do in life.
Whether it's the art I collect
or the clothes I wear...
I'm not desperate
for anyone's approval.
Still throwing shade
at my borrowed couture.
What can I say?
I just prefer
to see everyone's true colors.
So I ran a spectral analysis
to isolate the original canvas
underneath the Gore.
I think it's a painting
of Ocean currents. You were right.
The Joker splattered some poor guy
all over a map to Coryana?
But we'll need to restore the canvas
to locate the island.
- But that means...
- You're gonna need to steal it.
I didn't know Safiyah had family.
We weren't blood.
Apparently, we weren't anything.
- Why does she want me dead?
- Oh, no offense,
but I have way too much drama
in my life to care.
She's obviously losing her touch
if she sent you.
I'm sorry.
Did you just call me a bad assassin?
Not to Monday morning quarterback...
but you had ample opportunity
to kill me.
You knew I was staying here
which means
you could have killed me in my sleep.
But, maybe you don't know
how to pick a lock.
Fine. Surprise attack
in the bar bathroom.
Easy, private.
At the very least,
you can ambush me in my truck.
I have a backseat,
and I don't lock my doors.
But instead, you,
what, make a scene at the bar...
get my attention...
indulge in small talk? Get drunk?
Safiyah must be desperate
if she sent you.
I needed more answers
before I could kill you.
I've never seen you
before in my life.
Nor I you, which is why
I needed to know more
before I made Ocean
bleed the red sea.
How do you even know
what Coryana looks like?
Because I was there five years ago.
That's impossible.
I was there five years ago.
How peculiar.
Well, I suppose you could kill me
and then spend the rest
of your life on the run...
seeing as none
of this changes the fact
the island queen
still wants you dead.
Or, we could give her a jingle.
I'm good with option "A".
Safiyah, we both know
this isn't about a stupid flower.
And what do you think it's about?
Me having the one thing you can't.
- What the hell was that?
- Exactly.
Option "B" it is.
There should be
a dispenser next to the sink with...
You know, products.
I see it.
A lot of firepower in that room,
so you're gonna have to move fast.
Batwoman, status check. You find it?
Target identified.
I just need to take it
for further analysis.
We'll monitor from here.
Batwoman?
I think we have competition.
- Who?
- You ever heard of Wolf Spider?
Shoot him
before he gets too high.
- Miss, Miss, this way, please.
- No. Ryan!
Hand it over.
Damn.
Painting's on the move.
Do you need medical?
Just slow him down. I'll be there.
We're on it.
Nimble little bastard.
Little taser action
will slow him down.
- Damn it! Get me closer.
- I'm on it.
Fricking cartridge is jammed.
- Dude, what did you do?
- He jumped in front of me.
Get some ties on him.
This isn't good. Call for medical.
Status check.
Target acquired. We got the painting.
- Let's go.
- What? What are you doing?
We can't leave him here.
Moore wants the painting,
not an excessive force headline.
Let's go.
Someone else will clean him up.
Evan?
Evan!
Evan, can you hear me?
We're gonna need
a blood drive after this.
- He's gonna recover, right?
- Well, considering he was
hip-checked
by a 4,800-pound hunk
of toxic masculinity...
he's doing great.
Distal femur fracture,
dislocated elbow,
minor concussion...
but when the bone shattered,
it nicked his femoral artery.
So if you hadn't been there
to bring him in in time...
he would have bled out.
Okay. What...
what happened back there?
You want to know what happened?
I listened to you over my gut,
and now look.
I meant what happened to you?
You sounded
like you were in rough shape.
- You called for backup.
- This isn't about me.
This is about us...
this team
and how I can't keep working
for your approval.
I wanted to suit up and not think
about you comparing me
to Kate Kane for once.
So I agreed to partner
with the Crows.
And for what?
You sided with the guys
who killed your old man.
Your taste sucks.
But you know what?
I wear the suit, I take the bullets.
So when I say I have
a bad feeling about something...
you two listen.
Did Her Majesty say when she'd
grace us with a callback?
Would you just sit there
without talking?
I have spent more years of my life
in captivity than any elephant
in the Gotham zoo.
The key to surviving,
keep yourself entertained.
Rough childhood?
You could say I come
by my abandonment issues
honestly, yeah.
How do you know Safiyah?
I was squatting on a yacht
in Gotham harbor.
Safiyah's minions were pirating it
while I was on board
and apparently, she was impressed
by the fight I put up.
And she let you stay?
- Yeah.
- No way.
The island's cardinal rule
is no outsiders.
Why don't I remember
any of this?
That's the thing.
You should,
and I should remember you.
The fact that we both have
the same memories
makes me think
that Safiyah did something to...
Get us to forget.
You think Safiyah
erased our memory?
Some of them.
The thing is we might never know.
Tell me you ordered delivery
and those aren't
One, two, three
assassins approaching.
The Many Arms of Death.
More relatives of yours, I presume.
Yeah. Can you cut me loose?
I can't trust you.
You don't trust me to defend myself
from murder?
- Where's Ocean?
- Hey.
Surprise.
Hey. Do you have any cash?
We should probably leave
the maid a tip.
You're dark.
Shouldn't have doubted me.
Let's go. You're driving.
Badges of the Crows who did this.
That's not enough.
Burn it all down, girl.
The whole thing.
I can't do that.
I believe in the mission
of the Crows.
An organization
that decides what justice is
based on who can pay
the most money?
That beats information
out of its suspects?
That runs someone over
for stealing a painting?
That's what you believe in?
You think two men losing
their jobs isn't enough?
You're right.
But I'm fighting
to change the culture.
Yeah?
Well, good luck with that.
But if you want to party with me,
add your badge
to that little pile over there.
Until then,
this partnership is over.
What about the painting?
Our forensics team
is still working on it.
Don't you want to know
where Coryana is?
We'll see who gets there first.
Mary Hamilton.
Awkward.
Because I know you're Wolf Spider?
Because I'm pretty sure I'm naked.
Oh, very much so.
Evan, you need to find a better suit.
Spandex is no match
for an oncoming SUV.
But it's so comfortable.
Then, maybe find a safer excuse
to play dress-up.
Gotham's elite
take themselves too seriously.
Who else is gonna eye-roll them
with as much style as me?
The Crows got the painting.
I was stealing it for Kate.
Thought I had a better chance
at grabbing it
than the Crows.
Hey.
Don't beat yourself up about it
because it turns out nobody actually
got the Napier painting.
It was a forgery.
- That's impossible.
- No.
Batwoman took a sample
of the organic compound
that was painted over
the original canvas
and it was pig's blood.
Napier would've never
used pig's blood.
Right.
So the Crows ended up
with a decoy copy,
and the original
is still out there somewhere.
And so is Kate.
Oh, my God.
Once we get some distance
from the many arms,
we can try to figure out
what Safiyah did to us and why.
Looks like you're not as fast
as you think, buddy boy.
They got you pretty bad back there.
Hey. You all right?
Yeah. Eyes on the road.
What's with you?
Nothing.
Can you check in the back real quick?
Is there a white tube back there?
Yeah.
What is this?
You ever hear of a guy
called Jack Napier?