[WHETHAN AND GRANDSON'S
"ALL IN MY HEAD" PLAYING]
[GRANDSON:]
♪ All in my ♪
♪ Jump ♪
♪ I'm stuck with these voices... ♪
[VESPER:]
As if there were
a shortage of syringes
in Gotham's gutters,
a new party drug
just hit the streets
that apparently makes
an amphetamine high
feel like your Earl Grey
has steeped for too long..
It seems the gang known
as the False Face Society
is showing their entrepreneurial side
by making
and distributing Snakebite,
known for its dual-pronged
injector needles,
which are said to give
a double whammy dose
of fantasy and fright,
so more fang for your buck.
This trippy two-for-one is
part psychedelic mushroom oil,
part concentrated Fear Toxin.
It's already sunk its teeth
into the city,
becoming the most sought-after
high on the street.
Users are calling it
the ultimate escapism,
but doctors warn that Snakebite
is as lethal as it is addictive.
Talk to me, Gotham.
Am I the only one
who's feeling rattled?
[GRANDSON:]
♪ I'm stuck
with these voices ♪
♪ They're all in my head ♪
Are you...
Are you real?
You're throwing
your life away.
That crap will
kill you.
Certainly get
you close.
That's the point.
Fear, fantasy,
whatever makes your blood pump.
Who sold you this stuff?
Sorry. Can't give a plug.
Aah!
I will ask you this
just one more time.
Who is your dealer?
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL]
Target acquired.
[LUKE:]
You're not actually
gonna run him over, right?
And ruin my new paint job?
[HIGH-PITCHED SQUEAL]
What the?
[TOMMY:]
You're not Batwoman!
[BATMOBILE BEEPING]
[HORN HONKING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[LUKE:]
What was that?
[ RYAN:]
I don't know.
Steering got a little stiff.
Huh!
[GROANS]
You get off on
ruining lives?
I don't tell my clients
what to do..
Well,
I'm gonna tell you what to do.
Stop destroying lives!
Who's your boss?
[ALARM RINGING]
[GRUNTING]
YOU TELL HIM
I WILL FIND
THE HEAD OF THE SNAKE,
AND I WILL CUT
IT OFF.
I COULDN'T GET THE BAT-LIGHT,
SO I YANKED THE DOOR.
YOU SET THIS OFF?
MY BROTHER LEFT
FOR SCHOOL,
AND HE NEVER SHOWED UP.
HE'S BEEN GONE
FOR 3 MONTHS,
AND NOBODY CARES.
DO YOU CARE, BATWOMAN?
JACOB: I HAVE
RECEIVED INTELLIGENCE
SUGGESTING THAT MY DAUGHTER
KATE KANE IS ALIVE.
I BELIEVE THAT SHE SURVIVED
THE CRASH
OR PERHAPS WASN'T EVEN
ON THE AIRCRAFT TO BEGIN WITH.
I ALSO BELIEVE THAT MY DAUGHTER
IS COLLATERAL DAMAGE
BETWEEN TWO WARRING PARTIES,
AND I AM PERSONALLY OFFERING
A MILLION-DOLLAR CASH REWARD
TO ANYONE WHO CAN PROVIDE
INFORMATION INTO WHO TOOK HER
OR HOW THAT HAPPENED.
REPORTER: WHAT DO YOU
TELL CRITICS WHO THINK
THIS IS A FUTILE ATTEMPT
TO RECTIFY
YOUR FAILED SEARCH
FOR BETH KANE?
WELL, I--I TELL THEM THAT I AM
A FATHER WHO NEEDS YOUR HELP
TO FIND HIS DAUGHTER,
AND THIS SEARCH
WILL NOT FAIL.
THANK YOU.
[DEWITT:]
WITH THE LARGEST
CASH REWARD IN GOTHAM HISTORY,
CROWS COMMANDER JACOB KANE
HAS GALVANIZED THE CITY
TO HELP FIND HIS DAUGHTER
KATE KANE,
NOW PUBLICLY DECLARED MISSING.
ARE YOU SEEING THIS?
ALL THIS PRESS COMBINED
WITH A $1 MILLION REWARD?
WE'RE GONNA FIND KATE.
[SIGHS]
WHAT?
NOTHING.
SOPHIE JUST TOLD US
THAT KATE IS ALIVE
ON AN ISLAND
IN THE MEDITERRANEAN.
YEAH, AND THE PERSON
WHO TOLD SOPHIE
THAT KATE'S ALIVE
IS NAMED ALICE,
AND ALICE HEARD IT
FROM SOME MYSTERY WOMAN
NAMED SAFIYAH,
WHO JUST HIRED A HITMAN
TO TRY AND KILL ME,
SO WE ARE PLAYING
A GAME OF TELEPHONE
WITH A BUNCH
OF HOMICIDAL WOMEN.
OR ALICE IS TELLING
THE TRUTH,
AND KATE NEEDS US
TO FIND HER.
OR SHE'S NOT,
AND WE'RE GETTING
OUR HOPES UP
FOR NOTHING.
SEE, ALICE CAN'T GET
MY HOPES UP
BECAUSE I NEVER LOST HOPE
TO BEGIN WITH.
[SIGHS]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO WORK WITH SOMEONE
WHO WANTS TO FIND KATE
AS BADLY AS I DO.
[ANCHOR:]
LOCAL FIREMEN RUSHED
TO THE SCENE OF A...
[RYAN:]
HEY. TEAM MEETING.
WHERE'S LUKE?
BURROWING DOWN
A RABBIT HOLE.
WELL, CLEARLY,
YOU'RE FREE TODAY.
WE'VE GOT OURSELVES
A BATMISSION.
BLACK, MALE,
FOSTER KID, JUVIE.
IN CASE YOU'RE WONDERING
WHY GCPD ISN'T LOOKING FOR HIM,
THOSE 5 WORDS.
THEY PROBABLY JUST
WROTE HIM OFF AS A RUNAWAY.
HOW LONG HAS HE
BEEN MISSING?
COUPLE OF MONTHS.
OH, WAIT. I ONCE LIVED
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD
HE'S FROM--
WAYSIDE HEIGHTS,
AKA WASTESIDE.
IS THAT WHERE YOU
LIVED WITH CORA?
NO. WASTESIDE WAS YEARS
BEFORE MAMA FOUND ME.
THIS WAS ONE
OF THE GROUP HOMES,
BUT THERE WAS NOTHING
HOMEY ABOUT IT.
GIRL: CHECK IT. NEW GIRL.
HI. I'M RYAN.
I'M 12.
MY FAVORITE ANIMAL'S
THE SNOW LEOPARD.
MY FAVORITE COLOR'S
YELLOW.
MY LAST FOSTER PARENTS
SAID I WATCH TOO MUCH TV.
DID YOUR LAST FOSTER MAMA
TELL YOU THAT YOU
TALK TOO DAMN MUCH?
HA HA HA!
[RAP ON WINDOW]
GIRL, MUFFLED: YO. OPEN UP.
I KNOW YOU HEAR ME.
THANKS.
GONNA GET YOUR
ASS BUSTED.
GONNA BE BORING
YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
AM I ON YOUR BED
OR SOMETHING?
NO. I'M JUST NOSY.
"GHOST KID"?
HE AIN'T A SUPERHERO.
SAYS WHO?
ALL HE CAN DO IS BE INVISIBLE.
MAYBE PEOPLE WHO FEEL
INVISIBLE THINK HE'S DOPE.
WHO? LIKE YOU?
FOR THE RECORD,
I SEE YOU.
NEW RULE. YOU KEEP
OPENING THAT WINDOW
FOR ME,
AND I'VE GOT YOUR BACK
WHEN YOU NEED SOMEONE.
[MARY:] SO DO YOU
REMEMBER THE AREA?
RYAN?
THE POLICE REPORT
SAYS HE DISAPPEARED
BETWEEN HOME
AND SCHOOL.
WELL, WORTH CHECKING OUT
HIS ROUTE.
FIELD TRIP? I'LL DRIVE.
THE BATMOBILE?
EH.
I ACTUALLY LOVE
VINTAGE VANS.
WELL, UH, MY
CARBURETOR CHOKES,
FUEL LEAKS,
AND I DON'T HAVE
ANY AIR BAGS,
BUT, YEAH, IF YOU
WANT TO TAKE A SELFIE
IN MY LIVING ROOM
FOR INSTA,
BE MY GUEST.
WAIT. YOU, LIKE,
LIVE HERE LIVE HERE.
LIKE, FULL-TIME?
WHO ELSE WOULD KEEP
MY PLANT COMPANY?
WAIT. HOLD UP.
[GEARS GRINDING]
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
GIVE ME A SEC.
[YOUNG RYAN]
CRAP.
[SPINNER RACK SQUEAKING]
GARBAGE.
YES!
WHAT YOU DOING,
SWEETIE?
I'M NOT STEALING.
THESE ARE FREE.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT POLICE.
AROUND HERE, I'M KNOWN
AS THE NEIGHBORHOOD
CANDY LADY.
JELLY BEAN?
NAH.
HEH.
SO...MY SON...
JUST LEFT
FOR BOARDING SCHOOL--
HEH--AND NOW,
I GOT A MINIVAN
FULL OF COMIC BOOKS.
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO DONATE THEM,
BUT, UH, MAYBE YOU
MIGHT WANT TO PICK
THROUGH THEM FIRST.
DEPENDS.
WHAT'S HE ALL GOT?
TOO MANY,
AND BY THE LOOKS
OF YOUR STASH,
I'M GUESSING YOUR MOM
HAS THE SAME PROBLEM
I DO, HUH? HEH HEH.
I'M GOOD. THANKS.
NO WORRIES, SWEETIE.
JUST AN OFFER.
WELL, I'LL JUST
GET THESE INSIDE.
HAPPY HUNTING!
WAIT.
MAYBE I'LL TAKE A PEEK.
WHY...ARE WE HERE?
BECAUSE I THINK KEVIN
WAS GRABBED FROM HERE
TO BE BRAINWASHED
AND SOLD TO A GANG.
AND YOU GOT
ALL THAT
FROM A JANKY
COMIC BOOK STOREFRONT?
I GOT ALL THAT
BECAUSE THE SAME DAMN THING
HAPPENED TO ME.
[ALICE HUMMING]
OH. LET ME GUESS.
YOU'RE NOT
A MORNING PERSON.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING IN MY CONDO?
SAMPLING THE PRODUCTS
IN YOUR GUEST BATH.
OF COURSE YOUR THEME
IS LAVENDER.
ALICE!
FINE. ALLOW ME
TO REMIND YOU
WHAT HAPPENED LESS
THAN 48 HOURS AGO
WHEN I EXPLAINED
TO YOU I MADE A DEAL
WITH SAFIYAH FOR KATE.
SHE GIVES ME KATE,
AND IN RETURN,
YOU AND I HELP HER
FIND SOMEONE.
I DON'T NEED TO PARTNER
WITH YOU TO FIND KATE.
WELL, NOW THAT
I THINK ABOUT IT,
YOU DO HAVE DOUBLE LOCKS
ON ALL YOUR DOORS,
NO FASHIONABLE ATTIRE--
I LOOKED--
AND NOT A SINGLE THING
PAST ITS EXPIRATION DATE
IN YOUR FRIDGE.
RISK TERRIFIES YOU,
AND I'M A RISK,
AND IT'S QUITE OBVIOUS
THAT YOU'RE NOT WILLING
TO RISK ANYTHING FOR MY SISTER,
SO I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND KATE
THE SAFE, REGIMENTED,
BY-THE-BOOKS WAY.
SEEMS TO HAVE GOTTEN YOU
PRETTY FAR.
CUTE PRESS CONFERENCE
BY THE WAY.
A MILLION-DOLLAR REWARD
IS SURE TO GET THE WOMAN
WHO OWNS AN ISLAND
TO SPILL THE BEANS.
STOP.
WHAT DO WE NEED
TO DO?
YOU NEED TO POWER
UP YOUR COMPUTER
AND USE THAT "ALL-ACCESS"
CROWS PASS OF YOURS
TO FIND
A GUY NAMED OCEAN,
AND I...
NEED SOME MORE MILK
FOR TEA...
PARTNER.
WHELAN, GET ART
AN ANTIQUITIES STARTED
ON FINDING THE ORIGINAL.
THIS IS THE MYSTERIOUS
JACK NAPIER PIECE.
YEAH.
IT'S HIDEOUS.
WHO'S SAFIYAH?
THE WOMAN WHO HAS
MY DAUGHTER APPARENTLY.
WE CAN'T LOCATE HER,
BUT SINCE THIS WAS
THE LAST THING
ON KATE'S PHONE,
WE THINK IT WILL HELP.
IT WAS STOLEN APPARENTLY
FROM AN ACTIVE CRIME SCENE
AND IS NOW RUMORED
TO BE BOUNCING AROUND
THE BLACK MARKET.
ON IT, SIR.
[RYAN:]
THE CLERK
REMEMBERED SEEING
A MINIVAN LURKING
AROUND
THE COMIC BOOK STORE.
THAT MEANS IT'S
POSSIBLE SHE'S STILL
STALKING THAT PLACE
ALL THESE YEARS LATER.
YOU'RE TELLING ME A WOMAN'S
BEEN LURKING IN THE SHADOWS,
PLUCKING KIDS
OFF THE STREET
FOR THE LAST DECADE AND A HALF?
THAT'S THE POINT.
SHE DOESN'T NEED SHADOWS.
SHE'S A BLUE-EYED
SUBURBAN HOUSEWIFE
WHO TARGETS KIDS
NO ONE CARES ABOUT.
SHE FIGURES OUT WHO HAS
A FAMILY, WHO DOESN'T,
AND THEN SHE MAKES
HER MOVE.
SHE SPRAYED SOMETHING
IN MY FACE.
I WAS SO DISORIENTED
BY THE TIME I WOKE UP,
I COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
WHERE THE HELL I WAS.
DOES WAYNE HAVE CAMERAS
IN WAYSIDE?
[MARY:]
I DON'T KNOW.
[RYAN TYPING]
WHAT'D THIS MONSTER
DO TO YOU, RYAN?
WHAT DID SHE DO?
SHE PREYED ON
EVERY FOSTER KID'S
GREATEST FEAR,
THAT WE DON'T MATTER
BECAUSE WE'RE INVISIBLE.
[YOUNG RYAN:]
LET ME GO!
YOU CAN'T KEEP ME HERE.
WELL, WHEN SOMEONE
COMES TO CLAIM YOU,
YOU CAN LEAVE,
BUT UNTIL THEN,
I'M JUST A GOOD SAMARITAN
WHO FOUND A LOST CHILD
WANDERING THE STREETS.
THERE'S NOTHING GOOD
ABOUT YOU!
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
LOOK. THERE ARE
60 JELLY BEANS
IN THIS JAR,
AND EVERY DAY
THAT YOU'RE HERE,
I'LL REMOVE ONE,
AND BY THE TIME
THERE ARE NO MORE
JELLY BEANS LEFT,
YOU'LL REALIZE
I AM THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S HERE FOR YOU.
ME...THE SWEET
NEIGHBORHOOD CANDY LADY.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
I'M GONNA HELP YOU
FIND YOUR NEW FAMILY,
ONE WHO APPRECIATES YOU,
ONE WHO SEES YOU
FOR YOUR TRUE POTENTIAL.
SOMEONE WILL COME FOR ME
AND KICK YOUR ASS!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BREAK ME.
DO YOU REALLY
BELIEVE THAT?
THINK ABOUT IT.
IN ALL THOSE COMIC BOOKS
THAT YOU LOVE SO MUCH,
HAVE YOU EVER READ
ABOUT ONE OF THOSE HEROES
SAVING A KID LIKE YOU?
[RYAN:]
THE SAD TRUTH IS
SHE WAS RIGHT.
HEROES DIDN'T SAVE
KIDS LIKE ME.
I'M SO SORRY.
HONESTLY, SO MUCH CRAP
HAS HAPPENED SINCE,
I HADN'T THOUGHT
ABOUT IT MUCH TILL NOW,
BUT THE THING
I REMEMBER IS
BY THE TIME KEVIN GETS
TO THE BOTTOM
OF THIS CANDY JAR
THE CANDY LADY
WILL HAVE HIM BELIEVE
HE HAS NO OTHER CHOICE.
[DOOR OPENS]
DON'T STOP
ON MY BEHALF.
IT'S NORMAL TO WANT
TO LEAVE.
STRANGE PLACE,
STRANGE PEOPLE.
HA HA HA!
BUT SOON IT WON'T
SEEM SO STRANGE.
I'M HERE
FOR MY JELLY BEAN.
SOMEONE WILL NOTICE
I'M MISSING.
WOULDN'T THAT BE
A NICE CHANGE OF PACE?
[DOOR SHUTS]
THAT'S WHEN OUR
LITTLE GAME STARTED.
SHE HAD 60 DAYS
TO BREAK ME,
AND I HAD 60 DAYS
TO PROVE HER WRONG.
[DOOR OPENS]
GOOD MORNING,
SWEETIE.
[DOOR SHUTS]
[DOOR OPENS]
STILL NO INQUIRIES. TCK.
BATMAN STOPPED
THE JOKER LAST NIGHT.
IT'S ALL OVER
THE NEWS!
UNFORTUNATELY...
YOU'RE NOT.
[JELLY BEANS RATTLING]
[DOOR SHUTS, LOCKS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[LOCK TURNS]
[YOUNG RYAN:]
WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SHH! DON'T YOU
MAKE A SOUND.
[DOOR SHUTS, LOCKS]
GOOD MORNING, MA'AM.
WE'RE WONDERING
IF YOU CAN HELP US
WITH A MISSING PERSONS CASE.
WE'RE VOLUNTEERS
FROM GOTHAM U LOOKING
FOR THIS GIRL LAST SEEN
A COUPLE WEEKS AGO.
GOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
WORRIED.
[RYAN:]
I NEVER
SAW HER NERVOUS,
NEVER SAW HER SWEAT,
BUT WHEN I HEARD
THOSE VOICES
OUTSIDE THE WINDOW,
I KNEW WHY.
[MUFFLED]
I'M HERE!
I SAW THAT
SEARCH PARTY OUTSIDE,
AND I THOUGHT I'D
DONE IT,
THOUGHT I'D WON.
I THOUGHT I HAD
PROVED TO THAT BITCH
THAT I WAS WORTH
SOMETHING TO SOMEONE.
HELP ME! I'M HERE!
THAT IS SO
UPSETTING.
UH, WHAT DOES
THE LITTLE GIRL
LOOK LIKE?
[BANGING]
SHE'S 13, FAIR SKIN,
BLUE EYES.
[ECHOING]
FAIR SKIN, BLUE EYES.
SHE WAS LAST SEEN
WEARING A NECKLACE
WITH A RED STONE.
OH, MY GOSH.
THAT IS JUST AWFUL.
I WILL DEFINITELY KEEP
MY EYES PEELED.
[RYAN:] BUT THEY WEREN'T
LOOKING FOR ME.
THEY WERE LOOKING
FOR SOME WHITE GIRL
BECAUSE WHEN WHITE GIRLS
GO MISSING,
PEOPLE GET
OFF THEIR ASSES,
AND THEY DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IT.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
HANG ON.
A SEARCH TEAM WAS LOOKING
FOR A 13-YEAR-OLD WHITE GIRL
WEARING A RED STONE
NECKLACE?
I NOW HOW TO FIND
THE CANDY LADY.
HOW?
THAT GIRL WAS BETH KANE.
YOU MIND?
I REALLY THOUGHT
YOU'D BE BETTER AT THIS.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR A MAN
NAMED OCEAN.
MM-HMM.
I'M HAPPY TO TELL YOU
EVERYTHING YOU WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT THE 7 SEAS,
BUT THERE'S ONLY
SO FAR I CAN GET
WITHOUT A LAST NAME.
YEAH. CORYANA DOESN'T
REALLY DO LAST NAMES.
SAFIYAH, OCEAN,
TATIANA.
IT'S ALL
VERY BIBLICAL.
THEN WE NEED
ANOTHER ANGLE.
IN HINDSIGHT,
I DON'T KNOW WHY
I THOUGHT YOU COULD
HELP ME FIGURE OUT
WHO THIS PERSON IS
CONSIDERING YOU DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW YOU WERE
SWAPPING SPIT
WITH YOUR FORMER FLAME.
I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO GO.
AND I THINK YOU'RE
HAUNTED.
KATE DISAPPEARED
WITH SO MUCH
LEFT UNSAID
BETWEEN YOU TWO,
AND IT'S KILLING YOU,
WHICH IS PRECISELY
WHY I WANT TO
WORK WITH YOU--
BECAUSE YOU'LL STOP
AT NOTHING TO FIND HER.
IS THAT WHAT YOU ARE?
HAUNTED?
WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO SAY, SOPH,
THAT I MISS MY SISTER
MORE THAN ANYTHING,
THAT I REGRET SPENDING
THE LAST YEAR
TERRORIZING HER,
NOW THAT SHE'S GONE
I REALIZE
HOW MUCH SHE
MEANT TO ME?
IF IT'S THE TRUTH.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LUKE:]
YO, SOPHIE.
IT'S LUKE FOX.
I CAN'T BE SEEN
WORKING WITH YOU.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
ALICE, DON'T!
WHAT THE HELL?
I DIDN'T ORDER
TAKEOUT,
BUT I'LL TAKE YOU
OUT ANYWAY.
KATE WAS OBSESSED
WITH FINDING BETH.
SHE COLLECTED
EVERY PIECE
OF DOCUMENTATION
HAVING TO DO
WITH THE SEARCH,
INCLUDING LOGS
OF WHO SEARCHED WHERE.
NOW WE JUST HAVE TO
FIND THEM.
OOH! I DO NOT THINK
I WAS SUPPOSED TO SEE THIS.
OH, MY GOD!
THANK YOU.
THIS IS MINE.
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
KATE WAS BORROWING THOSE.
NO. I'VE JUST KIND OF
STARTED MOVING IN.
WAIT. YOU WENT
FROM THE 56th FLOOR
OF A RIVERSIDE PENTHOUSE
TO A LOFT
ABOVE A LOUD GAY BAR?
A GAY BAR
THAT I NOW RUN.
FIGURED IT WOULD
SAVE ME THE COMMUTE.
BINGO.
I GET IT.
YOU MOVE INTO HER PLACE,
YOU TAKE OVER
HER BAR.
IF I LOST MY SISTER,
I'D WANT TO HANG ON
TO EVERY PIECE
OF HER, TOO.
YOU KNOW, SPEAKING
OF SHORTER COMMUTES
TO WORK,
YOU SHOULD TOTALLY
LIVE HERE.
WITH YOU?
I'M SERIOUS.
I MEAN, IT'S ALREADY
PAID FOR.
THERE'S AN EXTRA BEDROOM.
THE BATHROOM IS HUGE,
AND NO OFFENSE,
YOUR PLANT WAS LOOKING
KIND OF SAD IN YOUR VAN.
THIS HAS CORNER SUNLIGHT,
AND THERE'S A CUTE--
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SELL
MY ASS ON MOVING
OUT OF MY VAN.
YES, I'D LOVE TO
LIVE HERE.
OK.
GOOD.
KATE COLLECTED
ALL OF THIS AS A KID?
YEAH. THE GCPD STOPPED
LOOKING FOR BETH.
SEARCH PARTIES
STOPPED LOOKING FOR BETH.
EVENTUALLY,
EVEN OUR DAD
STOPPED LOOKING FOR HER,
BUT KATE NEVER DID.
SHE REMINDS ME
OF SOMEONE.
HMM?
MY EX.
SHE NEVER STOPPED
LOOKING FOR ME EITHER.
NO. SHE GOT YOU, TOO?
THAT'S WHAT
SHE THINKS.
TOLD YOU I GOT
YOUR BACK.
[RYAN:]
SHE ALLOWED
HERSELF TO GET CAUGHT
TO HELP BREAK ME OUT.
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
I REMEMBER EVER
FEELING LIKE
I ACTUALLY MATTERED
TO SOMEONE.
HMM.
WELL, IF ANGELIQUE
WAS THERE,
THEN MAYBE SHE REMEMBERS
WHERE THE HOUSE IS.
YOU GOT TO CALL HER.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I CAN'T. THINGS
TOOK A TURN.
WE DON'T EVEN
SPEAK ANYMORE.
LISTEN. AS A PERSON
WITH SEASON TICKETS
TO CRAZY LESBIAN DRAMA,
I CAN APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT ON BEHALF
OF KEVIN JOHNSON,
YOU GOT TO MAKE
AN EXCEPTION.
MMM.
SEE? TOOK A TURN.
MUST HAVE CHANGED
HER NUMBER.
WAIT, WAIT.
MAYBE THIS WILL HELP.
POINT ROCK,
GOTHAM HOPE SEARCH GROUP,
GOTHAM U's
YOUTH VOLUNTEERS.
ACCORDING TO THIS,
ON SATURDAY, OCTOBER 1,
THEY WENT DOOR TO DOOR.
THIS IS A MAP
OF THEIR ROUTE.
THIS MUST BE WHERE
THE CANDY LADY LIVES.
YEAH.
I'M COMING FOR YOU, KEVIN.
WAIT. AREN'T YOU
GONNA SUIT UP?
NO. SHE NEEDS
TO SEE MY FACE.
WELL, HOW CAN I HELP?
YOU CAN CLEAR OUT
MY BEDROOM,
WHICH YOU'RE CURRENTLY
USING AS YOUR
WALK-IN CLOSET.
I NEED TO DO THIS
ALONE.
GO GET KEVIN BACK...ROOMIE!
ALICE,
PUT THE GUN DOWN.
SORRY, SOPH,
BUT THREESOMES
AREN'T MY THING,
ESPECIALLY WHEN 1/3
WORKED WITH KATE
TO LOCK ME IN
AT ARKHAM.
HE CAN HELP US.
US?
ARE YOU NOT BEING
HELD HOSTAGE RIGHT NOW?
WHAT THE HELL
IS HAPPENING?
OH. SOPH AND I HAVE
BEEN TASKED BY SAFIYAH
TO FIND A MAN,
AND ONCE WE DO
AND I KILL HIM,
WE GET KATE BACK.
WAIT. WHAT?
YOU NEVER SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT KILLING HIM.
HEH. DIDN'T I?
WELL, THIS ONE COMES
WITH SPECIAL INSTRUCTIONS.
ABRACADABRA. I KILL HIM
WITH THIS.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
THERE'S BEEN 100 TIPS
SINCE THE ANNOUNCEMENT,
BUT THE ONE ON WAYSIDE
SOUNDS HALF LEGIT.
I'LL SWING BY, CHECK IT OUT,
LET YOU KNOW WHAT I FIND.
NEVER TOUCH MY GUN AGAIN.
SO SHOULD I STAY,
OR...
WE CAN USE YOUR HELP.
[DOOR OPENS]
CAN I HELP YOU,
SWEETIE?
I'M HERE TO CLAIM
KEVIN JOHNSON.
WHO?
15, MALE, AFRICAN-AMERICAN,
LAST SEEN...WITH YOU.
AND WHO MIGHT
YOU BE?
SOMEONE WHO CARES.
I HAVE SEEN HIM,
AND HE'S FOUND A FAMILY
WHO LOVES HIM.
[GAGGING]
GET HER INSIDE.
HOW EXACTLY AM I
SUPPOSED TO FIND A GUY
WITH NO LAST NAME
ON A LAPTOP?
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
WITH ACTUAL CALORIES IN HERE?
THERE'S RAT POISON
UNDER THE SINK.
LOOK. I APPRECIATE
THAT THE CROWS
CAN GET PAST
MOST ENCRYPTION FIELDS,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
DO US ANY FAVORS HERE.
THIS ISLAND MUST HAVE
THE MOST ADVANCED TECH
IN THE WORLD
BECAUSE IT'S
NOT SHOWING UP
ON ANY SATELLITES.
YOU CAN SEE
FOR YOURSELF.
IT'S A DEAD END.
WAIT. WHAT IS...
ANY CHANCE THERE'S
SOMETHING AT WAYNE
WITH MORE FIREPOWER?
100%.
LET ME DO A DEEP DIVE,
AND I'LL SEE WHAT
I CAN FIND.
BEHOLD THE ONLY CARBS
IN THIS HELLHOLE.
BAGUETTE?
I'M GOOD.
THEN I GUESS WE WAIT.
TELL ME YOU RECORDED
"90 DAY FIANCEÉ."
I'M GONNA FIND YOUR DAD
AND SEE IF HIS LEAD
AMOUNTED TO ANYTHING.
IF YOU WANT TO AVOID
BEING ARRESTED,
I'D STAY PUT.
CAN YOU PICK ME UP
A 6-PACK WHEN YOU'RE OUT?
[YOUNG RYAN:]
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU LET YOURSELF GET CAUGHT.
I HEARD ABOUT
THIS LADY CREEPING
AROUND GALAXY HERO
COMICS,
SO I WENT THERE
AND MADE SURE
SHE SAW ME.
WHY DIDN'T ANYONE
COME FOR ME?
EVERYONE THOUGHT
YOU RAN AWAY,
BUT I KNEW YOU'D NEVER
LEAVE YOUR "GHOST KID"
COLLECTION BEHIND.
HA HA HA!
[RUBBER BAND STRETCHING]
OHH! AGH!
NO!
[COUGHING]
THIS IS EXACTLY
WHY NOBODY
WANTS YOU.
OHH!
COME ON, RYAN.
WE GOT TO GO BEFORE SHE WAKES.
RYAN!
RYAN, YOU GOT TO
FIGHT THIS.
RYAN, FIGHT!
FIGHT LIKE GHOST KID
WOULD FIGHT.
REMEMBER WHEN HE LOST
HIS LAME-ASS INVISIBILITY
AND EVERYONE KEPT
THROWING CRAP AT HIM
BUT HE KEPT FIGHTING
ANYWAY?
RYAN, GET UP!
YOU READ "GHOST KID"?
UNH.
[GRUNTING]
OK.
[THUD]
UNH. COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON.
OOH! OK.
OK, OK.
COME ON.
OH. RIGHT THERE.
MMM. AHH.
[GLASS CRUNCHES]
HUH! AHH!
AAH!
UGH!
YOU DON'T REMEMBER ME,
HUH, BITCH?
HUH!
I'M THE GIRL
YOU COULDN'T BREAK!
UNH!
WHERE IS KEVIN?
KEVIN RAN OUT
OF JELLY BEANS.
WHO DID YOU SELL HIM TO?
NO ONE EVER REALLY
KNEW HIS FACE,
AND NOW THAT IT'S
HIDDEN BEHIND A MASK--
HA HA HA!
NO ONE EVER WILL.
UNH!
YOU RUDY?
KANE, RIGHT?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
LIKE I SAID ON THE PHONE,
BEFORE THE PLANE TOOK OFF,
I WAS WORKING THE TARMAC
AS A MARSHAL,
YOU KNOW, THE GUY
WITH THE ORANGE BATONS--
YEAH. I KNOW
WHAT--WHAT THAT IS.
SO RIGHT BEFORE
THE PLANE TAKES OFF,
I NOTICE A SUSPICIOUS SUV
PULL UP TO THE AIRCRAFT,
AND I'M THINKING TO MYSELF,
"WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?"
BECAUSE ONLY CATERING
AND EMERGENCY VEHICLES
ARE ALLOWED
THAT FAR OUT.
AGH!
HEH. DAMN, KEVIN.
YOU SMOOTH.
NOW...LET'S GO
AND EARN YOU YOUR MASK.
I'M HERE. WHAT MAKES
YOU THINK OCEAN IS?
[LUKE:]
BECAUSE WHILE YOU
AND ALICE WERE BICKERING
OVER WHAT TEMP
TO KEEP YOUR THERMOSTAT,
I WAS TEXTING
THE ONLY PERSON WE KNOW
WHO KNOWS SAFIYAH.
JULIA?
YEAH.
TURNS OUT JULIA HAD HEARD
OCEAN LEFT THE ISLAND
A FEW YEARS BACK,
SO SHE WENT LOOKING
FOR HIM HERSELF,
HOPING TO GET MORE INTEL
ON SAFIYAH.
SO WHERE'S HE?
WELL, SHE WAS WAYLAID,
BUT SHE DID NARROW DOWN
HIS HIDEOUT TO
4 POSSIBLE LOCATIONS.
IT LOOKS LIKE TWO
WERE DEMOLISHED,
ONE IS NOW
AN ICE CREAM PARLOR, AND--
I'M SITTING IN FRONT
OF THE FOURTH.
BE CAREFUL.
COPY THAT.
[WOMAN:]
YOU BREAK IT,
YOU BOUGHT IT.
UNH! OHH! AGH!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
DO I KNOW YOU?
UNH!
IF YOU DID, YOU WOULD
HAVE SEEN THAT COMING.
[ALICE:]
LET HER GO.
WHERE'S OCEAN?
WHO?
LOOK. I JUST CAME HERE
LOOKING TO BAG THE PLACE,
AND CLEARLY,
IT'S NOT WORTH IT,
SO YOU TWO
CAN HAVE IT.
[SIGHS]
TSK, TSK, TSK, TSK.
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT
WE WERE BONDING.
DID YOU REALLY THINK
I'D TRUST YOU?
I WANT TO FIND KATE
JUST LIKE YOU.
THE QUESTION IS WHY?
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT,
TO APOLOGIZE,
TO PROMISE YOU'LL
CHANGE YOUR WAYS?
I THINK WE BOTH
KNOW THE ANSWER
TO THAT QUESTION.
I'M GONNA FIND
MY SISTER,
AND I'M GONNA
KILL HER.
YO, KEVIN.
CANDY LADY SAYS
YOU'RE RIPE.
PROVE IT.
KILL A CROW.
BUT HE DIDN'T
DO NOTHING.
HE'S NOT ON TRIAL.
YOU ARE.
YOU WANT TO BE
IN THE FAMILY, RIGHT?
PROVE IT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DO THIS.
YOU KNOW, I DO HAVE
A LEGIT TIP FOR YOU,
COMMANDER.
DON'T COME DOWN TO
FALSE FACE SOCIETY'S
HOOD SOLO.
[WHOOSH]
HE DIDN'T.
[WOMAN:]
♪ I'M NOT GONNA
SHED A TEAR, BABY ♪
♪ YOU CAN WATCH ME MOVE
AND THAT'S FOR MAKING ME
SWEAT OUT MY EDGES.
[GUNSHOT]
KEVIN, NO, NO, NO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I WANT A FAMILY,
AND THEY WANT ME.
KID, PUT THE GUN DOWN.
KEVIN, LISTEN TO ME.
YOU DO THIS, AND YOU
THROW YOUR ENTIRE LIFE AWAY.
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME.
KEVIN--HEY. WAIT.
I DO, THOUGH.
I KNOW YOU HAVE
A BROTHER.
I KNOW THAT YOU THINK
NO ONE CARES ABOUT YOU,
AND I KNOW THAT IF YOU
PULL THAT TRIGGER
YOU'LL BECOME EXACTLY WHAT
THE CANDY LADY SAYS YOU ARE--
INVISIBLE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT ME?
BECAUSE I SET OUT
TO FIND YOU,
BECAUSE YOU MATTER.
I SEE YOU,
AND YOU ARE MEANT
FOR SO MUCH MORE THAN THIS.
PROTECT HIM.
THIS IS A FALSE FACE SOCIETY
HOT SPOT.
THERE'S BOUND TO BE
MORE CREEPING.
HOW'D YOU KNOW
HE WAS HERE?
EASY.
I LOOKED.
[DEWITT:]
CANDICE LONG,
AKA THE CANDY LADY,
WAS CAPTURED TONIGHT
AFTER BATWOMAN UNCOVERED
A 20-YEAR CONSPIRACY INVOLVING
THE FALSE FACE SOCIETY
AND CHILD TRAFFICKING.
THIS STREET-TO-GANG PIPELINE
INCLUDES KEVIN JOHNSON,
WHO CREDITS BOTH BATWOMAN
AND CROWS COMMANDER JACOB KANE
FOR HIS RESCUE EARLIER TONIGHT,
WHICH BEGS
THE OBVIOUS QUESTION--
IS THERE A BAT-CROW PARTNERSHIP
ON THE HORIZON?
AT LEAST ONE OF US
DID SOMETHING RIGHT TODAY.
HALF RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER
THOUGHT I'D SAY THIS,
BUT IF BATWOMAN
HADN'T BEEN THERE,
I PROBABLY
WOULDN'T BE HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
ALICE HAPPENED, SIR.
SHE WANTS TO FIND KATE,
AND IT'S IMPERATIVE
THAT WE FIND HER FIRST.
I'M TOTALLY STEALING
THIS JACKET FYI.
SO YOU'RE ALREADY
RAIDING MY CLOSET.
DUH!
HA!
[SIGHS]
[AG AND NILU'S
"FOUND A HOME" PLAYING]
SHE NEVER STOPPED LOOKING,
EVEN WHEN ALL
THE EVIDENCE SAID
THAT SHE WAS CRAZY.
YOU KNOW, I CAN
LIVE IN HER PLACE
AND TAKE OVER HER BAR
AND HOLD ON TO ALL
THE LITTLE PIECES OF HER,
BUT NONE OF IT
WILL BRING ME CLOSURE
IF I DON'T
ACTUALLY LOOK.
I DON'T WANT TO
BELIEVE ALICE,
BUT I--I DON'T WANT
TO BELIEVE THAT
KATE'S DEAD EITHER.
THEN MAYBE IT'S TIME
WE START THINKING
A LITTLE CRAZY.
YEAH.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
HEY. I GOT TO GO.
EVERYTHING OK?
YEAH. I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
[NILU:]
♪ ALONE
♪ WHERE EVERY WORD IS TRUE
♪ AND YOU
♪ MY FEET HAVE TRAVELED FAR
♪ MY ARMS HAVE BEEN...
LOOK WHO MIGHT HAVE FOUND
THE KEY TO THE OCEAN.
[NILU:]
♪ OUTSTRETCHED
♪ I WAS LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING I HADN'T SEEN YET ♪
[GASPS]
[MEN GRUNTING]
[SAFIYAH:]
OCEAN.
[NILU:]
♪ AND NOW I DON'T HAVE
SO FAR... ♪
HI.
[EXHALES]
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
[NILU:]
♪ BECAUSE IN YOU
I FOUND ♪
♪ I FOUND A HOME
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH
WRONG NUMBER?
SERIOUSLY?
YOU DIDN'T TAKE MY CALLS
FOR TWO YEARS.
I HAD TO PLAY HARD TO GET
FOR A MINUTE.
[NILU:]
♪ MY CHEST
♪ WHERE MY FEARS HAVE COME...
WHY AM I HERE, RYAN?
[NILU:]
♪ TO REST
BATWOMAN CAUGHT
THE CANDY LADY.
[NILU:]
♪ I FOUND
DAMN.
YEAH. DAMN.
[NILU:]
♪ AND YOU FOUND...
NEXT QUESTION.
WHY COULDN'T YOU JUST
TELL ME THAT OVER TEXT?
BECAUSE MAYBE
I MISS THE GIRL
WHO ALWAYS HAD
MY BACK.
TRUCE?
[NILU:]
♪ I THINK I'VE
ALWAYS KNOWN ♪
♪ IN YOU I'VE FOUND A HOME
[MAN:]
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!
Original Captions by  CBS Corporation