Now we mustn't wake him.
Oh, I loathe the bats!
What is happening?
Why are they here?
Because bats eat rats, Alice.
Rat...
Meet Mouse.
I'm gonna need your help
one last time,
my little Mouse.
Someone... Quite literally
crashed our tea party,...
but she forgot to take
her party favor,...
so I'm gonna need you
to make sure she gets it.
Twinkle, twinkle, little bat
How I wonder where you're at
Up above the world you fly
Like a tea tray in the sky
Twinkle, twinkle, little bat
Up until your brain went splat...
It's like a treat.
Where's your cash?
I got three collection agencies
asking me the same thing.
You got an atm card?
You're just setting yourself
up for more disappointment.
Guess you got nothing
except a smart mouth.
Thank you!
And I don't know about
your other security guards
but I have been trained in half
a dozen forms of martial arts
so, beating up bad guys
won't be a problem.
You were certainly
around enough of them...
In Blackgate.
Well, what it doesn't say
is that I didn't do it.
Why'd you tell the judge you did?
To avoid doing 15 years
instead of 18 months.
Judge gave me a choice...
Plead out to a lesser charge,
do a bullet and a half.
Look.
I get it.
Blackgate doesn't look good
on a resume
but it did give me
a valuable skillset.
Every second you're inside,
you're assessing threats
trying to figure out
who's dangerous.
You get real good
at reading people.
Faces can tell you a lot.
And what does mine tell you?
That I'm not getting this job.
In this exclusive video
you can see Crows officers
opening fire on Batwoman.
This ambush comes after
the Crow's own Jacob Kane
forged an alliance with the bat.
This shocking footage
has sparked anger
among Gotham citizens
and a pro-Batwoman rally
has been planned for tomorrow
in Gotham city Plaza
to demand the return
of the caped crusader
who hasn't been seen
since the firefight with Crows.
Commander
they're here.
Time to see how long
we've been out of the loop.
I'm sorry. Kate was what?
Because that sounded
a lot like Batwoman.
She was your sister.
She never told you?
Please. Like, Kate
would ever trust me with a secret.
How could you not know?
You two spent nearly
every day together.
You were her associate.
Assistant actually
and it looks like she was good
at keeping secrets
from both of us.
We know she didn't work alone.
Who were her other friends,
people she was close to?
Dad, now you're just rubbing it in.
Kate spent years
trying to push me away.
It's not like she was about to use
"I am Batwoman" as an icebreaker.
Can you think of anyone
who wanted to harm her
or Batwoman, anybody
who might have
sabotaged her plane?
I thought you said,
it was an accident.
We're not ruling anything out.
Just looking into any
possible enemies.
You mean other than every agent
in this building, right,
or maybe just the ones
that lured her into a trap,
tried to gun her down
on the 50-yard line.
You know, it's too bad
she didn't have someone who loved her
watching her back.
I think we're done here.
Can we just talk, please?
Oh, now you got
something to say
after staying quiet for months
about who Batwoman really was?
It wasn't my secret to tell.
No, just your secret to keep.
Can't imagine Kate would trust you
with the contents of her safe
and not trust you
with everything else.
You really fooled me.
I guess about a lot of things.
Hey, you got any of this
in generic?
Thanks. Now do the safe.
Hands in the air.
Ryan wilder.
I'll note my surprise in the report.
Hey, Soph. Love the hair.
It's Agent Moore.
I figure we've done
this enough times
to be on a first-name basis.
You get demoted? I don't know.
C-store robbery seems
a little low-rent for you.
Funny. I was gonna say
it's a step up for you.
Got tired of covering for
your drug-dealing lady friend?
Ex-lady friend.
Is that why she wasn't driving
the getaway car this time?
I already told them
I didn't rob that place.
Yeah, I read that.
I also read that you were
standing over a bloody cashier
with your prints on the gun.
Because I was trying to stop it.
Casting yourself as the hero?
Now that's new.
Got the security footage.
Her story checks out.
Okay. Sorry for the mistake.
Yeah. The Crow's last mistake
only cost me 18 months of my life
and counting.
Piece of advice.
If you're always
in the wrong place at the wrong time,
maybe you should find
a new place.
And tell me where that is.
Because by my count,
I've been brought in
for questioning more times
for stuff I didn't do
than an actual
serial killer like Alice
has been arrested for stuff she did.
You think I don't know
the real reason
Jacob kane won't put
a bullet in her?
Any sympathy he had for her died
a long time ago.
What are you talking about?
That if Alice weren't white,
she'd be dead.
Sorry for the inconvenience,
Ms. Wilder.
You're free to go.
Sympathy for that psychopath?
Ryan.
What are you doing here?
Does your dad know about all this?
Somehow, I've managed
to keep it a secret.
Guess that's what your family does,
keeping secrets?
I actually pulled an all-nighter,
so you're gonna have
to be a little more clear.
Alice is Beth Kane, isn't she?
Who told you that?
Girl goes missing 16 years ago,
no bodies found.
That was Alice
before she was Alice.
It's complicated.
Because she's your sister, too.
I mean, does covering up
for her run in the family?
That bitch killed my mom.
I would never help her.
I'm sorry.
Alice poisoned my mom and me
and then gave us one dose
of the antidote, so...
My mom died in my arms.
Tell me where I can find her
and I will get justice
for both of our moms.
Couple homeless people
dropped him off.
Found him in the tunnels,
most of him anyway.
Okay, I know I'm not a doctor
but I am pretty sure
there is nothing you can do for him.
Oh, my god. It's Mouse.
Need a tissue?
Believe it or not, I'm not here
to kill you, Pennywhistle.
If I was, I'd just swipe left
and delete you.
Quite the opposite.
I'm here to save your life.
See, I'm planning something big,
high body count,
and it would be a shame
if one of those bodies was yours.
Since when do you care about my life
or any other?
Since our mutual enemy
killed my dear sister before I could.
Safiyah?
Wait. You didn't actually think
Kate's plane crash
was a mechanical failure, did you?
That's not exactly Safiyah's M.O.
Well, Pennyroyal,
we all have to step outside
our comfort zones, grow, expand,
do things
we would normally never fathom doing,
which is why I'm proposing
a little supervillain,
superspy team-up.
I already have
a brilliantly terrifying plan.
They say revenge
is a dish best served cold,
but I think the portions
are big enough for us to split.
Why would I ever work
with a psychopath?
Because there's another psychopath
hunting you
who's even scarier than me...
Let's be real.
I'm not afraid of her.
You should be.
She can get you anywhere.
Just ask Kate.
Retribution is coming for both of us,
Pennyloafer.
If we can work together
and get
to that sister-killing psycho bitch
before she gets to us,
you know,
have each other's backs.
Yeah.
Until you stick a knife in mine.
Well, we could do
a couple of trust falls first.
Work up to the idea?
How does that sound?
Sounds like you're desperate.
Kate was the only person
who had any sympathy left for you.
Now that she's gone,
you don't have anyone.
Oh, you know what else
I don't have?
A knife sticking out of me.
At least it wasn't in your back.
So, I guess
we have two uninvited guests.
What the hell are you doing here?
At the moment, trying not to puke.
What kind of animal did this?
There's got to be
a thousand bites here.
All I know
is this is a bad way to go.
It would be, but all these bites
were post-mortem.
Mouse was poisoned.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah,
because it's the same toxin
that killed my mom,
and the only person
with access to it...
- Alice.
- I thought you said
that Mouse was Alice's,
like, only friend in the world.
Well, they must have
had a falling out,
which is more than
a little disturbing
given that Mouse was Alice's anchor
to any semblance of humanity.
And if she killed him,
she must really be unraveling.
Wait, is he still...
- No.
- Then how is he moving?
I don't know.
What? I really hate bats.
I'm here at Gotham City Plaza,
where citizens have gathered
to show their support for Batwoman,
who hasn't been seen in Gotham
since the Crows ambushed her
in Goliaths Stadium over a week ago,
and despite the Crows
threatening to make arrests,
these protestors have made it clear
that they're not going anywhere.
"We want the bat!"
So, it wasn't enough
for her to poison Mouse?
She had to feed him to bats, too?
Yeah, I think this is her version
of closure.
Yeah, don't bet on that.
Julia just said Alice put
a butterfly knife into her ribs.
She'll live.
Not sure we can say the same
for anyone else.
What do you mean?
Alice told Julia
she was planning something,
said she used the words
"brilliant" and "terrifying,"
which for Alice
is pretty much redundant.
Didn't give a where or when
but said the body
count would be high.
Okay, so some sort of public event,
a densely populated area.
And the Goliaths aren't playing,
so it can't be the stadium.
Guys.
Philharmonic doesn't start up
for a few weeks.
She's got 330 square miles
of Gotham to choose from.
- Guys.
- Yes?
I think I can narrow it down.
Batwoman rally.
"We want the bat!"
Got to admit,
there's a kind
of twisted poetry to killing
the people demanding
the return of her sister.
We got to get those people
out of there.
Listen to them.
They're not going anywhere
without Batwoman.
Okay, so we put Julia in the suit.
She's worn it before, it fits.
She can tell them all to go home.
I think she's too hurt.
It's not an option.
I'll do it.
No.
Well, I don't think you have time
to hold auditions.
I think people will know
you're not Batwoman.
I did really great my first time
in the suit.
Hello! Black!
Okay, I think that she knows that,
and, what, you put her
on top of a 20-story building,
people will be focused on the suit,
not the person in it,
and we're talking, what, 20 minutes?
You... Mary, no!
Well, you're out of options,
and you're out of time.
Put me in the suit.
"We want the bat!"
This is an unlawful assembly.
You are hereby ordered
to disperse,
or you risk arrest and prosecution.
"We want the bat!"
We gave them a warning.
Arrest them. Bus them out of here.
Sir, these people are here
because of Kate.
They want the same thing we do,
for her to be back.
"We want the bat!"
Okay. Nobody saw that.
Yeah. You want to use the cape
to slow your descent.
Things that would have been nice
to know
before I jumped 10 stories.
Nothing's stopping you from asking
before throwing yourself
off a building, FYI.
- Okay.
- Now look heroic.
How's that?
Straighten that back
and lose the hands on the hips
because it's overkill.
Now clench those fists, chin up,
and now try and angle that cape so it
catches the wind.
Good?
There she is! There she is!
"We want the bat!"
Kate?
Get that imposter off the roof.
Citizens of Gotham,
you need to get out
of here immediately.
No, seriously, people,
your lives are in danger.
No, really, people.
I appreciate your support,
but you all need to return
to your homes.
You've got them fooled,
but not me.
I don't know who you are,
but you're not Batwoman.
Wait. Is that Alice?
Ryan, talk to me.
I'm a little busy right now.
Do not engage.
Okay, she's a killer.
I am well aware of that.
What exactly are you doing
in my sister's hand-me-downs?
The one thing she wouldn't do.
I'm gonna kill you.
Okay, look.
I know what she did to your mom,
and I get what she took
away from you,
but Batwoman does not kill.
Well, like you said,
I'm not Batwoman.
I cannot let you do this.
Don't think you're in the position
to stop me.
Ryan.
Ryan!
Well, the suit's for real.
What about the girl inside?
Let's find out.
Ryan!
I knew we should have never
let her near that suit.
Can you blame her after everything
that Alice has done?
You... You can't seriously
be okay with this.
You know what
I'm really not okay with?
Everybody just expecting
me to get over the fact
that Alice killed my mom,
and maybe if Kate would have done
what Ryan's trying to do,
she'd still be alive.
You willing to bet Kate's legacy
on that?
It's over for you.
On the contrary,
we're just getting started.
Oh, we got a problem.
- Care to be more specific.
- Okay. It's a big problem.
Radar footprint's huge.
Whatever it is,
it's heading straight for Ryan.
Was that supposed
to do something?
It appears we're under attack
from bats.
Thousands are running for cover.
I've never seen anything... Look out!
Hey, Ryan. Ryan, come in.
Alice used some kind of device
to draw the bats here.
Oh, my god.
There's freaking bats everywhere.
You don't think these are the bats
that Alice fed Mouse to?
And they could be the carriers
for the toxin that killed him.
I got to get back to the clinic.
I'm picking up a subsonic frequency
drawing the bats to the plaza.
It must be some kind of transmitter.
You got to get down there.
I'll be there in one minute.
These people don't have a minute.
Ryan!
Damn it!
I'm bringing
the suit's echolocation online.
Found it.
Hey, guys, guys.
Come on. Get inside.
- Who are you?
- The chick who just saved your life.
These bats are toxic.
Anyone who's bitten,
get them to the hospital.
- Now, what should I do?
- Smash the damn thing.
No. It'll send these toxic bats
all over the city.
You got a better idea?
I might.
I just don't think either of us
is gonna like this.
Let's get it in there.
We got a lot more coming.
Just get them in here.
We'll figure it out.
Okay.
Any pain?
I'll take that as a yes.
Okay.
No, no, no.
I'll get you something
to make you more comfortable.
I think.
Relax, steppy.
I've already lost one of my sisters.
I'm not about to lose the...
only one I have left.
You really believe Kate's dead?
You know, better than anyone
that nobody means there's still hope.
I envy you, sis.
You still haven't kicked
hope to the curb.
See, she and I,
we have an understanding.
I stay out of hope's way,
and she stays out of mine.
That way, she's not there
to lie to me
about Kate being alive.
Now, while there's no hope
for our dear sister,
there may be for the Bat-fans.
You're giving me your blood?
Oh, no.
Actually, that's your blood.
I swiped it from you
when Nocturna tried to drain you,
so technically, it's a regift.
It's a rare vintage find...
with hints of desert rose,
and it's the only thing
that will treat that nasty,
little toxin.
Poisoning my mom wasn't enough.
You had to go
and poison all of Gotham, too,
and now, I'm just supposed to believe
that you gift wrapped the antidote?
I just figured I'd missed
a lot of your birthdays, so...
I think you miss Kate.
I think underneath all of your crazy,
this is your cry for help.
This your sick way of grieving?
I met the new girl.
This one's actually willing
to kill me.
She's gonna be a...
Handful.
You got three lanes.
Try to stay in one of them.
Oh, give me a break.
I can barely get my van to do 40.
Hey. Got more coming in.
I heard a report
that Gotham city general's
got more than 250.
They don't know what this is
or how to treat it.
Guess they don't have this.
It's the only thing in the
world that can save them.
- Where'd you get it?
- From Alice.
You can't possibly trust her.
I don't think
we have a choice.
Even if Alice is telling the truth,
you can't cure all the bite victims
with just that.
No, I can't, but if I give it
to Hamilton Dynamics,
maybe they can synthesize enough
to save everyone,
or at least I hope they can,
but there's only one way to find out.
I got a vacant warehouse
off the Schwartz bypass, 2.3 miles.
No. Not enough time.
I need something closer.
Okay.
There's a decommissioned
subway station at needer avenue,
- should be empty.
- No, no, no.
That's a homeless encampment.
There's people down there.
Okay, okay. Working on it.
No, rush.
Luke, I might have an idea.
Talk to me.
Probably better if I ask
for forgiveness than for permission.
Ryan, what are you doing?
Wish I knew.
Hey!
What are you doing?
- Get off the bus now!
- No.
Please.
- Come on.
- Are you kidding me?
What, are you crazy?
Get down!
Batwoman?
Oh, no, no. I'm not really Batwoman.
Well, you are to me.
- If you...
- After a night of terror,
hope has returned to Gotham,
and it's arrived on the back
of a Hamilton Dynamics truck.
Thanks to the quick action taken
by the technology firm,
everyone infected
is receiving treatment.
The lines are long, and frankly,
so is the needle.
Hamilton dynamics
is remaining tight-lipped
on how they were able
to generate a serum so quickly,
but we're all certainly glad
they did.
- As for the swarm...
- I mean, a little credit
would have been nice.
All I did
was give you your magic ingredient
for your miracle cure,
but you do you,
Hamilton dynamics.
What's Alice's play here?
Good deeds aren't her thing,
and I think we both know
she didn't just grow a conscience.
She went through a lot of trouble
to unleash a plague
onto an entire city
only to play ninth inning Jonas Salk.
She's too cunning and calculating.
This is part of something bigger.
If this is the opener,
I don't think we're ready
for the main event.
Me neither.
I just hope the new Batwoman is.
Me, too.
What do you know
about the new Batwoman?
Do you know who she is?
For the record, no,
but short of a name,
is there any answer
I could give you that you'd believe?
Probably not.
Well, maybe I can give you
a consolation prize,
a possible location on Alice.
I had them analyze
the floor mats on my SUV
after my little chat with Alice.
Turns out her boots left behind
traces of triethyl benzene,
a byproduct
of tire manufacturing.
I'm guessing
she's holed up somewhere near
the Dresner motor plant.
Good.
Let's keep this between us.
Backup will just scare her off.
Did she say she loved you?
In the letter,
did Kate say she loved you?
What does it matter?
I just want to know if we're over
because you don't trust me
or because I'm not Kate.
Both.
So, what, you didn't ask me
enough questions the first time?
You gonna break out the waterboard?
Look.
I know I hauled you in here
and interrogated you
like some suspect,
and I'm sorry about that.
I'm trying.
I am.
I just don't want to make
the same mistakes
that I made with Beth.
I don't want to give up hope
that Kate's alive.
You believe she's still alive,
don't you?
I... I think that
if we're gonna find her
you and I have to work together.
I didn't know
the whole dry- cleaning situation,
but I think that burnt bat smell
is here to stay.
And I was kind of hoping
I could be, too.
I appreciate everything you did.
But saving
a whole bunch of lives twice
- isn't good enough?
- We already have a Batwoman.
Where was she last night?
Best thing that ever happened to me
was the day mama Cora found me.
Second best thing
was the day I found that suit,
but I can't help but to feel
like that suit found me.
This city needs hope, Luke.
Hell, we all need it,
and I saw it today
in the face of a young girl
who's been told her entire life
that hope doesn't exist.
Give me a chance,
and I can bring
that hope back to Gotham.
Look. Kate Kane
was top of her class at one
of the most elite military academies
in the world,
and she still struggled
to take down criminals.
Maybe she didn't spend
enough time with them.
I have been trapped
in a life surrounded by criminals.
I know how they think, how they act,
but most of all,
I know how to stop them.
I hope you're right
because if Alice
is planning something big,
then the city's gonna need
a Batwoman,
and honestly, so do I.
Batwoman...
Has a code.
No, killing.
Fine.
Until Kate's back.
Come on.
I'll show you around.
It's my first time giving the tour.
Greetings, G-town.
So, how was your night?
In what could have been
a real Batastrophe,
victory was pulled
from the tiny jaws of defeat
by our returning champion Batwoman,
but some eyewitnesses report
that last night's heroics
were courtesy of a new lady bat.
Is this true? Did the old one
just throw in the cowl?
What's going on here?
Talk to me, Gotham.
Dear Bruce, Happy Halloween.
A few tricks, one nice treat.
Tonight, I saw a girl
who reminded me of myself.
Scared but fearless.
Determined not to let
the darkness of Gotham
get the best of her.
People like her are
the hope this city needs.
I've never looked good in red.
Put them on.
Behind your back.
She's mine.
The Desert Rose
was not meant for Gotham,
and now your little stunt
with that miracle cure
has drawn Safiyah's Wrath.
Well, that was
what I intended, so...
Stupid girl.
My dear, sweet Tatiana,
if you were sent here to kill me,
my head would already be
in your carry-on
on the way back to Coryana.
Safiyah will see you die for this.
Maybe, but first, she has to see me.