Oh, God.
Hey!
Batwoman to Batcave.
We need medics to the rooftop
lot above Harper's Plaza.
Batwoman to Batcave. Do you copy?
I need medics now.
Batwoman to Batcave!
You never told me the 911 operator
was a Batwoman fangirl.
Dude's gonna live.
I should have told you
not to work tonight.
You know, I might just
need a little time.
Of course.
Mary and I can cover Bat duties,
try to I.D. the stabby chick
- making lawyer kabobs.
- I mean...
I need time alone.
Copy.
You know I'm here
if you need me, right?
Special Agent Russell Tavaroff
has just been released on bond.
He'll be a free man as he awaits trial
accused of falsifying
evidence to justify
the shooting of an
unarmed Gotham citizen.
The uproar over Crows misconduct
has been ignored by Gotham officials
until one hero spoke up,
former Crows Commander Jacob Kane.
Two Crows agents shot...
Jacob Kane.
I expose Kane as the godfather
of a fraudulent security racket,
and now these cloying
half-wits in the fake news
are crowning him a hero.
Haven't you done enough, Roman?
You imprisoned the man's daughter,
then brainwashed her into your own.
He murdered my Circe.
So, toying with Kane's
daughter is your way of...
feeling better about him
killing yours?
I apologize, Your Royal Highness
but when you gave me the details
of Kate Kane's flight
out of National City
you knew exactly
what I had in mind for her.
Speaking of you owing me a favor
I was hoping to employ
your daughter's services
to settle my affairs in Gotham.
I have reason to believe
that Circe's unique
attributes could benefit us both.
Whatever it is,
I don't want her involved.
She's finally got her life back.
Last I heard, she was running around
with a tree stapled to her face.
Oh, she's ready
to make her grand reentry
into Gotham's influencer life.
After all, my P.R. team
covered up the incident
that landed her in Arkham
to begin with
and her death, yada yada.
They've put together
a very millennial cover story
to explain her disappearance.
Three words...
Malibu, rehab, retreat.
This is the crown jewel.
A life lived but once
is a life lived not at all.
The newest line from
Janus Cosmetics has arrived...
Rebirth.
It wasn't enough
that she believed she was my Circe.
Between the new face
and a strict regimen
of Janus restorative burn cream
she now looks like her too.
I know Enigma gave
her Circe's memories
but who gave her Circe's face?
If you can believe it,
that rambling sewer rat Alice.
You brought Kate Kane
and Alice together?
- When was this?
- Two days ago. Why?
Alice is Beth Kane, you idiot.
You're coming with us, kiddo.
If you're wearing yoga pants,
this is so much worse than I thought.
Now tell me what I'm walking into.
This is a government safe house.
Bidets in the bathroom.
They wouldn't even give us hand soap
for the community center.
Turns out the lawyer
whose computer was stolen
byKill Bill superfan was
working with judges
to place people
into witness relocation.
And all that top-secret location
information was on his computer.
Exactly, so sword lady's
looking for somebody
in witness relocation,
so I placed a trace
on all of his outgoing calls,
assuming that he'd reach
out to the witnesses,
- give them a heads-up.
- And you figured all that out?
Oh, you know, I may have outsourced
the fancy parts to Sophie.
Anyway, we are starting with this guy
because the lawyer called
him first, called him a lot,
but he never picked up.
Starting to know why.
Found our vic.
Same perp left a sword in him.
Definitely trying
to make a statement.
Oh, man. Poor guy was blind.
This isn't your fight, Batwoman.
Why is that?
Because I can actually fight back?
Tatiana?
DNA match complete.
My God.
It really is you.
You've got me confused
with a dead girl.
No, you've got you
confused with a dead girl.
Two dozen inmates used
Circe Sionis as a doormat
on their way out of Arkham.
Listen.
I know this is a lot to handle.
Hey!
Sorry, but did you want her
to escape?
How do we get Kate back?
There's a secret keyword
to unlock her memories
except the woman
who did that to her is dead.
The other option is we jog
her memory piece by piece
- using personal objects.
- That's where these come in.
Everything that's left
of Kate's childhood.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Ocean, meet Daddy.
Daddy, meet Ocean.
- Good to meet you, Mr. Kane.
- Right.
What do we do now?
When Enigma locked
me out of my memories
I forced my way back
in with a photograph.
Her work is formidable
but...
As soon as the first crack appears
she'll go mad wanting
to know the truth about her life.
Enigma worked on you too?
Daddy, you don't get this extra
without a little shove.
- I thought the shove was Cartwright.
- No. He didn't fully break me.
- I was too strong.
- I can attest to that.
Alice may have been angry
and reckless and ornery
but... she could still love.
What are you saying, that... Enigma
took away your ability to love?
I'll let you get on with it.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Kane.
Yeah. This Mr. Kane thing
is definitely weird for me.
I want the guy to like me.
Call me old-fashioned.
If you told me I'd be in
the Crows headquarters
with my father, my sister,
and my... boy toy
and I wouldn't be the one in cuffs...
No one ever accused you
of being predictable.
Call you later.
Good.
Ezra Castellanos. Never heard of him.
Probably,
because up until a few days ago,
he was being protected by Crows
Security in witness protection.
Five years ago, Ezra's eyes
were gouged out with a soup spoon
by a woman named Circe Sionis.
So, this case was sealed
but Luke has a thingy
that unseals seals.
Okay. Then.
Circe's the daughter
of Janus Cosmetics
founder Roman Sionis.
Former model claimed self-defense
after Ezra assaulted her at a party
and after she went to Arkham,
Ezra was afraid the Sionis
family would come after him,
so he went into WITSEC.
Didn't Alice stop by the other day
asking if someone named
Circe showed up to you?
- Yeah and now I'm just confused.
- Yeah. I'm gonna check on Luke.
Well, we could try and track him down
with his fancy hacker tools.
Assuming you know
which buttons to press.
Okay.
You stalking me, Fox?
It's law enforcement only.
They let you in and last I checked,
your new occupation
is unemployed haircut.
Two whiskeys neat.
Look. I understand
the problem here, okay?
Yeah. I'm free on bail,
my charges are gonna be dropped
and as far as the law is concerned,
well, we're back
to you being a car thief
who pulled a gun, so...
I'm not throwing my career away
because your daddy didn't teach you
how to stay out of the wrong
place at the wrong time.
Oh. See, if I were you,
I would not talk about my father.
You come here looking for a fight?
You looking for another
fake excuse to shoot me?
So, how do you propose
we settle this?
Now I heard you won
the Crows hold them tournament
two years in a row.
You are a stalker.
Really hope you have a plan, kid.
You know, some of us are
just here to play cards.
I like punk rock. How edgy.
You should remember this bag.
I found a joint in this pocket,
- grounded you for the entire summer.
- Harsh. It wasn't even coke.
You think he would try memories
I would actually want to remember.
You said it ended up being
the best summer you ever had.
I am not Kate Kane.
And even if I was, what makes you
think
I would want to come back
to a father
who stopped looking
for both daughters
and a literal evil twin?
What am I missing?
This.
When we were kids,
you had a big crush
on Jenny Goldberg.
You only liked her
because she skateboarded
but you were so excited
because she liked you back
except you weren't out yet.
You wanted to tell me you were gay,
but you kept chickening out.
You knew I had
to be the first to know...
but I was also the hardest
because I mattered
the most to you, me...
Beth...
your twin who spent nine months
in the womb with you
and you were scared
of pushing me away
so I made you that stupid mug
to say I already knew
and I loved you.
- I'm locked in a room.
- What room?
A... a basement, a cell.
- I... I can smell formaldehyde.
- Cartwright's.
I can't get out.
Why am I here?
Who's there?
Beth? Beth, is that you?
That's the basement
I spent my childhood in.
You've been there.
Do you remember?
It's... it's more of a feeling I'm...
I'm screaming,
but I can't get your attention.
That... that's not what happened.
Maybe it's a metaphor.
Circe's subconscious is a cell,
- and Kate needs me to free her.
- How can you be sure?
Because it's all I ever wanted.
Okay. I'm gonna take your hands,
so just...
Don't break mine.
Beth?
Are you there?
Kate, it's me. I'm here.
I'm not gonna leave you.
I remember now.
You found me,
- but I couldn't find you.
- It's okay.
There's still time.
Poker? Really? We need you home.
We think Safiyah's in Gotham.
- Thought you and Safiyah were good.
- We are, but the guys who her lackey
ran her sword through can't
really say the same thing.
Okay. Well, you said
you and Mary got this,
and I'm in the middle
of a game right now, so...
Look. We will give you
the space to do your thing,
but we need a hand.
In this family, we take care
of each other first, right?
Every doctor in that hospital
thought I was gonna die
in that bed, but you and Mary
slipped me the Desert Rose
and I woke right up.
Okay. If there was a thank
you somewhere in there, I...
I didn't want to wake up.
How can you say that?
When I was under, I saw my dad
and, I mean, he was right there.
Why the hell would I want to live
in a world where we
get shot for no reason,
where the gunmen get out of jail free
so it's not a matter of if
there's another bullet coming,
it's when?
Why would I go through it
when I can be with my dad again?
I got to get back to my game.
What? What do you mean Kate's alive?
She was declared dead. Julia I.D.ed
her parietal skull bone.
Her DNA checks out.
I ran her prints myself.
Look. Everything's a little
bit complicated just now.
The only thing you need to know
is that Kate is alive
and safe with me at Crows,
where no one can hurt her.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Just give us a little bit more time.
She's not quite herself.
Someone brainwashed her
into thinking
that she was someone else.
- Who?
- Turns out Black Mask
is cosmetics guru Roman Sionis.
He hypnotized Kate into thinking
that she was his daughter Circe.
Kate is Circe Sionis.
Dad, you need to be careful.
We have reason to believe
that Circe's connected to Safiyah.
What? How?
Dad?
Daddy?
- Run!
- Where?
Anywhere. I'll find you.
Miss me?
He was saying
that the DNA checks out,
but Kate thinks she's Circe Sionis
and she's been alive
this entire time
which doesn't actually make sense
because Julia wouldn't lie
to us and say
that she found Kate's skull
because everybody knows
that you can't survive
without a skull!
- Mary.
- Sorry. Just freaking out right now.
Me, too. Pulling up to the Crows.
Luke needs to know that Kate's alive.
I know we did the right
thing saving his life
and I knew he'd have
a lot to work through, but...
Right now, it feels like
we just added to his pain.
It sucks.
I'm glad to have you
on the comms, Batcave.
I'll call you back.
Are you Kate Kane?
Can I get back to you on that?
Need a ride?
Call.
Raise.
I'm out.
Reraise.
All-in.
Oh. Sorry. Do I have you covered?
Yeah. I have a lot more
chips than you.
Look. If you got me beat and you want
to start a little collection
with your buddies here
so you can match my chips
I'll just hang out.
You want to let me in
on the grudge with this?
What? Grudge?
This is just a friendly game.
Okay.
Why haven't I seen you
around here before?
Name's John Diggle.
I'm from Star City.
I'm in town on a contract
with A.R.G.U.S.
Well, hey. Welcome.
Please. Allow me
to remove this little...
Distraction,
who's been playing with us.
Buddy, Gotham City is our town
and the house always wins.
I mean, people do say that.
It's true. The house does win a lot
because it cheats.
But then sometimes, I mean, the house
is just so damn stupid
that it can cheat
and still manage to lose.
The man made a straight.
What no applause
for that, for that
gut-shot straight draw?
I mean and the speech?
No style points for that?
Okay. Whatever.
I've been running
from this fight my whole life...
And it has gotten me nowhere.
First you're up, then you're down.
I don't know if you're
gonna take any comfort
from this, Jake, but, now,
you're down and out for good.
True for both of us, Black Mask,
unless you think Gotham's
gonna buy its zit cream
- from a psychotic gang leader.
- Tough call. It's a good zit cream.
On the topic of hereditary diseases,
Gotham is about to find out
that your daughter, Beth Kane
is none other than
the knife-slinging,
nursery-rhyme-named Alice.
My people will make sure
GCPD is on your doorstep
before you can clear this up.
GCPD on my doorstep?
You know what?
That's a fantastic idea. Gentlemen.
If you try to blow the whistle
on the Sionis family,
not only will the public
think you're as crazy as
your daughter,
but the GCPD will,
misplace any evidence
you happen to dig up
and I will personally make sure
that any family you have left
suffers immensely.
Jacob Kane, you're under arrest
for aiding and abetting
the criminal at large known as Alice.
Come on.
Is this what you really wanted?
I'm taking my money back.
That's enough!
Easy, Star City.
- It's not your fight.
- He won.
You saw the blatant disrespect
at the table.
In Gotham City, we hold the line
against punks like this.
I hear you shot him the other day,
and now you're upset that
he's not showing you respect?
I never thought I'd see you again.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
I think she's still
trying to figure things out.
Oh. Yeah. Of course. Right.
Just any questions you have, I'm here
or not, you know.
I'm not trying to smother you.
- I need a drink.
- I...
Did you find my dad?
No. She said a bunch
of False Face goons raided the joint.
Then she described someone
wearing a hair chain
and holding two big-ass swords.
- Tatiana.
- She thinks Tatiana wanted Alice.
Alice was at the Crows
with, with my dad?
- Literally, what is happening?
- Kate?
Okay. Don't get too excited.
There's still a lot
she doesn't remember.
Sophie.
So, Alice just told
you about some mug
and that was it, really?
Alice? Really?
Where is my father?
Okay. Let's chill.
Just give her a minute.
Hey. We know it's a lot.
Maybe you should sit down.
Yeah. That sounds good.
Beth?
Where are you?
Where did you go?
I think you've caused
quite enough trouble.
Hey, Kate. You're good.
You're safe, okay?
No!
You just carry one
of those around?
Oh, yeah. Syringe chock full
of benzos?
Comes in handy in Gotham.
- Everyone okay?
- Everyone but Kate.
What the hell happened?
I think Kate and Circe
are duking it out in her head,
- and Circe's winning right now.
- So, if Alice is the lynchpin
to jogging more of Kate's memories
- and Safiyah has her...
- No, no, no.
Even if I could stomach the idea
of saving Alice's life right now,
Safiyah came all the way from Coryana
for the pyro who torched
her entire kingdom,
so what could we possibly offer her
that would be better than that?
- Gotham steakhouse gift card or...
- She could rebuild that kingdom...
If I give her the Desert Rose.
Ryan...
No. It's your last connection
to your mom.
You're really willing to do that?
Willing is pushing it.
More like we don't have
anything else to bargain with.
Even if you're willing
to make the trade,
how do we even find her?
Maybe this is a good excuse
to show Luke
just how badly his friends need him.
Hey. You good?
Yeah.
Your old man's Lucius Fox, right?
Put together some details
when you were having
that friendly game of hold them.
You lost your old man young.
That's, that's hard, man.
That's real hard.
My old man was a marine
deployed overseas
when I was a boy, killed in action.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- It's all right.
But it left me with a lot of
questions about him and me,
so I get it when those questions
become more important
than anything else in the world, man.
Believe me, I get it.
What you have to remember is that
we all end up in the same
place eventually, man,
and you'll see your father soon
enough.
What changes with time
is what you get to tell him
you did while you were on the earth.
Okay. So...
I'm just supposed to ignore the fact
that I'm still angry as hell?
No, brother. Don't ignore it. Use it.
You carry the torch
for the great Fox family.
You stand for justice.
You're gonna need anger
to win that fight.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Just some, fogginess, dizziness.
Something's not right.
Lifetime of anger has its side
effects, you know what I mean?
You know we have a world-renowned
neurology department
at Gotham General?
I can get you a connect if you want.
That's actually why I'm here.
Have an appointment in the morning.
Is it supposed to do that?
No.
That's highly unusual.
- In fact, I think it's...
- It's morse code.
- Need...
- Fox... Help.
I should go.
You know, you seem pretty
important for a man
who's trying to get his
ass kicked in an alley.
Good thing you're alive.
Thanks.
Take care of yourself, Luke Fox.
Hello. This is Dana DeWitt,
and I'm coming to you live
from Grand Street downtown
outside of GCPD headquarters.
Earlier today, we got word
of the shocking arrest
of former Crows Commander
Jacob Kane
who is rumored to be... There he is.
Mr. Kane,
is it true you're the father
of one of Gotham's
most notorious monsters?
It's not like that, Dana.
Yes, she's my daughter
and her name is Beth.
She's not a monster.
She's a victim of evil men and women
who stole her childhood
and manipulated her mind
of a father who... who didn't
come through for her
when she needed him.
Beth has had the hardest life
of anyone I've ever known
and yet...
she has this humanity inside of her.
I can't imagine ever
having that strength
so if Gotham is angry at me,
then so be it.
I ask only this of them as a father.
When you judge Alice for her crimes
remember Beth.
She's in here, my queen.
My dear...
I believe you owe me an island.
This is deep.
How many times you get hit?
You should've saw him, okay?
Didn't realize poker
was a contact sport.
Wasn't there an emergency?
Safiyah's holding Alice
somewhere in Gotham,
so we need
your brilliant decoder brain
to figure out how to find her...
and save her.
Okay. I give up.
What are you not telling me?
Kate's still alive.
There's nothing left of Coryana.
Your scorching was
thorough and complete.
Nine villagers perished in the blaze,
so if you have managed
to maintain a list
after all these years,
do include them in your grand total.
You told me you had my sister.
- What did you expect?
- If I'm honest, that,...
a tantrum...
because at the end of the day, Alice,
you're just a spoiled child
who believes she deserves
more than she's earned.
What is this?
- Chill. I come in peace.
- Let her in.
What are you doing here?
I've had this plant a long time.
I didn't even know what
it was or what it could do
until recently,
but even before I knew,
it was my favorite thing
in the whole world.
- And why is that?
- A woman I counted as my mother,
she died a while back,
and this plant was
my last connection to her.
And yet you brought it to offer
in what I presume is
a trade for Alice?
Your enemy.
Alice is the key to getting
her sister's memories back.
The choice is easy.
Revenge is short-lived,
but rebuilding your island,
it's a no-brainer.
What I don't understand
is what's in this for you.
I see someone giving up
her most valued possession
to save a woman she hates
to unlock the memories
of another woman
she doesn't even know.
It's either remarkable
or remarkably stupid.
I know what Kate Kane stands for
and I owe a debt
to the symbol she created.
Found my second chance
at a life because of her.
I've never met her, but...
I believe you'd make Kate Kane proud.
I accept your offer.
If I can't have you,
at least I can have my kingdom.
Thank you... My queen.
I'll make sure to tell Ocean
you send your regards.
Alice, let's go.
It's funny.
Here you are a literal queen
and yet I have my boyfriend
and my sister
and all you have is a little flower.
Oh, there you go again, believing you
deserve more than you've earned.
What did you do?
Where's Tatiana?
Don't play dumb, Alice.
You always knew deep
down a girl like you
could never be worthy
of having it all.
Hey. Easy.
We brought you to a place
we thought you'd be more comfortable.
- You kind of lashed out at Mary.
- I did? Is she okay?
She's fine.
She's worried about you.
Who am I?
- Whose face is this?
- We'll get to that.
Do you remember anything
you've been
put through all these months?
- Why are you here?
- Because you don't seem
to want to stay in there
like a good girl
so now we're gonna have
to do things the messy way.
Hey. Are you okay?
Can I get you a glass
of water or something?
I'm gonna need something
stronger than that.
There's an amazing bottle
of tasteless vodka
in my office desk, bottom drawer.
Would you mind?
- I'll go check.
- Thank you.
- Ocean isn't answering his phone.
- I don't care.
You heard what Safiyah said.
And I didn't give up my plant
so you could run off
to your boyfriend.
- Get in the car!
- Or what?
You'll kill me,
drag me against my will?
You need me alive and cooperative.
I don't need you.
Your sister needs you.
If she really is back
to being Kate Kane
then my disappointing her
will come as no surprise.
Ocean? Ocean?
So, Safiyah took her
little magic knife
out of you
so you could stick it in me.
That's sweet. You can keep it.
This isn't the magic one.
Ocean?
No, no, no.
You're safe? How
is that even possible?
Blackgate's worst offenders are
all people that you put there.
Judge granted my petition
for change of venue.
I'm being transferred to Metropolis.
Okay. That's a start.
I'll start making calls,
line up character witnesses and...
Mary, we're not gonna
beat these charges,
not with Roman Sionis
pulling the strings
and Alice's reputation
hanging over me.
She earned that reputation, not you,
so you don't deserve to take the fall
for the things that she did.
Mary, I want you to
promise me something.
Seeing Kate and Alice
together gave me hope.
When I saw how Kate was buried
under this grotesque
stranger named Circe
I understood the same thing
must have happened to... to Beth.
If Circe and Alice go away,
we can get Kate and Beth back.
There's only one person
- who can make that happen.
- Dad...
I understood she took a lot from you,
took a lot from all of us, but...
I just wish you could have seen Beth
before the accident.
Hoping one day you get the chance to.
That's why I'm counting on you
to save both your sisters.
No pressure!
Never had to worry about you before.
Not gonna start now.
I love you, Mary.
I love you too.
Remind me to never do
a serial killer a favor again.
I'm sorry you lost your plant.
I know it meant a lot to you,
seeing as I babysat it.
Okay. The plant does not
matter to me right now.
I know you want to see Kate,
but I got something to say.
I am so sorry
for what happened to you.
I have no idea what it's like
to walk in your shoes,
but let me make something very clear.
I am not sorry I made sure you lived
so screw your choice.
You're not leaving me.
- Hey. Did you see Kate down there?
- No. We thought she was up here.
I left for two seconds
to get her something
and when I came back, she was gone.
When did you get in?
I've been calling everybody
looking for you.
Am I Kate Kane?
Kate Kane? Who? No. No, no,
sweetheart. You're my baby girl.
Why am I having her memories?
Why do I have her fingerprints
and why do I know where she keeps
her fricking alcohol in her office?
You're having an episode.
Let's practice our grounding
techniques.
Tell me what's happening.
You're having an episode,
sweetheart. Please.
Tell her, Roman, or I will.
I've always held the belief
that a woman has a right to decide
exactly who she wants to be.