Dear Kate...
It doesn't feel real to say goodbye.
Unbeknownst to us,
Julia Pennyworth spent months
with a recovery team
combing the ocean floor
for any sign of you.
She found something caught,
a parietal skull bone
in the shores outside of Bludhaven,
had three different labs match it
to your DNA.
It was enough to confirm
you were gone
and since I can't exactly
be there to say
goodbye in person, I'll say it here
in the place where I feel like
I know you the best
and since I can't lay flowers
at your gravesite either,
I have another idea.
This plant was my connection
to my mama.
Then it turned out to be
more than a plant.
It's a desert rose from Coryana
probably snuck over to the states
by an islander named Ocean
who eventually gave it
to my ex for safekeeping
who then gave it to me,
having no idea that its serum
was actually a miracle cure.
Like you, this plant is one of a kind
and like you, it gave me
a second chance.
Beyond all earthly words
and songs of blessing,
praise and comfort.
So now when I look at it,
I won't just think of my mama
I'll think of Kate Kane.
I'll think of the woman who saved
a hell of a lot of people
the woman who created
a family for everyone
the woman who would keep us
from surrendering to our demons,
the woman who inspired people
to stay true to themselves
even when it felt impossible
to always be there
whenever someone needed them
who brought out our humanity,
even in the darkest of moments
and the woman who changed me.
Like everything good in my life
I thought my time
as the bat was temporary
but it's for real now
and I'm not in your shadow anymore.
I'm it.
I am Batwoman.
Goodbye, Kate Kane.
Thank you for changing my life.
May your memory be a blessing.
May her memory be a blessing.
Your family has declared
you dead, Kate Kane...
But sit tight.
We'll make them believe
in life after death.
- Rolling?
- Okay. Here they come.
Nice and tight on Forbes, please.
Commissioner Forbes, it's not news
that the GCPD
has been working tirelessly
to put snakebite dealers behind bars,
but it's now rumored you're getting
your help from Batwoman.
- Can you comment?
- There's no question
we will put a stop to Snakebite
and its manufacturers,
the False Face Society.
But this drug,
it has its teeth in people.
It's addictive,
it's sexy and it's lethal.
The last I checked, Dana, the GCPD
was never one to turn down
a little extra help
from a vigilante.
Now I have a ten-hour
budget meeting to get to.
I'm actually here to talk about
that budget meeting, commissioner.
Oh, goody. Let me guess...
You want to defund the police.
Defunding the police
means reducing your budget
in areas like officer bonuses
and cannabis regulation
and redistributing the funds
to things like mental health
education, employment, housing.
Where do you think
the money comes from
every time we have to
clean a building
you and your friends graffiti tag?
Got it. So spray paint
will get your attention
but not your own officers
killing four unarmed black men
- this year alone?
- It's an elected position, sweetie.
You don't like me? Run.
Right?
I've never had sweet potato
pancakes before
but if I had
these would be my favorite.
It's all about the skillet.
Thank you for this
and for letting me cry
at odd hours of the day
and letting me finish
all the ice cream in the freezer.
I'm gonna need that
replaced actually.
No way.
These past few weeks, you know,
have been really, really tough.
But somehow, it all feels
a little less awful
when you're around
and I know Luke feels it too
so thank you.
You and Luke
you saved my life.
We have to take care of each other.
Yeah.
Got it.
- It smells so good in here.
- Yeah.
Ang?
What are you doing here?
Didn't mean to interrupt,
but I did, so I was
hoping we could talk.
There's nothing left to talk about.
Well, then maybe just listen
because I'm trying to say I'm sorry.
Okay. I am gonna take this
and these downstairs
out of earshot...
Maybe.
I... I said some
pretty awful things
to you a while back.
Well, I mean, in your defense
you were in the process
of dumping me.
Ryan, you worked with the Crows
to lojack my phone.
Ok. I know you didn't just come
all this way to relive this...
I miss you.
You've always been my constant,
and you made every
crappy group home
feel like a real home.
And then Cora adopted you,
and I was, like, on my own, crushed
but happy for you.
I... I just couldn't
fight to keep you then,
but...
Now I can.
Ang...
I am moving forward in my life.
And as long as you keep
doing your thing
slinging Snakebite
we don't work.
I'm getting out.
You said you couldn't get out.
No. I said I didn't want to
but False Face found out that Ocean
taught me how to make Snakebite.
And with Ocean M.I.A.,
they wanted me to open my own lab,
but I don't want to be
the Walter White of Gotham city.
I found someone
worth turning my life around for.
Just...
Think about it
because I know
my mind is already made up.
Kate Kane sat on a wall.
Kate Kane had a great fall.
All the bat's gadgets
and all the bat's men
couldn't put Kate together again.
It's a pity you're coming
all the way from Coryana
just to die.
Should have figured
you were in here.
I'm sorry. What is happening?
Don't be silly.
You invited me for tea.
We've got extra eyes!
Come on! We got to go!
We're coming for you!
Commissioner Forbes' chalk outline
represents one of the most
brazen criminal events
in recent Gotham history.
I'm joined by Janus cosmetics
CEO Roman Sionis.
Mr. Sionis, I understand
you have something
you'd like to say
to the Gotham public.
Yes. Thank you, Dana.
You know, it shouldn't take
a businessperson to step in here,
but I have made a career
out of concealing blemishes
and quite frankly,
the makeover this city needs
comes from an ugly
I've never seen before.
So, yes, I am here
to speak on behalf
of the people without a platform
like the hundreds who work for me
who say they're scared
to death, Dana.
They are scared to death
of the criminal element
lurking behind masks,
but I'm not here
to beg for help today.
I'm here to offer it.
To the law enforcement
in charge of protecting us,
what can we do?
How can we help you?
Because enough is enough.
The gangs in the city are stupid
but not kill the commissioner stupid.
It's common knowledge that
Forbes was having an affair.
I wouldn't eliminate
lady spite killing.
Or any recently released inmate
who may feel
like Forbes screwed them over.
License plates, facial rec.
Any vehicle that didn't
stop long enough
at a stoplight last night
gets put through the system.
- I don't get it.
- I thought he was gunned down
- on those steps.
- He was.
Where the hell's the commissioner?
There's nothing there.
Hang on. Go back.
Check out the timestamp.
Someone scrubbed five minutes
on both sides of the murder.
You got to be kidding me.
I want the name
of everyone in this city
with access to this feed.
So whoever shot the commissioner
has access to the city's CCTV.
This was a well-planned execution.
Wait. Rewind again.
Look at the far right after the jump.
- Someone tagged it.
- Can you get a closer angle at that?
- Yeah.
- Someone could have been
tagging the building
while the shooting was happening.
Then got the hell out of dodge,
left behind work in progress.
Which means the tagger
could have seen the shooter.
And the shooter could have seen them,
so how do we track down
a potential witness and protect them
solely off the words
"defund the police?"
- I think I found it.
- Literally how?
Social media. Figured the "x"
inside the "o" and monochrome
on top of the neon
was some sort of signature.
Definitely could be the same artist.
I'll get the user's info.
Hey!
So...
We just gonna act like Angelique
didn't come by yesterday, or...
- Yep.
- I thought that was over.
It was. Major dumper's remorse.
You were listening?
Well, you know, just in case
I had to step in and defend.
So spill. We taking her back?
I don't know.
I love her.
She's a huge part of my life.
But?
Hey, I'm in.
So no real name.
It's someone's Finstad
but I matched the login information
to another profile.
Jordan Moore.
You don't think she's
any relation to...
Sir, where are you?
the commissioner was assassinated
and that pompous ass Roman Sionis
is getting more airtime
then the Crows commander.
Maybe you should release
a statement or something.
Call me!
what the actual hell?
Jordan!
What is happening?
I saw Commissioner Forbes
get gunned down.
What?
Look. I... I didn't know
where else to go.
I'm... I'm scared to go home.
I feel like I'm being followed.
Hey, hey. I got you.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Let's go upstairs.
I'll take your witness statement.
Are you kidding me? I'm not giving
my name to the Crows.
I may as well just do
a sit-down with Vesper Fairchild.
Do you have any idea
what a huge deal this is?
There's no other witnesses.
I don't care.
The Crows don't keep people
like me safe and you know it.
I came to Sophie,
my sister, for help,
not Sophie the crow.
- Get down!
- Told you they were following me!
Who's they?
Now is when you pull your gun!
Damn.
You're Batwoman.
It's False Face.
So the commissioner's
hot take on Snakebite
got his ass killed.
How did you know we were here?
Jordan wasn't at her place
so I hoped she went
to her sister for help.
Apparently False Face
had the same idea.
Sorry. How, how do you
know my life?
I've seen your skills around Gotham
and I know you were tagging
city hall last night.
Seriously?
Girl, so not the point right now.
I need you to tell me
everything you saw.
You don't get it. I snitch,
it comes back to me.
They saw me there.
They'll know it was me.
The costume party
on the ground tells me.
They already know it was you.
You can trust her.
There were three dudes.
Two got out of the car
and gunned down Forbes,
one in a gas mask
and one in a hockey mask
- and then a driver.
- Was he wearing a mask?
She. Yes. A... a baby doll thing.
So it could be literally anyone.
It isn't enough.
You're off the hook.
Consider yourself lucky.
Don't know if it helps,
but I saw the driver's bracelet.
It was a big gold key.
It looked ritz.
Everything OK?
Get her somewhere safe.
I'll figure this out.
You and your friend,
go tell your boss we're good here.
The girl will keep her mouth shut
and you will leave her alone.
You're not real, this tea's not real,
and this cup is...
- Not real.
- Correct, but...
You don't want reality.
That's the point.
No... I just spent the last two weeks
in the bowels of a ship
trying to escape
a godforsaken island.
Trust me.
If I were to conjure up some fantasy,
this would not be it.
You mean the same island
you risked everything
to get to in order to see me again?
Well, here we are.
Of course. I ask the universe
for my sister
and this is what I get.
I'm not sure why that's surprising.
You never get what you want.
Cheers to that.
Nothing about your plan
unfolded the way you wanted.
After we left you in this cell
for 11 years,
you set out to make sure your
family never left you again.
But Dad helped lock you
at Arkham and I'm dead.
Am I so mentally disturbed
that my imagination created you
to rub it in?
You created me because
you were always the one
who got us into trouble,
but I was always
the one clever enough
to get us out of it.
- What trouble?
- Your pain.
What if I told you I had a way
to make it disappear?
Ang, open up. It's me.
Hey.
You said you were getting out, Ang!
Okay.
Your energy
is super intense right now.
Who killed the commissioner?
What were you thinking
driving the getaway car?
Who else knows?
That is not the appropriate response
to what I just said.
You want me to end up dead?
- Who else knows?
- I do!
That should be enough!
I don't even know what
I was doing there.
I said I wanted out,
and they were willing to let me go
if I just did this one last thing.
They gave me a mask, keys
and an address.
Am I supposed to
believe you right now?
When have I ever lied to you?
If my name is out,
False Face will kill me
to protect themselves.
Then out them.
Turn in the actual killers.
Tell the court what you just told me.
You didn't know.
False Face is run by a psychopath
named Black Mask
who will leave me for dead in a sewer
before I ever get on a witness stand.
I can protect you.
You?
How?
This is going to sound...
Insane...
But...
I know Batwoman.
How do you think I know
you got wrapped up in this crap?
You and your comic book heroes.
Yeah. Well, thanks to me
and my comic book heroes
your ass has an out
if you're willing to take it,
but you need to take it.
Can I think about it?
What do you mean
you're letting her think about it?
She just gunned down
the commissioner.
She drove the getaway car.
Oh, right.
She didn't pull the trigger.
She just stepped on the gas. Yes.
Please give her
all the time she needs.
Ryan's right. If Jordan testifies
against False Face, they'll kill her.
But if Angelique does,
Jordan doesn't have to.
Exactly. Ang just needs time.
She'll make the right decision.
She could have gone to the cops
when you were busted
for her drugs on you.
- She didn't.
- She's changed.
You literally just said the words,
"she drove the getaway car."
Okay.
You have my back, right?
I've been down this road before
with another Batwoman... Kate...
and she found every excuse
in the book
to justify her twin sister's actions.
And you've always been
the one to remind me
that my mom died because of it.
Angelique is not Alice.
No one is ever Alice until they are
because someone let them be.
Maybe you don't have to wait
for Angelique to turn herself in.
You can do that for her.
You all are supposed to be my team.
What do you mean? We are your team,
which makes you our leader.
This is it. This is your chance
to make the right call.
I'll give Angelique an hour to talk,
but after that,
I'll call the cops myself.
No. I personally
never thought Safiyah
was responsible for
Kate's plane blowing up.
Not her M.O.
The NTSB concluded
that based on the weather
and the atmosphere, it was
likely a lightning strike
that knocked out the controls.
A recalled circuit breaker
could have sparked
an electrical fire in the cockpit.
I take it. I'm reading their report
because you don't believe that.
Over the last few months,
I've discovered
that one of my daughters
was Batwoman
while the other ran an
illegal underground medical clinic,
so I'm not taking anything
at face value anymore.
Sir...
I... I can't even imagine
what you must be feeling
as a father right now,
but Kate would want
you to find peace.
Then eliminate each
and every one of her enemies
who could have done this
or find me the one who did
so I can kill him myself.
And... If I find nothing
that contradicts this report,
then will you please accept it
as what I believe it is?
A horrible and tragic accident?
Convince me I'm wrong
and I'll let this go.
This is your idea of a safe space?
I need a drink
and you only have expensive wine
I'm not allowed to look at.
You wouldn't even be
in any danger right now
if you hadn't been out tagging again.
It's how I express myself.
Then grab a notepad.
Defacing property is illegal.
Oh, my god.
Why did Batwoman have to save me?
I... I was having more fun
having a crowbar swung to my face.
Sounds like y'all could stand
to be less sober right now.
Two club sodas.
Vodka with a vodka back.
Ryan, this is
my little sister Jordan.
So you were saved by Batwoman.
- That's dope.
- Yeah. I mean, it was... Fine.
Fine?
- It's Batwoman.
- Yeah.
But she's so... Cringe.
At least she ditched the party wig.
Harsh words for someone
who just saved your life.
- She's one of them.
- One of who?
Cops, Crows, the law.
Just another suit
who shoots first and asks later.
Okay...
Then...
How will you stop
Gotham's crime problem?
Before it starts.
Currently, I'm working
with grassroots organizations
to get funding
for a community center off skid row.
I'm on a council to move money
to neighborhood-led
safety initiatives
and I phone bank
for no new jails in Gotham city.
This one's on the house.
She's... Passionate.
I can see that.
Let's go.
Okay.
So... The vibes are there
and sis just came out of the closet.
What are you talking about?
This is me being your wing woman,
in case you missed it.
Mom told you?
Just because she needs to take
time with it
doesn't mean I do.
Thank you.
So...
Bartender chick? Fire.
Nope. Not happening.
Not even an enemies-to-lovers maybe.
You're gonna have to swipe right
on someone eventually.
I got to make a call.
Stay put.
Hey, I need you to ask
a favor of your associate.
She doesn't really do favors per se.
I think Batwoman has intel
on a member of False Face.
Perp, I'm looking into was wearing
some kind of key bracelet.
Seemed to ring a bell with her.
Why not use the Crows?
It'll take forensics months.
Luke, False Face just
executed the commissioner
in cold blood because he
spoke out against Snakebite.
I'll see what I can do.
Why didn't you just tell her?
Because Ryan told us she's got this.
I know, but wouldn't
it just be easier
if Sophie handled it?
Angelique is Ryan's
lesbian Achilles heel.
She's not gonna
turn her over to the authorities
and this way,
we don't have to either.
We told Ryan we'd
hold her accountable
and that doesn't mean going behind
her back the first chance we get.
Definitely didn't have
Luke puts his faith
in a snakebite dealer
on my bingo card.
I'm putting my faith in Ryan.
You were right. We're the bat team,
and the only way it works
is we have each other's back
even if we don't always agree.
I'm really glad you're calling.
You were right.
I got into this thinking
I'd found some...
Version of a family.
I never signed up
to watch someone get gunned down.
Then you're ready to make it right.
Who killed the commissioner?
You really friends with Batwoman?
I'm here.
We need to find a safe house
for Angelique
until the real killers
are behind bars.
I know an underground clinic
that's not being used at the moment.
Perfect. Anything else
anyone wants to add?
Starts with an "s,"
ends with me saying,
"I told you so"?
Even if we don't agree
with the method,
we have to trust you
to make the hard decisions.
We're a team.
Angelique?
They got to her.
Angelique Martin,
I understand you're interested
in leaving the False Face Society.
A word to the wise.
That's what leaving looks like.
Angelique's phone sent a signal
from the west yard
30 minutes ago, then died.
So she's somewhere
inside a janky, old sawmill?
Gotham bad guys wouldn't
have it any other way.
Tell me about it.
Found her.
Batwoman, I think they found you.
- You. You okay?
- Ask them that.
Batwoman, come in. Are you there?
Don't, no. Please, please. Help me.
Oh, my god.
Luke.
They must have taken my comms.
Find the witness, bring her to me.
Very simple task...
And you failed.
Consider this
your termination notice.
No, no, please. Come on.
No, please, please.
Stop it, stop it. Please!
Oh, god! please, please!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Next!
what the hell are you doing?
It's an H.R. Matter.
What are you Osha?
I'm here for your prisoner.
Let her go. She's not like you.
Oh, please. Enlighten me.
Who am I?
You're a sadistic drug lord.
Okay. I can see
why you might think that,
but it's Gotham
that's sadistic, not me.
And they say
the best way to change the system
is from within.
You're not changing crap.
And you are?
I'm doing my best every damn day!
your best isn't good enough
and I know that better
than anyone.
My daughter was imprisoned
by the Crows
and killed by Batwoman.
I never killed anyone.
But you've taken on the symbol
of the woman who did.
So tell me, is that change
or is that just pandering
to a sick city
that worships
extremist Crows and bats?
Maybe you wouldn't bother me
so much if I said I was a squirrel.
You've really convinced yourself
this creepy mask is a symbol for,
what, a concerned citizen?
No.
It's a symbol of liberation
from people like you,
people who think they'll
never be held accountable
as long as they pretend
that what they do is justice.
Look. We all have pain in our past.
You can't use it to do this.
I promise you if you let us go
I will find out
what happened to your daughter.
There will be accountability.
There will indeed.
But not because of anything you did.
Thank you!
Got an SOS from Luke.
He said your comms went off.
You're safe now.
I got you.
Damn. Ryan was actually serious.
Angelique's gonna take down
False Face
and we're gonna protect her.
What is this?
- That would be my confession.
- Come on.
We both know you didn't pull
the trigger on Forbes.
A witness saw you drive
the getaway car.
Why confess to a crime
you didn't commit?
I knew the Crows were dumb.
I didn't know they were deaf too.
If you give me the names
of the shooters right now,
I can help arrange a plea deal.
You could go free.
I killed Forbes
I pulled the trigger
and I acted alone.
Now read me my damn rights
and take me to jail.
Why throw away your life for a gang
that doesn't give a crap about you?
Want to tell me what I'm missing?
Your sister's at the bar.
She can throw them back.
Not who I'm looking for.
Your girl Angelique,
she wanted me to give you something.
Please just talk to me
Oh, I know these...
Why do you have this?
where's Angelique?
She's on her way to jail.
- I'm sorry.
- What did you do?
she confessed.
- She's taking the fall.
- It was your job to stop her.
Trust me I tried.
She knew she would
have been protected.
Why would she destroy
the rest of her life
to cover for a bunch
of False Face thugs?
Because apparently
Black Mask threatened
to kill a certain bartender
that Angelique had been texting
with to get back together.
Angelique was willing
to risk her own life,
but there was one thing
she wasn't willing to risk...
You.
I'm sorry.
You know she didn't do it.
You can't let her get away with it.
That's how the law works.
And that's exactly why
all these systems are broken.
You're right.
So what are you gonna do about it?
I don't know,
but I know that
can't be the way it is.
Hey. When did you become so wise?
When you stopped seeing me
as your little sister.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but you'll always be my little sis.
Hi. I'm agent Julia Pennyworth.
I'm investigating the crash
of flight GC9K23.
Yeah. Agent Pennyworth.
We spoke about this last month.
I'm sorry?
You called last month inquiring
about the third loader.
I explained it was a reporting error.
We only employ two loaders
at national city's private airport.
I think you've mistaken me
for somebody else.
I just started
my investigation today.
Julia, right? It's Kurt.
We talked about your accent.
We both used to summer camp
in Oxfordshire.
Why don't I remember
speaking with you?
When we learned Kate was gone
I asked myself what my legacy
would be as Batwoman
but that wasn't the right question.
The question isn't
who am I in the suit.
It's who am I out of it.
Two days ago, I didn't know.
Bruce Wayne had
the bat code for himself.
I'm declaring the three rules
of the bat team.
Rule number three.
We've got each other's backs...
Always.
- Works for me.
- Me, too.
So if we've got each other's back,
that means rule number two.
We hold each other accountable.
Like you did for me today.
Most importantly, we stand
for something bigger than ourselves.
It's a little easier said than done.
What are you thinking?
Batwoman takes some
of the awful off the streets
but the bat team needs to
replace it with something positive.
That's how change happens.
Getting adopted by Mama Cora,
that was my game changer
but Angelique didn't have that.
We are going to take down
Black Mask and his False Face gang.
But what are we gonna bring to Gotham
that no other guy comes along
and gets his hooks in other kids?
Jordan Moore is working
on building a community center.
I want us to bring it to life.
What do you say?
you guys want to help me?
So the key to making
my pain disappear
is to dig up my dead cat?
I am not opening
a dead kitty's coffin.
Then why'd you dig the hole?
Okay. My interest is piqued.
What is happening?
This is what you do, Alice.
What you did that day in your cell
when you learned to sew faces
using human flesh?
Then you did it again when you found
your mother's head in a freezer.
I'm having a psychotic break.
When your reality is too much
for you to process,
you imagine things askew,
so they're easier to digest.
You pretend you're
in wonderland drinking tea,
or you black out
your own moral code
to scorch a woman to death
Or you see your dead sister.
I'm not handling Kate's
death very well, am I?
you're in shock
and you know
that once it wears off
you'll be struck
by a tsunami of grief.
How does one deal
with grief exactly?
That's the problem.
You've never done
that before
and you're scared
of what it will make you do.
Or undo.
Spare yourself the pain.
Your mind is limitless, Alice.
If it can make you believe you're
petting your dead cat right now,
it can make you believe anything.
It can make me believe
in a world where Kate never existed.
I can forget you, Kate.
Poor thing.
What happened to her face?
She fought my men while
they were pulling her from the plane.
Didn't go so well for her.
I suppose it's for the best.
Facial recognition
leads to memory recall.
Leave us.
Hello.
My name is Enigma.
You won't be needing this anymore.
It's time to say goodbye...
to Kate Kane.