It's all there.
Tell me where I can find
the Jack Napier painting.
Your painting is being
held by The Collective,
private club of connoisseurs
of outlawed artwork and antiquities.
You want to tie the room together
with a vintage canvas that takes you
inside the mind of
psychotic criminality?
These are the people you need to know.
I want an introduction.
Oh. The top Crow?
Your biggest clients
are in The Collective.
They pay your bills.
You walk up to their doorstep
trying to grab that Napier,
they're gonna ask you for a refund. Unh!
You're from Coryana.
You're gonna tell Safiyah
to give my daughter back.
Unh!
Aah!
I got a report of a guy
lurking around East End
with a spiky pole.
It doesn't concern you, Batwoman.
That so? Because he's
hanging off my line,
so why don't you tell me
what kind of fish I caught?
There's an item I'm looking for.
It's gonna help me find my daughter.
The woman holding her captive
doesn't want me to find it.
Safiyah? She sent this guy?
Weapon fits the M.O. of her assassins,
but I'll confirm after
you hand him over now.
I don't take orders from Crows,
and I got a better shot at finding
Kate Kane before you do.
"All Crows are bastards".
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Morning, Gotham.
Guess the early bird gives us the bird.
Acrobatic art prankster
Wolf Spider was at it again,
rolling his eyes at the entire city
from the top of the Gotham
Century skyscraper
with an iridescent emoji,
millennial hacktivism at its finest
and almost enough to distract us
from an even juicier Bat story.
Another sighting of Batwoman 2.0
and top Crow Jacob Kane together,
this time working in the
East End crime scene.
Are we looking at Gotham's
newest power couple?
No. Jeez.
I thought Batwoman was cool.
Hey. We don't know what they were doing.
Maybe Batwoman was saving his ass.
Thought you might be hungry
after last night's reconnecting.
Still sleepy.
I wish you could do
something about that.
You can take the day off.
Mmm. I can't.
As cute as I look in
your ridiculous robe,
I should get home and change first.
You walk of shaming for me?
Like the old days.
Speaking of the old days,
it's time you got that
apology I owe you.
My partying was out of control,
and you took my stash
thinking it would help me,
and instead, it got
your ass thrown in jail,
and I get why you didn't
want me to visit you.
You served 18 months for me, Ry,
and it's time I start paying you back.
One for you, one for me?
I love it,
but we're good.
You got your life together.
That's all I wanted.
Ohh! Hey. What is this?
It's... a work injury.
You fall on a corkscrew?
Ryan, you need to get that looked at.
Yeah. I just got this job.
I don't need my boss
thinking I can't hack it.
You tend bar. She'll understand.
All these years later
still worrying about me.
It's kind of cute.
- You know what's kind of cute?
- Hmm?
You...
without that nastiness on your shoulder.
You take care of everyone else.
Take care of yourself for once.
Giving you an antibiotic.
So... it's just an infection?
Well, it might have turned necrotic
if you had waited any longer.
Are you sure you're not
having any other symptoms
that you're not telling me about?
No. I...
Maybe a little more tired than normal.
Okay. Okay.
Kate would pop two of these,
and she'd be back in fighting shape.
- Okay. Cool.
- But if you're hurt,
you should sit out a few days.
Right. Did Kate ever sit out?
Kate was never shot with anything
that pierced through the Batsuit,
and you shouldn't
compare yourself to her.
What's my choice, huh?
Everybody else is.
I know you don't have a Twitter,
so I assume you mean Luke.
Just don't tell him about this, okay?
I don't need another reason
for him not to trust me.
He's been questioning
every decision I make.
Not to backseat drive, but aren't you
proficient in 6 different
forms of martial arts?
What's the point of
just leaving him here?
I told him we wanted
the location of Coryana.
He'll give it up. Take
it from a foster kid.
It is amazing how well you behave
when you are literally starving.
We don't have time to wait him out.
If Alice finds Ocean
before we find Coryana,
Safiyah's gonna give Kate to her,
- and Alice is going to kill her.
- Okay. So do your hacker thing
and get some info on the spiky pole guy
to speed this up.
I already tried.
I tracked his movements and confirmed
that he wasn't after Jacob Kane.
He was stalking the guy
that he killed in the alley,
but the victim was an investment analyst
at Gotham Capital with no record.
What's he got to do with Coryana?
Sir, I'm not defending her actions,
but my guess is she's
after what we're after...
Kate's location.
Let her keep Safiyah's thug.
We got a new lead on the Napier...
Evan Blake, old friend of Kate's
and a fixture on the Gotham art scene.
Just flew back from a trip to Berlin.
He was caught a couple of years ago
with plundered artifact and
forced to pay restitution.
In other words, a likely
member of The Collective
who might cooperate.
Commander, you're underselling
our entire origin story.
Katie Kane saved my life.
- Really?
- Gotham Prep.
It's eighth grade, and the winter formal
is a multiverse shattering crisis
because I'm "straight".
Kate was way out by then,
I had this tragic crush,
and I asked her to the dance.
I'm sure she wanted to
roll her eyes so hard,
but with the grace of a saint,
she said yes.
The only time you'll
ever hear teenage Kate
described as a saint.
My parents take me to pick her up,
and Kate is jaw-dropping
in this tailored velvet suit,
just radiating queer confidence.
I on the other hand dissolve
into a monsoon of tears.
Kate races me up to her bedroom,
and we go through the whole thing.
"I'm gay". "I know".
We make it to the dance,
and I came out by default
because I wore Kate's Alexander McQueen
off-the-shoulder mini,
which begged a lot of questions,
but I wasn't afraid anymore.
I was glowing,
and then Kate ditched me to
make out with Maggie Watson.
Sounds like our girl.
So you need my help with
Kate's disappearance.
I'm here for you.
Kate was looking for a piece of artwork,
something that may have gotten her
on the wrong side of
someone very dangerous.
Our theory is if we find the item
it will lead us to her captor.
Well, you've come to the right art snob.
I was senior editor at the
Gotham Museum of Antiquities,
I curate my own private collections,
I've got my hands in
a bit of everything.
Yeah. We know. Agent Moore.
Kate was looking for a canvas
painted by Jack Napier,
alias the Joker.
You're aware of it, yes?
I know the legend.
Psychotic evildoer breaks into home,
splashes homeowner's guts
all over some old painting
in the foyer and calls it modern art.
It's a bit on the nose if you ask me.
Not to mention illegal
to buy, sell, or possess
since it was stolen from
an active crime scene.
I'm sorry. Should there be a harsh light
shining in my eyes right now?
Because the Kate I knew
never gave a crap about art,
and I haven't spoken with her in years.
We have reason to believe
that you're affiliated
with The Collective.
Heh.
We'll work to get you full immunity
if you help us make contact.
Immunity from what, Ms. Moore?
I'm a perfect angel.
I thought you were here friend.
I love Katie, but this
feels like entrapment.
If you need to contact me again,
I'll refer you to my lawyers.
I want all our tech inside
every device Evan owns,
round-the-clock revolving tails.
Yes, sir, but there could be
an easier way to locate Coryana...
with Batwoman's help.
Let me ask her for
access to her prisoner.
Batwoman or whoever it is
who stepped in for my daughter,
I am not gonna grovel at her feet.
Then let me do it
or at least ask nicely
because Alice will do
a lot worse than grovel
to find Kate before we do.
_
Ocean.
Hi.
What do you call it when you're sure
you've met someone...
You're sure you've never met?
A stay of execution.
♪ There's a full moon,
I'm howlin' tonight ♪
♪ And there's a-blood
on the thorn of a rose ♪
Vodka on the rocks.
♪ Think you're gonna love tonight ♪
♪ Listen, girl, well, I
think you should know ♪
Visiting from Gotham?
Why? Do I look depressed?
You've got the sophistication
of a city mouse.
Heh. Mouse. Ahem. Touchy subject.
Don't you think mice are cute?
I had a mouse in my life.
I loved him like a brother,
and when he started holding me back
from my dreams, I killed him.
Heh.
Shoot. Um...
I think it's my turn to, uh...
♪ You better wait ♪
♪ Before your heart is turned to slate ♪
That is the fastest I've ever
seen him take the hint.
Can I join you
in case he decides to try it again?
Pretty sure he's in the
next county by now,
but by all means.
Last time I came here
to meet a Batwoman,
the vibes... were different.
Please say this isn't a booty call.
Look. I don't know
where you got this idea
that all Crows are bastards,
but some of us are trying
to make a difference.
Well, in my experience,
when the crows fly together,
they call it a murder for a reason.
I want to offer you a deal.
You get everything we know
about Safiyah and Coryana,
and we get access to your prisoner.
So you can beat him
within an inch of his life.
He's a murderer who knows
where Kate's being held.
I'll think about it.
You should be doing everything
in your power to help Kate.
I don't need a Crow telling
me how to do my job.
I'm not speaking to you as a Crow.
Kate's the love of my life,
and I need your help to get her back.
Hell to the no. No.
Working with the Crows
makes my skin crawl.
Screw that. No.
It's not like we're hosting
them a fundraiser.
Trust me. We make a
deal that sounds good,
they'll break it.
Not if we're dealing with Sophie.
Sophie has hauled my
ass in for questioning
so many times she knows
my damn coffee order. No!
Will you talk some sense
into her, please?
We're at a dead end,
Ryan. Look. I'm sorry,
but you're outvoted.
I get it. You want Kate back,
but the Crows have tried
to ruin my life for fun.
I'm not helping them!
Okay. So.
Crows horror stories.
You want me to go, or...
do you want to do yours first?
My girl Angelique had a drug habit,
and on a very ugly night,
she was gone, like a different person,
so I found her stash, and I took it,
thinking I could somehow
straighten her out,
bring her back.
I'm on the street, crying,
no question what kind
of night I'm having,
and I pass these two Crows,
and one of them yells out,
"You'd be cuter with
a smile on your face".
And my mama told me what to do about it.
I pay them no mind and keep moving,
but they... they wouldn't let it go,
so my hand went out, my
finger went up, and boom,
those Crows had what they wanted.
They found the drugs and
thought they were yours.
Sorry that happened to you.
What was yours?
Um... the Crows...
killed my father.
Wait. What?
Really?
Really.
It's, uh, not a story for today,
but, um...
It's the worst thing that
ever happened to me.
I should have let you go first.
Look. I will never forgive them,
and I don't want to
help the Crows either,
but we need them to help us.
Remember, this isn't punishment
just for the sake of it.
Given this murderer
every opportunity to talk,
so unless you have any other ideas,
it's time to take this
to the next level.
You've got some choices.
You can give us the
location of Coryana...
Unh!
You can get us in touch with Safiyah
or the man known as Ocean.
Help us find the Napier painting.
Listen to me.
It is not worth what
they're gonna do to you.
The Many Arms will kill whoever
lays hands on that painting.
You'll never find Coryana.
I never said the two were related.
The painting gets us
to Coryana? Is it a map?
Cyanide capsule!
- Let's get him down!
- It's too late. It's too late.
Kane pushed him too hard,
and now we're at a dead end.
Maybe not.
We've been surveilling a suspect
we linked to the Napier,
and we just got a hit on its location.
A group called The Collective
is having a special exhibition
tomorrow night
to auction the painting off.
Why now?
Word must have gotten back to the owner
about the body that
dropped the other night.
Too much heat.
You doing anything tomorrow night?
You looking for a date to this thing?
We don't have an insider,
but we need someone with
no connection to the Crows
who can infiltrate the event
and grab the Napier
without getting caught.
I go alone.
No Crows at the location,
no surveillance,
and I want you directly in charge
of any Crows assigned to this mission.
This is a one-off. We're not partners.
So... Ocean... what do you do?
I... bore people to death
by telling them
I'm a soil technician.
Ooh. That sounds like a fancy name
for dirt nerd,
but you smiled when you said it,
so... you must like your work.
I grew up in nature.
My family cultivated everything
we ever needed
from the land.
In a place like Gotham,
where everything is concrete,
isn't that incredible?
So tell me,
where is this magical
place you hail from?
♪ And I chase my whiskey
with the blues ♪
I'm meeting an associate.
Should splash some water on my face.
5 shots... no regrets.
Hey. Can I ask you something?
Have we met somewhere before?
Think I'd remember you.
♪ Chase my whiskey with the blues ♪
Probably just thinking
about somebody else.
Oh, well.
Do you mind...
shutting the shade?
You slept through half the day.
5 shots, no regrets.
Shall I explain?
I do wish you would.
Some lunatic on a far-away island
is holding my sister hostage,
and she won't hand her
over until I gut you
and air mail the evidence.
This woman got a name?
Enough women want you
dead I need to be specific?
Just answer the damn question.
Safiyah.
Although her obedient island
followers call her queen.
Not me.
I called her sister.
I have 3 words.
Who... is she?
Ohh! Mm-wha! Look!
♪ We're making snow melt ♪
Wait. Are you sure art collectors
are supposed to have this much swag?
Well, first of all,
they're not art collectors.
They're outlaws, and if
Evan Blake is the style guide,
this party's about to look
like "The Hunger Games".
What's Evan Blake's deal?
Ohh.
He and I were always
angling for Kate's affection.
Nope. He was way more competitive
and had... heh... a
lot more flair than me.
Now he's overeducated, and apparently,
he's addicted to mischief.
The Crows say that he runs
the door for The Collective.
Oh. No.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, I think I can make this work.
I'd say so.
H-Hey. I... I brought the plan...
I... I brought the game plan.
The event is inside a private hangar
at Gotham International.
It's actually a pretty
clever way of doing this.
So The Collective flies in,
they unload their pieces,
they buy, sell, party,
then they load back up, fly away.
No customs, no TSA, maximum security.
How are we sneaking the
Batsuit through that security?
See, we just happen to have VIP access
to every square inch of that terminal.
Yeah. Between Wayne Enterprises
and Hamilton Dynamics,
we burn more private jet fuel
than the Hadids, Kardashians,
and the Air Force combined.
Yeah. So with our resources,
Crows' intelligence, and a secret agent
that no one's going to
suspect... Ryan Wilder.
Wait. I'm just supposed
to talk my way inside?
Oh, no.
Did you think Mary had
all the accessories?
Look at this precision metalwork.
The weight is perfectly balanced.
What's the provenance?
Which Bat did it belong to?
Woman.
- 1.0 or...
- Current model.
The batarang is a stunning piece.
We'll make an exception
and allow it into the exhibition.
Okay. I'm really loving that dress.
Didn't it debut in London?
- Nailed it.
- Huh.
Actually, it was New York, winter '18.
Well, I heard there was a dress code,
so I borrowed it from a friend.
Heard from who exactly?
Of course, I'm a big believer
in the first amendment
except when it comes to
the shenanigans that go on
behind The Collective's closed doors.
Ha ha! Evan baby,
what are you doing to my girl here?
You beat me here.
Ang, big night. Patrons
need their party favors.
Ahh.
And this one's yours?
Yeah. I totally spaced on the heads up.
It's fine. You're forgiven.
Any questions?
Pronouns?
He/him, they/them.
I go with the flow.
Now, you two, go forth and do crimes.
Ang, what are you doing here?
Saving your ass at the door.
You can't just slide into the DMs.
You need a referral.
What party favors was he talking about?
Ang, no.
What do you want me to say?
That you weren't lying
through your teeth
when you told me you'd
pulled your life together.
For your information, I'm clean.
4 months, but do you
know what people need
to pull their lives together? Money.
If you get caught, distribution
is 8-10 at Blackgate.
Says the girl turning Batwoman's
missing hardware
into an Etsy shop.
We know what I'm doing here.
What are you doing here?
Save it.
You are the only one here who's judging.
- Is this thing on?
- Loud and clear.
Want to try channel two?
No, not really.
Batwoman to Moore.
Copy. You're late.
Thought maybe you got cold feet.
Believe it or not, I ran into an ex.
Oh. Okay. Well, I hope
he's not gonna be drama.
She, and always.
Let you know when I find the painting.
Stand by.
Luke... got the target.
Okay. Great.
Give me a good look.
Okay. Moving on to the next phase.
A lot of interest in this one.
Yeah. It's kind of gimmicky, isn't it?
Oh, it's dreadful, zero technique,
but, you know, celebrity artists.
Hmm. Help me to understand the appeal
in owning something like this.
Some of the people here... total sickos.
- And you?
- I don't like being told
what I can and can't do in life.
Whether it's the art I collect
or the clothes I wear,
I'm not desperate for anyone's approval.
Still throwing shade
at my borrowed couture.
Heh. What can I say?
I just prefer to see
everyone's true colors.
So I ran a spectral analysis
to isolate the original canvas
underneath the Gore.
I think it's a painting
of ocean currents.
- You were right.
- The Joker splattered some poor guy
all over a map to Coryana?
But we'll need to restore the canvas
to locate the island.
But that means...
You're gonna need to steal it.
I didn't know Safiyah had family.
We weren't blood.
Apparently, we weren't anything.
Why does she want me dead?
Oh, no offense,
but I have way too much
drama in my life to care.
She's obviously losing
her touch if she sent you.
I'm sorry. Did you just
call me a bad assassin?
Not to Monday morning quarterback,
but you had ample
opportunity to kill me.
You knew I was staying here,
which means you could
have killed me in my sleep,
but maybe you don't
know how to pick a lock.
Fine. Surprise attack
in the bar bathroom...
easy, private.
At the very least, you can
ambush me in my truck.
I have a backseat, and
I don't lock my doors,
but instead, you, what,
make a scene at the bar,
get my attention,
indulge in smalltalk, get drunk.
Heh. Safiyah must be
desperate if she sent you.
I needed more answers
before I could kill you.
I've never seen you before in my life.
Nor I you, which is why
I needed to know more
before I made Ocean bleed the red sea.
How do you even know
what Coryana looks like?
Because I was there 5 years ago.
That's impossible.
I was there 5 years ago.
- How peculiar.
- Hmm.
Well, I suppose you could kill me
and then spend the rest
of your life on the run,
seeing as none of this changes the fact
the island queen still wants you dead,
or we could give her a jingle.
I'm good with option "A".
Safiyah, we both know this
isn't about a stupid flower.
And what do you think it's about?
Me having the one thing you can't.
What the hell was that?
Exactly.
Option "B" it is.
Ahem.
There should be a dispenser
next to the sink
with... uh, you know, products.
I see it.
A lot of firepower in that room,
so you're gonna have to move fast.
Batwoman, status check. You find it?
Target identified. I
just need to take it
for further analysis.
We'll monitor from here.
Uh... Batwoman?
I think we have competition.
Who?
You ever heard of Wolf Spider?
Shoot him before he gets too high!
Miss... Miss, this way, please.
No. Ryan!
Hand it over.
- Hyah!
- Unh!
Ugh!
Damn.
Unh!
Ugh! Ohh.
Painting's on the move.
Do you need medical?
Ugh. Just slow him down. I'll be there.
We're on it.
Nimble little bastard.
Little taser action will slow him down.
Damn it! Get me closer.
I'm on it.
Aw. Fricking cartridge is jammed!
Dude, what did you do?
He jumped in front of me.
Get some ties on him.
This isn't good. Call for medical.
Status check.
Target acquired. We got the painting.
- Let's go.
- What? What are you doing?
We can't leave him here.
Moore wants the painting,
not an excessive force headline.
Let's go.
Someone else will clean him up.
Evan?
Evan! Evan, can you hear me?
We're gonna need
a blood drive after this.
He's gonna recover, right?
Well, considering he was hip
checked by a 4,800-pound hunk
of toxic masculinity,
he's doing great.
Distal femur fracture, dislocated elbow,
minor concussion,
but when the bone shattered,
it nicked his femoral artery,
so if you hadn't been there
to bring him in in time,
he would have bled out.
Okay. What... what happened back there?
You want to know what happened?
I listened to you over
my gut, and now look.
I meant what happened to you?
You sounded like you
were in rough shape.
You called for backup.
This isn't about me.
This is about us,
this team and how I can't keep working
for your approval.
I wanted to suit up
and not think about you comparing
me to Kate Kane for once,
so I agreed to partner with the Crows,
and for what?
You sided with the guys
who killed your old man.
Your taste sucks,
but you know what?
I wear the suit, I take the bullets,
so when I say I have a bad
feeling about something,
you two, listen!
Did her majesty say when
she'd grace us with a callback?
Would you just sit there
without talking?
I have spent more years of my life
in captivity than any elephant
in the Gotham zoo.
The key to surviving...
keep yourself entertained.
Rough childhood?
You could say I come by my
abandonment issues honestly, yeah.
How do you know Safiyah?
I was squatting on a yacht
in Gotham Harbor.
Safiyah's minions were pirating
it while I was on board,
and apparently, she was impressed
by the fight I put up.
And she let you stay?
- Yeah.
- No way.
The island's cardinal
rule is no outsiders.
Hmm.
Why don't I remember any of this?
That's the thing.
You should, and I should remember you.
The fact that we both
have the same memories
makes me think that
Safiyah did something
to get us to forget.
You think Safiyah erased our memory?
Some of them.
The thing is we might never know.
Tell me you ordered delivery
and those aren't 1, 2...
3 assassins approaching.
Hmm.
The Many Arms of Death.
Oh. More relatives of yours, I presume.
Yeah. Can you, uh, cut me loose?
I can't trust you.
You don't trust me to defend
myself from murder?
Where's Ocean?
Hey.
Surprise.
Aah!
Hey. Do you have any cash?
We should probably leave the maid a tip.
You're dark.
Shouldn't have doubted me.
Let's go. You're driving.
Badges of the Crows who did this.
That's not enough,
burn it all down, girl, the whole thing.
I can't do that.
I believe in the mission of the Crows.
An organization that
decides what justice is
based on who can pay the most money,
that beats information
out of its suspects,
that runs someone over
for stealing a painting?
That's what you believe in?
You think two men losing
their jobs isn't enough?
You're right, but I'm fighting
to change the culture.
Yeah? Well, good luck with that,
but if you want to party with me,
add your badge to that
little pile over there.
Until then, this partnership is over.
What about the painting?
Our forensics team is
still working on it.
Don't you want to know where Coryana is?
We'll see who gets there first.
Mary Hamilton. Heh heh. Awkward.
Because I know you're Wolf Spider?
Because I'm pretty sure I'm naked.
Oh, very much so.
Evan, you need to find a better suit.
Spandex is no match for an oncoming SUV.
Mmm. But it's so comfortable.
Then maybe find a safer
excuse to play dress-up.
Gotham's elite take
themselves too seriously.
Who else is gonna eye-roll them
with as much style as me?
The Crows got the painting.
I was stealing it for Kate.
Thought I had a better
chance at grabbing it
than the Crows.
Hey. Don't beat yourself up about it
because it turns out nobody
actually got the Napier painting.
It was a forgery.
- That's impossible.
- No.
Batwoman took a sample
of the organic compound
that was painted over
the original canvas,
and it was pig's blood.
Napier would've never used pig's blood.
Right. So the Crows ended up
with a decoy copy, and the original
is still out there somewhere,
and so is Kate.
Oh, my God.
Once we get some distance
from the Many Arms,
we can try to figure out
what Safiyah did to us
and why.
Looks like you're not as fast
as you think, buddy boy.
They got you pretty bad back there.
Hey. You all right?
Uh... yeah. Eyes on the road.
What's with you?
Nothing.
Can you check in the back real quick?
Is there a white tube back there?
Yeah.
What is this?
You ever hear of a guy
called Jack Napier?
Greg, move your head!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -