Patient A is a 10-year-old male
with stage-IV leukemia.
On January 31st,
he was bitten by a bat
during the attacks in Gotham Square.
And he immediately began
showing signs of sepsis.
Later that night,
he received a dose
of the miracle serum, BP296...
to relieve the sepsis immediately.
He's here today, however,
because we discovered 72 hours later,
that it also cured his stage-IV
Leukemia. Completely.
So today, we've isolated
his white blood cells
in an attempt to siphon and replicate
their curative properties.
We are now mixing them
in our synthetic granulocytes.
And we are now injecting them
into Patient B
an 80-year-old male
with a similar cancer.
Our hypothesis
is that the new solution
will attack his cancer
in the same way.
We'll check back in 24 hours
and look for progress.
We need help in here!
Just try to sit back.
Just try to relax.
Help! Help!
The toxin spread by the bats
was intentionally designed
by Hamilton without a cure.
That serum cured it.
And not just that,
it reversed hereditary conditions.
Eradicated anemia, malaria,
all types of blood diseases.
- We can't replicate it, sir...
- Try again.
Sir, with all due respect,
how many people have to die
for me to make my point?
How many people get to live
if I make mine?
Whatever was in the antidote
for that bat toxin
is gonna change
modern medicine forever.
The supply was exhausted
before we knew its potential
and it can't be synthesized.
It's gone, sir.
Well, it came from somewhere, right?
Do you really think someone's
gonna just hand over
the secret to a miracle cure?
No. I expect they're
gonna cherish it
like it's the most valuable thing
in the world.
- Don't let this door close.
- What's this one's deal?
- Mr. Hellzinger...
- What? What's happening?
Aaron. It's me. It's Dr. Rogers.
Tell... tell me you got a...
Tell me you got a fix, Doc.
Not at the moment, I'm afraid.
I didn't do anything. Help me!
Aaron, you're okay.
You just,
you just had an episode.
- I can't keep living like this.
- That's why I'm here.
There is a cure for you...
and for dozens of other patients
that are cooped up in here.
And Aaron,
you're gonna help me get it.
The role of Batwoman will now
be played by...
Well, we don't actually
know her name.
But 2.0 seems to be
sticking around for a while.
You got some big boots to fill,
new girl.
Hope you like all-nighters.
Hi.
Nobody robs banks anymore?
You got to loot mom
and pop shops?
- Are you good?
- Little busy.
Your heart rate is flooring it
right now.
- If you need back up...
- I need you to let me
do my job right now!
You believe it or not, the pacing?
It isn't healing me.
What the hell is taking them
so long?
Hey, you!
We have been waiting for a doctor
for two hours.
Oh, actually I'm not her attending...
Oh, actually, have you ever heard
of a little issue
in your medical community
called implicit bias?
Sorry, we're coding down
the hall...
- Let me educate you on something...
- Ang, please, he's busy...
It's the reason black women
die of neglect
at a disproportionately high rate
in this country.
We're not having that tonight.
You need to get my girl
some actual care
before you need your own.
I'll find your attending.
Okay.
That was extra.
Also, thank you for bringing me here.
I don't know who else
you'd call at 2.00am.
And if you did...
I would have been a little jeal.
- Yeah.
- Only you, babe.
Miss Wilder. I'm Dr. Rodriguez.
I understand you have an infection?
Yeah.
I've had it a couple of months.
This is really extensive.
- How'd you get this?
- A spider...
At my work's stockroom.
We'll get you some antibiotics.
Should start to clear up
in about 48 hours.
That's it?
When she showed up at my doorstep
she could barely stand.
Run some tests or something.
Unfortunately, her insurance
doesn't cover any bloodwork.
I'll cover it, then.
Someone will be by to draw blood.
You're blowing up.
- Now, you have a shortage of words?
- You know what I do, Ryan.
I don't need you
judging me for it.
I'm not judging you.
I want you to get out while you can.
- Get out?
- Yeah.
Ryan, I trap for the rich and famous.
The things I know about them,
about my plug...
I can't just "get out".
You can if you let me help you.
Look, I got to go, okay?
We'll pick this up later.
To be clear, you think I pulled out
a tube of my lipstick
wrote this note
hunted you down,
and then tossed it at your feet
because I don't have
anything better to do?
Safiyah seems to thinks so.
I told you, I don't have anything
to do with Kate Kane
and I didn't send this note.
And I think if you really believed
I tried to blow up
your sister's airplane...
this conversation would look
a lot more
like you fumbling to kill me again.
I wasn't "fumbling".
I was due-diligencing.
It will be very clear
when I transition to actual murder.
I'm sure. Look, I'm a botanist.
I work alone. I keep to myself.
The idea of picking a fight
with a warlord
sounds like a lot of work.
Trust me, it's a full-time job.
So, why does she think that you tried
to frame her for my sister's death?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
The last thing I need
is to be in the middle
of two crazy bitches
trying to rip each other's hair out.
Have a nice life.
Doesn't it bother you
that we both magically forgot
being on Coryana together?
That there were obviously pieces
of both our memories wiped?
I grow psychedelic mushrooms
for a living.
You think it's the first memory
I've lost?
Did you forget that she has
an army?
Those guys she sent are just
the beginning and you know it.
Even if you run to the ends
of the Earth,
she has plenty of assassins
with pointy weapons
and a lot of frequent flyer miles.
So, why does she think
you framed her?
I trained her army.
I followed her rules.
I was a good little soldier.
And then, I got bored.
You tried to leave.
Not just leave.
I tried to leave with one of her
precious flowers.
I thought I could grow it here,
do some good,
make a decent living.
I got busted and she exiled me.
So, you got to leave, just without
your little green parting gift?
Woke up in Gotham Harbor
with the worst hangover of my life.
Meaning, you don't remember the how,
the where and the with whoms.
Are ready to hear what I think?
I've had an option this whole time?
I think that you didn't get caught
trying to leave the island
with the Desert Rose.
Based on my little hot flashes
I think we got caught...
together.
And I think she let us keep
all our memories...
except the ones, specifically...
of each other.
Can you believe the audacity
of that lawyer?
He knows everything
that you went through with Beth.
And now he's trying to browbeat you
into declaring another daughter dead.
So that he can what,
claim his three percent
of Kate's multi-million dollar
estate?
It's disgusting.
He should have his license revoked.
You know, if this med school thing
doesn't work out
there's always litigation.
Thanks for bringing me.
- Moore, what'd you find?
- The Napier's a fake.
What? How is that possible?
It's pig's blood.
According to our forensics tech,
the real Jack Napier
would've favored a more...
biologically human pigmentation.
So it's a dead-end.
Not exactly.
We found a partial print.
ID'd the forger
to a 30-something male in Gotham.
Well, that means there's
a good chance
he knows a hell of a lot
about the original.
- What's his name?
- Ocean.
The guy Alice was looking for,
and now we know why.
I might be able to track him down
but I need permission
to use the high-frequency
generator receiver.
- Granted. Get it done.
- Copy that, sir.
Okay, I give up.
What's a high-frequency generator
recei...
Not open yet.
Door was.
Good to see you staying
out of trouble.
Good to have your approval
that I don't care about.
Still not open.
I've been building a case
on your girl Angelique Martin.
Looks like Snakebite's
her new money-maker.
Her name's linked
to five outstanding possession cases.
Party kids. No loyalty.
- What do you want, Crow-phie?
- She's the little fish.
I'm looking for her supplier.
A grower linked
to the psychedelic mushrooms
being used in Snakebite.
Goes by Ocean.
- Never heard of him.
- Angelique has.
I saw her at his apartment
before he split.
I just need your help getting
his new location from her.
Sure, I'll just casually
text her and ask.
You don't have to ask her anything.
Once this is within range
of her cell...
it'll install
an invisible high-frequency
generator-receiver app.
Essentially turns her cell
into a digital and audio microphone.
I just need you to get it
close enough to transfer.
You can't be serious right now?
As serious as your girl
doing eight-to-10 at Blackgate.
Okay. First of all...
technology like this should not
exist in a free society.
Second, screw you.
I'm not betraying my girlfriend.
This is the same Angelique
who let you
take the fall for her, right?
Who continues to sell
even after you served time
for being caught
with her drugs on you?
Do the right thing here, Ryan.
I'll get you the information
you want.
And then this file right here?
It disappears.
Is that clear?
I do this, you can't touch her.
You can't protect her forever.
No. But I can protect her
from you.
Is that clear?
Crystal.
- Mary?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
He didn't hurt me.
What is this place?
I don't know.
Looks like some sort
of underground clinic.
Not that I've ever seen one.
Finally.
Okay, hi. First hostage.
Unfortunately, no.
No, I mean me.
I've never done this before.
But if all goes right...
Okay...
I forgot what I was gonna say!
Sorry! Spontaneous rage issues!
My brain's a little wonky.
What do you want?
The antidote. The antidote
Hamilton used on the bat toxin.
We don't have anything to do
with Hamilton Dynamics anymore.
I don't know anything
about the antidote.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to her.
They said it's somewhere
in this underground lab.
So, where is it?
She doesn't know anything
about it either...
Actually, I know literally
everything about it.
There's none left.
No!
I can't kill her. I need her.
Where... where did you get it?
Long story short.
On the night that total bitch
named Alice
poisoned my mom and me...
She gave me the cure a.k.a
the serum
from this fabled island flower.
It's called the Desert Rose.
Okay, but a few months later,
I had this blood...
Let's just call it a transfusion
and it was no longer
in my system anymore.
But unbeknownst to me,
Alice stole a pint
of the transfusion blood.
And on the night of the bat attack,
she gave it back to me.
She gave it back to me
and said it would save everyone
because it still contained
the Desert Rose.
I gave to Hamilton and I told him
to make an antidote.
To my shock, it actually worked.
Why you didn't tell me about this?
Would you have believed me?
I believe you and I need you
to make more.
Don't you think that I tried?
The solution only retains stability
after one generation.
Hamilton doctors could extract it
from my blood
to treat patients with it.
But once it's been extracted
from the second bloodstream
it loses its curative properties.
Trust me. I would love nothing more
than to be the one who finds
the cure for blood disease.
You're not learning all this
at Gotham U, are you?
No, Dad. I'm not.
Oh, God. This isn't the way
that I wanted to tell you.
But I've been practicing
underground medicine for two years.
What do you mean
underground medicine?
I mean, the reason why he's here
looking for the antidote...
is because the antidote came
from here.
This is my clinic.
Damn it.
Oh, I know your client
is a major star
and way too busy
to walk to an ATM.
But that still doesn't change
the fact
that I don't use cash apps.
This isn't her
save the pigs charity. Bye.
What?
You kept the plant I gave you.
What, like, five years ago?
You're soft, babe.
How are you feeling?
Hopeful.
Because...
- I don't get it.
- It's your uniform.
For your new job at the Hold-Up.
It's legit and I can protect you.
- Well, you will protect me.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Because you said you wanted out.
This is me giving you a way out.
That's very, very sweet, Ry.
Good, because you start tomorrow
and gays order some weird-ass drinks
- that you have to learn how to...
- I don't want out.
- Wait, but you said that...
- I lied.
I like my job. I'm good at it.
People actually respect me.
What people?
You sling to influencers.
Sorry, I'm not living up
to your moral standards.
But some of us didn't get
Brangelina'd
- from the group home.
- What is that supposed to mean?
Somebody found you, Ry.
And you got a new life.
I didn't.
I didn't know what it felt like
to be found by something.
Now, I do.
- I went to prison for you.
- And I have apologized for that.
It doesn't count
if you don't change... Oh, my...
- I can't. The room is spinning.
- Ry.
- What... what... what can I do?
- My medicine is in the bathroom.
What is happening to me?
I think they're underneath
the sink.
- I don't see them.
- Are you sure?
They should be under there.
They were
in the medicine cabinet.
I need to go check
in on some people.
Take these, please.
And I'm not saying
that as some "shady dealer".
Consider this mis-filed.
I know this was hard for you.
But you don't, though.
Because you don't know
what we've been through.
I know you're right back
in the exact same situation
you already served time for
and you're choosing to stay there.
Why?
You've never been in love, huh?
- Of course I've been in love.
- And now you're alone.
See, when I care about someone,
I fight for them.
- Ryan speaking.
- Ms. Wilder, this is Dr. Rodriguez
from Gotham City General.
I'd like you to come
in for retesting.
What's wrong with the first test?
Unfortunately, I think there was
a contamination with the sample.
Contamination? What?
Lab contaminants.
We're picking up a presence
of radioactive material.
So, unless you were
taking selfies at Chernobyl
you wouldn't have read-outs
like these.
The front desk will give you
a call to set up an appointment.
Have a good day.
Okay.
You gonna need to learn
to make more of that serum
right now, or he dies.
We told you. There is no antidote.
There is none.
- Who are you working for?
- No... no... no. No names.
That's the rules...
Pain meds?
Far cabinet. Far cabinet.
Over there, far cabinet.
- Did he hit your celiac artery?
- I'm fine.
I'm more concerned
with how I could be blind
to yet another daughter's
secret life.
It's not your fault.
When you met my mom,
all of your energy was focused
on finding Beth.
And then when you couldn't
find her...
it was about building The Crows.
And now...
It's all about finding Kate.
And the truth in there is...
I've never really been
on your radar.
- Mary.
- It's okay.
- I can tell him about Coryana.
- No, absolutely not.
- He's gonna kill you.
- He kills me, he's got nothing.
I have had years
of resistance training.
I'll be fine.
That craniotomy scar...
Is that what you're trying
to heal?
Shrinks called me amygdala.
Said I had my circuits mixed up,
that I reacted wrong to things.
Saw a puppy, I got pissed off.
Saw a kid crying,
it cracked me up.
Then five years ago...
the doctors decided
I'd be the perfect lab rat
for this secret experimental
treatment,
so they fried the bad parts
of my brain with UV light.
Some two dozen treatments later,
I go to a movie.
I'm sitting there, at one point...
I start laughing.
And then I hear
everybody else around me...
and they were laughing too.
That'd never happened before.
For the first time in my life
I felt normal.
The UV-exposure, it worked?
It did. For a week.
And then cancer bloomed
in my brain...
like a cherry blossom.
And sometimes...
the tumor rubs up
against my amygdala...
And...
- I have an unfortunate moment!
- Stop!
Please. Please, stop. Stop.
You don't want to do this.
You're gonna kill him.
Don't you get it?
My amygdala's infested with cancer.
His pain doesn't compute with me.
I don't feel anything...
But angry.
- Okay. There's more antidote.
- Where?
- Mary, no.
- There's an island
and if you can get there,
you can have all the cure
that you want.
Just, just let my dad go.
How do I get there?
She doesn't want anyone knowing
the location of the island.
So she blitzed my memory
so I could never get back.
She didn't just erase that day.
She erased our entire existence
from each other.
- That's not strange to you?
- You're right, Alice.
Maybe, you were the one busted
stealing the Desert Rose
and maybe you framed me
to save your own ass.
I don't think I would've
done that.
Why? Too honorable?
You helped me gut three men
yesterday.
You really don't remember, do you?
Remember what?
You and I had a thing together.
From the looks of it,
it should've been memorable.
Oh, crap.
Yeah. My thoughts exactly.
Kryptonite is comprised
of sodium, lithium, boron
and elements not found on earth.
As a result, this makes it
the singular material
that can penetrate the batsuit,
and the only failsafe
that protects the suit
against corruption.
Hey, there you are.
- You haven't checked in all day.
- Sorry.
I was busy betraying my girlfriend
so your Crow, Sophie,
can make a drug bust.
Oh, you mean Ocean?
- How do you know about that?
- Sophie told me
that he forged
the fake Jack Napier painting
and might know where
the real one is.
So her story about having
a case on Angelique
to catch her dealer.
It was all BS?
No, it's not all BS.
We need Ocean to find Kate.
What does he have to do
with Kate?
According to Alice,
he has ties to Coryana.
So we ran a search,
but the guy's practically a ghost.
I'm gonna need you to go back
to the part
where you said,
"according to Alice".
- When were you talking to Alice?
- Yeah. Right, so...
at Sophie's condo the other day,
she was there.
And when I showed up,
she put a gun on me.
And then you left
and promptly called 911.
And then you left,
and promptly called 911
to tell the cops the location
of the bitch
- whose gang killed my mom.
- Right now,
Alice is our only way to Coryana.
It's Mary, I...
- Hey, not a great time.
- Lucas, hey.
I'm gonna need you to bring me
that map to Coryana.
What? What are you talking about?
My dad and I are here at my clinic
and he asked to see it.
What the hell is your dad doing
at the clinic?
I'll tell you as soon as you
bring me the map.
Okay? Fast as you can.
You know, like a bat out of hell.
- Mary, everything good?
- I'm fine, Lucas.
Just bring me the map,
I'm not messing around.
Her dad can't know about the clinic.
She's never called me Lucas.
Ever. Not once.
"A bat out of hell"?
Something's wrong.
I need to get to her.
- What's up with you?
- No, no, no. I just...
- just need some space.
- Okay. Well, what can I do...
I don't need your...
Ryan? Ryan? Hey!
Ryan? What's going on?
It doesn't make sense.
You're a painter.
Do I have to draw you a picture?
When two people don't hate
each other very much...
I mean, Coryana was remote,
but I was never desperate.
Well, apparently I was.
- Where are you going?
- To call Safiyah's side-chick.
Can I assume it's done?
I was calling your henchman.
Do you normally answer the phone
for your underlings?
It's normally not you.
How are you, Alice?
I've never asked this to a woman,
but...
You didn't happen to roofie me
for six months straight, did you?
Because I'm hitting
a lot of potholes
on memory lane that need filling.
What did you do to me?
I made you a woman who could
put a knife
through a man's heart.
- Tell me everything you erased.
- Happy to.
But first, ask yourself,
is that really what I want?
Wouldn't it be so much easier
not having
an emotional attachment to the man
you've been tasked to kill?
Why don't you ask someone
who has emotional attachments?
Says the girl willing to do
anything to get her sister back.
I wondered why you tasked me
with such a specific
piece of work, and...
Now, I know.
So you could sit back
and watch me kill an old flame.
- You're sick.
- No, Alice.
Sick would be telling you
all the details
of your story with Ocean
and then asking you to kill him.
Which, again, I am happy to do,
if you so desire.
Let me know what you decide.
Did that just pulsate?
This is why no one can help me.
This is from the kryptonite?
You said you were fine.
I thought I was.
I knew it could pierce the batsuit.
But when you survived Tommy
shooting you
I assumed it meant it was only fatal
if the shot hit a vital organ.
No. Kryptonite kills.
Just hella slow.
Why didn't you say anything?
What was I about to say
after I begged to put on the suit?
"Hey, can I take a sick day?"
I spent every second in that thing
trying to convince you
I'm at least half as good as Kate.
Wasn't about to give you
one more reason to doubt me.
I'm sorry.
Hey, we don't have time for this.
- I need to get to Mary.
- You can barely walk.
You can keep telling me
everything I can't do...
or you can make yourself useful
and have my back for once.
You're an idiot.
Now, use my weight against me.
I think Safiyah will like you.
I wanna escape...
and I want you to come with me.
- What did you see?
That this is
getting complicated.
Hands where I can see them.
Oh, we're kind of in the middle
of a thing.
I'm not here for you.
Ocean. I'm Agent Moore
with The Crows.
- Where's the Napier painting?
- What Napier painting?
The one you were looking
at when you forged the fake.
No, idea
what you're talking about.
It'll take two minutes
to have this place
swarming with a bunch of Crows
looking to catch the man
responsible
for Gotham's latest
drug epidemic.
Give me the map,
and I'll let you go.
Map? Oh, now I'm intrigued.
- Hand it over.
- Don't.
The faster she gets to the island,
the faster I need you dead.
Not my problem.
Show me the map!
I got the map.
Any chance you know how to read
a nautical chart?
No, but you need to bring it
to the clinic.
I think someone's got Mary.
She said her dad is with her
and that she needs the map.
Oh, my God. Okay, I'm on my way.
She said it's deadly serious,
and this goes without saying,
but you can't actually
hand it over.
I won't.
But I'm also not gonna gamble
with their lives.
- What are you doing?
- That island is growing
the only thing on this planet
that has a shot of curing me.
I'm not putting my life
in the hands of some Crow.
Ryan...
The suit can discharge
a single dose of adrenaline.
When you need a boost,
say the word.
- I got this.
- I know.
You're one of them, aren't you?
I'm so stupid.
- Stupid, stupid, stupid!
- Stop! No.
Stop! Stop! Just stop! One of who?
Just another lying Hamilton.
What? What are you talking about?
Hamilton doctors did this to you?
That's not possible.
You said this happened
five years ago.
Yeah, my mom was CEO then.
She would've never signed off
on secret human testing.
Why do you think
they call it secret, genius?
My new doctors, they promised...
They promised, they promised
to fix me.
Did you know
that this was happening?
Apparently, there's a lot
I don't know about.
Oh, my God!
Drop it or I shoot!
Stop! She brought the map!
- Do not kill her!
- Your family did this to me!
Get her out of here.
Go out the back.
I'm not leaving my agent
in a damn hallway!
I'll protect her. I promise you.
Now, go.
Luke, now.
Batwoman to Batcave. I got it.
It's okay, he's...
Sedate him in the car.
- We don't need any incidents.
- Who are you?
- Just a man looking for a map.
- Don't give it to him.
I will shoot this Crow
in the head.
Her blood will be on your hands,
Batwoman.
Is that really how you want
to start your legacy?
We need that map.
I know.
But I also can't let you die.
What do you mean, she's dying?
I looked at the wound.
The meds were working.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- She asked me not to.
- But we're the Bat Team.
- Not to her.
The meds aren't working.
Her prolonged exposure to
the kryptonite radiation is lethal.
Ryan's only hope is
the Desert Rose
which is on Coryana with Kate,
who we're never gonna see again.
Since putting on the suit,
Ryan's...
Ryan's made the streets safer.
She's inspired the city
and she helped us find Kate.
And she's done it all
while having a terminal illness.
I mean, if that's not a hero,
what the hell is?
So we're gonna find Coryana.
We're gonna get Kate back
and we're gonna save Ryan's life.
Except, we have no way
of doing any of those things.
That's not true.
We have my dad.
If these people have anything
to do with Hamilton,
I want to be the first to know
about it.
I want that map in my hands.
I shouldn't have said anything
about Coryana.
You were acting on instinct.
That man was totally unhinged.
Do you think mom knew
what they were doing to that guy?
I think your mom was
a lot like you.
A woman who would do anything
to help people.
I know you're pissed about
the clinic.
I'm shutting it down, Mary.
- Why? Why would you do that?
- It's illegal.
Yeah, but a lot of people
in Gotham
can't afford healthcare
in the legal way.
Practicing without a license,
impersonating a doctor,
possession of narcotics.
Need I go on?
But I've saved hundreds,
maybe thousands of lives.
And even more than that,
I make people feel
like they're worthy
of being alive.
Gotham City General
can't say that.
I'm not questioning your passion
or the good that you've done,
but did you not listen
to what the man said?
This is exactly
how your mother started.
With good intentions and a lot
of disappearing lines in the sand.
Mom knew about the clinic.
She was proud of me.
She was conducting
human experiments, Mary.
Well, I wouldn't do that.
Every sick person who walks
through your front door
is an experiment
because you are not qualified.
So, is this what being a dad
means to you?
You've finally paid attention
to me?
And then you take away the thing
that means the most to me?
I liked you better
when you acted like I didn't exist.
Hey.
I didn't actually think
you would come.
I did.
- You don't look so hot.
- Yeah.
It's kind of what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Something pretty serious.
Like what? No, wait. Let me guess.
Cops got you on the hook
for something.
- Why would you think that?
- I don't know, Ryan.
Why would I think that?
I have no idea.
Is it maybe...
Because you slipped some
creepy spy tech onto my phone?
Oh, no.
I heard static and half my apps
stopped working.
And my tech guy thinks
he deleted it, but...
Who knows?
The feds could be listening
to every word of this.
I... I... I did not have a choice.
You did, though.
- And you chose to snitch.
- They had a case on you.
You would be
in a holding cell right now.
That's not how this works, Ryan.
The cops? The Crows?
They're not the ones I'm afraid of.
You know, what? My bad, Ang.
I am so sorry that you can't
drug-deal in peace.
I am so sorry I cannot trust you...
Oh, don't you dare
turn this around me!
How do I know you don't have
this whose place bugged?
How do I know you're even
who you say you are?
Because you know me!
You are the only person
that knows me!
And I need you right now.
I really need you.
You should have thought of that
before you ratted me out.
- Hello, again.
- This is where I say thank you.
- For what?
- Your advice.
The less I knew the better.
Ocean's dead.
- I'll need to see his body.
- And I'll bring it.
And you'll give me Kate.
Now, send your little errand-girl
to come fetch.
I'll be damned.
You're a bigger lunatic
than I thought.
Thank you.