Come on. Hurry it up.
Easy.
You lasted three
pathetic days behind bars.
Before you broke
and tried to bring me down.
I swear.
- I didn't sell you out.
- If you'd taken a fall as I asked,
Did you really think
I was gonna let you rot in prison?
I needed you...
to be my Michelin-star chef.
Ever since Ocean's disappearance
We've had issues with quality control.
He always said
the Snakebite formula
was toxic if it wasn't cooked using
his "secret method."
I can help you.
Well, the final ingredient
will be delivered soon
and if I've gone through
all this trouble
Just to find out you
can't cook after all, well...
at least I have what I need
to dissolve your body.
Hey, we don't know much,
but the good news is
I think she's alive.
You didn't find a body?
It was an ambush.
We found the bodies of the agents
transporting her,
but Angelique was gone.
Okay, okay.
So False Face got her.
Well, where did It happen?
Descriptions, place!
Ryan, leave this alone.
False Face is dropping
bodies all over Gotham.
Will you let me help you?
How? How can you help us?
I know, Angelique the best.
Stand down and let me do my job.
I'll call you when I have news.
Crowphie says Ang was
kidnapped by False Face.
Damn it. If Ang had
just let me help her.
And said False Face wanted her
to cook Snakebite, yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's why she tried to get out.
- She didn't want that life.
- Well, they still want it for her.
Eyewitnesses reported that two cars
ambushed the SUV that Ang was inside.
A couple hours later, those same cars
were involved in a heist
at Gotham pharmaceutical.
They're stocking up on supplies.
Do they need anything else?
The one ingredient that wouldn't
be at that warehouse is fear toxin.
So, they'll hit somewhere else.
Can you put a trace on those cars?
Well, I flagged them
both in the city grid
so as soon as either one makes an
appearance on traffic cams,
- you're up, Batwoman.
- Good. I'll be ready.
You gonna loop in Sophie?
So, Ang can slip through
her fingers again?
Not a chance.
Dr. Rhyme?
From the look of things.
I'm Jackson, your new patient.
Yes. My 5.30.
Please sit down.
I am sitting, so...
This is very disturbing.
You mean, my divorce?
I can read between the lines,
you sick puppy.
Who hurt you?
I'm so sorry. I'm running late.
What is going on here?
Lost cause.
I saved you the headache...
Enigma.
You were working
with Julia Pennyworth.
And I appreciate you
sending her on a long...
vacation.
Because I need some
alone time with you.
Safiyah hired me
to erase your memories of Ocean.
You're obviously here
to get them back.
I assume that's what
this is all about.
From what I recall
you were in love
I made you forget your feelings
And consequently
helped turn you into...
You.
Keep them.
I don't need the hassle.
Then why did you track me down?
I have someone else.
I need to forget.
My sister.
Kate.
Don't deviate
from your individual route.
You have four minutes
to reach pickup
or we'll consider you burned.
See you at the finish line.
Tell me where they're going!
You have no idea
what you've just done.
I'm burned.
Thanks a lot.
Excuse me?
No, It's not my fault you stole
the car I was looking for!
I was undercover!
We I.D.ed the driver
and brought him into custody
- so I could switch places.
- Are you in the middle of the heist?
- Get in the car and drive!
- I told you.
I'm burned!
Black Mask gives out
the location on these phones
minutes before the heist begins.
And he only gives the drop-off info
after the pickup is complete.
And if you show up late...
They know something's
up and aborted.
Everything was on the phone.
Now, it's wiped.
And I got nothing.
You're the one who said
we'd never be partners.
Stay out of my business.
You are alive because you have
an uncanny ability to erase memories.
And as much as my dear sister
is very much deceased in reality...
She lives on...
In here.
I've been having
hallucinations of her.
What does she look like?
The way she did when we were 13
before everything changed.
Do you understand...
why she appears to you as a child
and why that means you
shouldn't erase her?
You are working pro-bono here, doc.
Why don't we just...
skip through the diagnosis,
and go straight to the treatment?
Because you're asking me
to excise a person
From your memory
who's been in your life
since you shared your mother's womb.
Whether you admit it or not,
Kate matters to you.
Erasing her will radically
change your personality.
Yeah. I'll stop hallucinating.
Kate's memory isn't a cancer
inside your brain.
In fact, I believe she's
your last moral compass.
Well, I'd hate to lose that.
You are a monster, Alice...
But you're rational.
Imagine,
if you were at the mercy of
every dark impulse.
Is that what you want?
I am not into self-reflection...
And considering this,
is apparently our doing,
I'd say you owe me.
Okay, but...
we have to do this safely.
So...
you need to confront Kate,
and make these visions disappear.
Then in theory, I can wipe
her from your memory
Without completely fracturing your
psyche.
It's the only way this
might work.
Now, see, that is
a positive attitude.
Okay.
Commander, I have an update. I...
Agent Moore.
Agent Tavaroff and I
were just discussing
Your False Face operation.
What's the latest?
Unfortunately, Batwoman interfered
And they aborted the whole thing.
Do you have a line
on the other drivers?
Not yet.
Black Mask executed
three Crows agents.
If he gets away with that, It's gonna
be open season on us all.
That'll be all, Tavaroff.
Yes, Commander.
I'll find another way in.
You put yourself behind the wheel
of a heist car?
I didn't have time to bring
another agent up to speed, sir.
Do you want to know my theory?
I think...
you guaranteed your informant
She'd be safe and now,
Black Mask has her.
You're making it personal
and it's gonna get you killed.
I'm doing my job. I...
So am I.
Effective immediately,
I'm putting Agent Tavaroff
in charge of the operation.
Sir, respectfully,
Russell Tavaroff shouldn't be
leading a hostage recovery.
He'll go in guns blazing.
False Face declared war on us,
not the other way around!
I am not letting you throw
yourself in front of a bullet
for Angelique Martin!
She picked her side!
Commander, what is this
actually about?
- You've been really off lately...
- Get out!
Get out!
My lead on Angelique didn't pan out.
That's it?
You're giving up?
Kane sent me home.
Got my cover blown
by Batwoman, but...
somehow...
that's my fault.
Come on, Soph.
This is BS.
Ryan.
I don't want to freak you out
but the new guy who's taken the lead
He is going to scorch the earth
to take down False Face
And that includes Angelique.
Okay. Does this guy know
where Angelique is?
It's only a matter of time.
Okay. Well, we need
to find her first.
What I need is an undercover asset
Who can drive a car like
she just qualified for the Indy 500.
- Why is that?
- False Face
is planning another fear toxin heist
just as soon as
he finds a new driver.
Oh, no.
- No way.
- Come on.
I am good. I can prove it to you.
Girl, it is way too dangerous.
Okay, so is sitting here
feeling sorry for ourselves
when a homicidal drug lord
is using my ex to cook his dope.
Look.
You and I got Ang into this mess.
We need to find her
before your Crows do.
What other options have you got?
Take a deep breath, Alice.
What is that?
What do you feel?
Don't be a smartass.
Just answer quickly.
A warm hand.
Good.
Go figure.
So, you want me
to leave you alone?
Turns out you're a paradox.
You gave me the idea
to erase Kate in my mind.
Kudos for that.
But you also happen to be Kate,
so...
there's the door.
What am I missing?
Stop that.
Make me!
You always thought, you knew me
better than I knew myself.
That's why you're so scared of me.
I can see you have
so much love to give.
You would see it, too,
if you just look at yourself.
You condescending,
little know-it-all.
Do you want to know
who I really am?
A manipulator.
I wanted you to think I loved you
as much as you loved me
because that's what sisters do
but I felt nothing!
For you.
For anyone.
You're not remembering right.
I should have told you the truth.
I was born
with this bad brain
And it is only capable of hate
and jealousy, and bitterness.
That's not true.
You wouldn't have taken
so many bullets to save me.
Beth...
I'm your sister
and I'll always believe in you.
Thanks, sis.
That means a lot to me.
Except it doesn't
because you're dead.
A master manipulator
with no feelings.
Give me a break.
Isn't she so silly?
No, no, no.
I just got rid of you!
Doctor...
I'm beginning to think
You're toying with me.
Nice!
Okay, okay. Let me see.
Mary was sweet enough
to lend us her car
But if there is so much as a bug
on the windshield after this,
she made it clear we'll both
end up In the trunk.
Look at all these...
Cylinders.
Can I take it for a spin?
I got some info from the last
driver on how he was hired.
You'll have to run through a series
of street-racing moves.
No way of knowing
what they'll be.
- Piece of cake.
- They're gonna interview you.
You'll have to know
everything about this car
- and how to maneuver it.
- Okay, okay. Well,
we got the gas pedal.
I'm kidding, okay?
Do you know what red-lining is,
what backpedaling means,
how to measure your camber
and airflow?
Are you helping me,
or are you just looking for an
excuse to call this off?
I just want this to work.
We are going to get Ang back, okay?
I'll do my part. I'll study.
What happens after they hire me?
You'll wait for the
coordinates of the pickup,
They'll put the payload in your car,
and on your way to the drop-off,
you pull over and place
the tracking device
inside the fear toxin canister.
That will lead us
to where they have Angelique.
Okay. When's the interview?
Without the Crows,
I had to reach out to someone
for help setting it up.
But don't worry.
He's trustworthy.
Ryan, is it?
Look here.
No prob, Larry.
- Luke. Luke. Sorry, sorry.
- No worries.
You're Mary's roommate, yeah?
You know what? I... I actually think
I served you here once.
Shirley Temple, right?
I don't think that was me.
Can we save the getting
to know each other part for later?
Come on.
Yeah.
All right.
I just deployed your false identity.
Robyn Wilde?
Yeah. It's...
harder to screw up if it's closer
to your real name.
So, you are a fast
and furious getaway driver
with a rap sheet ten-mile long
and I'm gonna spoof
a text message
from a known False Face associate
recommending you for the job.
And...
Done.
Luke...
I owe you one.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
I'm gonna go gas up the car.
What's this?
Comms for us to communicate
without Sophie knowing.
A tracker to place
on the fear toxin,
and a portable version
of the Batmobile's A.I.
A.I?
What A.I?
You didn't notice I installed it
with the new paint job?
What?
I thought my driving skills
were getting better.
Yeah, no.
Hook it up to Mary's ride
so you don't bounce
off too many walls.
Fine.
Hey.
I'm just gonna say it.
I realize Ang is in trouble,
but you teaming up
with Sophie like this, these lies...
it's a bad idea.
She's gonna figure out who you are.
She's smart.
She still thinks I'm lucky
not to be in jail.
I'll be fine.
You said confront Kate
so I destroyed that little
snot-nosed twerp
and then Ocean comes in
and ruins it!
I wasn't even thinking
about him!
When Safiyah ordered me
to erase your memories of Ocean,
you begged me not to do it.
Begged?
Either you're being dramatic,
or I was.
Ocean came back into your life,
and unlocked a piece
of your memory.
Which is proof that Kate,
your subconscious was correct.
You are capable
of emotion and attachment.
Do you want to know
why you're wrong?
Because I killed Ocean...
And I felt...
Nothing.
So, rip these hideous ghosts
out of my mind!
Not impressed?
Come on. I just did a 360,
and drifted
the entire width of the Tarmac
like Fast & Furious: Gotham Drift.
What's the horsepower on your ride?
Well, she came
with the standard 1,500
till I tuned the ECU
and now, she tops out at 1,774.
Speed...
I've hit 305, but I can
push her in a pinch.
First job's tonight.
Kind of waiting for an
important phone call here.
Hey. We got a problem.
FAA says there's an unknown
drone in the sky above you.
It's got to be False Face.
If you pull over to plant that
tracker, they'll see it.
We got to call this off.
We won't get
another chance at this.
Maybe I can do it without stopping.
Fear toxin canisters
are double sealed, unstable.
If you inhale even
one breath of the stuff...
Can you just trust me on this?
No! Abort! Abort, Ryan!
Hey, Luke.
Exactly how intelligent is my A.I.?
You'll be fine. It works in remote
just like your Batmobile.
I'm really missing
my Batsuit right now.
You have the cargo,
you have your route.
If you're late,
we'll consider you burned.
See you at the finish line.
Let's go.
Okay.
You're up, batcave.
Okay. Okay.
Seriously?
And I'm the one who's
a bad driver?
Sorry, sorry. Still getting
the hang of this.
Oh, crap.
We got Crows on our tail.
How fast can you take over again?
I just need a little more time.
Hold her steady.
I'm opening up
The canister right now.
Was that gunfire? are we hit?
Can you just try to lose them?
Red light!
Oh, god, Oh, god, oh, god!
Tracker's on.
Who's the best driver
in all of Gotham?
Oh, that's me.
Sophie.
Come bow down to your girl!
Ryan.
Hey! Where's Sophie?
She asked for the tracker data
and told me to meet you guys here.
She ditched us for the Crows?
No.
No, no, no. She...
She was too worried they'd storm
the place and kill Ang.
She's taking on False Face herself.
Cut deeper this time.
I want Ocean gone.
Shut your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
Focus on what your
senses are telling you.
What you hear.
What you feel.
That happened fast.
It's almost like you'd
rather be here with me.
Are we sure
we're in my subconscious?
What am I doing
in Ocean's sex dream?
I'm guessing you brought me...
here...
to apologize.
Why'd you kill me?
Wouldn't you like to know?
You killed me
for nothing.
You would have done
the same to me.
No. No chance in hell.
There's screwed up,
and then there's you.
Is this real?
This feels real.
You tell me. I thought
you said you killed him.
I'm alive.
And very pissed off.
I... stabbed you.
I watched you die.
Let's roll the replay.
Safiyah wanted me dead.
She enlisted a woman who
could twirl a balisong in her sleep
but insisted
you use one of her knives instead.
She dipped the blade
in desert rose.
Didn't I say...
you're a crappy assassin?
Don't tell me
you're working for Safiyah.
Her fancy, out-of-network
lobotomist stole our memories.
We deserved worse.
I betrayed my sister.
I jeopardized my entire island's
safety because of you.
An outsider.
I'm in Gotham on other business
but I thought I'd track you down
look you in the eye
and ask you myself...
Why'd you do it?
I'm relieved my other
victims can't ask me the same.
Alice!
I need to know.
If I regret it?
If I've thought of you...
every day...
since Coryana?
It was the only way
I could get my sister back.
See?
Manipulator.
Mockingbird anew.
What did you do?
The one thing I promised Safiyah
I would never do.
You'll be fine In a few minutes.
Ciao.
You'll forget all about Ocean,
and your love for each other!
Safiyah, no.
You... you can't do this.
I remember us.
Hi.
Everything.
She's unlocking our memories.
You shouldn't be here.
- Where's Angelique?
- No, no, no.
You're not the one
asking the questions.
How did you find this place?
Why did you come here alone?
If I only kill one Crow today,
I'll fall asleep depressed.
I have eyes
on Crows headquarters.
There's no activity, there's no
strike team being mobilized.
You did come here
alone, didn't you?
They're on their way.
It's funny.
When I told the bat
how personal this was to me,
I thought the Crows would take
me more seriously
Not less.
Oh, she didn't tell you.
Well, that's an embarrassing
lack of coordination.
- We'll work on it.
- No, you won't.
I don't know how you
found this facility,
but it's important to me
that you're not followed.
Don't worry, though.
I'll make sure
we dump your body
somewhere they'll find it.
Come on.
So, this is how it goes?
She saves you,
you save her. Sweet.
But now who's left
to save you both?
We're tired of your crap.
We don't need anyone
else saving us.
Angelique. Where is she?
I'll be happy to show you.
Wave hello to your fans, Angelique.
Hey.
I need you to watch,
as these two let me go.
And if they don't
I need you to shoot her.
Now, that is some terrific branding,
but you should really
consider bringing a gun
to a gun fight.
Sorry for the delay
getting these delivered.
Minor catastrophe
at my warehouse.
Mondays, you know.
Things better here?
Just finished the first cook,
But this is all-new equipment
and I want to talk to you
about how we should roll it out.
Well, I thought we might
allow you to be
- The ceremonial first recipient.
- Actually...
I'm sober.
You don't want me
lose my time, do you?
Couldn't care less, my dear.
Wait!
I was Ocean's assistant, but he
never gave me the full technique.
I had to guess.
And this formula
could be deadly?
You are an endless disappointment.
Oh! I'll help you find Ocean.
How'd you know where to find me?
Got lucky.
Safiyah gave me Enigma's info
And told me to use it If I needed
help on my mission,
So, when I called the doc yesterday
she said someone
was tracking her
that her identity might be blown.
Figured it was you.
And this supersecret mission
Safiyah sent you on?
You destroyed all of the
desert rose on Coryana.
She really didn't have, like,
a seed bunker or something?
Never thought we needed one.
That island had been safe
for hundreds of years
until you came around.
Put that up on my wall.
Safiyah thought our
family's legacy was destroyed
until I told her there was one
plant left.
The one you stole.
Do you know where it is?
Safiyah thinks Batwoman has it.
That's why she's not dead
from kryptonite poisoning.
Look.
I made my feelings very clear
on Coryana both times.
You've been...
Harder to read
what with the stabbing and all.
Do you regret it?
Does it matter?
Answer the damn question.
I had a world-class shrink tell me
that I was a monster today, so...
Do...
You...
Regret it?
Are you not hearing me?
I literally had it in me
to stab a knife through your heart.
So?
So...
Just in case I get the urge again
We should...
probably get something
out of the way.
Damn.
Agent Tavaroff.
Think we've got
everything we need here.
We'll meet you back at the lab.
Thank you.
I'll be a few minutes behind you.
You'll be fine.
It works in remote just
like your Batmobile.
Oh. I'm really missing
my Batsuit right now.
Oh, my God.