[RAT SQUEAKING]
SHH.
NOW WE MUSTN'T WAKE HIM.
OH, I LOATHE THE BATS!
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
WHY ARE THEY HERE?
BECAUSE BATS EAT
RATS, ALICE.
RAT...MEET MOUSE.
I'M GONNA NEED YOUR HELP
ONE LAST TIME,
MY LITTLE MOUSE.
SOMEONE...QUITE LITERALLY
CRASHED OUR TEA PARTY,
BUT SHE FORGOT TO TAKE
HER PARTY FAVOR,
SO I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO
MAKE SURE SHE GETS IT.
♪ TWINKLE, TWINKLE,
LITTLE BAT ♪
♪ HOW I WONDER
WHERE YOU'RE AT ♪
♪ UP ABOVE THE WORLD YOU FLY
♪ LIKE A TEA TRAY IN THE SKY
[BATS SQUEAKING]
♪ TWINKLE, TWINKLE,
LITTLE BAT ♪
♪ UP UNTIL YOUR BRAIN
WENT SPLAT ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
UNH!
TRICK-OR-TREAT.
UGH!
WHERE'S YOUR CASH?
I GOT 3
COLLECTION AGENCIES
ASKING ME
THE SAME THING.
YOU GOT AN ATM CARD?
YOU'RE JUST SETTING
YOURSELF UP FOR MORE
DISAPPOINTMENT.
GUESS YOU GOT NOTHING
EXCEPT A SMART MOUTH.
[WHOOSH]
OOH! UNH!
[PUNCHES LANDING]
MAN: AGH!
[GRUNTING]
THANK YOU!
AND I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOUR OTHER
SECURITY GUARDS,
BUT I HAVE BEEN TRAINED
IN HALF A DOZEN FORMS
OF MARTIAL ARTS,
SO BEATING UP BAD GUYS
WON'T BE A PROBLEM.
YOU WERE CERTAINLY
AROUND ENOUGH OF THEM...
IN BLACKGATE.
WELL, WHAT IT DOESN'T SAY
IS THAT
I DIDN'T DO IT.
WHY'D YOU TELL
THE JUDGE YOU DID?
TO AVOID DOING 15 YEARS
INSTEAD OF 18 MONTHS.
JUDGE GAVE ME A CHOICE--
PLEAD OUT
TO A LESSER CHARGE,
DO A BULLET AND A HALF.
LOOK. I GET IT.
BLACKGATE DOESN'T LOOK GOOD
ON A RESUME,
BUT IT DID GIVE ME
A VALUABLE SKILLSET.
EVERY SECOND YOU'RE INSIDE,
YOU'RE ASSESSING THREATS,
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHO'S DANGEROUS.
YOU GET REAL GOOD
AT READING PEOPLE.
FACES CAN TELL YOU A LOT.
AND WHAT DOES MINE
TELL YOU?
THAT I'M NOT GETTING
THIS JOB.
DANA DEWITT: IN THIS
EXCLUSIVE VIDEO,
YOU CAN SEE CROWS OFFICERS
OPENING FIRE ON BATWOMAN.
THIS AMBUSH COMES
AFTER THE CROWS' OWN JACOB KANE
FORGED AN ALLIANCE WITH THE BAT.
THIS SHOCKING FOOTAGE
HAS SPARKED ANGER
AMONG GOTHAM CITIZENS,
AND A PRO-BATWOMAN RALLY
HAS BEEN PLANNED FOR TOMORROW
IN GOTHAM CITY PLAZA
TO DEMAND THE RETURN
OF THE CAPED CRUSADER,
WHO HASN'T BEEN SEEN
SINCE THE FIREFIGHT WITH CROWS.
COMMANDER,
THEY'RE HERE.
OH. TIME TO SEE HOW LONG
WE'VE BEEN OUT OF THE LOOP.
MARY: I'M SORRY.
KATE WAS WHAT?
BECAUSE THAT SOUNDED
A LOT LIKE BATWOMAN.
SHE WAS YOUR SISTER.
SHE NEVER TOLD YOU?
PLEASE. LIKE, KATE WOULD
EVER TRUST ME WITH A SECRET.
SOPHIE: HOW COULD YOU
NOT KNOW?
YOU TWO SPENT NEARLY
EVERY DAY TOGETHER.
YOU WERE HER ASSOCIATE.
ASSISTANT ACTUALLY,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
SHE WAS GOOD
AT KEEPING SECRETS
FROM BOTH OF US.
JACOB: WE KNOW SHE
DIDN'T WORK ALONE.
WHO WERE HER
OTHER FRIENDS,
PEOPLE SHE WAS
CLOSE TO?
DAD, NOW YOU'RE JUST
RUBBING IT IN.
KATE SPENT YEARS TRYING
TO PUSH ME AWAY.
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE WAS
ABOUT TO USE "I AM BATWOMAN"
AS AN ICEBREAKER.
CAN YOU THINK OF ANYONE
WHO WANTED TO HARM HER
OR BATWOMAN, ANYBODY
WHO MIGHT HAVE
SABOTAGED HER PLANE?
LUKE: I THOUGHT YOU SAID
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
WE'RE NOT RULING
ANYTHING OUT.
JUST LOOKING INTO ANY
POSSIBLE ENEMIES.
YOU MEAN OTHER THAN EVERY
AGENT IN THIS BUILDING, RIGHT,
OR MAYBE JUST THE ONES
THAT LURED HER INTO A TRAP,
TRIED TO GUN HER DOWN
ON THE 50-YARD LINE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOO BAD
SHE DIDN'T HAVE SOMEONE
WHO LOVED HER
WATCHING HER BACK.
I THINK WE'RE
DONE HERE.
CAN WE JUST TALK, PLEASE?
OH. NOW YOU GOT
SOMETHING TO SAY
AFTER STAYING QUIET
FOR MONTHS ABOUT WHO
BATWOMAN REALLY WAS?
IT WASN'T MY SECRET
TO TELL.
NO. JUST YOUR SECRET
TO KEEP.
CAN'T IMAGINE KATE
WOULD TRUST YOU
WITH THE CONTENTS OF HER SAFE
AND NOT TRUST YOU
WITH EVERYTHING ELSE.
YOU REALLY FOOLED ME.
I GUESS ABOUT A LOT
OF THINGS.
OHH.
[GUNSHOT]
UNH!
HEY. YOU GOT ANY OF THIS
IN GENERIC?
THANKS. NOW DO
THE SAFE.
UNH!
RYAN: HYAH!
ROBBER: UGH!
UNH!
ROBBER: HUH! AGH!
[GUN COCKS]
HANDS IN THE AIR.
RYAN WILDER.
I'LL NOTE MY SURPRISE
IN THE REPORT.
HEY, SOPH.
LOVE THE HAIR.
IT'S AGENT MOORE.
I FIGURE WE'VE DONE
THIS ENOUGH TIMES
TO BE ON
A FIRST-NAME BASIS.
YOU GET DEMOTED?
I DON'T KNOW.
C-STORE ROBBERY SEEMS
A LITTLE LOW-RENT
FOR YOU.
FUNNY. I WAS GONNA SAY
IT'S A STEP UP FOR YOU.
GOT TIRED OF COVERING
FOR YOUR DRUG-DEALING
LADY FRIEND?
EX-LADY FRIEND.
IS THAT WHY SHE WASN'T
DRIVING THE GETAWAY CAR
THIS TIME?
I ALREADY TOLD THEM
I DIDN'T ROB
THAT PLACE.
YEAH. I READ THAT.
I ALSO READ THAT YOU WERE
STANDING OVER A BLOODY CASHIER
WITH YOUR PRINTS
ON THE GUN.
BECAUSE I WAS TYING
TO STOP IT.
CASTING YOURSELF
AS THE HERO?
NOW THAT'S NEW.
GOT THE SECURITY FOOTAGE.
HER STORY CHECKS OUT.
OK. SORRY
FOR THE MISTAKE.
YEAH. THE CROWS'
LAST MISTAKE
ONLY COST ME
18 MONTHS OF MY LIFE
AND COUNTING.
PIECE OF ADVICE.
IF YOU'RE ALWAYS
IN THE WRONG PLACE
AT THE WRONG TIME,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD FIND
A NEW PLACE.
AND TELL ME
WHERE THAT IS.
BECAUSE BY MY COUNT,
I'VE BEEN BROUGHT IN
FOR QUESTIONING
MORE TIMES FOR STUFF
I DIDN'T DO
THAN AN ACTUAL
SERIAL KILLER
LIKE ALICE
HAS BEEN ARRESTED
FOR STUFF SHE DID.
YOU THINK I DON'T
KNOW THE REAL REASON
JACOB KANE WON'T PUT
A BULLET IN HER?
ANY SYMPATHY HE HAD
FOR HER DIED A LONG TIME AGO.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
THAT IF ALICE
WEREN'T WHITE,
SHE'D BE DEAD.
SORRY FOR THE INCONVENIENCE,
MS. WILDER.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
SYMPATHY FOR THAT
PSYCHOPATH?
RYAN.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
DOES YOUR DAD KNOW
ABOUT ALL THIS?
SOMEHOW, I'VE MANAGED
TO KEEP IT A SECRET.
GUESS THAT'S WHAT YOUR
FAMILY DOES, HUH,
KEEPING SECRETS?
I ACTUALLY PULLED
AN ALL-NIGHTER,
SO YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO BE
A LITTLE MORE CLEAR.
ALICE IS BETH KANE,
ISN'T SHE?
WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
GIRL GOES MISSING
16 YEARS AGO,
NO BODY'S FOUND.
THAT WAS ALICE
BEFORE SHE WAS ALICE.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
BECAUSE SHE'S
YOUR SISTER, TOO.
I MEAN, DOES COVERING UP
FOR HER RUN IN THE FAMILY?
THAT BITCH KILLED
MY MOM.
I WOULD NEVER HELP HER.
I'M SORRY.
ALICE POISONED
MY MOM AND ME
AND THEN GAVE US
ONE DOSE OF THE ANTIDOTE,
SO...MY MOM DIED
IN MY ARMS.
TELL ME
WHERE I CAN FIND HER,
AND I WILL GET JUSTICE
FOR BOTH OF OUR MOMS.
[GURNEY RATTLING]
MAN: COUPLE HOMELESS PEOPLE
DROPPED HIM OFF.
FOUND HIM IN THE TUNNELS,
MOST OF HIM ANYWAY.
OHH!
OK. UM, I KNOW
I'M NOT A DOCTOR,
BUT I AM PRETTY SURE
THERE IS NOTHING YOU
CAN DO FOR HIM.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S MOUSE.
[LOCK BEEPS]
ALICE: NEED A TISSUE?
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I'M NOT HERE TO KILL
YOU, PENNYWHISTLE.
IF I WAS, I'D JUST
SWIPE LEFT AND DELETE YOU.
TSK, TSK, TSK, TSK.
QUITE THE OPPOSITE.
I'M HERE TO SAVE YOUR LIFE.
SEE, I'M PLANNING
SOMETHING BIG,
HIGH BODY COUNT,
AND IT WOULD BE A SHAME
IF ONE OF THOSE BODIES
WAS YOURS.
SINCE WHEN DO YOU CARE
ABOUT MY LIFE
OR ANY OTHER?
SINCE OUR MUTUAL ENEMY
KILLED MY DEAR SISTER
BEFORE I COULD.
SAFIYAH?
WAIT. YOU DIDN'T ACTUALLY
THINK KATE'S PLANE CRASH
WAS A MECHANICAL FAILURE,
DID YOU?
THAT'S NOT EXACTLY
SAFIYAH'S M.O.
WELL, PENNYROYAL,
WE ALL HAVE TO STEP
OUTSIDE OUR COMFORT ZONES,
GROW, EXPAND, DO THINGS
WE WOULD NORMALLY
NEVER FATHOM DOING,
WHICH IS WHY I'M PROPOSING
A LITTLE SUPERVILLAIN,
SUPERSPY TEAM-UP.
I ALREADY HAVE
A BRILLIANTLY
TERRIFYING PLAN.
THEY SAY REVENGE IS A DISH
BEST SERVED COLD,
BUT I THINK THE PORTIONS
ARE BIG ENOUGH
FOR US TO SPLIT.
WHY WOULD I EVER WORK
WITH A PSYCHOPATH?
BECAUSE THERE'S ANOTHER
PSYCHOPATH HUNTING YOU
WHO'S EVEN SCARIER
THAN ME--LET'S BE REAL.
I'M NOT AFRAID OF HER.
YOU SHOULD BE.
[WHISPERING]
SHE CAN GET YOU ANYWHERE.
[NORMAL VOICE]
JUST ASK KATE.
RETRIBUTION IS COMING
FOR BOTH OF US, PENNYLOAFER.
IF WE CAN WORK TOGETHER
AND GET
TO THAT SISTER-KILLING
PSYCHO BITCH
BEFORE SHE GETS TO US,
YOU KNOW, HAVE EACH
OTHER'S BACKS.
HEH. YEAH.
UNTIL YOU STICK
A KNIFE IN MINE.
WELL, WE COULD DO A COUPLE
OF TRUST FALLS FIRST.
HMM? WORK UP TO THE IDEA?
HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE DESPERATE.
KATE WAS THE ONLY
PERSON WHO HAD
ANY SYMPATHY
LEFT FOR YOU.
NOW THAT SHE'S GONE,
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYONE.
OH. YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
I DON'T HAVE?
A KNIFE STICKING
OUT OF ME.
UNH!
AT LAST IT WASN'T
IN YOUR BACK.
[GROANS]
LUKE: SO I GUESS WE HAVE
TWO UNINVITED GUESTS.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
AT THE MOMENT,
TRYING NOT TO PUKE.
WHAT KIND OF ANIMAL
DID THIS?
THERE'S GOT TO BE
A THOUSAND BITES HERE.
ALL I KNOW IS THIS IS
A BAD WAY TO GO.
MARY: IT WOULD BE,
BUT ALL THESE BITES
WERE POST-MORTEM.
MOUSE WAS POISONED.
-ARE YOU SURE?
-YEAH,
BECAUSE IT'S THE SAME TOXIN
THAT KILLED MY MOM,
AND THE ONLY PERSON
WITH ACCESS TO IT...
ALICE.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID THAT
MOUSE WAS ALICE'S,
LIKE, ONLY FRIEND
IN THE WORLD.
WELL, THEY MUST HAVE
HAD A FALLING OUT,
WHICH IS MORE THAN
A LITTLE DISTURBING
GIVEN THAT MOUSE WAS
ALICE'S ANCHOR
TO ANY SEMBLANCE
OF HUMANITY.
AND IF SHE KILLED HIM,
SHE MUST REALLY BE UNRAVELING.
[THUMP]
WAIT. IS HE STILL--
-NO.
-THEN HOW IS HE MOVING?
I DON'T KNOW.
[BAT CHIRPING]
AAH!
WHAT? I REALLY HATE BATS.
I'M HERE AT GOTHAM CITY PLAZA,
WHERE CITIZENS HAVE GATHERED
TO SHOW THEIR SUPPORT
FOR BATWOMAN, WHO HASN'T
BEEN SEEN IN GOTHAM
SINCE THE CROWS AMBUSHED HER
IN GOLIATHS STADIUM
OVER A WEEK AGO,
AND DESPITE THE CROWS
THREATENING TO MAKE ARRESTS,
THESE PROTESTORS HAVE
MADE IT CLEAR
THAT THEY'RE
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
[PROTESTORS CHANTING,
"WE WANT THE BAT!"]
SO IT WASN'T ENOUGH
FOR HER TO POISON MOUSE?
SHE HAD TO FEED HIM
TO BATS, TOO?
YEAH. I THINK THIS IS
HER VERSION OF CLOSURE.
LUKE: YEAH.
DON'T BET ON THAT.
JULIA JUST SAID ALICE PUT
A BUTTERFLY KNIFE
INTO HER RIBS.
SHE'LL LIVE.
NOT SURE WE CAN SAY
THE SAME
FOR ANYONE ELSE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ALICE TOLD JULIA
SHE WAS PLANNING
SOMETHING,
SAID SHE USED
THE WORDS "BRILLIANT"
AND "TERRIFYING,"
WHICH FOR ALICE
IS PRETTY MUCH
REDUNDANT.
DIDN'T GIVE
A WHERE OR WHEN
BUT SAID
THE BODY COUNT
WOULD BE HIGH.
OK. SO SOME SORT
OF PUBLIC EVENT,
A DENSELY POPULATED AREA.
AND THE GOLIATHS
AREN'T PLAYING,
SO IT CAN'T BE
THE STADIUM.
GUYS.
PHILHARMONIC DOESN'T START UP
FOR A FEW WEEKS.
SHE'S GOT 330 SQUARE MILES
OF GOTHAM TO CHOOSE FROM.
-GUYS.
-YES?
I THINK I CAN
NARROW IT DOWN.
BATWOMAN RALLY.
[CROWD CHANTING,
"WE WANT THE BAT!"]
GOT TO ADMIT,
THERE'S A KIND OF
TWISTED POETRY TO KILLING
THE PEOPLE DEMANDING
THE RETURN OF HER SISTER.
WE GOT TO GET THOSE PEOPLE
OUT OF THERE.
LISTEN TO THEM.
THEY'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE
WITHOUT BATWOMAN.
OK. SO WE PUT JULIA
IN THE SUIT.
SHE'S WORN IT BEFORE,
IT FITS.
SHE CAN TELL THEM
ALL TO GO HOME.
I THINK
SHE'S TOO HURT.
IT'S NOT AN OPTION.
I'LL DO IT.
NO.
WELL, I DON'T THINK
YOU HAVE TIME TO
HOLD AUDITIONS.
I THINK PEOPLE
WILL KNOW YOU'RE
NOT BATWOMAN.
I DID REALLY GREAT
MY FIRST TIME IN THE SUIT.
HELLO! BLACK!
OK. I THINK THAT
SHE KNOWS THAT,
AND, WHAT, YOU PUT HER
ON TOP OF A 20-STORY BUILDING,
PEOPLE WILL BE FOCUSED
ON THE SUIT, NOT
THE PERSON IN IT,
AND WE'RE TALKING, WHAT,
20 MINUTES?
YOU--MARY, NO!
WELL, YOU'RE OUT OF OPTIONS,
AND YOU'RE OUT OF TIME.
PUT ME IN THE SUIT.
[PROTESTORS CONTINUE CHANTING,
"WE WANT THE BAT!"]
THIS IS AN UNLAWFUL ASSEMBLY.
YOU ARE HEREBY ORDERED
TO DISPERSE,
OR YOU RISK ARREST
AND PROSECUTION.
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
[SIREN]
WE GAVE THEM A WARNING.
ARREST THEM. BUS THEM
OUT OF HERE.
SIR, THESE PEOPLE ARE HERE
BECAUSE OF KATE.
THEY WANT
THE SAME THING WE DO,
FOR HER TO BE BACK.
[CHANTING, "WE WANT THE BAT!"]
OK. NOBODY SAW THAT.
YEAH. YOU WANT TO USE
THE CAPE TO SLOW
YOUR DESCENT.
THINGS THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
NICE TO KNOW
BEFORE I JUMPED 10 STORIES.
NOTHING'S STOPPING YOU
FROM ASKING
BEFORE THROWING YOURSELF
OFF A BUILDING, FYI.
RYAN: OK.
MARY: NOW LOOK HEROIC!
OK.
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
HOW'S THAT?
STRAIGHTEN
THAT BACK
AND LOSE THE HANDS
ON THE HIPS
BECAUSE
IT'S OVERKILL.
NOW CLENCH THOSE FISTS,
CHIN UP,
AND NOW TRY AND ANGLE
THAT CAPE SO IT
CATCHES THE WIND.
GOOD?
THERE SHE IS!
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
KATE?
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
GET THAT IMPOSTER
OFF THE ROOF.
CITIZENS OF GOTHAM,
YOU NEED TO GET OUT
OF HERE IMMEDIATELY.
[CHEERING]
NO. SERIOUSLY, PEOPLE,
YOUR LIVES ARE IN DANGER.
NO. REALLY, PEOPLE.
I APPRECIATE YOUR SUPPORT,
BUT YOU ALL NEED TO RETURN
TO YOUR HOMES.
[SLOW CLAP]
ALICE: YOU'VE GOT
THEM FOOLED,
BUT NOT ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU ARE,
BUT YOU'RE NOT
BATWOMAN.
WAIT. IS THAT ALICE?
LUKE: UH, RYAN,
TALK TO ME.
RYAN: I'M A LITTLE
BUSY RIGHT NOW.
DO NOT ENGAGE.
OK. SHE'S A KILLER.
I AM WELL AWARE
OF THAT.
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU DOING
IN MY SISTER'S HAND-ME-DOWNS?
THE ONE THING
SHE WOULDN'T DO.
I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
OK. LOOK. I KNOW
WHAT SHE DID TO YOUR MOM,
AND I GET WHAT SHE TOOK
AWAY FROM YOU,
BUT BATWOMAN
DOES NOT KILL.
WELL, LIKE YOU SAID,
I'M NOT BATWOMAN.
I CANNOT LET YOU DO THIS.
DON'T THINK YOU'RE
IN THE POSITION
TO STOP ME.
[BEEP, STATIC]
RYAN. RYAN!
[SIGHS]
WELL, THE SUIT'S FOR REAL.
WHAT ABOUT
THE GIRL INSIDE?
LET'S FIND OUT.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
RYAN!
I KNEW WE SHOULD HAVE NEVER
LET HER NEAR THAT SUIT.
CAN YOU BLAME HER
AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT ALICE HAS DONE?
YOU--YOU CAN'T SERIOUSLY
BE OK WITH THIS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M
REALLY NOT OK WITH?
EVERYBODY JUST EXPECTING
ME TO GET OVER THE FACT
THAT ALICE KILLED MY MOM,
AND MAYBE IF KATE
WOULD HAVE DONE WHAT
RYAN'S TRYING TO DO,
SHE'D STILL BE ALIVE.
YOU WILLING TO BET
KATE'S LEGACY ON THAT?
IT'S OVER FOR YOU.
ON THE CONTRARY,
WE'RE JUST GETTING
STARTED.
[BEEP BEEP BEEP]
[BARKING]
OH, WE GOT A PROBLEM.
CARE TO BE
MORE SPECIFIC.
OK. IT'S A BIG PROBLEM.
RADAR FOOTPRINT'S HUGE.
WHATEVER IT IS, IT'S
HEADING STRAIGHT FOR RYAN.
WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO
DO SOMETHING?
SHH.
[WINGS FLUTTERING,
BATS CHIRPING]
[SCREECHING]
[SCREAMING]
IT APPEARS WE'RE UNDER ATTACK
FROM BATS.
THOUSANDS ARE RUNNING FOR COVER.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING--
LOOK OUT!
AAH!
LUKE: HEY, RYAN.
RYAN, COME IN.
ALICE USED SOME KIND
OF DEVICE
TO DRAW THE BATS HERE.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
OH, MY GOD.
THERE'S FREAKING
BATS EVERYWHERE.
RYAN: YOU DON'T THINK
THESE ARE THE BATS
THAT ALICE FED MOUSE TO?
AND THEY COULD BE
THE CARRIERS
FOR THE TOXIN
THAT KILLED HIM.
I GOT TO GET BACK
TO THE CLINIC.
[DOOR SHUTS]
I'M PICKING UP
A SUBSONIC FREQUENCY
DRAWING THE BATS
TO THE PLAZA.
IT MUST BE SOME KIND
OF TRANSMITTER.
YOU GOT TO GET
DOWN THERE.
I'LL BE THERE
IN ONE MINUTE.
THESE PEOPLE DON'T
HAVE A MINUTE.
RYAN!
DAMN IT!
[SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
I'M BRINGING THE SUIT'S
ECHOLOCATION ONLINE.
UNH!
FOUND IT.
SOPHIE: HEY, GUYS, GUYS.
COME ON. GET INSIDE.
UNH!
WHO ARE YOU?
THE CHICK WHO JUST
SAVED YOUR LIFE.
THESE BATS ARE TOXIC.
ANYONE WHO'S BITTEN,
GET THEM TO THE HOSPITAL.
NOW WHAT SHOULD I DO?
SMASH THE DAMN
THING.
NO. IT'LL SEND THESE
TOXIC BATS ALL OVER THE CITY.
YOU GOT
A BETTER IDEA?
I MIGHT. I JUST DON'T THINK
EITHER OF US IS GONNA LIKE THIS.
MAN: LET'S GET IT
IN THERE.
WE GOT A LOT MORE
COMING.
JUST GET THEM IN HERE.
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
OK.
ANY PAIN?
[MOANING]
I'LL TAKE THAT
AS A YES.
OK.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'LL GET YOU SOMETHING TO
MAKE YOU MORE COMFORTABLE.
[GRUNTS]
I...THINK.
RELAX, STEPPY.
I'VE ALREADY LOST
ONE OF MY SISTERS.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO LOSE
THE, UH,
ONLY ONE I HAVE LEFT.
YOU REALLY BELIEVE
KATE'S DEAD?
YOU KNOW BETTER
THAN ANYONE
THAT NO BODY MEANS
THERE'S STILL HOPE.
OH. I ENVY YOU, SIS.
YOU STILL HAVEN'T KICKED
HOPE TO THE CURB.
SEE, SHE AND I, WE HAVE
AN UNDERSTANDING.
I STAY OUT OF HOPE'S WAY,
AND SHE STAYS OUT OF MINE.
THAT WAY, SHE'S NOT THERE
TO LIE TO ME
ABOUT KATE BEING ALIVE.
NOW WHILE THERE'S
NO HOPE FOR OUR DEAR SISTER,
THERE MAY BE
FOR THE BATFANS.
YOU'RE GIVING ME
YOUR BLOOD?
OH, NO. ACTUALLY,
THAT'S YOUR BLOOD.
I SWIPED IT FROM YOU
WHEN NOCTURNA TRIED
TO DRAIN YOU,
SO TECHNICALLY,
IT'S A REGIFT.
IT'S A RARE
VINTAGE FIND
WITH HINTS OF DESERT ROSE,
AND IT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT WILL TREAT
THAT NASTY, LITTLE TOXIN.
POISONING MY MOM
WASN'T ENOUGH.
YOU HAD TO GO AND POISON
ALL OF GOTHAM, TOO,
AND NOW I'M JUST
SUPPOSED TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU GIFT WRAPPED
THE ANTIDOTE?
HEH. I JUST FIGURED
I'D MISSED A LOT
OF YOUR BIRTHDAYS,
SO...HEH HEH HEH.
I THINK YOU MISS KATE.
I THINK UNDERNEATH
ALL OF YOUR CRAZY,
THIS IS YOUR CRY
FOR HELP.
THIS YOUR SICK WAY
OF GRIEVING?
I MET THE NEW GIRL.
THIS ONE'S ACTUALLY
WILLING TO KILL ME.
SHE'S GONNA BE
A...HANDFUL.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
YOU GOT 3 LANES.
TRY TO STAY IN ONE OF THEM.
OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
I CAN BARELY GET
MY VAN TO DO 40.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
HEY. GOT MORE COMING IN.
I HEARD A REPORT
THAT GOTHAM CITY GENERAL'S
GOT MORE THAN 250.
THEY DON'T KNOW
WHAT THIS IS
OR HOW TO TREAT IT.
GUESS THEY DON'T
HAVE THIS.
IT'S THE ONLY THING
IN THE WORLD THAT
CAN SAVE THEM.
-WHERE'D YOU GET IT?
-FROM ALICE.
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY
TRUST HER.
I DON'T THINK
WE HAVE A CHOICE.
EVEN IF ALICE IS
TELLING THE TRUTH,
YOU CAN'T CURE ALL
THE BITE VICTIMS
WITH JUST THAT.
NO, I CAN'T,
BUT IF I GIVE IT
TO HAMILTON DYNAMICS,
MAYBE THEY CAN SYNTHESIZE
ENOUGH TO SAVE EVERYONE,
OR AT LEAST
I HOPE THEY CAN,
BUT THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
I GOT
A VACANT WAREHOUSE
OFF THE SCHWARTZ
BYPASS, 2.3 MILES.
NO. NOT ENOUGH TIME.
I NEED SOMETHING CLOSER.
OK.
THERE'S A DECOMMISSIONED
SUBWAY STATION
AT NEEDER AVENUE,
SHOULD BE EMPTY.
NO, NO, NO. THAT'S
A HOMELESS ENCAMPMENT.
THERE'S PEOPLE DOWN THERE.
OK, OK.
WORKING ON IT.
NO RUSH.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
LUKE, I MIGHT HAVE
AN IDEA.
TALK TO ME.
PROBABLY BETTER IF I ASK
FOR FORGIVENESS
THAN FOR PERMISSION.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
RYAN, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
WISH I KNEW.
DRIVER: HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET OFF THE BUS NOW!
NO.
-PLEASE.
-WHOA!
-COME ON.
-ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
[BATS SCREECHING]
RYAN: GET DOWN!
BATWOMAN?
OH, NO, NO. I'M NOT
REALLY BATWOMAN.
WELL, YOU ARE TO ME.
AFTER A NIGHT OF TERROR,
HOPE HAS RETURNED TO GOTHAM,
AND IT'S ARRIVED ON THE BACK
OF A HAMILTON DYNAMICS TRUCK.
THANKS TO THE QUICK ACTION
TAKEN BY THE TECHNOLOGY FIRM,
EVERYONE INFECTED
IS RECEIVING TREATMENT.
THE LINES ARE LONG,
AND FRANKLY, SO IS THE NEEDLE.
HAMILTON DYNAMICS IS REMAINING
TIGHT-LIPPED
ON HOW THEY WERE ABLE TO
GENERATE A SERUM SO QUICKLY,
BUT WE'RE ALL CERTAINLY
GLAD THEY DID.
AS FOR THE SWARM...
I MEAN, A LITTLE
CREDIT WOULD
HAVE BEEN NICE.
ALL I DID WAS
GIVE YOU YOUR
MAGIC INGREDIENT
FOR YOUR MIRACLE CURE,
BUT YOU DO YOU,
HAMILTON DYNAMICS.
WHAT'S ALICE'S PLAY HERE?
GOOD DEEDS AREN'T HER THING,
AND I THINK WE BOTH KNOW
SHE DIDN'T JUST GROW
A CONSCIENCE.
SHE WENT THROUGH
A LOT OF TROUBLE
TO UNLEASH A PLAGUE
ONTO AN ENTIRE CITY
ONLY TO PLAY NINTH INNING
JONAS SALK.
SHE'S TOO CUNNING
AND CALCULATING.
THIS IS PART
OF SOMETHING BIGGER.
IF THIS IS THE OPENER,
I DON'T THINK WE'RE
READY FOR THE MAIN EVENT.
ME NEITHER. I JUST HOPE
THE NEW BATWOMAN IS.
[SIGHS]
ME, TOO.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE NEW BATWOMAN?
-UHH.
-DO YOU KNOW WHO SHE IS?
FOR THE RECORD, NO,
BUT SHORT OF A NAME,
IS THERE ANY ANSWER
I COULD GIVE YOU THAT
YOU'D BELIEVE?
PROBABLY NOT.
WELL, MAYBE I CAN GIVE YOU
A CONSOLATION PRIZE,
A POSSIBLE LOCATION
ON ALICE.
I HAD THEM ANALYZE
THE FLOOR MATS ON MY SUV
AFTER MY LITTLE CHAT
WITH ALICE.
TURNS OUT HER BOOTS
LEFT BEHIND TRACES
OF TRI-ETHYL BENZENE,
A BYPRODUCT
OF TIRE MANUFACTURING.
I'M GUESSING SHE'S
HOLED UP SOMEWHERE
NEAR THE DRESNER
MOTOR PLANT.
GOOD. LET'S KEEP
THIS BETWEEN US.
BACKUP WILL JUST
SCARE HER OFF.
DID SHE SAY
SHE LOVED YOU?
IN THE LETTER,
DID KATE SAY
SHE LOVED YOU?
WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
IF WE'RE OVER
BECAUSE YOU DON'T TRUST ME
OR...BECAUSE I'M
NOT KATE.
BOTH.
SO, WHAT,
YOU DIDN'T ASK ME
ENOUGH QUESTIONS
THE FIRST TIME?
YOU GONNA BREAK OUT
THE WATERBOARD?
LOOK. I KNOW I HAULED
YOU IN HERE
AND INTERROGATED YOU
LIKE SOME SUSPECT,
AND I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I'M TRYING. I AM.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO
MAKE THE SAME MISTAKES
THAT I MADE WITH BETH.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP
HOPE THAT KATE'S ALIVE.
YOU BELIEVE SHE'S STILL
ALIVE, DON'T YOU?
I--I THINK THAT
IF WE'RE GONNA FIND HER
YOU AND I HAVE TO
WORK TOGETHER.
I DIDN'T KNOW THE WHOLE
DRY-CLEANING SITUATION,
BUT I THINK THAT BURNT BAT
SMELL IS HERE TO STAY.
HEH.
AND I WAS KIND OF
HOPING I COULD
BE, TOO.
I APPRECIATE
EVERYTHING YOU DID.
BUT SAVING
A WHOLE BUNCH
OF LIVES TWICE
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH?
WE ALREADY HAVE
A BATWOMAN.
WHERE WAS SHE
LAST NIGHT?
BEST THING THAT EVER
HAPPENED TO ME
WAS THE DAY
MAMA CORA FOUND ME.
SECOND BEST THING
WAS THE DAY I FOUND
THAT SUIT,
BUT I CAN'T HELP
BUT TO FEEL LIKE
THAT SUIT FOUND ME.
THIS CITY NEEDS HOPE,
LUKE.
HELL, WE ALL NEED IT,
AND I SAW IT TODAY
IN THE FACE
OF A YOUNG GIRL
WHO'S BEEN TOLD HER
ENTIRE LIFE
THAT HOPE DOESN'T
EXIST.
GIVE ME A CHANCE,
AND I CAN BRING THAT
HOPE BACK TO GOTHAM.
LOOK. KATE KANE WAS TOP
OF HER CLASS
AT ONE OF THE MOST
ELITE MILITARY ACADEMIES
IN THE WORLD,
AND SHE STILL STRUGGLED
TO TAKE DOWN CRIMINALS.
MAYBE SHE DIDN'T
SPEND ENOUGH TIME
WITH THEM.
I HAVE BEEN TRAPPED
IN A LIFE SURROUNDED
BY CRIMINALS.
I KNOW HOW THEY THINK,
HOW THEY ACT,
BUT MOST OF ALL,
I KNOW HOW TO STOP THEM.
MARY: I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT
BECAUSE IF ALICE IS
PLANNING SOMETHING BIG,
THEN THE CITY'S GONNA NEED
A BATWOMAN,
AND HONESTLY, SO DO I.
BATWOMAN...HAS A CODE.
NO KILLING.
[SIGHS]
FINE. UNTIL KATE'S BACK.
COME ON. I'LL SHOW
YOU AROUND. HA!
IT'S MY FIRST TIME
GIVING THE TOUR.
WOMAN: ♪ AND EVERYTHING
IS MOVING ON ♪
VESPER FAIRCHILD:
GREETINGS, G-TOWN.
SO HOW WAS YOUR NIGHT?
IN WHAT COULD HAVE BEEN
A REAL BATASTROPHE,
VICTORY WAS PULLED
FROM THE TINY JAWS OF DEFEAT
BY OUR RETURNING CHAMPION
BATWOMAN,
BUT SOME EYEWITNESSES REPORT
THAT LAST NIGHT'S HEROICS
WERE COURTESY OF A NEW LADY BAT.
IS THIS TRUE? DID THE OLD ONE
JUST THROW IN THE COWL?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
TALK TO ME, GOTHAM.
WOMAN: ♪ WHEN IN IT FILLS UP
YOUR BREATH ♪
♪ AND IN YOUR SOUL
♪ YOU'RE NEVER THE SAME
♪ THIS THE MO-O-O-OMENT
♪ AH, OOH, OOH, OOH,
OOH, OOH, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ OOH, OOH, OOH
♪ LEARNING FROM EVERY SINGLE
STUTTER ♪
♪ A SELF-REVOLUTION
♪ THE ONLY THING
THAT NEVER FIT ♪
♪ YOU FEEL ON DISPLAY
RYAN, VOICE-OVER: "DEAR BRUCE,
HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
"A FEW TRICKS,
ONE NICE TREAT.
"TONIGHT, I SAW A GIRL
WHO REMINDED ME OF MYSELF.
SCARED BUT FEARLESS."
AGH!
[GRUNTING]
"DETERMINED NOT TO LET
THE DARKNESS OF GOTHAM
"GET THE BEST OF HER.
PEOPLE LIKE HER ARE
THE HOPE THIS CITY NEEDS."
WOMAN: ♪ THE ONE WHERE
YOU FIND YOU ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER FORGET
♪ WHEN IT FILLS UP YOUR BREATH
♪ AND IN YOUR SOUL
♪ YOU'RE NEVER THE SAME
♪ THIS IS THE M-O-O-O-OMENT
I'VE NEVER LOOKED
GOOD IN RED.
PUT THEM ON.
BEHIND YOUR BACK.
WOMAN: SHE'S MINE.
UNH!
[THUD]
THE DESERT ROSE
WAS NOT MEANT FOR GOTHAM,
AND NOW YOUR LITTLE STUNT
WITH THAT MIRACLE CURE
HAS DRAWN SAFIYAH'S WRATH.
WELL, THAT WAS
WHAT I INTENDED, SO...
STUPID GIRL.
MY DEAR, SWEET
TATIANA,
IF YOU WERE SENT
HERE TO KILL ME,
MY HEAD WOULD ALREADY
BE IN YOUR CARRY-ON
ON THE WAY BACK
TO CORYANA.
SAFIYAH WILL SEE YOU
DIE FOR THIS.
MAYBE, BUT FIRST,
SHE HAS TO SEE ME.
UNH!
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!