Previously, on
"Batwoman"...
Ryan's only hope
is the desert Rose,
which is on Coryana
with Kate.
- Who's Safiyah?
- The woman who has my daughter.
We can't locate her,
but since this was
the last thing on Kate's phone,
we think it will help.
The many arms
will kill whoever
lays hands
on that painting.
You'll never find
Coryana.
The painting gets us to Coryana?
Is it a map?
Aah! It feels like
my brain is hemorrhaging.
It's even nastier
since yesterday.
It kind of reeks, too.
It kind of...
Thanks, Luke!
Very helpful!
Ok. Remember
a few days ago
when I deleted half the dvr
to make room for your shows?
- What?
- Just remember you like me, ok?
- What the hell just happened?
- I am trying really hard
not to seriously
freak out right now,
but I'm pretty sure
the kryptonite
just entered her brain.
*BATWOMAN*
Season 02  Episode 07
Episode Title:
"It's Best You Stop Digging "
Aired on:
March 14, 2021
I not only
have to fly to Gotham,
but then you make me
Wade through a mile
of rabid rats
to find you?
It's a wee bit remote,
but these types of places
kind of have to be.
This was ocean's smoke-out,
wu-wu meditation spot.
Was?
As promised,
Tatiana.
I think you'll find
the ocean is dead calm.
Got to admit I didn't
think you had it in you.
Unh!
You really shouldn't
be thinking at all, Tatiana.
It's not your strong suit.
I never would have
traded that map for Alice
if I'd known I'd be forced
to hand it right back over
to a bunch of thugs.
Some highly paid thugs
it turns out.
Aaron helzinger wanted the desert
Rose to heal his damaged amygdala.
He also claimed that
Hamilton doctors
had been experimenting
on his brain.
We can assume
those same doctors
were the ones who sent him to
Mary and me for more antidote.
These are all
the doctors he's seen?
Yeah. Most of them work for
upstanding regional hospitals
except one...
Dr. Ethan Rogers.
Rogers was Helzinger's last
known neurologist, worked in a lab.
Appears to have been running
off-the-grid medical experiments.
You think Rogers was
responsible for taking the map?
We found that
garnick logistics was owned
by an offshore company held
by Hamilton dynamics.
It appears we have
unearthed yet another
of Catherine's
dirty, little secrets.
- Let's go get that map, sir.
- Let's go get that map.
Good morning,
my little lesbian pet.
What is this?
Oh, this? Yeah.
This is storytime.
See, you are going to take
me down memoryless Lane,
tell me the who, what,
where, and why
ocean and I were
experiencing fleeting moments
of forgotten memory.
Does it really matter?
He's dead.
Yeah. Well, I think you'll
find you have that in common
if you don't start
talking!
Thought you'd figured it
out by now.
Safiyah had
your memories wiped.
I know, but Safiyah
rules over an island.
I was an orphan
runaway.
What was so threatening
about little old me?
To understand what made
you a threat,
you have to understand
what made you appealing.
You and Safiyah had
a common enemy.
Catherine Hamilton?
I remember.
After Catherine
burned Safiyah
on an island
defense system,
Safiyah instructed us
to steal one of her yachts
to teach her a lesson.
Turns out vengeful minds
think alike
because we found you
stowed away in the cabin,
wearing her clothes, swilling
her 5-figure bottles of champagne.
Why the hell
am I here?
Can I kill
her now?
Leave us, please.
She's a filthy
outsider.
- We have no use for her.
- She is my prisoner.
I will deal with her
my way.
You fought off 4
of my men
before we put you down.
To me, you were
a feral animal,
but to Safiyah,
you were something else.
You were special.
Relax. I'm not
going to hurt you,
and from the looks of
what you did to my men,
I wouldn't stand
a chance.
Why am I here?
What do you want?
First, I'd like to know why
a beautiful young woman
with her entire life
ahead of her
was found sequestered
away on a boat
floating in the middle
of nowhere.
Let's just say I've grown
accustomed to small spaces.
The real world can be an
overwhelming place sometimes.
I understand we both
have a bone to pick
with Catherine
Hamilton-Kane.
She convinced
my entire family
I was dead while I spent
the last 11 years
in my kidnapper's
basement cell.
And here you are,
a siren once trapped
in a net,
who somehow
found her way out.
Safiyah liked you
because she was inspired by you.
Whatever story you told her
of your captivity,
you did the one thing
she never could...
Escape. She would never
admit it,
but to this day, she considers
herself a prisoner of Coryana.
Oh. Poor thing.
It must be so hard
being handed a kingdom,
but I remember
all of this.
When did ocean
factor in?
When Safiyah realized
you had purpose.
Technically,
you were our prisoner,
but she wanted to harness
the rage you had for Catherine
by making you one
of her loyal soldiers
except you were
an untamed and angry girl.
You needed discipline.
And Safiyah knew exactly
who would teach you
how to be a good,
little soldier.
Ocean.
Hi.
There are
very few rules on our island...
No leaving, no stealing
the desert Rose,
and if Safiyah wants
something, she gets it,
and Safiyah wanted
your loyalty
so that after you went home
to Gotham
to get revenge
against your family
you would come back
and join hers.
And what did I want?
You wanted ocean.
Hey. Come here.
Sophie thinks they might
know who took the map.
They're bringing an
army of crows to his work.
So what happens next?
Does Ryan suit up
and jump on the jet
with them?
No. She's never
gonna make it.
She has acute radiation.
Her bone marrow
is disintegrating.
Her circulatory system
is failing.
Ok. So what do you
suggest?
I think we need to ask
my dad to bring
a flower back
with Kate.
If he finds the map
and if he gets there in time,
not to mention, Mary, that the
man just shut down your clinic.
- I know.
- How do you think he'll react to
finding out that you're
on the bat team?
I'm still in
the brainstorming phase.
Oh!
Ryan!
So you're telling me
that...
A little crush
on the first cute boy
I laid eyes on
after escaping captivity
for 11 years
threw the island queen
into a tizzy?
It wasn't like that.
In fact, at first,
no one even noticed.
Let me guess-
clandestine trysts
by the water well?
No.
The reason
no one noticed
was because you two
hated each other.
Unh!
Now use my weight
against me.
Unh!
Aah! Ohh!
The game
is never over.
What's the point
of this?
Has anyone ever heard
of a gun?
Guns can jam,
get taken.
The real fight
is in here,
and that they can't
take away.
Preparation, engagement,
commitment.
Surrendering to false gods
and ideologies.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means there is
a whole world
outside the island that
you know nothing about...
Books, food, electricity...
And Safiyah likes to
keep it that way
so that you stay close
and loyal and uninspired.
Unh!
As the weeks passed,
you two became
each other's sparring partners.
I think Safiyah
will like you.
This is a waste
of time.
You're not even
trying.
You're wasting
your own time.
Well, if it's all
the same to you,
I'd rather waste my time
and go get drunk.
W-What do you really want?
Revenge?
Why?
Because your family moved
on after more than a decade?
Catherine Hamilton lied
through her teeth
so they would
forget me.
Or maybe she did them
a favor.
You said they looked
for a year.
You weren't gonna be found.
What were they supposed to do,
sit around and be miserable
for the next decade?
Is that really
what you wanted,
the family you supposedly
love and miss so much?
You don't need to learn
how to fight, Alice.
You need to learn
how to feel.
Baby...
Are you sure you want to
be going where you're going?
You know
I have faith
in your
decision-making.
All I'm cautioning
is be mindful
the company you keep.
Other people judge
your friends.
Mama... angelique is
a good person.
Mm-hmm. She also
gets in trouble,
and I don't want you
getting roped into her drama.
You were put
on this earth
for bigger and better
things, child.
I know.
You tell me this every day. Ha!
Mama?
What the?
What happened?
Why'd you stop?
Mama.
Mama, what happened?
Batwoman,
do you copy? Batwoman!
She just hit
92 miles per hour,
and she's not answering
her comms.
Where the hell
is she going?
She's headed
towards the west end.
What the hell's up there?
- Oh, no.
- What?
Of course that's
where she went.
Where?
Where's she going?
Her brain isn't
working,
- so she turned to her heart.
- What?
Oh, my god!
What he actual hell?
Angie. Angelique.
How do you know
my name?
And are... are you ok?
I...
Hey. Where's
your wine opener?
Oh, my god!
- She doesn't drink.
- I don't drink.
I'm sorry. How do you
know my life?
Angie, what is
going on?
- Angie.
- Shouldn't you be out,
like, fighting crime?
I'm looking
for your friend...
Ocean.
Can I have two seconds?
Ok.
Ahem. Sorry.
No idea, uh, who you're
talking about.
Maybe you know
what this is.
Whoa. What are you
gonna do, slash me?
Look. The dude grows shrooms
in a concrete jungle.
If you can't find him, maybe
you shouldn't quit your day job.
Or I'll haul your ass
into the cops,
and I'll let them
sweat it out of you.
All right. Fine.
You got me.
You'll find him
in coventry.
I'll give you
a head start.
Aah!
Grab her legs.
This is the
Gotham city police department.
Stop and back away
from the suspect.
I repeat.
Back away from the suspect.
You are interfering
in a police response.
Freeze. You are under arrest
and ordered not to move.
Repeat. You are under arrest...
I'll meet you
in the batcave.
- Why are you giving me the keys?
- I have to take the Batmobile.
- I can take the Batmobile.
- You've never driven it before.
- I've never driven your car before.
- Mary, no!
- Yes!
- No!
- Mary!
- Yes!
- Release the suspect.
- We don't have time for this.
- Give me, give me!
You are under arrest
and ordered...
Hell, yeah!
Mama?
Mama!
Why are you here?
Why did you do this
to us?
You must be mad,
or you wouldn't have
come here.
Why did you kill her?
What was the point?
Huh!
You know how much pain
you caused me?
How do you do that?
How do you just murder
someone's mom
and move on like
it doesn't matter?
Ha ha ha!
Huh!
Tell me you remember her!
Tell me her name!
Cora. Cora Lewis.
What are you doing?
I'm getting the justice...
Aah!
My mother deserves.
Ok. Ok. So I hid
the Batmobile keys in dino,
and I'm putting
an extra tracker
in her gauntlet cuffs in case
she decides to run off again
and thinks to turn off
her GPS.
- What are you doing?
- I'm mixing two
complementary
cardiotonics
to calm down her mind
and speed up her system
and hopefully pull her
out of these hallucinations,
but... this isn't
gonna last,
and since I don't have
access to my clinic anymore,
I'm gonna need
a few supplies.
Ok. Great. Do I look
like postmates, or...
No, nor do you
look like a doctor,
which is who needs to
stay with her right now,
unless you want to
give it a shot,
you know, put her life in
your hands just for funsies?
Ok. I'll be back.
Hmm?
Ah, ah, ah.
Save some
for the fishies.
So Safiyah and I
shared a common enemy,
she thought I'd be
a good soldier,
and I started to hate-crush
her metaphorical brother.
Call me old-fashioned, but I'm
missing the motive for a lobotomy.
You're really not
getting it, are you?
Well, you're not exactly
unfolding the plot
to a shakespearian
drama here.
Safiyah would claim she
wanted you for her army,
survival instincts
would make you
an excellent fighter
and advisor.
And what would you
claim?
That she was
in love with you.
I heard there was wine.
Sounds like training's
going well.
I have yet to see
the point of an army.
You have no crime here,
everyone walks around
with a smile.
I'm in Roman pleasantville.
That's actually why
I invited you here,
to tell you
about the desert Rose.
It's delicate and vibrant
and in the wrong hands one of the
most dangerous weapons in the world.
This?
Its serum can cure illness,
hereditary disease.
It can expunge toxins,
pathogens.
This simple flower
is a miracle cure-all, Alice,
and it's my birthright
to protect it at all costs.
- Hence the army.
On occasion, word of a mystical
flower on a faraway island
draws unwanted attention.
If outsiders were able
to come take it,
we'd be left with nothing,
and our sanctuary
would be destroyed.
Why don't you just
grow more?
According to the lore,
centuries ago,
the women of a village
in Europe
banded together to escape
their abusive husbands.
They'd heard tell
of an island
under the constellations
of cassiopeia and Andromeda,
and they fled here
with their children in tow.
Months later, the men
they escaped tracked them down.
As their ships landed,
the men were met
by a ferocious
female army.
The women succeeded in
driving the men back into the sea.
However, it was
at great cost.
Many women lay dead,
slaughtered.
Only my ancestors
and a few others survived.
The next day, a field
of roses bloomed
in the very spot
of the battle.
The women claimed the
blood that had been spilled
was sacred,
its protective feminine
essence enriched the land.
They wrote that only
a woman's life force
could birth this medicine
destined to save mankind.
Heh heh.
She knew she
couldn't tell you how she felt,
so she showed you.
She entrusted you
with her most
valued secret.
And someone was
a little jealous?
Ha ha ha!
You weren't a threat
to me, Alice.
You were a threat to the
entire island of Coryana.
Not even, like, a teeny,
weeny, itty, bitty bit jealous?
I'm Safiyah's
right hand.
It's my job
to tell her
when there's a fox
in the henhouse.
So you think I'm a fox?
I think you're
a distraction.
I think you're in love
with her.
You are such a child.
Well, you're the one who can't
admit you're in love with her.
- Of course, I'm in love with her.
- Ha ha ha!
And you'd better believe
that when the first
opportunity arose
for me to destroy you
I did not hesitate.
Let's go, let's go!
Got to wonder if Catherine
ever wandered these halls.
Guess there's a lot
you didn't know about her.
Well, apparently,
it runs in the family.
Turns out Mary was operating
an illegal medical clinic
out of
a church basement.
Really? That's... huh.
Did you know?
- Sir...
- You got to be kidding me.
No one wants to tell
me anything around here.
Because I knew you'd
shut it down.
That place was her life.
She helped a lot
of people.
Have you two
spoken since?
I refuse to let her
turn into her mother.
Catherine cut a lot
of corners at Hamilton.
Look where it got us.
I'll take that
as a no.
Synthetic granulocytes.
My god.
Now injecting them
in patient B,
an 80-year-old male
with a similar cancer.
Our hypothesis is that
the new solution
Dr. Rogers!
So much for our lead.
So we'll
check back in 24 hours
and look for progress.
Help!
Uh, just calm down, breathe.
We need help in here!
Try to breathe.
What the hell are we
dealing with?
Ryan, can you hear me?
This kryptonite gives
a worse hangover
than $2.00 Tequila.
Wait. How did I get
back here?
Luke and I found you
outside of Angelique's.
Yeah.
But good news...
I got to drive the Batmobile.
Bad news... the wipers button
and the rocket launchers
look very similar.
Someone should
label those.
What did you do?
I should be asking you
that, Missy.
Why'd you go to Angelique's
in the batsuit?
I needed a lead
on ocean.
You're dying,
and you waste
your last gasps
of energy on him?
No. I find ocean,
I find Alice
so I can hear
her last gasp.
- Ryan.
- No. I am not going down
without getting justice
for both of our moms.
Let's just get some
more fluids in you first,
and then we can talk...
Bucket list.
This is Rogers' office.
We looked
into the deceased,
and everyone seems
to have been involved
in the experiments
with the desert Rose.
My guess is they were trying
to create more and failed.
Coryana sent their
assassins to cover their tracks.
I believe Safiyah calls them
the many arms of death.
Let's just hope they didn't
find the map that Rogers stole.
It has to be around here
somewhere.
Hang on.
Bingo.
They beat us to it.
Agh! Agh!
Sir.
They have my Kate,
damn it.
I can't stand losing
another daughter like this.
When I was being held
in that cell,
my father and sister
came looking for me.
I was told if I made a sound
they'd be shot,
but Kate, my, um...
my twin,
she found my cell,
and I heard her
put her hand on the door,
so I did the same,
and I just stood there
silently... Praying
that she would...
Feel me.
And she never did?
You asked
why I want revenge.
It's because I can't
forget moments like that.
Then don't,
but do you really
want to spend
the rest of your life trying
to get her to apologize?
Because that's not
how this works.
She's your sister.
She will spend
every waking moment
trying to fix it,
to fix you,
and she can't.
Only you can do that.
You got out,
you got your second chance.
Let it go.
Be happy.
You make that sound
so...
So easy.
It is.
At least it is now.
Desert Rose snips.
I'll plant them,
nurture them,
feed them blood
so they bloom.
Pretty soon, all of mankind
will have its miracle drug,
and I'll have money
to travel the world.
You are not supposed
to have those.
There's a lot Safiyah
tells us we can't have.
I want to do
what you did.
I want to escape,
I want to start over
and experience life
outside this island.
And I want you
to come with me.
The man
you were willing
to change your life for,
the one person who
offered you a second chance
and freedom
from your past
is the same man Safiyah
convinced you to stab
through the heart.
Ha ha ha!
I'm sorry. That's it?
That's your big
mic drop moment?
"Surprise! You killed
your soul mate
that you don't even
remember."
Yeah. I found my
mother's head in a freezer,
so if you're trying
to shock me,
you're gonna have to
do a little better than that.
Don't you think you
should be lying down?
Angelique said
he grew shrooms
in a concrete jungle,
meaning he would need
some type
of indoor forest.
That means a neighborhood
with a high moisture level.
- North side by the water.
- Wait. What?
He'd have to block out
his windows,
wouldn't want
questions asked,
and he'd have to draw
a crapload of power
for all those
grow lamps.
Oh! The grow lamps.
Ryan, you need to
lie down.
I need to find Alice.
No. I... I can't let you
kill Alice.
Do you love
your mom?
Of course I do.
Do you believe
in what we do here?
You know I do.
Then how can we stand
behind this symbol
and claim we fight
for justice
and we stand up
for victims
and we protect
our streets
with a legitimate serial-killing
psychopath out there,
living, breathing,
looking for a way to find
your sister
- and kill her, too?
- And we will stop her!
When?
When two crows bring
me some miracle flower
from an island
we can't get to?
- That's what I was...
- Did they find the map?
Did they find the map?
The map's gone.
Alice took our moms
from us, Mary.
Do you ever
for a second
think about what your life
would be like
if she were
still here?
If she could be proud
of you for one more day,
if you could ask her
for advice
or tell her
about a crush
or hear her tell you
she loves you?
A million times a day.
I am as good as dead,
Mary,
and I am not
leaving here
without getting
justice,
so... you can step
out of my way
and let me do
my thing,
or I can go
through you.
Keys are in dino.
What are you doing?
Packing up.
We're done.
You don't want to
know more?
What's to know?
Safiyah got jealous,
so she took away
my memory of ocean
to punish me.
I could have saved
a lot of time
by reading the back
of the book.
It wasn't as simple as plucking
out just those memories.
There was
collateral damage.
I never thought
I'd see the day
that a man I considered
a brother
would be kneeling before me
a betrayer of his island
and his people!
That flower is
everything to us,
that which defines us,
that which is the key
to our survival!
Safiyah, we both know this
isn't about a stupid flower.
And what do you
think it's about?
Me having the one thing
you can't.
Alice
is a snake
that slithered
into our garden.
Let me kill her.
We're not killing anyone.
I'm going to visit
a punishment upon her
that fits the crime.
Find enigma,
bring her to me.
Safiyah, no.
You can't do this.
Yes, my queen.
You wanted to take
the one thing that was
precious to me.
I will take what's
most precious to you...
Each other!
- Who's enigma?
- A hypnotist.
She wants to screw
with our heads.
You're not a snake, Alice.
You're just
a broken little girl,
who sought refuge
from her trauma
by escaping
into a fantastical book!
I know the big, wild world
seemed daunting to you.
I was going to show you
how easily
you could rise and thrive,
but instead, you turned to
him for solace and rehabilitation.
She didn't do
anything wrong!
You are going to
go home, Alice!
You are going to embrace
this fairytale persona of yours,
and you're going to imbue it
with fury!
You will build
your own army,
you will become your own queen,
and you will carry out
the vengeance on your family
that you
so desperately crave,
and you'll forget
all about ocean
and your love
for each other!
Don't do this,
Safiyah.
With the memories came
the love and humanity that
was bubbling up inside of you.
Safiyah took that
and in turn
activated this...
Cold, hard,
vengeance-obsessed
killing machine.
You would have
run away with ocean
and started
a new life,
happy, free, in love.
Instead, Safiyah
turned you into herself.
You look upset.
Shakespearian enough
for you?
Take the body.
I'll call you
for my pickup.
Where are you going?
Oh, I'm not requesting
an audience with the queen
dressed like this.
Gotcha.
- Enigma did this?
- Mm-hmm.
Of course.
She's a hypnotist.
Owed Safiyah
a favor.
Safiyah and her legion
of lady loyalists.
Tatiana found out you were
stealing the desert Rose.
Good riddance.
That flower's meant to save lives,
yet it destroys
everything it touches.
And... I guess
this is it.
There's a bar
in portofino
I've always
wanted to try.
Cobblestone streets,
view of the harbor.
What about you?
What now?
Uh... now I'm off
to Coryana
to get my final revenge
on my sister.
Unless... you have
a reason to stop me.
Live your life.
See you, Alice.
Where's Ryan?
My dad couldn't find
the map,
so there's no way
to find Coryana.
Why are her comms off?
Where is she?
- She's gonna die.
- Mary, where is Ryan?
Alice, do you know
who I am?
Ok. I've had a day.
Can we do this in,
say, 2... 3 weeks?
Do you know who I am?
Honestly, so many women
keep showing up
in that outfit, it's
impossible to keep track.
How's this?
You killed my mom,
and now I'm here
to kill you.
Heh. You're kidding,
right?
That's what this
is about?
My mom was Cora Lewis.
Your gang beat her to death
on December 13, 2015.
I get it.
Mommy died,
and now you're
a "woman on fire,"
which means I'm
responsible for spawning
not one batwoman...
But two.
- You think this is funny?
- Yes.
My mom meant
everything to me!
I have no memory
of your mommy.
- Liar!
- Unh!
Aah!
Aw. Did you hurt
yourself?
Is that my fault, too?
Unh!
Aah! Ohh!
Aah!
Hyah!
- Raah!
- Aah!
I wasn't the one
who killed her.
Your army did
because of you
because you turned them
into coldblooded killers!
- Ha ha ha!
- Aah!
Agh!
Ryan!
This isn't the girl
I raised.
But she killed you.
Agh!
Ugh.
I don't know
what made you this way,
but you're not
worth it.
You'll never
be worth it!
It wasn't my fault.
Everything's
your fault.
Now leave!
No sign of Alice
anywhere, sir.
You know, I figured out
why Catherine lied
and said that Beth
was dead.
She was doing me a favor.
The only thing worse than
losing one of your children
is the cycle
of waking up every morning
with hope and then
having it ripped away
and losing them all over
again by dinner.
Sir, you really
should get some sleep.
I won't sleep until
I have my family back.
This must be
the airport shuttle.
Get in.
Air Coryana terminal,
Jeevsy.
Where's Alice?
Hello to you, too.
Well, I realized killing
her would only
make me more like her.
Kind of went along
with what you guys were saying.
Great.
So where is she?
- I let her go.
- What?! Ok.
There's not killing,
but there's still apprehending.
We need her to go
to Coryana.
No, we don't.
She'll kill Kate.
I'll stop her.
I put a tracker
in her boot.
We follow her,
we find Coryana,
we save Kate.
And we get you
the desert Rose.
Sync corrections by srjanapala
Resynced by
== Flatto (subscene.com) ==