Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey. Eli, knock it off.
Do yourself a favor.
Don't make me your problem.
What the hell's going on?
Sir, this man is trying
to steal a car.
This guy is a known car thief.
You know what?
I have photographic evidence.
Gun!
27-year-old male
with multiple gunshot wounds
to the abdomen.
He lost consciousness en route.
Vitals are unstable
and he lost over a liter of blood
at the scene.
Get him up to the O.R. now.
So, Agent Tavaroff,
the Crows have been
through this type
of officer-involved shooting before.
We need to investigate
the incident with Luke Fox
and get your story,
so run us through what happened.
Well, Agent Miller
and I were on patrol
when we heard a car alarm.
We arrived to find
a suspicious-looking man
loitering near a vehicle.
We approached.
Suspect reached inside his jacket
and pulled out a gun.
Luke Fox used to work
for my daughter.
He seems more like the type to wield
a keyboard than a gun.
Well, I don't know him,
but I know what I saw.
Suspect turned to shoot
and I fired before he could
do the same to us.
Sounds like you should be commended
for your bravery, Agent Tavaroff.
Any more questions?
We have to review
the bodycam footage.
Send in Agent Miller.
Of course, sir. Thank you.
Lost his pulse.
We need to start CPR now.
He's flatlining.
Hello?
Dad?
How many times was she shot?
Two. The first bullet caused injury
to his kidney, spleen, colon.
The second tore through a major vein,
causing massive blood loss.
Already coded twice
and right now, he's in a coma.
They're not sure
if he's gonna make it.
Wait. Tell me everything
that happened.
We were on the phone.
He saw some guy jack a car
- so he said, he would handle it.
- What do you mean "handle it"?
Oh, god. I don't know.
So, when he didn't call me back,
I got worried and...
You realized he couldn't handle it.
- Why didn't Luke just call it in?
- I told him to, but he said that
he recognized the guy
from your holding cell.
- Eli or something.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. White boy.
He was in jail with us
for stealing a car.
You think that he did this?
For his sake...
I hope not.
I will let Batwoman sort
that one out.
I've nominated myself
to save Luke's life.
So, why aren't you
at Gotham General right now?
Because Gotham General
doesn't have this.
Things I don't want
to know for a thousand, Alex.
Curiouser and curiouser.
What?
Typically when one storms out
after winning an argument
they don't come crawling back.
Takes the drama out of it.
Figured.
I'd ditch the evidence.
Probably for the best considering
whose daughter that is.
No idea.
Riddle me that.
Might want to ditch this, too.
So... You think I won the argument?
No. I think you stopped me
from retrieving the password
to Kate's memory bank
and now, I'm left
puzzling through her files,
trying to retrieve some answer key
so I can get Kate's memory back.
Still won't give up on Kate?
I know why I'm invested,
but why is Black Mask so obsessed
with knowing all the dirty details
of the Kane family?
Our dead doctor's
been sending him her research.
I don't care.
I told you how I feel.
Your sister isn't worth
you getting killed over.
Fine.
I guess I'm on my own then.
I didn't do anything.
You're driving a stolen car, dumbass.
I prefer the term borrowed.
Yeah?
Were you borrowing a car earlier
when you shot the guy
who tried to stop you?
It wasn't like that.
The Crows rolled up out of nowhere.
What do you mean the Crows rolled up?
They did this?
I've never shot a gun in my life.
How are you here
and he's in the hospital?
They saw us both.
I may have said
he was boosting the ride.
You think maybe
that was gonna get him shot?
He was stupid enough
to grab his phone.
Next thing I knew,
someone yelled out "gun"
and then fired.
How the hell did you get away?
I saw a chance and I ran.
They didn't bother to follow.
I swear. That's how it went down.
What did they look like?
Badge numbers, I.D.s, plates.
Ta... Tavaroff.
I heard the one guy scream,
"What'd you do?" At him.
You know, if that guy
had just minded his business
and let me take the car
I'd have been out of there
and he'd be fine.
You're saying this is his fault?
It's the truth.
He didn't need
to make me his problem.
And the Crows didn't need
to shoot him.
Sounds like your beef is with them,
so how about letting me go.
How about not?
Maybe you should have minded
your own business.
Dad.
- Dad.
- You know it's impossible
to get your old man's attention
when he's deep in thought.
Bruce.
What are you doing here?
You called me here.
I... I didn't...
Why would I call you here?
Luke, you've been shot.
You brought me here
because you have a choice to make.
Gotham reels
from the latest shooting
of a black man
at the hands of the Crows.
This incident comes on the heels
of the recent Crows controversy
where some say excessive
firepower was used
to contain the latest
Snakebite epidemic.
Crow officials have yet
to release a statement on the issue
and per their official policy
they refuse to release
the names of the agents involved.
Behind me,
protestors are gathering...
How much longer?
An hour or two tops.
Crows let the real suspect get away,
didn't even bother chasing him.
I left him for the GCPD.
They can't get away with this.
We have to get justice for Luke.
Focus on saving him.
I'll take care of the Crows.
How do you access the freaking
internet on this thing?
I think...
Okay.
- Son of a bitch.
- Is that the agent who shot Luke?
Russell Tavaroff.
He was responsible
for the massacre at the church,
crashed my False Face operation
two weeks ago.
Of course, he did this!
Hey. You need backup?
Not me, but I can call Sophie.
I want to see how Russell does
against someone who is bulletproof.
Hang on, Luke. Help is on the way.
You've got to be kidding me.
Get out of here.
I'm going to assume
if Batwoman were here
she wouldn't have sent you
to shoo me away
with a big box store brand taser.
Rest assured...
I'm not afraid of you.
Yeah. Okay.
How are you still even here?
Didn't False Face deal
with you already?
Actually, that's what brings me.
I was wondering
if you had any unexpected run-ins
with Black Mask's side chick?
Goes by Circe.
Never heard of her.
Are you sure?
She used to run around
in a wooden hockey mask.
Now, she's
a supermodel-esque assassin.
I'm sorry. Why am I supposed
to care about this person?
You aren't...
and turns out,
she doesn't care about you either.
Well, helpful as always. Toodles.
There's always a reason with you.
Who is she?
Turns out Black Mask
is the only person
who hates the Kane family
more than I do
and as much
as I'm unwilling to admit it,
that includes you.
Watch your back, steppy.
So, you came here to warn me
out of the goodness
of your empty chest cavity?
Enemy of my enemy and all that.
Aren't you besties with Batty?
Maybe it's worth keeping her
within reach if you want to live.
I know you're in love...
And maybe if you'd seen
it earlier in your life,
you might not be the monster
that you are today.
As much as I hate you, Alice,
everyone deserves love.
Not so easy now, is it?
Confess to what you did and maybe
I'll let you keep breathing.
- It's not your fight.
- Yeah?
You shot an innocent,
unarmed black man.
- The fight is in my DNA.
- Innocent?
I looked him up.
Kid was released from jail
hours before we caught him stealing
a car.
He broke the law
just like you're doing right now.
Body go bye- bye?
Can't be traced back to us.
"Us".
That word does have
a nice domestic flare to it,
even in the context
of disposing of a body.
You made your priorities clear.
I'm headed out, so if there's a point
you're trying to make,
make it.
I betrayed you, I killed you,
I... I even chose my sister over you
and yet, still
I haven't fully pushed you away,
so either you're a masochist
or you hate yourself,
but which one is it?
You're infuriating, unpredictable
and yes, you tried to kill me...
But I can't help who I love.
We're survivors, orphans
who made our way
in this world alone except somehow,
we found each other.
Whatever we felt for each other
was enough
to bring back our memories.
That's real, Alice.
My whole life I've been caged...
by Cartwright and then Safiyah,
even my own sister.
For the first time, I'm free...
to make my own choices.
- So choose.
- No.
Because I want it all.
I... I... I want you
and I want my sister back
and if you truly loved me,
you would want me
to have it all, too.
Have to admit kind
of surprised you called me.
- Don't know many Crows.
- Ex-Crow.
Them either. I need your help.
You okay?
- You should see the Crows's truck.
- The Crows ran you down?
One of Russell Tavaroff's boys.
He has people watching his back,
so I need you
to tell me everything about him
and his crew.
Are you sure you don't want to be
with Luke right now?
- Luke's gonna be fine.
- Fine?
He's unconscious in the ICU.
Mary's on her way
to the hospital with Desert Rose.
It will save his life.
Excuse me, I need to see Luke.
And I need you to step back.
Since when did this ICU room become
the hottest club in Gotham?
No one's allowed in.
No.
I just spoke to Luke's doctor
and I'm not no one.
I'm Mary Hamilton,
daughter of Jacob Kane, your boss,
so unless you want
to be pulling shifts
at the Gotham Mall,
I suggest you let me in.
We're here on your father's orders.
The Crows have issued a statement
on the incident
along with newly released
body camera footage.
We should warn viewers
that this footage is disturbing.
Wait. How was Luke holding a gun?
This makes me want to puke.
The Crows have just released the name
of the armed suspect... Lucas Fox
who was released from jail
hours before the confrontation.
The gun found at the scene
was also connected
to a recent gas station robbery.
27-year-old Fox is the son
of the late Wayne Foundation CEO
Lucius Fox and currently works
as head of security at Wayne Tower.
They literally photoshopped
a gun into Luke's hand
in the bodycam footage.
Not just any gun.
It was linked to an armed robbery,
which means when Luke wakes up
they're gonna charge him for robbery
and attempted assault.
If Luke wakes.
There are two agents
stationed outside his door.
Mary couldn't get them removed.
If Mary can't administer
the Desert Rose...
Luke's gonna die.
How is there a damn video
of Luke carrying a gun?
- I don't know.
- Well, think!
Because I highly doubt Tavaroff
has a degree in alpha bro
and digital art!
Tavaroff is a bully
with a bunch of lackeys,
who will do whatever he wants.
It was probably one of them.
A murder of Crows.
Okay. So tell me how to get
my hands on the original footage.
What time is it?
1.45.
All the bodycam metadata is sent
to the Crows's air-gapped server,
which always deletes
at 3.00am every night.
If we can get
the metadata off that server
we can compare it
to the footage playing on the news
and prove the original was altered.
Well, that just flowed
right off your tongue.
What are you talking about?
Tell me...
How many times
have you seen something
like this happen
and never said anything?
How many times have you participated
in something like this?
Never. I never knew it went this far
and when I did, I quit.
Yesterday!
Not long ago,
you threw down the badges
of the two agents
who ran over Wolf Spider
and you told me
you could change the culture.
- You knew it was broken.
- Ryan, I didn't shoot Luke
so please stop acting
like this is my fault.
It's not! It's mine!
- What?
- It's my fault.
Luke got shot because of me.
That's crazy.
Why would you blame yourself?
I gave him hell
for being a bystander.
I called him privileged.
Ryan, you didn't do this.
Luke... Put himself in the way...
because of me.
Sophie, he can't die.
How are you here right now?
How is... how is... he?
What is going on?
Where do you think we are right now?
- In your office.
- Are we, though, really?
This is...
My subconscious.
Exactly.
Right now,
you are lying in a hospital room.
Doctors have no idea how to fix you.
A machine is keeping you alive,
and you have a choice to make.
You can hang on,
or you can let go and join him.
Okay. If this is purgatory,
does that mean that you're dead?
You tell me, Luke.
It's your subconscious.
So... What's it gonna be, buddy?
Bruce, I don't know.
I just want to go talk to my dad.
No. Doesn't work that way.
What do you mean?
He is right there.
Why can't I just go talk to him?
Because if you go talk
to the old man, that's it.
You're dead.
Your decision's been made.
There's no going back.
Moore, I thought you quit.
Come to change your mind?
Russell Tavaroff
is not the agent you think he is.
Well, I could say the same about you.
Doesn't reflect well on me
when my best agent hands
in her badge without even
discussing it with me first.
There's nothing to discuss.
Last year,
we said we'd drain the swamp
once we discovered
Agent Robles was hired
to kill Lucius Fox.
Now, we're right back
where we started,
another Crow lying
about another Fox case.
You quit less than 24 hours ago,
and then you come in here
and you tell me
how to run my operation?
I'm asking to reexamine
the facts of the case.
Two years ago,
I tracked down a rapist.
He attacked several women,
we all knew he did it,
but the evidence was circumstantial.
It wouldn't hold up in court
so when airtight evidence
appeared at the last minute,
I didn't question where it came from
because he was guilty.
We put a rapist behind bars.
I know we did,
but we also bent the rules.
And how many lives have we saved?
All I'm saying is if evidence
could appear out of thin air once
it can appear again.
I have been loyal
to you since day one.
Five years, no questions asked,
but...
Once I saw the truth,
I couldn't unsee it
so I'm begging you, sir, please
open your eyes
before anyone else has to die.
Just landed in the Crows' nest.
Copy. Just hacked
into the Crows's camera feed.
You've got six minutes
before the data wipe activates.
- What about Luke?
- It's in motion.
So, hot tip.
Coffee at the hospital cafe
is extra tragic,
but I brought these fresh.
I actually came back
to apologize for my behavior earlier.
You know, "I'm Mary Hamilton."
Who do I think
I am... Kimmy K, right?
You're just doing your jobs and...
So heroically, too.
The entire city of Gotham
owes you both
a huge debt of gratitude.
From us all.
This is so stupid. Dad.
Dad, it's Luke.
Okay. What is happening?
Science.
The land of the living
is pulling you back.
Vitals are stabilizing,
wounds are healing.
On paper, you could get up tomorrow
and go for a jog.
You're about survive, my friend.
Now, are you staying,
or are you going?
Because if you wait much longer
that decision
is gonna be made for you.
I'm...
Bruce.
- You asked to see me, Commander.
- Yeah.
Can you, help me
with something, Tavaroff?
Luke Fox never
had so much as a speeding ticket
parking ticket, fix-it ticket.
Hell, he's never even had
a late payment on a bill.
How does a guy
like that suddenly graduate
to GTA, robbery
and possession of a firearm?
I can't say, sir.
You'll have to ask him when he wakes.
The Snakebite case two days ago
resulted in nearly a dozen deaths.
Agent Moore's final report
indicated requesting
the use of nonlethal force
to subdue the users.
Well, my crew and I
were surrounded by cannibals
high out of their mind, sir.
Well, you could have used tear gas,
stun guns.
Come on. This organization
has its own damn armory.
Well, if we had an IA investigation
every time a firearm was discharged
we'd never make it back
into the field, sir.
And if I was to look
at all your cases
how many of these instances
would I find?
How many would we find
in yours, Commander?
What about lighting up Batwoman
at Goliaths Stadium?
The Crows have never shied away
from using extreme force.
That is not why I started the Crows.
Well, that's who we are now.
Well, then maybe we need
to take a long, hard look
at ourselves and ask
if the Crows deserve to exist.
In the meantime,
I want your badge, I want your gun
and I want you out of here.
You are sidelined until I can conduct
a full investigation into you
and your little posse.
If that's what you got to do, sir.
Or maybe... We'll be just fine
if we get rid of the problem.
- I'm here.
- Okay, Batwoman.
According to the report,
Tavaroff's footage
will be in stack 815.
It should be on your right.
We really need you
to wait in the visitor's lounge.
Oh, I'm just saying
I am happy to consult my dad
about better benefits.
I mean, you bravely put yourselves
in the line of fire
and that's your pension?
Seriously, I...
Think about your life,
think about your choices
because the Crows hurt people
like my friend Luke
so just ask yourselves
who are you really protecting here?
Mary Hamilton, crazy seeing you here.
Evan Blake.
I bought you a coffee.
You failed to mention Luke
was a cutie pie.
Luke got the Desert Rose.
- Is he awake?
- Not yet.
We're at three minutes to 3.00am.
- Password worked. I'm in.
- Good.
Found the bodycam files.
- Oh, no.
- Talk to me.
There's hundreds
of files in Tavaroff's folder.
If it's by date,
it'd be the last entry.
They're not saved by date
because why would the Crows
make something easy?
Can you get Luke's
before it's destroyed?
I can't find Luke's footage.
- Oh, my god.
- What?
Tavaroff and his murder
have the commander.
He's not conscious.
You need to stop them.
I need to save Luke
before these files are erased.
You don't kidnap the commander
and plan to let him live.
They're gonna kill Jacob Kane.
Figure out where they took him.
Saw the Snakebite kits in the trash
when I was tying him up.
Commander's a fricking junkie.
So...
Let's give him...
the worst high he's ever had.
Dude, three? That'll kill him.
He was gonna turn us all in.
It's either us or him.
Do you want to go to jail?
How about you or you?
All it takes is a half-wit judge
and a soft jury and we're all done.
That's what I thought.
Now...
Shut up...
and let the Commander...
enjoy his last high.
Lights.
I wanted you to see this.
Have fun at Blackgate.
Thanks.
You know what
I gave up to save your ass?
Clearing Luke Fox's name.
Your boys are trying
to ruin his life.
- I... I didn't know it was this bad.
- Yeah? Well, you should have.
You want to do good, I get it.
I bend the rules too
but at least I have a code.
What's yours?
I gave you the match
and the gas can, Commander.
It's up to you to do the rest.
Burn it down
or you're just as bad as them.
Luke's mom just pulled into the lot.
Why isn't he waking up?
It doesn't make any sense.
His vitals have stabilized.
He should be awake by now.
After one dose...
of the Desert Rose serum
my Kryptonite poisoning
went away immediately.
Are you sure Wolf Spider
did it right?
I'm positive. I watched him do it.
- Then why isn't it working?
- I don't know.
I should have been
the one to inject it.
I should have been there.
I could have done more.
Two Crows agents shot
and framed and Luke Fox
by placing a gun
at the scene when he, in fact
did not have a weapon
in his possession.
Even more disturbing,
the doctored bodycam footage
to make it look as though the phone
in Mr. Fox's hand was that gun.
Will you be releasing
the real bodycam footage?
Unfortunately, it was destroyed
but I am personally willing
to testify to this in court.
In the meantime, the agents involved
in this deep fake are being held
for assault with the intent to kill.
I am lucky that Batwoman
was there to save my life.
What does this say
about the Crows as an organization
and you as its leader?
Well, I started the Crows
because I wanted to protect Gotham
from the kind of monsters
who would highjack a school bus
and run a family off
the road like they were nothing
but somewhere along the way,
the Crows began cutting corners
to get results.
While Agent Tavaroff
is directly responsible
for what happened to Mr. Fox
I am guilty of harboring these types
of actions for years.
I want to offer a direct apology
to the Fox family for all the hurt
that we have caused,
but these are not isolated moments
and apologies mean nothing
without actions.
I have therefore come
to the conclusion
that there is only one
way to make amends.
As the founder
and majority shareholder
I have decided to disband
the Crows effective immediately.
What will this mean
for the security of Gotham?
When did you first...
You did that.
You shut them down.
They can't hurt anyone anymore.
We did it, Luke
so I'm gonna need you
to wake up now, please
because there
is no Bat team without you.
Come on, Luke.
Wake up.
Who else is gonna roll
their eyes at me
every time I threaten
to redecorate the Batcave...
Or ignore my fashion advice,
even though clearly only own a suit?
It's me and you
in the Batcave, Luke, so...
We need you.
I need you, so...
- This is so unfair.
- None of this is fair.
It doesn't matter
that you worked for Batman
or both Batwomen
that you saved hundreds of lives
cleaned up entire neighborhoods.
You have given hope
to thousands of people.
You still got shot...
And there is a whole mess
of people out there
willing to believe
that you deserved it
just because you're black.
Then what's the point?
It's not for me to say
but you need to decide...
- Now.
- You left
and I... I've always wondered why.
Why you just walked away,
hung up the cape...
And it's because it's just all
so damn depressing.
Because no matter what good
we try to put into the world
it's still a world
where this happens.
And I don't want to live
in that world anymore.
I want to be with my dad.
And that's your choice.
Look up...
Okay. Hey, Dad. It's Luke.
I'm... I'm here.
I think he's waking up.
Luke.
You're alive.
Welcome back.
You did the right thing.
Thanks to you.
Doesn't matter how we get there, sir.
What matters is that we do.
This is why I always looked up
to you.
You were always
my best agent, Moore.
The fact that I've broken
into this parking structure
more times
than I can count says the Crows
maybe weren't all that great
at security anyway.
It's been a long day, Alice.
What do you want?
I need your help...
and I know what you're thinking...
"Me help you? I've made
it my paternal legacy
to disappoint you
at every opportunity".
Alice.
Kate's alive.
- Not this again.
- No, Daddy, she's alive.
Not maybe possibly being held
on an invisible island somewhere.
She's here in Gotham
under the influence of Black Mask
so you and I are gonna do
the one thing
that you Kate never did for me.
We are gonna stop at nothing,
and we're gonna get her back.