[K.S. RHOADS' "THUNDERWING"
PLAYING]
RYAN: DEAR KATE...
RHOADS: ♪ YOU LOOK
TO THE HEAVENS ♪
RYAN: IT DOESN'T FEEL REAL
TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
RHOADS: ♪ YOU KNOW WHO YOU ARE ♪
♪ SAY YOU'RE GONNA SAVE IT
FOR ANOTHER LIFETIME ♪
UNBEKNOWNST TO US,
JULIA PENNYWORTH SPENT MONTHS
WITH A RECOVERY TEAM
COMBING THE OCEAN FLOOR
FOR ANY SIGN OF YOU.
SHE FOUND SOMETHING CAUGHT,
A PARIETAL SKULL BONE
IN THE SHORES OUTSIDE
OF BLUDHAVEN,
HAD 3 DIFFERENT LABS MATCH IT
TO YOUR DNA.
IT WAS ENOUGH TO CONFIRM
YOU WERE GONE,
AND SINCE I CAN'T EXACTLY
BE THERE TO SAY
GOOD-BYE IN PERSON,
I'LL SAY IT HERE
IN THE PLACE WHERE I FEEL LIKE
I KNOW YOU THE BEST,
AND SINCE I CAN'T LAY FLOWERS
AT YOUR GRAVESITE EITHER,
I HAVE ANOTHER IDEA.
THIS PLANT WAS MY CONNECTION
TO MY MAMA.
THEN IT TURNED OUT TO BE
MORE THAN A PLANT.
IT'S A DESERT ROSE FROM CORYANA,
PROBABLY SNUCK OVER
TO THE STATES
BY AN ISLANDER NAMED OCEAN,
WHO EVENTUALLY GAVE IT
TO MY EX FOR SAFEKEEPING,
WHO THEN GAVE IT TO ME,
HAVING NO IDEA THAT ITS SERUM
WAS ACTUALLY A MIRACLE CURE.
LIKE YOU, THIS PLANT IS
ONE OF A KIND,
AND LIKE YOU, IT GAVE ME
A SECOND CHANCE.
BEYOND ALL EARTHLY WORDS
AND SONGS OF BLESSING,
PRAISE, AND COMFORT.
RHOADS: ♪ THUNDERWINGS
ARE BEATING ♪
RYAN: SO NOW WHEN I LOOK AT IT,
I WON'T JUST THINK OF MY MAMA.
I'LL THINK OF KATE KANE,
AND I'LL THINK OF THE WOMAN
WHO SAVED
A HELL OF A LOT OF PEOPLE,
THE WOMAN WHO CREATED
A FAMILY FOR EVERYONE,
THE WOMAN WHO WOULD KEEP US
FROM SURRENDERING
TO OUR DEMONS,
THE WOMAN WHO INSPIRED PEOPLE
TO STAY TRUE TO THEMSELVES
EVEN WHEN IT FELT IMPOSSIBLE,
TO ALWAYS BE THERE
WHENEVER SOMEONE NEEDED THEM,
WHO BROUGHT OUT OUR HUMANITY,
EVEN IN THE DARKEST OF MOMENTS,
AND THE WOMAN WHO CHANGED ME.
LIKE EVERYTHING GOOD IN MY LIFE,
I THOUGHT MY TIME
WITH THE BAT WAS TEMPORARY,
BUT IT'S FOR REAL NOW,
AND I'M NOT
IN YOUR SHADOW ANYMORE.
I'M IT.
I AM BATWOMAN.
GOOD-BYE, KATE KANE.
THANK YOU FOR CHANGING MY LIFE.
MAY YOUR MEMORY BE A BLESSING.
MAY HER MEMORY
BE A BLESSING.
RHOADS: ♪ WHEN THE WATER
GETS HIGH ♪
ALL: MAY HER MEMORY
BE A BLESSING.
RHOADS: ♪ TELL ME CAN YOU
FEEL IT? ♪
♪ THUNDERWINGS ARE BEATING
IN THE SKY ♪
[HEAVY BREATHING]
YOUR FAMILY HAS DECLARED
YOU DEAD, KATE KANE...
BUT SIT TIGHT.
WE'LL MAKE THEM BELIEVE
IN LIFE AFTER DEATH.
DANA DEWITT: ROLLING? OK.
HERE THEY COME.
NICE AND TIGHT
ON FORBES, PLEASE.
COMMISSIONER FORBES,
IT'S NOT NEWS
THAT THE GCPD HAS BEEN
WORKING TIRELESSLY
TO PUT SNAKEBITE DEALERS
BEHIND BARS,
BUT IT'S NOW RUMORED
YOU'RE GETTING YOUR HELP
FROM BATWOMAN.
-CAN YOU COMMENT?
-THERE'S NO QUESTION
WE WILL PUT A STOP
TO SNAKEBITE
AND ITS MANUFACTURERS,
THE FALSE FACE SOCIETY,
BUT THIS DRUG,
IT HAS ITS TEETH
IN PEOPLE,
IT'S ADDICTIVE,
IT'S SEXY,
AND IT'S LETHAL.
THE LAST I CHECKED,
DANA, THE GCPD
WAS NEVER ONE TO
TURN DOWN A LITTLE
EXTRA HELP
FROM A VIGILANTE.
NOW I HAVE A 10-HOUR
BUDGET MEETING
TO GET TO.
I'M ACTUALLY HERE TO TALK
ABOUT THAT BUDGET MEETING,
COMMISSIONER.
OH, GOODY.
LET ME GUESS--
YOU WANT TO DEFUND
THE POLICE.
DEFUNDING THE POLICE
MEANS REDUCING YOUR BUDGET
IN AREAS LIKE OFFICER BONUSES
AND CANNABIS REGULATION
AND REDISTRIBUTING
THE FUNDS TO THINGS
LIKE MENTAL HEALTH,
EDUCATION, EMPLOYMENT,
HOUSING.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
THE MONEY COMES FROM
EVERY TIME WE HAVE TO CLEAN
A BUILDING
YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
GRAFFITI TAGS, HUH?
GOT IT. SO SPRAY PAINT
WILL GET YOUR ATTENTION
BUT NOT YOUR OWN OFFICERS
KILLING 4 UNARMED BLACK MEN
THIS YEAR ALONE?
IT'S AN ELECTED POSITION,
SWEETIE.
YOU DON'T LIKE ME,
RUN.
-MMM!
-RIGHT?
I'VE NEVER HAD
SWEET POTATO
PANCAKES BEFORE,
BUT IF I HAD,
THESE WOULD BE
MY FAVORITE.
-IT'S ALL ABOUT THE SKILLET.
-MMM.
THANK YOU FOR THIS
AND FOR LETTING ME CRY
AT ODD HOURS OF THE DAY
AND LETTING ME FINISH
ALL THE ICE CREAM
IN THE FREEZER.
I'M GONNA NEED THAT
REPLACED ACTUALLY.
MMM. NO WAY.
THESE PAST FEW WEEKS,
YOU KNOW,
HAVE BEEN
REALLY, REALLY TOUGH,
BUT SOMEHOW, IT ALL
FEELS A LITTLE
LESS AWFUL
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND,
AND I KNOW LUKE
FEELS IT, TOO,
SO THANK YOU.
YOU AND LUKE,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
WE HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF EACH OTHER.
YEAH.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
GOT IT.
OH!
-IT SMELLS SO GOOD IN HERE.
-YEAH.
RYAN: ANG?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UH, DIDN'T MEAN
TO INTERRUPT,
BUT I DID, SO I WAS
HOPING WE COULD TALK.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
TO TALK ABOUT.
WELL, THEN MAYBE
JUST LISTEN
BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO
SAY I'M SORRY.
MARY: UH, OK.
I AM GONNA TAKE THIS
AND THESE DOWNSTAIRS
OUT OF EARSHOT...MAYBE.
I, UH--I SAID SOME
PRETTY AWFUL THINGS
TO YOU A WHILE BACK.
WELL, I MEAN,
IN YOUR DEFENSE,
YOU WERE IN THE PROCESS
OF DUMPING ME.
RY, YOU WORKED
WITH THE CROWS TO
LOJACK MY PHONE.
OK. I KNOW YOU DIDN'T
JUST COME ALL THIS WAY
TO RELIVE THIS--
I MISS YOU.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN
MY CONSTANT,
AND YOU MADE EVERY
CRAPPY GROUP HOME
FEEL LIKE
A REAL HOME,
AND THEN CORA
ADOPTED YOU,
AND I WAS, LIKE,
ON MY OWN, CRUSHED
BUT HAPPY FOR YOU.
I--I JUST COULDN'T
FIGHT TO KEEP YOU THEN,
BUT...NOW I CAN.
ANG...
I AM MOVING FORWARD
IN MY LIFE,
AND AS LONG AS YOU KEEP
DOING YOUR THING,
SLINGING SNAKEBITE,
WE DON'T WORK.
I'M GETTING OUT.
YOU SAID YOU COULDN'T
GET OUT.
NO. I SAID
I DIDN'T WANT TO,
BUT FALSE FACE
FOUND OUT THAT OCEAN
TAUGHT ME HOW TO
MAKE SNAKEBITE,
AND WITH OCEAN M.I.A.,
THEY WANTED ME TO
OPEN MY OWN LAB,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO
BE THE WALTER WHITE
OF GOTHAM CITY.
UH...
I FOUND SOMEONE
WORTH TURNING
MY LIFE AROUND FOR.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT
BECAUSE I KNOW
MY MIND IS
ALREADY MADE UP.
ALICE: KATE KANE SAT ON A WALL.
KATE KANE HAD A GREAT FALL.
ALL THE BAT'S GADGETS
AND ALL THE BAT'S MEN
COULDN'T PUT KATE
TOGETHER AGAIN.
[SIGHS]
[CREAK]
[SQUEAKING]
IT'S A PITY YOU'RE COMING
ALL THE WAY FROM CORYANA
JUST TO DIE.
SHOULD HAVE FIGURED
YOU WERE IN HERE.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
DON'T BE SILLY.
YOU INVITED ME FOR TEA.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[CLATTER]
WE'VE GOT EXTRA EYES!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[SIRENS]
COME ON!
WE GOT TO GO!
WE'RE COMING FOR YOU!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
DEWITT: COMMISSIONER FORBES'
CHALK OUTLINE
REPRESENTS ONE OF THE MOST
BRAZEN CRIMINAL EVENTS
IN RECENT GOTHAM HISTORY.
I'M JOINED BY JANUS COSMETICS
CEO ROMAN SIONIS.
MR. SIONIS, I UNDERSTAND
YOU HAVE SOMETHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY
TO THE GOTHAM PUBLIC.
YES. THANK YOU, DANA.
YOU KNOW, IT SHOULDN'T TAKE
A BUSINESSPERSON
TO STEP IN HERE,
BUT I HAVE MADE A CAREER
OUT OF CONCEALING BLEMISHES,
AND QUITE FRANKLY,
THE MAKEOVER THIS CITY NEEDS
COMES FROM AN UGLY
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE,
SO, YES, I AM HERE
TO SPEAK ON BEHALF
OF THE PEOPLE
WITHOUT A PLATFORM
LIKE THE HUNDREDS
WHO WORK FOR ME
WHO SAY THEY'RE SCARED
TO DEATH, DANA.
THEY ARE SCARED TO DEATH
OF THE CRIMINAL ELEMENT
LURKING BEHIND MASKS,
BUT I'M NOT HERE
TO BEG FOR HELP TODAY.
I'M HERE TO OFFER IT.
TO THE LAW ENFORCEMENT
IN CHARGE OF PROTECTING US,
WHAT CAN WE DO, HMM?
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
BECAUSE ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
THE GANGS IN THE CITY
ARE STUPID
BUT NOT KILL
THE COMMISSIONER STUPID.
IT'S COMMON KNOWLEDGE THAT
FORBES WAS HAVING AN AFFAIR.
I WOULDN'T ELIMINATE
LADY SPITE KILLING.
OR ANY RECENTLY
RELEASED INMATE
WHO MAY FEEL LIKE
FORBES SCREWED
THEM OVER.
LICENSE PLATES,
FACIAL REC.
ANY VEHICLE THAT DIDN'T
STOP LONG ENOUGH
AT A STOPLIGHT LAST NIGHT
GETS PUT THROUGH THE SYSTEM.
-I DON'T GET IT.
-I THOUGHT HE WAS GUNNED DOWN
-ON THOSE STEPS.
-HE WAS.
WHERE THE HELL'S
THE COMMISSIONER?
THERE'S NOTHING THERE.
HANG ON. GO BACK.
CHECK OUT
THE TIMESTAMP.
SOMEONE SCRUBBED 5 MINUTES
ON BOTH SIDES OF THE MURDER.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
I WANT THE NAME
OF EVERYONE IN THIS CITY
WITH ACCESS TO THIS FEED.
MARY: SO WHOEVER
SHOT THE COMMISSIONER
HAS ACCESS
TO THE CITY'S CCTV.
THIS WAS A WELL-PLANNED
EXECUTION.
WHOA, WHOA. WAIT.
REWIND AGAIN.
LOOK AT THE FAR RIGHT
AFTER THE JUMP.
SOMEONE TAGGED IT.
CAN YOU GET A CLOSER
ANGLE AT THAT?
-YEAH.
-SOMEONE COULD HAVE BEEN
TAGGING THE BUILDING
WHILE THE SHOOTING
WAS HAPPENING.
THEN GOT THE HELL
OUT OF DODGE,
LEFT BEHIND WORK
IN PROGRESS.
WHICH MEANS THE TAGGER
COULD HAVE SEEN THE SHOOTER.
AND THE SHOOTER COULD
HAVE SEEN THEM,
SO HOW DO WE TRACK DOWN
A POTENTIAL WITNESS
AND PROTECT THEM SOLELY OFF
THE WORDS "DEFUND THE POLICE?"
-I THINK I FOUND IT.
-LITERALLY HOW?
SOCIAL MEDIA.
FIGURED THE "X"
INSIDE THE "O"
AND MONOCHROME
ON TOP OF THE NEON
WAS SOME SORT
OF SIGNATURE.
DEFINITELY COULD BE
THE SAME ARTIST.
I'LL GET
THE USER'S INFO.
HEY!
SO...WE JUST GONNA
ACT LIKE ANGELIQUE
DIDN'T COME BY
YESTERDAY, OR--
-YEP.
-WHOA. I THOUGHT THAT WAS OVER.
IT WAS. MAJOR
DUMPER'S REMORSE.
YOU WERE LISTENING?
WELL, YOU KNOW, JUST
IN CASE I HAD TO
STEP IN AND DEFEND.
SO SPILL.
WE TAKING HER BACK?
I DON'T KNOW.
I LOVE HER.
SHE'S A HUGE PART
OF MY LIFE.
BUT?
LUKE: HEY. I'M IN.
SO NO REAL NAME.
IT'S SOMEONE'S FINSTA,
BUT I MATCHED THE LOGIN
INFORMATION
TO ANOTHER PROFILE.
JORDAN MOORE.
YOU DON'T THINK SHE'S
ANY RELATION TO...
SIR, WHERE ARE YOU?
THE COMMISSIONER
WAS ASSASSINATED,
AND THAT POMPOUS ASS
ROMAN SIONIS
IS GETTING MORE AIRTIME
THEN THE CROWS COMMANDER.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD RELEASE
A STATEMENT OR SOMETHING.
CALL ME!
[GASP]
WHAT THE ACTUAL HELL?
JORDAN! UHH.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
I SAW COMMISSIONER FORBES
GET GUNNED DOWN.
WHAT?!
LOOK. I--I DIDN'T KNOW
WHERE ELSE TO GO.
I'M--I'M SCARED
TO GO HOME.
I FEEL LIKE I'M
BEING FOLLOWED.
HEY, HEY. I GOT YOU.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA
BE ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO UPSTAIRS.
I'LL TAKE YOUR
WITNESS STATEMENT.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I'M NOT GIVING MY NAME
TO THE CROWS.
I MAY AS WELL JUST DO
A SIT-DOWN WITH
VESPER FAIRCHILD.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT A HUGE DEAL THIS IS?
THERE'S NO OTHER
WITNESSES.
I DON'T CARE.
THE CROWS DON'T KEEP
PEOPLE LIKE ME SAFE,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
I CAME TO SOPHIE,
MY SISTER, FOR HELP,
NOT SOPHIE THE CROW.
[TAP ON WINDOW]
GET DOWN!
TOLD YOU THEY WERE
FOLLOWING ME!
WHO'S THEY?
NOW IS WHEN YOU
PULL YOUR GUN!
[BONE CRACKS]
HUH!
AGH!
DAMN.
YOU'RE BATWOMAN.
IT'S FALSE FACE.
SO THE COMMISSIONER'S
HOT TAKE ON SNAKEBITE
GOT HIS ASS KILLED.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WE WERE HERE?
RYAN: JORDAN WASN'T
AT HER PLACE,
SO I HOPED SHE WENT
TO HER SISTER FOR HELP.
APPARENTLY FALSE FACE
HAD THE SAME IDEA.
SORRY. H-HOW DO YOU
KNOW MY LIFE?
I'VE SEEN YOUR SKILLS
AROUND GOTHAM,
AND I KNOW YOU WERE TAGGING
CITY HALL LAST NIGHT.
SERIOUSLY?
GIRL, SO NOT
THE POINT RIGHT NOW.
RYAN: I NEED YOU
TO TELL ME
EVERYTHING YOU SAW.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
I SNITCH,
IT COMES BACK
TO ME.
THEY SAW ME THERE.
THEY'LL KNOW IT
WAS ME.
THE COSTUME PARTY
ON THE GROUND TELLS ME.
THEY ALREADY KNOW
IT WAS YOU.
YOU CAN TRUST HER.
THERE WERE 3 DUDES.
TWO GOT OUT
OF THE CAR
AND GUNNED DOWN
FORBES,
ONE IN A GAS MASK
AND ONE
IN A HOCKEY MASK
AND THEN A DRIVER.
WAS HE WEARING
A MASK?
SHE. YES.
A--A BABY DOLL THING.
RYAN: SO IT COULD BE
LITERALLY ANYONE.
IT ISN'T ENOUGH.
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK.
CONSIDER YOURSELF LUCKY.
DON'T KNOW IF IT HELPS,
BUT I SAW
THE DRIVER'S BRACELET.
IT WAS A BIG GOLD KEY.
IT LOOKED RITZ.
EVERYTHING OK?
GET HER SOMEWHERE SAFE.
I'LL FIGURE THIS OUT.
YOU AND YOUR FRIEND
GO TELL YOUR BOSS
WE'RE GOOD HERE.
THE GIRL WILL KEEP
HER MOUTH SHUT,
AND YOU WILL LEAVE
HER ALONE.
ALICE: YOU'RE NOT REAL,
THIS TEA'S NOT REAL,
AND THIS CUP
IS...NOT REAL.
CORRECT, BUT YOU DON'T
WANT REALITY.
THAT'S THE POINT.
NO. I JUST SPENT
THE LAST TWO WEEKS
IN THE BOWELS
OF A SHIP,
TRYING TO ESCAPE
A GODFORSAKEN ISLAND.
TRUST ME. IF I WERE
TO CONJURE UP
SOME FANTASY,
THIS WOULD NOT BE IT.
YOU MEAN THE SAME ISLAND
YOU RISKED EVERYTHING
TO GET TO IN ORDER TO
SEE ME AGAIN?
WELL, HERE WE ARE.
OF COURSE. I ASK
THE UNIVERSE
FOR MY SISTER,
AND THIS IS
WHAT I GET.
I'M NOT SURE WHY
THAT'S SURPRISING.
YOU NEVER GET
WHAT YOU WANT.
CHEERS TO THAT.
NOTHING ABOUT YOUR PLAN
UNFOLDED THE WAY YOU WANTED.
AFTER WE LEFT YOU IN THIS CELL
FOR 11 YEARS,
YOU SET OUT TO MAKE SURE
YOUR FAMILY NEVER LEFT
YOU AGAIN,
BUT DAD HELPED LOCK YOU
AT ARKHAM,
AND I'M DEAD.
AM I SO MENTALLY
DISTURBED
THAT MY IMAGINATION
CREATED YOU
TO RUB IT IN?
YOU CREATED ME BECAUSE
YOU WERE ALWAYS THE ONE
WHO GOT US INTO TROUBLE,
BUT I WAS ALWAYS THE ONE
CLEVER ENOUGH
TO GET US OUT OF IT.
-WHAT TROUBLE?
-YOUR PAIN.
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
I HAD A WAY
TO MAKE IT DISAPPEAR?
ANG, OPEN UP.
IT'S ME.
HEY.
YOU SAID YOU WERE
GETTING OUT, ANG!
OK. YOUR ENERGY IS
SUPERINTENSE RIGHT NOW.
WHO KILLED
THE COMMISSIONER?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
DRIVING THE GETAWAY CAR?
WHO ELSE KNOWS?
THAT IS NOT
THE APPROPRIATE
RESPONSE
TO WHAT I JUST SAID.
YOU WANT ME TO
END UP DEAD?
-WHO ELSE KNOWS?
-I DO!
THAT SHOULD BE
ENOUGH!
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
I WAS DOING THERE.
I SAID I WANTED OUT,
AND THEY WERE WILLING
TO LET ME GO
IF I JUST DID
THIS ONE LAST THING.
THEY GAVE ME A MASK,
KEYS, AND AN ADDRESS.
AM I SUPPOSED TO
BELIEVE YOU RIGHT NOW?
WHEN HAVE I EVER LIED
TO YOU?
IF MY NAME IS OUT,
FALSE FACE WILL KILL ME
TO PROTECT THEMSELVES.
THEN OUT THEM.
TURN IN THE ACTUAL
KILLERS.
TELL THE COURT WHAT
YOU JUST TOLD ME.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW.
FALSE FACE IS RUN
BY A PSYCHOPATH
NAMED BLACK MASK,
WHO WILL LEAVE ME
FOR DEAD IN A SEWER
BEFORE I EVER GET
ON A WITNESS STAND.
I CAN PROTECT YOU.
YOU? HOW?
THIS IS GOING TO
SOUND...INSANE...
BUT...
I KNOW BATWOMAN.
OK.
HOW DO YOU THINK I KNOW
YOU GOT WRAPPED UP
IN THIS CRAP?
[SIGHS]
YOU AND YOUR
COMIC BOOK HEROES.
YEAH. WELL, THANKS
TO ME AND MY
COMIC BOOK HEROES,
YOUR ASS HAS AN OUT
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO TAKE IT,
BUT YOU NEED TO TAKE IT.
CAN I THINK
ABOUT IT?
LUKE: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU'RE LETTING HER
THINK ABOUT IT?
SHE JUST GUNNED DOWN
THE COMMISSIONER.
SHE DROVE
THE GETAWAY CAR.
OH, RIGHT. SHE DIDN'T
PULL THE TRIGGER.
SHE JUST STEPPED
ON THE GAS.
YES. PLEASE GIVE HER
ALL THE TIME SHE NEEDS.
RYAN'S RIGHT.
IF JORDAN TESTIFIES
AGAINST FALSE FACE,
THEY'LL KILL HER,
BUT IF ANGELIQUE DOES,
JORDAN DOESN'T HAVE TO.
EXACTLY. ANG
JUST NEEDS TIME.
SHE'LL MAKE
THE RIGHT DECISION.
SHE COULD HAVE GONE
TO THE COPS
WHEN YOU WERE BUSTED
FOR HER DRUGS ON YOU.
-SHE DIDN'T.
-SHE'S CHANGED.
YOU LITERALLY JUST
SAID THE WORDS,
"SHE DROVE
THE GETAWAY CAR."
OK. YOU HAVE
MY BACK, RIGHT?
I'VE BEEN DOWN THIS ROAD
BEFORE WITH ANOTHER
BATWOMAN--KATE--
AND SHE FOUND EVERY
EXCUSE IN THE BOOK
TO JUSTIFY
HER TWIN SISTER'S ACTIONS,
AND YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN
THE ONE TO REMIND ME
THAT MY MOM DIED
BECAUSE OF IT.
ANGELIQUE IS NOT ALICE.
NO ONE IS EVER ALICE
UNTIL THEY ARE
BECAUSE SOMEONE
LET THEM BE.
MAYBE YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WAIT FOR ANGELIQUE
TO TURN HERSELF IN.
YOU CAN DO THAT FOR HER.
Y'ALL ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE MY TEAM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WE ARE YOUR TEAM,
WHICH MAKES YOU
OUR LEADER.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE
TO MAKE THE RIGHT CALL.
I'LL GIVE ANGELIQUE
AN HOUR TO TALK,
BUT AFTER THAT,
I'LL CALL THE COPS MYSELF.
NO. I PERSONALLY
NEVER THOUGHT SAFIYAH
WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR
KATE'S PLANE BLOWING UP.
NOT HER M.O.
THE NTSB CONCLUDED
THAT BASED ON THE WEATHER
AND THE ATMOSPHERE IT WAS
LIKELY A LIGHTNING STRIKE
THAT KNOCKED OUT
THE CONTROLS.
A RECALLED CIRCUIT BREAKER
COULD HAVE SPARKED
AN ELECTRICAL FIRE
IN THE COCKPIT.
I TAKE IT I'M READING
THEIR REPORT
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
BELIEVE THAT.
OVER THE LAST FEW MONTHS,
I'VE DISCOVERED
THAT ONE OF MY DAUGHTERS
WAS BATWOMAN
WHILE THE OTHER RAN
AN ILLEGAL UNDERGROUND
MEDICAL CLINIC,
SO I'M NOT TAKING ANYTHING
AT FACE VALUE ANYMORE.
SIR...I--I CAN'T
EVEN IMAGINE
WHAT YOU MUST BE
FEELING AS A FATHER
RIGHT NOW,
BUT KATE WOULD WANT
YOU TO FIND PEACE.
THEN ELIMINATE EACH
AND EVERY ONE OF HER ENEMIES
WHO COULD HAVE DONE THIS
OR FIND ME THE ONE WHO DID
SO I CAN KILL HIM
MYSELF.
AND...IF I FIND
NOTHING THAT
CONTRADICTS
THIS REPORT,
THEN WILL YOU PLEASE
ACCEPT IT
AS WHAT I BELIEVE
IT IS,
A HORRIBLE
AND TRAGIC ACCIDENT?
CONVINCE ME I'M WRONG,
AND I'LL LET THIS GO.
WOMAN: ♪ I AM
THE ABSOLUTE GODDESS ♪
♪ DON'T GOT THE TIME
TO BE MODEST ♪
THIS IS YOUR IDEA
OF A SAFE SPACE?
I NEED A DRINK,
AND YOU ONLY HAVE
EXPENSIVE WINE
I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO LOOK AT.
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN BE
IN ANY DANGER RIGHT NOW
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN
OUT TAGGING AGAIN.
IT'S HOW I EXPRESS
MYSELF.
THEN GRAB A NOTEPAD.
DEFACING PROPERTY
IS ILLEGAL.
OH, MY GOD.
WHY DID BATWOMAN
HAVE TO SAVE ME?
I--I WAS HAVING
MORE FUN
HAVING A CROWBAR
SWUNG TO MY FACE.
SOUNDS LIKE Y'ALL COULD STAND
TO BE LESS SOBER RIGHT NOW.
TWO CLUB SODAS.
UH, VODKA
WITH A VODKA BACK.
RYAN, THIS IS
MY LITTLER SISTER JORDAN.
HMM. SO YOU WERE SAVED
BY BATWOMAN.
THAT'S DOPE.
YEAH. I MEAN,
IT WAS...FINE.
FINE? IT'S BATWOMAN.
YEAH, BUT SHE'S SO...
CRINGE.
AT LEAST SHE DITCHED
THE PARTY WIG.
HARSH WORDS FOR SOMEONE
WHO JUST SAVED YOUR LIFE.
-SHE'S ONE OF THEM.
-ONE OF WHO?
COPS, CROWS, THE LAW.
JUST ANOTHER SUIT
WHO SHOOTS FIRST
AND ASKS LATER.
RYAN: OK. THEN...
HOW WILL YOU STOP
GOTHAM'S CRIME PROBLEM?
BEFORE IT STARTS.
CURRENTLY, I'M WORKING
WITH GRASSROOTS
ORGANIZATIONS
TO GET FUNDING
FOR A COMMUNITY CENTER
OFF SKID ROW,
I'M ON A COUNCIL
TO MOVE MONEY
TO NEIGHBORHOOD-LED
SAFETY INITIATIVES,
AND I PHONE BANK
FOR NO NEW JAILS
IN GOTHAM CITY.
THIS ONE'S
ON THE HOUSE.
SHE'S...PASSIONATE.
I CAN SEE THAT.
LET'S GO.
OK.
SO...THE VIBES
ARE THERE,
AND SIS JUST CAME
OUT OF THE CLOSET.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THIS IS ME BEING
YOUR WINGWOMAN--
IN CASE YOU
MISSED IT.
MOM TOLD YOU?
JUST BECAUSE SHE
NEEDS TO TAKE
TIME WITH IT
DOESN'T MEAN I DO.
THANK YOU.
SO...BARTENDER CHICK--
FIRE!
NOPE. NOT HAPPENING.
NOT EVEN
AN ENEMIES-TO-LOVERS MAYBE.
YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO SWIPE RIGHT
ON SOMEONE EVENTUALLY.
I GOT TO MAKE A CALL.
STAY PUT.
HEY. I NEED YOU TO ASK
A FAVOR OF YOUR ASSOCIATE.
LUKE: SHE DOESN'T REALLY
DO FAVORS PER SE.
SOPHIE: I THINK BATWOMAN
HAS INTEL ON A MEMBER
OF FALSE FACE.
PERP I'M LOOKING INTO
WAS WEARING SOME KIND
OF KEY BRACELET.
SEEMED TO RING A BELL
WITH HER.
WHY NOT USE THE CROWS?
IT'LL TAKE
FORENSICS MONTHS.
LUKE, FALSE FACE JUST
EXECUTED THE COMMISSIONER
IN COLD BLOOD BECAUSE HE
SPOKE OUT AGAINST SNAKEBITE.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST TELL HER?
BECAUSE RYAN TOLD US
SHE'S GOT THIS.
I KNOW, BUT WOULDN'T
IT JUST BE EASIER
IF SOPHIE HANDLED IT?
ANGELIQUE IS RYAN'S
LESBIAN ACHILLES HEEL.
SHE'S NOT GONNA
TURN HER OVER
TO THE AUTHORITIES,
AND THIS WAY,
WE DON'T HAVE TO EITHER.
WE TOLD RYAN WE'D
HOLD HER ACCOUNTABLE,
AND THAT DOESN'T MEAN
GOING BEHIND HER BACK
THE FIRST CHANCE WE GET.
DEFINITELY DIDN'T HAVE
LUKE PUTS HIS FAITH
IN A SNAKEBITE DEALER
ON MY BINGO CARD.
I'M PUTTING MY FAITH
IN RYAN.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
WE'RE THE BAT TEAM,
AND THE ONLY WAY IT WORKS
IS WE HAVE EACH OTHER'S BACK,
EVEN IF WE DON'T
ALWAYS AGREE.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU'RE CALLING.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I GOT INTO THIS
THINKING I'D FOUND
SOME VERSION
OF A FAMILY.
I NEVER SIGNED UP
TO WATCH SOMEONE
GET GUNNED DOWN.
THEN YOU'RE READY
TO MAKE IT RIGHT.
WHO KILLED
THE COMMISSIONER?
YOU REALLY FRIENDS
WITH BATWOMAN?
I'M HERE.
WE NEED TO FIND A SAFE HOUSE
FOR ANGELIQUE
UNTIL THE REAL KILLERS
ARE BEHIND BARS.
I KNOW AN UNDERGROUND CLINIC
THAT'S NOT BEING USED
AT THE MOMENT.
PERFECT. ANYTHING ELSE
ANYONE WANTS TO ADD?
STARTS WITH AN "S,"
ENDS WITH ME SAYING,
"I TOLD YOU SO"?
EVEN IF WE DON'T AGREE
WITH THE METHOD,
WE HAVE TO TRUST YOU
TO MAKE THE HARD DECISIONS.
WE'RE A TEAM.
ANGELIQUE? ANGELIQUE?
THEY GOT TO HER.
AAH!
OH, OH, OH!
BLACK MASK:
ANGELIQUE MARTIN,
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE
INTERESTED IN LEAVING
THE FALSE FACE SOCIETY.
A WORD TO THE WISE.
THAT'S WHAT LEAVING
LOOKS LIKE.
LUKE: ANGELIQUE'S PHONE
SENT A SIGNAL
FROM THE WEST YARD
30 MINUTES AGO, THEN DIED.
RYAN: SO SHE'S SOMEWHERE
INSIDE A JANKY, OLD SAWMILL?
GOTHAM BAD GUYS WOULDN'T
HAVE IT ANY OTHER WAY.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
[LENSES CLICK]
FOUND HER.
BATWOMAN, I THINK
THEY FOUND YOU.
[ALL GRUNTING]
LUKE: YO. YOU OK?
ASK THEM THAT.
BATWOMAN, COME IN.
ARE YOU THERE?
MAN: DON'T, NO.
PLEASE, PLEASE. HELP ME.
OH, MY GOD.
LUKE.
THEY MUST HAVE
TAKEN MY COMMS.
BLACK MASK: FIND THE WITNESS,
BRING HER TO ME.
VERY SIMPLE TASK...
AND YOU FAILED.
CONSIDER THIS
YOUR TERMINATION NOTICE.
NO, NO, PLEASE. COME ON.
NO, PLEASE, PLEASE.
STOP IT, STOP IT.
PLEASE!
OH, GOD!
PLEASE, PLEASE!
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY,
I'M SORRY!
OH, GOD!
[SCREAMING]
BLACK MASK: AHH. NEXT!
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S AN H.R. MATTER.
WHAT ARE YOU--OSHA?
I'M HERE
FOR YOUR PRISONER.
LET HER GO.
SHE'S NOT LIKE YOU.
OH, PLEASE.
ENLIGHTEN ME.
WHO AM I?
YOU'RE A SADISTIC
DRUG LORD.
OK. I CAN SEE
WHY YOU MIGHT
THINK THAT,
BUT IT'S GOTHAM
THAT'S SADISTIC,
NOT ME,
AND THEY SAY
THE BEST WAY TO
CHANGE THE SYSTEM
IS FROM WITHIN.
YOU'RE NOT CHANGING CRAP.
AND YOU ARE?
I'M DOING MY BEST
EVERY DAMN DAY!
YOUR BEST ISN'T
GOOD ENOUGH,
AND I KNOW THAT BETTER
THAN ANYONE.
MY DAUGHTER WAS IMPRISONED
BY THE CROWS
AND KILLED BY BATWOMAN.
I NEVER KILLED
ANYONE.
BUT YOU'VE TAKEN
ON THE SYMBOL
OF THE WOMAN WHO DID,
SO TELL ME
IS THAT CHANGE,
OR IS THAT JUST PANDERING
TO A SICK CITY
THAT WORSHIPS
EXTREMIST CROWS AND BATS?
MAYBE YOU WOULDN'T BOTHER
ME SO MUCH IF I SAID
I WAS A SQUIRREL.
YOU'VE REALLY
CONVINCED YOURSELF
THIS CREEPY MASK IS
A SYMBOL FOR, WHAT,
A CONCERNED CITIZEN?
NO. IT'S A SYMBOL
OF LIBERATION
FROM PEOPLE LIKE YOU,
PEOPLE WHO THINK THEY'LL
NEVER BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE
AS LONG AS THEY PRETEND
THAT WHAT THEY DO IS JUSTICE.
LOOK. WE ALL HAVE
PAIN IN OUR PAST.
YOU CAN'T USE IT
TO DO THIS.
I PROMISE YOU
IF YOU LET US GO
I WILL FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR DAUGHTER.
THERE WILL BE
ACCOUNTABILITY.
OH! THERE WILL INDEED.
BUT NOT BECAUSE
OF ANYTHING YOU DID.
[BLADE WHIRRING]
[RYAN GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
THANK YOU!
GOT AN SOS FROM LUKE.
HE SAID YOUR COMMS
WENT OFF.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
I GOT YOU.
DAMN. RYAN WAS
ACTUALLY SERIOUS.
ANGELIQUE'S GONNA TAKE DOWN
FALSE FACE,
AND WE'RE GONNA
PROTECT HER.
WHAT IS THIS?
THAT WOULD BE
MY CONFESSION.
COME ON. WE BOTH KNOW
YOU DIDN'T PULL
THE TRIGGER ON FORBES.
A WITNESS SAW YOU DRIVE
THE GETAWAY CAR.
WHY CONFESS TO A CRIME
YOU DIDN'T COMMIT?
I KNEW THE CROWS
WERE DUMB.
I DIDN'T KNOW THEY
WERE DEAF, TOO.
IF YOU GIVE ME THE NAMES
OF THE SHOOTERS RIGHT NOW,
I CAN HELP ARRANGE
A PLEA DEAL.
YOU COULD GO FREE.
I KILLED FORBES,
I PULLED THE TRIGGER,
AND I ACTED ALONE.
NOW READ ME
MY DAMN RIGHTS
AND TAKE ME TO JAIL.
WHY THROW AWAY
YOUR LIFE FOR A GANG
THAT DOESN'T GIVE
A CRAP ABOUT YOU?
WANT TO TELL ME
WHAT I'M MISSING?
JAX ANDERSON:
♪ ALL OF MY FRIENDS ARE DYING ♪
♪ AND I THINK I KNOW
THE REASON ♪
YOUR SISTER'S
AT THE BAR.
SHE CAN THROW THEM BACK.
NOT WHO I'M
LOOKING FOR.
YOUR GIRL ANGELIQUE,
SHE WANTED ME
TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING.
ANDERSON:
♪ PLEASE JUST TALK TO ME ♪
♪ OH, I KNOW THESE... ♪
WHY DO YOU HAVE THIS?
WHERE'S ANGELIQUE?
SHE'S ON HER WAY
TO JAIL.
-I'M SORRY.
-WHAT DID YOU DO?
SHE CONFESSED.
SHE'S TAKING THE FALL.
IT WAS YOUR JOB
TO STOP HER.
TRUST ME I TRIED.
SHE KNEW SHE WOULD
HAVE BEEN PROTECTED.
WHY WOULD SHE DESTROY
THE REST OF HER LIFE
TO COVER FOR A BUNCH
OF FALSE FACE THUGS?
BECAUSE APPARENTLY
BLACK MASK THREATENED
TO KILL A CERTAIN
BARTENDER
THAT ANGELIQUE
HAD BEEN TEXTING WITH
TO GET BACK TOGETHER.
ANGELIQUE WAS WILLING
TO RISK HER OWN LIFE,
BUT THERE WAS
ONE THING SHE WASN'T
WILLING TO RISK--
YOU.
I'M SORRY.
ANDERSON: ♪ POWER TO SAVE ♪
♪ YOU HAVE THE POWER TO WOUND ♪
♪ THE WAY THAT YOU USE... ♪
YOU KNOW SHE DIDN'T
DO IT.
YOU CAN'T LET HER
GET AWAY WITH IT.
THAT'S HOW
THE LAW WORKS.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
ALL THESE SYSTEMS
ARE BROKEN.
ANDERSON: ♪ I KNOW THESE ARE
GONNA BE HARD TIMES ♪
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I KNOW THAT
CAN'T BE THE WAY IT IS.
ANDERSON: ♪ BLUE SKIES ♪
HEY. WHEN DID YOU
BECOME SO WISE?
WHEN YOU STOPPED SEEING ME
AS YOUR LITTLE SISTER.
OOH. WELL, I HATE
TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
MY LITTLE SIS.
ANDERSON: ♪ DON'T YOU LOSE
YOUR LIGHT ♪
HI. I'M AGENT JULIA PENNYWORTH.
I'M INVESTIGATING THE CRASH
OF FLIGHT GC9K23.
MAN: AH, YEAH.
AGENT PENNYWORTH.
WE SPOKE ABOUT THIS
LAST MONTH.
UM, I'M SORRY?
YOU CALLED LAST MONTH
INQUIRING
ABOUT THE THIRD LOADER.
I EXPLAINED IT WAS
A REPORTING ERROR.
WE ONLY EMPLOY TWO LOADERS
AT NATIONAL CITY'S
PRIVATE AIRPORT.
UM--HEH. I THINK
YOU'VE MISTAKEN ME
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
I JUST STARTED
MY INVESTIGATION TODAY.
JULIA, RIGHT?
IT'S KURT.
WE TALKED
ABOUT YOUR ACCENT.
WE BOTH USED TO SUMMER CAMP
IN OXFORDSHIRE.
WHY DON'T I REMEMBER
SPEAKING WITH YOU?
WHEN WE LEARNED
KATE WAS GONE,
I ASKED MYSELF WHAT
MY LEGACY WOULD BE
AS BATWOMAN,
BUT THAT WASN'T
THE RIGHT QUESTION.
THE QUESTION ISN'T
WHO AM I IN THE SUIT.
IT'S WHO AM I
OUT OF IT.
TWO DAYS AGO,
I DIDN'T KNOW.
BRUCE WAYNE HAD
THE BAT CODE FOR HIMSELF.
I'M DECLARING THE 3 RULES
OF THE BAT TEAM.
RULE NUMBER 3--
WE'VE GOT
EACH OTHER'S BACKS...
ALWAYS.
-WORKS FOR ME.
-ME, TOO.
SO IF WE'VE GOT
EACH OTHER'S BACK,
THAT MEANS RULE NUMBER TWO.
WE HOLD
EACH OTHER ACCOUNTABLE.
LIKE YOU DID
FOR ME TODAY.
MOST IMPORTANTLY,
WE STAND FOR SOMETHING
BIGGER THAN OURSELVES.
IT'S A LITTLE EASIER
SAID THAN DONE.
WHAT ARE YOU
THINKING?
BATWOMAN TAKES SOME
OF THE AWFUL OFF THE STREETS,
BUT THE BAT TEAM NEEDS TO
REPLACE IT
WITH SOMETHING POSITIVE.
THAT'S HOW CHANGE HAPPENS.
GETTING ADOPTED BY MAMA CORA,
THAT WAS MY GAME CHANGER,
BUT ANGELIQUE
DIDN'T HAVE THAT.
WE ARE GOING TO TAKE DOWN
BLACK MASK
AND HIS FALSE FACE GANG,
BUT WHAT ARE WE GONNA
BRING TO GOTHAM
SO THAT NO OTHER GUY
COMES ALONG
AND GETS HIS HOOKS
IN OTHER KIDS?
JORDAN MOORE IS WORKING
ON BUILDING A COMMUNITY CENTER.
I WANT US TO BRING IT
TO LIFE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU GUYS WANT TO HELP ME?
SO THE KEY TO MAKING
MY PAIN DISAPPEAR
IS TO DIG UP
MY DEAD CAT?
HMM.
[THUD]
I AM NOT OPENING
A DEAD KITTY'S COFFIN.
THEN WHY'D YOU DIG
THE HOLE?
OK. MY INTEREST
IS PIQUED.
[MEOW]
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
THIS IS WHAT YOU
DO, ALICE.
WHAT YOU DID THAT DAY
IN YOUR CELL
WHEN YOU LEARNED
TO SEW FACES USING
HUMAN FLESH.
THEN YOU DID IT AGAIN
WHEN YOU FOUND
YOUR MOTHER'S HEAD
IN A FREEZER.
[MEOW]
I'M HAVING
A PSYCHOTIC BREAK.
WHEN YOUR REALITY
IS TOO MUCH FOR YOU
TO PROCESS,
YOU IMAGINE THINGS
ASKEW
SO THEY'RE EASIER
TO DIGEST.
YOU PRETEND YOU'RE
IN WONDERLAND
DRINKING TEA,
OR YOU BLACK OUT
YOUR OWN MORAL CODE
TO SCORCH A WOMAN
TO DEATH,
OR YOU SEE
YOUR DEAD SISTER.
I'M NOT HANDLING KATE'S
DEATH VERY WELL, AM I?
YOU'RE IN SHOCK,
AND YOU KNOW
THAT ONCE IT
WEARS OFF
YOU'LL BE STRUCK
BY A TSUNAMI OF GRIEF.
HOW DOES ONE DEAL
WITH GRIEF EXACTLY?
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
YOU'VE NEVER DONE
THAT BEFORE,
AND YOU'RE SCARED
OF WHAT IT WILL
MAKE YOU DO.
OR UNDO.
SPARE YOURSELF
THE PAIN.
YOUR MIND IS
LIMITLESS, ALICE.
IF IT CAN MAKE YOU
BELIEVE YOU'RE PETTING
YOUR DEAD CAT RIGHT NOW,
IT CAN MAKE YOU
BELIEVE ANYTHING.
IT CAN MAKE ME BELIEVE
IN A WORLD WHERE KATE
NEVER EXISTED.
I CAN FORGET YOU, KATE.
POOR THING.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO HER FACE?
SHE FOUGHT MY MEN
WHILE THEY WERE PULLING
HER FROM THE PLANE.
DIDN'T GO SO WELL
FOR HER.
I SUPPOSE IT'S
FOR THE BEST.
FACIAL RECOGNITION
LEADS TO MEMORY RECALL.
LEAVE US.
HELLO.
MY NAME IS ENIGMA.
YOU WON'T BE NEEDING
THIS ANYMORE.
IT'S TIME TO SAY
GOOD-BYE...
TO KATE KANE.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!