Patient "a" Is A 10-year-old Male
With Stage-iv Leukemia.
On January 31, He Was Bitten
By A Bat During The Attacks
In Gotham Square,
And He Immediately Began
Showing Signs Of Sepsis.
Later That Night,
He Received A Dose
Of The Miracle Serum Bp296,
Which Relieved
The Sepsis Immediately.
He's Here Today, However,
Because We Discovered
72 Hours Later
That It Also Cured
His Stage-iv Leukemia
Completely.
So Today, We've Isolated
His White Blood Cells
In An Attempt To Siphon
And Replicate
Their Curative Properties.
We're Now Mixing Them
In Our Synthetic Granulocytes,
And We Are Now Injecting
Them Into Patient B,
An 80-year-old Male
With A Similar Cancer.
Our Hypothesis Is That
The New Solution
Will Attack His Cancer
In The Same Way.
We'll Check Back In 24 Hours
And Look For Progress.
[instruments Beeping]
[gagging]
Oh. We Need Help
In Here!
Just--just Try To Sit Back.
Just Try To Relax.
Help! Help!
[patient B Coughing]
Doctor: Oh, Oh--
The Toxin Spread
By The Bats
Was Intentionally
Designed By Hamilton
Without A Cure.
That Serum Cured It,
And Not Just That,
It Reversed
Hereditary Conditions,
Eradicated Anemia,
Malaria, All Types
Of Blood Diseases.
We Can't
Replicate It, Sir.
Try Again.
Sir, With
All Due Respect,
How Many People Have To Die
For Me To Make My Point?
And How Many People
Get To Live
If I Make Mine?
Whatever Was
In The Antidote
For That Bat Toxin
Is Gonna Change
Modern Medicine Forever.
The Supply Was Exhausted
Before We Knew Its Potential,
And It Can't Be
Synthesized.
It's Gone, Sir.
Well, It Came
From Somewhere, Right?
You Really Think Someone's
Just Gonna Hand Over
The Secret
To A Miracle Cure?
No. I Expect They're
Gonna Cherish It
Like It's The Most
Valuable Thing
In The World.
[beep]
Don't Let
This Door Close.
What's This One's Deal?
-mr. Helzinger.
-what? What's Happening?
Aaron, It's Me.
It's Dr. Rogers.
Uh, Tell Me You
Got A--tell Me
You Got A Fix,
Doc.
Not At The Moment,
I'm Afraid.
Aah!
[grunting]
I Didn't Do
Anything.
Help Me!
Aaron: Agh!
[grunting]
Aaron, You're Ok.
You Just--you Just
Had An Episode, Ok?
I Can't Keep Living
Like This.
Well, That's
Why I'm Here.
There Is A Cure
For You
And For Dozens
Of Their Patients
That Are Cooped Up
In Here,
And, Aaron, You're
Gonna Help Me Get It.
Vesper: The Role Of Batwoman
Will Now Be Played By--
Well, We Don't Actually
Know Her Name,
But 2.0 Seems To Be Sticking
Around For A While.
You Got Some Big Boots
To Fill, New Girl.
Hope You Like All-nighters.
Woman: ♪ I'm Fighting
When The City Don't Sleep ♪
♪ Can't Put A Lion On Leash
Hi.
Unh!
♪ No Place For The Wicked
Nobody Robs Banks
Anymore?
You Got To Loot
Mom And Pop Shops?
♪ No Taming Me
♪ I Move My Feet
To The Tempo ♪
[all Grunting]
[groaning]
Luke On Comms: Are You Good?
Ryan: Little Busy.
Your Heart Rate
Is Flooring It
Right Now.
-if You Need Backup--
-i Need You To Let Me
Do My Job Right Now!
Woman: ♪ I Walk These Streets
To The Tempo ♪
♪ I, I, I Survive
[breathing Heavily]
Woman: ♪ Go Do Your Recon
♪ Find Out Who You're
Messing With ♪
♪ Because I'm The Real One
♪ You Don't Want To Step
To This ♪
Ryan: Agh!
Yo. Believe It Or Not,
The Pacing,
It Isn't Healing Me.
What The Hell's
Taking Them So Long?
Hey! You!
We Have Been Waiting
For A Doctor
For Two Hours.
Oh. Actually, I'm Not
Her Attending.
Oh. Actually,
Have You Heard
Of A Little Issue
In Your Medical
Community Called
Implicit Bias?
I'm Sorry. We're Coding
Down The Hall.
Let Me Educate You
On Something.
Ang, Please.
He's Busy.
It Is The Reason
Black Women Die Of Neglect
At A Disproportionately
High Rate In This Country.
We're Not Having
That Tonight.
You Need To Get My Girl
Some Actual Care
Before You Need
Your Own.
I'll Find
Your Attending.
Ok. Um...
That Was Extra.
Also, Thank You
For Bringing Me Here.
I Don't Know Who Else
You'd Call At 2 A.m.,
-and If You Did...
-uh-uh.
I Would Have Been
A Little Jeal.
Only You, Babe.
Ms. Wilder,
I'm Dr. Rodriguez.
I Understand You
Have An Infection.
Yeah. Um, I've Had It
A Couple Of Months.
Oh. This Is
Really Extensive.
-how'd You Get This?
-a Spider...
In My Work's Stockroom.
We'll Get You Some
Antibiotics.
Should Start To Clear
Up In About 48 Hours.
That's It?
When She Showed Up
At My Doorstep,
She Could Barely Stand.
Run Some Tests
Or Something.
Unfortunately,
Her Insurance Doesn't
Cover Any Bloodwork.
I'll Cover It, Then.
Someone Will Be By
To Draw Blood.
[cell Phone Vibrating]
You're Blowing Up.
Now You Have
A Shortage Of Words.
You Know What I Do,
Ryan.
I Don't Need You
Judging Me For It.
I'm Not Judging You.
I Want You To Get Out
While You Can.
-get Out?
-yeah.
Ryan, I Trap
For The Rich And Famous.
The Things I Know About Them,
About My Plug,
I Can't Just "get Out."
You And If You
Let Me Help You.
Look. I Got To Go, Ok?
-we'll Pick This Up Later?
-mm-hmm.
Ocean: To Be Clear,
You Think
I Pulled Out A Tube
Of My Lipstick,
Wrote This Note,
Hunted You Down,
And Then Tossed It
At Our Feet
Because I Don't Have
Anything Better To Do?
Safiyah Seems
To Think So.
I Told You,
I Don't Have Anything
To Do With Kate Kane,
And I Didn't
Send This Note,
And I Think If You
Really Believed
I Tried To Blow Up
Your Sister's Airplane,
This Conversation
Would Look A Lot More
Like You Fumbling
To Kill Me Again.
I Wasn't Fumbling.
I Was Due-diligencing.
It Will Be Very Clear
When I Transition
To Actual Murder.
Hmm. I'm Sure.
Look. I'm A Botanist.
I Work Alone,
I Keep To Myself.
The Idea Of Picking
A Fight With A Warlord
Sounds Like
A Lot Of Work.
Trust Me.
It's A Full-time Job.
So Why Does She Think
That You Tried To Frame Her
For My Sister's Death?
Why Don't You
Ask Her Yourself?
The Last Thing I Need
Is To Be In The Middle
Of Two Crazy Bitches
Trying To Rip
Each Other's Hair Out.
Have A Nice Life.
Doesn't It Bother You
That We Both
Magically Forgot Being
On Coryana Together,
That There Were Obviously
Pieces Of Both Our
Memories Wiped?
I Grow Psychedelic
Mushrooms For A Living.
You Think It's
The First Memory
I've Lost.
But Did You Forget
That She Has An Army?
Those Guys She Sent
Are Just The Beginning,
And You Know It.
Even If You Run
To The Ends Of The Earth,
She Has Plenty Of Assassins
With Pointy Weapons
And A Lot
Of Frequent Flyer Miles,
So Why Does She Think
You Framed Her?
I Trained Her Army.
I Followed Her Rules,
I Was A Good
Little Solder,
And Then I Got Bored.
-you Tried To Leave.
-uh-uh.
Not Just Leave.
I Tried To Leave
With One Of Her
Precious Flowers.
I Thought I Could
Grow It Here,
Do Some Good,
Make A Decent Living.
I Got Busted,
And She Exiled Me.
So You Got To Leave,
Just Without Your Little,
Green Parting Gift.
Woke Up
In Gotham Harbor
With The Worst
Hangover Of Life.
Meaning You Didn't
Remember The How,
The Where,
The With Whoms.
Are You Ready To Hear
What I Think?
I've Had An Option
This Whole Time?
I Think That You
Didn't Get Caught
Trying To Leave The Island
With The Desert Rose.
Based On My Little--
Tch--hot Flashes,
I Think We Got Caught...
Together,
And I Think She Let Us
Keep All Our Memories
Except The Ones
Specifically
With Each Other.
Mary: Can You Believe
The Audacity Of That Lawyer?
He Knows Everything
That You Went Through
With Beth,
And Now He's Trying
To Browbeat You
Into Declaring
Another Daughter Dead
So That He Can,
What, Claim His 3%
Of Kate's
Multimillion-dollar Estate?
Uhh. It's Disgusting.
He Should Have
His License Revoked.
You Know, If This
Med School Thing
Doesn't Work Out,
There's Always
Litigation.
Heh. Thanks
For Bringing Me.
[cell Phone Vibrating]
Moore,
What'd You Find?
-the Napier's A Fake.
-what?
How Is That Possible?
It's Pig's Blood.
According To Our Forensics Tech,
The Real Jack Napier
Would Have Favored
A More...
Biologically Human Pigmentation.
So It's A Dead End.
Not Exactly.
We Found A Partial Print,
I.d.ed The Forger To
A 30-something Male In Gotham.
Well, That Means
There's A Good Chance
He Knows
A Hell Of A Lot
About The Original.
-what's His Name?
-ocean,
The Guy Alice
Is Looking For,
And Now We Know Why.
I Might Be Able
To Track Him Down,
But I Need Permission
To Use The High-frequency
Generator Receiver.
-granted. Get It Done.
-copy That, Sir.
Ok. I Give Up.
What's A High-frequency
Generator Rec--
Not Open Yet.
The Door Was.
Good To See You
Staying Out Of Trouble.
Good To Have
Your Approval That...
I Don't Care About.
Still Not Open.
I've Been Building A Case
On Your Girl Angelique Martin.
Looks Like Snakebite's
Her New Money Maker.
Her Name's Linked
To 5 Outstanding
Possession Cases.
Party Kids,
No Loyalty.
What Do You Want,
Crow-phie?
She's The Little Fish.
I'm Looking
For Her Supplier,
A Grower Linked
To The Psychedelic Mushrooms
Being Used In Snakebite.
Goes By Ocean.
Never Heard Of Him.
Angelique Has.
I Saw Her At His Apartment
Before He Split.
I Just Need Your Help
Getting His New Location
From Her.
Sure. I'll Just
Casually Text Her
And Ask.
You Don't Have To
Ask Her Anything.
Once This Is Within
Range Of Her Cell,
It'll Install An Invisible
High-frequency Generator
Receiver App.
Essentially Turns
Her Cell Into A Digital
And Audio Microphone.
I Just Need You To Get It
Close Enough To Transfer.
You Can't Be Serious
Right Now.
As Serious As Your Girl
Doing 8 To 10 At Blackgate.
Ok. First Of All,
Technology Like This
Should Not Exist
In A Free Society.
Second, Screw You.
I'm Not Betraying
My Girlfriend.
This Is The Same Angelique
Who Let You Take
The Fall For Her, Right,
Who Continues To Sell
Even After You Served
Time For Being Caught
With Her Drugs On You?
Do The Right Thing
Here, Ryan.
I'll Get You
The Information
You Want,
And Then This File
Right Here,
It Disappears.
Is That Clear?
I Do This,
You Can't Touch Her.
You Can't
Protect Her Forever.
No, But I Can
Protect Her From You.
Is That Clear?
Crystal.
-mary?
-i'm Fine. I'm Fine.
-he Didn't Hurt Me.
-ugh.
What Is This Place?
I Don't Know.
Looks Like Some Sort
Of Underground Clinic...
Not That I've
Ever Seen One.
Aaron: Finally. Ok.
Hi. First Hostage.
Heh. Unfortunately, No.
No. I Mean Me.
I've Never Done
This Before,
But If All
Goes Right--
[clatter]
All Goes Right--
Now I Forgot What
I Was Gonna Say!
[gasps]
Sorry. Spontaneous
Rage Issues!
M-my Brain's
A Little Wonky.
What Do You Want?
The Antidote.
The Antidote
Hamilton Used
On The Bat Toxin.
We Don't Have
Anything To Do
With Hamilton Dynamics
Anymore.
I Don't Know Anything
About The Antidote.
I'm Not Talking
To You.
I'm Talking To Her.
They Said It's
Somewhere In This
Underground Lab,
So Where Is It?
She Doesn't Know
Anything About It Either.
Actually, I Know Literally
Everything About It.
There's None Left.
-no!
-aah!
Oh, I Can't Kill Her.
I Need Her.
W-where Did You
Get It?
Long Story Short,
On The Night
A Total Bitch
Named Alice
Poisoned My Mom And Me,
She Gave Me The Cure,
Aka The Serum,
From This Fabled
Island Flower.
It's Called
The Desert Rose, Ok,
But A Few Months Later,
I Had This Blood--
Well, Let's Just
Call It A Transfusion,
And It Was No Longer
In My System Anymore,
But, Unbeknownst To Me,
Alice Stole A Pint
Of The Transfusion Blood,
And On The Night
Of The Bat Attack,
She Gave It Back To Me.
She Gave It Back To Me,
And She Said It Would
Save Everyone
Because It Still Contained
The Desert Rose.
I Gave It To Hamilton,
And I Told Them
To Make An Antidote.
To My Shock,
It Actually Worked.
Why Didn't You Tell Me
About This?
Would You Have
Believed Me?
I Believe You,
And I Need You
To Make More.
Don't You Think
That I Tried?
The Solution Only Retains
Stability After One Generation.
-huh?
-hamilton Doctors
Could Extract It
From My Blood
To Treat Patients
With It,
But Once It's Been
Extracted From
The Second Bloodstream,
It Loses Its
Curative Properties.
Trust Me. I Would
Love Nothing More
Than To Be The One
Who Finds The Cure
For Blood Disease.
Yagh! Ugh! Ugh!
Argh!
You're Learning All
This At Gotham U., Are You?
No, Dad. I'm Not.
Oh, God.
This Isn't The Way
That I Wanted To Tell You,
But I've...been Practicing
Underground Medicine
For Two Years.
What Do You Mean
Underground Medicine?
I Mean, The Reason
Why He's Here Looking
For The Antidote
Is Because The Antidote
Came From Here.
This Is My Clinic.
[groans]
Damn It.
[door Opening]
Angelique: Oh,
I Know Your Client
Is A Major Star
And Way Too Busy
To Walk To An Atm,
But That Still
Doesn't Change
The Fact
That I Don't Use
Cash Apps.
This Isn't Her Save
The Pigs Charity.
Bye.
Mm-hmm.
What?
Angelique:
You Kept The Plant
I Gave You, What,
Like, 5 Years Ago?
You're Soft, Babe.
How Are You Feeling?
Hopeful...
Because...
I Don't Get It.
It's Your Uniform
For Your New Job
At The Hold-up.
It's Legit,
And I Can Protect You.
-oh. You Will Protect Me?
-yeah.
-ok.
-because You Said
You Wanted Out.
This Is Me Giving
You A Way Out.
That's Very,
Very Sweet, Ry.
Good Because You
Start Tomorrow,
And Gays Order
Some Weird-ass Drinks
That You Have
To Learn How To--
I Don't Want Out.
-wait, But You Said That You--
-i Lied.
I Like My Job.
I'm Good At It.
People Actually
Respect Me.
What People?
You Sling
To Influencers.
Sorry I'm Not Living Up
To Your Moral Standards,
But Some Of Us Didn't
Get Brangelinaed
From The Group Home.
What Is That
Supposed To Mean?
Somebody Found You, Ry,
And You Got A New Life.
I Didn't.
I Didn't Know What It
Felt Like To Be Found
By Something.
Now I Do.
I Went To Prison
For You.
And I Have Apologized
For That.
It Doesn't Count
If You Don't Chan--
Oh, My God!
[gasps]
-i Can't--
-ry.
The Room Is Spinning.
Aah!
What--what Can I Do?
My Medicine's
In The Bathroom.
[moans]
[breathing Heavily]
What Is Happening To Me?
I Think They're
Underneath The Sink.
[device Beeping]
Angelique:
I Don't See Them.
Are You Sure?
They Should Be
Under There.
[exhales]
They Were
In The Medicine Cabinet.
-mmm.
-i Need To Go Check In
On Some People.
Take These, Please,
And I'm Not Saying
That As Some
Shady Dealer.
Consider This Misfiled.
I Know This Was
Hard For You.
But You Don't,
Though,
Because You Don't
Know What We've
Been Through.
I Know You're Right Back
In The Exact Same Situation
You Already Served Time For,
And You're Choosing
To Stay There.
Why?
You've Never Been
In Love, Huh?
Of Course I've
Been In Love.
And Now You're Alone.
See, When I Care
About Someone,
I Fight For Them.
[cell Phone Vibrating]
Ryan Speaking.
Ms. Wilder, This
Is Dr. Rodriguez
From Gotham City General.
I'd Like You To Come In
For Retesting.
What's Wrong
With The First Test?
Unfortunately, I Think
There Was A Contamination
With The Sample.
Contamination? What?
Lab Contaminants.
We're Picking Up A Presence
Of Radioactive Material,
So Unless You Were Taking
Selfies At Chernobyl,
You Wouldn't Have
Readouts Like These.
The Front Desk Will
Give You A Call To Set Up
An Appointment.
Have A Good Day.
Ok. You're Gonna Need
To Learn To Make More
Of That Serum
Right Now,
Or He Dies.
I Told You There Is
No Antidote.
There Is None.
-unh!
-aah!
Who Are You Working For?
No, No, No.
No Names.
That's The Rules.
Gah!
Agh!
Pain Meds.
Far Cab--
Far Cabinet.
Over There. Far Cabinet.
Did He Hit
Your Celiac Artery?
I'm Fine.
I'm More Concerned
With How I Could
Be Blind To Yet
Another Daughter's
Secret Life.
Heh. It's Not Your Fault.
When You Met My Mom,
All Of Your Energy
Was Focused
On Finding Beth,
And Then When You
Couldn't Find Her,
It Was About Building
The Crows,
And Now...it's All
About Finding Kate.
Truth Of The Matter Is
I've Never Really
Been On Your Radar.
Mary.
It's Ok.
I Could Tell Him
About Coryana.
No. Absolutely Not.
He's Gonna Kill You.
If He Kills Me,
He's Got Nothing.
I Have Had Years
Of Resistance Training.
I'll Be Fine.
[bottles Clatter]
[pills Rattle]
That Craniotomy Scar,
Is That What You're
Trying To Heal?
Shrinks Called Me
Amygdala,
Said I Had My
Circuits Mixed Up,
That I Reacted
Wrong To Things.
Saw A Puppy,
I Got Pissed Off.
Saw A Kid Crying,
It Cracked Me Up.
Then 5 Years Ago,
The Doctors Decided
I'd Be The Perfect
Lab Rat
For This Secret
Experimental Treatment,
So They Fried
The Bad Parts
Of My Brain
With Uv Light.
Some Two Dozen
Treatments Later,
I Go To A Movie.
I'm Sitting There.
At One Point,
I Started Laughing,
And Then I Hear
Everybody Else
Around Me,
And They Were
Laughing, Too.
That Had Never
Happened Before.
For The First Time
In My Life,
I--i Felt Normal.
The Uv Exposure,
It Worked?
It Did...for A Week,
And Then Cancer
Bloomed In My Brain
Like A Cherry Blossom.
Sometimes,
The Tumor Rubs Up
Against My Amygdala,
And...
Jacob: Agh!
Amygdala: I Have
An Unfortunate Moment!
Please, Please,
Please Stop, Stop!
You Don't Want
To Do This.
You're Gonna Kill Him.
Don't You Get It?
My Amygdala Is
Infested With Cancer.
His Pain Doesn't
Compute With Me.
I Don't Feel
Anything But Angry.
Ok. There's
More Antidote.
-where?
-mary, No.
There's An Island,
And If You Can Get There,
You Can Have All The Cure
That You Want.
Just--just Let
My Dad Go.
How Do I Get There?
She Doesn't Want
Anyone Knowing
The Location
Of The Island,
So She Blitzed
My Memory
So I Can Never
Get Back.
She Didn't Just
Erase That Day.
She Erased Our
Entire Existence
From Each Other.
That's Not
Strange To You?
You're Right, Alice.
Maybe You Were
The One Busted
Stealing The Desert Rose,
And Maybe You
Framed Me
To Save
Your Own Ass.
I Don't Think
I Would Have Done That.
Why? Too Honorable?
You Helped Me Gut
3 Men Yesterday.
You Really Don't
Remember, Do You?
Remember What?
You And I Had
A Thing Together.
From The Looks Of It,
It Should Have Been Memorable.
Oh, Crap.
Yeah. My Thoughts
Exactly.
Ryan: "kryptonite
Is Comprised Of Sodium,
"lithium, Boron, And Elements
Not Found On Earth.
"as A Result, This Makes It
The Singular Material
"that Can Penetrate The Batsuit
"and The Only Failsafe
That Protects The Suit
Against Corruption."
[door Opening]
Hey. There You Are.
You Haven't
Checked In All Day.
Sorry. I Was Busy
Betraying My Girlfriend
So Your Crow Sophie
Can Make A Drug Bust.
-oh, You Mean Ocean.
-how Do You Know About That?
Sophie Told Me That
He Forged The Fake
Jack Napier Painting
And Might Know
Where The Real One Is.
So Her Story About
Having A Case
On Angelique
To Catch Her Dealer,
It Was All B.s.?
No. It Was Not All B.s.
We Need Ocean To Find Kate.
What Does He Have
To Do With Kate?
According To Alice,
He Has Ties To Coryana,
So We Ran A Search,
But The Guy's
Practically A Ghost.
I'm Gonna Need You
To Go Back To The Part
Where You Said,
"according To Alice."
When Were You
Talking To Alice?
Yeah. Right.
So At Sophie's Condo
The Other Day,
She Was There,
And When I Showed Up,
She Pulled A Gun On Me.
And Then You Left
And Promptly Called 911.
And Promptly Called 911
To Tell The Cops
The Location
Of The Bitch Whose Gang
Killed My Mom.
Right Now, Alice Is
Our Only Way To Coryana.
[cell Phone Vibrating]
It's Mary.
Hey. Uh,
Not A Great Time.
Lucas, Hey. I'm Gonna
Need You To Bring Me
That Map To Coryana.
What? What Are You
Talking About?
My Dad And I Are Here
At My Clinic,
And He Asked To See It.
What The Hell Is Your Dad
Doing At The Clinic?
I'll Tell You As Soon
As You Bring Me The Map, Ok?
Fast As You Can,
You Know, Like
A Bat Out Of Hell.
Mary, Everything Good?
I'm Fine, Lucas.
Just Bring Me The Map.
I'm Not Messing Around.
Her Dad Can't Know
About The Clinic.
She's Never Called Me
Lucas Ever, Not Once.
"a Bat Out Of Hell"?
Something's Wrong.
I Need To Get To Her.
-ohh!
-whoa. What's Up With You? Hey.
No, No, No. I Just--
I Just Need Some Space.
Ok. What--what Can I--
I Don't Need
Your--ohh!
Whoa, Ryan,
Ryan, Hey.
Ryan,
What's Going On?
It Doesn't
Make Sense.
You're A Painter?
Do I Have To
Draw You A...picture?
When Two People Don't Hate
Each Other Very Much...
I Mean, Coryana
Was Remote,
But I Was Never
Desperate.
Well...apparently,
I Was.
Where You Going?
To Call Safiyah's
Side-chick.
Safiyah: Can I Assume
It's Done?
I Was Calling
Your Henchman.
Do You Normally Answer
The Phone For Your
Underlings?
It's Normally Not You.
How Are You, Alice?
I've Never Asked
This To A Woman, But...
You Didn't Happen
To Roofie Me
For 6 Months Straight,
Did You,
Because I'm Hitting
A Lot Of Potholes
On Memory Lane
That Need Filling.
What Did You
Do To Me?
I Made You A Woman
Who Could Put A Knife
Through A Man's Heart.
Tell Me Everything
You Erased.
Happy To,
But First, Ask Yourself,
"is That Really
What I Want?"
Wouldn't It Be
So Much Easier Not Having
An Emotional Attachment
To The Man You've Been
Tasked To Kill?
Why Don't You Ask
Someone Who Has
Emotional Attachments?
Says The Girl Willing
To Do Anything To Get
Her Sister Back.
I Wondered Why You
Tasked Me With Such
A Specific Piece
Of Work,
And...now I Know.
So You Could Sit Back
And Watch Me Kill
An Old Flame. Heh.
You're Sick.
No, Alice.
Sick Would Telling You
All The Details
Of Your Story With Ocean
And Then Asking You
To Kill Him,
Which, Again, I Am Happy
To Do If You So Desire.
Let Me Know
What You Decide.
[ryan Grunting]
Did That Just
Pulsate?
This Is Why No One
Can Help Me.
This From
The Kryptonite?
You Said You
Were Fine.
[grunting]
I Thought I Was.
I Knew It Could
Pierce The Batsuit,
But When You Survived
Tommy Shooting You,
I Assumed It Meant
It Was Only Fatal
If The Shot Hit
A Vital Organ.
No. Kryptonite Kills,
Just Hella Slow.
Why Didn't You Say
Anything?
What I Was About To
Say After I Begged
To Put On The Suit?
"hey. Got To Take
A Sick Day"?
I Spend Every Second
In That Thing
Trying To Convince
You I'm At Least Half
As Good As Kate.
Wasn't About To Give
You One More Reason
To Doubt Me.
Um, I'm Sorry.
We Don't Have Time
For This.
I Need To Get To Mary.
You Can Barely Walk.
You Can Keep Telling Me
Everything I Can't Do,
Or You Can Make
Yourself Useful
And Have My Back
For Once.
Hyah!
Emily Blue: ♪ Emotions Come,
I Don't Know Why ♪
♪ Cover Up Love's Alibi
You're An Idiot.
♪ Call Me...
Now Use My Weight
Against Me.
♪ On The Line
♪ Call Me, Call Me
Any Day Or Night ♪
♪ Call Me
I Think Safiyah
Will Like You.
I Want To Escape,
And I Want You
To Come With Me.
♪ Call Me, My Love
♪ Call Me, Call Me Any,
Anytime ♪
♪ Call Me
-what'd You See?
-what Did You See?
That This Is, Um,
Getting Complicated.
[gun Cocks]
Sophie: Hands
Where I Can See Them.
Oh, We're Kind Of
In The Middle
Of A Thing.
I'm Not Here For You.
[sighs]
Ocean, I'm Agent Moore
With The Crows.
Where's
The Napier Painting?
What Napier Painting?
The One You Were Looking At
When You Forged The Fake.
No Idea What You're
Talking About.
It'll Take Two Minutes
To Have This Place Swarming
With A Bunch Of Crows,
Looking To Catch The Man
Responsible For Gotham's
Latest Drug Epidemic.
Give Me The Map,
And I'll Let You Go.
Map? Oh, Now
I'm Intrigued.
-hand It Over.
-don't.
The Faster She Gets
To The Island,
The Faster I'll
Need You Dead.
[gunshot]
Not My Problem.
Show Me The Map!
I Got The Map.
Any Chance You Know
How To Read A Nautical Chart?
No, But You Need To
Bring It To The Clinic.
I Think Someone's
Got Mary.
She Said Her Dad
Is With Her And That
She Needs The Map.
Oh, My God. Ok.
I'm On My Way.
She Sounded
Deadly Serious,
And This Goes
Without Saying,
But You Can't Actually
Hand It Over.
I Won't, But I'm Also
Not Gonna Gamble
With Their Lives.
What Are You Doing?
That Island Is Growing
The Only Thing
On This Planet That Has
A Shot At Curing Me.
I'm Not Putting My Life
In The Hands Of Some Crow.
Look, Ryan.
The Suit Can Discharge
A Single Dose
Of Adrenaline.
When You Need A Boost,
Say The Word.
I Got This.
I Know.
You're One Of Them,
Aren't You?
I'm So Stupid.
Stupid, Stupid!
Ohh. No.
Stop, Stop, Stop!
Stop, Stop!
One Of Who?
Just Another Lying
Hamilton.
What? What Are You
Talking About?
Hamilton Doctors
Did This To You?
It's Not Possible.
You Said This Happened
5 Years Ago.
Yeah. My Mom
Was Ceo Then.
She Would Have Never
Signed Off On Secret
Human Testing.
Why Do You Think
They Call It
Secret, Genius?
And Your Doctors,
They Promised--
They Promised,
They Promised
To Fix Me!
Did You Know That
This Was Happening?
Apparently There's A Lot
I Don't Know About.
Jacob: Unh!
Raah!
Mary: Oh, My God!
Sophie: Drop It,
Or I Shoot!
Mary: Stop, Stop!
She Brought The Map!
You're Not A Killer!
Your Family Did This
To Me!
Ryan: Huh! Hyah!
Get Her Out Of Here.
Go Out The Back.
I'm Not Leaving My Agent
In A Damn Hallway.
I'll Protect Her,
I Promise You.
Now Go!
[groans]
Luke...now.
[beep Beep]
Ohh! Huh!
Batwoman To Batcave,
I Got It.
That's Ok. He's--
Sedate Him
In The Car.
We Don't Need
Any Incidents.
Who Are You?
Just A Man Looking
For A Map.
Don't Give It To Him.
I Will Shoot
This Crow In The Head.
Her Blood Will Be
On Your Hands,
Batwoman.
Is That Really How
You Want To Start
Your Legacy?
We Need That Map.
I Know....
But I Also Can't
Let You Die.
What Do You Mean
She's Dying?
I Looked At The Wound.
The Meds Were Working.
Why Didn't You
Tell Me?
She Asked Me Not To.
-but We're The Batteam.
-not To Her.
Well, The Meds
Aren't Working.
Her Prolonged Exposure
To The Kryptonite Radiation
Is Lethal.
Ryan's Only Hope
Is The Desert Rose,
Which Is On Coryana
With Kate,
Who We're Never
Gonna See Again.
Since Putting On
The Suit, Ryan's--
Ryan's Made
The Streets Safer,
She's Inspired The City,
And She Helped Us
Find Kate,
And She's Done It All
While Having
A Terminal Illness.
I Mean, If That's
Not A Hero,
What He Hell Is?
So We're Gonna
Find Coryana,
We're Gonna
Get Kate Back,
And We're Gonna
Save Ryan's Life.
Except We Have No Way
Of Doing Any
Of Those Things.
That's Not True.
We Have My Dad.
Jacob: If These People Have
Anything To Do With Hamilton,
I Want To Be The First
To Know About It.
I Want That Map In My Hands.
I Shouldn't Have Said
Anything About Coryana.
You Were Acting
On Instinct.
That Man Was
Totally Unhinged.
Do You Think Mom
Knew What They Were
Doing To That Guy?
I Think Your Mom
Was A Lot Like You,
A Woman Who Would Do
Anything To Help People.
I Know You're Pissed
About The Clinic.
I'm Shutting It
Down, Mary.
-why? Why Would You Do That?
-it's Illegal.
Yeah, But A Lot
Of People In Gotham
Can't Afford Health Care
In The Legal Way.
Practicing Without A License,
Impersonating A Doctor,
Possession Of Narcotics,
Need I Go On?
I've Saved Hundreds,
Maybe Thousands
Of Lives,
And Even More
Than That, I Make
People Feel Like
They're Worthy
Of Being Alive!
Gotham City General
Can't Say That.
I'm Not Questioning
Your Passion Or The Good
That You've Done,
But Did You Not Listen
To What The Man Said?
This Is Exactly How
Your Mother Started--
With Good Intentions
And A Lot Of Disappearing
Lines In The Sand.
Mom Knew
About The Clinic.
She Was Proud Of Me.
She Was Conducting
Human Experiments, Mary.
Well, I Wouldn't
Do That.
Every Sick Person
Who Walks Through
Your Front Door
Is An Experiment Because
You Are Not Qualified.
So Is This What Being
A Dad Means To You?
You Finally Pay
Attention To Me,
And Then You Take
Away The Thing
That Means
The Most To Me.
I Liked You Better
When You Acted Like
I Didn't Exist.
[door Opens And Closes]
Angelique: Hey.
Ryan: I Didn't
Actually Think
You Would Come.
I Did.
You Don't Look So Hot.
Yeah. It's Kind Of
What I Wanted To
Talk To You About.
It's Something
Pretty Serious.
Like What? No. Wait.
Let Me Guess.
Cops Got You On The Hook
For Something.
Why Would You
Think That?
I Don't Know, Ryan.
Why Would I Think That?
I Have No Idea.
Is It Maybe...
Because You Slipped
Some Creepy Spy Tech
Onto My Phone?
[sighs]
Oh, No.
I Heard Static,
And Half My Apps
Stopped Working,
And My Tech Guy
Thinks He Deleted It,
But Who Knows?
The Feds Could Be Listening
To Every Word Of This.
I--i Did Not
Have A Choice.
You Did, Though,
And You Chose To Snitch.
They Had A Case
On You.
You Would Be
In A Holding Cell
Right Now.
That's Not How
This Works, Ryan.
The Cops, The Crows,
They're Not The Ones
I'm Afraid Of.
You Know What?
My Bad, Ang.
I Am So Sorry That
You Can't Drug-deal
In Peace.
I Am So Sorry
I Cannot Trust You.
Oh, Don't You Dare
Turn This Around On Me!
How Do I Know You Don't
Have This Whole Place Bugged?
How Do I Know You're
Even Who You Say You Are?
Because You Know Me!
You Are The Only
Person That Knows Me,
And I Need You
Right Now,
I Really Need You.
You Should Have Thought
Of That Before You
Ratted Me Out.
Joy Oladokun: ♪ Did You Ever
Really Love Me? ♪
Ryan: N-n-no.
♪ And Did You Ever
Really Love Me? ♪
[door Slams]
Chorus: ♪ Ooh, Ooh,
Ooh, Ooh, Ooh ♪
♪ Did You Ever Really
Love Me? ♪
♪ Ooh, Ooh, Ooh, Ooh,
Ooh, Ooh, Ooh, Ooh ♪
Safiyah: Hello Again.
This Is Where
I Say Thank You.
-for What?
-your Advice.
The Less I Knew,
The Better.
Ocean's Dead.
I'll Need To See
His Body.
And I'll Bring It,
And You'll Give Me Kate.
Now Send Your Little
Errand Girl To Come Fetch.
I'll Be Damned.
You're A Bigger
Lunatic Than I Thought.
Thank You.
Man: Greg, Move Your Head!