I'm looking for a missing woman
brunette, high cheek bones
looks an awful lot like
your cover girl over there.
I... I don't know.
Well, what about
your boss Roman Sionis?
Sometimes likes to side
hustle as Black Mask.
I'm just a security guard.
Machine pistol. It's a little rich
for a rent-a-cop.
Yeah, but the ammo is
standard issue False Face.
Now, you want to tell me
what I want to know
or do we need to find out
if your boss tests
- his products on animals?
- I ain't telling you anything.
"Rekindle".
Does it hurt as bad as it smells?
Let's try...
Remember.
Now... You want to
find out what I can do
- with a mascara wand?
- All right, all right!
All I know is he's gone underground.
- What about his daughter?
- I don't know.
You got to believe me.
- And you believed him?
- What did you want me to do, go
through the entire product line?
Am I the only one who
can smell me right now?
We're getting no signs
of Kate on traffic cams
and facial recognition
is not getting any hits.
None of the hospitals in 20 miles
have admitted Kate,
Circe, or any Jane Doe
matching that description.
Okay. How long since
she wandered off?
- Ten hours?
- Long time, especially in Gotham.
So what do we do, just
sit around and wait?
- Anything?
- Just a belligerent drunk
at the Hold-Up acting
like they own the place.
Hey!
Come on!
We got a dead soldier.
Yeah. So that drunk acting
like she owns the place?
- Turns out she does.
- Another one?
All that Bat-tech and the one place
we didn't look was inside
of a tequila bottle.
Water by the nightstand.
Trashcan by the bed.
Head tilted to the side.
Mary...
You remember.
How do we know each other again?
Okay.
Baby steps.
- How's she doing?
- Sleeping.
For now anyway,
but we got her back, so yeah!
Definite yeah.
Guys, she went from attacking Mary
to ditching Sophie to treating half
the lesbians in Gotham
to an open bar.
Is anyone else worried about what
she's gonna do when she wakes up?
Well, if I found out
my memory had been wiped
and then reprogrammed
into a dead supermodel
I'd go on a 12-hour bar crawl too.
I mean, if we're freaked, imagine
what it must be like for her.
She needs time.
And I hate to admit it,
but maybe my dad was right.
What Kate needs is her sister.
The other one.
Please don't leave me.
Stay with me.
Oh, my God.
Fix him.
- Alice, he's gone.
- No, he's not.
There's nothing I can do.
Save his life, or yours is over!
That won't bring Ocean back.
I know how this feels.
That unbearable pain
and numb emptiness all at once
like you're watching it all
from a million miles away,
but it's happening
right in front of you.
I know.
You're the reason I know.
Is that why you're here...
To gloat?
No.
I wouldn't wish this on anyone.
Not even you.
Then why are you here?
It's about Kate.
She's fine. She's doing great.
I just...
I just came to thank you...
For saving her.
Look at what it's cost me.
I should have left
with him when I had the chance.
What's going on?
Well, I figured if Kate's got
a few gaps in her memory
maybe she could use an old-school
backup to reboot from.
I think it's more than
just a few gaps
in her memory, Luke.
What are you saying?
Kate's not okay
and we can't rush this.
She's been through
unimaginable trauma.
A deranged shrink hypnotized her
into believing a masked
supervillain was her dad
and the person in charge
of her recovery was Alice
and that's just the stuff
we know about.
Well, I know Kate. I mean,
she survived gas attacks
a bomb-throwing bird, a chick
who thought she was a vampire.
She'll survive this.
You don't have to convince me.
I read those journals, too.
Then you know how resilient she is.
She has never backed
down from a fight ever.
Then we'll be lucky to have her back.
That's right.
This your way of telling me
we were in a book club together?
See? You still remember
how to be a smartass.
I never realized how much
I miss that.
Yeah. You kept journals,
like, meticulously.
I thought it could trigger
some memories,
your own voice, your own handwriting.
Maybe reading about who you were
will remind you of who you are.
It, it's no beach read, but...
Good because I seem to
remember not liking the beach.
Then you're making progress.
And I'm starting
to remember why we were friends.
Yes. Just friends.
And what kind of friend would I be
if I didn't bring you
something a little more fun
than some dusty, old books
to help kickstart your memories?
That is...
Unless you forgot how to ride.
Hi, Dad.
How's the hand?
I'm more concerned
about you, sweetheart.
- How are you feeling?
- Grateful actually to you
for saving me from a life
of Kate Kane.
Concert tees and single earrings?
She should wear
a size two wet blanket.
It would be more on brand.
Her bar is cool, though.
Can I have it when we're done?
I'll make sure it's still standing
when we're finished.
Here. These should help us
get started.
Turns out Kate Kane had a thing
for putting her feels on paper.
If you can suffer through all
the "Dear diary, being
Batwoman is so hard"
it's basically a user manual
for the Batcave.
Well done, my dear.
And once I have everything I need
to give me back my island,
you have my blessing
to bring this one to its knees.
Yeah. You are coming too.
Hello?
Hey, Ryan.
You were hoping I'd be Kate.
- No. I mean...
- Come on.
I'm not thinking all of this
is for me.
Pretty sure I know what memories
you're trying to jog.
All right. All right. You got me.
So you, Kate and Batwoman 1.0.
That's a pretty drama-filled
love triangle.
Well, if there's some parts
of our history
she doesn't remember,
it might not be the worst thing.
So, where do you two go from here?
Looks like I could ask
you the same thing.
If Kate's gonna get her life back,
she should have her loft back, too.
Look. If you need a place to crash,
I've got a surprisingly
comfortable pull-out couch.
Thanks, but I got a place lined up.
It's a little small, but it's got
a killer view of the river.
Girl, you know just
because Kate's returned
it doesn't mean you have
to give everything back.
The suit's hers.
I was just keeping it warm for her.
You made the suit your own
just like you made Batwoman your own
and you've proven yourself
to every single person in Gotham.
There's one person
I haven't proven myself to
and she's the only other person
who knows what this job takes.
Kate will be so proud
of what you've done.
Like letting Black Mask
take over the city
and now he's superteaming
with Safiyah?
Yeah. Well, not to pile on
but you can add recruiting
ex-Crows to that mix.
Word on the street is
he's offering top dollar.
Every one of you
signed up to protect this city
with a noble purpose in your hearts
and what did you get in return?
Your hands tied
by corrupt politicians
who care more about
some criminal's rights
than what is right,
a system more concerned
with the red tape
than the red blood running
through our streets.
The people you're there
to defend would rather defund.
Well, I'm here to pick up the tab.
I'm gonna give you the tools you need
and the free rein to use them
so what do you say?
Who wants to take off the gloves...
And put on the mask?
Yeah!
Help yourselves, gentlemen.
Not a big fan of the speech?
I worked on it all night.
Just can't shake the suspicion
that I'm the same cog
in a different machine.
First Jacob Kane's, now yours.
What's the difference?
What's in this for me?
You don't want to be a cog?
I respect that.
What if I told you...
You could be the machine?
- Hello! Still working here.
- I know,
and I know who you're working for.
Yeah. Those False Face guys
downstairs
aren't gonna be helping you.
- What do you want?
- To follow the money.
I hear your boss has been
putting ex-Crows on the payroll.
I'm not telling you anything.
You don't have to.
Anybody an expert in QuickBooks?
Because somebody's got
Black Mask by the piggy bank.
Hello?
Hangover aside
it sure felt nice to be back
in my old bed again
and back behind my old desk.
After everything that's happened
I just can't believe
you're sitting right here.
You know where I can't wait to be?
Out there in the suit,
protecting Gotham again.
Well, Mama.
Back where we started.
You'd think by now
I'd be used to having
the good things that happen
to me getting taken away.
You...
Plant you...
And now the Bat.
I know what you're gonna say.
Maybe the reason I kept saying Kate
wasn't ready is because...
I wasn't ready to leave.
And you'd also tell me make the most
of what time you have left.
Message received, Mama.
Okay, Black Mask.
Let's see where you've been spending
all of that Snakebite money
because it looks like
you are trying to buy a damn army.
- Hands where I can see them!
- What the hell is this?
Get off of me!
Hey. Get your damn hands off my
stuff!
I don't think this is your stuff.
But I'm thinking these
are definitely yours.
Look like Snakebite injectors to me.
- You guys planted that.
- That's what they all say.
Get her out of here.
Hi.
Good-bye, my love.
Earth to earth...
Ashes to ashes...
Dust to dust...
Ocean to ocean.
I've come to pay my respects.
Ryan Wilder.
Or should I call you Batwoman?
Depends.
Should I call you Roman Sionis
or Black Mask?
I have to admit, I was surprised
to find out the caped crusader
was nine-to-five-ing it as a barkeep.
And I was surprised
to find out that Gotham's
latest supervillain
was a cosmetics mogul.
Mary Kay joining your legion of doom?
No. I am merely a concerned citizen
trying to restore justice
to a lawless city like you.
We are nothing alike.
We both wear masks
to avenge the wrongs
perpetrated against us.
I must say I feel
that given the right push
together we could give
this city its soul back.
Yeah and all I have
to do is give up mine.
Well, now you're just being selfish.
Why should you be
the only masked vigilante
who gets to be the arbiter
of justice?
Why shouldn't everyone
have the same opportunity?
After all, it feels good, doesn't it?
It does. It feels good to fight
for people who are powerless,
people trapped by a broken system,
people like your daughter.
I know what happened to her
how she was assaulted
how the Crows covered it up
made her look crazy,
then threw her in Arkham
- where she suffered and died.
- Where she was murdered.
You know what? Maybe we do
have something in common
because...
I know that rage you feel
the need to make someone pay
but using her to justify
what you're doing
is dishonoring her memory.
I don't put much stock in the words
of a repeat drug offender.
Neither do judges for that matter
not that you're going to live
to see one.
No hard feelings, Wilder
but I can't have
you getting in my way.
Good-bye, Batwoman.
Arrested? For what?
Possession of drug paraphernalia
with intent to distribute.
- Snakebite injectors.
- So she was set up.
We need to have all
hands on deck for this.
Where's Kate right now?
"I'm telling you this because I know
you'll figure it out eventually
and I want you
to know that lying to you
was the hardest thing I've ever done,
but I lied because..."
"I love you".
So there's that.
And I don't know if you
remember writing that
or even feeing it, but...
But there's not a day that went by
that I didn't read your letter.
I guess I thought we'd have
all the time in the world
for me to tell you
everything that I felt, but...
Then suddenly our time was up
and all I had was that letter
with all of your feelings
and no time left to tell you mine.
And now, I'm thinking I should
have taken a little more time
- before laying all this on you.
- No.
No.
I'm just glad I don't have
to lie to you anymore.
Ryan's been arrested.
Hey. How the hell does
Roman know Ryan is Batwoman?
Ryan didn't say.
Probably because she was so focused
on using her one phone call
to warn us he was gonna
have her killed.
- Where is she now?
- Ryan's being held
in a secure holding area
at the Gotham City Courthouse.
Cell phone pings show
50-plus cops in that area,
but we don't know who's on
Black Mask's payroll and who isn't.
All it takes is one to make sure
Ryan dies in custody.
Then they make up any story
they want after that.
It's not gonna be an
easy extraction, okay?
It's gonna be hard to tell the
friendlies from the unfriendlies.
I think your old cowl's
around here somewhere
but I hope you weren't kidding
when you said you
wanted to suit up again.
Ryan risked everything
to save my life.
How can I not do the same?
Actually, it's we.
I'm going with you.
I just got you back.
I'm not losing you again.
That is so sweet.
I'll take the Batbike,
you take the U-Haul.
What?
No!
I want you to know that lying to you
was the easiest thing
I've ever done.
Unbelievable.
You were less than one week away
from your parole board review.
I was gonna recommend
you be discharged
from supervised release.
You were this close to putting
your past mistakes behind you
and then you get caught
with Snakebite injectors?
They were not mine.
Well, that sounds familiar?
Last time, they weren't yours either,
only now you've added
intent to distribute
and violation of your parole
to the possession charge.
We're talking real time, Ryan.
Do you have any idea how
absolutely screwed you are?
Yes...
But I don't think you do.
I have been set up.
- Right. Really? By who? The GCPD?
- No. Black Mask, who owns the GCPD
and they are trying to kill me.
Okay. So I'm guessing they
didn't find any Snakebite
because you got high on it.
Trust me.
I am not going to make it out
of this building alive.
Okay.
Fine.
Indulging this paranoid fantasy
because apparently
that's what I do now.
Why would one of Gotham's
worst criminal masterminds
want to target you?
Because I'm Batwoman.
Ryan, you can't expect me
to believe any of this!
You saw that six-man SWAT team
that brought me in here.
You saw how many guards
are waiting outside.
You saw all of
that firepower for a bag full
of empty Snakebite injectors.
Now, I need you to see me.
Stand up.
Do you see me?
Hold on!
I need to speak with Judge Hamada.
I have reason to believe my parolee
is being railroaded.
What the hell
is going on in there?
- Damn it.
- Wait!
You're gonna need this.
It'll get you out of
the parking garage exit
if you hurry.
Thank you.
Not just for this
but for believing me.
Anytime...
Batwoman.
No royal guard
to accompany the queen.
I'd love to meet Tatiana's
replacement.
I've known
where you are at all times.
If I wanted you dead,
I would have tasked
the men who tracked
you here to do it.
So you came alone.
Well, that's gutsy.
You wouldn't dare kill me.
Besides, that would be no fun
for you.
Even after you killed my Ocean!
His death, however tragic,
was a necessary sacrifice.
He wasn't one of your
island hippies, you wench!
You said you loved him
like a brother.
And I've taken him
from you just the way
you took the thing I loved most
the Desert Rose.
Now, we are even.
Let this war between us die
with Ocean
before you join him.
So much for the war ending
because that sounded an awful lot
like you threatening to kill me.
My dear...
- I'm here to save you.
- From what?
A yummy, daddy-approved boyfriend?
From the thing you fear most...
Spending the rest
of your days locked in a cage.
A storm is coming for Gotham
and only one place
you can seek shelter.
There she is.
And where's that?
Coming down off of
a haloperidol bender
courtesy of this little guy.
Other side effects,
you can look forward to
include confusion, nausea...
And hopefully not vomiting
because we're stuck in here.
Kate... Circe... Whatever
the hell we call her...
Really did a number on this thing.
- She was playing us the whole time.
- Yeah.
We were so desperate
to have her back
we fell for it.
Pretty sure pouring your heart out
to a sleeper agent has that beat.
But...
She could have
killed us and she didn't.
Maybe there's still some
Kate left in there.
Or maybe just enough
to give the keys to the castle.
You know, I know we're
excited about Kate being back
but I really could have
used a helping hand.
So could we!
What the hell happened?
Remember when I said
I know Kate better than you do?
Only works if it's really Kate.
It was Circe
pretending the whole time.
- So, where is she now?
- No idea.
Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna have
to cut through it.
Where the hell are the weapons?
There's one.
You have the coolest toys.
And here I was thinking
I was the girl who had everything.
I guess now I do.
Running away. How heroic.
Come back with me.
Come home.
You want me to come back
to Coryana with you?
Well, that depends.
Do you have any non-smoking
rooms available?
No, because I'm pretty
sure that I turned
your little island into
an all-inclusive ashtray.
Not for much longer.
Coryana will soon be abloom
with Desert Rose once more
thanks to a small cutting
from one of Poison Ivy's vines.
Its rather aggressive growth
properties
will soon turn my one
rose into thousands.
Poison Ivy?
Didn't know you had the green
thumb girl on speed dial.
I don't. I simply struck
a gentlewoman's agreement
with a new friend
to procure it for me.
You see, she was all
too eager to help me
once I had a sword driven through
the powerful man who had wronged her
along with the men
who condemned her to Arkham
where she was trampled.
Circe Sionis.
You didn't really think you'd
gotten your sister back, did you?
If you're not gonna give me
something to shoot at
I'm gonna have to improvise.
Kate, I know that there's still
a small part of you in there
that doesn't want to kill us!
Unfortunately,
but that small part of me
is not my trigger finger.
I'm really getting
the hang of this now.
Then again, it is just like shooting
at sad, needy, pathetic
fish in a barrel.
This nose cost more
than everything in here.
It's not your nose. Otherwise,
I would have broken it.
Don't pull your
punches on my account.
I know I won't.
This is why Gucci made belts
and not lassos.
Hey. These gonna be strong enough?
They're titanium. Let's find out.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- Yeah, yeah. Come on.
Let her go!
Don't do this.
You're not gonna shoot me.
Because you love me.
Ryan, don't feel bad.
Kate wasn't strong enough
to be me either.
You have nothing.
No boyfriend, no sister.
I'm all you have left
except for enemies.
Soon, Gotham will
offer you no sanctuary.
But you will?
Of course, my dear.
Who else is going to protect you?
Who else is going to love you?
You're all alone. You have no family
other than me.
I know.
Because you took them from me.
And I'll remove
your Desert Rose dagger
once I get them back
and then we'll talk.
But you're right.
Killing you...
That would be no fun.
But making you suffer...
Now, that's a different story.
Radiation gauges,
biohazard level three?
What is this place?
Well, it was where
Bruce kept the weapons
and other bad stuff he confiscated
from all the villains he took down.
And now Circe has them.
Look, Ryan. I'm sorry.
You warned us not to rush things
and we all just wanted
Kate back so bad
we just didn't question it
but you did.
It doesn't matter now.
She has WMDs, the Batbike
my suit, my weapons.
Look. I know it's bad
but we'll figure it out.
We always do.
I hope you're right, Mary
because if I'm being honest...
I'm scared as hell.
Joker's acid flower.
Clayface's mud, Killer Croc's tooth.
Why you collecting all this stuff
from Batman's enemies?
So I can succeed where they failed.
Shall we get started?