You.
How are you...
Your eyes.
You have our father's eyes.
Kate.
Who?
Kate, it's me Alice.
God, you talk a lot.
I come bearing concealer.
Oh, my god.
Circe.
You brought my Circe back to me.
You've earned your freedom.
Go.
I think I should stay,
you know, make sure
the skin sticks to the musculature.
I wouldn't want dear Circe to prune.
I run a cosmetics empire.
She'll be fine.
You, on the other hand,
will be minus one tongue
should you utter a single word
of what you've seen here tonight.
My men will see you out.
Daddy.
She's kind of creeping me out.
Yes. We're all confused.
Why are you still here?
Consider me a memory.
What is this, the smurf edition?
It's supposed to be red and yellow.
Cooks made a couple modifications.
Damn, bitch.
Call me a bitch again.
On second thought...
Hello?
I just want to help you.
Shut up.
Okay?
No judgment.
When Jesus talked
about those who eat my flesh,
I'm pretty sure this
is not what he meant.
A cannibalistic churchgoer
tried taking a bite
out of the bat last night
after gnawing a hole
through a fellow parishioner.
Talk to me, Gotham.
How many of these zombified zealots
are out there?
Because I, for one, am hoping
this was their last supper.
Thank you so much.
That money will go directly
toward our new computer lab.
You see this?
In person.
I'm never eating spaghetti again.
This wasn't at the church.
A disemboweled body was found
at amusement mile this morning.
So, what, there's more than one
flesh-eating zombie in this city?
I think we should wrap it up
and go figure this out.
Oh, hell, no.
Let the GCPD deal with that.
Look. Black folks
and horror do not mix.
Okay. Some woman just donated
a literal basketball court.
Look at you making it rain
With other people's money.
- What's up, Imani?
- Hey. How's your mom?
My mom?
Because she broke her ankle
last night at work
which is why I took you to her office
so that you could drive her car home.
Right. Sorry, Mom's fine.
You know,
rest, ice, compress, elevate.
Good. Good.
Ryan made it sound way worse.
I'm sure she did.
Anyway, I should go schmooze.
Maybe there's a tennis
court somewhere in here.
Thank you.
- You look cute.
- Thank you.
I had to bail on Imani last night.
Yeah, I got that. Weird lie though.
What the hell is this?
You're blocking a hydrant, buddy.
Thank you.
All right, whatever.
Let's just do this.
How did Kate date?
Terribly. Why do you think
she was so broody all the time?
Okay, but I don't brood
so we're gonna have
to figure something out.
Well, welcome to the glamorous life
of double identities.
Most people you care about
are only gonna get to know
one of you
so either step up your lying game
or get your brood on.
Welcome, officers. Can I help you?
Got a call about a noise complaint.
What is this?
It's a fundraiser
for the Sheldon Park
Community Center.
Explains it.
Explains what?
Why you people are so loud.
You people?
Need to see a permit for the noise.
I'm the manager. Is there a problem?
They want a permit.
We don't have a permit.
It's a bar. We're allowed to be open.
Not according to her.
It's a fundraiser.
So, if you don't have
the proper paperwork
you got two choices.
You can shut it down
or you can pay a $2,500 fine
and a mark on your liquor license.
Really? This is Gotham freaking City.
There isn't a bigger crime
happening right now
besides a bunch of black
and brown folks
Dancing to pop hits?
Okay, officers, it's not a big deal.
We are more than willing to turn
the music down, so...
We don't have to turn anything down.
The music has been the same level
it always has been.
And we apologize for that, Ryan.
Okay. So, we're fine.
We're cool. Thank you.
Screw that, Luke.
They came in here
trying to start stuff
because god forbid too many
of us gather together.
- I need you to come down...
- Don't touch me.
What are you doing?
Hey, get off of me!
Stop it! Stop!
My god! Stop!
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one,
then one will be
appointed for you by the court.
What is all this?
Party's over.
I can see that. Where's the manager?
In the paddy on her way downtown.
What? What the hell happened here?
I said the party's over.
Got it.
Apparently,
for noise and capacity violations.
Okay. Well, I assume
the security cameras will confirm.
Are you accusing me
of falsifying my report?
Trust me. That's a lot better
than what I should be
accusing you of right now.
Ma'am, there's no need
to get aggressive.
Aggressive? I'm a Crow
who knows what she's talking about.
Look.
Quit wasting my time,
or I'll have you removed.
I would love to see
how that works out for you.
- Do you know Mary's cell?
- No.
- What about the clinic?
Who actually knows people's numbers
by heart anymore?
Do you really think
that's helping anything?
Excuse me, Mr.-Pardon-us-officer.
We'll turn the music
all the way down.
Okay. What exactly would you like
to say to me right now?
We could have used your backup.
Yeah. I was your backup,
but, no, excuse me for trying to
defuse the situation peacefully.
Peacefully? That's a privilege.
A priv...
A privilege. Okay.
Ryan, I'm sure that you think
that growing up with rich white kids
taught me how to play nice,
but it taught me
how to keep my head down.
There is a difference.
I don't just run into fights
when I know I can't win.
Okay. How about we just focus
on getting out of here?
Yeah.
Sophie.
I could call the Crows hotline
and see if they can connect me.
Yeah.
That's definitely going to voicemail.
What?
What is happening to me?
Hi. Hey, hey, hey.
Back off.
Something's wrong.
I know I don't know you,
but for some reason,
I just want to eat your face off.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I...
I don't know what's happening to me.
- Just run.
- What?
No, go. Run! Go! Get out of here!
How did I just do that?
Easy, brother.
Oh, my god. Okay. Listen.
I took a hit of Snakebite,
and it did something crazy to me.
I need medics
in the alley off Grand Avenue.
- I need help.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
I just want to help you through this.
Did you tell him you were a Crow?
Yes. He didn't believe me.
Damn. Even the Crow-card
didn't work?
Okay. For the record,
I wasn't playing a card.
He needed to know
that I knew what I was talking about.
Okay, but we all know
if you had been wearing your uniform,
you wouldn't be sitting
with us right now.
And we all know
if you hadn't touched a cop,
he'd have no reason
to play the assault-card.
Are you saying
it's my fault I'm in here?
No, but in the cop's mind, it is.
It's like whenever I think
we're getting somewhere
you remind you will always be
a Crow first.
These conversations
are always so awkward, Dr. Rhyme
but I think it's time that I moved on,
you know, found a new therapist
someone who actually
had my best interests in mind.
Someone who would mention
in my therapy sessions
to erase my sister from my memory
that she's actually alive.
And not only alive
but brainwashed by you
into believing
that she's some dead girl
named Circe Sionis.
Needless to say, Dr. Rhyme
you're fired.
Now, I couldn't tell you about Kate.
Roman would have tortured me
to death.
I was, I was hedging my bets.
Oh. So it's... it's Roman
that you're afraid of.
Tell me how to break the spell,
so I can get Kate back.
It's not that simple.
I merely grazed Ocean's arm
and all my memories of him
started to return.
Because I simply removed Ocean
from your subconscious.
Your sister underwent days
of uninterrupted hypnosis.
For her to embrace another persona
I had to shatter her psyche
into a million pieces.
Help me not to kill you right now.
Find me something of hers
something simple
something uniquely Kate-Kate.
That will rattle a core memory.
Bring it to me
and we'll go from there.
Is this necessary?
You were 10 chest compressions away
from full-blown flat lining
so I'm keeping you for observation.
Mary, I feel fine.
Then you can tell me
what the hell is going on.
I was attacked in my car
by some false face thugs.
They, they injected me
to make a point.
"Stop messing with us."
I'm not your daughter right now.
I'm your doctor
and I counted 16 track marks
on your arms and legs
so this wasn't just one time.
What is going on with you?
Help. Help. Help.
I need your help.
Here!
Who are you?
My name's Richard Monaghan
but you're gonna know me as the guy
who's gonna try to eat you alive.
Finally.
Ocean.
Not a good time.
Fresh bullet wound.
What are you doing here?
I've been waiting
for you to come back.
- Where have you been?
- Black Mask's wine cellar.
It's... it's a long story.
I got to go.
Hey. Hey, hey.
I've been down here for two days
waiting for you to show up.
What's going on?
Trust me.
You don't want to deal with this.
Would I be here if that were true?
Hey.
You can talk to me.
Kate's alive.
Hey.
Want to tell me
what you took besides Snakebite?
Nothing. I swear to god.
Then I should just be seeing
the psilocybin from the mushrooms
and the diethylamide
from the fear toxin,
but your readings look
like a Latin midterm from hell.
Mephedrone causes panic attacks,
mood swings, and violent episodes,
and your glucose levels
are weirdly high,
which could explain
the insatiable hunger sort of.
Why do I want to eat people?
I am still working on that.
How did this happen?
Were you bitten or something?
No, no. I took some weird
new version of Snakebite.
How'd you know about this place?
She helped my friend from the gym
with a heroin O.D.
What do you mean
by new version of Snakebite?
It was blue.
They're usually red and yellow.
It looked off. I don't know.
I didn't really care.
Just wanted to get my fix.
I just wanted to see her.
Who?
My wife.
The love of my life.
She died in a car crash
before we really even got a chance
to know each other
and the Snakebite changed that.
It lets me sit down with her
and, you know, have those
meaningful conversations.
Gave me a do-over.
I think it's important
to so see people of color
especially black people,
in law enforcement.
I know it's a flawed system
but I also know I can make it better.
How?
Because I grew up
in a community policed
by people
who didn't look like me,
and now I have the power
to change that.
I want to show little black girls
that they can go to top-tier schools
and stand up to bullies
and be trusted
to make life-and-death decisions.
And I admire that.
I really do,
but, Sophie,
the Crows are just the wall
between the one percent and reality.
I risk my life every day
face exposed to the world
to protect this city.
You know that.
So do not sit there
and tell me that's not brave.
Heh. You can choose when to be Ryan
and when to be Batwoman.
I don't have that option.
I am Sophie Moore in that uniform,
and I am Sophie Moore out of it
for better or for worse.
I can't just turn it off.
Look, Ryan.
We get it.
You know,
life hasn't been easy for you.
But none of ours has.
I'm sorry I got heated.
We're all heated, girl,
but that's how we burn it down.
- All right. Come on. Let's go.
- Come on.
If I was gonna a steal a car,
would it really be a station wagon?
Let's go.
Grand theft auto. You?
Literally nothing.
Cops, man.
Always trying to hold us down.
Us?
Those deprived of our justice
and freedom.
Power to the people.
Oh, god. Oh, my god.
At least we're safer in here
than we are out there, right?
Why? what's happening?
You haven't heard?
Gotham's been taken over by zombies.
4612 to base.
We have a major problem down here.
We have a 10- 33 out to Batwoman.
All available officers respond
to an incident downtown.
Another attack reported
at 3rd and banks.
Freaking things are everywhere.
Where the hell's Batwoman?
We need to get out of here.
Wilder, Fox, Moore, clear out.
Wait, Imani. You did this?
A civil rights attorney
is in the lobby
handing out three counts
of unlawful arrest
racial discrimination, and assault.
That's right. Stick it to the man.
Thank you. Seriously.
It shouldn't have happened
in the first place
but on the plus side,
my night just opened up. Yours?
Ryan.
There's this thing I have to do.
Sounds important.
I'm sorry, Imani.
It's cool.
I'll see you when a see you.
Still hungry.
I need more gauze.
When'd you learn how to suture?
Twenty years in the military.
Bed three needs a transfusion.
Fridge is in the corner,
alphabetical order.
So, you chose the zombie apocalypse
to turn off your phone?
I'll explain later.
I take it you're watching the news.
More like the news is here.
My clinic is filled
with people missing chunks
of their bodies.
Any idea who's attacking them?
Users of a bad batch of Snakebite.
The chemical makeup changed.
False face
doesn't know how to make it
without Angelique and Ocean.
New cooks must have improvised.
Well, whatever it is, it's resulted
In a mephedrone spike so intense
That it's actually changed
the composition of their pupils.
Snakebite accesses
the brain's memory storage
in the hippocampus.
I think this new recipe
makes people crave memories
but thanks
to some major synaptic misfirings
someone else's memories.
And that's why they're eating brains.
I think I know how to fix this.
Listen up.
This new strain of Snakebite
is killing people.
Our task
is to seize all paraphernalia
and to subdue any users
with nonlethal force
until we can figure out a treatment.
All the attacks occurred
within a four-block radius
of Gotham Presbyterian.
We think the original batch
targeted the addicts
squatting in that church.
As in Gotham Presbyterian
Outside Crows district?
Inside or outside Crows districts,
these are innocent citizens.
Kane issue this order?
The commander
isn't answering his phone
at the moment.
So, he probably doesn't know
that you were just arrested?
Shouldn't you at least take
the day off
just to wash away
the jailhouse stench first, Moore?
That's acting commander,
as in your boss.
Want to test the limits
of what that means, Tavaroff?
All right.
Let's kick some zombie ass, boys.
According to Mary,
a controlled dose of clonazepam
will sedate brain activity
which will neutralize
the effects of the mephedrone
and force the bad Snakebite
out of their systems.
Okay. So how do we dose
that many people all at once?
At once?
Please tell me that's a gas gun.
Not exactly.
You have to inject each person
one at a time.
- But that means...
- You're about to get up close
and personal
to some truly nasty cannibals.
I thought you came back to kill her.
What, now you're her lackey?
Something like that.
I take it you found something
of Kate's
that I can use to unlock her.
Quite literally.
The keys to her motorcycle.
You see...
I was the first to walk, talk,
wear a training bra
but when it came to riding bikes
my dear sister was finally first.
Kate loved her stupid bike
and these were the keys
to her one as an adult
a red triumph.
And what core feeling
will her motorcycle keys provoke?
Freedom.
Kate rode her motorcycle to be free.
Fee from the burden
of protecting this city
free from my father's
overbearing grip
free from the burden
of having to save her...
irredeemable sister.
It's promising.
But...
My clients come to me
hoping I can reverse their loved ones.
Dementia, Alzheimer's.
I warn them
that with restored memory...
comes a flood of remembered pain
sorrow, and hatred.
My smartest clients
eventually realize
that their loved ones' lost memories
were possibly the best thing
that could have happened
to the both of them.
Do you understand that, Alice?
You won't be getting back
the sister you want.
You'll be getting back
the girl smart enough
to lock up a psychopath in Arkham.
Answer the question!
Will it work?
Yes.
Between the keys
and Kate's trigger word,
I'm optimistic.
I'm sorry.
What trigger word?
This item will help her to remember
Who she is at heart,
but unlocking her brain
is like decrypting a computer.
You need a password.
What is it?
No, no, no.
Run!
Okay, everyone. keep your chill.
I'm here to try to get you help.
Seriously, guys, I am not here
to kick your ass... booty
but I will if I have to.
Bat cave to Batwoman. Status check.
All good.
Tavaroff, why do I hear gunfire?
Tavaroff, do you copy? Hold fire.
Sorry, commander.
They were a lost cause.
Let's find whatever Snakebite
they left.
Let's wrap this up.
Thank you for this.
I don't know
what I would have done without you.
Don't thank me.
None of these people
would be alive right now
if it weren't for you
and this clinic.
You wanted to see Kate
and Beth again, didn't you?
That's why you kept using.
The Snakebite let you redo all
of the mistakes you made with them
and gave you a do-over.
Yeah. You're right.
I wanted to see Kate and Beth again.
What do you want me to say, Dad?
Do you want me to feel sorry for you?
You don't think
that I wanted a do-over?
I lost all the same people
that you did.
I feel the same pain
that you do every day,
every night.
Because I lost everything too
except I'm not trying to escape it.
I'm trying to learn
how to live with it
because apparently
I was dumb enough
to think that you would
do the same thing for me.
You want so badly to live
in this fantasy
with the two daughters that you lost
that you can't see
that you are losing
the one daughter you have left.
Oh, my god.
Get the hell away from us.
Go on. get the hell away.
Hey, hey. Hey. You got any food?
You got any food? I'm so hungry.
Hey. Somebody give me some food?
- Hey!
- Fee...
10.33 to Medina.
I got one in the alley.
Copy. En route.
Hands in the air.
Now!
You're gonna be okay, buddy.
Easy.
Easy. We're gonna get you some help.
Should have stopped me
when you had the chance.
That was way too close.
Thank god you were here.
You're lucky. Almost didn't make it.
The GCPD reportedly located
a false face hideout
storing what they believe
is the last bad Snakebite batch.
authorities say there were
22 victims in total
and thank the quick action
by the Crows
for keeping the death toll
from being even higher.
Who wants shots?
Can we have shots, please?
Thank you. Yeah. I'll take all these.
Thanks.
Actually, I'm gonna need all of these
after the day I've had.
I'm out.
Yeah. I should call Imani anyway.
I mean, I'm leaving the Crows.
I didn't listen when my sister
warned me about them.
I didn't listen when you two
warned me about them
and what kills me
is I didn't even listen
when my own gut warned me
about them.
Hate, ignorance, apathy...
It's bigger than me.
They don't deserve you.
Besides,
we need you with the good guys.
To different minds...
But the same heart.
Come on. Come on. No!
What did you do?
The thing I knew you couldn't.
So you picked now to get your revenge
on her for screwing with our heads?
This has nothing to do with that.
Then why kill the only person
who can help me get Kate back?
Because I don't want you
to get Kate back.
I don't expect you to get it.
Oh, I get it.
You're jealous because you think
if I get Kate back I won't want you.
I love you.
What?
You said it yourself.
You sat in a cell for 11 years
Waiting for your sister to find you,
did she?
Am I the only one who finds it ironic
that freedom is Kate's
emotional touchstone?
How nice must that be.
Tell me something, Alice.
After you escaped
and you finally came face to face
11 years later,
did she even recognize you?
Did Kate recognize you
the way you recognized her
Through the burns, the new voice
the different personality?
No.
And Kate tried,
but you were too hard to fix, Alice
and when she had to choose
between her city and you
what did she choose?
You've made your point.
She chose a bunch of strangers
over her own twin.
She locked you in another cell.
She gave up on you.
That's not love, Alice.
That's apathy.
Kate is toxic
and you're better off thinking
she's dead.
The way you marched
into that station was epic.
Everyone was shook.
So, why are you treating me
to these watered-down drinks?
Oh, my bad.
Here. I know the owner.
My mama would have liked you.
I would have liked her, too.
After all, I'm sure
you got all of that from her.
All of what?
Grit, integrity, honesty.
Not entirely honest.
Not with you.
Truth is...
I haven't been sharing all of me
with you.
Yeah. I can take a hint.
I was actually surprised
when I saw your name pop up
on my phone.
So, what are you, CIA or something?
It's complicated.
Needless to say,
I've been giving you.
The watered-down version of me, too.
You deserve way better,
and I am sorry
I can't give that to you right now.
Well, for the record,
I'd rather you be CIA
than dating around 15 other ladies.
Neither are correct
but feel free to keep guessing.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Just checking in to see
if you needed an extra hand.
Hilarious. Where are you?
I need a drink
and Ryan's out
breaking Imani's heart.
I'm headed to my Uber.
Do you want to meet up somewhere
- No way.
- What?
- He really is a car thief.
- Who?
Oh. Eli I think is name was.
We met in the holding cell,
and he is full on jacking a car
right now.
Get out of there and call 911.
Nah. I got this. I'll call you back.
Yo, Eli.
How do you know my name?
Dude from jail.
"Power to the people."
Right.
Get lost. Don't need heat.
Look. I'm not letting you do this.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey. Eli, knock it off.
Hey, Eli. Stop.
Do yourself a favor.
Don't make me your problem.
What the hell's going on?
- Okay. Look...
- Sir, this man
is trying to steal a car.
- And now he's attacking me.
- Whoa, whoa. No.
Okay. This guy is a known car thief.
His name is E... Eli something,
And I'm trying to stop him.
You know what?
- I have photographic evidence.
- Gun!