[keys clacking loudly]
- I FOUND THIS TYPEWRITER
NEXT TO THE COURTYARD DUMPSTER--
AN OLD UNDERWOOD FIVE
WITH ORIGINAL CARRIAGE RETURN.
[dings]
AH.
I TOOK HER HOME,
POLISHED HER UP,
AND BOUGHT A BRAND-NEW RIBBON
OFF OF ELECTRONICBAY.COM.
- OKAY, SOMEBODY'S GOT
TO DO SOMETHING.
I'M GETTING A CLUSTER HEADACHE.
- OH, WHOA, WHOA,
HE'S LEAVING.
- LET'S GO.
I'M GONNA THROW IT AWAY.
NO, I'M NOT.
IT WEIGHS A BILLION TONS.
- WHAT IS HE TYPING ANYWAY?
- "IF YOU SONS OF BITCHES
TRY TO REMOVE THIS TYPEWRITER,
I'LL KILL YOU."
- I'M GONNA TYPE
EVERY WORD I KNOW.
RECTANGLE!
AMERICA!
MEGAPHONE!
MONDAY!
BUTTHOLE.
[triumphant music]
*
- WELL, I HATE TO BE THE BEARER
OF BAD TIDINGS,
BUT THESE INTERVIEWS ARE
MORE IMPORTANT THAN WE THOUGHT.
HARVEST FEST
IS TWO WEEKS AWAY,
AND AWARENESS IS STILL
PRETTY LOW.
- BOY, 35%.
- IT'S ACTUALLY 34.2%.
- [robotic voice]
34.2%.
I AM BEN,
THE NUMBERS ROBOT.
- IT'S JUST
AN EXACT, UH, CALCULATION.
- [robotic voice]
IT IS JUST AN EXACT CALCULATION.
- ALL RIGHT.
- SO WE'RE DOING
A HUGE MEDIA BLITZ
TO PUBLICIZE
THE HARVEST FESTIVAL,
AND WE'VE GOT TV,
NEWSPAPER, RADIO,
AND I EVEN CALLED OPRAH.
WELL, I TRIED TO CALL OPRAH.
I-I COULDN'T GET HER NUMBER.
I'M PUTTING IT OUT THERE
LIKE THE SECRET...
AND HOPEFULLY SHE'LL CALL ME.
OUR FIRST INTERVIEW
IS AT 93.7 F.M.
WITH CRAZY IRA AND THE DOUCHE.
- [imitating DJ]
CRAZY IRA AND THE DOUCHE.
- THEY ARE PAWNEE'S MOST
HILARIOUS DRIVE-TIME RADIO GUYS.
- SO MUCH BETTER THAN
TUBBY TONY AND THE PAPAYA.
AM I RIGHT?
- THEY'RE SERIOUSLY SO FUNNY.
- IS THIS RIGHT?
- THIS FEELS ALMOST PERFECT,
BUT I DON'T THINK YOUR CORE
HAS MAXIMIZED ELASTICITY.
- OKAY, UM, I'LL COME BACK
IF YOU GUYS ARE BEING WEIRD.
- NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU'RE EXACTLY THE PERSON
THAT I MOST WANT TO TALK TO
RIGHT AT THIS MOMENT.
AND LUNGE.
- OH.
HAVE YOU GIVEN MY OFFER
ANY MORE THOUGHT?
- WHAT EXACTLY WOULD HAPPEN
IF I SAID YES?
- WELL, YOU WOULD WORK
AT THE STATE HOUSE.
YOU WOULD COORDINATE
MY PROFESSIONAL
AND PERSONAL SCHEDULE,
AND WE WOULD GIVE YOU
A SMALL RELOCATION FEE
FOR YOUR MOVE TO INDIANAPOLIS.
- [softly]
OH, THAT SOUNDS BORING.
[normal voice] BUT I HAVE
NOTHING KEEPING ME HERE.
DO YOU HAVE INTERNET
IN YOUR OFFICE?
- [snaps fingers]
YES.
FINE. I'LL DO IT.
- THAT IS LITERALLY
THE BEST NEWS
THAT I'VE HEARD ALL DAY.
- UNLIKE APRIL,
I STILL DO NOT KNOW
WHAT MY FUTURE HOLDS
WITH CHRIS,
AND IT'S STARTING
TO BUM ME OUT.
I NEED SOME MORE VITAMIN "D."
YEAH.
- OH, HEY, CRAZY.
WHAT WAS THAT MEETING ABOUT?
- OH, IT TURNS OUT
CHRIS IS MY REAL DAD.
- I THINK YOU'RE LYING.
I THINK I KNOW
WHAT THAT MEETING WAS ABOUT.
YOU CAN'T GO TO INDIANAPOLIS.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING
THAT I CAN DO TO CONVINCE YOU
HOW MUCH I CARE ABOUT YOU.
[gasps] TELL ME
YOUR LEAST FAVORITE THINGS
YOU HAVE TO DO EVERY DAY,
AND I'LL DO THEM FOR A MONTH.
- FINE.
IF YOU DO EVERYTHING I HATE
FOR A MONTH,
THEN I MIGHT BEGIN TO THINK
ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY
OF THINKING
ABOUT MAYBE STAYING.
- THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO HEAR.
YOU WON'T LIVE
TO REGRET THIS.
- UNLESS ANDY CAN UN-KISS ANN,
THEN I'M NOT GONNA CHANGE
MY MIND.
BUT IF HE WANTS TO TAKE
MY DUMB SISTER
TO HER DUMB DANCE CLASS,
THEN I'M NOT GONNA
DUMB STOP HIM.
- CRAZY IRA AND THE DOUCHE--
93.7.
- YOU KNOW WHY
I'D NEVER BE AN ASTRONAUT?
TWO WORDS--SPACE FARTS.
YOU CAN'T ROLL DOWN
THE WINDOW OF THE SHUTTLE.
AM I RIGHT, FOLKS?
- HOUSTON, WE HAVE A...
[farting]
NOW, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT, NEIL ARMSTRONG?
THAT'S ONE SMALL...
[farting] FOR MAN.
ONE GIANT...
[farting] FOR MANKIND.
ALL RIGHT, SWITCHING GEARS
HERE NOW.
WE GOT LESLIE KNOPE
AND TOM HAVERFART...
[farting] AND, UH, BEN WYATT,
AND THEY'RE IN THE HIZZY
TO TALK ABOUT AN UPCOMING EVENT
CALLED THE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
- WELL, THE DOUCHE,
IT'S A PAWNEE TRADITION,
AND IT'S WHERE FUN
MEETS AWESOME...
MEETS AGRICULTURE.
AND IT IS GOING TO BE
NEXT MONTH RIGHT HERE IN PAWNEE.
AND SPOILER ALERT--
IT'S GONNA HAVE
THE BEST CORN MAZE EVER.
- YOU LOST YOUR VIRGINITY IN
A CORN MAZE, DIDN'T YOU, DOUCHE?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT,
TO YOUR MOM.
[woman moaning]
- CRAZY IRA,
CLEAN YOUR ROOM!
- THERE'S ALSO
GONNA BE HAYRIDES.
- "HEY, RIDE ME"...IS WHAT
CRAZY IRA'S MOM SAID.
- STOP IT!
[woman moaning]
- CHINA JOE, YOU ARE A POET.
[laughing]
- MY BIRD IS MISSING.
I NEED A PERMIT
TO POST SIGNS.
- OH, LET ME JUST LOOK
FOR THAT FORM.
- THERE'S NO TIME!
HE CAN FLY!
- NINE THINGS
APRIL HATES TO DO.
"NUMBER ONE, RUN
THE PERMITS DESK FOR AN HOUR."
THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
I EAT RUNNING THE PERMITS DESK
FOR AN HOUR FOR BREAKFAST.
OW, THAT'S--OW.
- HENRY, STOP IT.
- OW.
OKAY, HENRY.
CUTE KID.
- ANDY, GOT A SEC?
- YEAH.
- HENRY.
- WHY ARE YOU WORKING
THE PERMITS DESK?
AND WHY WAS THAT CHILD
CLUBBING YOUR NUGGETS?
- I'M TRYING TO STOP APRIL
FROM TAKING A JOB WITH CHRIS,
SO I'M DOING EVERYTHING SHE
HATES DOING FOR THE NEXT MONTH.
- THAT'S GOING TO WORK?
- SHE SAID IT MIGHT.
BUT IT'S ALL I GOT, MAN.
- GIVE ME THE LIST.
I'LL HELP YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
THANK YOU.
- YOU GOT IT.
NO, I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THEIR RELATIONSHIP.
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO LOSE APRIL.
I WOULD NEVER BE ABLE TO FIND
A WORSE ASSISTANT.
- OKAY, THANKS, LESLIE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT
WE REALLY WANT TO DO TODAY
IS HAVE A CHAT
WITH BEN WYATT HERE.
- COME ON, BEN.
- COME ON, BEN!
- I'M MORE OF A BEHIND
THE SCENES KIND OF GUY.
- WELL, IT'S EITHER COME WITH US
OR GET IN THE SPANK CHAIR.
SO MAYBE IT'S TIME
FOR AN INTERVIEW.
COME ON, EVERYBODY,
GIVE HIM A HAND.
- COME ON OVER, BEN.
- OH, YEAH.
SO THIS GUY, BEN WYATT,
WE'RE LOOKING HIM UP
ON ALTAVISTA.
HE'S FROM SOME HICK TOWN--
PARTRIDGE, MINNESOTA--
AND WHEN HE'S 18,
HE'S ELECTED MAYOR.
[patriotic music]
*
[farting]
- THAT'S FUNNY.
THAT'S FUNNY.
- HE'S 18,
BECOMES THE MAYOR,
AND THEN BLOWS THE WHOLE BUDGET
ON AN ICE-SKATING RINK.
CITY GOES BANKRUPT.
[explosion]
- YOU'RE OUT OF THERE.
- WHAT DID
YOU CALL IT AGAIN, BEN?
- [laughing]
WHAT WAS IT CALLED? SAY IT.
- ICE TOWN.
[laughter]
- I WAS JUST A--
I WAS A KID,
AND, UM, WHEN YOU--YOU--
YOU END UP GETTING OUT THERE
AND, UH--AND THERE'S A--
- OH, I REALLY WISH YOU GUYS
COULD SEE THIS GUY RIGHT NOW.
HE IS "DRAUNCHED" IS SWEAT.
- THERE'S--THERE'S ALSO GONNA BE
PONIES AT THE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S TAKE A CALLER
FROM DOUCHE NATION.
ALL RIGHT, TALK TO ME, CALLER.
- WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
JUST DOUCHEIN' OVER HERE
IN EAGLETON.
- SWEET.
- SEEMS LIKE 18
IS PRETTY YOUNG FOR A MAYOR.
WHAT WERE YOU, LIKE, 12?
- [laughing]
- THE FUNNY, UM...
WHEN...
I GUESS...
THE FORTUNATE, UM...
CAN WE JUST SORT OF--
[video game sound effect]
- GAME OVER, MAN.
GAME OVER.
- NICE JOB, MAN.
WAS THAT YOUR FIRST TIME
TALKING TO OTHER PEOPLE?
'CAUSE IT CAME OFF THAT WAY.
YOU EMBARRASSED ME
IN FRONT OF THE DOUCHE.
- I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS.
I JUST--I HAVEN'T HAD TO DEAL
WITH THAT MAYOR STUFF
FOR 17 YEARS.
I GUESS I'M NOT
TOTALLY OVER IT.
- NO WORRIES. LOOK, IT WAS JUST
A BUMP IN THE ROAD.
- OKAY.
- FORTUNATELY, THE LESLIE-MOBILE
IS AN ALL-TERRAIN VEHICLE.
SO EVERYTHING INVOLVING BEN
IS FINE.
I JUST NEED TO TALK TO YOU
IN PRIVATE
ABOUT SOMETHING DIFFERENT
THAT IS NOT BEN RELATED.
BEN, GOOD JOB.
- YOUR BOY'S A NIGHTMARE.
- I KNOW, BUT WE NEED HIM.
IF THEY ASK US ABOUT THE BUDGET,
HE'S OUR NUMBERS GUY.
- WELL, WE SHOULD JUST SLAP
A PAIR OF RAY-BANS
ON A CALCULATOR,
'CAUSE THAT WOULD BE
WAY MORE CHARMING.
- I'LL DO
THE NEWSPAPER INTERVIEW.
YOU AND BEN DO CHANNEL 4.
PERD HAPLEY IS A BIG SOFTY.
IT'LL BE A PUFF PIECE.
HE CAN DO IT.
- SO HOW ARE YOU
LIKING PAWNEE?
- UM, THERE ARE A LOT OF...
A LOT OF CARS.
I MEAN, NOT TOO MANY...
TRUCKS AND STUFF.
BUT, UH, YEAH.
- COOL.
GOOD TALK, ICE TOWN.
- OKAY.
- WOW. WHO KNEW THAT
WATERCRESS, GARBANZO BEANS,
AND WALNUTS COULD COMPLEMENT
EACH OTHER SO WELL?
- GOOD DRESSING TOO, RIGHT?
FLAXSEED AND AGAVE--
SAME BASIC INGREDIENTS
AS BIRD FEED.
- [sighs]
I'M JUST GONNA COME RIGHT OUT
AND SAY IT.
I WANT TO DEFINE
YOUR BAGUA.
- OKAY. WHAT'S THAT?
- IT'S A FENG SHUI TERM.
THE ENERGY IN THIS HOUSE
IS A LITTLE STALE,
BUT I THINK
I COULD REDEFINE YOUR FLOW
IN A VERY POSITIVE WAY.
- GREAT.
I'M NOT REALLY ATTACHED
TO THE WAY THIS STUFF
IS ARRANGED
OR THE STUFF ITSELF
OR THIS HOUSE EVEN, REALLY.
- GREAT.
LET'S DO IT.
- AM I NOT BEING
OBVIOUS ENOUGH?
I FEEL LIKE
I'M BEING OBVIOUS.
- THIS JUST IN.
HARVEST FESTIVAL?
MORE LIKE HARVEST "BESTIVAL."
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT
HAS PLANTED THE SEEDS,
AND NOW THEY'RE
HARVESTING THE REWARDS.
- GREAT, YOU DONE?
- THEY'LL PUT THE "FUN"
IN FUNNEL CAKE.
OKAY, NOW I'M DONE.
- TELL ME ABOUT BEN WYATT.
- SURE.
HE WORKS
FOR THE STATE GOVERNMENT,
AND HE'S BEEN COMING TO ADVISE
US ABOUT OUR BUDGET.
- OH, COME ON, LESLIE.
THE DOUCHE BLEW THE STORY
WIDE OPEN.
BEN WYATT BANKRUPTS A TOWN
AND THEN COMES TO PAWNEE
TO TELL US
HOW TO SPEND OUR MONEY?
- THERE'S
NO STORY HERE, SHAUNA.
HE'S JUST
A DEDICATED CIVIL SERVANT
WHO'S DOING WHATEVER HE CAN
TO MAKE SURE
THAT THIS IS THE BEST
HARVEST FESTIVAL EVER.
AND HE'S EASY ON THE EYES TOO.
[chuckles]
- UM, WHAT EXACTLY IS THE NATURE
OF YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM?
- STRICTLY PROFESSIONAL,
JUST FRIENDS.
- SO ARE YOU COLLEAGUES,
OR ARE YOU FRIENDS?
- WE ARE COLLEAGUES
WITH BENEFITS.
WE'RE COLLEAGUES
WHO BENEFIT FROM THE FACT
THAT WE'RE ALSO FRIENDS.
I'M SORRY, SHAUNA.
I THINK I NEED TO GO.
BUT, UM, THANK YOU
SO MUCH.
AND AS ALWAYS, EVERYTHING
I SAID IS OFF THE RECORD.
OKAY? BYE.
- WHAT'S THE NEXT TASK?
- OH, WE HAVE TO WRITE HER
GRANDMOTHER A THANK-YOU NOTE
FOR A BIRTHDAY CHECK.
IT HAS TO BE REALLY GOOD, TOO,
'CAUSE IT'S FIVE MONTHS LATE.
- NEVER WRITTEN
A THANK-YOU NOTE BEFORE.
THIS WILL BE FUN.
WHAT DOES SHE CALL HER?
- GAMMA.
NO, NANNAW.
OR NANNA--
GIZMO.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
THIS IS FOR YOUR GIZMO.
I THINK YOU'LL FIND
IT'S PRETTY GOOD.
- "DEAR APRIL'S GRANDMOTHER."
I SAID GRANDFATHER.
- OH. OOPS.
OKAY.
- "YOU ARE A BEAUTIFUL
AND AMAZING WOMAN--" MAN.
"I HOPE SOMEDAY I CAN BECOME
HALF THE WOMAN YOU ARE."
HE'S A MAN.
"THANK YOU FOR THE $500."
IT WAS $5.
"ENJOY THE MOUSE RAT CD."
HE IS DEAF.
- OKAY, DO YOU WANT ME TO MAKE
THOSE CHANGES, OR IS IT GOOD?
- BEFORE WE DO
THIS NEXT INTERVIEW,
THERE'S A LITTLE SECRET
I WANT TO LET YOU IN ON.
IT'S CALLED
THE HAVERFORD SCHMOOZE.
- I WAS JUST CAUGHT OFF GUARD.
I'M FINE.
- THREE EASY STEPS--
SMILE...
FRIENDLY PHYSICAL CONTACT,
AND FLATTERY.
HEY, PERD, IS YOUR DAD ROBOCOP?
'CAUSE YOU'RE ARMS ARE GUNS.
- ROBOCOP DIDN'T HAVE
GUNS FOR ARMS.
- OH, MY GOD. THAT'S SO
NOT THE POINT, YOU NERD.
- I'M JUST SAYING.
WHY ARE WE GOING TO A MALL?
- I'M GETTING YOU A NEW SUIT.
I'VE LET THIS GO ON
LONG ENOUGH.
- I LIKE THIS SUIT.
- YOU SHOULDN'T...
'CAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE GARBAGE.
- YOUR SUIT LOOKS
MORE LIKE GARBAGE.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH.
- 'CAUSE BROOKS BROTHERS BOYS
DOESN'T MAKE GARBAGE.
- OKAY, THIS NEXT THING IS
A PHOTOGRAPHY-CLASS ASSIGNMENT.
CAN YOU FIGURE THAT OUT?
- "ENCAPSULATE THE SPIRIT
OF MELANCHOLY."
- MELANCHOLY.
- GIVE ME THIS.
EASY.
BOOM--A SAD DESK.
BOOM--SAD WALL.
IT'S ART.
ANYTHING IS ANYTHING.
- OH, RIGHT ON.
UH, I'M GONNA GO DROP THIS OFF
AND PICK UP THE MAIL.
- SAD FLOOR.
- IT DOES LOOK SAD...
KIND OF.
SORRY FOR STEPPING
ON YOU, FLOOR.
[door opens, closes
- HEY.
YOU GOT ANDY
DOING ALL YOUR WORK FOR YOU?
- YES. BUT HE SAID
HE WANTED TO DO IT.
I'M ONLY DOING IT
BECAUSE I'M GETTING--
- YEAH, I DON'T CARE.
I GOT SOMETHING TO ADD
TO YOUR LIST.
YEP.
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S THE STUFF.
- APRIL REALLY DOES THIS
EVERY DAY?
- YES.
WORK THE HEEL.
- ANDY, CAN I BE NEXT?
- YEAH.
- I'VE GOT A CORN SO BIG
YOU COULD SLAP BUTTER ON IT.
- WELCOME
TO YA' HEARD WITH PERD.
I'M PERD HAPLEY.
THE STORY OF OUR GUESTS TODAY
IS THAT THEY ARE
FROM THE DEPARTMENT
OF PARKS AND RECREATION--
BEN WYATT AND TOM HAVERFORD.
- WHAT UP, PERD?
BIG FAN.
- ME TOO, PERD.
WHAT UP?
- THE THING ABOUT
THIS FIRST QUESTION IS--
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
ABOUT THE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
- PERD,
IT'S GONNA BE AMAZING--
CARNIVAL RIDES, GAMES.
SWEETUMS IS EVEN BUILDING
A PLUS-SIZED ROLLER COASTER
FOR SOME OF PAWNEE'S OBESE
THRILL SEEKERS.
YOU MUST BE THIS WIDE TO RIDE.
- WOW. THAT'S GONNA BE
A PRETTY BIG ROLLER COASTER.
- YEP.
- HEY, GUYS, HOW'D IT GO?
- WELL, THERE WERE
SOME STICKY MOMENTS.
- LET'S GO
TO THE VIDEOTAPE.
- AH! LOOK...
WHO HASN'T HAD GAY THOUGHTS?
WHO?
- YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE
I MIGHT NEED GLASSES.
IS THERE A BIRD IN HERE?
I SWEAR I KEEP SEEING A BIRD
IN THE STUDIO.
- HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
- HE WAS FINE UNTIL PERD
STARTED ASKING HIM
ABOUT THE BOY-MAYOR STUFF.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU LOOK PSYCHOTIC.
- I WAS 18
WHEN I WAS ELECTED MAYOR, OKAY?
SO EXCUSE ME FOR THAT.
CINDY ECKERT HAD JUST TURNED ME
DOWN FOR SENIOR PROM.
DO YOU KNOW HOW THAT FEEL--
I SHOULD CALL HER.
I SHOULD. I--
NO, I SHOULDN'T.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO, AND
I'M PROUD OF MYSELF FOR THAT.
- AND THEN HE TALKED
ABOUT FEELING UP CINDY ECKERT
FOR THE FIRST TIME
FOR ABOUT FIVE MINUTES.
AND THEN THE SHOW ENDED...
AS DID OUR CAREERS
AND PROBABLY HARVEST FEST.
[camera shutter clicks]
- BOOM--SADNESS.
THAT'S THE ONE.
- NATALIE. HEY.
IT'S ME, ANDY.
- YOU'RE
AN HOUR AND HALF LATE.
- I KNOW. I KNOW.
I HAD TO MASSAGE
A TON OF FEET--
SUPER SORRY.
COME ON, GET IN. I-I NEED TO DO
EVERYTHING ON APRIL'S LIST,
OR SHE'S NOT GONNA
GO OUT WITH ME.
- YOU'RE INTO APRIL?
- AH.
COME ON.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT
IN THE CAR.
- HOLD ON.
I'LL GET MY BOOKS.
- OKAY.
- OKAY, GREAT.
CALL ME.
THAT SHOULD BE
SOME DAMAGE CONTROL.
I'M HAVING DINNER
WITH PERD HAPLEY.
TOM, WHAT DO WE HAVE?
- I'VE GOTTEN CALLS
FROM A DOZEN BUSINESSES
THINKING ABOUT PULLING
THEIR SPONSORSHIPS.
SWEETUMS MIGHT CANCEL
THE FAT-COASTER.
- OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, LOOK, WE NEED TO FOCUS.
WE STILL HAVE
THE PAWNEE TODAY INTERVIEW.
- WELL, IS IT TOO LATE
TO CANCEL?
- YEAH, YEAH,
IT'S TOO LATE TO CANCEL.
JOAN CALLAMEZZO RUNS
THIS TOWN.
BUT, BEN,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
IN FRONT OF THE CAMERA.
- FINE WITH ME.
- ARE YOU TRYING TO LURE
THIS YOUNG LADY INTO YOUR VAN?
- YEAH.
BUT SHE'S BEING
REALLY DIFFICULT ABOUT IT.
UH, AND IT'S ACTUALLY
NOT MY VAN.
UH, I STOLE IT
FROM A FRIEND OF MINE.
I TECHNICALLY
SHOULDN'T BE EVEN DRIVING,
BECAUSE, UH, MY LICENSE
IS CRAZY EXPIRED.
[chuckles]
- THAT'S, UH, DWYER.
D-W-Y-E-R.
- OH, DUDE!
COME ON,
I GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
NATALIE, TELL THIS GUY
YOU KNOW ME.
- [laughs]
- JOAN!
OH, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE JENNIFER ANISTON
FILMING A MOVIE HERE.
[both laugh]
JOAN, LET'S MAKE
A PACT, OKAY?
IF WE'RE BOTH STILL SINGLE
IN AN HOUR, LET'S GET MARRIED.
- TOM, I'M ALREADY MARRIED.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT, TO SEAL.
OH, I CONFUSED YOU
WITH HEIDI KLUM AGAIN.
- OH!
- SEE YOU LATER, JOAN.
THAT'S HOW IT'S DONE.
[Joan laughing]
- OKAY, FIVE, FOUR...
- HELLO, AND WELCOME
TO PAWNEE TODAY.
I'M JOAN CALLAMEZZO.
TODAY'S GUEST IS LESLIE KNOPE,
WHO IS HERE TO TELL US
HOW THIS YEAR'S HARVEST FESTIVAL
IS GOING TO BANKRUPT THE CITY.
- WELL, JOAN, ACTUALLY,
THERE'S A LOT
OF FALSE INFORMATION
FLYING AROUND.
THE HARVEST FESTIVAL IS--
- JUST JUMPING RIGHT IN.
THAT'S RUDE.
- I JUST WANT EVERYONE TO KNOW
WHAT AN EXTRAORDINARY EVENT
THIS IS GOING TO BE.
- BUT AT WHAT COST?
HOW MANY CITIES
DOES BEN WYATT NEED TO DESTROY
BEFORE HE'S PUT BEHIND BARS?
- BEN WYATT
HAS DONE NOTHING WRONG.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU WANT TO ASK
HIM QUESTIONS,
LET'S GO FOR IT, HUH?
JUST ASK ANY QUESTION
ABOUT HIS PAST OR PRESENT.
JUST GET IT OVER WITH.
BEN, LET'S GET UP HERE.
YEAH, YEAH, COME ON.
WE'LL JUST ASK HIM
A BUNCH OF QUESTIONS,
AND THEN WE'LL GET EVERYTHING
CLEARED AND OUT OF THE WAY.
SOUND GOOD?
YEAH?
- GREAT.
- GOOD.
UH, LET'S TAKE
SOME CALLS, JOAN.
- WHY DON'T YOU?
- OKAY.
UH, CALLER, ARE YOU THERE?
- YEAH, HOW CAN YOU JUSTIFY
RAISING TAXES
FOR SOMETHING
THAT WILL HURT THE TOWN?
- I...
FOR...
- UH, JUST TO ADD
TO WHAT BEN'S STAMMERING ABOUT,
UM, WE AREN'T GOING
TO RAISE TAXES,
SO THAT'S THAT.
[chuckles]
NEXT CALLER.
- DO YOU FISH, APRIL?
- NO.
FISH ARE GROSS.
- LET ME GIVE YOU
A PIECE OF FISHING ADVICE.
- I SAID I DON'T--
- WHEN YOU HAVE A FISH
ON THE LINE,
YOU DON'T JUST DRAG IT
BEHIND THE BOAT.
YOU EITHER REEL IT IN,
OR YOU CUT HIM LOOSE,
ESPECIALLY
IF HE'S A NICE FISH
WITH A BIG,
LOVABLE FISH HEART.
- YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- MAYBE NOT.
MAYBE YOU REALLY DO HATE ANDY.
MAYBE MOVING TO INDIANAPOLIS
JUST TO GET REVENGE ON HIM
IS A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
WHAT DO I KNOW?
[cell phone rings, vibrates]
- YOU ARE GOING TO LOVE THIS.
VEROSIAN TEA REALLY SUPERCHARGES
THE BACTERIA IN YOUR COLON.
PLUS, IT SMELLS INTERESTING.
WAFT IT.
- ARE WE ACTUALLY EVER
GONNA DRINK IT,
OR WE'RE JUST GONNA SNIFF IT?
I LOVE SNIFFING.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
- YOU ARE HILARIOUS.
- SO YOU'RE LEAVING SOON.
- UM, BACK
TO INDIANAPOLIS BRIEFLY
AND THEN ON TO A TOWN
CALLED SNERLING, INDIANA,
FOR SEVERAL MONTHS.
- NEVER HEARD OF IT.
- IT'S QUITE SMALL.
THE COWS OUTNUMBER THE PEOPLE
40 TO 1.
IT SOUNDS AMAZING.
- I LIKE YOU A LOT.
I LOVE SPENDING TIME
WITH YOU.
- AND I THOROUGHLY
ENJOY YOU, ANN PERKINS.
- I JUST THINK WE NEED TO TALK
ABOUT WHAT THAT MEANS FOR US.
I DON'T WANT TO BE CLINGY.
I--
- PLEASE, IT IS SOMETHING
THAT WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT,
AND WE SHOULD DO THAT
RIGHT NOW.
- I'M SO HAPPY YOU SAID THAT.
WOW, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
- YES, IT'S VERY HARD
TO DRINK.
- YEAH, WHY SHOULD WE TRUST
THIS BEN WYATT GUY?
- BECAUSE I'M TRUSTY.
TRUST ME.
I'M TRUSTWORTHY.
AND I AM WORKING
VERY HARD TO...
[sighs] MAKE SURE THAT THIS TOWN
GETS BACK ON ITS FEET.
- THERE WE GO.
OKAY, GREAT.
NEXT CALLER.
- SO I LOOKED YOU UP
ON ALTAVISTA,
AND I FOUND OUT
THAT THE LAST SEVEN TOWNS
YOU'VE GONE TO
ENDED UP BANKRUPT.
- OKAY, FIRST OF ALL,
WHY DOES EVERYONE IN THIS TOWN
USE ALTAVISTA?
IS IT 1997?
AND SECOND,
I AM A BUDGET SPECIALIST.
I WENT TO THOSE TOWNS
BECAUSE THEY WERE BANKRUPT,
AND NOW THEY AREN'T.
AND, YEAH, I SCREWED UP
WHEN I WAS 18,
BUT WHO DOESN'T DO DUMB STUFF
WHEN THEY'RE 18?
JOAN?
- I STOLE MY...
[clears throat]
GYM TEACHER'S HUSBAND.
- SO THERE YOU GO.
- WELL, WHAT ELSE
DO YOU GOT, CALLERS?
GOING ONCE, GOING TWI--
OH, HERE WE GO.
- YEAH, HI.
UM, CAN YOU TELL ME MORE
ABOUT THE CORN MAZE
AT THE HARVEST FESTIVAL?
ARE DOGS ALLOWED?
- HELLO.
- HOW DID IT GO TODAY?
- IT WAS SUPER FUN.
- IT WAS?
- YEAH.
DO YOU HAVE A LIST
FOR TOMORROW?
- [scoffs]
YOU WANT TO DO THIS AGAIN
TOMORROW?
- YES, I DO.
I MEAN, THAT'S THE DEAL, RIGHT?
I GOT TO DO IT
FOR A WHOLE MONTH
AND THEN YOU'RE NOT GONNA MOVE
TO INDIANAPOLIS--
- I BETTER BE THE ONLY PERSON
YOU KISSED TODAY.
- I AM...
I'M POSITIVE THAT YOU ARE.
- [chuckles]
IF I THOUGHT YOU WERE SERIOUS,
I'D BE OFFENDED, PERD,
BUT I KNOW THAT WE'RE BUDDIES,
AND I KNOW
YOU WOULDN'T DO THAT TO ME.
BUT, NO, THIS IS A BIRTHMARK,
PERD, OKAY?
THIS IS THE LITTLE SCAR I GOT
WHEN I WAS NINE
AND I FELL OFF MY BIKE,
SO, NO, I'M NOT PERFECT!
- I CAN'T LOOK AWAY.
- IT'S A--IT'S AMAZING.
- OKAY, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, NO.
HERE'S THE BEST PART.
- OKAY, UH, THAT'S ALL THE TIME
WE HAVE HERE ON YA' HEARD.
I'M PERD HAPLEY,
CHANNEL 4.
- [scoffs]
MORE LIKE "TURD CRAPLEY."
- YES, YES.
- YEAH?
- BRAVO.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.