Good morning, Ron.
Morning.
I know how much you enjoy paperwork,
but don't hover.
Nice bench.
Is that new?
No, that's been there
since the '90s.
What are you doing for
your birthday on Friday?
Nothing. I never...
Aha!
Oh, God.
Birthday,
birthday, birthday
It's your birthday
It's your birthday,
and I know when it is
Ron refuses to tell anyone
when his birthday is.
He's even had it redacted
on all government documents.
Three years of investigations,
phone calls,
Freedom of Information Act requests,
and still, I had nothing,
until a well-placed bribe to a
gentleman at Baskin-Robbins revealed
Ron's birthday is on Friday.
Damn it. I was so careful.
Well, you blew it.
All for a free scoop
of Rum Raisin.
Was it worth it,
Ron? Was it?
I command you
to do nothing.
I'm not gonna do nothing.
I'm gonna do something.
And it's gonna
be really big.
I have a lot of years
to make up for.
I don't like loud noises
and people making a fuss,
and I especially don't like
people celebrating
because they know a piece of
private information about me.
Plus, the whole thing
is a scam.
Birthdays were invented
by Hallmark to sell cards.
They put up a fence.
Who?
No!
What's that?
There's a small park on the line
between Pawnee and Eagleton, and...
Last night Eagleton put up
a fence around their side
to keep us disgusting Pawnee
hobos off their precious land.
There's even a security guard.
You got to show Eagleton I.D. to get in.
Eagleton is a bunch
of rich snobs.
And that's coming from
someone who has a Mercedes.
With a Harman Kardon Logic
7 surround-sound system.
Who builds a fence to keep
kids out of a playground?
Three words,
Lindsay Carlisle Shay.
Who?
Lindsay Carlisle Shay and I
used to be best friends.
We worked together at the
Pawnee Parks Department.
Then she went to work
in Eagleton
and "fixed her deviated septum" and
lost 35 pounds and lost something else.
What was it again?
Oh, yeah. Her soul.
Is the Eagleton side really that
much better than the Pawnee side?
To be fair, yeah.
Our side is this scrappy
piece of land
where kids go to smash
fluorescent light tubes.
But it has a lot of heart.
That's what people always
say when something sucks.
We should stand up
for our town, okay?
Pawneeans are just
as good as Eagletonians,
although on average,
we are several inches shorter
and 80 pounds heavier.
People in Eagleton
are straight up mean to us.
I would never set foot
over there.
But it's the only place that I can get
my Bumble and Bumble hair care products,
so I'm there
every eight days.
Okay, well, I am on
"Operation No More Fence,"
so I'm putting you in charge of "Operation
Ron's Party, colon, Shock And Awe."
I am all over it.
I just need you to do
what's on that list.
Leslie has a lot of qualities
I find horrifying.
But the worst one by far
is how thoughtful she can be.
It's the only park
in our neighborhood.
I mean, where are my kids
supposed to play, the rock quarry?
There's rocks in there.
Why don't we just set fire to the fence?
You know, set it ablaze.
That's arson.
Well, let's leave that up to the
lawyers. The point is, it would work.
Why don't we build a fence
around their fence?
Why?
It would give us two fences,
so if they needed to get to their
fence for maintenance and whatnot,
their pants might get caught.
My son Joey tried to scale that
fence to play on the Eagleton side,
and he fell
and hurt his arm.
You need to get those people
to tear that fence down.
This woman's right.
I promise you,
citizens of Pawnee,
and sweet, brave Joey,
I will tear down
that fence.
Okay, I'm just gonna suggest one
more time that we burn it down.
But whatever
you guys think.
Yeah. Great.
Yes, hi.
I have a question about
your inflatable saxophones.
Do those come
in different sizes?
I'm gonna need
about 40 dozen of those.
Also, what about your
neon gangster fedora hats?
That was rude.
Whatever's going on here,
stop it immediately.
I was just talking
on the phone.
To whom?
It was personal.
I would never make a work-related call.
You know that.
Lindsay!
Leslie Knope.
Hi.
Has it really been
five years?
It has.
You look amazing.
Thank you. This place hasn't changed
a bit. Still loveable, but grimy.
Hello, there. I'm Ben Wyatt.
I'm assistant city manager...
Hi, Dan.
Ben.
It's not important.
It won't come up again.
This is Ann.
She is my best friend.
Hi.
Now.
And she's a nurse,
and she works at a hospital.
Oh.
Nice to meet you. I'm sorry.
It's just, nursing...
You must be
so tired and sad.
It's really nice outside.
Shall we speak in my courtyard?
Yeah.
Well, thank you so much
for stopping by.
I was passing through
Pawnee anyway.
I do a lot of charity
work here.
There's only so much
you can do.
You know, I found a picture
of you from back in the day.
Oh.
Look at that.
Let me get a closer look.
So let's talk
about Lafayette Park.
Oh, yes. The fence.
I'm only trying
to protect our children.
Come on, Lindsay,
this isn't you.
When we used to work
here together,
we loved the fact
that parks were for everyone.
That's what makes
them so great.
You know what's
really great?
A private park
that's not for everyone.
Wowsers.
What do you care?
It's just a crappy
little park.
Well, someone
once told me
that there's no such thing
as small parks,
just small ideas.
Hmm.
And that someone
was this woman.
You can take it if you want.
I have many copies and the negatives.
And I have a JPEG.
The fence stays up.
Lindsay, if we...
Sweetie,
and I mean this
in the nicest possible way,
Pawnee is and always will be
a dirty, little nightmare
from which you will
never wake up.
But it was good
seeing you.
What? I'm not asleep.
I'm awake.
I'm wide awake,
and I got my eyes on you.
That's what I would've said if I
had thought of it in the moment.
What did I say instead?
Wow! This is where
they have their public forums?
Yeah, it's not
that great.
They had a valet.
Yes, Eagleton is
nicer than Pawnee.
And, yes, because of their cupcake factory,
the air always smells like vanilla.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
But their people are not
inherently better than our people.
The only thing they beat us in is
life expectancy, beauty pageants,
and average income.
Who cares?
Factoid alert.
Eagleton was founded
by former Pawneeans.
Pawnee was established
in May of 1817.
And by July,
finding the smell unpleasant
and the soil untenable,
all the wealthy people
evacuated to Eagleton.
Hello, Pawnee.
Welcome to our public forum.
Hi, I'm Thomas
Montgomery Haverford.
Okay.
Well, nice outfit.
What, did you just come
from the stables?
Yes. I was just
at the stables.
You look like
you've been working hard.
You have a million
fly-aways right now.
Would you like to borrow
a mirror or a self-help book?
I would not.
I would like you to get off
your high horse, Lindsay.
Pun intended.
You know if I had your job,
there would be no fence there.
Well, you don't have my job because
you knew you couldn't handle it.
The forum is beginning.
We've got a little bit
of Eagleton business,
and then I'll introduce you.
Great.
Look how pretty
the people are.
Hey, Ron.
How's the street parking
at your house?
What?
Can you handle, like, 20 cars
or a double-decker party bus?
There is no street parking
at my house.
My house is not even
on a street.
Do you have space
for, like, a huge circus tent?
Hey, Ron. Have you seen...
What the hell?
No!
Oh!
Well, looks like there won't be
any balloons for the birthday boy.
These were for a sick child
at the hospital.
My office, now.
I don't work for you.
Don't care.
Decisions, decisions.
I think I'm gonna go with the porcini
mushrooms and boursin, s'il vous plaît.
...that the Eagleton-Pawnee fence
does a lot more harm than it does good.
Hello. I'm Bertram Rolands,
a citizen of Eagleton.
With all due respect,
Ms. Knope,
can't you just clean up
your side of the park,
put some new equipment there?
Well, we would love
to do that,
but, unfortunately,
money is tight right now.
Hello. I'm Christine Porter.
I want to respectfully say
that I'm in favor of the fence.
I see it as a kind
of punishment for Pawnee
that might inspire your
town to clean up its act.
Well, I would like
to respectfully say
that any child should be able
to play in any park,
regardless of wealth
or status.
Anyway, this is
Joey Plunkett.
Joey, wave to the audience.
Oh, you can't, because
you broke your arm
climbing that fence.
I can wave with this arm.
No, you can't.
Both your arms are broken.
All due respect,
I recognize that boy.
He was caught selling
fireworks to Eagleton kids.
Well, with more due respect,
a lot of boys do that in our town.
You cannot be sure that he is the one.
This is a perfect example of
how we're going to help you.
Here's to you, Joey,
and your mother
and to every Pawnee citizen
who might have a bright future
if they fundamentally change
everything about themselves.
Thanks to Leslie Knope.
I'm not done.
Isn't she trying
her hardest?
So cute and so good.
I'm only gonna ask
you this once.
What is going on
with my birthday?
Oh, my God. Ron,
it's your birthday.
Happy Birthday.
Shut your damn mouth.
This is a fun conversation.
Just tell me what
Leslie is planning.
Honestly, I don't know.
I haven't heard anything.
Why don't you tell me what she
did for your last birthday?
Oh, well,
that was intense.
She totally surprised me.
She kidnapped me
from work,
and then she took me
to that place, Señor Vega's,
you know, where
the mariachi band comes out.
They put a big sombrero on you, and
then everybody sings "Happy Birthday"?
Damn it.
And then we went
back to my house,
and she invited
basically everyone I knew,
and she had this great guy
doing face painting,
and I had my face painted
like a fairy tiger.
Ugh.
Also, she did it, like,
a week before my birthday,
which is genius,
'cause I had no idea it was coming.
And then there was
a bouncy castle.
Did you know they made
those for adults?
Mmm-hmm.
Maybe I'll change it up this time.
Can I try the andouille sausage?
Tom, let's go.
What? No.
Hey, not you too.
It's gross. I don't like it.
It's disgusting.
Did you guys get
your public forum gift bag?
There's an iPod touch in here.
Man, she used to not be like this.
Eagleton really changed her.
Yeah, what exactly happened
between the two of you, anyway?
Five years ago, Eagleton
offered me that job.
And you said no?
Are you insane?
I talked it over with Lindsay,
and we made a pact
that we would stay
in Pawnee together
and work hard and fight to make
Pawnee a better place to live.
And then they offered her the job,
and she took it and disappeared.
Wow.
Verbena-scented soy candles!
You want me
to do what, now?
Send Leslie somewhere on an assignment,
a conference or something,
and make her take April and
freeze their bank accounts.
I don't understand.
Is Leslie's work unsatisfactory?
No, it has nothing to do
with her work.
I don't want
to get into it.
Ron, look,
this is me, okay?
You know you can talk
to me about anything.
Well, it's my birthday
on Friday.
Hey! Happy Birthday.
I'm ending this right now.
I'm just gonna leave early and go home.
Unless...
That's exactly what
she wants me to do.
All right, everybody
just grab a bag and open it up
and then try to find
some dirty stuff in there.
What are you doing?
Eagleton treats us like garbage.
We're gonna treat them like garbage.
We're gonna take
these bags of trash,
and we're gonna throw it over
to their side of the park.
And then we're just gonna let the
stink and the raccoons run wild.
Well, isn't that just playing
right into what they think of you?
Oh, my God. What am I thinking?
Let's just stop this.
Put everything
back in the truck.
Let's back it up.
No, no, no, no.
Leslie, you promised we could
throw garbage everywhere.
Wow.
I didn't expect to see the
whole Parks Department here,
although it is, sadly,
one of the nicest spots in town.
I am so sick
of this, Lindsay.
Wait, Leslie.
I've got this.
You listen to me,
Lindsay Carlisle Shay.
Why don't you take
your fancy dog,
get in your Escalade,
and if you have
any job openings,
maybe you should let
me know about 'em.
Come on, man.
No!
I'm sick of
being treated
like I'm not willing to relocate
to Eagleton, because I am!
So here's what
you could do, lady.
Take this resume
and shove it into
your human resources slot.
Oh, yeah!
Shove it there!
No.
You might have a fancy car
and a mahogany purse,
or whatever rich people have,
but I remember something
that you're trying to forget.
You're a Pawnee girl.
No, Leslie, I'm not.
Well, then why do you
come here at dinnertime
and get takeout from the
legendary J.J.'s Diner?
It's not for me.
These waffles make
great dog laxatives.
Don't you dare
feed that waffle to that dog
to get it to poop.
Sambuca need to make?
There you go.
Leslie.
How dare you?
No!
- Get her, Leslie!
Garbage fight!
Ugh!
I want her arrested for
attempted murder.
For God's sake, Knope.
Get a grip.
Thank God you're here!
I want her arrested!
She attacked me,
and then she hurled my
Kate Spade headband somewhere.
I think my Eagleton
colleagues would agree
that we don't want to make
a federal case out of this,
so I suggest you both apologize
to each other,
and we pretend
this never happened.
I will never apologize to her.
- Nor I her.
- "Nor I her."
I doth proclaim to be
a stupid fartface.
Nice retort. Did G.B. Shaw
write that for you?
Did G.B. Shaw write
your stupid fartface?
Ladies, if you don't apologize,
we're gonna have to toss
the both of you in jail.
So just swallow your pride...
Say you're sorry.
We hope you enjoy
your evening here
at the Eagleton holding cell.
Can I offer you anything...
herbal tea, Greek yogurt?
No.
Morning, Ron.
Ooh, dude, you forgot
to put a shirt on.
I do it all the time.
It's fine.
- I slept here.
- Sweet.
So a little birdie told me
it's your birthday coming up.
How about
a free birthday shoe shine?
What did this
little birdie tell you
is going to happen
for my birthday?
Oh, nice try, Ron. You're not
getting anything out of me.
Andrew, please.
Ron, look,
I love you like a father
who's not that much
older than me...
like a young Uncle...
or like, uh, you were
my camp counselor,
but we're adults,
so we hang out,
and it's not weird, you know.
Or, actually,
here's what it is.
You're my Lacrosse coach.
I get it. I get it.
What's the point?
Well, coach,
Leslie swore me to secrecy,
so I can't say anything.
I owe her so much.
I can't ruin it for her.
- Well, I respect that.
- Mm-hmm.
- See you later.
- Okay...
Not if I see you first,
Uncle Ron.
And I probably will,
'cause Leslie assigned me
to the kidnap squad.
Hey, jailbird.
Beautiful Ann, thank you
for coming to get me.
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
Are you okay?
It was a rough night,
but I survived.
Scone?
- They only have maple walnut.
- Yeah. Thank you.
Why did you get arrested?
What did you do?
The only thing I'm guilty of
is loving Pawnee...
And punching Lindsay
in the face
and shoving a coffee filter
down her pants.
But in my defense, I believe
that assault should be legal
if a person is a jerk.
Why are you letting her
get to you like this?
Because she's a stupid jerk...
Because we were best friends
and then she sold out
everything that we believed in.
And the worst part?
To her, our friendship...
it's like it never happened.
Well, first of all,
this color looks amazing on you.
Thank you.
Second of all,
the whole fence thing...
she's obviously trying
to get a rise out of you.
Third of all, she knows
she only got the job
because you turned it down,
which must drive her nuts.
But most importantly,
you say the word,
and I will beat her senseless
with a baseball bat.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God. Okay, we have
a lot of work to do.
Ann, put these scones
in your bra.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Can we just stop off
at the, um, lobby?
'Cause the prison gift bags
are amazing.
Hey, batter, batter,
batter, batter, batter.
Hey, batter, batter, batter,
batter, batter, batter, batter.
Hey, batter, bah.
Lucas with a crazy base hit!
Dude, stop rooting
for the other team.
You're just mad 'cause
they are lighting you up.
- What's going on here?
- Hi, Lindsay.
Introducing the Pawnee
wiffle ball league.
It's an idea
that I came up with
after my best friend, Ann,
over there
said she wanted to bash your
head in with a baseball bat.
And I want to thank you
for the fence.
There's no way we could afford
that high-quality wood.
What if someone
hits a home run?
How will you get the ball back?
One of the many
Eagleton kids who signed up
will just pop over and grab it.
Hey, what are you doing
tonight?
- Why?
- I don't know.
I thought maybe you could bust
out your old jazz sweatshirt,
and you and I could go
to Sullivan's for a beer.
Yeah, I do still have
that sweatshirt.
I know you do.
Foul ball!
- You did all this in a day?
- Yeah.
All right.
I work with some
really great people.
Good job, guys.
Great job.
Hey, did you hear the news?
Ben and Chris want us to go
into Conference Room "C"
for a meeting.
Let's get this over with.
Happy Birthday, Ron.
Ann said you had a big party...
sombreros, karaoke.
Yeah, I did that for Ann.
Why would I throw Ron Swanson
an Ann Perkins party?
What about the giant list
of things April was doing?
That was just a list
of ways to mess with you.
- She do 'em all?
- She did indeed.
So I have rented
Bridge on the River Kwai
and The Dirty Dozen.
Artie from security
is outside the door,
so no one will bother you.
And a cab will be here
whenever you're ready
to take you home.
Thank you.
Do you remember what you
said to me five years ago
when Eagleton offered me
that job,
and I asked you
for your advice?
Uh, "do whatever
the hell you want.
What do I care?"
Right, but then, after,
when I pressed you,
what did you say?
I believe I said
that I thought
we worked well together
and that I might disagree
with your philosophy,
but I respected you.
And I said that you'll get
a lot of job offers
in your life,
but you only have one hometown.
Yes.
That's how I remember it.
This, by the way,
is a one-time-only situation.
Next year, your birthday party
is gonna be a rager.
Mmm!
Mmm.