- RON? JACK COOPER
FROM THE CONTROLLER'S OFFICE.
GOT A--
GOT A SECOND?
- SURE, WHAT CAN I
DO YOU FOR?
- FRANKLY, THIS IS
A LITTLE AWKWARD.
WE'VE RECEIVED THIS LETTER
FROM A COLLECTION AGENCY
ABOUT AN OUTSTANDING DEBT
FROM THE PAWNEE
PUBLIC LIBRARY.
IT APPEARS
YOU HAVE AN OVERDUE BOOK.
- OH, DO I?
- IT'S NOT
THE SIZE OF THE BOAT:
EMBRACING LIFE
WITH A MICRO-PENIS.
- TAMMY.
MY EX-WIFE TAMMY
LIKES TO CHECK IN
EVERY SO OFTEN
AND MAKE SURE
I'M DOING OKAY.
AND IF I AM, SHE TRIES
TO [bleep] EVERYTHING UP.
- OKAY, I PRE-DIALED 911,
SO ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS PRESS SEND.
- YOU'RE WORRYING
OVER NOTHING.
- IF SHE BINDS YOUR HANDS
AND YOU CAN'T REACH YOUR PHONE,
JUST TRY TO
CHEW YOURSELF FREE.
WHALE TALE.
SHE'S FLASHING A WHALE TALE.
ABORT. ABORT.
- HELLO, TAMMY.
- OH.
HELLO, RON.
I DIDN'T SEE YOU COME IN.
I WAS JUST CHECKING MYSELF
FOR SCOLIOSIS.
- AND?
- STRAIGHT AS AN ARROW.
JUST LIKE SOMEBODY ELSE
I KNOW.
JERKY?
- CALL OFF THE DOGS.
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
THAT IN MY ENTIRE
ADULT LIFE,
I HAVE NEVER CHECKED
A BOOK OUT OF THE LIBRARY.
- OH, MY GOD,
SHE'S AMAZING.
- OOH...
MMM.
- I ADMIT THERE WAS A TIME
WHEN THAT SORT OF BEHAVIOR
WOULD'VE DRIVEN ME WILD.
BUT I AM IN A HEALTHY
RELATIONSHIP NOW, TAMMY.
- A RELATIONSHIP?
WITH WHOM?
- A LOVELY, INTELLIGENT,
SELF-POSSESSED
PEDIATRIC SURGEON
NAMED WENDY.
- SOUNDS LIKE A REAL WHORE.
- CLEAR THE LATE CHARGES
AND CUT THE CRAP.
GOOD DAY.
- GOOD DAY, LESLIE.
- GOOD--GOOD DAY.
[triumphant music]
*
- OKAY, SO WE'RE
ORDERING THEM
A TOTAL OF 30 PIZZAS
SO LET'S TALK TOPPINGS.
- SAUSAGE, ONION,
AND PEPPERS.
SCIENTIFICALLY PROVEN
TO BE THE BEST TOPPINGS.
- NICE.
- SHOULD WE THROW IN
SOME SALADS
FOR A HEALTHY OPTION?
- WOW, DON'T BE
SUCH A JERRY, BEN.
- YEAH, BEN, THESE GUYS
ARE COPS, NOT BALLERINAS.
SO WE ARE THROWING
A LITTLE SHINDIG
FOR THE POLICE DEPARTMENT
BECAUSE WE'RE ASKING THEM
TO VOLUNTEER AS SECURITY
DURING THE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS
ABOUT BIG OUTDOOR GATHERINGS
THAT MAKES EVERYONE
WANT TO URINATE
ALL OVER EVERYTHING,
BUT IT DOES.
AND THEY DO.
- OKAY,
HOW ABOUT SOME CALZONES?
- CALZONES ARE LIKE PIZZAS
BUT THEY'RE HARDER TO EAT.
THEY'RE DUMB
AND SO WAS THAT IDEA.
- SERIOUSLY?
- THIS IS EMBARRASSING FOR YOU.
- SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
RON, YOU READY?
- ABSOLUTELY, MY DEAR.
I AM OFF TO HAVE
A MID-MORNING PRE-LUNCH
WITH MY LADY FRIEND,
BUT I WILL BE BACK
IN TIME FOR LUNCH.
- ALL RIGHT.
- OH, RON'S GIRLFRIEND'S
PRETTY.
- [laughs]
TOM'S EX-WIFE.
- OH.
- I DON'T WANT TO
SEE THEM TOGETHER.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE
RUBBING IT IN MY FACE.
SO ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
IS CAPTAIN MUSTACHE
PLOWING MY EX-WIFE.
- AND YOU IMAGINE
HE'S WEARING A CAPE
WHILE HE'S PLOWING HER?
- WHAT?
- NO, JUST,
CAPTAIN MUSTACHE?
I MEAN, IF ALL YOU CAN THINK OF
IS RON, YOU KNOW--[grunting]--
MAYBE PUT HIM IN SOME TIGHTS
AND A CAPE
AND THEN--AND THEN
IT WOULD BE FUNNY.
- NOW, I'M IMAGINING
A CAPE.
- APRIL?
- DID YOU CALL ME?
- I DID CALL YOU.
GOOD EARS.
- CHRIS'S ASSISTANT
WENT BACK TO INDIANAPOLIS,
SO HE'S BORROWING ME
FOR A FEW DAYS.
YAY.
- I'D LIKE YOU TO GET ME
SOME MORE POST-ITS.
I'D LIKE THEM
IN MULTIPLE COLORS.
I'D LIKE GREEN.
I'D LIKE YELLOW.
DO NOT BUY ORANGE.
I DO NOT WANT ORANGE.
I HAVE PLENTY OF ORANGE.
- GOT IT.
YOU WANT FIVE MILLION
ORANGE POST-ITS.
- THAT'S HILARIOUS.
OH, WAIT!
I HAVE A POST-IT FOR YOU.
IT SAYS, "GREAT JOB."
- MMM.
- GREAT JOB!
- THERE YOU GO.
- THEY'RE GETTING REALLY OLD
AND I'M AN ONLY CHILD.
I JUST FEEL LIKE
THE RIGHT THING TO DO
IS TO MOVE BACK HOME.
- I'M SORRY TO SEE YOU GO.
I'VE REALLY COME TO THINK
OF YOU AS...
A COMPANION.
- HEY, I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'D WANT TO MOVE TO CANADA?
- [chokes, spits]
[laughs]
CANADA.
NO, I DON'T SUPPOSE I WOULD.
- HEY, I HATE TO NAG,
BUT SHOULDN'T
WE BE TALKING STRATEGY,
LIKE, WHEN TO ASK THE CHIEF
FOR THIS HUGE CRITICAL FAVOR?
- YES. I KNOW EXACTLY
WHEN WE SHOULD DO IT.
POST PIZZA,
PRE ICE CREAM,
BETWEEN HIS THIRD
AND FOURTH BEER.
HE'LL BE FULL BUT NOT STUFFED,
TIPSY BUT NOT DRUNK.
SHOULD BE AROUND 9:00.
- OKAY, SO YOU'VE
THOUGHT THIS THROUGH.
- JUST SIT TIGHT.
I'LL GET YOU A BEER.
CAN I HAVE
TWO BEERS PLEASE?
HEY, YOU OKAY?
- WENDY AND I ARE OVER.
SHE'S MOVING BACK
TO CANADA.
IT'S TOO BAD.
I JUST TAUGHT HER
HOW TO WHITTLE.
SHE MADE ME THIS
TINY SHARPENED STICK.
- LOOK, I'M GONNA TELL YOU
WHAT I TELL ALL MY GIRLFRIENDS
WHEN THEY GET DUMPED.
MEN ARE DOGS.
- THANK YOU, LESLIE.
THAT DOES NOT APPLY
TO THIS SITUATION AT ALL.
BUT THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
- THIS IS A DISASTER.
YOU'RE NOT INTO FOOTBALL?
I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
WRONG WITH YOU.
I KNEW IT.
I KNEW IT, KNEW IT, KNEW IT.
- HONESTLY, I HAVEN'T FELT
THIS GOOD IN YEARS.
AND IT'S NOT JUST BECAUSE
OF THE SUPPLEMENTS
HE HAS ME TAKING
AND THE SOLUBLE FIBER
AND THE INCREASE
IN REGULARITY.
IT'S HIM.
HE'S, UH, MOVING BACK
TO INDIANAPOLIS
IN A COUPLE OF WEEKS,
WHICH SUCKS.
BUT IF HE ASKED ME
TO MOVE WITH HIM,
I THINK I WOULD.
- I WOULD LIKE A LOCAL BEER.
I'D LIKE IT IN A BOTTLE.
I'D LIKE THE BOTTLE
TO BE COLD.
- I WOULD LIKE
A GLASS OF WHITE WINE.
I WOULD LIKE IT
TO BE CHARDONNAY.
AND I WOULD LIKE THAT
WITH ONE ICE CUBE.
THANKS.
- CHIEF TRUMPLE?
- HEY, KNOPE.
- YOU KNOW BEN WYATT
FROM THE STATE BUDGET OFFICE.
- YEAH, HOW'S IT GOING?
- HELLO.
- THANKS FOR THE PARTY.
GOOD PIZZA.
- GREAT. SO, YEAH, THE PIZZA'S
DYNAMITE, ISN'T IT?
- I JUST SAID
IT WAS GOOD PIZZA.
IT'S GOOD.
PIZZA'S GOOD.
- YOU, UH,
YOU KNOW WHAT I LIKE?
CALZONES.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH THIS GUY?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL CHECK IN WITH YOU LATER.
- TAKE IT EASY.
- YEAH, WILL DO.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- I WAS GETTING SOMEWHERE
WITH THAT.
- YEAH, GREAT SMALL TALK
OVER THERE.
OKAY, LET ME HANDLE THIS.
- I GET A LITTLE NERVOUS
WITH COPS.
- I'M IN CONTROL.
- WHAT'S UP?
TOM HAVERFORD'S
IN THE BUILDING.
- WHOO!
- TOM, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
- SAME THING YOU'RE DOING,
CELEBRATING PAWNEE'S FINEST.
I BELIEVE YOU KNOW
MY DATE, TAMMY SWANSON.
- HIYA, RON.
- OH. HIYA, RON.
- HEY, RON.
- I'M SORRY.
IS SEEING YOUR EX-WIFE
ON MY ARM
MAKING YOU UNCOMFORTABLE?
GEE, I CAN'T IMAGINE WHY.
OR CAN I?
OOH, I LIKE THIS SONG.
DO YOU WANNA DANCE, TAMMY?
- OH, YEAH. YEAH.
OOH. UH.
- I KNOW TAMMY SEEMS SCARY.
BUT REALLY, SHE'S JUST
A MANIPULATIVE, PSYCHOTIC,
LIBRARY-BOOK-PEDALING,
SEX-CRAZED SHE-DEMON.
- UH! YEAH.
[laughs]
- I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH.
- TAMMY.
- UH. OH, HI, RON.
I WAS JUST TASTING
MY NEW BOYFRIEND, GLENN.
- TOM.
- YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE MIXED UP IN, SON.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT YOU.
IT'S ABOUT ME.
- TYPICAL RON SWANSON.
ALWAYS THINKING ABOUT YOURSELF.
MAYBE WE LIKE EACH OTHER.
- YEAH, MAYBE WE DO.
- AH-EEY! OKAY.
LET'S TAKE IT EASY.
- TAMMY, LEAVE HIM
OUT OF THIS.
- OH, SO IT'S OKAY FOR YOU
TO HAVE A GIRLFRIEND,
BUT I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO SEE ANYBODY?
- DAMN IT, WOMAN.
JUST CRAWL BACK IN TO
THE DANK HOLE YOU CAME FROM
AND LEAVE
MY FRIENDS ALONE.
- OH! OKAY, OKAY.
LET'S SETTLE DOWN.
- WHAT SEEMS TO BE
THE PROBLEM?
- WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM?
- IS THERE A PROBLEM HERE?
BASICALLY WHAT WE HAD HERE WAS
A DISPUTE OF A DOMESTIC NATURE.
- WHITE MALE, 40, 45.
- CAUCASIAN MALE.
STOCKY BUILD.
- APPROXIMATELY 5'10".
- VERBAL ALTERCATION TRANSPIRED
AT APPROXIMATELY 8:55 P.M.
WITH A FEMALE UNSUB.
APPEARS TO BE SLIGHTLY
INTOXICATED.
CLAIMS TO BE AN EX-SPOUSE.
REAL PIECE OF WORK.
- REAL PIECE OF WORK.
- I KNOW WHY
YOU'RE DOING THIS,
AND YOU'RE MAKING
A HUGE MISTAKE.
- FIGHT FIRE
WITH FIRE, LESLIE.
HE DATES MY EX,
I DATE HIS.
- RON AND WENDY AREN'T
EVEN DATING ANYMORE.
SHE'S MOVING BACK
TO CANADA.
- WHAT?
- UH-OH. OH, GOD.
OKAY, HEY.
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
- RON AND I ARE GOING
TO GET A CUP OF COFFEE
AND TALK THINGS OUT.
- IT'S TIME FOR TAMMY AND ME
TO BURY THE HATCHET
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
[moaning and groaning]
- IT'S BEEN LIKE THIS
FOR HOURS.
- RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE.
- YEAH. YEAH.
- HEY, SWANSON!
[banging]
SNAP OUT OF IT!
- LESLIE.
CONGRATULATE US.
- RON'S GOT ONE
JUST LIKE IT ON HIS PENIS.
- OH, YEAH.
- WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED TO YOU?
- WELL...
[indistinct yelling]
- THANK YOU.
- [laughs]
- ROCK AND ROLL!
YEAH, BABY!
- I GOT IT!
- UH!
- YOU MAY NOW
KISS THE BRIDE.
[Wedding March playing]
*
- IT'S BEEN KIND OF
A CRAZY NIGHT.
- COME BACK, COME BACK.
[moaning and groaning]
- APRIL, COULD YOU
COME IN HERE A SECOND?
APRIL, WAY TO COME IN.
GREAT INITIATIVE.
- YOU CALLED ME IN.
- LISTEN, COULD YOU PLEASE
CALL ANN PERKINS
AND TELL HER THAT I WILL BE
UNABLE TO ENJOY LUNCH
WITH HER TODAY,
AS I AM JUST SWAMPED.
ALL DAY.
- COPY THAT.
HI, ANN.
THIS IS APRIL.
I'M JUST CALLING
TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT CHRIS CAN'T
MAKE LUNCH TODAY.
I KNEW YOU WOULDN'T CARE.
GOOD-BYE.
- THEY STARTED HAVING SEX
AT THE COURT HOUSE.
WE HAD NO CHOICE.
- OH, WELL,
I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND.
CHIEF, I NEED TO ASK YOU
A HUGE FAVOR.
- LESLIE.
- RON IS A GOOD MAN
WHO JUST GOT CAUGHT UP
IN SOMETHING TERRIBLE.
AND I WAS HOPING THAT MAYBE
YOU WOULD
REDUCE HIS CHARGES AND
RELEASE HIM INTO MY CUSTODY.
- ALL RIGHT.
BUT KEEP HIM AWAY
FROM THAT CRAZY LIBRARIAN.
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
- IN FACT, I DON'T WANT HIM
WITHIN 500 FEET
OF THE LIBRARY.
- THAT'S GOOD ADVICE
FOR ALL OF US.
- NOTHING BUT TROUBLE THERE.
- THANKS A LOT, BRO.
- HEY, STOP.
- SORRY.
- [groans]
TAKE ME BACK TO TAMMY.
- FOR THE MILLIONTH TIME,
NO.
- THAT WAS NOT THE FAVOR
WE NEEDED TO ASK FOR, LESLIE.
IF WE DON'T GET THE POLICE
FOR THE HARVEST FESTIVAL,
THERE IS NO HARVEST FESTIVAL.
- I KNOW.
I'LL FIGURE IT OUT LATER.
- CAN YOU TURN THE RADIO OFF.
THIS IS OUR SONG.
- YOUR SONG IS
DANCING ON THE CEILING
BY LIONEL RITCHIE?
OH, WOW,
LOOK AT THAT.
YOU SHAVED OFF
PART OF YOUR MUSTACHE.
THAT'S LOVELY.
- I DIDN'T SHAVE IT OFF.
IT RUBBED OFF...
FROM FRICTION.
- UHH!
- UHHH!
- RON SWANSON,
THIS IS AN INTERVENTION.
YOU HAVE BEEN SPENDING
THE LAST 24 HOURS
SIPPING ON JOY JUICE
AND TRIPPING ON TAMMY.
WELL, THE PEOPLE IN THIS ROOM
ARE YOUR METHADONE.
AND WE'RE HERE
TO GET YOU CLEAN.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
HOLY MATRIMONY,
THERE'S THE MAN OF THE HOUR.
- JERRY, WHAT IS THIS?
- THAT IS THE SET
OF TUMBLERS
THAT I GOT
FROM THE REGISTRY.
- THIS IS AN INTERVENTION.
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID
ON THE PHONE
IT WAS A RECEPTION.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S BEGIN.
- I WOULD LIKE TO ADDRESS
THE GOOFY-LOOKING,
DIRTY-KIMONO-WEARING,
CORN-ROWED CLOWN IN THE ROOM.
IF YOU SEE RON SWANSON,
CAN YOU GIVE HIM THIS MESSAGE?
YOU USED TO BE A MAN.
YOU NEED TO GET
YOUR HOUSE IN ORDER.
LOOK, I LOVE YOU
LIKE A BROTHER
BUT RIGHT NOW,
I HATE YOU
LIKE MY ACTUAL BROTHER,
LEVONDRIOUS,
WHO I HATE.
- OKAY, TOM.
- RON, YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOUR SKIN IS GLOWING.
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU SO HAPPY.
- OKAY, SIT DOWN.
- ANDY.
- RON, I DO NOT REALLY
UNDERSTAND
WHAT IS GOING ON
RIGHT NOW.
BUT NO MATTER WHAT,
YOU MUST KEEP GOING.
- NO.
- YOU MUST STOP.
I LOVE YOU, BUDDY.
FOLLOW YOUR DREAMS.
- POWERFUL STUFF.
- APRIL?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I WORK FOR YOUR BOYFRIEND.
- I CAME TO SEE WHY CHRIS
STOOD ME UP FOR LUNCH,
BUT I THINK I JUST
FIGURED IT OUT.
- BECAUSE HE
DOESN'T LIKE YOU?
- NO, I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT'S NOT IT.
- ACTUALLY IT'S BECAUSE
I DIDN'T CALL YOU DELIBERATELY.
WHICH, IF YOU ASK ME,
IS A FIREABLE OFFENSE.
SO I WOULD TELL HIM THAT.
ALSO, HE'S NOT
INTO YOU SEXUALLY.
- MMM.
- ANN PERKINS.
APRIL LUDGATE.
LITERALLY TWO OF
MY FAVORITE PEOPLE ON EARTH.
I'M SORRY THAT I HAD
TO CANCEL LUNCH.
- NOT AT ALL.
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
APRIL HERE WAS VERY
APOLOGETIC ON THE PHONE.
SHE ALSO SENT ME FLOWERS.
- APRIL.
NICE TOUCH.
- HELLO, RON.
IT'S RON.
IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS,
IT MEANS THAT ONCE AGAIN
YOU HAVE DANCED
WITH THE DEVIL.
RIGHT NOW,
YOU'RE PROBABLY THINKING
TAMMY'S CHANGED.
WE'LL BE HAPPY TOGETHER.
BUT YOU'RE ONLY
THINKING THAT
BECAUSE SHE'S
A MONSTROUS PARASITE
WHO ENTERED THROUGH
YOUR PRIVATES
AND LODGED HERSELF
IN YOUR BRAIN.
SO YOU HAVE TWO CHOICES--
ONE, GET RID OF TAMMY,
OR TWO, LOBOTOMY
AND CASTRATION.
CHOOSE WISELY.
YOU STUPID [bleep].
THIS IS A WASTE OF TIME.
YOU PEOPLE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- THAT WAS YOU ON THE TAPE.
THAT WAS YOU TALKING.
- RON? RON!
RON.
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
[chuckling]
AH!
- RON. STOP IT.
GOD, PLEASE.
RON, DON'T DO THAT.
- OH, IT'S DONE, LESLIE.
TAMMY AND I ARE IN LOVE,
AND WE'RE GONNA START A FAMILY
TOGETHER.
IN FACT, SHE'S OVULATING.
SO IF YOU'LL EXCUSE US,
WE'RE HEADING OFF
ON OUR HONEYMOON.
- WOW. WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- JERRY.
- WE'RE GONNA SPEND 11 DAYS
IN MY CABIN IN THE WOODS.
- WE BOUGHT
10 CASES OF GATORADE
AND A 40-POUND BAG
OF PEANUTS FOR ENERGY.
- OH, GOD.
- GIVE ME IT.
- ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
EXCUSE ME.
- OH, YEAH.
OH, GOD.
- ANN AND I ARE HEADED OUT,
AND I JUST
WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR EVERYTHING TODAY,
AND I WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
[knocking]
- HI, CHRIS.
UH, RON SWANSON
HAS SENT ME OVER
TO DELIVER TO YOU
THIS DOCUMENT.
- "TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN,
DEAR CHRIS,
"THERE IS AN EMERGENCY REGARDING
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT,
"AND APRIL MAY JUST BE
THE ONLY PERSON WHO CAN HELP.
"I CAN'T GET INTO DETAILS
BECAUSE IT'S SUPER-CLASSIFIED.
"PLEASE RELEASE APRIL
BACK TO US PERMANENTLY.
"GOD BLESS AMERICA.
LOVE, BERT MACKLIN, FBI."
- WHAT?
- OKAY. WELL, BYE.
- APRIL, LISTEN.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO
WORK FOR ME,
I'M NOT GONNA FORCE YOU.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
- SHE DIDN'T DO THAT.
THAT--THAT WAS--
DUDE, I THINK IT SOUNDS
LIKE IT WAS MACKLIN'S CALL.
- LOOK, I GET IT.
YOU'RE YOUNG,
AND TRYING ISN'T COOL.
BUT I THINK YOU'RE SMART.
I'M GONNA BE GOING BACK
TO INDIANAPOLIS SOON,
AND I THINK YOU SHOULD
COME WORK FOR ME.
- WOW, MOVE ALL THE WAY
TO INDIANAPOLIS,
SO I CAN PICK UP YOUR
VITAMINS AND SUPPLEMENTS.
- EVERYBODY
STARTS SOMEWHERE.
YOU'LL TRAVEL,
AND YOU WILL MEET
INTERESTING PEOPLE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
- OKAY. I WILL.
- APPARENTLY HE WANTS APRIL
TO MOVE TO INDIANAPOLIS
WITH HIM.
SO THAT'S SOMETHING.
[tapping]
- I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY.
- LOOK, I JUST WANTED TO
SHOW HIM WHAT IT FELT LIKE
TO HAVE YOUR EX-WIFE
DATE SOMEONE YOU KNOW.
WHATEVER HAPPENED AFTER THAT
IS NOT MY FAULT.
- YES, IT IS.
TOM, YOU DID
A REALLY CRAPPY THING,
AND I THINK DEEP DOWN,
YOU KNOW THAT.
WHATEVER HAPPENS
TO RON SWANSON IS ON YOU.
[knocking]
- EXCUSE ME, CHIEF.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
- HEY, CALZONE BOY,
WHAT'S UP?
- WELL, HERE'S HOPING THAT
THAT NICKNAME DOESN'T STICK.
RIGHT?
BUT THAT'S NOT
WHY I'M HERE.
UH, LESLIE KNOPE ASKED YOU
FOR A FAVOR THE OTHER DAY,
BUT THE REAL FAVOR WE NEED
IS MUCH BIGGER.
- YOU MEAN,
LIKE CALZONE-SIZED?
- AH! SURE.
WE NEED
THE PAWNEE POLICE FORCE
TO VOLUNTEER AS SECURITY
DURING THE UPCOMING
HARVEST FESTIVAL.
NOW, THE CITY WON'T LET US
THROW THE FESTIVAL UNLESS--
- SAY NO MORE.
JUST SEND ME A SCHEDULE OF HOW
MANY OFFICERS YOU NEED AND WHEN.
- REALLY?
JUST LIKE THAT?
- LESLIE KNOPE GETS
AS MANY FAVORS AS SHE NEEDS.
- CAN I ASK WHY?
- BECAUSE SHE'S
THE KIND OF A PERSON
WHO USES FAVORS
TO HELP OTHER PEOPLE.
AND ALSO, MY BUDDY DAVE
WAS THE CRANKIEST BASTARD
IN THE DEPARTMENT
TILL HE STARTED
DATING LESLIE.
- HUH. SO SHE...
OKAY.
ARE THEY STILL DATING OR--?
- NO. MOVED TO SAN DIEGO
A YEAR AGO.
- OH.
WAS IT A SERIOUS THING,
OR--?
- WHAT DO YOU CARE?
YOU A PERVERT?
- NOPE, NOPE.
I'M ALL GOOD.
UM, EVERYTHING'S FINE.
THIS IS FINE.
- DON'T THINK
I WON'T DO IT.
I'LL WEAR THIS TO WORK.
[laughter]
ALL RIGHT,
WE GOT A LITTLE ONE.
OOH, WHAT'S IN HERE, HUH?
[gasps]
A NEW LIBRARY CARD?
- READ THE NAME.
- "TAMMY SWANSON SWANSON."
[laughter]
YOU GUYS, THAT'S AMAZING.
- WELL, YOU ABOUT READY
TO GO, MY LOVE?
- YEAH.
- WAIT, RON!
STOP!
JERRY, WHAT THE HELL?
DON'T DO IT.
SHE DOESN'T LOVE YOU.
- YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- YES, I DO, OKAY?
WHEN I ASKED HER
TO BE MY DATE,
SHE CACKLED
FOR A FULL MINUTE
AND SAID, AND I QUOTE,
"ANYTHING TO MAKE RON
MISERABLE."
IT'S NOT REAL, MAN.
SHE'S JUST MESSING
WITH YOU.
- HE'S LYING, RON.
STAY OUT OF THIS, GLENN.
- IT'S TOM.
AND I'M NOT LYING.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU
DESTROY RON.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO--OW!
OW! AAH!
- OH!
HE'S ATTACKING ME, RON!
KILL HIM!
- [groans]
- [growls]
- [screams]
- [laughs]
YEAH!
DO YOUR WORST, GLENN!
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
- AAAAH!
- AAH!
[moans]
- WHY ARE YOU
HITTING YOURSELF, GLENN?
STOP HITTING YOURSELF.
- TAMMY, THAT'S ENOUGH!
- WHAT?
HEY, BABY.
- YOU ALMOST HAD ME.
AGAIN.
BUT SEEING YOU PICK
ON THIS PATHETIC,
DEFENSELESS LITTLE MAN...
- HEY.
- REMINDED ME WHAT KIND
OF A MONSTER YOU ARE.
- YOU'RE A JOKE.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
A MAN ANYMORE.
OH, AND BY THE WAY,
LAST NIGHT,
I FAKED FOUR
OUT OF THE SEVEN.
- HMM. SO DID I.
LET'S GO, SON.
- HEY.
SORRY ABOUT THE WHOLE MESS.
THE CRISIS
HAS BEEN AVERTED,
SO LET'S GO TALK
TO THE CHIEF.
- OH, I ALREADY
TALKED TO HIM.
THEY'LL GIVE US THE HOURS
WE NEED, NO PROBLEM.
- GREAT. WHAT A RELIEF.
- YEAH.
HEY, ARE YOU HUNGRY?
I HAVEN'T EATEN.
- YOU KNOW, YEAH.
THERE'S A REALLY GREAT
CALZONE PLACE
OVER IN IDIOTVILLE.
- OH, REALLY?
- DOWN ON TERRIBLE IDEA AVENUE.
- OKAY. THAT'S WEIRD.
'CAUSE I THOUGHT IT WAS ON
BEATING-A-DEAD-HORSE BOULEVARD.
- CALZONES ARE POINTLESS.
THEY'RE JUST PIZZA
THAT'S HARDER TO EAT.
NO ONE LIKES THEM.
GOOD DAY, SIR.
- LESLIE, I--
YOU KNOW, I--
- I'M JUST KIDDING.
LET'S GO.
- OH.
[laughs weakly]
OKAY. THAT WAS FUNNY.
- HIGH AND TIGHT.
- DO YOU THINK
IT'S GONNA LEAVE A SCAR?
- TOM, WOMEN LIKE SCARS.
SHOWS YOU SURVIVED
AN ATTACK,
AND THEY'LL ASSUME
THE ATTACK WAS FROM A MAN.
- SORRY, RON,
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
- AH.
TO TRUE LOVE.
MAY WE BOTH FIND IT.
- I'LL DRINK TO THAT.
NICE GLASSES.
- WEDDING PRESENT
FROM JERRY.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA
RETURN THEM?
- NAH.
TOO MUCH HASSLE.