- GIDDYUP, GIDDYUP!
- MEET LESLIE KNOPE.
- WHAP!
I AM THE PANTS QUEEN!
- LESLIE LOVES
WHIPPED CREAM,
DANCING WITH FRIENDS,
AND WORKING HARD
FOR THE PARKS DEPARTMENT
OF PAWNEE, INDIANA.
- CUT IT OUT, TOM.
- IT NEVER GETS OLD.
- SHE ALSO LOVES
HER COWORKERS
AT CITY HALL,
RON SWANSON...
TOM HAVERFORD...
[humming]
- TOMMY TIMBERLAKE.
- APRIL LUDGATE...
- MY MOM'S PUERTO RICAN.
THAT'S WHY I'M SO LIVELY
AND COLORFUL.
- AND ANDY DWYER.
- UH-OH.
[crash]
NAILED IT.
- APRIL AND ANDY
LIKE EACH OTHER.
BUT ANDY ACCIDENTALLY KISSED
HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND,
ANN PERKINS...
- OOH.
- APRIL LEFT.
- APRIL!
- AND HE HASN'T
SEEN HER SINCE.
IN THE MIDST
OF ALL THIS LOVE,
TWO BLACK HATS RODE
INTO TOWN...
- SCIENTISTS BELIEVE
THAT THE FIRST HUMAN BEING
WHO WILL LIVE 150 YEARS
HAS ALREADY BEEN BORN.
I BELIEVE I AM
THAT HUMAN BEING.
- AND THEY BROUGHT WITH THEM
SOME DISTURBING NEWS.
- EFFECTIVE TOMORROW MORNING,
THE ENTIRE GOVERNMENT
WILL BE SHUT DOWN
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
- WHAT WILL LESLIE
DO NEXT?
WILL APRIL AND ANDY
MAKE UP AND MAKE OUT?
FIND OUT THIS SEASON
ON PARKS AND RECREATION.
STARTING RIGHT NOW.
[horn beeps]
- RON...WE'RE BACK.
- BULLY.
- THE BANKRUPT GOVERNMENT
OF PAWNEE
HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN
ALL SUMMER,
SO IT'S BEEN THREE MONTHS
OF NO WORK,
NO MEETINGS, NO MEMOS,
NO LATE NIGHTS, NOTHING.
I WOULDN'T WISH IT
ON MY WORST ENEMY.
OH, ROUNDING UP THE TEAM.
SO EXCITING.
I HAVE GOOSEBUMPS.
FEEL.
- AND THAT'S WHY THEY CALL ME
PRINCE CHARMING.
'CAUSE I ALWAYS FIND
THE GLASS SLIPPER
FOR MY CINDERELLA.
- THESE ARE WAY TOO TIGHT.
- WELL, THE REAL CINDERELLA
DIDN'T HAVE HIPPO FEET.
- TOM, WE'RE BACK.
[claps]
- JEREMY!
SUCK IT!
BY THE WAY, I'VE BEEN
GIVING AWAY FREE SPORTS BRAS
TO THE GIRLS
AT HOT DOG ON A STICK.
- LOOK, WE CAN DANCE
ALL DAY,
BUT IT'S TIME
TO STEP UP.
ARE YOU BUYING
4,000 RUBBER NIPPLES FROM ME
OR NOT?
- DEE, YOU HAVE A VISITOR.
- WE BACK?
- WE'RE BACK.
- ALL RIGHT.
[birds chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
- JERRY.
- OH, MY GOSH.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
LESLIE.
- THE NIGHTMARE'S OVER, JERRY.
WE'RE GOING BACK TO WORK.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA NEED
THIS ANYMORE.
[splash]
COME ON!
- I CALLED SHOTGUN.
EVERYBODY HEARD ME.
[triumphant music]
*
- WELL...
I AM USUALLY NOT ONE
FOR SPEECHES.
SO GOOD-BYE.
- BREAK'S OVER, MOFOS.
OKAY, HERE'S THE SITUATION.
WE ARE OPERATING
ON A SHOESTRING BUDGET.
PARK SERVICES
HAVE BEEN SLASHED.
BUT WE ARE ALL STILL HERE.
AND WE HAVE A JOB
TO DO.
- MAKE THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST PIZZA.
- NO, MAKE THIS TOWN FUN
FOR THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVE HERE.
- FINE, BUT AFTER THAT,
THE PIZZA IS
OUR TOP PRIORITY.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
- WE'RE GETTING PIZZA?
- APRIL, HEY.
IT'S ME, ANDY.
DWYER.
UH, THIS IS, LIKE,
THE 200TH MESSAGE I'VE LEFT YOU
WITHOUT A RESPONSE.
SO...
IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO TELL ME SOMETHING,
I DO NOT KNOW
WHAT IT IS
BECAUSE YOU WON'T
CALL ME BACK.
- IT IS TRULY GREAT
TO SEE ALL OF YOU.
HUH?
IT'S GREAT NEWS.
OKAY, I HAVE TO RUN.
BEN.
- THE BAD NEWS,
WHICH...
I GET TO DELIVER,
IS THIS:
YOUR ONLY WORK
FOR THE TIME BEING
WILL BE EXISTING
PARK MAINTENANCE.
SO THAT JUST MEANS
THAT WE'RE
IN MAINTENANCE MODE!
- YEAH!
- JERRY.
- OKAY, SEE, I'VE SPENT
THE LAST FEW MONTHS
BRAINSTORMING,
AND I HAVE
SOME REALLY GREAT IDEAS,
AND I PUT THEM
IN MY IDEA BINDERS.
I MEAN, THEY'RE COLOR-CODED,
FOR GOD'S SAKE.
- OKAY, ACTUALLY, YEAH.
THERE IS--
THERE IS ONE THING
THAT YOU WILL BE DOING.
APPARENTLY,
IN INDIANA,
IF YOU DON'T PROVIDE
A BASKETBALL LEAGUE,
PEOPLE GET VERY UPSET.
AND, QUITE FRANKLY,
THROW THINGS AT YOU
AND CALL YOU NAMES.
LIKE TURD BOY.
I--WHATEVER.
POINT IS, I REINSTATED
YOUTH BASKETBALL.
- IT SAYS HERE YOU ONLY HAVE
MONEY FOR TWO TEAMS.
- YEAH, THEY'RE GONNA DEVELOP
A GREAT RIVALRY.
[whistle blows]
- UNDER MY TUTELAGE,
YOU WILL GROW
FROM BOYS INTO MEN.
FROM MEN INTO GLADIATORS.
AND FROM GLADIATORS
INTO SWANSONS.
BEHOLD.
THE SWANSON PYRAMID
OF GREATNESS.
I'VE BEEN DEVELOPING
THE SWANSON PYRAMID OF GREATNESS
FOR YEARS.
IT'S A PERFECTLY
CALIBRATED RECIPE
FOR MAXIMUM PERSONAL
ACHIEVEMENT.
CATEGORIES INCLUDE:
CAPITALISM, GOD'S WAY
OF DETERMINING
WHO IS SMART,
AND WHO IS POOR.
CRYING, ACCEPTABLE
AT FUNERALS
AND THE GRAND CANYON.
RAGE, POISE,
PROPERTY RIGHTS.
FISH, FOR SPORT ONLY.
NOT FOR MEAT.
FISH MEAT IS PRACTICALLY
A VEGETABLE.
HAIRCUTS.
THERE ARE THREE
ACCEPTABLE HAIRCUTS.
HIGH AND TIGHT,
CREW CUT,
BUZZ CUT.
ARE THE SCISSORS BROKEN
IN YOUR HOUSE, SON?
- SO YOU HAPPY
TO BE BACK AT WORK?
- WELL, OUR BUDGET'S
BEEN SLASHED TO ZERO.
I TRIED TO BUY FERTILIZER
THE OTHER DAY
FOR THE SOCCER FIELD.
REQUEST DENIED.
WE LITERALLY CAN'T BUY
[bleep].
- OH, I'M SO SORRY.
- NO, I MEAN, LOOK.
WHEN WE WERE KIDS,
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT
WOULD DO THESE BIG PROJECTS.
WINTER JAMBOREE,
THE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
IT'S LIKE THEY DON'T HAVE FAITH
IN US ANYMORE.
I'M NOT A PAPER-PUSHER,
ANN.
I NEED TO BE OUT
IN THE STREETS,
PLANTING TREES
AND CRACKING SKULLS.
- LESLIE KNOPE.
ANN PERKINS.
HOW ARE MY TWO FAVORITE PEOPLE
IN THIS ENTIRE TOWN?
- NOT GOOD, CHRIS.
THERE'S A WHOLE LINE OF PEOPLE
IN MY OFFICE
COMPLAINING THAT
ALL THEIR PROGRAMS
HAVE BEEN SLASHED.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT THAT?
- NO.
- DAMN, SORRY, LESLIE.
ANN, COULD I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
- SO HOW'S IT GOING?
- SAVE IT, OKAY?
I KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE
FAITH IN ME
AND MY DEPARTMENT,
AND THAT'S FINE.
BUT DON'T EXPECT ME
TO SIT HERE
AND CHIT-CHAT WITH YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, FAIR ENOUGH.
- GO THE OTHER WAY.
- BUT I'M JUST GOING
TO THAT--
ALL RIGHT, UH--
- LOOK, I'M VERY FLATTERED.
BUT AGAIN,
I DON'T THINK
I SHOULD GO OUT
WITH YOU.
- CAN I ASK YOU
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
WE HAD A GREAT TIME
THE NIGHT YOU GOT DRUNK
AND KISSED ME.
AND YOU DID USE
YOUR TONGUE.
- I JUST DON'T THINK
I'M IN A PLACE
TO GO OUT WITH ANYONE
RIGHT NOW.
- OKAY, WELL,
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND,
YOU KNOW WHERE
TO FIND ME, ANN PERKINS.
LESLIE KNOPE.
- YES.
DID HE ASK YOU OUT AGAIN?
- HE DID, HE DID.
HE IS NOTHING
IF NOT PERSISTENT.
AND HOT.
HE'S VER--
HE'S PRETTY HOT.
YEAH, HE'S HOT.
BUT HE'S INTENSE.
BUT HE'S REALLY,
REALLY HOT.
BUT HE'S YOUR BOSS.
- OH, MY GOD,
I JUST THOUGHT OF AN IDEA
OF HOW WE CAN SAVE
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT.
- GREAT.
- LET ME ASK YOU
ONE QUESTION.
WOULD YOU BE COOL
DOING THINGS
THAT A PROSTITUTE DOES?
- UH...
- MINUS THE MONEY.
- DEFINITELY YES, THEN.
- THANKS, ANN.
- LOOKING SHARP.
BEAUTIFUL.
THE BACKBOARD
IS YOUR FRIEND.
[roaring]
- AAAA, BAM!
BOOM!
I'D SAY MY COACHING STYLE
IS CENTERED
AROUND FUNDAMENTALS,
WITH AN EMPHASIS
ON FUN.
HEY, WATCH THIS.
GO GET IT!
AND A SECOND EMPHASIS
ON MENTAL.
YEAH, IT CAN BE
HARD WORK,
BUT EVERY TIME I LOOK
ONE OF THESE KIDS
IN THE EYES
AND HE CALLS ME COACH...
THAT'S HOW I KNOW
I AGREED TO BE A COACH.
- MOUSE RAT!
- CARNAGE!
- OKAY, GENTLEMEN,
IT'S TIME
FOR THE PREGAME
COIN TOSS.
- THERE'S NO COIN TOSS
IN BASKETBALL.
ARE THOSE WOMEN'S SNEAKERS?
- YES, THEY ARE, RON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY FIT BETTER.
I GOT AN EMPLOYEE DISCOUNT.
AND THE BEST PART IS,
NO ONE CAN TELL.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO THIS.
MATCH POINT,
TOUCHDOWN, ET CETERA.
[whistle blows]
- YEAH, GO MY TEAM.
ALL RIGHT.
- OKAY, I LIKE
WHAT YOU'RE WEARING,
BUT I NEED IT TO BE
300% SEXIER.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
OF THOSE SHIRTS
THAT LOOK WET
ALL THE TIME?
OR--OR, LIKE,
A METAL BIKINI?
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT'S
ALWAYS SEXY?
FINGERLESS GLOVES.
- WHAT ABOUT IF I WEAR
THIS NORMAL, SANE OUTFIT?
- YEAH, OKAY,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO EAT
SOMETHING SEXY, THEN,
LIKE A BANANA.
- FOR DINNER?
- WELL, WHAT'S SEXY FOOD?
ASPARAGUS?
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT'S SEXY?
TURKEY CHILI.
- MMM.
- YUM.
- AND HOW, EXACTLY,
AM I SUPPOSED TO CASUALLY STEER
THE CONVERSATION
TOWARDS THE PARKS
DEPARTMENT BUDGET?
- OKAY, IT'S TOTALLY EASY.
TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU BE CHRIS.
I'LL BE YOU.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
- OKAY.
[clears throat]
- ANN PERKINS.
YOU ARE WONDERFUL
AND AMAZING,
AND I'M HAPPY
TO BE HERE WITH YOU.
- THANK YOU, CHRIS.
I'M WEARING A TUXEDO VEST
WITH NO SHIRT ON
UNDERNEATH.
UH-OH.
- CAN I GET YOU A DRINK?
I LOVE EVERY SINGLE BEVERAGE
IN THE WORLD.
- I WOULD LIKE SOME WINE.
AND, OOPS,
MY VEST POPPED OPEN.
JUST LIKE THE BUDGET
NEEDS TO POP OPEN,
AND YOU NEED TO POUR IT
INTO MY PARKS DEPARTMENT.
- GREAT.
- I AM SO EXCITED
THAT YOU FINALLY AGREED
TO GO OUT WITH ME.
WHAT A MAGNIFICENT
FLIP-FLOP.
- YOU'RE A MAGNIFICENT
ASKER-OUTER.
- TELL ME EVERY SINGLE DETAIL
OF YOUR DAY.
I LOVE DATES.
I LOVE CONNECTING
WITH SOMEONE.
I LOVE ENGAGING THEM.
I LOVE BEING SURPRISED
BY THEM.
I HAVE NEVER HAD
A BAD DATE.
THEY'VE ALL BEEN EITHER GREAT
OR PHENOMENALLY GREAT.
NURSES ARE THE MOST
UNDERVALUED MEMBERS
OF OUR SOCIETY BY FAR.
I THINK ALL OF YOU
SHOULD MAKE AS MUCH MONEY
AS THE CEO OF GOOGLE.
- WOW, THANK YOU.
I AGREE.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- WHY AM I SO POSITIVE
ALL THE TIME?
- YES, THAT'S EXACTLY
THE QUESTION.
- I WAS BORN
WITH A BLOOD DISORDER.
AND MY PARENTS WERE TOLD
THAT I HAD THREE WEEKS
TO LIVE.
AND HERE I STILL AM,
SOME 2,000-ODD WEEKS LATER.
AND I HAVE ENJOYED
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
- I THINK IT'S GOING WELL.
HE'S ACTUALLY
A REALLY NICE GUY.
[Leslie on phone]
- YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
OKAY, SO HAVE YOU ASKED HIM
YET ABOUT THE MONEY?
- WELL, IT'S A DATE,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S KIND OF HARD
TO CASUALLY BRING UP
THE PARKS BUDGET
WHEN YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT YOUR FAVORITE MOVIES.
- JURASSIC PARK,
PARKS ARE SO GREAT,
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT
NEEDS MONEY.
I JUST DID IT
IN THREE MOVES.
- WELL, THEN, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST COME HERE
AND DO IT YOURSELF?
- OKAY.
- HOLY CRAP.
- WHAT? CHRIS AND ANN?
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
- WE ARE ON A DATE.
AND IT IS GOING
PHENOMENALLY.
- THANKS, BUT I'LL STAY
FOR JUST ONE DRINK.
I'M SO HAPPY
I RAN INTO YOU
BECAUSE I WANTED
TO SPEAK TO YOU--
- WELL, WELL, WELL.
- BEN.
WHAT A FUN SURPRISE.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU WERE COMING HERE TONIGHT
ON A DATE.
AND, HEY,
LESLIE IS JOINING YOU
ON THIS WONDERFULLY
ROMANTIC OCCASION.
HOW 'BOUT THAT?
- FANTASTIC.
- IT IS.
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
- SURE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I'M JUST CONFIRMING
A SUSPICION I HAD, LESLIE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH THIS DATE.
- UH-HUH.
- THEY'RE BOTH SO BEAUTIFUL.
THEY PROBABLY JUST WANT
TO SEE EACH OTHER NAKED.
- OKAY, WELL, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO.
AND YOU'RE NOT THAT GOOD
AT BEING SNEAKY.
- YES, I AM.
- NO, YOU'RE NOT.
- I'M GREAT AT BEING SNEAKY.
- CLEARLY YOU'RE NOT.
- HEY, YOU GUYS.
LET'S ALL HAVE DINNER
TOGETHER.
THE MORE THE MERRIER.
- GREAT.
- GOOD JOB, GUYS.
YEP.
ALL RIGHT, ERIC,
TAKING A REST,
OR ARE YOU HURT?
TAKING A REST?
SMART.
- DESTROY THEM, GENTLEMEN.
FEEL NO SYMPATHY.
- YES, RON SWANSON IS DATING
MY EX-WIFE, WENDY.
BIG DEAL.
MY GIRLFRIEND, LUCY,
IS THE SEXIEST WOMAN
IN TOWN.
SHE'S CUBAN,
SHE'S GOT TATTOOS,
AND SHE'S INTO ME,
WHICH, AS FAR AS
I'M CONCERNED,
IS THE SEXIEST QUALITY
A WOMAN CAN HAVE.
- OH, I HAVE AN IDEA.
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE
REALLY FUN AFTER DINNER?
WE SHOULD TAKE A WALK
BY THE POND IN RAMSETT PARK.
- WALKING IN PARKS CAN BE
VERY ROMANTIC.
- YEAH, TOO BAD THE PARK'S
ALWAYS CLOSED, THOUGH.
- OKAY, WELL,
YOU TWO ARE ON A DATE.
SO LESLIE AND I
SHOULD PROBABLY GET GOING.
- UH, WELL, I'M ACTUALLY
HAVING A GOOD TIME
WITH EVERYONE.
CHRIS?
- OH, ME, TOO.
I'M HAVING A FANTASTIC TIME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE TAKE
THIS WHOLE
DATE-PLUS-TWO-
OTHER-PEOPLE THING
UP INTO THE STRATOSPHERE?
- * DON'T STOP
MAKE IT POP *
* DEEJAY BLOW MY SPEAKERS UP
* TONIGHT I'MA FIGHT
* TILL WE SEE THE SUNLIGHT *
- THIS PLACE IS OUTSTANDING.
GREAT CALL, LESLIE KNOPE.
- THANKS.
- LOOK, EVEN BEN'S DANCING.
- THAT'S THE WAY
TO SHOOT THE BALL, CHIGNOLI.
HUSTLE BACK.
[clapping]
[blows whistle]
- UH...
IT'S A FOUL.
- WHAT?
ON WHOM?
- YOUR TEAM.
NUMBER 50.
HE WAS DOUBLE DRIBBLING.
- HE'S ON DEFENSE.
- EXACTLY.
IT'S A TECHNICAL DIFFICULTY,
SO THAT MEANS
ANDY'S TEAM THROWS
THE BALL
FROM THE STRIPEY THING.
LET'S GO.
- THE STRIPEY THING?
[hip-hop music]
*
- HEY, THERE.
HOW'S IT GOING?
- GREAT, THANKS.
- CAN I BUY YOU
A DRINK?
- OH, I'M VERY FLATTERED,
BUT THIS IS MY
STUNNINGLY GORGEOUS DATE,
ANN PERKINS.
- OH, HI.
- HI.
- SORRY.
- OH, NO PROBLEM.
IN FACT, LET ME BUY
ALL OF YOU A DRINK
FOR BEING
SO WELCOMING TODAY.
WAITER.
- I THINK I MAY
ACTUALLY LIKE CHRIS.
- ON THE HOUSE, LESLIE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
I'M SORT OF A GAY HERO.
LAST YEAR, I MARRIED
TWO PENGUINS AT THE ZOO,
AND IT TURNED OUT
THEY WERE BOTH GAY.
- PENGUIN WEDDING.
- MM-HMM.
- THAT'S CUTE.
- IT WAS SO CUTE.
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT HOW
CUTE IT WAS.
WHY DON'T YOU THINK
I SHOULD HAVE THE MONEY?
- GOOD LORD, REALLY?
LOOK.
WHEN I WAS 18,
AND I BECAME MAYOR
OF MY HOMETOWN,
I USED EVERY
LAST DOLLAR WE HAD
TO OPEN A GIANT
WINTER SPORTS COMPLEX.
CALLED IT ICETOWN.
- AND IT TURNED OUT GREAT,
AND EVERYONE LOVED IT.
- UH, YEAH, KINDA.
IT WAS NEVER COMPLETED,
AND I GOT IMPEACHED.
NEWSPAPER HEADLINE WAS,
"ICETOWN COSTS ICE CLOWN
HIS TOWN CROWN."
- YUCK.
- THEY WERE BIG INTO RHYMES.
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK ICETOWN
SOUNDS GREAT.
AND THE POINT IS,
AT LEAST YOU TRIED
SOMETHING.
[whistle blows]
- FOUL!
[blows again]
FOUL ON NUMBER THREE
FOR TAKING A NUMBER TWO
ON NUMBER FOUR.
[Andy laughing]
[blows whistle]
ROUGHING THE PASSER.
DOUBLE DRIBBLING.
THAT'S A FOUL.
THAT'S A FOUL FOR TOUCHING
THE BASKETBALL.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT IT?
NOTHING.
YOU FOULED.
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
OKAY.
YOU'RE EJECTED.
[whistle blowing]
OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER
THERE, RON?
NO PLAYERS LEFT?
YAY, ANDY'S TEAM!
LOOK AT 'EM GO!
- COME ON.
NOW YOU'RE OPENLY
CHEERING FOR THE OTHER TEAM?
PUT MY BOYS BACK IN.
- YOU MADE ME THE REF.
DEAL WITH IT.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
TAKE THIS UNIFORM OFF.
- HEY, HEY.
- YOU DON'T DESERVE TO WEAR IT.
[whistle blowing]
- RON'S EJECTED
FOR MOLESTING THE REF.
- OH, YEAH?
I'M EJECTED?
- YES, YOU ARE.
- TOM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M EJECTING YOU.
YOU'RE EJECTED, TOO.
EVERYONE'S EJECTED.
- OH, YEAH?
SHE'S EJECTED?
- YEAH.
- RRRRAAAAGH!
- GO AHEAD, GO.
WELL, THAT'S A FORFEIT.
ANDY'S TEAM WINS.
- NO WAY!
WE WON!
OH, MAN!
EAT IT!
HA, HA, HA, HA!
[all chanting]
ANDY, ANDY, ANDY!
YEAH!
AH-HA-HA!
YES!
I DEDICATE THIS VICTORY
TO APRIL LUDGATE.
IT FEELS GOOD.
AND IT FEELS STICKY.
FROM THE GATORADE.
- WE'RE BARELY ABLE
TO FUNCTION.
WE COULD REALLY USE
THAT MONEY.
- BUT YOU KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
I'M IN SUCH A GOOD MOOD,
OR BECAUSE OF THE CHARMING
ANN PERKINS,
BUT I AM GOING
TO SERIOUSLY CONSIDER THAT.
- REALLY?
THAT'S GREAT.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
LET'S BOOGIE.
- MISSION ACCOMPLISHED?
- UH-OH.
- YEAH.
THERE'S A MISSION, UH,
THAT ANN HAD THOUGHT OF.
IT WAS BOTH
OF OUR IDEAS,
BUT IT WAS MOSTLY ANN'S.
WE...
I HAD MENTIONED TO ANN
THAT IT WOULD BE FUN
IF YOU TWO WENT
ON A DATE.
SO THEN...
YOU COULD, UH,
TALK ABOUT THE MONEY
AND THEN, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE GIVE IT TO ME.
- WOW.
I'VE JUST HAD
MY FIRST BAD DATE.
[sadly]
ANN PERKINS.
- NOT THAT SNEAKY.
- APRIL!
APRIL.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
OH, MY GOD.
- HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
- I'M OKAY.
I'M DYING TO SEE YOU.
I CALLED AND TEXTED YOU,
LIKE, A BILLION TIMES.
- OH, I'M SORRY.
I WAS IN VENEZUELA.
- OH, REALLY?
WOW.
[British accent]
ACROSS THE POND.
WOW.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
I WOULDA HEARD FROM YOU
AT LEAST ONCE
BECAUSE OF WHAT HAPPENED.
ANN KISSING ME?
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT THAT.
IT WAS SO STUPID,
AND IT MEANT NOTHING.
- I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S TOTALLY FINE.
HEY.
THIS IS MY BOYFRIEND, EDUARDO.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
- ¿LISTO PARA LONCHE?
- SI.
- THAT MEANS WE'RE GOING
TO LUNCH.
- HOW DO YOU SAY
HAVE A GREAT TIME,
DON'T CHOKE ON ANYTHING?
- BYE.
- LESLIE ASKED ME
TO DO HER A FAVOR,
AND I LOVE HER,
SO I DID IT.
I'M SORRY, AND I'M HERE
TO EAT CROW.
I LIKE YOU A LOT.
LET'S GO OUT AGAIN.
- ANN PERKINS.
- BUDGET SOLUTION NUMBER 28.
USE GRAZING SHEEP
TO MOW GRASS IN PARKS.
NOTE: TIRED SHEEP
COULD BECOME FOOD
OR SWEATERS.
[groans]
- WELL, I GOT MY ANSWER.
ABOUT APRIL.
SHE HATES ME.
YEAH.
AND SHE GOT A BOYFRIEND,
I GUESS,
FROM SOME CITY
IN MEXICO.
SO...
WHAT DO I DO?
- OKAY.
WELL, WHEN YOUR BACK'S
AGAINST THE WALL
AND ODDS ARE STACKED
AGAINST YOU,
YOU JUST--
YOU--
YOU SWING THE HARDEST,
DAMN IT.
YOU GO BIG,
OR YOU GO HOME.
AND YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE
THE KIND OF GUY WHO GOES HOME.
- I'M NOT.
I DON'T EVEN REALLY
HAVE A HOME.
- GO GET HER, ANDY!
- OKAY.
OKAY, THANKS, LESLIE!
- OKAY, SO WE KNOW THE PEOPLE
WHO RUN THIS GOVERNMENT
HAVE NO FAITH IN US.
MY PLAN IS GONNA CHANGE THAT
AND BRING THE BUDGET BACK.
AND THE ANSWER'S BEEN
RIGHT IN FRONT OF US
THE WHOLE TIME.
- EW, CHECK YOUR TESTICLES?
- NO, NOT THAT.
ALTHOUGH THAT IS
VERY GOOD ADVICE.
I'M LOOKING AT YOU,
JERRY.
NO, WHAT'S GONNA SAVE US
IS RIGHT THERE.
GENTLEMEN, I REALIZE
THAT TIMES ARE TOUGH,
AND THE BUDGET IS TIGHT.
BUT IF THE PEOPLE OF THIS TOWN
HAVE NOTHING ELSE TO DO
BUT SIT IN THEIR HOUSES
AND PLAY VIDEO GAMES,
THEN PAWNEE WILL DIE.
AND WE REFUSE
TO LET THAT HAPPEN.
[whispering]
NOW.
THIS TOWN WAS HISTORICALLY
KNOWN FOR TWO THINGS.
[Chariots of Fire Theme
playing]
WIDESPREAD OBESITY
AND THE ANNUAL
PAWNEE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
PEOPLE FROM ALL OVER INDIANA
WOULD COME
AND GAZE IN WONDERMENT
AT HOW FAT
OUR CITIZENS WERE.
AND WHILE THEY WERE HERE,
THEY WOULD ALSO ATTEND
THE FESTIVAL.
A FULL WEEK
OF CORN MAZES,
HAYRIDES, FERRIS WHEELS,
PUMPKINS THE SIZE
OF JEEPS.
WE LOST THAT FESTIVAL
A FEW YEARS AGO,
DUE TO ANOTHER ROUND
OF BUDGET CUTS.
AND I PROPOSE
WE BRING THE FESTIVAL BACK.
WITH TICKET SALES
AND CORPORATE SPONSORSHIP,
WE'LL EARN ALL
THAT MONEY BACK.
AND BELIEVE ME,
PEOPLE WILL COME.
- WHAT IF THEY DON'T?
- WELL...
THEN YOU ELIMINATE
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT.
- AND YOU GUYS ARE ALL
ON BOARD WITH THIS.
- AYE.
- YES.
- LOOK, WE'RE NOT
JUST PENCIL PUSHERS.
WE ARE A REFLECTION
OF THE COMMUNITY.
AND WE BELIEVE THAT WE CAN
STRENGTHEN THAT COMMUNITY.
BECAUSE IN THE END,
THE REASON WHY
WE'RE ALL HERE
IS TO BRING PEOPLE TOGETHER.
*
- THAT...
LITERALLY...
IS THE MOST MOVING THING
I'VE EVER HEARD.
AND A GOOD IDEA.
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
- EXCELLENT.
GREAT, OKAY, SO EVERYBODY,
WE'RE GONNA PARTY HARD
FOR 15 MINUTES.
THEN WE'RE GONNA HAVE
OUR FIRST BRAINSTORMING SESSION.
- HELLO, APRIL.
DO YOU LIKE THE FLOWERS?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ALL DUE RESPECT, EDUARDO.
YOU SEEM LIKE
A GREAT GUY.
BUT I LIKE APRIL,
AND I'M COMING AFTER HER
WITH EVERYTHING I'VE GOT.
SO DO YOU WANT
TO GO OUT WITH ME?
- NO.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA
SAY YES,
BUT THAT'S OKAY.
BECAUSE I'LL BE BACK TOMORROW
TO ASK YOU AGAIN.
AND AGAIN THE NEXT DAY.
AND THE NEXT DAY.
NOT FRIDAY.
I HAVE TO GO VISIT
MY COUSIN.
BUT I WILL BE BACK
AFTER THAT
TO ASK YOU AGAIN.
- [speaking Spanish]
AH! YOU SHOULD DO IT.
UH, FOLLOW YOU DREAM.
- OH, MY GOD.
REALLY?
THAT'S AWESOME.
[laughs]
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com