CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme song plays)
D-ohh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
( Get Smart theme playing)
Eh!
(floor creaking)
Okay, Mother’s Day
gift check.
Let’s see what you got.
I picked Mom a bouquet
of Erigeron elatiors.
Daisies.
Flowers.
Hmm?
Oh, flow... yeah.
Lis, your stupid present
will only last a week.
Mine will sit in a closet
for years.
Bart, we made her
the same thing.
Aw, this is even worse
than you think.
Look.
Kids, we’re going
Mother’s Day shopping.
I’m glad this holiday
only comes every four years.
Let’s see,
what would she like?
Twenty on the trifecta?
Her wedding china back?
(gasps)
I could get Marge
a new window
just like this one.
Hey, Dad, why don’t we try
the Sprawl-Mart?
Yeah, I love Sprawl-Mart.
They’ve got everything.
Even Christian videos
with talking vegetables.
Mighty Yamses,
we are weary of building
your food pyramid.
Let my pickles go!
Mm, Moses.
(drooling)
Welcome to Sprawl-Mart.
Grandpa?
You have a job?
How dare you challenge
my perceptions
of what old people
can do.
I’m a greeter.
I’m here to make
every visit special.
And to size up
potential shoplifters.
Like I can’t shoplift
with my mouth.
(muffled):
Haw, haw.
Wow, look at
all this stuff.
Oh, look, Jaclyn Smith has
her own line of axe heads.
Yeah,
it’s impressive,
but I still haven’t found
the perfect gift for Marge.
Only imperfect stuff for me.
Hey, look,
it’s Hairy Ass Tubman.
(both laughing)
Well, well, if it isn’t
Fatty and Smell-Ma.
Your names can’t hurt us.
(grunts)
Oh.
Aunts Patty and Selma,
can you help us pick out
a Mother’s Day gift?
You can give her
one of these.
The Kitchen Carnival.
We got one
when we appeared
on an episode
of The Price is Right,
which the network
refused to air.
Apparently, we’re not
"TV pretty."
Wow, it’s a machine
that makes carnival food
at home.
"Endorsed by the American
Carny Association."
Wow.
I never thought
I’d say this,
but you slags
are all right.
All this attention.
I feel like a secretary
on Administrative
Professionals' Day.
Marge, you’re going to
love my present.
It is so thoughtful,
it makes the kids’ gifts
look like crap.
(both groaning)
"Kitchen Carnival"?
I love it!
Thank you, Homie.
Oh, Marge,
get a room.
(humming tune)
(carnival music playing)
Only my hairdresser
knows for sure.
Hmm, dare I pour caramel
over the cotton candy?
(insane laughter)
(thunder crashes)
(insane laughter continues)
I’m going to pour caramel
on my clothes,
and then finally
I can eat my shorts.
(both scream)
What is that?!
This is 85 pounds
of tooth-melting sugar.
Dig in.
(noisy chewing)
That’s it, kids.
Suckle Daddy’s
sugar ball.
♪♪
Chief, that guys shouldn’t be
in the carpool lane.
His passenger is just
a big piece of candy.
I wish mine was.
-What?
-Nothing.
Homer, are you
spooning that snack?
That’s my old lady.
(snoring)
Huh?
Ants!
(birds chirping)
Birds!
(cat meowing)
Cats!
Flanderses!
(sobbing)
I was saving sugar
for my wedding night.
Homie, it’s time
you got rid of that thing.
All the candy
is rotting your brain.
I think you should
get rid of her.
Then we can be together...
forever!
Maybe you’re right,
Marge.
Or maybe you’re right,
candy ball.
No, Marge.
Hmm, then again...
Definitely Marge.
Good-bye, old friend.
I’ll think of you whenever
I have a stroke
or a heart attack.
(grunting)
POW!
(growling)
Oh, my God,
I’m gonna be killed by a bear.
Well, I guess I don’t
have to worry anymore
about the dangers of smoking.
Smooth.
-(whimpering)
-(roaring)
Homie!
What happened to you?!
Marge, please.
I’m too upset
to talk about it.
But seeing you like this
is more than I can bear.
Bear?!
(screaming)
BROCKMAN:
The angry president woke up,
crawled out of his grave
and went back to work.
(chicken clucking)
That sound can mean
only one thing--
it’s time for another
installment of "Kent’s
Cowards."
Today’s clip comes straight
from the Springfield dump.
(snarling)
Dad, you got attacked
by a bear?
I did a lot of stuff today.
I went to Starbucks,
but you didn’t see that
on tape.
(whimpering)
(crying)
(sobbing)
Ah.
(whimpering)
(chuckling)
That hilarious footage
was shot by
local hunter
Grant Conner--
not with a gun,
but with a camera.
That’s right, Kent.
I often get guns
and cameras confused.
One time, tragically,
at a wedding...
I don’t care if they think
you’re a coward, Dad.
You did the right thing,
hiding and crying.
Yeah, we’d rather have
a live sissy
mincing around the house
than some dead hero any day.
Choke on your candor!
-(grunting)
-(choking)
You can strangle Bart,
but you can’t strangle
your humiliation.
It’s a deal.
-(grunting)
-(choking)
Hey, Simpson,
I heard your dad’s afraid
of a little old
giant grizzly bear.
The only thing my dad’s
afraid of
is paying child support.
My dad once beat up
six employees at KFC,
and he’d been up
for three days.
SMITHERS:
Homer Simpson,
report to Mr. Burns’ office
immediately.
(screams)
(whimpering)
(all laughing)
What a delightful
practically-based joke.
Hello?
Anyone home?
Marge? Maggie?
(screaming)
The Bear Went Over
the Mountain?!
The Berenstain Bears?!
Ah, Goldilocks.
And Three Bears?!
Oh, God,
they’re in our food.
Teddy Grahams, Gummi Bears.
("Teddy Bear’s Picnic"
playing)
Are you a Care Bear?
I’m an intensive care bear.
Why does a bear
need a crowbar?
I don’t like
to get my hands dirty.
-("Mexican Hat Dance" playing)
-(screams)
(bears growling)
(sobbing)
Crying in the corner,
huh?
Mind if I join you?
No, go ahead.
(sobbing)
(both sobbing)
All right, that’s enough,
Fraidy Sue.
Here’s what
you got to do:
Find that bear
that whupped you,
and whup him back.
Can I fight
human-style?
By slowly poisoning
his environment
until he loses his fur
and becomes sterile?
You cowardly Swede.
You face that bear
like a man,
or I’ll never speak
to you again.
But how will I find out
what you had for lunch
in 1928?
I have a web site.
Welcome to my home page.
Why don’t you visit
more often?
Mr. Simpson,
if you want to
find that bear
that attacked you,
use this.
It tracks an electronic tag
I stuck in the bear’s ear.
It’s the same technology
they use to keep tabs
on Gary Busey.
Finally, science has joined
forces with revenge.
Now, listen, the bull grizzly
is seven feet tall,
weighs more than
a Mazda Miata
and can tear
through a tree
like a Jewish mother
through self-esteem.
Next time you face him,
you better have some way
to protect yourself.
♪ It’s the eye
of the tiger ♪
♪ It’s the thrill
of the fight ♪
♪ Risin’ up to the challenge
of our rival... ♪
Looking good.
And I did it all without
wasting money
on one of those stupid
welder’s masks.
(sizzling)
Behold! The ultimate
in anti-bear technolgy:
The Bear Buster 5000.
Available wherever
fat men dream.
(fanfare music)
Oh, dear Lord.
Check it out, ladies.
A suit that makes me
completely invulnerable
to bear attack.
-(gasps)
-(laughs)
Homer, there’s no rear
on that thing.
I know. If I get really scared,
I don’t want to ruin the suit.
Now look here, Mister,
I forbid you to fight a bear.
What kind of example
would I be
if I didn’t take revenge
on things?
Dad, you can’t take
revenge on an animal.
That’s the whole point
of Moby Dick.
Lisa, the point
of Moby Dick
is "be yourself."
You’re not going,
and that’s final.
(sputtering)
Fine.
But do you know how
ridiculous you look right now?
(clanking)
Marge, are you awake?
Marge?
(chuckles)
(grunting)
(loud clanking)
(door creaking)
Hmm?
(chuckling)
Marge is sure going
to be steamed
-when she finds you missing.
-Or dead.
Gentlemen, sometimes a man
must put his marriage at risk
for reasons that are
confusing even to him.
You’re sneaking out
to fight that bear.
I want to go, too.
No way.
If something
happens to me,
you have to carry on
the Simpson name.
Screw that.
When I grow up,
I’m legally changing
my name to Joe Kickass.
That is so cool.
All right, you can come.
Lisa, I think
your father just left.
And Bart’s missing,
too.
I’ve got a bad feeling
about this.
Let’s check
the suit closet.
Suit, suit, astronaut outfit,
Southern Belle,
Renaissance dandy,
Country-western octopus...
(gasps)
It’s gone.
That man
and his foolish pride.
We’ve got to go
follow him.
(grunts)
I just wanted to see
what it was like.
(Southern accent):
Howdy, y’all.
If you don’t like my song,
I’ll spray you with ink.
(chuckles)
Wow, I never realized
how hot this suit is.
I’m sweating out
all my blood lust.
Why don’t you take
a bath in the river?
This bear tracker stopped
beeping a half hour ago.
Suh-weet.
Hey, the batteries
are missing from this thing.
Yeah, we borrowed them
for the radio.
♪ Skyrockets in flight ♪
♪ Afternoon delight... ♪
Rub-a-dub-dub,
I’m washing the blub.
(roaring)
Oh, my God!
Lenny! Carl! Bart!
♪ Rubbing sticks and stones
together makes
the sparks ignite ♪
(Homer screaming)
♪ And the thought of loving
you is getting so exciting ♪
♪ Skyrockets in flight... ♪
Mr. Connor, thank you
for helping find my husband.
I don’t want my last words
to him to be,
"Clip your toenails.
They look like Fritos."
Mom! Mom!
Stop the car!
Dad went to take a bath,
and the bear carried him off!
Yeah, it almost wrecked
the whole trip.
Ma’am, I will find
your husband
before that bear kills him.
But first, a snack.
(roaring)
I guess this is it.
If I’m gonna die,
I’m gonna die a man.
(loud roaring)
-(electronic zapping)
-(groaning roars)
(whimpering)
Is this thing
hurting you?
Hm.
-(electronic zapping)
-Yow!
(screaming hysterically)
(yelling incoherently)
(panting)
Okay,
it’s probably the tag.
But just to be sure...
-(electronic zapping)
-Ow! Aah!
(continues screaming
hysterically)
Hey, you’re not mean.
It was just this tag
that made you go ape-scat.
We’re not so different.
Give me a hug.
(chuckles)
Geez! I don’t know why bear hugs
enjoy such a great reputation.
SONNY & CHER:
♪ I guess that’s so,
we don’t have a pot ♪
♪ But at least I’m sure ♪
-(growls)
-♪ Of all the things ♪
♪ We got ♪
♪ Babe ♪
-(giggling)
-♪ I got you, babe ♪
(grunts)
-♪ I got you, babe... ♪
-(laughing)
That’s... that’s funny.
(gunshot ricochets)
Oh, no.
The hunter has become
the hunter.
He must be
following this thing.
Well, I’m going to make sure
it never harms
another living creature.
(grunts)
(electronic zapping)
NEWSMAN (over radio):
A killer bear is on the loose
in Springfield Forest,
and local laughingstock
Homer Simpson
is missing and presumed mauled.
(chuckles):
Wrong again, liberal media.
A bounty has been placed
on the rogue bear
in the amount of $10,000.
Don’t worry,
I’ll find you someplace safe.
The bear’s no
longer wearing his
tracking device.
And it looks like
he’s headed toward that...
(mocking):
wildlife sanctuary.
Is there any sign
of my husband?
Hmm, your husband appears
to be traveling with the bear,
either as hostage
or as what we call
a "forest bride."
Ew!
Okay, you want to go
over there.
(neon sign buzzing)
Wait. Hold on.
Something
doesn’t feel right.
(groaning)
Wait. Stop.
I know bullets
can be scary sometimes,
but I have an idea.
First,
we pull off all your fur.
(loud roaring)
All right, all right,
I’m still thinking.
(gasps):
They’re looking
for a male bear, right?
(growls)
Oh. It’s so easy to condemn,
so hard to create.
Okay, boys, that bear’s going
to make a dash for freedom,
unless we take him down.
Yeah, all the way down.
What you said
didn’t really add much.
I know.
I just wanted to belong.
Well, we all feel that way
sometimes.
(all racking slides)
(metal clanking)
It’s Homer! Don’t shoot!
(quietly):
Go. Go.
It’s that bear!
Aim for the holes
in the colander!
He made it!
He’s finally
protected from man.
Yeah, but now he’s being
attacked by an elephant.
(trumpeting)
Well, I’m proud
of you, Homie.
You set out to
fight an animal,
and you ended up
saving its life.
What can I say?
I love nature.
Circle of life.
(theme song plays)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem