CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(whimpers)
That's
a saltwater croc,
the largest reptile
in the world.
Ow, crikey!
She's got me
by the dangle-down!
This naughty little Sheila
can snap a man's rib cage
like...
(loud crack)
Like that!
(screaming)
-Hey! I'm watching that!
-Not any more.
MALE ANNOUNCER: Malibu Stacey
wants a craft room.
And Malibu Ken needs a closet
for all his beach thongs.
They'll get help
from designer Jeremy on...
We'll also show you how to turn
a shoe box
into a you-box!
BART: Oh...
I missed the feeding frenzy.
I hope you're happy.
Obviously, yes.
(grunting)
HANK HILL: Bobby,
I got propane in my urethra.
MALE ANNOUNCER:
We'll be right back
with Who Will Marry
A Million Bears?
♪ I like ice cream,
I like ice cream ♪
♪ How 'bout you... ♪
Look, Maggie,
a show for babies.
♪ Topped with chocolate syrup,
topped with chocolate syrup ♪
♪ Whipped cream,
too whipped cream, too! ♪
Mom, that's Roofi.
His music is why
babies are idiots.
Well, Maggie likes Roofi.
And babies only like
good things.
Why don't you let us
watch TV
and get her
a Roofi CD?
Bart!
On't-day ell-tay om-may uffi-ray
as-hay e-say e-days.
Y-whay at-nay? Ut-whay auld-cay
o-gay ong-wray?
E'll-shay uy-bay
em-thay, upid-stay.
Ou-ay ow-knay, I-ay as-way
oung-yay unce-way oo-tay.
-Ap-cray.
(Roofi singing)
♪ One, two, tie your shoe ♪
♪ Three, four ♪
♪ Pick up the floor ♪
♪ Five, six,
don't play tricks ♪
♪ Seven, eight,
clean your plate ♪
♪ Nine, ten ♪
♪ Start over again ♪
-♪ One, two ♪
-(groaning)
♪ Tie your shoe ♪
♪ Three, four,
pick up the floor ♪
♪ Five, six,
don't play tricks... ♪
It's on batteries.
♪ Nine, ten,
start over again... ♪
Backed up by solar power.
(groaning)
♪ Three, four,
pick up the floor ♪
♪ Five, six,
don't play tricks ♪
♪ Seven, eight,
clean your plate ♪
♪ Nine, ten,
start over again... ♪
(gasps)
Look, Maggie-- funny Daddy.
(screaming)
Ow... too hard.
♪ ...Nine, ten,
start over again ♪
♪ One, two, tie your shoe ♪
♪ Three, four,
pick up the floor ♪
(screaming)
♪ ... Three, four,
pick up the floor... ♪
(shuddering)
(bell ringing)
Time to go home, Bart.
You don't understand,
I can't go home!
You gotta give me detention.
Look. I fed
the gerbil coffee!
(screaming)
Eh.
Please, make me write something
on the chalkboard
a thousand times!
We all got tired
of that chalkboard years ago.
Now go home.
♪ So he went upstairs ♪
♪ And knocked on the door ♪
♪ There's a helpful bear
on the 28th floor ♪
♪ 28th floor, 28th floor ♪
♪ There's a helpful bear
on the 28th floor ♪
Aw, look how happy she is.
Her eyes aren't focused.
(snarling)
It makes her happy.
So does sucking on the dog.
Hello, Springfield!
Roofi is coming to your town!
One show only!
Tickets will go fast.
Very fast!
So your parents should be
getting in line.
If you don't come,
Roofi will be sad
and the helpful bear,
she will die.
(coughing)
♪ Tickets, tickets,
buy them now ♪
♪ Roofi, he will show you how ♪
♪ Visa, Amex, or MC
or make out ♪
♪ a check to me ♪
Give Daddy
the remote, Maggie.
Give Daddy the...
D'oh!
(chuckling)
Mmmmmmmm!
Oh, wise guy, eh?
(moaning)
(moans like Curly
of the Three Stooges)
MARGE: I got
the Roofi tickets!
I got them fair and square
and I kept my dignity.
Not like Janey's mom.
(whooping like Curly)
Whatever!
(horns honking)
(gasps)
This concert is oversold.
It's as if a music promoter
acted unscrupulously!
(opening of "Gimme Shelter"
by The Rolling Stones)
ANNOUNCER:
And now, our opening act:
in their first live show
since Tinky Winky was acquitted
of manslaughter...
Not guilty!
ANNOUNCER:
...the Teletubbies!
(cheering)
Custard!
(chanting):
Custard, custard...
They make the Blue Man Group
look like Mummenschanz,
which is still pretty good.
Oh... the second one
wants custard, too?
That's a little repetitive.
(thunder crashes)
MARGE:
Oh, no!
It's raining and Maggie's
diapers are extra-absorbent!
(crying)
How's the crowd, Steve?
Awful fussy.
You're kidding me.
Did you make funny faces?
You did? Well, did you
jiggle your keys?
I did it all, man.
ANNOUNCER:
And now
here's Roofi!
♪ Sing the nonsense song ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ Yum, yum, wow ♪
♪ Whoop, dee, wee ♪
♪ Flibberty, flabberty ♪
♪ One, two, three... ♪
Ow!
Okay, who threw that?
Who threw it?
(crying)
KENT BROCKMAN:
A playdate
with disaster
at Cletus's farm!
I'm at the first aid tent,
where overwhelmed doctors
are trying to sort out
the owies from the boo-boos.
Now, I'm told we have the leader
of the babies on the line.
Tyler, is there
a peaceful solution possible?
(baby cooing
and pushing phone buttons)
(gasping)
All right, that's it!
Show's over!
Five, six, so long, hicks!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, you don't
want to go in there.
Some of those babies
have their teeth.
And those super-sharp
little fingernails.
Better leave it
to the professionals.
I don't feel right...
clubbing women
and children, Chief.
I hear ya.
Some days are tougher
than others.
Just close your eyes and club.
This is it, boys.
We'll have to tummy-kiss
our way out!
(sounds of tummy kissing
and blowing raspberries)
There's a bouncy one here,
Chief.
BROCKMAN:
Baby's got backlash!
Springfield citizens
are outraged
about the destruction
caused by the bad babies.
Bad babies.
Yes, you was.
They destroyed my home...
and the equity
I'd built up therein.
Asked if he intends
to take legal action,
the farmer replied,
"I ain't fungified
hidee-hoo 'bout no
legrification no ways,"
then scratched his rear,
hitched up his pants...
and scratched his rear again.
QUIMBY: That riot
has far-reaching consequences.
Kabul refuses to be
our sister city anymore.
I have no sister city!
(grunts)
The babies' damage
exceeds $1 million,
which will now be sucked
out of your pockets.
(air rushing)
MAN: My loose change!
Let me now introduce a woman
who wants to make sure
that what I just did
never happens again.
Good evening.
I'm Lindsay Naegle,
and I am the founder
of SSCCATAGAPP,
Singles, Seniors, Childless
Couples, and Teens, And Gays
Against Parasitic Parents.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Catchy name.
We're tired of picking up the
bills for other people's kids.
We already pay millions
every year in school taxes.
(crowd shouting angrily)
Excuse me, everyone.
I'm a mother.
(crowd booing)
And I'm an American!
(cheering)
I bake apple pies.
And I love baseball!
(booing)
Save your breath for blowing up
water wings, breeder.
I dream of an America
with nudity and "F" words
on network TV,
where the whole world
doesn't stop
because a school bus did.
Children are the future.
Today belongs to me!
(crowd cheering)
You can't change the rules
in the middle of the game!
We never would've had these kids
if we thought
we had to pay for them.
Promises were made!
Hey, tough tortellini!
I'm sick of printing
children's menu.
Let Mickey Meatball find
his own way out of the maze.
Pooey!
We're tired
of buying overpriced tickets
for your lousy school plays.
Then how would we ever
get to see Camelot?
We'll merely watch
the movie on tape.
Is that better?
To me, Ralph Wiggum
is Sir Lancelot.
♪ If ever I would leave you ♪
♪ It wouldn't be in summer... ♪
(crowd booing)
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's kill every child...
friendly thing in town!
(loud cheering)
(high-pitched):
It's time to put away
childish things...
(deep voiced):
and become a man.
♪ Talkin' 'bout my generation ♪
♪ I hope I die
before I get old ♪
-ELECTRONIC VOICE: Y, Y, Y...
-♪ Talkin' 'bout my
generation ♪
♪ My generation ♪
♪ My generation, baby ♪
♪ Why don't you all ♪
♪ Fade away? ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout my generation ♪
♪ And don't try to dig
what we all s-s-say... ♪
BROCKMAN:
Kids are people,
too-- worthless,
incomplete people.
That's the battle cry
as single Springfieldites
are continuing to run roughshod
over children and families.
From now on, children acting up
in public places
will be lightly Tased.
LITTLE BOY:
Mommy, pick me up.
(electronic zapping,
loud thud)
I wasn't kidding.
And in downtown Springfield,
a statue is being erected
to America's
most misunderstood hero,
the deadbeat dad.
(birds chirping)
That's all?
Just a statue?
This country makes me sick.
♪ Sign, sign ♪
♪ Everywhere a sign ♪
♪ Blocking out the scenery,
breaking my mind ♪
♪ Do this, don't do that,
can't you read ♪
-♪ The sign? ♪
-ALL (chanting):
Gamble! Gamble! Gamble!
(crunching and grinding)
(birds chirping)
(marker squeaking)
(saxophone playing
slow, sensuous jazz)
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, yeah. Mm.
Ms. Naegle, I'm sorry
to surprise you like this,
but I thought if we met
face-to-face,
we could settle
our differences.
Well, let's make it quick.
I know you have to get back
to your kids,
and I'm late
for a skydiving massage.
I'll cut to the chase.
I brought with me
the very best reason
I can think of
for what I believe in.
Her name is Lisa,
and I wouldn't trade her
for all the sleep-in
Sundays
and speed dating
in the world.
Ms. Naegle,
even though I disagree
with your principles,
I certainly admire
your success.
Well, Lisa, I would be proud
if one of the eggs I sold
turned out like you.
Mmm.
Mom, I locked your keys
in the car.
Then wait in the shadows!
Also, Maggie puked
in your purse again.
Poor me.
All my purse is full of
is disposable income.
Sorry, Marge,
I don't think I'll ever
understand your point of view.
Not even with all my free time.
Then I guess
this means war,
with the most powerful
weapon at my disposal:
a voter-sponsored
initiative.
(gasps):
You wouldn't dare!
I've already drawn up
the petition.
(dramatic chord plays)
Well, I'm not worried.
You won't get that thing
on the ballot
until the November
general election.
(tires screeching)
No, the March primary.
(dramatic chord plays)
Mom, can we get
a pretzel?
We've got pretzels
at home.
Not cinnamon.
(dramatic chord plays)
Well, we finally
got things
the way we want them.
Not a highchair
or complimentary
crayon in sight.
I'm going to tell
an anecdote
about love making,
without having
to look around.
Truly we have entered
a golden age.
(shouting)
Attention, everyone.
I wish to announce
the formation of PPASSCCATAG--
Proud Parents Against
Singles, Seniors,
Childless Couples
and Teens and Gays.
"Pupasscatag" is also
a disease of the brainstem.
That's how I'll remember it.
(chuckles)
To overturn these horrible
anti-family laws,
we've prepared the "Families
Come First" initiative.
Now, the first thing
we're going to need is money.
(crickets chirping)
I'm so sorry, Marge,
but I guess you get the bill.
(crickets chirping)
Oh, for the love of pizza.
Luigi Risotto?
That's-a me.
I'm from the U.S.
Immigration Department.
(crickets chirping)
Save our families!
Sign our petition!
The only petitions
that I sign
are to bring back
canceled sitcoms, thank you.
America needs the wisdom
of Herman's Head
now more than ever.
Well, howdy, ma'am.
I represent
the Tobacco Lobby,
and frankly, no politics
gets done in this country
without a little help from us.
(gasps)
Now we own you!
But I haven't endorsed it yet!
Football injury.
(chuckling)
Now why don't you just
sign the check?
(wailing voices)
Forget it.
(screams)
I guess no one gives a damn
about the American
family anymore.
I'll sign
your petition.
Mr. Burns?
You care about children?
Yes.
Particularly
their supple young organs.
Oh, unfenced back yard pools,
where would I be without you?
Hey, if Burns is
signing that petition,
maybe we should, too.
Yeah, rich guys always want
what's best for everyone.
Coming up later,
what your dog can tell you
about your prostate.
Mm.
But first, Marge Simpson's
"Families Come First" initiative
seems to be gaining steam,
leading her opponents to counter
with this commercial.
As a mother, I love my family.
That's why I'm against
the "Families Come First"
initiative.
"Families Come First"
will hurt families,
and I love my family
too much for that.
I'm Marge Simpson,
and even I'm against
"Families Come First."
Now it's time to do some coke
off the blade of a knife.
Hmph! That ad makes me look
like a criminal.
Then why did you appear in it?
That wasn't me.
Maybe she was you,
and you're not!
How many kids
do we have?
Three.
Wrong, lady!
Oh, wait, the baby.
MARGE:
I try my best.
They ridicule me.
They mock everything
I cherish.
Honey, this marriage
is a partnership.
When you fall, I pick you up.
And when you can't
finish a sandwich,
I eat that sandwich.
You're my rock, Homie.
And I promise this rock
is going to weigh you down
for the rest of your life.
Aw...
Honey, no one messes
with my missus.
I'll come down on those guys
like the garage door
on Bart's bike.
What are you
going to do?
You just leave
everything to Homer.
And now, I believe you
owe me half a sandwich.
I always keep one
near the bed for you.
HOMER:
Here comes my commercial.
In six, five,
four...
I probably should have
watched it first.
HOMER'S VOICE:
You've probably heard
a lot of bad things
about "Families Come First,"
but newspaper writers
are a bunch of jerks.
Who really opposes
"Families Come First"?
Many childless advocates
are like Ben Affleck--
famous, successful people
from... out of state!
They live in fancy houses
in other places.
"Families Come First"
is supported
by lifelong Springfieldians
you know and trust
like me,
Milhouse's Dad,
Bumblebee Man,
Surly Duff,
and that jerk
that goes "Yeees?!"
For more information,
visit our Website,
www.al-jazeera.com.
We're not affiliated.
We're just piggybacking
on their message board.
(mystic voice):
I am Rudy Giuliani.
Do as I command you.
I am Rudy Guiliani.
It says "Yes on 232".
We want no on 232,
Yes on 242.
Either way.
The important thing
is the system works.
And the bumper stickers
misspelled "on."
They all say "Yes No 242".
And it's the night
before the election,
and you haven't
handed them out.
(groans)
I need to be alone right now.
Marge, wait.
(mystic voice):
I am Rudy Giuliani.
You must
forgive Homer.
I am Rudy Giuliani.
You must
forgive Homer.
I am...
Bart,
we're going to lose.
We have to do
something.
Lis, kids are the problem,
maybe kids
can be the solution.
Okay, but how?
Hey, I'm the visionary.
You come up with
the nuts and bolts.
(groaning)
(gasps):
Oh, my God!
I just had my most
brilliant idea ever.
Don't you mean
my most brilliant idea ever?
You don't even know
what the idea is.
I know you have an ugly face.
Bart, why are we fighting?
Because we're kids.
(snaps)
Kids!
Maybe that's the answer.
(groans)
(gasps)
There's the enemy.
Give them all you got.
I love you!
Arg.
KIDS: I love you!
I love you!
I love you.
I love glue.
Aw, such
a sweet little thing.
Time to destroy your future.
Feeling... flu-ish.
Fever...
nausea...
Child germs... No!
Must... participate in...
democratic... pro...
cess.
(groans)
(spitting and groaning)
I'm afraid
the polls have closed.
And on Prop 242,
the winner is... yeees!
(groaning)
For all their
disposable income,
for all
their leisure time,
the had no immunity against
God's lowliest creatures:
children.
Looks like everything's
back the way it was,
which is the only way
it should ever be.
HOMER: Great.
Let's dump these kids
in an R-rated movie
while we go
someplace nice.
Can I bring
my laser pointer?
What do I care?
ROOFI:
♪ One, two, tie your shoe ♪
♪ Three, four,
pick up the floor ♪
♪ Five, six,
don't play tricks ♪
♪ Seven, eight,
clean your plate ♪
♪ Nine, ten,
start over again ♪
♪ One, two, tie your shoe ♪
♪ Three, four,
pick up the floor ♪
♪ Five, six,
don't play tricks ♪
♪ Seven, eight,
clean your plate ♪
♪ Nine, ten,
start over again ♪
♪ One, two, tie your shoe ♪
♪ Three, four,
pick up the floor ♪
♪ Five, six,
don't play tricks ♪
♪ Seven, eight,
clean your plate ♪
♪ Nine, ten,
start over again ♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem