CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme song plays)
D-oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(squishing)
Look, Smithers,
crackle-berries!
Spot me a federal,
will you?
Sir, I’ve spotted you
over $100,000 this year.
Perhaps you could carry
your own money.
(chuckles)
Money is for the poor.
Why don’t you use
your ATM card?
Ah, yes,
the automated teller
machine-eola-trola-maton.
Ugh... oh... umph...
Ooh, Smithers,
guide me in.
My pleasure, sir.
Smithers,
what’s my password?
It’s your age, sir.
Excellent.
(beeping)
Let’s see...
what’s the smallest amount
of money I can think of?
$1,000!
Oh, my moolah!
It’s escaping my clutches!
(buzzer sounding)
Your kid sucks!
(mechanically):
Bring it on!
ANNOUNCER:
Hockey dads...
commence fighting!
"Hockey Dad" rules!
Feel the drunken wrath
of Chuck Shadowski!
(grunting)
Dad, stop!
It’s only assault...
don’t make it murder!
Ignore, ignore!
ANNOUNCER: You are a big man!
Big man!
-(gasps)
-What?
Umm... there’s a ladybug
in your hair.
Get it out!
Got it!
You’re a good friend,
Bart.
The best
you’ll ever have.
$1,000.
Do you know how much furniture
we could rent with this?
You’ll rent nothing!
This money is mine.
I found it!
Which means someone lost it.
You’ll have to put up flyers
and see if anyone claims it.
(both gasp)
Marge, this is why people
don’t tell you things.
(chuckling)
Well,
we put up a flyer.
Let’s see someone
claim that money now.
(chuckling)
Hey, what does
that flyer say?
What if it’s for
guitar lessons?
We must know!
I’m on it!
HOMER & BART:
Oh! Ah!
Uh-oh.
You know the drill.
Try to land on my back-fat.
Can you describe
the bill?
Describe? Sure, of course.
Whose picture is on it?
Uh... it would have to be
somebody famous...
I’m gonna say... Hitler.
Next!
MAN: Um...
does the bill have bank teller
blood on it?
No, it doesn’t.
I’m sorry
I wasted your time.
That’s the last of them.
You did the right thing,
Bart,
and now you can
keep the money.
Sweet!
What am I going to do
with $1,000?
(harp stums)
♪ It’s Bart’s moon party
from outer space ♪
♪ With R2-D2
playin’ the bass... ♪
(harp stums)
Hmm, no one’s touching
the hors d’oeuvres.
♪ It’s Bart’s moon party
from outer space... ♪
What?
Bart, why don’t you spend
the money
on something for Mom?
She does so much
for us.
Well... someday I’d like to go
on a nice vacation.
We’ve gone on plenty
of great vacations.
Yeah, but you always
wind up kidnapped,
or on a chain gang...
and I don’t even want
to get into
what happened on our honeymoon.
HOMER: I still don’t know
why you had
that photo enlarged.
Oh, forget it.
Bart, don’t waste
your money on me.
(sighing)
Great, lady.
MILHOUSE:
Look at the cross-hatching
on Grover Cleveland’s tie!
I completely buy
the illusion of shadow.
This must be worth,
like, a million dollars.
(bell ringing)
Time’s up!
Beat it, do-rags!
I want to see it some more.
If you let me
keep looking at it,
I’ll give you a quarter.
Hmm... this gives me an idea.
(classical music plays)
(all gasping)
What’s all this
other stuff?
Hey, I’m charging five bucks
to get in.
They deserve to see
the boy behind the bill.
Bart, that exhibit
over there is biased,
insensitive
and anti-feminist.
Ugh!
You can’t whitewash
history, Lise.
What do I get
if I join the museum
as a "Friend of Bart"?
A subscription
to BartForum magazine
and Bart will say
"eat my shorts"
on your home answering machine.
How much to have Bart
crank-call me?
(chuckling):
That would be hilarious.
Ah, that’s just me, though.
You know,
I love to laugh.
Young man, I believe
you have something
that belongs to me.
Prove it, Bony Curtis.
When the errant bill
struck my chest,
it left
a distinctive bruise.
Had my heart been inside
at the time,
it could have been fatal.
BART:
It’s a perfect match!
Yoink!
(scoffing)
Without that bill,
this ain’t a museum.
The Hard Rock Cafe
in Phoenix has better crap.
I’m recycling this pin
in disgust.
(sad music)
Bart, your museum took in
over $3,000!
Finally, I can get
what I’ve always wanted...
a used Toyota.
Bart, I don’t care
what Mom said.
I think you should use
this money
to take her
on a nice vacation.
Well... okay.
For Mom, I’ll do it.
Where should we go?
Well, I’d like to return
to Brazil,
but I hear the monkey problem
is even worse now.
I want to go
to England.
How come?
Back in 1944,
I was stationed over there
and I met a beautiful girl...
Edwina, my slowly-
opening flower,
I’m shipping out
in the morning.
Won’t you make
this night memorable?
Anything for you,
my brave Yank.
(romantic music)
I say... oh...
nice.
GRANDPA:
Little did I know I really was
shipping out in the morning.
♪♪
I’ll never forget you, Edwina!
But I did... until just now.
Grandpa,
that’s so romantic!
We gotta go to England!
That sounds great.
But only if your father
promises to behave.
Marge, I’ll be
on my best behavior.
You have my word
as a gentleman and a lady.
Now, let’s see,
which rifle should I bring?
(groaning)
♪♪
Hello.
Welcome
to the United Kingdom.
Prime Minister Tony Blair?
Why are you greeting lowlifes
like us at the airport?
Because I want to encourage
all the world
to come see the beauty
of 21st Century Britain.
Would an American dollar
encourage you
to leave us alone?
No, but thank you.
Tony... I mean,
Mr. Prime Minister...
what should we see first?
There’s so much to see here:
Parliament, Stratford-on-Avon,
the White Cliffs of Dover...
Oh, and you Americans
love castles--
there’s a huge one
in Edinburgh,
the city where I was born.
The place I was born
is now a gator farm.
Smashing.
Maybe you could give us
a personal tour
of your country.
I’d love to, but I’m late
for an appointment.
I’m greeting a lovely
Dutch couple at Gate 23.
Cheerio.
(spy music plays)
Wow, I can’t believe
we met Mr. Bean.
England is so classy.
Every cab
has its own butler.
Actually, I’m not a butler.
I had already hired this cab
when you got in,
but the more the merrier
and all that.
Make with the tea, Jeeves.
Yes, very good, sir.
We’re big-shot tourists
from everyone’s favorite
country: the USA.
We saved your ass
in Vietnam
and shared our prostitutes
with Hugh Grant.
So give me some free maps,
and none of that
dry British wit.
(dryly):
I wouldn’t dream of it, sir.
Thank you.
(groans)
Did you spend
an unforgettable night
with a soldier
from the U.S. Army in 1944?
You did?
Was he from the 1st
Infantry Division?
He was?
And was he a gentle,
caring lover?
He was?
Sorry I bothered you.
I don’t know
if I’m ever gonna find her.
Oh, Dad, I wish there was
something I could do.
Touch that mini bar
and you’re dead!
Oh...
("Rule Britannia" plays)
Look, it’s J.K. Rowling,
author of
the Harry Potter books.
You’ve turned
a generation of kids
on to reading.
Thank you, young muggle.
Can you tell me what happens
at the end of the series?
He grows up and marries you.
Is that what you want to hear?
Yes.
All right, who’s hungry?
We’re right near
a Judi Dench’s Fish and Chips.
(over speaker):
Welcome to
Judi Dench’s Fish and Chips.
Now completely free
of Mad Fish Disease.
Fish? I don’t know,
I’m not really a vegetarian.
Please order, or Miss Dench
will be furious.
She’ll beat us, she will.
JUDI DENCH:
Who are you talking to?
No one, mum, I swear.
I’ll "mum" you!
(punching)
Blimey!
(sign buzzes)
Well, Marge,
you got to admit,
I’ve been on my best
behavior this trip.
You punched out three people
on the street.
That was over
soccer results.
Can you believe
they gave Giggs
a yellow card
in the box?
Do you understand any part
of what you just said?
I understand
the word "gave."
Unless it means something
else in this country.
Word to the wise,
British candy is a bit sweeter
than what you’re used
to across the pond.
Look, tea bag,
just fork over the brown.
(British-style rock plays)
♪♪
(both tittering)
Homie, I don’t think
we’ll be able
to find the kids
from up here.
Now, now, let’s just look.
There’s Big Ben,
there’s Piccadilly Circus.
There’s Jimmy Page,
one of the greatest thieves
of American Black music
who ever walked the earth.
Bup, there’s the kids.
(spy music playing)
(motor whirring)
(groaning)
Look at those
filthy urchins.
Surely they could never be
taught proper manners.
One gold sovereign says
I could do just that.
Oh, it’s a bet,
Lord Daftwager.
You can’t bet
on my kids.
This is America, pal.
Don’t worry,
we’ll find more wagers.
I love you, Lord Daftwager.
Yes, and I you.
(moaning)
Yes, quite.
Oh, look at all these
classy British plays.
(man coughing)
I don’t have
a cherry orchard.
(gasps)
Sir Ian McKellen!
You’re my favorite
Shakespearean actor.
Thank you, my dear.
Please take these
free tickets to my play.
What? What play?
We thespians believe
it’s bad luck
to mention the name of this
particular play out loud.
You mean Macbeth?
Quiet, you blundering fool.
You’ll curse us all.
What, by saying Macbeth?
Aah!
Stop saying it!
Saying what?
Macbeth!
Aah! Now I’ve said it.
Oh, this is cool.
Macbeth! Macbeth!
Macbeth!
Bart, stop saying
"Macbeth."
Mom, you said "Macbeth."
Mr. Macbeth,
I’m really sorry.
That’s quite all right.
You didn’t know.
Now, if you’ll excuse me,
I have a performance to give.
Good luck.
It’s bad luck
to say that, too.
(gasping)
Homie,
you’re doing a great job
driving on the left.
This is turning out to be
our most enjoyable trip ever.
Yes, this trip
is entirely uneventful.
(chuckles)
Dad, no!
You turned
into a roundabout!
(circular screams)
MARGE: Turn, turn,
keep turning,
keep turning...
HOMER:
I see an opening.
MARGE: No, it’s too risky.
We’ll just wait till
the traffic thins out.
Turn, turn,
keep turning,
keep turning...
(fatigued):
...keep turning,
keep turning...
That’s it.
I’m acting the way
America acts best--
unilaterally.
(horns honking)
(screaming)
Okay, I’m gonna go over there
and see if they’re cool.
Okay, let’s see...
Oh, you can buff that out.
You can buff that out.
That’s factory error.
Oh, that thing’s
supposed to be on fire.
Lady, please.
Get back in your
overturned car.
Let the guys
handle this.
We’ll deal with him,
Your Majesty.
"Your Majesty"?
(imitates whiplash)
Dad, you rear-ended
the Queen of England.
The Queen of what?!
D-oh!
(grunts, screams)
(trumpet fanfare blares)
Changing of the guard.
(groans)
Wait, we have
to exchange insurance!
(screams):
Oh! Ow! Oh!
-(gavel bangs)
-Homer Simpson,
you are hereby charged
with damaging the Royal Coach,
and putting several dents
in the Royal Horse.
How do you plead?
Milord,
we Americans love queens,
be they homecoming or Dairy.
This woman, however,
is an impostor.
(gasping)
Her luggage is inscribed
"H.R.H.",
which means
her real name must be...
Henrietta R. Hippo..
Why did you let him
be his own barrister?
What difference
could it make?
He hit the friggin’ queen!
I guess
it’s just too much
for me to ask
for one vacation
where we don’t go to jail
or to a condo sales pitch.
Your Honor, I’ve completely
disappointed my wife.
That’s punishment enough.
You understand
these things.
You’re a grandmother.
I’m a man!
Oh! And a very manly one,
if I may say so, milord.
If I might say a word?
(gasping)
I haven’t had an easy life.
I’ve seen my country
ravaged by war,
my family torn by tragedy,
and then, as I was
innocently making my way
to the shops
to buy light bulbs,
I was blindsided
by this great,
lumbering brute.
Boy, she’s good.
If she were
100 years younger,
and I were
100 years older...
(lusty laugh)
If there is any love
left in you for me,
destroy him!
America rules!
Our Beatles are
way better than
your precious Rolling Stones!
In this cell
sits Homer Simpson,
the most villainous blackguard
to be held in this tower
since Edward the Puppy Eater.
(gasping)
Look at his great,
staring eyes.
Like saucers, they are!
(Cockney accent)
’E claimed he was me father,
’e did.
Bart, you’re not helping.
Poke the monster
with a stick!
Tuppence a jab!
C’mon, queue up, lads.
Oh, Marge,
I’m so sorry.
I should
have listened
to whatever
it was you were saying.
It’s partly my fault.
I’ve been nagging you
so much on this trip,
you couldn’t know
which nags to focus on.
Well, Marge,
if I die here,
there’s one thing
I want you to remember:
don’t buy
any videotapes in England.
They won’t work
in our VCR!
(sobbing)
Dear God of England,
please let me go.
In return, I will spell
the word "color" with a "u",
and I will use
the metric system
with every cubic milliliter
of blood in my...
Oh, I can’t do it.
It’s so stupid!
-LISA: Dad!
-Huh?
We found a secret tunnel
out of the tower.
It was used
by Sir Walter Raleigh!
A secret tunnel?
I don’t know.
Won’t that get me
in more trouble?
Homer, you couldn’t be
in more trouble.
They’re going to put
your head on a pike.
They’re practicing
with melons.
Smash it on.
Don’t worry it.
Let the pike
do the work.
Okay, what do I do?
Push the grey brick
in the back of the fireplace.
Sweet freedom,
here I...
(screams)
Put out the fire first.
Boy, it’s a good thing
I’m leaving
before I went nuts.
Good-bye, Sparkly Elves.
Good-bye!
Oh, my God!
We’ve made
a terrible mistake.
This tunnel comes out in the
worst possible place.
An elephant’s butt?
Yes, Bart,
an elephant’s butt.
Boy, a Krispy Kreme would
really clean up down here.
Hey, this place is amazing!
It’s fit for a duke,
or even an earl...
(gasps)
(blows whistle)
Uh-oh.
The queen’s in trouble.
And you didn’t want
to give her a whistle.
(screams)
Please, Your Majesty,
I know that I,
like many other Americans,
have behaved
like a total buffoon.
But we Americans
are England’s children.
I know we don’t call
as often as we should,
and we aren’t
as well-behaved
as our goody-two-shoes
brother, Canada--
who, by the way,
has never had a girlfriend.
I’m just saying...
But, please, find it
in your jewel-encrusted heart
to forgive me.
That was very sweet
of the queen,
letting you go
in exchange
for taking Madonna
back to America.
WOMAN (muffled):
I’m telling you!
I’m English!
Englishwomen
don’t pump gas naked.
See you
in Atlanta, jerk!
Abe Simpson,
are you leaving again
without saying good-bye?
Edwina,
you got my message!
Oh...
Sorry I never
saw you again.
I just felt
the cultural differences
between us
were too great.
Plus, as the boat
pulled away from the dock,
I thought
you looked fat.
You don’t have
to apologize, Abe.
You Yanks
saved our bacon.
Mmm!
Bacon!
D-oh!
Abe, this is
my daughter Abbey.
She’s 58 this month.
58?!
Well, 59 years ago,
your mother
and I were hav...
Oh! Well, gotta go!
See ya in heaven.
Dang!
Mummy, he’s everything
you said he was.
Lady,
you’re gorgeous.
You make Dame Edna
look like a dude!
Why, thank you.
You’re all right, love.
♪♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem