CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(yells):
Bart, I got it!
(groans)
(barking)
I ran here as fast as I...
(groans)
Bart, that creepy kid
is here!
(Homer groans)
(birds squawk)
Hey, Milhouse.
Oh, what's this?
"Psycho Cycle Conversion Kit?!"
Oh, wow, this will
look great on my bike.
Flame decal for the chain guard,
Marine Corps tassels,
bullet-proof seat,
and a rub-on tattoo for
that "special someone."
That's me.
"Biker chick?" Oh!
♪ Why don't you come with me,
little girl ♪
♪ On a magic carpet ride ♪
Now to turn on
the moto-mimic.
(engine revs like motorcycle)
Sounds like a motorcycle gang.
And we don't have backup.
We better lay low.
But, Chief,
what if they like pizza?
Way ahead of you, Lou.
(engine revving)
That is one bitchin' bike.
Daddy said a cuss word.
Lighten up, Roddy.
Haw-haw.
It's the baby bike brigade.
Hey, Bart, I used to have
a bike like that...
back before I was born.
Oh, no.
They've got big boy bikes.
Thanks for the tassels.
My mom can wear these
on her boobs at work.
(laughing)
Hey, give those back.
Gentlemen: first gear.
(grunts)
Oh, man, I sure I wish
I had a ten-speed bike.
A ten-speed bike?
What did your mother say?
She said "yes."
MARGE:
I said no.
I'm confused. Which is it?
It's no.
His old bike is fine.
Yeah, the kitchen
lady's right.
No new bike while your
old one still works.
I see. So if my old bike
didn't work,
I would automatically
get a new one?
That's right.
No questions asked.
(chuckles)
Boy, I'm really gonna miss you.
We've really had some great...
Ooh, a Mercedes!
(car crash)
What the Halle Berry?
Yes!
(gasps):
My bike!
My crappy, crappy bike!
I'm very sorry, Bart.
I'll pay for a new bike.
(low chuckling)
(meows)
This was a wake-up call.
From now on, I'll keep
my eyes on the road
and off my "Kool and the Gang"
air freshener.
Celebration's over, boys.
(cat screeches, thump)
(gasps)
Snowball!
(sobbing)
Snowball II,
I can't believe you're gone.
I wrote this poem for you.
It's called "Cat Math."
"Four paws plus one tail
plus nine lives
equals one special cat.
One special cat minus nine lives
equals one sad little girl."
(sobbing)
I know how you feel, Lis.
No kid wants
to outlive their pet.
(sobs)
Oh, Sweetie,
when I was your age
I lost my guinea pig
Cinnamon.
And I thought the pain
would never... (gasps)
(cries):
Oh, Cinnamon!
It should've been me
who chewed through
that extension cord.
There, there.
You're both right.
Son, would you like to ride
your new bike out of the store?
Can I, for true?
For true, son.
Hey, pally...
I don't want to downshift
your enthusiasm,
but that's
a floor model.
Your bike is in here.
I could put it together right
now for a small assembly fee.
Here we go.
Now it starts
with the fees.
I'll assemble it myself.
Dad, no.
Think of the bike.
I can make a bike.
I made you.
Yeah, great workmanship.
Hey, that's gonna win you
a lot of bar bets some day.
Oh, man, this is so confusing.
What the hell is this?
(groans):
Oh...
(gasps)
(yawns):
Bike's over there.
You actually did it.
You're the coolest, Dad.
(chuckles, then snores)
Look what my Dad
just built for me.
(impressive murmuring)
Hey, guys.
This butt's for you.
Oh, no!
No one does this to Dolph.
No one!
(chuckling)
Uh-oh. Whoa.
(grunts and groans)
I'm riding a unicycle
with my pants down.
This should be
every boy's dream.
Haw-haw!
Your dad's not handy.
Son, are you okay?
I brought a homemade
first aid kit.
It's spring-loaded
for quick access.
(screams):
D'oh!
(screaming)
(sighs):
Oh...
MAN: We now return
to Robot Rumble
on the Testosterone Network!
ANNOUNCER: Congratulations to
our winning father-and-son
team,
who will receive
a free appetizer
at Fuzzy Zoeller's Green Jacket
Steakhouse.
And you won't be teed off
when you come in,
because our steaks are cooked
to par-fection,
our leader-board is filled
with scrumptious--
two more pages--
I'm not reading this.
Hey, boy, what do you say
we build a robot?
Face it, you're not the most
mechanical guy in the world.
But you're good
at other things:
like... eating
while driving.
That's something.
And nobody gets madder
at the news.
First of all, thank you.
Secondly...
My son thinks I'm an oaf.
Mom, I'm not sure
I'm ready for a new cat.
When Bad Things Happen
To Cute Children
says that a new pet will pull
you out of your sorrow cycle.
That book doesn't know
how I feel.
Oh, it's very wise.
It's written by a rabbi--
who surfs!
All right, I'll look.
Too fluffy, too Siamese,
too needy,
too stuck-up, infected eye,
clearly a skunk.
-(gasps)
-Me-ow!
Welcome to the family,
Snowball III.
(purring)
There's nothing worse
than the look on a boy's face
when he says,
"Dad, I don't think you can
build a fully-functional robot."
(screams)
Robot, I command you:
do something cool.
(whirring and clanking)
Oh, I could quit now...
but then my son will never
look up to me.
Oh, why was I born a dad?
Why... do... I... suck?
Wait a minute.
What is it my dad
always said to me?
If you can't build
a robot... be a robot.
That's it!
(Krusty laughing)
It's Tuesday the first.
If you live in Krusty Brand
low income housing,
your rent is due.
(screams)
"Dear Bart, if this robot
doesn't prove I love you,
then you can both go to Hell."
Hey, it didn't fall apart.
Cool.
Now, stop.
Smash this six-pack.
Awesome!
I got to tell Milhouse.
Oh, the beer's gone.
I'll have to suck it
out of the shag.
(loud slurping)
(to tune of "Hokey Pokey"):
♪ You plop the cat food down ♪
♪ You toss the tin can out ♪
♪ You drop the worm pills in
and you stir it all about ♪
♪ You add a lot of lovin'
and you serve it to your cat ♪
♪ That's what it's all a... ♪
Snowball III?
(gasps)
(sobbing)
Oh, Lisa...
Honey, it's okay.
You're a Buddhist,
so you know your cats
are now reincarnated as
a higher form of life.
Like a dog, or a snowman.
Ashes to ashes,
dust to dust...
We've got to go
fight some robots.
Come on, Homer.
How long does it take to go
to the bathroom?
Huh?
"Dear, Bart..."
(Homer reading):
Well, I wish Homer was here.
But don't worry.
I've got a name all
picked out for you.
Chief Knockahomer, let's
win this one for Dad!
(bleeps and bloops)
ANNOUNCER:
In this corner,
operated
by Frank Murray
and little Frankie Jr...
Buzzkill!
And in this corner,
the challenger,
Chief Knockahomer!
There's no love lost between
these emotionless devices.
Robots rumble.
(bell dings)
♪♪
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
Geez, I'm the only one
in the audience over 15.
Are you here with
your children, sir?
Uh, yeah, my two kids...
Screw... and you.
(screams)
ANNOUNCER:
What's this?
Knockerhomer
has dropped his hammer.
Ow!
Doing it for the boy.
Pain is love.
To bleed is to care.
ANNOUNCER:
Can robots feel pain?
If so, we are horrible,
horrible people.
(groaning)
He's killing him softly
with his saw.
Killing him softly?
With his saw!
(crowd cheering)
Woo-hoo! I mean, beep-beep.
Mom, I'm not sure if I'm ready
to open my heart again,
but this kitten's name is
Coltrane.
Maybe it's a sign.
Coltrane?
Lisa, I'm glad you're
ready to love again.
But a kitty needs
a proper name,
like Whiskers.
Or Paws Scaggs.
Well, I think it's only fair
I get to name him.
You got to name me.
You should be glad I did.
Your father wanted
to call you Bartzeena.
Coltrane, would you like
to hear some music
written by your namesake?
(playing "Blue Train")
(screeching)
Coltrane?
Coltrane, you were with us
only briefly,
but we'll always have the ride
home from the shelter.
And, um... I guess that's it.
Amen.
And, Lord, if you think
I'm making lemon bars
for your bake sale Sunday, you'd
better stop killing our cats.
Mom, I'm not sure God responds
to threats and intimidation.
It's the only way
to talk to bullies.
...then Knockahomer did
three victory laps
and pretended
to drink a beer.
(chuckles)
Pretended.
Dad, what are
all those cuts?
Various bug bites and wounds.
Now, stop interrupting
your brother.
In my day, mechanical men had
funnel hats and showed respect.
Then it all changed
when they got the vote
and started tinkering
with our memories.
("Watching Scotty Grow"
playing)
♪ There he sits with
a pen and a yellow pad ♪
♪ What a handsome lad ♪
♪ That's my boy ♪
♪ B-R-L-F-Q
spells "Mom and Dad" ♪
♪ Well that ain't too bad ♪
♪ 'Cause that's my boy ♪
♪ So you can have your TV
and your night clubs ♪
♪ And you can have your
drive-in picture show... ♪
ANNOUNCER:
Well, if you ever want
to see a mailbox shoot a boy,
that's about as close
as you're going to get.
Dad, it was so great--
Knockahomer really
took a pounding,
but then he won.
Ooh! Oh, not so rough, Bart.
Daddy can't handle so much
love right now.
This robot's
the greatest thing
you've ever done for me.
I can't believe you've
never seen him fight.
Well, I've been busy, son.
They really need me over
at the nuclear plank.
Well, the next match
is Saturday.
Can you come then?
I don't think so, son.
But on
the other hand,
I may be closer
than you think.
Oh, so much metal
in my eye.
Ladies and gentlemen...
who am I kidding,
just gentlemen...
join us next week
for our title bout,
when Knockahomer will try
to unseat five-time
defending champion...
Smashius Clay, A.K.A.
Killhammad Aieee!
(crowd screaming)
Our robot can kick that
robot's ass, right, Dad?
(whimpering)
Dad?
Oh no! My recurring nightmare
is coming true.
There are many people I'd like
to thank for this award.
My wife, Anjelica Huston--
this is for you, Angie!
We did it!
ROBOT:
Speeches cannot be longer
than 30 seconds.
(screams)
Now a tribute to those who have
left us this past year.
(whimpering)
(whirring)
BART:
Sure, he's tough.
But he's never come up
against a wooden mallet.
(crowd cheering)
(shuts off TV)
Listen, son,
there's something
I have to tell you
about our robot.
(doorbell rings)
There it is!
The thing that makes us
respect Bart.
KIDS:
Ooh!
You guys are just in time.
My dad's about to tell me
something important
about our robot.
Uh... I...
just installed a chip
that makes it ten percent
more bloodthirsty!
ALL:
All right!
And if anything happens to me,
I want you bullies
to take care of my boy.
Don't worry.
I'll raise him like
the mean streets raised me.
I wish I'd had bullies
like you growing up.
ALL:
Mm!
Hey! Hey!
These cats would rather
take their chances
in the back room
than go home with you.
(hissing)
My job was to keep
Lisa's hope alive.
But instead,
she's really depressed.
You think
you've got problems.
Look what I just pulled
out of my arm!
(gasps)
That's what we in the business
call "a biggie."
Business?
What business?
The business of being a dad.
Can you hand me that magnet?
Sure.
(clanking)
Can you do my back?
I guess I'm not meant
to own a cat.
I'm much happier
petting this leaf.
(gasps)
(demented raving)
Wait, you don't want me
to have this cat!
(demented raving)
Look, you don't want to get
involved with a girl like me.
My cats have a nasty habit
of waking up dead.
Now go. Cough me out
of your life
like a bad fur ball.
(tires screech)
You're not hurt!
You're a good-luck kitty!
All right!
Ol' Gil's gonna collect big
from insurance!
I'll be eating food tonight!
(humming happily)
(explosion)
I'm keeping you!
You're Snowball Five.
But to save money on a new dish,
we'll just call you Snowball Two
and pretend this whole thing
never happened.
That's really a cheat,
isn't it?
I guess you're right,
Principal Tamzarian.
I'll just be moving along,
Lisa. Snowball Two.
(explosion)
Okay, I've been studying
Frink's robot,
and I've discovered
he has one small weak spot.
This goes here.
Uh-oh. His weak spot
is now his strongest point.
(loud moan)
That moan sounded almost human.
HOMER:
The hell it did.
(rock music plays)
(round-bell rings)
(grunts)
(grunting)
(staccato grunting)
(round-bell rings)
End of round one!
230 rounds to go!
(woozily):
♪ B-R-L-F-Q spells mom and dad ♪
♪ Well, that ain't too bad,
'cause that's my boy... ♪
You look a
little sluggish
out there, boy.
I'd better open you up.
(gasps)
Dad?!
Bart, I'm sorry.
I could never build a robot
this awesome.
I'm a fraud.
So, you fought
all those robots?
Affirmative.
That is so cool!
You really think so?
Yeah! Any Poindexter can throw
some nuts and bolts together.
You risked your own life,
even though you're the sole
provider for a family of five!
I am the luckiest kid
in the world.
And I'm the luckiest...
ANNOUNCER:
Round two!
Oh, no!
Dad!
(gasps)
(gasping)
That robot has given birth
to a man!
Hey, what gives?
He's not killing me!
I'll tell you
what gives.
I'm afraid he is subject
to Isaac Asimov's
laws of robotics.
With the sci-fi
and the so many books,
not too many good.
My robot is programmed
never to harm humans, you see.
Only to serve them.
(gasps)
He knows just how I like
my martinis...
full of alcohol.
Go! Go! Go!
Now's your chance!
(chuckles)
Bart, all that
button ever did
was send a mild electric shock
up my backside.
Why did you make it
do that?
-(zapping)
-Keep me focused.
And the winner is nature's
greatest killing machine:
man!
(booing)
Show me where
in the rule book
it says that a human
can't be a robot.
Right here. Rule one.
Well, then...
Join us next week for
more inconclusive action
on Robot Rumble!
I concur!
(booing)
Son, did you ever suspect
it was me?
Well, you did disappear a lot,
but I've gone whole summers
without seeing you.
(laughs)
Yeah, I'm pretty unreliable.
I like you, Son.
I like you, too, Dad.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem