Good grief,
this candy’s terrible.
Circus peanuts, raisins,
nicotine gum,
a library card...
You got
all the good stuff!
And yet I’m still
not satisfied.
(gulping)
Aah, you thieving hussy!
(choking)
Ow!
Aah!
(grunts)
You kids have got to learn
that actions
have consequences!
(angry grunt)
Eat fire, punks!
-Whoa!
-What the--
I’m still cold.
Will everyone please stop
fighting and burning!
Never!
(enraged roar)
-Beat the lumps.
-Hey!
Beat the lumps.
-BART: Ay, caramba!
Homie, I disagree
with your approach
to the children.
-(grunting)
-(gunshot)
-(yells)
-(racking slide)
-(gunshot)
-HOMER: Yeow!
Pathetic humans!
They’re showing a Halloween
episode in November!
Who’s still thinking
about Halloween?
We’ve already got our
Christmas decorations up!
KANG AND KODOS:
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas!
♪♪
(knocking)
(deep, sepulchral voice):
I am Death!
Death?
We don’t want any.
I have come
for Bart Simpson.
Bart,
run like the "wined"!
Mom, it’s "wind."
Well, I’ve only
read it in books.
(Benny Hill Show
theme song plays)
(scythe clangs)
Ooh!
Why you little...
(clang)
(ghoulish music plays)
Please, don’t take me!
Take Milhouse.
We all know there’s no
happy ending there.
Your time is up.
This is for Snowball One
and JFK!
(grunts)
Ow!
Cool.
Dad, do you realize
what you’ve done?
You’ve created a world
without Death.
Does this mean they’ll never
cancel the Jim Belushi Show?
I guess so.
Nooooo!
LISA:
A world without death.
(gunshots)
(yelling)
Frankie the Squealer,
why won’t you die?
Ohh! If I knew,
I’d tell ya, I swear!
(yelling)
I’d better call my wife...
tell her I’ll be late.
(gunshots)
(sighs)
If I knew this would
take so long, I’d
have put on the TV.
Pizza!
Money’s on the counter.
No tip.
Aah, you miserable bastard!
That’s why I’m up here.
Death...
Death,
we miss you so much.
You were a busboy
in the restaurant of life,
clearing away the oldies
and the sickies and the chokies.
And you made NASCAR racing
exciting.
Homer, it’s trash day.
Will you just take him out
to the curb?
I’ll curb him...
without enthusiasm.
Ooh, this robe’s
pretty soft.
Check it out!
I finally found a dead
guy’s clothes that fit me!
(all scream)
What? It’s not...
(screams):
My hand!
What’s happening?
Dad, you’ve become
the new Grim Reaper!
No way. Forget it.
I might occasionally
kill out of anger
or to illustrate a point,
but I am not a Grim Reaper!
-(robe tightens in)
-Ow! O-o-oh!
I’ll reap!
I’ll reap already!
HOMER: Jasper...
your time has come!
Where’s the regular guy?
Where’s Doug?
Never mind.
I’m Death now.
(disappointed sigh)
I liked Doug.
Ahh!
"My Dad’s Job."
My dad’s job takes him
to all parts of the community.
He performs a valuable service
but is often misunderstood,
like a vulture
or the flesh-eating maggot.
Would anyone like to see
Mr. Simpson harvest a soul?
Yeah! I would!
Me! Me!
You said something
about a hot meal?
(clears throat)
(body slumps to floor)
(children cheering)
("Charge" plays)
Oh, man,
these seats suck.
Leave everything to me.
Pardon me, coming through,
rest in peace, you’re dead,
take a dirt nap,
feed the worms...
(rhythmic sputter)
CROWD:
Hey!
Oh!
Hmm.
Dad, were all those
people on the list?
-I don’t know.
-(thud)
Okay, who am I giving
the finger to today?
(gasps in horror)
Not this! Anything but this!
Uh...
What was that
first one again?
(suspenseful music)
(groaning):
Oh...
(piercing scream)
(chopping sounds)
♪♪
Okay, God, I bumped off
the love of my life,
according
to Your divine whim.
Now release me
from this ghastly vocation.
GOD: No!
Come on!
GOD:
All right.
Whoo-hoo!
GOD:
Hey, wait a minute!
This isn’t Marge.
This is her fat sister, Selma.
It’s Patty, chump!
(laughs)
(engine revving)
(screeching)
GOD:
Doggone it! I am too old
and too rich for this.
Thanks for not
killing me, Homie.
Here’s an extra
pork chop.
(chuckles)
I’m gonna not kill you
every week.
(all laugh)
(ringing)
Yello?
Sir, I’m honored
to inform you
that you’ve won
the Nobel Prize.
The Nobel Prize!
Finally.
So, uh, it’s for what,
my whole deal?
This is Professor John Frink,
isn’t it?
If I say "no,"
do I still win?
I’ll tell Professor Frink
he’s won.
(speaking Swedish)
PROF. FRINK:
Great Glayvin in a glass!
The Nobel Prize.
They must have awarded it to me
for my invention
of a hammer with a screwdriver
on the other end.
It’s mildly convenient.
Just for that?
It was a slow year, yes.
I only wish my dear father
were here to see me win.
Is there a problem
with your father?
Well, our relationship
was never great.
Mother used to say
we got along
like positrons
and anti-neutrinos.
(laughing):
Oh, yes... I’m a geek.
I was always
a disappointment to him.
You see, he was one of
those he-man scientists
who worked on
the atom bomb by day
and slept with
Marilyn Monroe
by night
and sold secrets to
the Russians at lunch.
The last time I saw him alive,
he was going to study sharks.
I don’t want to go
on this oceanographic
expedition, Father.
I get seasick
taking a shower.
Clean but nauseous.
"Clean but nauseous,"
with the rolling
and the heaving
and the you make me sick.
You’ve disgraced the name
of John Nerdlebaum Frink.
-But, Father, I...
-(boat horn blows)
(cries)
We never spoke again.
Well, where is he now?
Maybe I can help you two
patch up your differences.
Uh, you’ll need to patch up
more than that.
(gasps):
Did a shark do that?
Yes, he was testing out
a new blood-based
suntan lotion.
You know, now that I have
my hammer-screwdriver
I could reanimate him
without the needless
switching of tools.
That’s always tedious
and annoying.
(thunder)
(sizzling)
I’m alive!
With the breathing
and the tingling
and the what’s this radiator
where my pupik should be?
Oh, Papa,
you’re back!
Now, we had to replace
several vital organs
with machinery,
but that doesn’t make you
any less of a man.
Except you have no penis...
in the traditional sense.
So, what am I,
some kind of a tin can man
from Planet Tomorrow?
Sir, your son has brought you
into the 21st century.
It’s a lot like the 20th,
except everybody’s afraid and
the stock market is much lower.
Polly don’t like
that cracker.
I’m getting me
a real spleen,
and then I’m gonna vent it
on you, boychik.
Oy! Shoving.
It almost sounded like
he plans to tear organs
out of living people.
Well, that’s my dad.
You can’t stop him.
(humming)
Hey, 700 Club.
You look like
a healthy specimen.
Well, I did finish first
in the Walk For The Cure...
of homosexuality.
Say "ah," baby.
Ah...
(choking)
I’m dying!
And there’s Heaven.
But who’s that?
Confucius?
And Milton Berle?
Boy, have I been barking up
the wrong tree.
Nice posture.
Oh, thank you.
Mother always said
a curvy spine
is the devil’s
roller coaster.
Hey, you can’t have that.
(screams)
Lost your spine, huh?
You just keep finding
new ways to disappoint me.
("Stayin’ Alive"
by the Bee Gees plays)
There you are.
Have you stopped
to think about
who you’re hurting
with this rampage?
The people I’ve killed?
No. Your son!
On the biggest day of his life,
when he accepts the Nobel Prize,
you’re not gonna be there.
Oh, dear God.
I’ve let my organ lust
come between me and my son.
(cries)
But it’s not too late.
You can still fly
to Stockholm.
Well, it’d better be
first class.
Comic Book Guy’s ass
won’t fit in coach.
You may
keep my posterior,
just please return
the "Jabba the Butt" tattoo.
(blows whistle)
ANNOUNCER:
He explored the behavior
of individual molecules
in a chemical reaction.
She’s the sexy star of Alias.
Please welcome Nobel Laureate
Dr. Dudley Herschbach
and Emmy Nominee
Jennifer Garner.
(applause)
♪ She blinded me
with science ♪
You know,
Dr. Herschbach,
our jobs are actually
not that different.
I disagree.
Winner of the Nobel Prize
in Physics:
Professor John Frink.
(applause)
Hi. Thank you.
This is a tremendous
honor.
However, I can’t help
being somewhat disheartened
that my father has become
a marauding ghoul.
Not anymore, Son.
(gasps)
I’m here to accept
the Nobel Prize for stupid.
Can you forgive me?
Oh, good Glayvin, Dad.
You’ve made receiving
the Nobel Prize
the happiest day
of my life.
Oh, the hug is good.
This is what the Nobel Prize
is all about.
The science and the love
and that physics
we call quantum.
Ain’t that right,
people?
(applause)
What a great crowd.
You all have such
big hearts
and such big brains...
with large, juicy dripping
with knowledge heads.
(gasps)
That’s it,
I’m going smorgasbord
on these Poindexters.
(audience gasps)
And I thought
Halle Berry went
nuts during her
acceptance speech.
I wish I was Death again.
That was cool.
Every brain unlocks more secrets
of the universe.
Muffins are surprisingly
high in calories.
The pyramids were actually
built by Sears.
He’s right.
It all checks out.
(screaming)
(groans)
This is more violent
than the Hip Hop Awards.
You’ve got to stop
your father.
Yes, but how?
He’s 63 years old...
pressure points here and here...
room temperature is
22 degrees Celsius...
Yes, this should
just about do it.
Balzac!
(faint groan)
Oh, Father,
you’re dying again.
But I can bring you back
to life, sir.
Son, it doesn’t take
five brains in your head
to know that’s a bad idea.
You saw I’d become a monster
and you stopped me like a man.
I’m proud of you.
And now it’s time for me
to go to hell.
Ow, ooh, ooh, ow, oy,
oy, ooh, ow, dead.
(crying)
This is the most exciting
Nobel Prize ceremony ever.
I disagree.
It must be tough
to win the Nobel Prize
and lose your father
on the same day.
Oh, I didn’t really
lose my father.
Thanks to my latest invention,
the soul catcher.
Let’s bring it out
and look at it.
FRINK SENIOR’S VOICE:
I may be a soul,
but I’m hungry.
Can you throw in
a little matzo?
Maybe a nice piece of fish.
Why of course,
Father.
Allow me to satisfy
your Hebraic desires.
That’s a good shmendeleh.
Oh, I’ve waited so long
to hear you say that.
What does it mean?
Is it dirty?
(ticking)
Ooh, baby!
Did I find something
to throw out today.
If you like space
in the attic,
are you gonna be happy.
Cool!
Comics from the ’70s!
BART:
Superman vs. Patty Hearst,
Evel Knievel
Jumps The Jackson 5,
Batman and Rhoda...
(gasps)
Check out these ads!
Let see, X-Ray Gum...
(gasps)
Cool.
Milhouse, do you have
your change purse?
MILHOUSE:
Always!
(doorbell rings)
Here you go, son.
"To stop time, click watch."
(ticking)
(ticking stops
Wow, she looks like
a background character
in a Hanna Barbera cartoon.
"To restart time,
click watch again."
What the...?!
Lisa,
that’s a filthy habit.
(chuckles maniacally)
If we’re both
touching the watch,
neither of us
will be affected.
Do you realize
what this means?
Yeah...
but you say it first.
We can do anything we want!
Let’s get really far
ahead on our homework!
Wait till
the other kids see
we’re already
on the red unit
of Adventures In Reading.
(moans)
SKINNER:
Due to budget cuts,
music class will now have
a two-drink minimum.
Cranapple juice
only counts as one. And...
(gasps)
My slacks!
They’ve descended!
(laughing)
(quiet giggle)
What the...?
Ooh.
D-oh!
I can’t go on.
(whimpering, moaning)
(crying)
Haw...
Haw?!
(laughing)
(watch ticking)
People,
Springfield is in crisis.
Fingers have been
shoved up noses,
pants have been
pulled down, and...
Mayors... have... been...
repeatedly...
humiliated. Dammit!
(angry grumbling)
I thought
our mysterious pranksters
might be here tonight,
so I covered the meeting hall
with ultraviolet powder.
Behold the perpetrators!
(electrical buzzing)
(all gasp)
It was those guys!
Come! Let us kill them
before learning
of the magical secret
which they possess.
(angry yelling)
Oh, that was close.
Bart,
look at the watch!
Milhouse,
we broke the watch!
Do you realize
what this means?
Yeah...
but you say it first.
(clicking)
Oh, man.
Things are stuck
like this forever.
Well,
I couldn’t be happier.
I’m the second coolest kid
on earth!
(silly humming)
Actually, I guess
we can do anything we want
and no one will stop us.
I’m gonna play
naked basketball!
No, you’re not.
The family looks good.
Thanks.
I just washed them.
Oh, that keeps happening.
Can I punch
Oscar de la Hoya
for a while?
Just keep it
above the belt.
(grunting)
(sighs)
You know, Milhouse,
I thought I’d love
eating only frosting
and giving
the pope a wedgie.
But I miss being a regular kid
in the real world,
getting a hug
from my mom...
Yeah, I thought I’d be happy
with my parents back together,
but it’s kind of hollow.
All right.
It says here we can learn
watch repair in eight
one-hour lessons.
Boy, that took forever.
Yeah, well I work better
in a structured environment.
Here goes nothing-- Wait!
When people see
all the stuff we did,
they’re gonna kill us.
Yeah,
and I can’t run too fast
after 15 years of eating
nothing but Gummi Worms.
I’m gonna quit tomorrow,
I swear!
What we need
is a scapegoat.
Okay,
acting natural and...
(angry yelling)
To repeat
what I said a moment ago:
"You are so dead."
(grunts and groans)
Dios Mio!
This kid is fun to hit!
(whistling)
Mmm. Why is Bart so tall
and shaggy?
Just one of
life’s mysteries.
Like, why is my nose
jammed full of army men?
Oh, come on,
don’t you get it?
Bart stopped time
with his magic stopwatch.
Jealous much?
Why can’t I tinker with
the fabric of existence?
Let the baby
have her bottle.
Huh. What happens
if I press this button?
Lisa!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
(growls)
Okay, that’s good.
Stop there.
♪ Put your glad rags on
and join me, hon ♪
♪ We’ll have some fun
when the clock strikes one ♪
♪ We’re gonna rock around
the clock tonight. ♪
♪♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
(screaming)
Enhanced by Fotokem