CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(anime music)
Happy Thanksgiving
from the entire
Channel 6 family,
including Kent Brockman,
who’s contractually permitted
to replace himself
with a cardboard cutout.
The real Kent is
in a rehab clinic.
We all wish him
the best... again.
I love the holiday season.
See you in spring, toes!
("Thus Spake Zarathustra"
playing)
And from all of us, best wishes
for a joyous holiday season.
Now, in the spirit of
the season, start shopping.
And for every dollar
of Krusty merchandise you buy,
I will be nice to a sick kid.
For legal purposes, sick kids
may include hookers with a cold
(chuckling)
♪ It’s the most wonderful
time of the year... ♪
(loud squawking)
♪ With the kids jingle belling
♪ And everyone telling you
be of good cheer ♪
♪ It’s the most wonderful
time of the year... ♪
(growling)
(snarling)
CARL:
Hey, Homer.
I’m your Secret Santa.
Merry Christmas, big guy.
Oh, my God!
A DVD player.
And the first season
of Magnum P.I.
with commentary
by John Hillerman.
Apparently, working in
Hawaii was a pleasure.
Oh Carl, you remembered
I like TV. Muah, muah, muah.
Who’s my Secret Santa?
Uh, I think it’s Homer.
Oh yes, I am...
Your present is right
in the other room.
(vending machine
dollar slot whirring)
Come on machine,
take my dollar.
Fine.
We’ll play it your way.
(glass shattering)
Here you go, Lenny.
May the spirit of Retsyn
be with you
all year long.
God bless God.
Amen.
This gift stinks.
Homer, you’re the most
selfish man I know.
Oh, come on...
Mr. Burns is way more selfish.
That evil old bone bag...
smelling of death...
nose like a vulture...
followed everywhere
by that kiss-ass Smithers...
Yes, that describes
Kathy in Personnel to a tee.
(shrieks)
All right, everyone,
it’s time
for your Christmas "boni."
Everyone gets a $5
cafeteria voucher...
(angry grumbling)
And for your boy,
a confectioner’s card
featuring a current
base-baller.
It’s that rookie
from the New York Nine.
HOMER:
Joe DiMaggio?
Yes... it seems they’ve
started letting ethnics
into the big leagues.
Oh look, it’s Kathy.
How are things
in personnel?
Excellent.
I need money for Christmas.
Can I get anything for this
Joe DiMaggio baseball card?
It’s kind of old.
I’m sorry, but I’m afraid
your card is only worth...
everything I’ve got!
Everything!
Take it!
Oh, no. I’ve smudged it
with nacho fingers.
I must deftly lick it off.
-Deftly.
-Thank you.
Freak.
And now we return
to the 1986 holiday classic...
Christmas
with the California Prunes
(playing soulful sax solo)
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ O pruny night ♪
♪ The stars are
sweetly wrinkled ♪
♪ We are the fruit that your
grandmother loves ♪
♪ Yeah... ♪
This is offensive
to Christians and prunes.
HOMER:
Hey, everybody,
We’re going shopping at the
Springfield Heights Promenade.
(gasps)
That’s the rich people’s mall.
Let’s shop till we droop.
I think that’s "drop."
That’s a very
violent image, Lisa.
♪ Silver and gold,
silver and gold ♪
♪ Means so much more
when I see... ♪
First we’ll buy gifts
for each other.
Then we’ll spend the rest
of the cash on a Christmas tree
so large, its absence
from the forest
will cause mudslides
and flooding.
(cheering)
Cool, a toy store.
Awesome. I’m blasting
all the state capitals.
Take that, Salem, Oregon.
Wait a minute,
this game is educational.
That’ll teach you to teach me.
Hmm. I think these are
my Homie’s size.
Excuse me, can I
ask you a favor?
Perfect. I’ll take it.
Um, we’ll do that.
Stand back
when you open it.
Doing pretty good so far.
A key ring for Marge,
key ring for Bart...
(gasps)
Ooh, that thing for me.
Oh, God,
it’s so unnecessary.
You have excellent taste.
This is our finest
talking astrolabe.
It also comes with a notepad and
a pen that works upside down.
I’m upside down so much.
Oh, if I buy this, I won’t
have anything left
for a Christmas tree...
Today is the birthday
of comedienne Margaret Cho.
That’s the birthday
I’m always forgetting.
I must have it.
What a mall.
Can we get our big
Christmas tree now?
Uh, sure, you know it.
(nervous chuckle)
The biggest tree from
the finest lot in town.
-(honking)
-Stupid jerk!
Dad, I don’t like the looks
of this neighborhood.
It’s fine.
Now everyone just relax,
lock your doors,
don’t make eye contact with
anyone, and listen to the radio.
(man with Southern accent)
Now let’s downshift
into the holiday spirit
with "Christmas Convoy."
♪ A star shone bright
that silent night ♪
♪ Ninety miles out
of manger-town ♪
♪ Haulin’ gold and myrhh
and frankincense ♪
♪ Three kings
put the hammer down ♪
♪ ’Cuz we got
Christmas convoy ♪
♪ Ain’t she
a beautiful thing? ♪
♪ We gotta roll
this truckin’ convoy ♪
♪ To see the newborn king ♪
♪ Con-voy ♪
♪ Ten-four, King of the Jews ♪
Gorgeous, huh?
And quite the bargain.
Isn’t it kind of dry?
Oh, it just needs a little love.
Why do the things
I love always burn?
Isn’t it sufficient.
I thought we had enough money
for a good tree.
Homer, is there something
you’re not telling us?
ASTROLABE:
It is 6:31 p.m.
in Montreal.
The moon is waxing tonight.
What’s that?
Uh... Whoo-hoo.
Maggie’s talking.
Hmm...
You wasted our money
on something extravagant
for yourself.
There’s a trickle-down
theory here.
If I’m happy, I’m less abusive
to the rest of you.
No, Dad. This time you
were just plain selfish.
I am not returnable.
(sobbing)
I will be testing my smoke
alarm for the next three hours.
(loud beeping)
(loud sobbing)
This is even sadder than
Tuesdays With Morrie.
Come on, Marge, I’m not
the only selfish person.
You have to get your hair
done at "Supercuts."
I guess regular "Cuts" just
isn’t good enough for you.
You just don’t
get it, do you?
Christmas is a time
to think of others,
but today you showed you
only care about yourself.
That’s not true.
I cared what you thought
once you found out.
You can sleep
on the couch tonight.
Can’t you yell at me now
and get it over with?
No. I’m going to parcel
my anger out
over the next
few days and weeks,
jabbing at you just when
you seem the most content.
(groans)
I don’t need her.
I’ve got you, Astrolabe.
ASTROLABE: Columbia’s
main export is coffee.
Exactly.
(man on television):
Now back to The Year
Santa Got Lost,
starring Jimmy Stewart
as the voice of Mr. Mailman.
Santa was in an awful pickle.
Beatniks had given drugs
to the reindeer,
and they were no darn good.
So Santa placed a call
to Secretary of Defense
Melvin Laird...
Jimmy Stewart as a puppet
is just wrong.
And now back to Mr. McGrew’s
Christmas Carol.
Mr. McGrew. I love that
blind, senile old man.
(knocking)
I can’t find
my way back to the home.
I heard you
the first five times.
(moans)
You work on Christmas
or you’re out of a job.
Is that clear, Cratchett?
Sir, I’m over here.
Ooh-hoo, I’m sorry.
Pardon me, ma’am.
I see you’re expecting.
May I listen
to the baby’s heartbeat?
(screams)
(laughing)
Oh, McGrew, once again
you’ve mistaken
something for something.
(meowing)
McGrew, I am the ghost
of Christmas past.
You’re so selfish, your
fiancée is about to leave you.
I don’t need love.
I have money.
Sweet, sweet money.
Yes, indeed.
Oh, my God. It’s like looking
at a cartoon version of myself.
Spirit, surely
there is some time
to reform my selfish ways.
Come on, Death.
Leave McGrew alone.
Take Tiny Tim.
(screaming)
No!
"Unloved by Al"? No!
"Unloved by all."
No!
(Homer moaning, whimpering)
(moaning)
I’ll be good.
Dad? Are you okay?
(gasps)
Children, children,
what day is this?
It’s Saturday,
December 6th.
Thank God!
There’s still four more days
till Christmas.
I have time
to reform my ways.
I just saw the greatest cartoon
of all time.
It was about a miser
who was visited by three ghosts
at Christmas.
And get this:
he learns a lesson!
Dad, what you saw
was A Christmas Carol.
It was written by
Charles Dickens 160 years ago.
Yeah, TV writers have been
milkin’ that goat for years.
Reform, Ebenezer Urkel.
You have alienated
everyone who loved you.
Did I do that?
Report, Mr. Sulu.
Captain, there appears
to be some sort of spirit
from an Earth holiday past.
Mr. Scott,
fire photon torpedoes.
It’s no use, Captain!
He’s showin’ visions of me
future... God, I’m so fat!
I said fire!
That last one looked
kind of good.
Marge,
TV and nightmares
have joined forces
to teach me a lesson.
From now on, I will
stop being selfish
and start being good.
In fact, I’ll be
the nicest man in town.
You’ve made that promise
before.
Yes, but this time
I’m sober... ish.
Well, the hobos sure will
appreciate our old clothes
and lima beans.
No need, Flanders.
I’ve already given them
my old clothes.
(mumbling)
Good-lookin’ group.
Oh, gee,
looks like this town
has a Good Sam log-jam.
These pants smell worse
than my old pants.
You’re welcome.
Listen, Lenny,
I know I was a pretty bad
Secret Santa,
so I wanted
to make it up to you.
Wow, a photo cube
with pictures of us!
And I filed down
all the sharp corners.
See, your eye
is completely safe.
Oh, wow,
it just stings a little!
(softly gasps)
Marge, do you want
this last pork chop?
I’ve dreamed of the day
you’d say that!
(happily sobs)
Oh, your thoughtfulness
tastes so good.
(sobs)
And tears are
the sweetest sauce.
All right, now you’re
starting to creep me out.
(organ playing softly)
(grunting)
Come on.
Why don’t you just take
my blood?
(whooshing)
Yes, I’m old.
Oh, very nice, Ned.
But, uh, I’m afraid you’re
a distant second this week.
HOMER: I’m not looking
for glory or wealth.
I’m just buying that stairway
to heaven Jesus sang of.
That was Led Zeppelin.
(scoffs)
Get back to your bong, hippie.
(chuckles)
Daddy, are you jealous
of Brother Homer?
Well, maybe just
a tad, Todd.
I’m jealous of girls ’cause
they get to wear dresses.
One problem
at a time, boy.
Homie, I’m so proud.
You changed more than
I could have imagined.
You’re even covering
your mouth when you burp.
Just like the Pope.
(loud burp)
Being unselfish
is a natural high,
like hiking or paint thinner.
And here’s another act
of Christian charity
I pulled out of my butt.
I built a skating rink
for the whole town.
(groans)
Activate the cloaking device!
Hm. Oh, I’m so depressed.
Engage candy bar.
Thank you.
♪ Here come sandwiches,
here come sandwiches ♪
♪ Right down boozy bum lane ♪
♪ Brother Ned’s
got cheese on bread ♪
♪ And a side order of shame ♪
♪ Bells... ♪
Where the H-E-C-K is everybody?
(gasps)
Here’s your skates.
Oh, you’ll have to
take off those boots.
Those are my feet.
Ew.
Oh, for the love of puppies.
Homer, you’re the nicest guy
in town.
Ha-ha.
Your position
has been usurped!
Usurped! You heard me!
Ha-ha, you’re sad
at Christmas!
This just in:
Santa Claus is dead.
(all scream)
Or he might as well be, because
there’s an even fatter man
who’s holding families
at nice-point:
Homer Simpson, seen here
in this retouched photo.
Ooh! That Homer
just burns my waffles.
Pain is the cleanser!
(doorbell rings)
Excuse me,
my car broke down.
Why, I’ll give you a jump.
I’ll rotate your tires.
I’ll even fold up
that map for you.
I know they can be a dickens
of a doozy.
Back off, creep!
I was looking
for Homer Simpson’s house.
(groans)
That tears it.
I’ll show Homer.
I’m gonna be the nicest man
this world has ever seen.
B...
I said "man," not "man-God."
Keep your pants on.
Here you go,
Principal Skinner,
Mrs. Skinner.
You’re actually giving
everyone in town
a Christmas present?
What’s your angle,
pervert?
Oh, my angle is
givin’ in this world,
livin’ in the next.
But how can you afford all this
on a widower’s salary?
Well, actually,
I picked up some extra cash
renting out my house
to a fraternity.
(music playing,
people talking)
ROD: Stay out
of our medicine cabinet!
Pathetic Flanders.
Thinking he can buy people’s
love with thoughtful gifts.
Cool. Mr. Flanders gave me
a Krusty-brand Operation game.
(buzzer)
Oh, you just tweezered
my wang.
I’ll show Flanders.
I’m gonna get everyone a car.
What’s that one good
American car?
Dad, you don’t have
to out-do Mr. Flanders.
Just remember the spirit
of the season.
Uh... is it despair?
Actually, most people now
feel Christmas has gotten
too materialistic.
In fact, as a Buddhist,
I believe people would be a lot
happier without presents.
Hmm. You’ve given me
a lot to think about.
LISA: People would be a lot
happier without presents.
Presents are material goods,
and attachment to material goods
kills the soul.
(police siren blaring)
I’m not going to jail again!
(tires squeal)
I’ve got it!
When everyone’s asleep,
I’ll take away their presents.
Then they’ll be happy.
Thanks, Buddha.
I got your badge number.
You better hope
I never get out.
♪ You’re a hero, Homer J ♪
♪ You’re as crafty as a skunk ♪
♪ They’ll thank you
in the morning ♪
♪ For stealing Flander’s junk ♪
♪ Homer J... ♪
♪ You’re a double-bacon
genius-burger ♪
♪ And just a little drunk ♪
Now to hear the joyous sound
of people waking up on Christmas
to discover they have
no presents.
LENNY:
Hey, where’s my presents?
DOLPH: Some jerk
stole Christmas!
Ho, I’ve been robbed!
Man, so this is how it feels.
I’d better see my shrink...
and rob his ass.
Someone snuck in
and took our presents.
(gasps)
Do you think
it was Papa?
I wouldn’t put it past him.
He stole my gold tooth
the night he left.
He didn’t leave,
he went to the store.
And when he comes back
I’ll wave those Pop-Tarts
right in your face.
They don’t sound happy,
but here comes a mob
shaking their fists
in gratitude.
(all yelling)
Give back our presents,
stupid man!
Your behavior, it’s like--
it’s like, not sanctioned
by any governing body.
You’re like, wild.
Um, shouldn’t you all be
singing carols or something?
(groaning)
(all yelling)
Stop!
Friends,
what Homer did was wrong.
But, uh,
I’ve been thinking.
Maybe I was just as wrong
to give you those gifts.
-(groaning)
-Hey!
Wait a minute, everyone!
There’s your Christmas,
up there.
(all gasp)
It’s a miracle!
That’s my last flare.
Somebody’d better come soon.
(howling)
Oh, thank goodness--
rescue dogs!
(growling)
FLANDERS:
"And the angel said
unto them, ’Fear not,
for, behold, I bring you good
tidings of great joy,
which shall be
to all people...’"
QUIMBY:
Stop that!
You can’t pray
on city property.
Let’s just say that on this day,
a million years ago,
a dude was born who most of us
think was magic,
but others don’t,
and that’s cool.
But we’re probably right.
Amen.
ALL: Amen.
And now, I think the only thing
left to do is
return all your gifts! Ned?
It’d be my pleasure, Homer!
(all happily yelling)
Oh, oh, joy.
Let’s see what we’ve,
uh, got here.
Oh, it’s a new brassiere.
But I don’t even have them--
but okay, I’ll make pretend.
What a great Christmas.
Not even Moe’s annual suicide
attempt can ruin it.
I ain’t got all day,
drama queen.
Get it over with.
I will,
and then you’ll all wish
you was nicer to me.
You... ah... who am I kidding?
I ain’t gonna jump.
Oh!
♪ Hark the herald angels sing ♪
♪ Glory to the newborn king ♪
♪ Peace on Earth
and mercy mild ♪
♪ God and sinner reconciled... ♪
Today is the birthday
of our Lord Jesus Christ
and singer Barbara Mandrell.
Merry Christmas.
♪ ...Above the skies ♪
♪ Hark the herald angels sing ♪
♪ Glory to the newborn king ♪
NELSON: Ha-ha.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem