CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme song plays)
D-ohh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
It’s too nice a day to be
outside doing chores.
Come in and watch TV.
Whoo-hoo!
Mom finally stopped caring.
Don’t go inside--
it’s a trap!
Yeah, she must have some kind
of super-chore in there.
Like getting the rat
out of Maggie’s room!
I’m not fooling around,
people!
Park your keisters
in front of that TV!
Now!
(screaming)
No!
(gasps)
(Homer screaming)
This counts as a bath!
(gurgling scream)
(click)
(chuckles)
The irrepressible
hundred-year-old skydiver
will be buried as soon
as his body is found.
Now it’s time
for the Channel 6
"Oops Patrol"!
This week one eagle-eyed viewer
spotted this hilarious headline.
(chuckling):
This week’s "Oops Patrol"
T-shirt goes to...
(fanfare plays)
Whom? Whom?
...Mrs. Marge Simpson
of Springfield.
Ta-dah!
Mom made the Oops Patrol!
Hot damn!
Bart, you’re not at school.
Don’t swear!
(humming)
What an amusing T-shirt,
Marge.
(chuckles)
I’ll trade you for a tote bag
that says "PROZAC."
No, thanks. I’m wearing
my cure for depression.
Come on, give me
that shirt.
I’ll put you at the top
of the heart transplant list.
My heart is fine.
It could always be
a little better.
Honey, this is your
moment in the sun,
and I couldn’t be more
pleased for your happiness.
Why was I born?
(straining)
Mmm!
Oh, T-shirt, bless the loom
that fruited you.
(gasps in shock):
Homer!
(straining)
Win your own T-shirt!
(annoyed groan)
HOMER:
Got to win a T-shirt.
Okay.
Get ready to laugh.
"Cranford Man Missing."
What’s he missing?
His pants? A train?
Give me a break!
Too soon, huh?
All right.
"Drought Threatens
To Turn West
Into Dessert."
Yum, yum.
I think I’d like some
whipped cream on my Wyoming.
Dad, the word’s "desert,"
and those farmers are suffering.
From what,
too much hot fudge?
Huh?
(weak laugh)
Come on, Bart,
show me some love.
Don’t drag me down
with you, old man.
Aah.
(crackling)
This is what happens when I go
for six hours without sleep.
HOMER:
(forced laugh)
No.
"For sale, Ford Festiva."
I’ll put that in the "maybes."
(dejected sigh)
I got to get that T-shirt.
(surprised gasp)
"World’s Biggest Pizza"!
Oh, my God!
Marge, wake up!
The newspaper
is talking to me!
Oh, relax.
I’m sure it’s just
your brain going crazy.
I wish!
Look at this headline.
Someone,
or something, knows
I love oversized food
and short, punchy articles.
So, they hid a message in
the first letter of each line.
See: "HOMER, MEET ME
4th STREET OVERPASS, MIDNITE."
Wait a minute.
This is today’s paper.
That meeting is tonight!
Don’t tell me
you’re actually going.
Marge, I don’t know
what this is,
but sometimes you’ve just
got to go with your gut.
You always
go with your gut.
This time, why don’t
you listen to your brain?
All right, I will.
(ukulele playing)
That’s why I don’t
listen to my brain.
And away we go!
(worried grunt)
HOMER:
Psst!
Hey, pal.
Hey, buddy.
Wake up.
Want to go on an adventure
with your old man?
(yawns)
No.
You have no choice.
There’s coffee
in the thermos.
(groans)
This is boring.
Can’t we go home?
This overpass
smells like urine.
They all do.
Fresh urine.
Hey, the bathroom’s
a block away.
-(zips up fly)
-WOMAN: Homer Simpson!
(gasps, screams)
(screams)
(screaming)
WOMAN: Aw, still
my little crybaby.
I’ll save you, Dad!
Ka-ra-te!
Grandma!
Oh, Bart, are you still
a little hell-raiser?
Yes’m.
Mom, you’re back!
Just like you were
back before,
then you left me again.
I love you so much,
but it’s so hard for me
to trust you.
Oh, what the heck.
Give me a hug, you.
Homer, you’re
hugging a bum.
I know! I’m working
my way up to you.
Hey! Give me back my wine!
(chuckles sheepishly)
(electrical buzzing)
Sorry about all
the cloak-and-dagger, Homer,
but the government
is still after me
for what I did
in the ’60s.
They’re probably tapping
your phones
(whispering):
and reading your mail.
(scoffs)
I think the government
has better things to do
than to read my mail.
Most people write letters
to movie stars.
This Simpson guy
writes to movies.
"Dear Die Hard , you rock.
Especially when that guy
was on the roof.
P.S. Do you know Mad Max ?"
To reach you, I called up my
friends in the liberal media
and planted that story
about the giant pizza.
You sure know me, Mom.
Pizza was the first food
he choked on.
Aww.
So, why are you back in town?
I saw this macaroni
pencil-holder Homer made me,
and I realized how much
I missed him.
I made this when I was five.
I had to do something--
your pencils were
all over the place.
Hey, it was the ’60s.
(all gasp)
Is that fugitive radical
Mona Simpson?
Yeah, and that’s Tokyo Rose
mopping the floor.
Hey, Joe, your girlfriend
sleeps with Tyrone Power.
Chief, I think
we’ve got a match here.
All right,
let’s check it out.
But if you’re wrong,
you and Lou
have to kiss each other.
Chief, I checked
with the union.
You can only
do that once.
Aah.
Cora, is there a back
way out of here?
Not for someone
who tips 9%.
Fine.
Right through there,
Santa Claus.
(tires squealing)
Mom, I swear on your
eventual grave,
I will never, ever,
let the police get
their hands on you.
Uh-oh.
Ha!
You guys are damn lucky.
All you destroyed were bricks,
mortar and attorneys.
Remember me...
as a drain on society.
(sharp groan)
(handcuffs snap shut)
Captured ’60s radical
Mona J. Simpson
goes on trial today
on decades-old charges
of sabotaging the C. Montgomery
Burns Germ Warfare Lab.
For those of you too young
to remember the ’60s,
here’s our stock montage.
(Jimi Hendrix playing
"All Along the Watchtower")
♪♪
You bet your sweet bippy.
What a shrill,
pointless decade.
During her years
on the lam,
Simpson led an exemplary life,
working as a crossing guard,
oral historian,
reader for the blind,
listener for the deaf,
and reacher
for the short.
Yet, local villain
Montgomery Burns--
seen here terrorizing children
in a 19th century woodcut--
insists that
she stand trial.
Kent, I want everyone
in your radio picture audience
to know that this woman
is a menace to decent people
and germ warriors
everywhere.
(snoring)
(gasps)
End communication.
-(gavel pounding)
-Now, Lisa, would you agree
that your grandmother
is a sweet, harmless woman
who could hardly be considered
a menace to society?
Oh, definitely.
If you ask me, she’s far less
dangerous than Bart.
If it please the court,
I would like to go
ape on my sister.
I object!
Judge, sidebar?
Very well.
Judge, do you have
a little sister?
Yes.
She used to call me
Fatty-boomalatty.
I’ll allow an Indian burn.
Thank you, Your Honor.
LISA: Ow!
Your Honor,
can you please focus
on the case at hand?
I’m sorry,
my wife left me this morning.
Now, I’m not a man
who’s good with words...
You got to say something,
she’s looking
at 20 years,
and my legal license
expires in 15 minutes.
I barely know my mother.
And every time I see her,
she’s taken away again.
And when a man doesn’t have
his mother, he winds up like me.
ALL: Aw!
I mean, I’m due back
in this same courtroom
three times today.
Hell, I torched a blood bank.
One cookie my ass!
Please, please,
give me back my mommy.
(all sobbing)
Your Honor, there is no way we
can find this defendant guilty.
(gasps)
Although I will miss
the jury room cold cuts.
And the Quality Inn more than
lived up to its name.
Case dismissed!
(cheering)
Business center,
workout room,
an honor bar
I was honored to use...
That’s enough.
And Peggy
in the coffee shop,
what a pistol.
A mere nod in her direction,
and the refill was in the mug.
The jets in the whirlpool
anticipated my every move.
When it was working.
And three dollars
for a local call?
They should be the ones
on trial!
-(cameras shutter)
-(reporters chattering)
Oh, Mom, I’m so happy.
I never want to
let you go.
Mom, I never want to
I’m not your mother.
Look, lady, just keep hugging
till we get to Mexico.
Mother...
Go hug your floozy.
Mother,
she’s right here.
She knows I’m kidding.
(whispers loudly):
I’m not kidding.
HOMER: Mmm.
Curse that
"Groovy Granny"!
This is America.
Justice should
favor the rich!
Sir, maybe you can
use a few huffs from
your ether bottle.
Oh, man, that’s good "E."
Well, now that
I’m free,
I intend to be a better
mother to my son.
Whoo-hoo!
I can be a little boy again!
A boy who gets
some on the side.
Oh, baby.
Now you’re free
to come back to me.
Dad, you testified
against her.
I read a book
that said women like jerks.
PAUL SIMON:
♪ But the mother and child
reunion... ♪
(knocking)
♪ Is only a motion away ♪
♪ Oh, little darling
of mine ♪
♪ I can’t for the life
of me ♪
♪ Remember a sadder day ♪
Look, Mom, look,
I’m riding by myself!
-(horn honks)
-(screaming)
(grunting and groaning)
(panting)
Homer, this really
isn’t necessary.
You weren’t around
for the birth of
your grandson,
and I want you to see it.
Wah, wah, wah.
Ain’t I cute?
You owe me a dirt bike.
Hey, guys,
I brought my mom.
Lenny Leonard?
I haven’t seen you
since you were this high.
I can jump off
the high dive.
Carl Carlson.
I remember when you,
Lenny and Stevie MacGregor
were like
the Three Musketeers.
Yeah, poor Stevie.
They never found
his head.
Mrs. Simpson,
when you took off,
you left a hole
in Homer’s heart
that he’s been trying to fill
with alcohol for 20 years...
God bless you.
Welcome
to your room, Mom.
I want you
to stay here forever.
Homer, it’s perfect.
Doesn’t this armoire
belong to Mr. Flanders?
You stole this entire room
from Ned Flander’s house.
Oh, well,
you snooze, you lose.
But can I have
my photo albums back?
Now get out
of my house!
And so in the spirit
of fence-mending
and grudge-not-bearing,
I hereby rename
the Burns Germ Warfare Lab
The Grandma Simpson
Peace Museum
and Kid-teractive
Learnatorium.
(cheering)
Grandma Simpson,
will you be the first
to sign the museum’s
guest book?
It’d be a real pleasure.
You know, when
I was on the run,
I always had to
sign a fake name,
like when I visited
a state park...
Indeed.
How about a national park?
Why, yes.
I’ve got it all
on this dictabelt.
Move in, boys.
(guns cocking)
What’s going on?
Supplying
false information
on a national park register
is a federal offense,
which you’ve committed
at every national park,
from Acadia to Zion.
You’re going away
for a long time, Mrs. Simpson.
Or should I call you...
Anita Bong-Hitt?
No! I can’t lose
my mother again!
(sobbing)
Don’t take her away!
(continued sobbing)
Stop messing with him.
The man lost his mother.
Just one more time.
(chuckling):
Okay.
It is pretty funny.
Aw.
(gasps)
(sobbing)
JOHN LENNON/PLASTIC ONE BAND:
♪ Mother ♪
♪ You had me ♪
♪ But I never had you ♪
♪ I wanted you ♪
♪ You didn’t want me... ♪
Dad, I’m just as sad
as you are.
What happened to Grandma
is an outrage.
How do you figure?
She was acquitted,
then they put her back in jail
on a technicality.
You’re right.
People should only be let
out of jail on technicalities.
Well, they’re
transferring Grandma
to a federal prison
tomorrow.
I say we hit them
where they live--
with a candlelight vigil.
Candlepin Bowling?
That’s a great idea!
We’ll play right after
I break your grandmother
out of prison.
(chair screeches)
ALL:
♪ I fought the law ♪
♪ And the law won ♪
Now just the innocent!
♪ I fought the law ♪
♪ And the law won ♪
Now just
the really innocent!
(laughter)
I hope this bus ride
never ends... (chuckles)
’cause I’m getting executed
when I get off.
Okay, boy,
flip through those
highway warnings
till we find one
that’ll stop that bus.
Next.
Pass.
(groans):
Boring.
Aw.
Ha ha! Loser!
Geez, pal.
-(tires screech)
-Would you look at that.
(coughing)
Homer! What on earth
are you doing?
-(buzzing)
-Mom, I love you.
I can’t let you
go to prison.
Who’s the wheel man,
Granny?
It’s my son, Homer.
OTHERS:
Aw...
Oh, isn’t he
darling.
He’s a big one!
(embarrassed chuckling):
Oh... st... stop it.
Take care, ladies.
I’m sure
you can make it back
to the prison
on your own.
ALL: We will.
You’re all right,
donut breath.
You’re like the son
I never killed.
(tires screech)
Mom, I’m gonna hide you
where there’s no one
around for miles--
Disney’s California
Adventure.
(sirens wailing)
BOTH: D-ohh!
Homer, get out now,
and no one will ever know
you were involved.
No! You’re my mother,
and I won’t leave you.
If you stay here,
you’ll be abandoning
your family
the way
I abandoned you.
(chuckles):
Yeah...
That did mess me up
pretty bad.
But I’m not gonna leave you.
I see you’ve made
your choice.
I love you, Homer.
(electronic zapping)
-(grunts)
-(horn honks)
Oh, that’s lucky.
Aah! Oh, brambles!
Briars!
Nettles! Thorns!
(sirens wailing)
Granny to the Man,
Granny to the Man.
This is the Man.
I think it’d be a gas
if you turned that
magic bus around
and kept on truckin’
to our pig pad.
I don’t know what you’re saying,
but I am not turning back.
Then listen to me, lady,
the only way
you’re getting off this mountain
is in a box.
Or a funicular.
What about
a hot air balloon?
Yeah, pipe down,
Jules Verne.
Go Mom! You can do it!
No...!
There’s still air
in that bus,
so for the next five minutes,
this is a rescue mission.
(explosion)
Make that
a salvage mission.
(loud rumbling)
Okay, everyone take
some free time,
and we’ll see you tomorrow
at 10:00.
Grandma, you’ll always
be an inspiration to me.
You taught me a criminal
can evade the law
well into old age.
Thanks
for the meatloaf recipe.
I claim it as my own.
Mona, I’ll always remember
raspberry trolley cars,
because my mind is shot.
Your last act as a mom
was to make me a better dad.
But at least now
I’ll never lose you again.
-(tires screeching)
-Whoa! Look out!
Oh!
Homer, it’s 2:00
in the morning.
I couldn’t sleep because
I thought there might be a sign
of my mom
in one of these articles.
They never did
find her body.
Then what was
in the coffin?
Last week’s garbage--
I missed the pickup date.
But it doesn’t matter,
because my mom is alive! See?
"I, M, O..."
"...K."
Get it? "I am okay."
Okay, Homie,
if it makes you feel better,
I think your mom’s
all right, too.
Hey, as long as
we’re thinking about her,
Grandma’s still alive.
Come on, big guy.
This'll help you get to sleep.
MONA:
Homer, your mother loves you.
I escaped from the bus
the moment before
it plunged off the cliff.
I then hitched a ride
from a nice young couple.
We had lunch
at a lovely diner.
They had clam chowder,
Rhode Island style.
I never knew
there was such a thing.
And the crackers
kept on comin’.
(theme song plays)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh.
Enhanced by Fotokem