CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme song plays)
D-ohh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(Polorid moto sound)
Oh, boy, Casino Night!
Finally, they’ll teach our kids
the dangers of
doubling down on a six.
I really
shouldn’t be here--
I have a problem
with games of chance.
I played Candyland
with Maggie
and ended up throwing vodka
in her face.
Aw, Marge, I bet you’ve gotten
that out of your system.
Bet... system...
betting system!
God is telling me to gamble!
-Hey!
Deal! Hit me! Hit me! Hit me!
Busted!
(squeals)
Welcome to Springfield
Elementary Casino Night.
My fee for this evening
goes to victims of my
criminal recidivism.
So, relax, have fun
and please, God,
don’t piss me off.
Congratulations.
Mr. Student Body President.
Your Casino Night
is a huge success.
Thanks, Principal Skinner.
I got the idea from an episode
of Saved By The Bell.
Mm, that was always on too
late for me.
I’ll put everything
on lucky 17.
D-ohh, d-ohh, d-ohh, d-ohh,
d-ohh, d-ohh, d-ohh!
Whoo-hoo!
D-ohh, d-ohh, d-ohh,
d-ohh, d-ohh, d-ohh, d-ohh,
d-ohh!
Whoo-hoo!
D-ohh, d-ohh!
D-ohh!
Whoo-hoo!
And the winner is...
17!
I win!
This is it, baby.
First thing tomorrow,
we’re getting
a PlayStation One!
Ooh...
I’d like to cash in
these chips.
Give me most
of it in cash
and the rest in
suitcases to carry the cash.
Sir,
this casino is for charity.
These chips are only redeemable
in cafeteria scrip
or a day at the ballpark
with Groundskeeper Willie.
I’ll be bringin’ sparkplugs
to chuck at people
I don’t like, like you!
But I’m up $200,000!
Give me my money!
You think I won’t
manhandle a little boy?!
You don’t understand--
it’s not real money!
None of these people
have won any money!
ALL: Huh?!
Didn’t anyone read the flyer?
It was sent home last Tuesday.
(yelling)
(screaming)
Look at me! I’m a big man!
But I break...
just like a little girl.
(clamoring)
Well, this was a disaster.
I should have known.
The same thing happened
on Saved by the Bell.
Care for a milk?
No, thank you.
Martin, in light
of this fiasco,
you’re going to have
to resign as president.
(choked up): I will have
that milk now.
Easy there. That’s whole milk.
I’m a private citizen now.
I can drink what I like.
You won’t have Martin Prince
to kick around anymore.
(military drum
and bugle dirge)
Well, I guess we’re gonna need
a new student body president.
We’re from
Acme Amusement Rental.
We’re looking
for Principal Skinner.
Uh... yes, we all are.
Whoo...
(humming)
Ohh.
Hey, student body president.
I could join past presidents
like Otto or Krusty.
Nelson, you’re running
for President?
I’m not saying I have
all the answers,
but I do have all the
answer keys to every test.
(students clamoring)
Fractions?
Dinosaurs?
Foreign money?
The first Thanksgiving?
Nelson,
what are you doing?
Real estate license exam?
My ticket to freedom!
ALL (chanting):
Nelson! Nelson!
(sotto voce):
I’m doomed.
(Lisa sighs)
I can’t beat Nelson.
Why don’t you start
a rumor that he’s...
ding-a-ling-a-ling!
(high-pitched, singsong):
Hello!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho,
what a delicious quiche!
I drive a pink Miata.
I can’t believe Nelson
is more popular than me.
♪ La, la, la, la, la,
la, la... ♪
Honey, you can be popular.
You’ve just got
to be yourself...
in a whole new way.
No, I’m gonna stick
to my platform
of incremental policy
amelioration:
fluoridated water fountains,
vegan lunch options...
(falsetto):
My name is Nelthon!
I use a thalad fork.
La-dee-dah!
I wash my face.
Where did you get that tutu?
(normal voice):
Clothesline.
(crazed laughter)
...and we deserve
a French teacher
who actually speaks French.
J’accuse, Monsieuz Kupferberg!
(Brooklyn accent):
What’s she yakkin’ about?
I rest my case.
(woman coughs)
Nelson, rebuttal?
Yo, everyone, it’s me, Nelson.
(students cheer)
(chanting): Nelson! Nelson!
Nelson! Nelson! Nelson!
♪ I’m not that cool ♪
♪ I don’t wear jeans ♪
♪ I’ve polished
an apple or two ♪
♪ But every grade
that I grubbed ♪
♪ I grubbed it for you ♪
♪ So call me bookworm ♪
♪ But I’ll never squirm
when there’s work to be done ♪
♪ Yes, I’ll take my lunch
at my desk ♪
(sobbing)
(thump)
♪ While you’re all
outside having fun... ♪
♪ Don’t vote for me,
kids of Springfield ♪
♪ Unless you want
an effective leader ♪
♪ I’ll talk to teachers ♪
♪ I’ll handle Skinner ♪
♪ A vote for Lisa
makes you the winner. ♪
STUDENTS: ♪ Vote Lisa,
vote Lisa, vote Lisa! ♪
Hey, I’ve got a song, too.
♪ I am Iron Man ♪
♪ Do, do, do, do, do, do, do ♪
♪ Vote for me! ♪
Aah, screw it.
"Lisa." "Lisa." "Lisa."
Wow, she even beat perennial
write-in candidate,
"Skinner Sucks."
Skinner!!
I’m worried.
This girl is extremely popular
and thinks for herself.
She’s like a female
Eleanor Roosevelt.
Yeah, the students will do
anything she says.
She’s captured
their imagination
like a bright piece of
construction paper.
Hmm, yeah.
We’ve got to find a way
to control her.
Hey, maybe that escaped
mental patient
you hired has some sort of
toxin in his shack...
Yes, hello, Willie.
Well, if you ask me,
a woman’s weakness
is her sense of vanity.
Vanity? You might have
something there, Edna.
So, when’s my inauguration?
Hmm, let’s see...
When hell freezes over,
tough guy.
You wanted to see me?
Actually, Lisa,
I wanted you to see you.
You’re our president now,
but you look like
the First Lady of "yawn."
What would you change?
TEACHERS: ♪ Eyes, pearls,
smile, hair points ♪
♪ Dress, voice, shoes,
Swatch Watch ♪
♪ I may be the new girl ♪
♪ But you can’t brainwash me ♪
♪ Just Osh-Kosh-B’gosh me ♪
♪ And then leave me be ♪
♪ To fight for kid-power ♪
♪ I must be heard, not seen ♪
♪ I have to lead wisely ♪
♪ Not just primp and preen! ♪
TEACHERS: ♪ Nails,
dimples, ears, scrunchie ♪
♪ Purse, lunch box, teeth,
Milhouse... ♪
♪ This cute-ing-up suits me ♪
♪ There’s beauty within me ♪
♪ So let’s Olsen-Twin me ♪
♪ Give them someone to love ♪
♪ This grownup makeover ♪
♪ Has made me a super-tween ♪
♪ For they are my people ♪
♪ And I am their queen! ♪
Oh, Lisa, you look
so successful.
Like you’re the wife
of a businessman.
I wish I had married
a businessman.
Then I’d have nice things.
Well, it’s a little
over the top,
but there’s no reason
I can’t look good
and take back the playground
from the gypsies.
Is our Frisbee now.
Hey, Lisa, can I get
a photo for the front page?
It’ll either be a picture
of you or the drinking fountain
that won’t stop running.
Make it snappy, Milhouse.
I’ve got an important meeting
in the teachers’ lounge.
The teachers’ lounge.
Is it true they make fun
of students in there?
Oh, don’t be silly.
GROUNDSKEEPER WILLIE:
Look at me, I’m Milhouse.
I’ve tucked me shirt
into me underpants!
(teachers laughing)
I’ve got no friends,
so I confide in Willie!
(laughing harder)
(nervous chuckle)
(laughter continues)
Oh, hello, Lisa.
We were just, uh...
discussing Vasco Da Gama.
Well, I have some ideas
for ways
we can improve
the classroom experience.
We need to get teachers
more involved.
Have them meet
with struggling kids
in the morning before school.
Fine. I’ll come in early
to meet with students.
And I’ll have
hypnotherapy when?
Or, we could hand out teachers’
home phone numbers
so kids can call them whenever
they have questions.
I’ve got a question:
You’re crazy.
Look, in the Swedish
public schools,
the students grade the teachers
on their performance...
Outstanding notions!
Each more implementable
than the last.
It’s a shame you can’t stay
to discuss them.
Here’s your schedule
for the day.
"Photo op helping
kindergartners
take off snow boots..."
"Move the brushfire
hazard needle..."
Um, shouldn’t I stay here
and work on school policy?
Lisa, you were elected
to be seen and enjoyed.
Don’t hide your light
in a smoky back room,
making dusty
old decisions.
(giggles)
Well, I am proud of my light.
But just in case you want
to do any more thinking,
I’m proud to present you
with an official key
to the study hall.
(gasps)
Use it anytime you like.
You mean I can come
to the school after hours,
weekends,
even during the summer?
Yes, it’s like
you’re Harry Potter
without the magic
and wonder.
Just sign these
authorization forms,
you can be on your way.
(chuckles)
That little girl should learn
to read things
before she signs them.
Excuse me?
I was wondering
if I should read
what I just signed.
Oh, it’s just standard key
release boilerplate.
Okay.
Boy, she’ll believe anything.
Key release boilerplate?
I find that very hard
to believe.
Mm-hmm, and yet there it is.
I’ll just lock this door.
Boy, this key opens
everything.
(groans)
And then, as school president,
I don’t have to take
the hearing test.
I’m so proud of you, Lisa.
What?
You’re like Geraldine Ferraro,
except you won
where she failed miserably.
Well, I think I can say
with all humility,
I am going to be the
best school president ever.
(sarcastically):
Bravo, Lisa. Bravo.
Aw, wasn’t that sweet?
Even your brother’s
adding his kudos.
I was being sarcastic.
You were?
(heavy sarcasm): No.
I was being sincere.
Oh, I’m so confused.
Lis,
Skinner is using you,
like a pawn on his
unholy chess set.
On my chess set,
the pawns are all Hamburglars.
♪ I’m so happy
with my evil plan ♪
♪ Say good-bye to music,
gym and art ♪
♪ Soon we will have
the perfect school ♪
♪ Where fun
and excitement never start ♪
♪ I’m so drunk,
I can barely see ♪
♪ But it helps me
get through another day ♪
♪ My stomach is filled
with haggis and hurt ♪
♪ I’ve got to go puke
in some hay. ♪
♪ Lisa is a fool ♪
♪ I think the rules are cool ♪
♪ I’ve fallen in the pool! ♪
Hmm, not a cloud
in the sky--
a perfect day to unveil
Operation SLAAAM:
So Long Athletics,
Art, And Music.
Care for a T-shirt?
T-shirt?
Why don’t you just
give me a sandwich board
that says "Male Prostitute"?
Oh, well... I...
Forgive me, sir.
(gasps)
They’ve taken everything!
Oh, no!
(sobbing)
Look what they’ve done
to my triangle!
I’m doing it!
I’m almost to the top!
Hello, self-esteem!
Repo man.
(grunts and groans)
Ha, ha!
I love this job.
"All extracurricular activities
are hereby canceled,
to be replaced by nothing."
(all gasp with horror)
Who would sign such an order?
"As ordered
by Principal Skinner
and approved by Student Body
President Lisa Simpson!"
(all gasp)
And to think I was going
to ask you to the dance.
I would have gone with you.
Well, you still can.
Well, I don’t feel like it now.
(groans)
That’s cool.
(slapping)
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
(deep rumbling)
Aah! Look, they’re taking away
the art room!
I’ll be cookin’ me Lean Cuisine
in your kiln tonight.
(evil laugh)
♪ What have I done? ♪
♪ What they wanted you to. ♪
♪ Skinner betrayed me! ♪
♪ But a tango takes two! ♪
I almost had a date.
I’ve got to tell
Willie about this.
(singsong):
Lisa is a sellout!
Lisa,
what’s a sellout?
With the band gone,
how’ll I know
who to beat up?
Oh, they eliminated
"English for Fat Kids"!
Okay, you’ll do.
(both grunting)
Lis, you made
this school even worse.
And it wasn’t exactly
San Diego State
to begin with.
They made me pretty
and popular
just so they could exploit me
and ruin my good name.
Lisa, you’ve got to
stand up to these guys,
and when you do,
people will remember you.
Just look
at these postage stamps.
There’s Bugs Bunny,
Fat Elvis,
Autumn in New England,
Bats of the Southwest...
all heroes.
You want to see
Elvis kiss a bat?
(mimics Elvis): Hey, baby,
come here. I want to kiss you.
Squeak, squeak, squeak!
No, don’t kiss me!
You tricked me into betraying
my fellow students!
Lisa, student government
is meaningless.
Look at your constitution.
It’s written
on the back of a place mat.
And not a good place mat.
It’s from some place
called Doodles.
I see.
Principal Skinner, may I make
an announcement to the school?
I can’t see the harm.
I hereby resign
as your president,
and for my last act,
I call a general
student strike,
effective immediately!
Give me that!
And student caught striking
will be severely disciplined,
unless all of you do it,
then I’m stymied.
Strike! Strike! Strike!
Lisa, please,
help me lure them back.
I had to do what I did.
Our budget is
stretched tighter
than Mother’s sauna pants.
Seymour, quit using me
in analogies.
Yes, Mother.
Principal Skinner,
I will not call off this strike
until you bring back
Music and Art.
-What about Gym?
-Meh.
(chanting):
Hey, hey, Seymour S.,
nurture our well-roundedness.
Sneeze, puke, burp, fart,
we want Music, Gym and Art!
Why didn’t I cancel Sign-Making
and Creative Chanting?
Principal Skinner,
can’t you just reinstate
those programs?
Would you be willing
to pay an extra $1.23 in taxes
to fund them?
No way! I’m saving
for a speedboat.
Strike! Strike!
Lisa, what are you doing?
This is the kind of
trouble-making
I expect
from your brother.
You do?
Cool, a blank check for mayhem.
(grunts)
(groans)
Mom, I was elected
to make this a better school.
Well, couldn’t you
just hang
some colorful crepe paper
in the gym?
They’ve taken away
our crepe paper.
Those fuddruckers!
(siren whoops)
Oh-oh, they heard me.
Remember, boys,
these are little kids,
so take out your tiny batons.
(chuckles)
Chief Wiggam,
we’re just like you policeman.
Don’t you ever feel
like the mayor doesn’t care
about you?
You mean the mayor
who kept me waiting
for two hours
in that restaurant?
I ate so much bread!
Sit down, boys.
We’re joining this strike.
Uh, Chief, are you sure
the mayor wasn’t at
a different
Olive Garden than you?
Well, I can’t take
that rattlesnake
out of his mailbox now,
now, can I?
Yes, Chief, you could.
Well, let me ask you this:
Shut up.
The Springfield student strike
has entered its fourth day
with no end in sight.
Today, Professional Buttinski
Michael Moore arrived
on the scene.
Kids who don’t get
to take Music and Art
are 10% more likely to become
chronically unemployed
and appear
in one of my movies.
Where’d you get
that statistic?
Your mother.
The student strikers have been
joined by other unions,
including the
Springfield goat milkers,
The Association of Newsroom
Cue Card Holders-- Ow!--
and the United Federation
of Theme Park Zombies.
Zombie eat brains,
but zombie cannot swallow
this injustice.
The heart of the strike
is former Student Body President
Lisa Simpson.
Her brother had this to say:
Lisa is a nut,
she has a rubber butt,
every time she turns
around it goes "putt-putt."
Indeed, but that rubber butt
doesn’t have much time
for turning around these days.
It’s pointed squarely
in the face
of the administration.
Skinner! We have got
to get these kids
back in school.
Willie, can’t you turn
your hose on them?
They are wee children.
I’d sooner turn it on myself.
Well,
that’s a good idea, too.
See here, you nose-wiping
hair-combers.
Back in Edinburgh, we had
a coal miner’s strike.
All we wanted were hats
with a wee light on top.
Then one day
the mine collapsed.
No one made it out alive.
Not even Willie.
Skinner!
I don’t mean to interrupt
your advice from the janitor,
but I say cut off the head
and the body will die.
You want to get rid of Lisa?
But she’s such a good student.
Yes, in fact, I think
she’s a little too good
for this school.
If we stand together,
we are strong.
ALL: Yay!
Lisa Simpson,
you’ve just been transferred
to the Springfield
Magnet School
for the Gifted
and Troublesome.
Please climb
into the idling bus.
But... but I...
♪ Poor Lisa! Poor Lisa! ♪
♪ Don’t cry for me,
kids of Springfield ♪
♪ You can still reach me
through E-mail ♪
♪ At smart girl six three ♪
♪ Underscore back slash
at Yahoo dot com ♪
♪ at Yahoo dot com ♪
Bonjour, Lisa.
Regardez notre bibliotheque.
Oh, this place is paradise.
Well, I guess this story
has a happy ending after all,
just like my last massage.
(tires screech)
I’m not driving
45 minutes a day!
You can’t go
to that school!
But this is my dream.
Why can’t you have
a normal dream
like being an
Olympic figure skater?
Okay, let me take
figure skating.
Are you crazy?
I’m not getting up at
6:30 every morning
so you can prance around
a frozen pond
and think
you’re better than me.
-Well, what can I be?
-I don’t know.
How about
a horse whisperer?
Okay.
Over my dead body.
♪♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem