CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
( bell ringing )
( whistle blows )
(playing the blues)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
("Ring of Fire" playing)
( humming "Ring of Fire" )
♪ Time to whiz in a foaming
bowl of china... ♪
D-oh!
A line for the bathroom?
What gives?
I don’t know,
but whoever’s in there
is taking
their sweet old time.
Son, can I have cuts?
No.
-Back cuts?
-Okay.
-Sweet.
-Hey!
Wait a minute.
If we’re all out here,
who’s in there?
(all gasp)
(gasping)
Maggie’s locked inside!
Now, calm down.
I’ll just unlock it
with this coat hanger.
(grunting)
(delighted giggle)
Oh, God, it’s baby blood!
Don’t worry,
I know just what to do.
Ow! Do-h! Ow! D-oh! Ow! Do-h!
Bart! You’re not
hitting hard enough!
(Marge gasping)
How’d you get her out?
I tried
the coat hanger again.
I don’t understand
why we only try ideas once.
(doorbell rings)
The door?
Now I’ll never get to pee.
Dr. Hibbert?
Is someone seriously ill?
Oh, I wish.
(chuckles)
No, I’m here because
of Bob Poochioni over there.
(confused yelp)
Two months ago,
Santa’s Little Helper
paid a booty call
to my purebred poodle,
Rosa Barks...
(chuckling)
and he had his eyes
on her prize!
I’m going to drop
that analogy now.
ALL:
Aw!
Oh, well,
I’m glad you think
they’re cute,
’cause they’re
your problem now.
You just lost a box, pal!
Wait, Santa’s Little Helper
had puppies before,
and then we got him neutered.
We did.
Homer took him.
Didn’t you?
Yeah, well, uh,
funny thing about that...
On our way to the clinic,
I decided to give him a night
his wang would never forget.
DONNA SUMMER:
♪ So let’s dance
the last dance ♪
♪ Let’s dance the last dance ♪
♪ Let’s dance
this last dance ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ The last dance ♪
♪ Last chance for love... ♪
Want to play
some air hockey?
$350 an hour.
You’re on!
Huh? Hmm?
I can’t neuter you, boy.
Not after all
we’ve been through.
But from now on,
you better save your lovin’
for the couch cushions.
(laughing)
(growling)
You broke our deal!
We had an
oral contract!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
You and Lisa
better go find homes
for these puppies.
and don’t just
dump them all off
on some crazy lady.
(incoherent ranting)
(cats mewing)
He’s an irritable, walleyed,
misfit bastard!
Just like Willie. Oh...
Hey, mister,
would you like a puppy?
No, but I’ll take one.
Okay.
I’m going to cherish
and care for this dog,
and there’s nothing you can do
to stop me.
(evil laugh)
(kisses)
(tires squealing)
Seen it, bad, boring,
saw it on the plane,
rerun, rerun, Telemundo, me,
turned it down, ABC,
banned from the set,
lame, lame, Regis...
(groaning)
Let’s see...
champagne or Slim Fast?
Oy, that really
passes the time.
(knock at door)
Want a puppy?
He’s at the peak
of cuteness.
(chuckling)
Aw. You could nuzzle me
all night.
That’s enough.
I said that’s enough!
Well, look at this.
You dragged me back
to my old neighborhood.
And it hasn’t changed a bit.
DSL! DSL! Who will buy
my high-speed connections?
♪ Brazilian wax! ♪
♪ Get your velvety smooth
Brazilian wax! ♪
Hey-- the Jewish Walk of Fame!
Here, go
on Sandy Koufax.
I lost ten grand
when he wouldn’t pitch
on Yom Kippur.
I did five shows that night!
Okay, boy, let’s find my star.
Albert Einstein. Lorne Michaels?
Shari Lewis? Lamb Chop?!
Why ain’t I here?!
I’m a bigger name
than Chaim Potok!
What is he,
some kind of Klingon?
I’m going to get
to the bottom of this.
Well, of course you
deserve a star, Krusty.
Let me just ask you
a few questions.
Full name?
Herschel Pinchas
Yoracham Krustofsky.
Good, good. Circumcision?
And then some.
(chuckles)
Date of bar mitzvah?
Well, I, uh...
You see, the truth is, uh...
I never had one.
No bar mitzvah?
In the eyes of God,
and the Springfield Jewish
Walk of Fame Committee,
you are not a Jewish man.
Now, see here.
Do you know how much I donate
to the B’nai B’rith?
Actually, I do.
Goodbye.
(thunder rumbling)
Krusty,
what’s wrong?
I just found out
I’m not Jewish.
(moaning)
I was turned down
by all those country clubs
for nothing!
Well, you’re still my hero.
So what?
Everything’s changed.
I thought I was
a self-hating Jew,
but it turns out I’m just
a plain old anti-Semite!
We have so
much to discuss.
(groans)
Oh, I know the reason
my life is so empty.
I never had a Bar Mitzvah.
Cheer up, Krusty.
You’re a clue
in the People Magazine
crossword puzzle.
What more can a man want?
Bart, the Bar Mitzvah is
the most important event
in a Jewish boy’s life.
It’s when he reads from
the Torah and becomes a man.
The sweet little shiksa’s
right.
Without a Bar Mitzvah,
I’m just a boy...
with a prostate
the size of a goat’s head.
Krusty, your dad’s a rabbi.
How could you not have had
a Bar Mitzvah?
Who knows?
I’ve lived so hard,
there’s big gaps
in my memory.
I remember learning
to ride a bike,
then pretty much nothing
till right now.
Why don’t
we ask your dad?
Yeah, right.
My father will put this
in a spiritual-philosophical
context.
I’ll tell you why
you didn’t have a Bar Mitzvah.
It’s because you’re a putz!
Everything is
a joke to you.
I was afraid
you’d make a mockery
out of the whole ceremony...
like you’re making a mockery
out of me right now!
Maybe I am, but you can’t argue
with the laughs.
Eh, so what? It’s not my job
to make kids laugh.
Yes, it is.
You’re a clown.
Oh, without a Bar Mitzvah,
I’m nothing!
(sobbing)
Krusty, you can still have
your Bar Mitzvah as an adult.
That’d be great!
Are you sure
that’s Kah-sher?
There’s nothing in the Talmud
that forbids it.
How do you know
all this stuff?
I have a Jewish
imaginary friend.
Her name is Rachel Cohen,
and she just got into Brandeis.
Wonderful!
( lively show theme music
playing )
Hey, hey, kids!
I’ve got a confession to make.
Underneath
all this plastic surgery,
I’m actually a Jew,
and from now on,
I’m embracing my faith.
(cheering)
What’s not to like?
And now I’ll teach you
my traditions
the way my people have passed
them down for centuries...
through animation.
(klezmer music playing)
(reciting a Hebrew prayer)
(squeals)
(giggles)
(shouting)
(squeaks)
Mouse-l Tov!
And that’s
what I believe in now.
(chuckling)
Krusty, that was
a great show.
Once I was clapping, and the
applause sign wasn’t even on!
Hey, that’s great,
but I got a problem.
This schedule has me
working on Saturdays.
That’s the Sabbath!
Well, we could tape
two shows on Friday.
Are you nuts?!
I can barely get through
one show on Friday,
even with the...
(sniffs)
Uh, you know, smelling flowers.
Such expensive flowers...
filled with remorse.
Anyway, we got to book
a guest host.
How about Jon Stewart?
He’s a son,
a lover, and a pundit
rolled into one sexy package.
(growls)
He’d be perfect,
so forget it!
I need a guest host so bad,
he can never replace me.
I need someone
who’s not intelligent...
-Mm...
-not good-looking...
-(gasps)
-and so utterly repellent, he...
I’m your man!
(grunting)
Man, are you unpleasant.
You’re in.
(door shuts)
Children, I wish to announce
that our show has undergone
a reformatting.
(cheering)
Let’s get ready
to listen quietly!
ALL:
Yay!
Now, tonight’s guest host...
the ultimate place-holder...
Homer Simpson!
Welcome to
the Homer Simpson Show.
I’m your host... next card...
Homer Simpson.
It’s great to be here
in... next card... Springfield.
My guests are...
Moe Szyslak,
local businessman;
Carl Carlson,
raconteur;
and Lenny Leonard,
three-time juror.
Gentlemen,
what’s on your minds?
Dad, you have
to say something.
Something meaningful.
You ever notice
how seats are too small
for normal-looking guys like me?
Theaters, airplanes...
Why, even here. Look!
(straining)
-(grunting)
I could not agree more.
(grunts)
Never go on the teacup ride
after eating at Beauty and
the Beast’s Fried Dough Chateau.
Hey, I got a question.
How come oldies stations
are always playing
the same song?
How ’bout some new oldies,
geniuses?
Boy, these guys
are right on the money.
Yeah, my neck is sore
from agreeing so much.
Hey, baby!
You lookin’
for a good time, huh?
Go home, turn on your
television, Channel 6!
Thanks for the tip!
Yeah, yeah,
twins, I get it.
Now, let’s watch something
I’m really interested in.
Who has more power,
Miss America or Miss U.S.A.?
I think one’s elected
and the other one’s appointed.
I think your water
just broke.
Will you be quiet?!
Now, you can’t mix
milk and meat.
You got that?
And on Christmas day,
you must eat Chinese food,
and pork
is strictly forbidden.
Uh-oh.
All these rules...
I feel like
I’m in a strip club!
Well, Dad,
what do you want
to talk about tonight?
Hmm...
Uh, listen, Homer,
I’d like to raise an issue.
Why so formal, Lenny?
You’re my go-to guy.
Well, about that,
you know, I’ve been
with the show
from the beginning,
and I was, uh... was wondering
if I could get a-a small
cost-of-living raise.
Interesting...
Please welcome new panelist,
Barney Gumbel.
Oh, that light’s
a little bright.
Do you think you could move it?
Please welcome our newest
panelist, Disco Stu.
Tsk!
Disco Stu knows his place.
My husband’s a power-mad star.
Maybe now we can get that
padding that goes under rugs.
"Ha-ma-shel be-khol-a-sher-la
sim-na yad-kha ta-khat..."
Very good!
You just earned
yourself a Dr. Brown’s.
Krusty,
you know Diane, Stu,
and Jeremy from the network.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Krusty, we’ve got some bad news.
We think
you’re super-talented...
Oh, God, you’re canceling me!
Krusty, Krusty,
TV is a fickle business.
You’ve had a good run,
but Homer Simpson’s
a fresh face, and...
You’re not doing this
fast enough.
You’re fired, too.
I’m... No!
(sobbing)
Ah, Simpson,
I hate to bother you
when you’re eating,
but you’re always eating.
Will you sign an autograph
for my boy?
My pleasure.
I eat Legos.
So did I, son.
And look
where I am today.
Boy, everybody loves my show.
It’s great, Dad.
You have tremendous power.
And now it’s time
to put it to use.
Yes, you’re right.
Duck, Mr. Lincoln!
Thank you, Homer.
No, Dad.
I mean, you should use
your time on the air
to say things that
really mean something.
Change the world
for the better!
I say live fast, die young,
and leave a big fat corpse.
Well, I took Bart’s advice
last week,
so I guess it’s Lisa’s turn.
Now, if you’ll excuse me.
You hit him high,
I’ll hit him low!
(grunting)
(chuckling)
Look, since my own network
dumped me,
I thought maybe
I could do a show on...
(groaning)
Fox.
Well, I’m sorry, Krusty.
People aren’t interested
in stars anymore.
They want reality.
Way ahead of you.
How about a show
where girls think
I’m a millionaire?
But what they don’t know is,
I’m rife with disease.
Okay, okay.
How about one where I move in
with a poor family
and laugh at ’em?
(chuckles)
You see, be...
Okay, how about
you televise my Bar Mitzvah?
Live!
Please. You people are known
for taking chances on crap.
You know, we’ve had a great time
on this show
"riffing" on small,
unimportant subjects.
Now, wait a minute.
Dirty words you can spell
on your calculator
is a very important subject.
(chuckles)
Boobs.
(laughing): That’s
just like what girls got.
Well, that’s all over now.
From now on, we will focus
solely on important issues.
Every year,
the gulf between rich
and poor nations gets larger.
Yet, the IMF insists
on unrealistic
debt-repayment schedules.
This show stinks!
I knew my son would blow it.
Where’s the remote?
Oh, it might as
well be in China.
SIDESHOW MEL:
Live, from Springfield Stadium,
it’s Krusty the Clown’s
Wet ’N’ Wild Bar Mitzvah!
Shalom, Springfield!
CROWD:
Shalom!
I can’t schmear you.
ALL (louder):
Shalom!
(humming scales
with Hebrew "H" sound)
Now to get you
in the Bar Mitzvah mood,
put your hands together
for the Beach Boys...
Experience!
(to the tune of "Kokomo")
♪ Mezuzah, menorah,
reading from the Torah ♪
♪ Pastrami, knishes,
on two sets of dishes ♪
♪ A church with no steeple
for God’s chosen people... ♪
(drumroll)
Now let’s meet a man
who’s muscle-bound,
and a man who’s bound not
to eat mussels,
Mr. T and Krusty the Clown.
T, I haven’t seen you
since we roasted Chevy Chase.
Yeah, we were
kind of rough on him.
I felt bad
for that guy.
You pitied the fool?
That’s one way
of putting it.
Time for me
to get into character.
( click )
Let’s scroll!
(applause and cheering)
"Bar-chu et Adonai
hamvorach, fool..."
Why should America consume 90%
of the world’s resources?
Argentina must devalue
her currency to pay her debts!
(sobbing)
You can’t leave.
I’m your ride home!
Dad, you blew it.
You listened to Lisa.
And then you lost
your stranglehold
on the audience.
I’ll audience you!
-(grunting)
-(choking)
So, that’s why Bart has all
those broken tracheal bones.
(scoffing)
Tight bow tie,
my ass!
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together
for the world’s largest
potato pancake!
That’s a lot of latke!
-(grunting)
-(gagging)
Three, two,
one, and...
you’re canceled.
Strike the set.
You have five minutes
to get off the lot.
Oh...
Don’t worry.
This will be quick
and painless.
There we go.
(pained groan)
Aw, Homie, you may have
lost your show,
but you went out
in the classiest way possible.
I’m proud of you.
Marge, I thank God every day
you settled for me.
(contented sigh)
Hey, where’s my car?
Oh, over there.
(crying)
Come on, Homie.
We’ll go to the "Make
Your Own Sundae" place.
Will you make my sundae for me?
Yes.
Thank you,
cast of The Lion King.
And now, for our grand finale,
the superstar of David,
Mr. T.
(fanfare plays)
I pity the shul
that won’t let Krusty in now.
Spin me, clown!
(laughing)
(fireworks whistling)
(all gasp)
(fireworks popping)
I wish
I had invested my money better.
(all laughing)
(pensive moan)
Krusty, the ratings were good.
Raymond rerun good!
Great, but there’s
one thing that’s still
nagging at me.
I want a real Bar Mitzvah.
In a temple.
Wonderful!
" ...ha-mo-shel
be-khol-a-sher-lo
sim-na yad-kha ta-khat..."
( whispering loudly )
I’m hungry.
Are they married yet?
They’re not
getting married!
Then whose garter is this?
I was trying
to hit the dentist.
And now, finally,
I am a man.
I pity the fool
who didn’t bring an
envelope to this
Bar Mitzvah!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem