[JUGHEAD] For years,
Riverdale had prided itself
as being the Town With Pep.
Safe. Innocent. Utopian.
- But after recent events...
- [TYPEWRITER CLICKING]
...there was no denying the darkness
that churned beneath Riverdale.
The inequality, the prejudice,
the fearmongering.
It had been bubbling to the surface
and very nearly exploded.
Now a reshuffling was happening.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Now some new way of thinking,
of being, was required.
Principal Featherhead
was stepping down from his cherished post.
The official story was...
"for personal reasons."
But word from the bird
was that he'd been identified
by an anonymous accuser
as an accessory
to Mayor Blossom's Soviet shenanigans.
[HAL] With the sudden vacancy
in the principal's office,
the PTA is initiating a county-wide search
for a replacement.
- Mm.
- Here's hoping this one makes the grade.
Yes.
[JUGHEAD] In light of recent revelations
and after much discussion,
Mr. and Mrs. Cooper had decided
to continue living on Elm Street
as husband and wife.
Though Mr. Cooper would be moving
into the basement bedroom.
A decision that...
frankly, flummoxed Betty.
[ALICE] You know the truth now, Betty.
Why didn't you leave Dad back then?
When you first learned about his affair
with Mrs. Muggs?
I didn't wanna break up our family
over his indiscretions.
I didn't want you and Polly
to grow up without a father.
Well, why don't you divorce Dad now?
What am I gonna do? My life
is so intertwined with your father's.
This is his house.
I don't own the station. I can't even
open a bank account of my own.
And what a...?
What about when you go off to college?
I'm gonna be alone.
You know that I have...
never been alone a day in my life?
I lived in my parents' house
until the day that I married your father.
[NANA] It's just the three
of us now, children.
May your idiot father and viper mother
both rot in a Russian gulag
for the rest of their miserable lives.
From your lips to Moloch's ears, Nana.
I always knew there was
something squirrelly about Mom and Dad.
In the meanwhile, it's up to us
to ensure that the Blossoms rise
from the ashes like phoenixes.
I wholeheartedly concur.
And, rest assured, I know exactly
what my first order of business will be.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
So, with Featherhead gone,
who's gonna run the asylum now?
Well, not to sound like Chicken Little,
but... what if it's Dr. Werthers?
There's gotta be
better candidates out there.
Like Captain Hook?
Or Godzilla?
Just so long
as they don't ask my uncle to step up.
I actually know the perfect candidate,
but we would need support
from the PTA to push it through.
My mom's president of the PTA, of course.
Well, that's a brick wall.
The last time we appealed to
your mom's better angels, she let us down.
She did, but I think that we should
give her another chance.
A lot has changed for her since then.
Well, in the meantime, I'm going to pay
a house call on good old Dr. Moldy.
Oh, I knew it.
Featherhead is barely out the door
and you're already
trying to take his office?
So, what's the plan?
Are you going to study us like lab rats
or experiment on us
like some two-bit Dr. Moreau?
Alas, Mr. Jones, I have no interest
in being principal of this school.
No, I'm off to do real work in Washington.
I'll be serving
on the president's subcommittee
looking into the causes
of juvenile delinquency.
Specifically its links
to comic books and other...
subversive forms of popular culture.
Well, golly.
Don't let the door hit you on the way out.
Oh, fear not, though.
My tribunal will still be doing the
important work of regulating comic books.
- Censoring them, you mean.
- As a matter of fact,
here is our response to your latest issue.
Which we rejected,
for the reasons outlined herein.
Good luck to you
and your colleagues at Pep Comics.
While it still exists.
Damn, Red. You still got it.
I'm just buzzing, Reg.
Buzzing.
Earlier this week,
Mrs. Grundy told us to read On the Road
by king of the Beats, Jack Kerouac.
Brought everything into focus for me.
"I was surprised, as always,
by how easy the act of leaving was.
And how good it felt.
The world was suddenly rich
with possibility."
- You really got the bug, huh?
- Yeah, I guess I do, Reg.
So much so that this summer
I'm gonna ride the rails. Hit the trails.
I'm gonna be a vagabond writer.
Hop trains, explore the country,
sleep under the stars,
and then write about my experiences,
wherever they may take me.
- And what's your mom gonna say about that?
- My mom can't say diddly-squat,
'cause I'm doing this
during summer vacation.
Well...
jumping trains doesn't beat going
to the best basketball camp in the world,
but if it floats your boat,
good on you, Arch.
So, as a parting gift, Dr. Werthers
rejected Zip Comics Number 42?
And what was his rationale, may I ask?
Well, it's gotta be because
of the last story in that issue.
- "The Comet."
- What?
- But that one's the cat's pajamas.
- I know.
It's based off a W.E.B. Du Bois story
that Tabitha clued me into
last time she was in town.
It's so romantic and philosophical.
After a comet hits
and destroys New York City,
a man and a woman come together
and fall in love.
Their problem is that it's a Black man
and a white woman who find each other.
I haven't even told Mr. Fieldstone yet.
I think it's gonna crush him.
I'm sure.
That "Comet" story is a masterpiece.
Honestly, my first thought
when I read it was,
"This would make for a fantabulous movie."
Well...
if anyone wants to get in touch
with Du Bois' representatives,
I have all their information.
[LIVELY, PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Just saying.
Mom. This is your chance
to do the right thing.
To make up for sitting on your hands
when I asked you to report on Emmett Till.
I know you regret that.
Mrs. Cooper,
when Riverdale High integrated,
three of the Black schools
in town shut down.
And suddenly dozens of great teachers
were kicked to the curb.
There's this incredible educator
who spent the last year driving a cab...
Girls, I would love to help,
but the rest of the PTA...
Mom.
Make them understand.
Riverdale is at a turning point.
Now is the time for a fresh start.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD APPLAUDING, CHEERING]
[ALICE CHUCKLES]
[CROWD WHISTLING]
Morning, students.
I know you've all had a difficult year.
I know your previous principal...
wasn't exactly open to change,
to new ideas,
to addressing the needs
of all his students.
Well...
let me make one thing clear.
I'm here... for every student.
That said...
the challenges that face us
are enormous and systemic,
and if you're not part of the solution,
then you're part of the problem.
So I challenge you all:
Be kind.
Be decent.
Be better.
Now, let's get to work!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ARCHIE] Principal Weatherbee?
- Yes.
Hi. I'm Archie. Archie Andrews.
Please, sit.
What can I do for you, Mr. Andrews?
Well, there used to be a teacher
who worked here, a real top-notch teach.
She was falsely accused
of being a Communist,
and she was fired for it.
- Her name's Mrs. Thornton.
- I know Edith Thornton very well.
She is a wonderful educator.
I know.
Well, that's why I was hoping that...
Let me see if I can't right this wrong.
Get Edith back here.
Well, that would be swell,
Principal Weatherbee.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[SUAVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hold on to your pom-poms,
my beloved paper-shakers,
because I'm back!
Cheryl, this is a private practice
for Vixens,
not has-been daughters of Russian spies.
Now that Principal Weatherbee is ushering
in a new golden age at Riverdale High,
I am launching a coup
to take back control of my Vixens.
Therefore, Evelyn,
I am challenging you to a dance-off.
Winner takes all.
- I refuse your challenge.
- [SCOFFS]
["ROCKIN' ROBIN" PLAYING ON STEREO]
♪ The pretty little raven
At the bird bandstand... ♪
That's not an option.
♪ They started going steady
And bless my soul ♪
♪ He out-bopped the buzzard
And the oriole ♪
♪ He rocks in the treetop all day long ♪
♪ Hoppin' and a-boppin'
And a-singin' his song ♪
♪ All the little birds on Jaybird Street ♪
♪ Love to hear the robin go
"Tweet, tweet, tweet" ♪
- ♪ Rockin' robin ♪
- ♪ Tweet, tweet, tweet ♪
- ♪ Tweet, tweedle-lee-dee ♪
♪ Blow, rockin' robin
'Cause we're really gonna rock tonight ♪
♪ Tweet, tweedle-lee-dee ♪
♪ Tweedle-lee deedle-dee-dee
Tweedle-lee deedle-dee-dee ♪
♪ Tweet, tweet ♪
[ARCH MUSIC PLAYING]
Your turn.
[SCREAMS]
[DOOR OPENS]
Today marks the beginning
of a new era for the Vixens.
To that end...
I have decided to live in the light.
I'm going steady with Toni Topaz.
And if anyone here
has a problem with that,
you are more than welcome to follow Evelyn
out that door and into a dumpster.
We're in full support of you, Cheryl.
And we also...
Want to live in the light.
[CHEERLEADERS APPLAUDING]
[JUGHEAD] Mr. Fieldstone,
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
I get it, kid. I get it.
"Rejected for not promoting
traditional American values."
You know what that's code for?
They didn't wanna see a Black man
and a white woman end up together.
- So, what do we do now?
- What do you mean?
We publish without the damn seal.
That's what we do.
Send it out in the world
and hope for the best.
I was hoping you'd say that.
And depending on the sales,
I was thinking next time we could...
There's not gonna be a next time, kid.
No, that's it for me. I'm done.
I mean, this is the best comic
I ever put together.
[GENTLE, EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
It's a work of art.
I mean, it actually says something.
And that tribunal couldn't care less.
So let the comic...
be Pep's swan song.
I can't imagine a better one.
In the meantime...
would you do me a favor, kid?
Would you write the last editorial?
Think of it as our eulogy.
For the final issue of Pep Comics.
It's been an honor, kid.
It really has.
[FIELDSTONE SIGHS]
Well... [CHUCKLES]
It was a beautiful dream while it lasted.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, my gosh. I've been waiting for this.
What did you get, hon?
[BETTY EXHALES]
It's the first copy of my book.
You wrote a book?
Your mom and dad
must be very proud of you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Oh, hey, Kev.
- What are you doing here?
- Audrey said you weren't feeling great,
so I thought I'd bring you
some of Pop's chicken noodle.
Oh. Well, I appreciate that. That's...
That's great.
[KEVIN] Coach Andrews?
What's going on?
Uh, I'm staying in the motel as well,
and, uh...
the shower in my room is on the fritz,
so, you... Your dad let me use his.
Yeah.
Right.
You wanna come in, grab a flop?
Um, no. No, um...
I should probably cut out.
[BETTY] Mom?
I have something that I wanna show you.
Oh.
What is it, Betty?
I wrote a book.
Goodness. Yes.
You... You did.
I see that you're on the cover.
In undergarments.
I really, really want you to read it.
Mm. It says right there in the title
it's for teenagers.
I mean, why would I read it?
Well, in an ideal world,
I'd love for you to be proud of me
for writing a book.
But I'll settle for you reading it
just... to get to know me better.
And maybe by getting to know me better,
you might get to know yourself better.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[ARCHIE] Oh, it is so great
to have you back, Mrs. Thornton.
Geraldine shared some
of your recent poems with me.
I do hope you plan
to stick with your writing.
Oh, I do.
In fact, this summer,
I'm gonna hit the rails.
Like all the Beat writers do.
I'm gonna see if I can get at least one...
great big juicy
Allen Ginsberg-like poem out of it.
Oh, that's wonderful.
You'll see what the world
beyond Riverdale is like.
It's exactly what you should be doing
at this point
in your development as a poet.
Clay?
Tell me,
have you ever read the story "The Comet"?
Of course. Multiple times, in fact.
I figured you would have.
In that case,
how would you feel about writing
and directing an adaptation of "The Comet"
as a major motion picture?
Is this a gag? I've actually been fiddling
with a screenplay version
of "The Comet" for years.
Well, thanks to Jughead,
I connected with Du Bois' agents,
and it turns out the movie rights
had been languishing for years.
So I snapped them up.
And I suspected
you'd be passionate about this.
Veronica, I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
It's going to be an uphill battle.
But there are things we can do,
like get the right star attached.
Someone like, say...
[BOTH] Sidney Poitier.
- Precisely.
- Can you get to him?
I might not be able to get to him,
but we both know someone who can.
Josie McCoy.
But, Clay...
if we're going to attach
a big star like Sidney,
your adaptation needs to be undeniable.
Don't worry. It will be.
And who needs to wait for summer?
I'll get going right away.
Wonderful.
In that case,
I'm thinking a premiere at Cannes
in the next four to five years.
How does that sound?
[VERONICA SQUEALS]
Hey.
- Why the long face?
- [SNIFFLES]
I just got the information packet
for Camp Evans.
My basketball camp.
Well...
Well, that's great, isn't it?
Turns out they flip-flopped
the dates on me,
and now it's smack-dab in the middle
of our annual sweet-corn harvest
back on the farm.
Well, can't you skip the harvest
this one time?
The corn we harvest
that single month supports our farm
for the rest of the year.
There's no way I can miss it.
My parents need me.
So I just...
I gotta forget about basketball camp.
[SNIFFLES]
Well... [SCOFFS]
...the heck with that.
No.
Reg, don't sweat it.
I'll take your place on the farm.
Stop goofing, Andrews.
You got other plans.
Well, whatever I had planned,
it's not as important
as getting you set up for college.
And going pro.
Besides, working the land with my hands?
Giving back to the earth?
And then writing about it
while leaned up against a haystack?
I mean, that's exactly
what a Beat writer should be doing.
My parents won't be able
to pay you, Archie.
- And it's not easy work.
- Reg.
I got it.
It's all part of the experience.
You're going to Camp Evans.
Let me take up the slack at Duck Creek.
Sleep in your barn, learn the ukulele,
break bread with your mom, your dad.
[HEARTWARMING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah.
Okay.
Sounds good.
Thanks, Archie.
I love you, Reg.
I love you too, Archie.
[CRYING QUIETLY]
[BETTY] Mom?
What is it? What's wrong?
I, uh...
I just finished your book.
And I'm speechless.
Well, I'm really glad that you read it.
Betty, you wrote a book.
A whole book.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
And you're right.
I did get to know you better.
And all those...
wonderful, intelligent,
promising young women.
So full of thoughts
and fears and struggles.
And dreams.
They have aspirations.
Yeah. That's true.
And then I think of myself,
and my biggest dream
was being Miss Riverdale.
Mom, you once told me
that you dreamed about being a stewardess.
Mm.
You wanted to see the world
and meet fascinating people
and be a fascinating person.
Yeah, well, that was a, uh...
silly dream from a young girl
a long time ago.
No, Mom.
No dream is silly.
I know you think
that it's too late for you, but it's not.
You can be happy.
Please, please...
please believe that.
[JUGHEAD] Chances are, you won't ever see
this issue on a newsstand.
Despite that, Pep Comics
has decided to release it.
We are publishing this, our final issue,
without the Comic Book Code
Seal of Approval.
Most likely, that means this issue will
end up in either a landfill or a bonfire.
[FIRE ROARS]
But we here at Pep Comics refuse to kneel
to the un-American censorship
that was specifically drafted
to silence stories like "The Comet."
We hope that this comic book
will find its way into your hands.
And, hopefully,
the stories in it will make you think.
And make you feel a little less alone.
So we at Pep Comics leave you
with this final message:
It is easier to tear down
than to build up.
Try to be a builder, not a destroyer.
With that in mind, enjoy this
humble adaptation of "The Comet"
by the great author W.E.B. Du Bois,
a man who faced unthinkable adversity
and still chose to believe
that the end of the world
was not a foregone conclusion.
There is always a chance
for a brighter, better, stronger future.
From all of us at Pep Comics,
this is adieu...
but not farewell.
We'll meet again.
[GENTLE, STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Tabitha.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Hi. What are you doing here?
- Hi, stranger.
- Oh!
Gee whiz.
You're a sight for sore eyes.
What happened to your glasses?
And what's that television doing here?
Jughead,
I am not the Tabitha who's traveling
across the country with the NAACP.
I'm the Tabitha that you've...
forgotten.
Uh...
What are you talking about?
Sit down.
Let me show you something.
- [INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
- [JUGHEAD ON TV] Our story's about a town.
- Wowee. Is this a color television?
- [JUGHEAD] A small town.
And the people who live in the town.
From a distance, it presents itself
like so many other small towns...
Is that my voice?
- ...all over the world. Safe.
- Just absorb.
Decent. Innocent.
And then I will explain everything.
[JUGHEAD] Get closer, though, and you
start seeing the shadows underneath.
The name of our town is Riverdale.
[SINGER ON TV] ♪ Tell me... ♪
[ANGEL TABITHA] Well?
I remember.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I remember everything.
That I sent you and everyone back to 1955
to save Riverdale from Bailey's Comet?
And that,
while you and all of your friends worked
to make this timeline less dark
and nihilistic and hopeless,
I was trying to untangle
the various timelines
that had gotten jumbled?
Shore up the multiverse, in other words.
We were successful?
You were.
You all did great.
All of your collective innate decency,
all of your struggles, have started
to reshape this town, this world.
And it will just keep getting better
and better.
Neat. [CHUCKLING]
Awesome.
I assume that you were successful too?
After much trial and error,
I realized it would be impossible
for me to untangle and...
And pull apart
all of the various timelines,
so, instead, I wove them all
into a single timeline.
This one.
And I used all of the energy
from all of the other timelines
to stabilize it and fortify it.
Great.
It is.
But, um...
now that it's stable...
I can't...
move anyone through time.
I can't send you all back to 2023.
So the others...
won't remember anything
about everything that happened before?
Well, I can't move them through time,
as I've said,
but I can show them.
I can show them what I showed you,
and then they can decide
whether or not they want
to remember their other...
adventures...
let's call them.
It's the least I can do.
[JUGHEAD] So I gathered my friends, again,
and I told them about the future...
and how we couldn't go back
to our previous lives
but they could remember them
if they chose to do so
and then decide if they wanted
to keep those memories or forget them.
Look, I know it's a lot to process,
so I'll just leave the decision to you.
If you're interested,
you know where to find me.
I wondered if any of them
would take me up on Tabitha's offer.
- [ARCHIE] Jughead.
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I drew the short straw.
If this is real, I figure
I might get a good poem out of it.
My own version of "Howl."
Come on.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
In the future,
this is called "binge-watching."
[JUGHEAD ON TV] Our story's about a town.
A small town.
And the people who live in the town.
From a distance, it presents itself
like so many other small towns
all over the world.
[DOO-WOP MUSIC PLAYING ON JUKEBOX]
I was a boxer.
Prisoner.
Football player.
I was a soldier.
Like my dad.
[ARCHIE SCOFFS]
I was with my dad.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
Then he...
Then he died again.
Well...
I promised the others I'd report back.
What are you gonna tell them?
I'm not sure.
I didn't think I'd ever see my dad again.
So I'm...
I'm glad about that.
[SIGHS]
But I don't know
if they'll wanna see what I saw.
That said, if anyone does,
they know where to find me.
[SIGHS]
- [DOOR OPENS & BELLS JINGLE]
- [VERONICA] Hey, Jughead?
Archie told us what you showed him.
We'd like to see what Archie saw.
Together.
Classic Bee and Vee style.
[JUGHEAD ON TV]
Our story's about a town. A small town.
Decent. Innocent.
Get closer, though, and you start seeing
the shadows underneath.
The name of our town is Riverdale.
[SINGER ON TV] ♪ Tell me... ♪
You could have prepared us a little more
for that, Jughead Jones.
[POP BALLAD PLAYING ON JUKEBOX]
[BETTY SNIFFLES]
There was...
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
...so much darkness...
in that world.
And my family?
My father was a killer.
My sister...
was murdered.
And then...
came back to life.
You and I...
we were together.
Yeah.
Till we weren't.
I was with Archie.
And I...
killed my husband, Chad.
And my father.
[DOOR OPENS & BELLS JINGLE]
What you're about to see is your past,
but it's also your future.
And some of it will be disturbing.
We can handle it.
At times, you might not
even recognize yourselves.
Where are Kevin and Julian?
Uh... Kevin asked if Clay
was in any of the stories on TV.
When Betty told him he wasn't,
he didn't wanna come.
When Julian found out
he was just a doll in the TV stories,
he didn't wanna come either.
But the rest of us wanna see
what our past was like.
Sounds good.
[JUGHEAD ON TV]
Our story's about a town. A small town.
Decent. Innocent.
Get closer, though,
and you start seeing
the shadows underneath...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANGEL TABITHA] Now you know.
Now you know what your lives were like
before the comet.
The adventures you had,
the people you loved, the people you lost.
The good.
The bad.
The bear.
The question is, do you wanna
carry this knowledge with you
for the rest of your lives
or... would you rather forget?
Because I can make that happen.
Because she's an angel.
Along those lines, Angel Tabitha...
Can I call you "Angel Tabitha"?
This is something
we've all been discussing,
and we were wondering...
could we, perhaps,
just remember the good things?
Forget all the serial killers
and superpowers
and Gargoyle Kings
and just remember the happy times we had?
It doesn't exactly work that way...
Actually, I can make that happen, yes.
I can hit a reset button
and only reshare the good memories.
I think after everything
you all have been through,
you deserve that much, at least.
["TWILIGHT TIME" PLAYING]
♪ Heavenly shades of night are falling ♪
♪ It's twilight time ♪
♪ Out of the mist your voice is calling ♪
♪ 'Tis twilight time ♪
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
♪ When purple-colored curtains
Mark the end of day ♪
♪ I'll hear you, my dear
At twilight time ♪
♪ Doo-doo ♪
♪ Deepening shadows gather splendor ♪
♪ As day is done ♪
♪ Fingers of night will soon surrender ♪
♪ The setting sun ♪
♪ I count the moments, darling
Till you're here with me ♪
♪ Together at last at twilight time ♪
♪ Doo-doo ♪
♪ Here in the afterglow of day ♪
♪ We keep our rendezvous
Beneath the blue ♪
♪ Here in the sweet and same old way ♪
♪ I fall in love again
As I did then ♪
♪ Deep in the dark
Your kiss will thrill me ♪
♪ Like days of old ♪
♪ Lighting the spark
Of love that fills me ♪
♪ With dreams untold ♪
♪ Each day I pray for evening
Just to be with you ♪
♪ Together at last at twilight time ♪
♪ Doo-doo ♪
♪ Here in the afterglow of day ♪
♪ We keep our rendezvous
Beneath the blue ♪
♪ Here in the sweet and same old way ♪
♪ I fall in love again
As I did then ♪
♪ Deep in the dark
Your kiss will thrill me ♪
♪ Like days of old ♪
♪ Lighting the spark
Of love that fills me ♪
♪ With dreams untold... ♪
Hey! Hey.
Is this the part where you ghost me?
Don't you wanna see how the movie ends?
I know how it ends, and so do you.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
Stay.
I can't.
Why not?
Well...
there's already another Tabitha here,
for one thing, in this universe.
And what happens to her?
She settles in Chicago.
She goes to business school
and then law school.
She's a civil-rights advocate
in every aspect of her life
for the rest of her life.
But we don't...?
Then that's all the more reason
that you should stay.
We lived together.
We had a life together.
- Was any of that real?
- Of course it was real.
Just like this is real.
It was all real. It all happened.
[ANGEL TABITHA SIGHS]
Hey.
Do you remember our epic date?
Before the end of the world, when we...
watched Titanic and then we ate at Pop's.
And we had a family.
- We grew old together.
- That time bubble still exists.
It's still protecting us, what we had,
what we will always have.
But from this point here?
There is only one path forward now.
And that is a good thing,
Jughead, trust me.
Wow, it really sucks that you had to die
to make all this happen.
Except I didn't.
Not anymore.
The comet, the end times, that doesn't...
That won't happen anymore.
We all took care of that.
Ah.
Classic time paradox.
Could I at least kiss you goodbye?
Jughead Jones, you read my mind.
[PASSIONATE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUGHEAD] And in the blink of an eye,
Angel Tabitha was gone.
But she had given us
the greatest gift of all:
our memories,
edited for maximum joy.
The good ones.
The ones we would cherish forever.
Though I chose to remember
not only the happy times
but the dark ones too.
I figured, as the unofficial chronicler
of our town,
that was my responsibility.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
But, as it happens,
I wasn't the only one
who decided to remember everything.
Betty did too.
More than most,
Betty understood that we are made up
of moments of both joy and pain,
happiness and suffering,
darkness and light,
and all the scars we collect
along the way.
[SOBS]
[TYPEWRITER CLICKING]
[JUGHEAD] Another cosmic reshuffling
had happened.
Or was happening again.
But the stage was set
for the final chapter of our epic saga
about the Town With Pep,
one that could only be called...
[WISTFUL POP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ I'm your baby... ♪
[JUGHEAD] ..."Goodbye, Riverdale."
♪ And you'll never leave me ♪
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ That you'll kiss me ♪
♪ Forever ♪
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]