[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
[GRUNDY] I saw the best minds
of my generation destroyed by madness
Starving, hysterical, naked
Angel-headed hipsters burning
For the ancient heavenly connection
To the starry dynamo
And the machinery of night
Floating across the tops of cities
Contemplating jazz
Is that from "Howl" by Allen Ginsberg?
Yeah. He performed it in San Francisco
earlier this year.
- Ginsberg, he's a Beat poet, isn't he?
- That's right, Betty.
He was there at the beginning,
at Columbia,
with Jack Kerouac and William Burroughs.
Sorry, but who are the Beats?
The Beats are...
Vagabond, rebel writers who reject
institutionalized American values
like materialism, conformity,
and heteronormativity.
Heteronormativity.
The Beats have a lot of sex, Archie.
And a lot of it with each other.
Even the men's men
like Kerouac and Cassady,
they have girlfriends,
but they also have... each other.
Bully for them.
Sounds like my kind of literary movement.
The Beats are a whole counter-culture,
dedicated to living their lives
a certain way,
always exploring, experimenting, hustling,
pushing the boundaries
of human experience,
you know, really living.
[CHUCKLES]
Uh, Mrs. Grundy, are we allowed
to continue reading "Howl"?
Yes. I already made copies.
Read it, and we will discuss it
at our next meeting.
- Bettie Page sure is a dolly and a half.
- She's an icon in fishnets.
- Even you'll have to agree, Lizzo.
- She's not bad.
But I'm gonna
let you two kittens in on a little secret.
That mag's nowheresville
compared to what I just got.
What are my eyes beholding?
The latest issue of Femme-And-In magazine,
an underground lesbian pinup mag.
- [SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
- Lizzo. Can we borrow this?
Oh, you can keep it, Topaz.
I always buy two copies.
Just, uh, don't get caught
with your hand in the cookie jar.
Whatever you wet rags
are doing tonight, drop it.
I got my hands on a stag film.
Wait, what's a stag film?
Jeez, Andrews, maybe it's time
to get your nose out of those poems.
It's a skin flick.
Complete with naked women.
Sometimes more than one.
Where'd you get something like that?
A buddy from Stonewall Prep lent it to me.
So who's game?
Come on, Fogarty, you gotta be horny
with your honey
under lock and key at the Sisters.
Where would we watch it?
Can hang a blanket up in my parents' barn.
Only glitch is we need a projector.
You two work at the movie theater, right?
Can you help a brother out?
The Babylonium does have
a smaller projector, but...
We wanna come too.
Fine.
Just don't expect it to be like one of
those wrestling movies you like to watch.
So, Robert Frost... you in?
- Yeah, we're in.
- [JULIAN] Right-o.
From all accounts,
you won't be disappointed.
My pal told me that
there's nothing they don't show.
[BOYS CHUCKLING]
[TYPEWRITER CLACKING]
Jeepers, Mr. Fieldstone,
it's like a funeral in here.
Did something happen?
[SIGHS] Yes. I got a letter
from that crackpot Werthers.
Apparently, wants to follow up his bonfire
with some cockamamie comic book code
he wants to ram down our throats.
- A code to do what?
- To censor our content.
Like the Hays Code censors movies.
I didn't spend two years fighting Nazis
in France to kowtow to fascists at home.
He and his board of experts
want to have a sit-down meeting?
Yeah, and look who that geezer's got
on his side of the table.
Mayor Blossom,
that chrome-domed principal,
some fuddy-duddy nun
from the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Golly, Mr. Fieldstone, you have to do it.
Might be the best way to defend Pep Comics
before this code becomes official.
Okay, fine. I'll try and get my hands
on a draft of Werthers' "recommendations"
before we go into the lion's den.
"We"?
You have tangled with Werthers before
and lived to tell the tale. So far.
What do you say? Will you step up?
You betcha.
Let's beat them at their own game.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
You know, babe,
what if we did a pinup shoot of our own?
Color me curious.
I've got a camera, and it has a timer
so we could both be in the pictures.
In that case, afterwards,
we could pick our favorite photo,
and then I could turn it
into the most fantabulous oil painting
in the tradition
of our favorite pulp novel covers.
I know exactly where
our clandestine photo shoot can be.
Tell me, where?
Thornhill's chapel.
No one in my unholy family ever uses it.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, if it isn't the Bobbsey Twins,
up to their old tricks again.
How many times do I have to tell you boys
that you're free to watch
your wrestling movies in our auditorium
after hours, of course,
and provided you clean up.
Oh. Uh, it's not that, Veronica. Um...
Julian got his hands on a stag film.
And he needs a projector to screen it.
You don't say.
I've heard about these smokers before.
So-called because
they're typically screened by men
in the back rooms of their private clubs
while smoking cigars
and enjoying hot toddies.
But I've never actually seen one,
though I've always been curious.
Exactly. Same as us.
Yeah, that's why we're helping the creep.
Why don't I make you a deal?
Tell Julian he can do a proper screening
here at the Babylonium tonight
and invite all his horndog friends,
but I get to come too
and invite a gal pal.
["W-O-M-A-N" PLAYING OVER RECORD PLAYER]
♪ Talking about you, a man ♪
♪ Always ready to go... ♪
[CAMERA CLICKS]
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
[TIMER TICKING]
♪ I'm a W.O.M.A.N. ♪
♪ A woman ♪
♪ Woman ♪
♪ Now that should teach you
About a W.O.M.A.N... ♪
- Thought you'd given me the brush off.
- I know. I'm sorry.
I had to wait for my mom
to take her sleeping pills.
I'm just glad you made it.
I didn't wanna be the only girl here,
and I knew you'd wanna take a gander.
Oh, yes.
Ever since reading about stag films
in Dr. Kingsley's book...
Well, the boys are already in the theater,
panting like a pack of rabid wolves.
- [BOYS BARKING AND HOWLING]
- It's showtime, fellas.
So settle down, and welcome
to the Riverdale premiere of...
The Wedding Night.
- Yeah!
- [VERONICA] Yes.
In which a young blushing bride
is initiated
into the mysteries of matrimony.
Behave yourselves, fellas.
Keep the roughhousing
and catcalling to a minimum.
And with that, enjoy the show.
[CHEERING]
[BOY] Shh, shh, shh!
[BOY] Oh, my God.
[BOYS BARKING AND HOWLING]
[BOYS] Yeah!
- [BOY 1] Yes.
- [BOY 2] Yeah!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Betty, what's wrong?
Stop! Stop the movie.
Stop! That woman is my sister.
- Your sister?
- Polly?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Cut the reel and, uh,
hit the lights, Clay.
[ALL BOOING]
Well, safe to say,
that was a twist no one saw coming.
When was the last time
you saw your sister?
A couple of years,
but, Vee, this doesn't make any sense.
Polly is a dancer on Broadway.
Maybe you should call Polly,
see if you can get some answers.
- ["SOMEBODY TOLD ME" PLAYING]
- [LINE RINGING]
- [POLLY] Hello?
- Polly?
It's Betty. I found your number
in Mom's address book.
Sorry to be calling you so late,
but we need to talk.
♪ Well, somebody told me ♪
♪ My gal was runnin' 'round ♪
♪ Yeah, somebody told me ♪
♪ I don't want her to be like that ♪
♪ 'Cause she's only actin' a clown ♪
- He didn't pass it to you. He was...
- So last night was a bust.
Tell you what, though.
I got Keller and Walker
to lend me a projector,
and I watched another movie I got
from my buddy at Stonewall Prep
after Cooper shut us down.
And, guys...
it's like the 10th wonder of the world.
Mm.
And guess what, for two bucks,
I'll rent you the projector and the movie,
which you can watch
in the privacy of your own home.
This time, with no interruptions.
What do you say, boys?
[VERONICA]
Okay, so you and Polly actually spoke?
Yes, but it was quick.
She's on her way to Riverdale now.
We're gonna meet at Pop's
so she can explain everything to me.
But she says she doesn't do
those films anymore.
- Right, she's on Broadway.
- No, actually, that's her cover story.
What she told me last night is,
she does... [WHISPERS] burlesque.
Really?
- Do your parents know that?
- Apparently.
I didn't ask them this morning.
They don't even know
that I reached out to Polly.
Well, for what it's worth,
burlesque is a legit art form.
In fact,
some burlesque performers are huge stars.
Gypsy Rose Lee, to name one.
Josephine Baker, to name another.
Well, she says her stage name
is Polly Amorous.
Cut the gas.
Polly Amorous?
Betty, she's the berries. I'm gonna flip.
What? Have you seen her perform?
No, I wish.
But I recognize that name from the trades.
I always thought she sounded
so glamorous and flossy.
I mean, I'd flat out die and go to heaven
to have her perform at the Babylonium.
- She kind of already did.
- Her burlesque show, you tickler.
Say, come to think of it,
maybe this is why
your mom is so terrified of S-E-X.
Maybe she's threatened by Polly.
Her independence, her sexuality,
her devil-may-care ways.
Well, hi-de-ho.
I must say, it's official,
you're a genius.
Photography is no big whoop
when you have subjects
as stunning as, well, us.
By the way, I was reading
the back pages of Femme-And-In,
and they publish amateur photos,
if that's something you're interested in.
Perhaps after we graduate high school?
In the meantime, how do you feel
about me painting a version of this?
That's my favorite one too.
I can't wait to see how you pulpify us.
[JUGHEAD] I know how you feel
about comic books, Veronica.
But I also know
that you're the top negotiator in town.
And though I'm not necessarily
a fanatic of comic books,
I don't think
they should be burned or banned.
But this code...
Yeah. Mr. Fieldstone got us a copy
ahead of the meeting.
What that crackpot Werthers
is proposing is insane.
I mean, it is straight out of 1984.
Big Brother is watching,
and he's trying to take your comic books.
These rules are more outrageous
than the Hays Code.
How can you possible spin any yarn
with all these blanket restrictions?
Heck, he's even trying to ban the words
"horror" and "terror" from our covers.
And some of these rules
are incredibly vague.
Werthers wants to outlaw stories
with horror, bloodshed, depravity, lust,
but he doesn't define
what those terms mean.
I think he's trying
to specifically target Pep Comics.
If he gets his way, the good doctor
is going to run us out of business.
So you came to me. Smart.
Well, first, don't get the gringles.
If they smell fear,
they will pounce on you.
Technically, this isn't a code.
It's a proposal. Their first offer.
So you and Mr. Fieldstone
should make a counterproposal.
Go through this draft, point by point.
Be crystal clear about what you want.
Yeah. Yeah, that's good.
You're in the right on this one, Jughead.
Don't doubt yourself.
It's really nice to see you again, Polly.
I missed you.
Oh, I missed you too, Betty.
I'm sorry that we're reconnecting
under these circumstances.
Oh, I figured you'd want this back.
Yes. Thank you.
Can I ask?
Why did you do it, Polly?
[SIGHS]
I got hoodwinked
into filming The Wedding Night
when I first got to New York.
I was young and naïve,
and fell in love with a fink
who steered me wrong.
I spent a year trying to track down
every copy I could find.
Thought I got them all.
Well, how did you get into burlesque?
It's funny.
Um, I auditioned for the Rockettes,
but I wasn't tall enough.
And then I saw Gypsy Rose Lee
perform at the Ziegfeld Follies
and I thought, "That is what I wanna do."
And whatever you might think
about burlesque,
I'm proud of my career.
It's on my terms, I make good money,
people respect me, and I respect myself.
So you don't have to worry.
I wanted to tell you that, face-to-face.
I'm so happy for you, Polly, really.
And to be perfectly honest,
I did a little burlesque show of my own.
Just for one person. Archie.
Archie from next door?
In our windows.
Well, you always were sweet on him.
How much did you say
Mom and Dad know about...?
My life?
Well, they don't know
about The Wedding Night, thank God,
but they do know about Polly Amorous.
I invited them to my show
a couple of years ago.
They walked out in the first five minutes
without saying a word. Not a peep.
Then I started hearing that mom was
telling people I was doing Guys and Dolls,
and I thought, well, that is it for me.
In their eyes, at least.
But it's fine.
I'm past that, truly.
I came here for you, Betty.
And I booked a room at the Cozy Time Motel
'cause I figured Mom and Dad
have no interest in seeing me.
Anyways, I don't wanna step foot
in that house ever again.
I understand. Believe me.
But I thought we could do
something fun tonight.
Go shopping or to the movies.
My treat, of course.
Well, actually,
if you're not rushing back to the city,
I was wondering if you might be willing
to meet a friend of mine.
She's a big fan of yours.
Of Polly Amorous.
A fan in Riverdale?
Absolutely. I never say no to a fan.
[POLLY CHUCKLES]
- [JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
- [POLLY] Oh, thanks.
It's been a journey.
Be still, my beating heart.
The Polly Amorous
sitting in my humble living room.
Now that we're gal pals,
you must tell me everything
about everything.
How is gay Paris, and old Madrid,
and every city in between?
I will let you know just after I get back
from my all-expenses-paid,
first-class European tour.
- Polly, you're going to Europe?
- Mm-hm.
Your sister is living the dream.
A new city and a different paramour
every night, I bet.
Well, not exactly.
- Oh?
- I...
I'm engaged.
You're engaged? To who?
His name is Langley Huggles.
He's a stock broker.
Completely devoted to me.
Keeps me grounded.
And housed in a penthouse
in the Upper West Side.
Ooh, la, la.
Polly, you were going to invite me
to the wedding, I hope?
Whatever tension there is
with Mom and Dad.
Sure I was.
Actually, I was gonna ask you
if you would be my maid of honor.
Well, I wouldn't be Veronica Lodge
if I didn't ask.
What do you think about doing
a one-night-only show
at my theater, the Babylonium?
I know Betty would love
to see you perform, as would I.
It's true. And maybe Mom would even come
since it's right here in town.
I wouldn't hold your breath
on that, Betty.
But as a matter of fact,
I am working on a new routine.
Well, then it's kismet.
And we'll keep it on the hush-hush.
Girls only.
[GROANS]
This is gonna be
the best $2 we've ever spent.
I'll say. Tonight, we become men.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
What, uh...? [CLEARS THROAT] What is this?
Don't know. Maybe they'll fight
over a girl or something.
- Right. Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
Dagnabbit!
That joker Julian
must've switched films on us as a gag.
Yeah.
Didn't Julian say something about
Kevin and Clay watching wrestling videos?
I don't know, but we should probably
turn this off, right? I mean...
Yeah. Yeah, we probably should.
[UNCOMFORTABLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe we just give it a minute
just to see if a girl comes in.
Yeah, that's a good idea. Let's do that.
Hey, that was wacko, right?
You think the guys in that movie were...
you know?
Well, some guys are that way.
Yeah, so...
Are Kevin and Clay?
I think.
Yeah. Maybe.
And, you know, there's an in-between.
What do you mean an in-between?
Like a little wiggle room to... explore.
We've been talking about it
in Mrs. Grundy's workshop.
These Beat poets would...
experiment with each other,
even though they were men's men
with girlfriends, wives, families.
They would...?
With other guys?
Do stuff.
Yeah.
With their buddies, just to see,
just to try it on for size.
I gotta take a cold shower.
Yeah, me too. I'll go after you.
And tomorrow you can bet your ass
that Julian Blossom
is gonna give us our $2 back.
Yeah.
Hey, Blossom!
What's the big idea
giving us a wrestling movie?
Oh, aren't you two in love?
I thought that flick might break the ice.
Get the ball, or balls, rolling.
Give us our damn money back
or I will pound you.
All right.
Get your filthy meat hooks off me.
There you go, ladies.
There's your two clams.
If anything, I should be paying you.
Your faces are priceless.
What about the damn stag film?
The one with Cooper's sister?
Betty took it, numbskull.
But I do have another smokey.
This one about a guy with two girls.
If you're interested.
This time I'll lend it to you gratis.
- What does that mean?
- [WHISPERS] It's free.
'Cause I'm that kind of guy.
Hey, all you hep kittens.
May we have your attention, please?
Clear your dance cards, ladies,
because the Babylonium is proud to present
a very special, one-night-only performance
by international burlesque star
and chanteuse,
the sensational Polly Amorous.
Who?
My sister Polly.
Wait, your sister's a burlesque star?
Things are starting
to make a hellish sense now.
In any case,
this is going to be a ladies night only.
No boys allowed.
Well, sounds like my kind of night.
So who's in?
[JUGHEAD] "Scenes dealing with
or instruments associated
with walking dead, torture,
vampires and vampirism, ghouls,
cannibalism,
and werewolfism are prohibited."
Wooden stakes are used to kill vampires,
but if Super Duck
used wooden stakes to pitch a tent,
would that be okay, or is that banned too?
Mr. Jones, please.
Clearly, context matters.
And shouldn't you be in class?
This is my lunch period.
"Suggestive and salacious illustration
or suggestive posture is unacceptable."
Could you be a little more specific
about which postures you mean?
Um, Sister, uh, perhaps you and the doctor
could demonstrate for us numbskulls?
Buffoons.
What about this item?
"All scenes of horror,
excessive bloodshed,
gory or gruesome crimes,
depravity, lust, sadism, and masochism
shall not be permitted"?
This code in its current state
violates the First Amendment.
Oh, surely you're not suggesting
that tripe like this
is protected by free speech.
Freedom of speech is protection of speech
that you don't agree with, Dr. Werthers.
What you are advocating for is censorship.
You even wanna ban the word "mystery"
from appearing on our covers.
Mr. Fieldstone, as an educator,
I believe this code
to be quite even-handed.
Well, I believe it
to be intentionally vague and confusing
so that you can apply it
to anything you wanna censor.
And who exactly defines
what "lurid," "unsavory,"
or "perverted" is?
Is that you, Dr. Werthers?
- Are we done here?
- [JUGHEAD] No, we are not done here.
We have a counterproposal
in the form of a rating system.
- A rating system?
- [FIELDSTONE] Yes.
Printed clearly on our covers.
A comic might be rated K for "kid"
or T for "teen" or A for "adult."
Don't be so naïve.
Stamping an A for "adult" on a comic book
would only make it
more desirable for young readers.
Riverdale's children and teenagers
must be protected at all costs.
You keep saying this,
but protected from what?
From the corrupting filth that you
and your colleagues peddle, Mr. Jones.
Tales of murder, lust, sex, and violence
that would, in turn,
prompt the same in their behavior.
Do you wanna know
what else has all of those themes?
The Bible, the plays of Shakespeare,
Bulfinch's Mythology...
Apples and oranges.
Wrongdoers are punished in the Bible.
Show me one Pep comic book
that glamorizes violence.
I don't read such depravity.
No, you just burn it.
Gentlemen, Sister, I think it's time
we wrap this up, don't you concur?
Wrap it up? We haven't even begun
to reach a compromise.
This meeting was never a negotiation.
It was offered to you as a courtesy.
All of your competitors
have already agreed
to comply with our comic book code.
You are, at the moment, the only holdouts.
If you do not abide by our strictures,
then you will not be able to print
the comic book code
seal of approval on your books.
No. No.
Not even Super Duck.
Which means that no newsstand in America
will sell or even carry your comic books.
They will be relegated to the trash heap.
Where they belong.
I know it's been a busy week,
but did you all have
a chance to read "Howl"?
Good, let's open it up for discussion.
What did you all think?
Dynamic and hallucinogenic.
A subterranean toppling of idolatry,
and an awakening.
Very good, Clay. Archie.
What did you think of Ginsberg's poem?
I...
couldn't sleep after reading it.
Where does a humdinger like "Howl"
even come from?
Well, Allen's lived a lot of life.
My husband says you can't be a real poet
without really living.
Well, in that case...
I'm never gonna be able
to write anything like "Howl."
Why would you say that, Archie?
Because look at me, Mrs. Grundy.
I'm a square. What am I gonna write about?
Jack Kerouac played football
in small-town Massachusetts
before going to Columbia to study writing.
Maybe it's more about
keeping an open mind about things.
Being open to trying new things
with different people.
Or more than one person.
Maybe two.
Let me ask you this, Archie.
Have you ever seen the sunrise?
Sure.
You mean like waking up early
for basketball practice?
No, no, I mean, staying up all night.
With your friends, drinking coffee,
and getting into
deep philosophical conversations
that last until the sky streaks pink
and yellow with the dawn's early light.
My husband and I do that once a month.
Let me tell you, it is...
transcendent.
It's like being reborn.
Betty, what's your take on "Howl"?
To be honest, Mrs. Grundy,
I'm halfway through it, and...
so far I...
appreciate how...
How it isn't afraid
to ask the hard questions?
To have the difficult conversations
that many of us
are too afraid to even begin?
[DOOR CLOSES]
Lady's Leisure?
Any interesting articles?
What can I do for you, Elizabeth?
I came here to see if you wanted
to join me and my gal pals
tonight at the Babylonium.
Oh.
Polly's performing.
What?
Polly's here?
In Riverdale?
And she's performing?
She is. I called her.
When were you planning on telling me
that my sister
is world-famous burlesque dancer?
Never, if I had my druthers.
So is that why you've been
so down on me all this time?
Are you punishing me for Polly's choices
or trying to make sure
that I don't follow in her footsteps?
Can't believe
your sister's here performing.
Well, she is.
She's living her life, Mom, without us,
because you decided to cut her off.
Did you know that she's engaged?
To a stock broker.
Don't you wanna go to her wedding?
Please just come to the show tonight, Mom.
Imagine what a great surprise
that it would be for her,
not to mention the best chance
we have to just be a family again.
In what world would I wanna go
and watch my daughter
debase herself for dirty old men?
It is not for dirty old men.
It is just for girls.
Well, I don't care
if it's for the Virgin Mary.
Well, I'm going.
And don't even try to forbid me,
because I'm proud of Polly,
and I want to support her,
and show her that I love
and accept her no matter what.
Unlike her mother.
You ready?
Ready.
[REGGIE] Yeah.
What? No.
No, no, no.
No! No!
What are we supposed to do now?
I'm horny as heck.
Me too, Reg.
Me too.
Wait.
I got an idea.
Now, it's a little raunchy,
but, I mean, if you're up for it...
["DIAMONDS AND PEARLS" PLAYING]
Well, well, well.
Looks like Twyla hit the jackpot tonight.
Now, which one of you hunks
of Wisconsin man cheese
is coming in first?
Or maybe you both wanna come in
at the same time?
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMEN SHOUTING AND CHEERING]
[SWAGGERING JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
Ladies and ladies.
The Babylonium takes great pleasure
in presenting the one, the only,
Ms. Polly Amorous.
[CHEERING]
["ROSE'S TURN" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Curtain up ♪
♪ Light the lights ♪
♪ Play it, boys ♪
♪ You either got it, or you ain't ♪
♪ And, boys, I got it ♪
♪ Some people got it and make it pay ♪
♪ Some people can't even give it away ♪
♪ This people's got it ♪
♪ And this people's spreading it around ♪
♪ You either have it ♪
♪ Or you've had it ♪
♪ Hello, everybody! ♪
♪ Mama's talking loud ♪
♪ Mama's doing fine ♪
♪ Mama's getting hot ♪
♪ Mama's going strong ♪
♪ Mama's moving on ♪
♪ Mama's all alone ♪
♪ Mama doesn't care ♪
♪ Mama's letting loose ♪
♪ Mama's got the stuff ♪
♪ Mama's letting go ♪
♪ Why did I do it? ♪
♪ Give them love
And what does it get you? ♪
♪ What does it get you? ♪
♪ One quick look
As each of them leaves you ♪
♪ All your life
And what does it get you? ♪
♪ Thanks a lot and out with the garbage ♪
♪ They take bows and you're batting zero ♪
♪ Everything's coming up roses ♪
♪ This time for me ♪
♪ For me ♪
[CHEERING]
Polly, that was spectacular.
Oh, it was okay.
Still working out the kinks.
Well, some of them.
I'm just glad I finally got to see
a bona fide burlesque star in the flesh.
But interestingly, not too much flesh.
Well, that is correct.
If you're good enough,
you can suggest more than show.
Well, you, my dear Ms. Amorous,
are better than good.
I'm just sorry that Mom didn't come.
I really thought that she might rally.
Oh, it's okay.
She doesn't believe in what I do.
But that's on her, not me or you.
But, Betty, if you take
anything from my visit, let it be this.
When you find the thing that you love,
just promise me that you'll do it.
No matter what Mom or anybody says.
I promise.
And...
I want nothing more
than to be your maid of honor.
[POLLY] Oh, Betty.
Oh. Consider yourself booked.
Wow.
Mrs. Grundy was right.
Staying up all night
really does make the dawn look...
Different somehow.
Yeah.
And now that we've...
expanded our horizons...
It seems like...
anything's possible at this point.
I love you, Reggie.
I love you too, bud.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sweetheart, something wrong?
Perhaps you should pray on it
in the chapel.
I don't get to go as often as I'd like,
but when I do, I find such comfort there.
[SCOFFS]
Toni, I have a question for you.
Do you still have the negatives
from our photo shoot?
Of course.
Why?
My hideous mother,
and by extension, my father...
I can't keep living at their mercy.
I wanna shut them up and shut them down.
Once and for all.
Didn't hear you come in last night.
I presume Polly's on her way
back to New York City?
- Yes.
- [ALICE SIGHS]
And I'm so jealous.
She has...
freedom,
a career she loves,
someone in her life who worships her.
That's more
than any one of us here can say.
Don't pick a fight with me, Elizabeth.
I'm not in the mood.
So when are you going to stop?
Stop sabotaging our family?
- Oh, is that what you think I'm doing?
- Isn't it?
Did you forget
when you disowned me as your daughter?
You drove Polly away.
We couldn't even have one night together,
the three of us,
because of your hang-ups.
You know what?
You are a sad, lonely woman.
And it is all your own doing.
But I'll tell you this, Mom.
I am not giving you
any more power over my life
because you will ruin it.
I'm going to do exactly what Polly did,
and the second I can leave this town,
I'm gone.
Fine.
Go!
Oh.
You should know, after last night,
I'm thinking of following
in Polly's footsteps
and becoming a burlesque dancer too.
Except maybe I'll take off all my clothes.
And then what will you tell your friends?
Or will you just pretend
that I don't exist
or that I died tragically?
- Elizabeth...
- It doesn't matter.
Because I won't be in this house.
I'll be far away from you,
doing whatever I want,
and you can't stop me.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
I'm surprised
it took you this long to do that.
[VERONICA] So, what happens now?
Well, if we don't follow their code,
we can't publish our comics
with their seal of approval.
And if we can't get that,
then publishers won't print our comics,
distributors will not ship them,
and newsstands will not sell them.
So we either follow their cockeyed rules
or we go the way of the dodos.
How can I have been so naïve?
I really thought
that there was a way through this.
You weren't naïve, Jughead.
You were fighting for what's right.
For what this country stands for.
Or what it's supposed to stand for.
Well, shucks.
Who even needs the Russian invasion
when we're happily destroying ourselves?
Don't you worry, Nick Charles.
We'll figure something out.
Oh, we will?
I mean...
I just sort of said that to say something.
But here we find ourselves...
once again.
Just the two of us.
We...
kind of blew it last time, didn't we?
We did.
But as I said...
here we are again.
Here we are again.
[PEACEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]