[JUGHEAD] After Mr. Cooper
told Mrs. Cooper
that Betty had been dancing in her window,
in her skivvies,
for Archie's, uh, benefit,
Mrs. Cooper phoned Hollywood, California,
So no wonder...
to give Hermione Lodge
a good old-fashioned East Coast what for
since Veronica had supplied
the skivvies in question.
Then Alice rang her good friend
Penelope Blossom
for advice about what to do,
mother to mother.
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
By what, Mother?
Operator, can you put me
through to Stratford, 747?
Alice Cooper needs help
saving her little hussy of a daughter.
Agnes. [CHUCKLES] You won't believe...
[JUGHEAD] So by morning, everyone knew
some version of what had happened,
most of it untrue.
And repercussions
were being felt far and near.
- She's never gonna talk to me, is she?
- Your mother just needs to understand
that you're a red-blooded
American young man,
and that Betty, well,
she's a voluptuous, ripe peach of a girl.
I just... I'm so embarrassed, Uncle Frank.
Well, were you caught
with your pants down?
Yes. Was what you were doing
a little raunchy?
Well, maybe.
But I'd be more worried if you weren't
showing an interest in that kitten.
But for now,
just keep up with your schoolwork,
focus on the basketball team,
stay away from Betty.
Take plenty of cold showers,
and we'll get you through this, Archie.
- All right?
- Yeah.
Good.
[ALICE] You cannot parade around naked
in front of boys.
Okay, again, Archie and I were not naked.
We were just...
having fun.
We were in separate houses, Mom.
What did you think was gonna happen?
With you, anything's possible.
Which is why, starting today,
you will be cutting a rug
on Riverdale Grandstand.
Mom, no.
Mom, I don't wanna be
part of Dad's dance show.
Only nerds and squares
are on Dad's dance show.
All right, enough of the sass, young lady.
You will be dancing from 3 to 6
every afternoon after school.
We will make sure
that you're nice and tuckered out
so there's no more late-night shows
with your pinky out of jail
for oversexed young men like Archie.
If I catch wind of you even saying hello
to that redheaded pervert, well...
You don't wanna see me frosted,
young lady.
["TWEEDLE DEE" PLAYING]
♪ Tweedle-y, tweedle-y, tweedle-y dee ♪
♪ I'm as happy as can be... ♪
Miss Veronica, pardon the interruption,
but a telegram arrived
from your parents, miss.
[GROANS] They must still be peeved
about Mrs. Cooper snitching on me.
"'Mija, you have been a bad girl.' Stop.
'Time to teach you a lesson.' Stop.
'No more allowance.' Stop.
'Report for work at the Babylonium Theater
today at 3:30, sharp.' Stop."
They're suspending my allowance
and making me get an after-school job?
Smithers, this is child abuse.
If they think they can break my spirit
as if I were a filly,
they're in for a rude awakening.
Hey, Dad.
Kevin, what are you doing with this?
Uh, it's... That's a bodybuilding magazine.
Where did you get that from,
that new pal of yours,
that Clay character?
His name's Clay Walker. No.
Uh, no, Dad. What...? What's going on?
I don't know.
I don't know, Kevin.
I mean, you cut your girlfriend loose,
you started hanging around
with strange boys,
and you're reading magazines like this.
I don't like much of any of it.
[JUGHEAD]
Meanwhile, I was wracked by guilt
over the fact that I betrayed my idol,
the science fiction writer
Brad Rayberry, when...
Mr. Jones.
[JUGHEAD]
...Featherhead called me on the carpet.
[WERTHERS] Care to explain this?
I have a part-time gig
writing comic books after school.
The content, Mr. Jones,
is what we're concerned about.
The violent, gruesome,
highly sexualized content,
all happening to students clearly
inspired by your peers here at Riverdale.
Aren't you ashamed to be associated
with such reprehensible dreck?
No, actually, I'm quite proud
to have my name on that cover.
And whose beeswax is it anyway
what I do with my time after school?
If we were to learn
that one of our students was involved
in the creation
and distribution of pornography,
we would absolutely expel them.
This is a comic book, sir.
This isn't a porno mag.
Well, we don't see them
as so very different, Mr. Jones.
Both are inappropriate for children,
both twist their minds and souls.
Cut the gas.
That's the biggest load of hooey
that's ever been laid on me in my life.
[FEATHERHEAD] It's very simple, Mr. Jones.
Sign this agreement
stating that you'll no longer write
horror and crime comic books,
and you'll remain a student here.
Refuse to sign it,
and we will take steps
to have you expelled.
[CHATTERING]
[CHATTERING STOPS]
- [BOY] Oh, my God.
- [GIRL] There she is.
- [WHISTLES]
- [STUDENTS CHUCKLING]
Andrews!
[BOYS APPLAUDING AND WHOOPING]
[VERONICA] Can I ask, how far did you get?
I'm hearing conflicting reports.
All we did was look at each other.
My favorite words in English,
"You can look, but you can't touch."
Well, Archie and I
won't be touching any time soon.
Or looking, for that matter.
Especially not now that I'm on
my dad's grody dance show every day.
- Riverdale Grandstand?
- Mm-hm.
I haven't seen it myself.
You know television makes my skin crawl,
but it seems like it could be a kick.
It's a bash.
More than that, it's an honor.
One, as dance captain,
I take very seriously.
Cheryl, how and why are you
a dance captain on Riverdale Grandstand?
Her parents are RIVW's biggest sponsor.
I do my part as dance captain
and spokeswoman.
- Vee, why don't you join the dance show?
- Absolutely not.
I would love to,
but I'm starting my new job
at the movie theater this afternoon.
Part of my punishment
for encouraging the corruption of minors.
Speaking of that, here's a list of rules
for participants, Betty,
in case you get any more pervy ideas.
"No chewing gum,
dress code strictly enforced,
no kissing, no groin-on-groin contact."
See you at 3:30. On the dot.
[BETTY SIGHS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Have fun now, Kevin.
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
- [FRANK] Everybody, bring it in.
I'm sure most of you know
your classmate Kevin Keller,
but as of today,
he's the newest member of our team,
so let's give him a big Bulldog welcome.
Swell. Just what we need,
a cream puff Bulldog.
[GLAMOROUS MUSIC PLAYING]
She's a knockout, isn't she?
Yes, she is. Fat city.
And you must be my new boss, Mr. Lemley.
Veronica Lodge.
And, please, whatever arrangement
my parents made with you,
let me assure you,
movie theaters are my happy place.
They have been ever since I attended
my first picture show, Babes in Arms.
So, what's my job? Ticket taker?
Popcorn girl? Usherette?
All of the above.
These days,
I can only afford a skeleton crew.
- That's pretty much you, me...
- And me.
I run the projector,
and try to keep on top of repairs
so that this place
doesn't collapse on itself.
- Enchanté, Clay.
- Enchanté.
I look forward
to getting to know you better
and being part of the team.
[HAL] All right, kids.
It's time for the Bop.
["I DO WHATTA DO" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ I do what, do what, do whatta do ♪
♪ I do whatta do ♪
♪ Well, they call it this
And you call it that ♪
♪ Say do this job, dig this cat... ♪
Betty, why aren't you dancing?
Because I don't wanna be here,
and I don't wanna dance.
You have to dance.
It's bad for ratings
if the camera pans this way
and catches the daughter
of our beloved host with the most
acting like a canceled stamp.
What do you what me to do?
Everyone's paired up.
That's not true. What about Dilton?
He hasn't had a steady partner since
Ethel went to Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
- Just don't maul him, for Pete's sake.
- Fine.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Just checking in.
- Don't stay up too late, now.
- Hey, Uncle Frank, um...
What were you and Sheriff Keller
talking about at practice today?
Oh, that he wants Kevin
to get more into sports.
He thinks he could use
some better male role models,
regular Joes like me and you.
Is something wrong with Kevin?
Well,
sometimes boys get confused
on how they're supposed to act.
But don't worry, Archie.
I promised Tom. You and me,
we'll straighten Kevin out.
Hey, Kev.
Hey, what are you doing during lunch?
I thought maybe we could hang out,
shoot some baskets.
Yeah, sure.
Gee, that's swell.
I'll see you in the gym.
Catch you later, Clay.
Mr. Rayberry.
I was wondering
if I could trade this check in for cash.
I don't trust banks.
[BERNIE] Sure, Mr. Rayberry.
Let me talk to Payroll.
Thank you.
- Again, I'm so sorry I...
- It's 12:30.
Shouldn't you be in school?
- I might have dropped out.
- Why?
Well, the finks at the top said
that if I don't stop writing comic books
and corrupting America's youth,
that I'll be expelled
for some cooked-up malarkey,
so I beat feet.
Huh.
Hope it's worth it.
What time is your lunch break, anyway?
Any time, I guess.
Hey, Kev. You know, you and I have been
in the same grade since kindergarten.
Why basketball? Why now?
Uh, it was my dad's idea.
I just think he wants me
to be a regular guy,
less of an off horse.
I mean, what does that even mean?
You know, a guy who likes sports,
who, um,
does like what you did with Betty.
Who isn't interested in things
like poetry, and drama,
and music, and movie stars, and...
- I like those things.
- Well, yeah, but you're...
What? What am I?
You're normal, Archie. You're normal.
Kevin, so are you.
Yeah, I wanna be, more than anything.
I just wanna be like everybody else.
[DOOR OPENS]
Ooh.
Again, and for the rest of my life,
I would like to apologize.
For stealing and reading my novel.
- For that, yeah. It was a chump move.
- Mm. Mm-hm.
You had every right to bite my head off.
I did.
That said, I, um...
I may have, uh, overreacted.
No, I totally understand
why you were being protective
over The Jupiter Journals,
Mr. Rayberry. I...
I think it's a masterpiece.
Huh.
If I wrote that manuscript,
I think I could die a happy man.
Well, before we start
planning your funeral,
let's talk about
you dropping out of school.
You should go back.
Education is important.
I just don't really see
why I have to choose
between writing comic books
and getting an education.
You shouldn't.
And this, young sir,
is what is known as a Gordian knot.
So tell me everything you know
about this Werthers clown.
Who he is, where he comes from,
what he's about, what he believes.
[BOYS WHISTLING]
- Fellas, an announcement.
- [BOYS CLAPPING AND WHOOPING]
Let's give a proud woof for Rogers here,
who finally did the dirty deed
with Jenny Stevens last night,
in the back of
his dad's Thunderbird no less.
[ALL WHOOPING AND CLAPPING]
Between Rogers and Andrews'
X-rated peep show with Betty Cooper,
we might wanna
rename our team the Horndogs.
[BOYS BARKING]
Question is,
which one of you fruitcakes is next?
Can't be a real man unless
you've gone all the way with a woman.
We all know Fogarty's solid.
You and Midge, right?
That's none of your beeswax there,
Blossom.
A man of mystery. Okay.
What about you, Keller?
What about you, Julian?
Pretty sure you're still a virgin.
Uh, keep dreaming.
Crossed into the promised land
on my 16th birthday,
when my dad took me to see Twyla Twyst.
Who's Twyla Twyst?
A floozy who works out of
the Cozy Time Motel behind the school.
Spend one night with her,
heck, even one hour,
and you'll never be the same.
What do you say, Keller?
You up for it?
- Put a lid on it, Julian. Kevin...
- [KEVIN] Yeah.
I'll do it. I'll go see her.
Attaboy, Keller. That's the spirit.
Let me know when and where.
[SLOW BALLAD PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
So, Clay, bring me up to speed.
Am I sensing you're a fellow cinephile?
It's actually what I wanna
study in college, filmmaking.
I know it sounds
nutty as a can of peanuts,
but I dream of one day inspiring people
like my hero inspired me.
- Oscar Micheaux.
- Who's he?
A Black director.
He started at the same time
as D. W. Griffith and Mary Pickford.
Well, if we're indulging
in pipe dreams today,
I've never been crazy about
being in front of the cameras,
but I do love being near them.
Well, maybe your destiny
is to run a studio one day,
and then you can hire me
to direct my first movie.
Deal.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, Mr. Lemley, when does our rush begin?
Um, you're looking at it.
Seems like it's gonna be
another slow night.
Uh, slow is one thing,
but graveyard-like is another.
What gives?
TV has taken a Dracula-sized bite
out of our business.
Also, that new drive-in
that's just opened up, the Starlight,
doesn't help either.
Excuse me, living rooms
and drive-ins cannot compete
with the experience of seeing a movie
in a palace like the Babylonium.
People need to be reminded of that.
How about an ad in the Riverdale Register?
Or what about a commercial on television
aired during Riverdale Grandstand?
All the kids will see it that way.
[JOVIAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Dancing up a storm sure is hard work.
That's why I like to fortify myself
throughout the day
with hearty helpings
of Blossom maple syrup.
- Try it on your pancakes...
- [JULIAN] Waffles...
- Biscuits...
- And even your favorite ice cream.
Nine out of 10 Americans agree
there is nothing quite like
the extra sweet flavor
of Blossom maple syrup.
And remember, kids,
it's not just for breakfast anymore.
Now in economy-sized tins.
[DIRECTOR] And cut!
["LISTEN TO ME, BABY"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
All right, kids, let's swing again
to "Listen to Me, Baby."
♪ Open your ears
Hear what I've got to say ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, open your ears
Hey there.
It's Betty, right?
I'm Troy.
My usual partner, Judy, has the mumps.
Wanna let me take you out for a spin?
Sure, you might as well.
Now, that's swell.
["MY MEMORIES OF YOU"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ All I have to keep me
Is my memories of you... ♪
♪ I sit alone at night... ♪
So is it true?
That you, uh, like it when guys watch you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come on, fess up.
I mean, we've all heard the story.
After we wrap here,
how about you and I go down to the river,
you can put on
a little private show for me?
Will you?
Get your paws off me, you creep.
[ALICE] Betty. Betty.
You cannot do that on live television.
Attagirl.
For the 100th time, it wasn't my fault.
Troy got fresh with me. He grabbed my...
If he did, it's because you have
created a fast reputation.
I barely touched him.
What is the matter with you?
You know what would solve this problem?
If you let me off Riverdale Grandstand.
You know what? I'll have a little chat
with all of the young men on our show,
and no one is going to dance with you.
Wait. So, what am I gonna be doing then?
You can sit in the corner
and stew like a sourpuss for all I care.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hi, Mr. Rayberry.
Oh, I'm sorry. Can I come in?
Sure, as long as you don't swipe anything.
Look, I've been thinking about it.
I don't wanna give up writing.
My high school diploma be damned.
I agree. And you're right,
you shouldn't stop writing.
But you do need a front.
- A cover.
- A front?
I have friends in Hollywood
who were blacklisted
when McCarthy was ringing the alarm
on the so-called communist threat,
and, uh, they kept writing,
but under pseudonyms.
You should do that. Hmm?
Publish what you want
under a different name,
and Werthers will be none the wiser.
Yeah, but do you really think
that Werthers is gonna buy
that I just quit
writing comic books altogether?
It's so simplistic, no?
Not if you muddy the waters.
Like if you tell Werthers
you're shifting your focus
off horror comic books
to, I don't know,
happy animal comic books.
Yeah. Yeah, like Super Duck.
Yeah, exactly.
Tell Werthers you're writing Super Duck,
uh, keep churning out the horror stories
under an alias,
and problem solved, right?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
God, Archie.
What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do? I...
Listen.
Just put yourself in her hands, Kevin.
Let nature take its course.
Is that how your first time went?
Kevin.
I'm still a virgin too.
You are?
Yeah.
Well, doesn't that beat all.
If I'm a virgin and you're a virgin,
why do I have to go to Twyla
and you don't?
Why do I have to prove something
It's funny how the world works, isn't it?
We're so pleased
you've come to your senses, Mr. Jones.
Just hold your horses.
We have some stipulations.
And what exactly is your interest in this,
Mr. Rayberry?
How do you even know Mr. Jones?
Well, we are colleagues at Pep Comics.
And I just most recently
started to mentor Jughead.
How, uh, magnanimous of you.
Jughead agrees to stop writing
horror comics, per this agreement.
But I will continue
to write comics for Pep.
Specifically Super Duck.
It's wholesome, family-friendly fare.
Unobjectionable, you might say.
Well, although we appreciate
Jughead's curbing the violent content
of his previous work...
Okay, let's cut the bull, doc. Okay?
What you were doing to my mentee
is unconstitutional.
And if you continue to harass him,
I am prepared to escalate this
as far as we need to go.
Are you talking about the PTA,
Mr. Rayberry?
Oh, I'm not talking about the PTA.
I'm talking about a little organization
called the U.S. Supreme Court.
So how does "Jones v. Board of Education"
sound to you?
I'm curious if the justices would take
the same stance regarding comic books
as you do, Mr. Werthers.
Namely, that they are as problematic
as hardcore pornography?
Gentlemen, let's not lose our heads.
I'm sure none of us
wanna blow this thing out of proportion.
And I'm not an expert,
but it seems to me
that this Super Duck character is, uh...
[CHUCKLES]
...quite harmless.
Wouldn't you agree, Dr. Werthers?
Yes. For the moment.
Great.
Well, this was just tops.
So glad to be back.
["LET'S MAKE LOVE TONIGHT"
PLAYING ON RECORD PLAYER]
♪ I've been waiting a long time ♪
♪ Just waiting... ♪
So, baby, Julian tells me
you're cruising for a good time.
Come. Dance with me.
You can follow my lead.
[WHISPERS] Let Twyla take care of you.
[DOOR BELLS JINGLING]
Hello.
Cooper.
Here you go. Thank you.
Betty.
Archie.
Thank you.
Uh, what are you up to?
Oh, you know, just...
picking up dinner
on my way home from the studio.
Say, uh, Betty.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Um...
When you and Kevin were dating...
what...?
How was he?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know. Uh, well...
his dad's got it into his head
that Kevin's funny, you know?
An off horse.
A little girly, I guess?
Archie, you don't expect me
to kiss and tell, do you?
No.
No, of course not.
Anyway, hopefully after tonight,
Kevin will straighten out and fly right.
What do you mean? Why?
What's happening tonight?
Nothing. [SIGHS]
God, I shouldn't have said anything.
Archie, what do you mean?
Tell me what's happening tonight.
Kevin, don't do it!
[KEVIN SNIFFLING]
Oh, God.
Am I too late? Did something bad happen?
The only thing that happened in here
was a whole lot of nothing.
We were having a little dance party,
I let down my hair a little,
then he started bawling like a baby,
saying, "I can't do it."
[TWYLA CHUCKLES]
But tonight might not be a total bust.
Come here, sugar.
You're a hunk and a half. Come to Twyla.
I'm just here for my friend.
Oh, he's your friend, is he?
That makes sense.
Twyla knows the score.
She's been around the block
more than once.
Take him.
He's all yours.
[ARCHIE] Come on, Kev. Let's split.
[KEVIN] Why'd you come get me, Archie?
I ran into Betty at Pop's.
I told her what was going on
and she blew a gasket.
She said I had to...
come and save you from doing something
that might scar you for life.
Boy, was she frosted.
What am I gonna say to the guys, Archie?
When they find out what happened,
what didn't happen,
it'll be the end of me.
I'm never gonna be a normal fella.
Hey, what about this?
We're gonna tell them
that you made it with Twyla.
That you went all the way.
I'll back you up.
And I'll give you some things to say.
Things that I've...
read in magazines
or heard my Uncle Frank say.
Don't worry, Kevin.
We're gonna get you on the stick
and sell it.
Okay.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
No matter who you are,
hot-rodder or cheerleader,
bookworm or jock,
square or beatnik,
deep down, we all yearn
for the same things.
Adventure, romance, excitement.
Well, what if I told you
that for just 49 cents,
you could have all that and more?
Movies have the power
to transport us all over the world,
but only if you see them in a theater
like the Babylonium.
They're magical, special places
where it even feels good to cry.
It's a scientific fact:
movies are better in movie theaters.
Come to the Babylonium
to laugh, to cry,
to sit in the dark and experience
something powerful together,
and fall in love with the movies again
for the first time.
Well, Mr. Lemley?
What did you think of the commercial?
Perfection.
So why don't you buy a few choice spots
and see if it gets word of mouth going?
Veronica, I've been negotiating
the sale of the Babylonium
to an interested party
for the last few months.
The official offer finally came through.
Who's buying it?
Well, it's your parents.
That's how I know them.
My parents?
[VERONICA SCOFFS]
They're not even
in the movie theater business.
They don't even appreciate movies.
Well, I assumed you knew.
It's my understanding they're gonna
turn the Babylonium into a parking lot.
Mr. Rayberry,
that Supreme Court bit was inspired.
You had Dr. Werthers quaking in his boots,
and Principal Featherhead's face
was priceless.
Straw men fall easily.
But I'm glad, though,
that you're going back to school,
and that you get
to keep writing comic books.
Mm. I wanted to talk to you about that.
What if you were to really be my mentor?
I'm open.
Let me finish this milkshake
before we sign any adoption papers, huh?
Right-o. Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Look, I did wanna tell you, though,
that I've decided to re-read my novel.
I think it's time.
An Edward Hopper original.
Bet you're worth a pretty penny.
Dad?
You had quite an eventful evening.
I know that you went and saw Twyla.
How?
Did Julian tell you?
Only because I asked for him
to suggest it to you in the first place.
[CHUCKLES]
I thought maybe if the idea
came from one of your classmates,
you might be more inclined to do it.
- Well...
- I spoke to Twyla.
Right after Archie came and rescued you.
She told me what happened.
That you couldn't or wouldn't.
That you started to cry.
I don't know
exactly what happened last night,
but Tom just called,
and he told me that Kevin
will no longer be on the basketball team.
Poor Tom.
I feel for him, having a son who's bent.
Such a shame.
What about your breakfast?
Lost my appetite.
Hmm.
I've been mulling over our conversation
from yesterday, Mr. Lemley,
and I'd like to buy the Babylonium.
More specifically,
I'd like to trade this painting
from my personal collection
for your theater.
I've spoken to Crestby's,
and I think you'll find that,
on the open market,
an original Hopper is worth much more
than what my parents are offering you.
- I'm deep in negotiations with your folks.
- I know.
But...
our commercial wasn't false advertising.
Going to the movies is special.
Working here at the Babylonium,
even briefly,
has rekindled something in me.
Plus, wouldn't you feel better
knowing that someone's keeping
the lights on and the projector running?
Showing the Babylonium the same love
and respect that you have all these years?
I don't know.
I think I messed up with Kevin, Betty.
- I think I made things worse.
- No, Arch.
You were trying to include him,
make him feel like a part of things.
You protected him as best as you could.
Well, isn't this a sight to behold?
My mother and father
wanted to invite any and all students
to this afternoon's taping
of Riverdale Grandstand.
- Why today's?
- [CHERYL] Because it's our 50th episode
and my parents wanna see
some fresh faces on screen.
Toodle-loo.
I can't believe
how screwed up the world is.
I know.
The hypocrisy.
No matter what we're going through,
what our parents are putting us through,
as long as we show up on Grandstand
smiling and dancing like trained seals,
everything is peachy keen.
And all the grownups do
is tell us what to think, how to act.
How to dress, who to date.
They're trying to control our lives,
and there's not a thing we can do.
[BETTY] Maybe.
But maybe not.
["KO KO MO (I LOVE YOU SO)"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Ko, ko, mo, ko, ko, mo
Ko, ko, mo ♪
♪ Oh, talk to me, baby
Whisper in my ear ♪
♪ Talk to me, baby
♪ Come a little closer
Don't have no fear ♪
♪ Don't you know... ♪
Okay, boys and girls.
Now it's time
for America's latest dance craze.
The twirl.
- ["RED HOT" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
- [AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
♪ My gal is red hot ♪
♪ Your gal ain't doodly-squat ♪
♪ Yes, she is
My gal is red hot ♪
♪ Your gal ain't doodly-squat ♪
♪ She ain't got a lotta money
But, loving, she's really got a lot ♪
♪ Ha, ha
My gal is red hot... ♪
- Hey.
- [BETTY] Hey.
You cool cats wanna see
what a real twirl looks like?
♪ Your gal ain't doodly-squat ♪
♪ She ain't got a lotta money
But, loving, she's really got a lot ♪
♪ My gal can do the shimmy
She can do the boogie too ♪
♪ And if she ain't a Jim Dandy
She's a snapperoo ♪
♪ Ooh, my gal is red hot ♪
♪ Your gal ain't doodly-squat ♪
♪ She ain't got a lotta money
But, loving, she's really got a lot ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ That's my gal, man
That's my gal... ♪
Alice. Alice.
- Alice!
- [ALICE SHRIEKS]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- No, no, no.
Stop filming.
Cut to commercial...
[TEST TONE PLAYING]
Do you have any idea
how much trouble
you could get the station in?
You're out of control.
No, Mom.
I am in complete control.
I knew exactly what I was doing and why.
What?
Now, Mother, may I please be excused
from future episodes
of Riverdale Grandstand?
You are off the show!
But you broke my heart, Betty.
[SMITHERS] You rang, Ms. Veronica?
Yes, Smithers.
I'd like you to send
a telegram to my parents.
Dear Mom and Dad. Stop.
I am now the new owner
of the Babylonium. Stop.
Which will never
turn into a parking lot. Stop.
My best to Uncle Orson. Stop.
[ARCHIE] Hey, Kev.
Clay.
What are you guys doing for lunch?
Um...
Sorry, Archie,
my basketball days are over.
Yeah, I heard.
I was actually hoping
to break bread with you guys.
Talk about things like music,
plays, movie stars.
Why not?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, that's boss.
Save me a spot in the lounge.
["HOT MAMA" PLAYING]
♪ I'm a hot mama ♪
- ♪ I'm known by that name ♪
- ♪ Hot mama ♪
♪ I'm just a hot mama ♪
- ♪ I'm known by that name ♪
- ♪ Hot mama ♪
♪ Hot mama ♪
♪ Hands off, daddy
If you can't cool the plane ♪
♪ Hot mama, hot mama ♪
♪ I'm warning all you chicks
Telling you what's right ♪
♪ Hot mama ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm warning all you chicks
Telling you what's right... ♪
[MUSIC DISTORTS, THEN STOPS]
Ms. Cooper.
Might I have a word with you in my office?
Your mother called me last night.
She's very concerned.
About you and your...
erratic behavior.
Yes, well, a teenage girl
with a mind and desires of her own,
it's all very concerning, isn't it?
Hmm.
You're so tortured, Betty.
What are we going to do with you?
[JUGHEAD] And with Dr. Werthers
shifting his glowering attention
from me to Betty...
I was now able to continue
my budding comic career on twin tracks
with the prospect
of Mr. Rayberry as my mentor
keeping me up and typing
late into the night.
[RELAXING MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD PLAYER]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Evening, sir.
Apologies for the late delivery.