[JUGHEAD] After my encounter
with the crazy cat lady
down the hall from Mr. Rayberry's,
I went back to Sheriff Keller.
But he wasn't buying what I was selling.
Walk me through this again.
Mr. Rayberry's neighbor heard milk bottles
the night that he was killed.
Ethel saw a milkman
the night that her parents were murdered.
So if you put two and two together,
I think it's no sweat
to say that we have a...
killer milkman at large.
- Do you agree?
- Mr. Rayberry killed himself.
- We have established that.
- No, you have. I have not.
Unless that neighbor said that they saw
someone dressed as a milkman,
saw, not heard,
then I am not reopening
that case again, Jughead.
So I think it's time
that you dropped this.
And don't forget our ban tomorrow night.
Halloween is for kids, all right?
It's not for teenagers
looking to make trouble.
[RADIO ANNOUNCER]
Rise and shine, Riverdale.
It's October 29, 1955,
which means it's high time
to get in the mood for Halloween.
[JUGHEAD] Killer milkman in Riverdale?
Better safe than sorry.
["DRAC'S BACK" PLAYING]
♪ Igor's in chains
And he's doing it right ♪
♪ The coffins are open
And left in the ground ♪
♪ Drac's back ♪
♪ Now is the time
To really shake them down ♪
♪ Drac's back, Drac's back ♪
♪ Drac's looking for his wife
All over the hall ♪
♪ Vampira, where are you? ♪
♪ Well, Vampira's getting up
And she's raring to go ♪
♪ Drac's back, Drac's... ♪
[RECORD SCRATCHES, MUSIC STOPS]
I admit, I usually get a better response
when I pull my witch costume
out of the mothballs.
What gives?
Well, it's not your costume, Vee.
You look...
like everything-plus.
It's just, um...
Riverdale has a funny relationship
with Halloween.
Dare I ask?
Unfortunately, we don't embrace
All Hallows' Eve
the same way Greendale does.
We have rules in Riverdale.
Trick-or-treating's for kids.
Teenagers aren't allowed
into the streets after sundown.
Why not?
There was a, uh...
A tragedy a few years back
on Halloween night.
A carload of Riverdale High students
were out raising heck,
and they ran off the road.
- They died. All four of them.
- Two Vixens, two Bulldogs.
So, what are teenagers
expected to do on Halloween?
[FANGS] Nothing much.
Stay at home.
Hand out candy to ankle-biters.
My dad and his officers drive around,
make sure no one's
cruising the roads, raising Cain.
Back home in Duck Creek,
we never celebrated Halloween.
But teenagers need Halloween.
To dress up in costumes and masks
and pretend to be someone else.
To be a kid again,
even if it's just for a night.
To kiss a girl or a boy in the dark
and blame it on the Halloween spirit.
To honor the dead.
The dead?
Back in Los Angeles,
my parents used to throw the most lavish
costume balls every Halloween night.
Then, afterwards,
in the wee hours of November 1st,
we'd all gather around the family altar,
just the three of us,
and light votive candles
to honor the dead.
And celebrate Día de los Muertos.
It was one of our only family traditions.
And my favorite, by far.
In any case,
it sounds like our gatekeepers
are trying to put the kibosh
on one of the most phantasmagoric
nights of the year.
Little do they know...
Halloween is practically my middle name.
And I have
every intention of celebrating it.
I mean, really, just when you think
this town couldn't get any kookier.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Put those milk cartons down!
No!
All right, everyone listen.
Don't drink fresh milk anymore.
Just drink powdered milk.
- [BETTY] Is he okay?
- [ARCHIE] I'm not even gonna try...
[JUGHEAD] Ethel, how are you?
I'm okay, Jughead.
I miss you.
I miss school.
Gosh, Ethel.
I don't mean to upset you further,
but there's been another murder.
- Do you remember the writer Brad Rayberry?
- The guy who wrote November County?
- He's your favorite, right?
- Yeah, he was.
I was working with him, but I suspect
that he's part of the Milkman murders.
Or he was killed by a milkman.
Murdered? Why?
Well, that's what
I'm trying to figure out.
Did your parents
have any connection to Rayberry?
No.
This can't be
just some big coincidence, can it?
I don't know, Jug.
But you know what I have been noodling on?
What?
The Milkman comic book?
The original one?
Maybe whoever wrote it
in the first place knows something.
Say, that's a good tip.
- I'm gonna look into that...
- Oh, gosh. I gotta go.
Sister Woodhouse
is giving me the evil eye,
but hopefully I will see you soon.
I can't believe you've never experienced
a real Halloween before, Reg.
Just like any other night.
Wake up early the next morning,
same as always.
Does that mean
you've never worn a costume?
Or gone trick-or-treating before?
I went cow-tipping with my cousins.
Does that count?
["IT'S A WOMAN'S WORLD" PLAYING]
♪ Woman's world ♪
♪ It's a woman's world ♪
♪ When she's in love ♪
♪ And he's so glad it is ♪
♪ For when it's hers, it's his ♪
[ARCHIE] All right, Betty.
Sorry, what?
I was just saying, since Reggie
hasn't had a real Halloween growing up...
why don't we give him one?
Yeah, absolutely.
What is a real Halloween anyhow?
Well, one, trick-or-treating.
Two, visiting a graveyard.
And three...
necking in a haunted house.
All very possible things
to do in a town like Riverdale.
[THUDDING NEARBY]
The projection room.
At this hour?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
And what are you two
doing here at the witching hour?
We were just...
We were on our way home
from the Dark Room,
and I forgot my keys earlier,
so we were just swinging by
to pick them up.
Well-parried, Clay.
What are you doing here?
Some late-night brainstorming.
Oh, and I have good news.
I know exactly what we're going to do
for Halloween night.
We're going to host a ghost show
here at the Babylonium.
And the powers that be
won't be able to object,
as technically, we'll be keeping
the teenyboppers off the streets.
I'm thinking 1920s glam
for the dress code.
Ginchy idea, no?
Yeah. Um, what's a ghost show?
[SIGHS] It's a little bit of this,
a little bit of that.
Monsters, movies, burlesque.
And then at midnight...
we raise the dead.
- [HAUNTING ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VERONICA] Hear ye, hear ye.
Come one, come all,
to the Babylonium's hair-raising
Halloween burlesque and ghost show.
One night only.
- There will be music.
- There will be mayhem.
And then, as Halloween
gives way to the Day of the Dead,
there will be a resurrection,
as the four Riverdale high students
who oh-so tragically died
on Halloween night all those years ago
return from the dead
before your very eyes.
Get your tickets fast,
before they vanish without a trace.
- [GIRL 1] I'll take a ticket.
- [GIRL 2] Me too.
[CHATTERING]
[JUGHEAD] Mr. Fieldstone,
do you remember who wrote
the Milkman story inside this issue?
I wanna ask him a couple questions.
Kid, I haven't the foggiest.
But most of our Pep Comic freelancers
will be at the annual
Halloween office party.
Why don't you come by and sniff around?
You might find the guy.
Thanks, Mr. Fieldstone. I'll do just that.
So, beauty queen, any plans for Halloween?
Because I was thinking
we could spend it together.
Veronica's got me roped
into her ghost show,
but it would be a gas
if you joined in on the fun too.
She's got some sort of floor show planned,
complete with a kickline.
That... we would perform?
In front of people?
Yeah.
You and me and Kevin and Clay.
Don't tell me you have stage fright.
No, but it is tradition that I host
a sleepover for the Vixens every year.
No big whoop.
I just thought Halloween's
the one night of the year
where everyone wears a mask,
and people like us,
you and me and Kevin and Clay,
we don't have to, you know?
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[FRANK] All right, fellas. Bring it in.
Just one last thing before we break.
Now, I know Halloween is coming up fast
and it used to be
Bulldog tradition to go out wilding.
I have one thing to say.
Don't do it.
Not on my watch.
Understood?
[ALL] Yes, coach!
All right, then.
Bravo.
Gold star, fellas.
Even I almost believed you.
- What are you bugging about, Julian?
- It's Halloween, Andrews.
Of course the Bulldogs are going wilding,
despite what coach says.
Count me out.
I'm playing the ghost show
at the Babylonium.
- No one asked you, greaser.
- [FANGS SCOFFS]
What about you two?
- You coming or what?
- No, I'm gonna sit this one out.
I promised my folks
I wouldn't cause trouble in Riverdale.
Good God, Mantle.
Let me know when you grow a pair.
For those of you
who actually care about tradition
and aren't namby-pamby cream puffs,
we're meeting tomorrow night.
School parking lot.
At sundown.
[BARKING]
I still can't fathom
that Reggie's never celebrated Halloween.
Go figure.
That's why Archie and I
are showing him what it's like.
In that case, you're excused
from my phantasmagoria at the Babylonium.
But tell me, Betty,
what's your skin in this game?
Because I'm sensing you have some.
Well, I used to get
butterflies for Archie.
I still do.
But now I think
I'm also getting them for Reggie.
You know...
you should use Halloween night
to figure out which way
your love compass is truly pointing.
And then?
And then let the spirit move you.
And then tell me all about it
the next day.
So, Cheryl, I've been thinking
about tomorrow's slumber party.
I think you and the girls,
instead of sleeping in your bedroom,
should decamp to the grand hall.
It's more open.
Less opportunity
for inappropriate hanky-panky.
Yuck, Mother. I'm trying to eat here.
Just make sure
that's good and secure, boys.
I don't want any lawsuits on my hands.
Wise words, Veronica.
Mrs. Cooper.
What a lovely yet unexpected surprise.
- Mm.
- What can I do for you?
I was in the neighborhood.
Just thought I would pop in.
How are ticket sales
going for your little ghost show?
Briskly.
We should be sold out.
[ALICE] You're new in town.
But this is how
we celebrate Halloween in Riverdale.
Everyone stays home
and watches Mr. Cooper and I
host Shock Theater on RIVW.
We dress up in singed clothes,
and we introduce old horror flicks.
We have a little banter in between.
It's quite the event.
We really gives families a tickle.
Well, we're not really
expecting a family crowd.
More... teenagers.
Exclusively.
You like to cause trouble,
don't you, Veronica?
You're a natural-born rabble-rouser.
I can tell.
At any rate, I will allow
this little ghost show to happen.
It's not gonna affect our ratings.
But I want you to know, young lady,
you've been put on notice.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[LOUD CLANG NEARBY]
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[PANTING]
Ethel.
How in the heck did you escape
the Sisters of Quiet Mercy?
I started hearing about secret tunnels
beneath the nunnery
right when I got there.
Spent every free moment I had
looking for them.
Found them a couple days ago.
It was your call that gave me the push
I needed to make a break for it.
I really couldn't...
bear to be there for another second.
The sisters are cruel and abusive.
Well, they'll probably
come looking for you.
- What's your plan?
- My birthday's in a couple months.
Once I'm 18,
I won't be a ward of the state anymore,
and I can live on my own.
I just need to make it until then.
Where are you gonna hide in the meantime?
This place isn't exactly safe, Ethel.
It got ransacked by John Law, remember?
But I do know a place that you could stay.
It's Mr. Rayberry's apartment.
It's still empty, and he's got rent paid
until the end of the year.
As long as staying
in a dead guy's apartment
doesn't give you the heebie-jeebies.
- Could be haunted.
- I would rather ghosts than the sisters.
Then you're made in the shade.
And I can get you a cheap Halloween mask
so you can walk the streets incognito.
Once we get to the party,
you won't have to worry.
And you can help me suss out
who wrote that Milkman comic.
How's that sound?
Yes, Midge?
How can I help you?
[SIGHS] Do you have a special request
for the sleepover?
Um, that's the thing. I...
I wanted to see if I might be excused
from the slumber party.
You see, Fangs is performing
at Veronica's ghost show
and it would be gangbusters to see him.
Midge, with all due respect
to your greaser boyfriend,
this is a Vixen tradition.
The center must hold.
Of course.
I figured as much.
But I had to at least try.
Wait.
As it happens,
I, too, am intrigued
by Veronica's midnight burlesque.
So if I asked Evelyn
to host the slumber party,
and you know that witchy witch would,
and we went to the Babylonium...
we can never, ever speak
of what we did or saw at the ghost show.
I'd be okay with that.
I'm good at keeping secrets.
Me, too, dear Midge.
Perhaps it's time
we both confide in each other.
Maybe on Halloween night,
after the festivities?
I'm on pins and needles.
[FEATHERHEAD] Mr. Jones.
Are you aware that your friend
Ethel Muggs went missing last night?
She escaped
from the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Ain't that a bite?
No. No, I had no idea.
So if we searched your train car,
she wouldn't be there?
Please, go ahead. Door's unlocked.
Uh, but if you could just not trash it
like you did last time.
The place is practically the Waldorf now.
Can I go?
["SPOOKSVILLE" PLAYING]
Dang.
- Your mom's costume work is top notch.
- Yeah.
She was keen to do it.
Started to get the weeps 'cause she said
it was probably the last time
she'll be sewing Halloween costumes.
[CHUCKLES] Until she has grandkids.
- Hey, what do you think Betty's going as?
- Maybe a princess?
Or... Rosie the Riveter.
Man, I can't believe
how much she knows about fixing up cars.
Yeah, how'd that happen anyway?
Her fixing your jalopy?
Did you ask, or did she offer?
No, she offered, but the truth is,
I was kind of getting
vibes off her, you know?
Vibrations.
Well, trust me, I know.
If I'm being honest,
I've been getting vibes from Betty
since way before you got to town, so...
And I still am.
You don't think Betty wants to make it
with one of us tonight, do you?
I hadn't considered that, but...
she ain't blind.
Well, she might wanna get with me, Reg.
Like I said, we do have a history.
Yeah.
Well...
Let's make a pact, then.
If something goes on
between Betty and one of us,
as soon as we start feeling
which way she's leaning,
then the other guy peels off and vamooses.
What do you say?
You got yourself a deal there,
Buck Rogers.
["VOODOO DRUMS" PLAYING]
[CHATTERING]
- ♪ Voodoo drum ♪
- ♪ Beating in my heart ♪
♪ Telling me I'll never leave my island ♪
[BERNIE] Jughead!
Welcome to the Madhouse of Mystery.
Who's your friend?
Or should I say "fiend"?
Bernie, this is Ethel. You may have met.
She's been here a couple times.
- Hi. Happy Halloween.
- And to you.
Get yourself a snootful and settle in.
It's gonna be a crazy night.
Okay, let's enter the fray.
Ask around, see if anyone knows
about the origin of the Milkman comic.
Good evening, ghouls and boils,
to what I'm sure will be
the most electrifying night of your life.
I'm your host...
Thanks for volunteering
to be our kid tonight, Dilton.
You're really going
above and beyond your duties as water boy.
It's no sweat, fellas.
It's kind of hard
to say no to a girl like Betty.
[FOLK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Oh, I knew somehow ♪
♪ Someone to plead ♪
♪ I need you desperately... ♪
Well, boys.
How do I look?
Wow. Gee whiz, Betty.
You look tremendous.
Ring the bell. I'm knocked out.
- Who are you supposed to be?
- Goldilocks, of course.
You know, she couldn't decide on a bed,
so she tried all three.
Shall we head out
and see where the night takes us?
A doctor of dentistry.
Oh, what are you complaining about?
["DEAD" PLAYING]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[ALL] Trick or treat!
♪ I saw a ghost and zombies
Lookin' very much alive ♪
♪ I was alone and bewildered... ♪
[JULIAN WHOOPING]
[BOY 1] Come on!
[BOY 2] Yeah!
[WHOOPING AND CHEERING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
That's it. I'm going home.
[REGGIE] Wait, Dilton.
We're just getting started.
I'm dressed as a pumpkin head.
And Julian and those clowns
have baseball bats.
I'm doneski.
It's okay, Dilton.
You've been a swell sport tonight.
You can go home.
Yeah, we've got
a cemetery to get to anyhow.
[BAND PLAYING ROCK MUSIC]
[CHEERING AND CHATTERING]
♪ In the afterlife ♪
♪ You could be headed
For the serious strife ♪
♪ Now you make the scene all day ♪
♪ But tomorrow there'll be hell to pay ♪
♪ In the afterlife ♪
♪ You could be headed for serious strife ♪
♪ Now you make the scene all day ♪
♪ But tomorrow there'll be hell to pay ♪
♪ People listen attentively ♪
♪ I mean about future calamity... ♪
- You made the scene.
- As promised.
Well, you look fab as a flapper.
How did it shake out
with the rest of the Vixens?
As far as anyone else is concerned,
Midge and I have been stricken
with 24-hour influenza
and we're self-quarantining.
Well, it means a lot to me
that you came and are willing to perform.
Veronica's over the moon about it.
So am I.
Well, as you say, it's Halloween.
If we can't let our masks slip tonight,
when can we?
Come on. Let's get you ready.
♪ Teeth are extruded
And bones are ground ♪
♪ And baked into cakes
Which are passed around ♪
['50S ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHATTERING]
So, Randall, you didn't write
The Milkman Cometh?
No, but I sure wish I had.
Best story Pep published last year.
Sorry I can't be more help.
Jonah, did you write The Milkman Cometh?
No, and between us,
I didn't think
it was such great shakes, either.
Did you write The Milkman Cometh?
Or do you know who did?
The Milkman?
Yeah, that was one of Ted's stories.
- Ted?
- Ted Sullivan, a journeyman writer.
Ted?
Ted Sullivan?
- Is he here?
- Uh, no.
Ted's dead.
A few weeks
after his Milkman story was published,
they found him kaput in his apartment.
Dead?
- How?
- Hung himself.
Left a note saying he'd never write
another story as good as the Milkman one.
It's a metaphor.
A critique of America.
It's saying that the enemy is us.
What are you talking about?
The enemy is here, at home.
It's not Mother Russia.
It's not the Communists.
It's not the Axis of Evil.
It's us.
We're the enemies.
Wholesome, conforming, homogenous America.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTH MIMICKING WOLVES HOWLING]
You know why wolves howl, don't you?
To attract a mate.
And how do you know that?
We've got lots of wolves in Duck Creek.
Packs and packs of them.
Well, it must have made it...
pretty scary growing up there.
More like exciting.
Though they never caused me any trouble.
Maybe because they recognized
a fellow... alpha.
Is that what you think you are?
An alpha?
- Uh...
- [VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[JULIAN WHOOPING]
Damn, Julian and his goons are still out.
Well, that's not good.
Wonder where the rest of our wolf pack is.
Gosh, Archie. I'm so sorry.
- I didn't even think about the fact that...
- That's okay. I'm okay.
I was thinking about how my mom and dad
used to take us trick-or-treating.
- You remember that?
- Of course.
You remember the year we dressed
as Becky Thatcher and Tom Sawyer?
Yeah, of course I do.
I went barefoot.
I stepped on a nail.
Right.
We've been friends for a really long time.
Yeah, we have been.
Feels like I've known you my entire life.
I feel the same way.
[REGGIE] Hey.
So where's this haunted house, anyway?
Well, come on,
and let me show you the way.
If you're brave enough.
[ARCHIE] So this is where it happened.
The murder you guys were telling me about?
Yes.
It's hard to imagine
your life ending so...
suddenly.
Violently.
My dad used to say, "Seize the day."
Like, is your next moment
gonna be your last before the big chill?
I'm gonna go see
if there's any 11-Up in the refrigerator.
[ARCHIE CLEARS THROAT]
Hey.
I'm gonna cut out of here.
No, you don't have to do that.
Come on, Andrews.
I saw you two
in the cemetery holding hands.
You don't need a seismograph
to pick up those vibrations.
Okay, Reg. If you say so.
I do.
[BETTY] Well, they're warm,
but I found some orange sodas
in the icebox.
Where'd Reggie go?
Oh. Got tired.
Called it a night.
That's too bad.
Yeah.
Isn't it?
Gals and ghouls,
thank you all for coming out tonight.
In just a few minutes,
we'll be screening our midnight feature,
Frankenstein,
starring my godfather Boris Karloff.
But before we do that,
you were all promised
a resurrection tonight, and a floor show.
[CHEERING]
Well, Veronica Lodge,
or should I say Victoria Frankenstein,
keeps her promises.
So without further ado,
I give you the electrifying return
of the four dead Riverdale High students,
so enjoy.
And don't dream it, friends.
Be it.
- [ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
♪ It was great when it all began ♪
♪ I was a regular Frankie fan ♪
♪ But it was over when he had the plan ♪
♪ To start working on a muscle man ♪
♪ Now the only thing that gives me hope ♪
♪ Is my love of a certain dope ♪
♪ Rose tints my world
Keeps me safe from my trouble and pain ♪
♪ I am just seven hours old ♪
♪ Truly beautiful to behold ♪
♪ And somebody should be told ♪
♪ My libido hasn't been controlled ♪
♪ Now the only thing I've come to trust ♪
♪ Is an orgasmic rush of lust ♪
♪ Rose tints my world
Keeps me safe from my trouble and pain ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ It's beyond me ♪
♪ Help me, Mommy ♪
♪ It'll be good, you'll see ♪
♪ Take this dream away ♪
♪ What's this? ♪
♪ Let's see ♪
♪ I feel sexy ♪
♪ What's come over me? ♪
♪ Here it comes again ♪
♪ I feel released ♪
♪ Bad times deceased ♪
♪ My confidence has increased ♪
♪ Reality is here ♪
♪ The game has been disbanded ♪
♪ My mind has been expanded ♪
♪ It's a gas that Frankie's landed ♪
♪ His lust is so sincere ♪
[CROWD CHEERING]
♪ What ever happened to Fay Wray? ♪
♪ That delicate, satin draped frame ♪
♪ As it clung to her thigh ♪
♪ How I started to cry ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanted to be dressed ♪
♪ Just the same ♪
♪ Give yourself over ♪
♪ To absolute pleasure ♪
♪ Swim the warm waters
Of sins of the flesh ♪
♪ Erotic nightmares ♪
♪ Beyond any measure ♪
♪ And sensual daydreams ♪
♪ To treasure forever ♪
♪ Can't you just see it? ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
[ALL] ♪ Don't dream it ♪
♪ Be it ♪
♪ Don't dream it ♪
[KEVIN] ♪ It's beyond me ♪
♪ Help me, Mommy ♪
♪ God bless Lilly Saint Cyr ♪
[CHEERING]
- [VEHICLE APPROACHING]
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[JULIAN] Well, well, well.
If it isn't Mantle the Magnificent.
I'm just walking home, Julian.
Oh, come on.
Don't be such a stick in the mud.
We're going across the bridge to Greendale
to raise some hell. Hop in.
Come on. Join the fun.
Unless you've got something better to do.
- Move over.
- [JULIAN CHUCKLES]
[JULIAN] Attaboy.
Well, here we are, I guess.
Here we are. Just the two of us.
- I'm really nervous.
- [BETTY CHUCKLES]
I think I wanna kiss you.
I feel exactly the same way.
[BOTTLES CLANKING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS] Oh, my God!
- What is it?
- There's someone out there.
There's no one. What did he look like?
This is gonna sound loony tunes,
but he looked like... a milkman?
- A milkman?
- Let's just go, Arch. Let's go.
All right. Let's punch it.
Well, gents.
Looks like we had ourselves
a smashing success.
For the ages.
I was in on the gag,
and even I had goose pimples.
All of which makes me think.
What if we institute
a weekly midnight movie?
A monster flick,
or something fun and campy.
It sounds like a gas.
But, uh, Veronica...
Kevin and I, we, um...
wanted to talk to you about something.
Oh.
What's that?
How long have you
been living at the Babylonium?
And why?
Is it trouble with your parents?
Look at you two Hardy Boys.
All right. You fellas got wise to me.
I am staying here.
But there isn't a problem.
There's nothing wrong.
The Pembrooke
is merely undergoing renovations.
That's all.
I'll be back in my regular digs
before Thanksgiving.
Now skedaddle.
And truly, everything's peachy.
[CHERYL] Midge, Fangs.
I don't know what to say about
your happy news except congratulations.
Oh, Cheryl. I've been dying
to tell you the truth for ages.
Well, of course,
your secret is safe with me.
Not to take anything away
from my honey bun,
but you two had a pretty big moment
during the floor show.
That was some kiss.
Yeah, I'm not complaining,
but it was pretty brazen, Cheryl.
If I'm ever challenged about it,
I will simply explain that I was possessed
by the Halloween spirit.
Can I just say that I'm really happy
that us four put our masks away,
even if it was only
for one short, magical night?
I wholeheartedly concur.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, despite our bogeyman ending,
this was the best Halloween
of my entire life, Betty Cooper.
Mine too.
[ALICE] Elizabeth!
Mrs. Cooper?
Why are you out so late?
Mom,
I thought you weren't my mother anymore.
I'm not, but you still live in this house,
so get your butt inside
right this instant.
Bye.
Get.
["ENVENENAME LOS LABIOS"
PLAYING ON RECORD PLAYER]
[SIGHS]
Do you wanna come in?
Oh, I would, but I'm pretty tuckered out.
Plus, I haven't fed Hot Dog,
so I'll just see you tomorrow.
Or later today, I guess.
Is that hunky-dory?
Yeah.
Sure.
Good night, Jug.
Good night.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
- Oh. I thought you were the milkman.
- Milkman?
I heard his bottles earlier today.
I thought he might have come back.
You heard his...?
Ethel?
[GRUNTING]
Jeepers.
I told everyone it was a milkman.
[FRANK] Archie.
Archie, wake up.
Come on. Get dressed.
Uncle Frank.
What's wrong?
There's been some kind of accident.
A car full of Bulldogs went off the bridge
and into Sweetwater River.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, is...? Are there any survivors?
We don't know yet.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]