[swing music playing]
[Jughead] Some towns are football towns.
Some are hockey towns.
Riverdale High had a so-so football team.
And in the dead of winter,
kids played hockey on Sweetwater River
once it had frozen solid.
But at its heart,
Riverdale was a basketball town,
long past its heyday, some would say.
Which was when
the Riverdale High Bulldogs,
led by point guard Fred Andrews,
were State Champions three years running.
[buzzer sounds]
[announcer]
That's another big loss for Riverdale.
[Archie] Hey, look, fellas.
We fought the good fight out there.
We got the rest of the season
to dust ourselves off.
- Get back on top.
- Not if we keep playing like pansies.
You're all a bunch of spineless,
pillow-soft chumps.
You're lucky my parents still sponsor us.
We're a panic and a half!
Cut the gas, captain.
Nobody's jazzed about
what happened out there.
The Bulldogs? We used to be unstoppable.
Back when your dad played,
they were the champs, not the chumps.
Now, I know that you
don't wanna spoil that legacy.
What did Mr. Blossom want?
I finally convinced our lead sponsor
to let me recruit an outside player.
Kid who knows how to win games.
You know me.
I'll take any help we can get.
- Who's the guy? A ringer?
- A farm kid out of Duck Creek.
6'3", 220 pounds, pure muscle. But fast.
- What's his name?
- Mantle.
Reggie "The Blur" Mantle.
- "The Blur"?
- 'Cause you never see him coming.
["Gee I Wish" playing]
♪ Well, gee, I wish
I had a little girl like you ♪
♪ Yes, gee, I wish ♪
♪ I had a little girl like you ♪
♪ Well, nobody, nobody
Knows what I would do... ♪
You know, I've been thinking.
What if you and I went steady?
Went steady? How would that work?
It's not like you can pin me.
Or like we can
walk down the halls holding hands.
I know, but...
it could be just for us.
Our secret.
Only we'd know.
Unless you don't want to.
That's just kind of a thing squares do,
you know? "Go steady."
That's a fair point.
Anyway, it's kind of like
we're already secretly going steady
if you think about it, so...
[grunts]
- You sure I can't give you a hand?
- No. I'm good.
So you're from Korea?
My mom's Korean.
My dad was born here. I was born here.
My Uncle Frank said you played
basketball for Stonewall Prep.
- What happened?
- You writing a book?
There's not much to tell. I dropped out.
[Frank]
Had a great chat with your folks, Reggie.
We're all squared away,
if you wanna say your "see you laters."
All right.
Archie and Frank tell me
that you grew up on a farm?
Yes, ma'am.
What was that like?
The farm's everything we have.
It's our family's legacy.
My dad came home from the war with
a chunk of shrapnel stuck in his shoulder.
So it slowed him down.
I couldn't let the family business
fall behind, so I stepped up.
Pitching in as much as I can.
What about the GI Bill?
Doesn't the government help you?
The Army doesn't give us any money.
We're not considered eligible.
Well, we are. Why not you guys?
Why do you think?
That's terrible.
Mayor Blossom will make sure your
family's farm stays afloat financially.
So you can just concentrate
on playing ball.
Thanks, coach.
[Archie] This is your cot.
There's more blankets down the hall
if you get cold or anything.
Oh, I emptied a drawer,
if you need any more space.
I can make some...
Who's that?
Uh, that is my neighbor.
Uh, you'll meet her at school.
We're actually supposed to be keeping
our curtains closed from now on.
[knock on door]
Betty, can I talk to you for a minute?
Sure, Dad. What's the word?
Uh, well...
I was talking to Dr. Werthers.
He wonders if it might not be prudent
to get you exercising more.
You know, to burn off
some of your excess energy.
He doesn't want me to go back
on Riverdale Grandstand, does he?
No, no, no.
He, uh...
He says too many temptations there.
Hmm.
Boys.
Well, he wondered if you...
If you might not fare better spending
more time with nice, decent girls.
Mm. Unlike Veronica.
Now, I've spoken with Clifford Blossom,
and he's going
to arrange it all with Cheryl.
Cheryl? What does Cheryl
have to do with any of this?
Um, well, Dr. Werthers thinks,
and your mother and I both agree,
you should join...
the Vixens.
[scoffs]
Oh, you looked snappy at the game, Topaz.
Never seen a wool sweater
filled out so nicely.
Thanks for the apple butter, Lizzo.
[chuckles] Let me guess,
you and the Queen of the Paper-Shakers
got chummy
in the janitor's closet afterwards?
More or less.
Nice work, if you can get it.
You figured out a good hustle.
You find these ripe cherries,
knowing they're in the closet,
which means there's a shelf life on them.
You can get what you want and move on.
No fuss, no muss.
Look, I gotta boogie.
I'll catch you later.
[Tabitha] It's so good to see you, Toni.
You too, Tabitha.
How has the tour
with Mrs. Till been going?
[Tabitha sighs]
Well, let me tell you,
she has been so strong.
So inspiring.
But the tour itself,
going from town to town
and seeing up close
what some people are capable of doing?
The inhumanity,
the hatred, the racial injustice.
I can only imagine.
Now, give me the scoop.
What have you been doing to keep busy?
Well, don't laugh, but I'm a cheerleader.
You are?
That's fun.
But you are still writing
for The Blue and Gold, I hope.
Honestly, I haven't been
doing much writing lately.
No.
So Betty Cooper is now a River Vixen?
Newly minted as of last night.
Much to my chagrin, might I add.
And you now own the Babylonium.
Paperwork was finalized this morning.
Right. And weren't you
the popcorn girl two days ago?
What can I say?
Veronica Lodge likes to burn rubber.
Hey, gang. You mind if we join you?
That all depends.
Are you gonna introduce us to your
strapping flutter bum of a new pal?
Hey. I'm Reggie Mantle.
Uh, I just got recruited to the Bulldogs.
Ah. I suspected a tall drink of water
like you was a sportsman.
Careful, Veronica.
You might get a ticket for speeding.
Hi. I'm Cheryl Blossom.
My parents sponsor the Bulldogs.
I am the captain of Riverdale High's
cheerleading squad, the Vixens.
So we'll be working closely together.
What about you? You a cheerleader?
I am. I'm Betty.
Nice to meet you, neighbor.
[all] Neighbor?
Reggie's bunking with us.
He's gonna help turn things
around for the Bulldogs.
He's already turned my day around.
But fill us in, Reginald.
Where are you from?
What do you do for kicks?
And do you like the movies?
There isn't a theater
in Duck Creek, and...
my family and I, we don't have a TV set.
Oh, well, you must come
to the Babylonium here in town.
It's a movie palace I own.
I own my own business, yes.
Or if you're interested
in some part-time work,
I'm always on the hunt for a few good men.
You'll have to excuse Veronica.
Clearly, she was raised by wolves.
I appreciate the, uh, invitation,
but I'm just here to play basketball
and win games.
Speaking of, uh, where's the gym?
[both] I could show you.
Come on. I'll take you.
[school bell rings]
Don't I know you?
Weren't you supposed to help me
keep track of my homework from afar?
Oh, my gosh. I'm so sorry, Tabitha.
I... I got preoccupied, I...
- I...
- It's okay.
It was much easier to coordinate with
Principal Featherhead than I anticipated,
so you are hereby absolved.
Well, heh, that's a relief.
So tell me. Why are you so preoccupied?
Oh, I got a job. I'm writing comic books.
Oh, how fun. What kind?
It's a broad range.
But I also got to meet and start
working for a literary hero of mine.
- Brad Rayberry.
- Oh, my gosh. I know Brad Rayberry.
I mean, not personally,
but I've read his books, his stories.
You read science fiction?
I read across all genres,
including science fiction.
Say, would you wanna meet him?
- Would it be an imposition?
- No, no. Not at all.
It's, um, negative perspiration.
I'm sure he would love it.
Okay. Great.
Veronica. Hey.
Kevin.
Don't tell me you're here
to see Singin' in the Rain again.
I'd think you'd have
the whole picture memorized by now.
I do, and I'm not.
I'm actually here 'cause
I wanted to see about getting a job.
At school,
you mentioned you were looking for...
- A few good men. Yes, I am.
- Yeah.
Since I called it quits
at the basketball team,
I've been looking for something to do,
and I love the movies.
Well, that's my biggest prerequisite.
And you're already pals with Clay.
I am.
Well, he's up in the projection booth
even as we speak.
But maybe you could
help me with something.
Yeah, with what?
Well, between us,
I happen to think Clay
is extremely dashing.
I've been dropping hints
that I'm interested
in something more than
a professional relationship with him.
But so far, no bites.
Maybe you could help me
suss him out a bit.
Um...
Do you mean, like...?
Like, is he seeing anyone?
That sort of thing.
- Yeah. Maybe.
- Well, in that case, when can you start?
[whistle blows]
All right, you turkeys. Bring it in.
We have ourselves a new player.
His name is Reggie Mantle.
So let's see what he can do.
We are gonna split up into two teams.
Julian, you're captain of one team.
Reggie, you've got the other.
Everyone else, pick a side.
[Fangs] Come on, guys.
We can't have a game
if it's three against seven.
We'll take Doiley too. That'll be enough.
- The water boy?
- [Reggie] Yeah.
- [Julian] What is this, a gag?
- Can it, Julian.
Dilton, you up for it?
Come on.
- [boy 1] Let's do this.
- [boy 2] Yeah.
[rock music playing]
[cheering]
- Nice! Good shot, Julian!
- Ooh!
[Frank] Thirty-eight all! Anyone's game!
[cheering]
[boy] Good shot!
Let's go! Game point!
- [blows whistle]
- [boys cheering]
Guys, how about
we get some burgers at Pop's?
Reggie hasn't tried them yet.
Come on. It's our post-practice tradition.
What gives?
Actually, I can't.
I got a bunch of homework to catch up on.
You know what, Andrews, you're right.
It is tradition.
I'm hungry enough to eat a horse.
Last one to Pop's treats!
You can come too, pipsqueak.
[Cheryl] Gather around, Vixens.
Now that our team's roster
is finally complete,
and with my family's
first big booster event coming up,
it is time to assign each Vixen
to their respective player.
Wait, what do you mean assigned?
It means that you show your player extra
personalized support through the season.
Baking him cookies, wearing his jersey,
helping him with his homework.
I, of course, will be paired with Julian.
And, Toni, you and Archie will be matched.
As for our new star player,
I was thinking...
Betty could be with Reggie.
[knock on door]
Maybe we leave him a note
and try again tomorrow?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Hey, maybe we can...
go catch a flick?
The Babylonium is playing
It Came From Beneath the Sea,
and Ray Harryhausen did the giant octopus.
Um, yes.
I would love to go to the movies with you.
Toni.
What's going on?
- We need to get real, Cheryl.
- What about?
I can't do this anymore.
The Vixens.
Is this about being paired with Archie?
Would you prefer someone else?
No, I don't wanna get paired with anyone.
That's the thing.
Baking for my own personal meathead is not
really what I want my life to be about.
This whole thing
just doesn't feel right anymore.
It's not me or who I wanna be.
A cheerleader.
I see.
Toni, this doesn't have anything to do
with me asking you to go steady, does it?
No. But now that you mention it...
I'm not the settling down type,
and I feel like I've lost myself.
I don't know,
this whole square scene isn't for me.
I need to figure myself out.
I'm sorry, Cheryl.
I just need some space.
Can we do a double-sized popcorn,
a large cola with extra ice,
two packs of the Senior Mints,
a Butterflinger,
a pack of those Mint BoGos,
a 3 Buccaneers, and a Skit-Skat?
Do you want anything?
Uh, no. I'm okay, thanks.
That'll be 75 cents.
Here you go.
Perfect. Keep the change.
- Enjoy the movie.
- Thank you.
- Well, isn't that fascinating.
- [Clay] What?
Jughead and Tabitha?
Going to the movies together?
I find that interesting. Don't you?
Could be they both
like science fiction flicks.
You know, Jughead and I
were entangled for a New York minute.
What happened?
I ended it.
How come? He's plenty handsome.
I suppose.
But between you and me,
he's a total oddball.
Lives in a train car too.
I prefer my men
to be a bit more continental.
Worldly.
With an air of mystery about them.
[Clay] I...
I should skedaddle to the booth,
get the next reel queued up.
Of course.
Clay?
Just think about picking up
what I'm putting down.
[chattering]
Um, what did you get for problem four?
You know, you don't have to do this.
What do you mean?
Oh, helping you with your homework
is one of my Vixen duties.
I'm also supposed to discreetly find out
what your favorite kind of cookie is
so I can bake you a batch.
- You don't have to do that either.
- Oh, but I do.
On the hush-hush, it's sort of my...
court-appointed punishment.
What do you mean?
Oh, I was ordered to join the Vixens
to curb my unhealthy physical urges.
Oh, you mean you haven't heard?
[sigh] Oh, yeah.
I sort of flashed my underwear
on live television.
You know, like Marilyn Monroe-style.
Is that how come you and Archie
have to have your curtains closed?
Oh. No.
Archie and I...
Well, you'll probably
hear about it anyways.
We were basically caught having a...
peep show in our windows.
A peep show?
Yeah, if you can even call it that.
[scoffs]
You know what?
I should... I should probably go.
Oh. No. No, no, no.
Nothing happened between us.
We didn't... No, we're not...
- I'm completely...
- Yeah.
Still. You... I'm living with the guy.
And we don't go in much
for peep shows and flashing panties
in Duck Creek, so it's...
This is...
Consider yourself relieved
of your, uh, Vixen duties, okay?
But, I...
Reg. You, uh, wanna grab lunch with us?
Thanks for the invite, but I'm gonna pass.
It wouldn't be with the team,
it would be with my other friends.
All the same,
I'm good.
[Toni]
I wanna try something out on you cats.
Ever since Featherhead refused
to publish my Emmett Till article
in The Blue and Gold,
I've been keen to start a literary society
for Riverdale's Black students.
A club that publishes a journal
focusing on Black voices and writing.
I think that's an excellent idea.
Yeah. I've been craving a forum
where I can publish my literary criticism,
poetry, and short fiction.
And this is something that you'd do
in addition to cheerleading?
No.
I gave that up.
What happened?
I joined the Vixens for the wrong reasons.
It was because I had a crush on a girl.
Cheryl Blossom.
But now that's over, so...
Anyway, I think publishing this journal
could really make a difference
for Black students at Riverdale.
It would. Definitely.
But what happened with Cheryl?
On the level, we're just so different.
She's rich, she's white, she's a Blossom.
The whole thing,
it would just be impossible.
I mean, it's hard.
But it's not impossible.
For Kevin and I,
we're also very different, so...
everything's a conversation.
But he's up for getting to know me
and what I'm all about.
And vice versa.
I hear that, Clay.
But you're also both preppies,
so at least you're starting off
on the same foot.
Fair enough.
I guess it all depends
on how much you like the person.
Kevin, you haven't seen Clay, have you?
He's running late.
Had some stuff at school.
Can we chat about something?
Of course.
It's just, it seems like you're coming on
really strong with Clay.
I might be.
Clay would never say anything,
but is that really appropriate?
Oh, Kevin.
Don't be such a wet rag.
What's wrong
with a little workplace flirtation?
It's not like Clay
is even remotely interested.
He's not. I know that for a fact.
Oh.
And why is that?
Because he's not attracted to...
assertive women?
No.
He's not attracted to any women.
Neither am I, for that matter.
I knew it.
I knew you were both
secret friends of Dorothy.
You knew? How?
You're both dreamy flutter bums
who can quote every line
of Norma Desmond's dialogue
in Sunset Blvd.
If you knew,
why would you make a play for Clay?
To test my hypothesis, of course.
You lucky dog. He is a hunk.
Say, what are the chances
Clay swings both ways?
Uh, he doesn't. We don't.
Double-checking, that's all.
You're okay with this?
Absolutely.
Kevin, the only thing
better than having a hunky boyfriend,
is having hunky friends who are boys.
The thing is...
I've always had more fun going out
with Toni and Tab, than, say...
Steve and Dennis.
Steve McQueen and Dennis Hopper.
Don't worry. We'll get you up to snuff.
Oh, Kevin.
I'm so excited.
This hick town
is finally starting to feel like home.
[Veronica chuckles]
[Frank] All right, fellas. Huddle up.
Julian has an announcement.
Tomorrow night,
my parents are hosting their annual
Bulldog Booster Basketball Mixer.
This year, it's also a fundraiser
to build us a new gym.
- Are the cheerleaders invited?
- Absolutely.
So dress spiffy.
Okay? Coats and ties.
Make sure you shower.
[Frank clears throat]
And, of course, we'll be welcoming
our newest Bulldog to the family.
I suppose.
You know, that Blossom mixer
may sound a little stuffy, but...
they're always a gas and a half.
Yeah, well, let me know how that goes.
- You're not going?
- No, I can't be distracted.
The NCAA is giving out scholarships
for college,
and if I get one of those,
I'm made in the shade.
Reggie, no man is an island.
Can't you do all that
and still cut loose a little?
Hell, Julian made it seem
like you're the guest of honor.
If that's what you heard...
you're a lot more naive than I thought.
Why are you being such a killjoy, Mantle?
Why can't you meet anyone halfway?
Meet halfway?
Julian and those guys haven't taken
one step towards me since I got here.
And you haven't heard anything
I've been saying.
Sophomore year,
I was recruited by Stonewall Prep.
And I was juiced to be there.
But I never belonged there.
And my teammates made that very clear.
[Bret] Oh!
You guys like rice, don't you?
Is that enough to take back
to your farm, yellow-belly?
[Bret laughing]
[Reggie] And that was day one.
During practice, the other players
would foul me on purpose.
And they did whatever they could
to run me out of there, and guess what?
It worked.
So this time,
I'm not meeting anyone halfway.
Not giving anyone an opening...
a chance to humiliate me,
ever again.
All right?
All right.
Reggie.
I'm sorry that happened to you.
But we're not like that here.
Aren't you?
Cheryl.
Toni.
Hello.
How are you?
I'm...
being stoic and strong
for the sake of my Vixens.
How are you?
Well, I'm petitioning for a new club.
And you, as junior class president,
are in charge
of the student council's financing.
I was hoping you could help us
secure some funding.
What kind of club is it?
It's a literary society
for Riverdale's Black students.
To share their ideas,
stories, and writings
with each other and the student body.
A way to express ourselves
on our own terms.
That's a really wonderful idea.
I'll put the request through today, but...
Toni, everything has to go
through Featherhead, so...
I know.
And I appreciate you trying.
And if Featherhead doesn't approve,
we'll make it work.
We always do.
Maybe a bake sale or something.
Well, I would contribute
my legendary cherry scones.
Toni, can I ask you a question?
Is part of the reason you broke up with me
because I'm white?
There was a lot of reasons, Cheryl.
All interconnected, but...
that was part of it, yeah.
I will try my absolute best
with Featherhead.
I promise.
[jazz music playing over speakers]
[chattering]
Fancy meeting you here.
Howdy-doody, Betty.
How's it going being a paper-shaker?
Oh, swell.
Werthers thought it would help me
burn off some excess energy.
Grownups don't have a clue.
No, they don't.
Anyways, I don't think I'll be a Vixen
for much longer.
Why's that?
Once my mother finds out
that I've been assigned
a basketball player to take care of,
she will... flip her lid.
[Archie] Oh, crap.
Um, will you excuse me, Betty? I, um...
- I'll take it.
- Thanks.
Archie.
Your uncle's telling me
that you're sharing a room with our, uh...
Our secret weapon.
Uh, you mean Reggie?
Yes. I am.
Well, as a former Bulldog myself...
I do appreciate the sacrifice.
It's no trouble at all.
I'm cranked to do it, really.
Well, I know I couldn't.
I mean, bunking with a...
We look upon him
as a necessary evil, Dennis.
A means to an end.
She's talking about winning.
Bulldogs must be champions this year.
Town needs something to rally behind.
And, you know, Frank,
when you suggested
bringing on a Korean prodigy...
[chuckles]
Well, I was skeptical.
But having seen him play... Whew.
I now see how inspired your thinking was.
Tell me something, Archie.
Does he, uh...
actually realize the opportunity
we're presenting to him and his family?
He does.
He just doesn't wanna fall behind
on his schoolwork.
Good for him.
But, uh...
Well, we don't care about that.
We just need him to be a loyal soldier
and bring us our championship trophy.
He does that,
preferably with a smile on his face...
there'll be no problems for us.
And none for his family.
[Archie] If you'll excuse me...
- I'm gonna get some fresh air.
- Yeah.
Good stuff.
Well, coach, here's to a winning season.
[Veronica] Reggie Mantle.
And here I thought
you weren't a fan of movies.
I didn't say that.
I said we didn't have any theaters
in Duck Creek.
I stand corrected.
And the fact that
I might've been here tonight
didn't influence your decision, I suppose?
If I'm being honest?
Oh, I insist upon honesty at all times.
Not at all.
Truth is,
I forgot that you worked at this place.
I don't work at it.
I own it.
Now, what can I get for you?
[clears throat]
A small popcorn.
No butter.
I'm training.
Here you go.
On the house.
Thanks.
How rude can you get?
Anyway, there's plenty of other fish
in the sea.
True.
But take a powder, Herman Melville,
because that is the real Moby Dick.
[Tabitha]
Wow. This is like the Orient Express.
[Jughead] That's exactly what I said.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
Um, I actually... I brought you something.
Here. This is for you to keep.
"Darkwater: Voices from Within the Veil
by W.E.B. Du Bois"?
- "Du Bois."
- Du Bois.
He is a sociologist
and a civil rights activist.
He's also one of my favorite authors.
Wow, it's a great title.
Which one should I start with?
Well, we've established
that you're a fan of science fiction.
- Mm-hm.
- And though it's more speculative fiction,
I would suggest a story that Du Bois wrote
called "The Comet."
- What's that one about?
- Oh. It's fantastic.
It's about this comet
that hits New York City,
then it kills everybody
except for two people:
A man named Jim and a woman named Julia.
And it's sort of
about this unlikely relationship
that develops between them.
And what's really interesting
is that Jim is Black and Julia's white.
And it's sort of one of the first times
an interracial relationship
has been depicted in science fiction.
Well, it sounds terrific.
- Yeah.
- I can't wait to read it.
Actually, I was thinking
that maybe we could read it together...
tonight, aloud, if...
If you wanted.
Yeah, that sounds swell.
How was the mixer?
It was Dullsville, honestly.
You didn't miss out on much.
Hmm. How were the cheerleaders?
All dolled-up?
I don't really wanna talk about it.
Hey, I'm gonna grab a shower.
Okay, you lug nuts.
Coach is in a meeting.
So I'm running warmups today.
Everyone good with that?
In that case, let's play ball.
[rock music playing]
[boy 1] Here we go.
[boy 2] Nice.
Come on. Banana boy, pass me the ball.
Pass me the ball!
[boys] Oh! Whoa!
[boy 3] Hey, come on.
Listen up.
We are not doing this crap.
If you haven't noticed,
Reggie here is our strongest player.
Our only shot
at making the playoffs this year.
So we're gonna rise to his level.
So if you don't wanna be chummy with him,
that's fine.
But the minute we hit this court,
we are teammates.
Fighting for each other.
If you can't get on board with that,
the door's right there.
That includes you too, captain.
[Cheryl] I hope this will suffice.
Funds for your new club.
Thank you, Cheryl.
I'm shocked Featherhead approved
a Black literary society.
He didn't.
Those funds were earmarked for...
something else.
But I believe your club
to be a much more worthy endeavor.
Well, I won't ask any more questions.
But thank you.
Of course.
I look forward
to reading your first issue.
Cheryl, wait.
Yes?
What are you doing
after cheerleading practice?
No plans.
Why?
If you want...
maybe we could meet at the Dark Room.
I would love that.
Do you mean to talk?
Yeah.
About what it would mean...
if we tried again.
I didn't sock Julian for you.
I know you don't need saving.
I did it for my own sake
and for the team's.
I didn't wanna believe
you were right about this town.
But, hell, maybe we are just as...
As messed up as any other place.
I don't know.
You wanna grab a burger at Pop's
on the way home?
Maybe we'll run into
some of the other fellas there?
Sure. If you're sure.
I am.
Just don't expect me
to sit with anyone or anything.
[Jughead]
Tabitha and I stayed up till dawn
reading and discussing Du Bois' stories.
The next day, I wanted to tell
Mr. Rayberry all about my swell night,
so I went back to his apartment.
What happened?
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but Brad Rayberry is dead.
What...? How did he die?
He, uh, killed himself.
Hung himself.
He left a note.
"I can no longer
continue living this way."
I'm sorry, Jughead.
I know that he was your friend.
[dramatic music playing]