[Jughead] Things were dire.
My friend Ethel's parents
had been brutally murdered
the night of the sock hop.
And suddenly, Ethel and I
were the prime suspects.
You drew this picture,
didn't you, Ethel?
And they're meant to be
your mother and father.
Yes, but it was a joke.
Then why did Mr. Jones hide it
under his mattress
like a dirty secret?
And is this where your
far-fetched story
about a killer milkman
came from? A comic book?
No, no. I saw a milkman
leaving my house--
Don't say anything else,
not until we talk to a lawyer.
You know, a picture is worth
a thousand words, Mr. Jones.
And these... Well, these
tell a very disturbing story.
Well...
Well, maybe
they'll be more talkative
down at the station.
Jughead, what's happening?
They're railroading us.
[Sheriff Keller]
Let's go, Jughead.
[students murmuring]
Where do you get off, Andrews,
taking advantage of my sister?
Going all the way with her
at Veronica's make-out party.
Okay, first of all,
you encouraged me
to date Cheryl.
And second of all, I didn't.
We did not go all the way.
That's not what
Cheryl's saying.
[door slams]
Cheryl, why did you
tell your brother
we went all the way?
We didn't, we kissed.
That's all we did.
We did more than that, Archie.
I mean, Bela Lugosi didn't
give me this beauty mark.
Oh, okay, okay.
We barely made it
to second base.
So why tell Julian
we scored a homerun?
I can't explain it.
But by saying that we did,
it's helping me...
with a problem I'm having.
Just know that by
corroborating my story...
you'd be protecting me.
Protecting you?
How and from whom?
My family.
Archie, please don't ask me
any more questions than that.
Anyway, it's just
a little white lie, right?
Really, who is it hurting?
♪ These are
The in-between years ♪
♪ We're going through ♪
I want to give this
back to you, Betty.
[Betty] That was fast.
Did you glean something
from it, at least?
I think so.
I think I know what you want.
And?
And I... I wanna wait
until marriage.
Oh, I see.
Well, how about this?
I'm not okay with you
making all of the decisions
in this relationship, Kevin.
So, as far as I'm concerned,
we're not going steady anymore.
[sighs]
[Toni] Betty, what is it?
Why are you crying?
Kevin and I broke up.
[sighs] Boys ruin everything.
What did he do?
[sighs] Well, we were talking
about having a more
physical relationship.
And an ultimatum was put down.
You wanted to wait
till marriage?
No, Kevin said he wanted
to wait until marriage.
So I broke up with him.
Don't be ashamed
of your desires, Betty.
More girls should do
what you did.
Ask for what they want
from their supposed boyfriends.
What do I do now?
Well, how about you and I
go to the Dark Room
and grab a coffee?
And Betty...
maybe this breakup is exactly
what the doctor ordered.
[Veronica]
How's poor Ethel doing?
I think she's in shock.
I can only imagine.
What are they saying to you?
Not much. Just that they
can only hold us
legally for 24 hours.
After which, they either have
to release us or charge us.
But you were at the dance.
We were all there together.
If there was some way
that we could prove the time
that Ethel's parents
were killed, it might be
enough to clear me.
Then I'd figure out a way
to exonerate Ethel.
Putting on my Nora Charles hat,
doesn't Riverdale
have a coroner?
That would have performed
an autopsy on the Muggs?
Every town has a coroner.
But I don't know who that is.
Let me find out.
I'll be back.
Hey, Veronica... Nora Charles?
The Thin Man
is one of my favorite films.
I had a feeling.
Mom, what's wrong?
Mrs. Blossom just came by.
Is it true what she's saying
you and Cheryl did?
How did this happen?
Mom, I don't really
feel comfortable
discussing this with you.
You think I do?
Never mind.
Just go upstairs
and change into your suit.
Why?
Because we're going over
to the Blossoms' for dinner,
to figure out a path
through this mess
that you and Cheryl made.
[soft music playing]
So, how was your trip
to Washington, Mr. Mayor?
Oh, Mary, please.
It's Clifford.
As for my trip, well,
it was, uh...
It was productive.
But...
to come home
to our fair town
torn asunder.
Two murders,
and our young people
in crisis.
World has indeed gone sideways.
Joe was right.
Senator McCarthy.
So, tell me, Archie.
What do you think
of the Russia problem?
The Russia problem, sir?
The Russians.
Arming themselves against us,
infiltrating us, undermining
our very way of life.
Well...
Well, Russia is a big...
It's a massive problem, sir.
It's, I mean, clearly...
You're a very smart
young man, Archie.
You remind me of your father.
Fred was a decent,
hard working,
red-blooded American.
Thank you, sir.
Mary, after dinner, I think
we should adjourn to my study.
We have much to discuss.
[Cheryl] I'm sorry
I never got to meet your dad.
You must miss him a lot.
Yeah, he was...
He was my best friend.
That is so sweet.
We used to go to the movies
almost every weekend.
-Westerns,
those were his favorites.
-[chuckles softly]
Mine too.
And afterwards we'd go
to Pop's for burgers.
We'd joke about riding
out west to California,
to live on a ranch.
[both laugh]
Being cowboys.
It's funny.
I think about that a lot.
♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ My darling ♪
♪ I've hungered for
Your touch ♪
♪ A long, lonely time ♪
All right.
First things first.
Let's get you that decaf.
You know what?
Betty, let's go.
You don't wanna see this.
See what?
♪ And time can do so much ♪
♪ Are you still mine? ♪
Oh, my gosh.
According to the time of death
on that certificate,
Jughead was at the dance
when Mr. and Mrs. Muggs
were murdered.
This doesn't account
for Ethel's whereabouts
at the time of the murders.
That may be the case.
But you can at least
release Jughead, can't you?
I'm sorry, but is that cell
gonna unlock itself?
Because I'm a very busy
teenager, Sheriff.
[scoffs]
[upbeat music playing
over speakers]
Mm.
I think they were trying
to starve me in there.
Thankfully, I managed
to get Ethel
to finally open up.
She told you where she was
when her parents were killed?
Mm-hmm. And her reluctance
to fess up makes sense too.
It turns out, she was doing
the car seat cha-cha
with, get this...
Julian Blossom.
Ethel was waiting
at the bus stop
to go to the dance
when Julian drove by
and offered to take her.
You going to the dance?
Come on, I'll give you a ride.
[Jughead] When instead,
he took her to Lover's Lane
and then tried
to put the moves on her.
As Ethel described it,
she welcomed it at first.
But Julian decided
to get a little handsy.
[Julian grunts]
[Jughead] Julian warned her
not to say anything
and that if she did, he would
call her a nymphomaniac.
Make her the town
laughingstock.
[Veronica sighs]
Of course, we know
what happened after that.
When she decided to go home
instead of the dance.
Terrible.
I say we talk to Julian
at school tomorrow.
Ethel thinks
that ratting him out
is only going to make
things worse for her.
And she may be right.
So it's up to Julian
to do the honorable thing.
God help us.
[door opens]
And where have you been,
young lady?
I was just having coffee
with my friend Toni.
Hmm. Well, Mrs. Keller called.
Did you break up
with Kevin today?
[sighs]
Oh, Betty, why did you do that?
He is so upset.
He's devastated.
Mrs. Keller doesn't know
where he is.
She's worried sick.
Kevin is fine.
I just saw him
at the coffeehouse.
And rest assured, he's found
a shoulder to cry on.
A very manly shoulder.
And?
And looking back, that's been
the problem with
us this whole time, Mom.
Kevin likes boys.
Oh, Elizabeth.
Here, honey, come sit.
[Alice sighs]
[scoffs]
Even if he does,
it's just a phase.
See, carnal passion like that,
it never lasts.
It will fade.
And then, eventually,
he'll be ready to--
To what?
To kiss me? To want to kiss me?
To marry you.
To settle down.
Start a family.
Mom, how could I possibly
marry and live with Kevin,
knowing the truth now?
You and Kevin,
you've been building
a relationship for two years.
I know.
And if he's going through some
kind of sexual identity crisis,
don't you owe it to him
to help him through it?
If only as a friend.
[light buzzing]
Holy heck.
[sighs]
Hot Dog.
Where'd they take you, boy?
Well... [sighs]
That was torture.
Well, Mr. Blossom said
some nice stuff
about Dad, at least.
Oh, Clifford Blossom
has always been a hypocrite.
And a war profiteer
and a draft dodger.
How is he a war profiteer?
He sold maple syrup
to the Army at a premium
during the Korean War.
[sighs]
I've always managed to give
the Blossoms a wide berth.
But now, thanks to you,
we'll be linked
for the rest of our lives.
What are you talking about?
The Blossoms and I
have had a long talk.
And we've decided that,
based on your actions,
the best thing to do
would be for you and Cheryl...
to get married.
Married?
Aren't Cheryl and I
too young to do that?
Dr. Werthers will be giving
you and Cheryl a test tomorrow.
I have to take a test now too?
A compatibility test.
Cupid's checklist, to make sure
that you and Cheryl are--
Compatible.
Yes, and psychologically
ready to get married.
[clears throat]
Mom, this can't be
what you want for me.
It isn't.
But if you're old enough to...
do what you did,
then you're old enough
to take responsibility for it.
Think of Cheryl's honor.
That poor girl's reputation
could be destroyed.
And I know you don't want that.
Gosh, Midge... Are you sure?
I'm never late.
I'm scared, Fangs.
Don't worry, baby.
I love you.
We're going to figure this out.
I promise.
[scoffs] What do you two want?
We know that you were
with Ethel before
arriving to the dance.
Is that what Ethel says?
[scoffs] She wishes.
[chuckles]
You're a terrible liar.
If you already know
the whole story,
then why the third degree?
Because they're trying
to bamboozle Ethel.
You were the only one
that was with her when
her parents were eighty-sixed.
So you can be her alibi.
But you need to tell the truth
to Sheriff Keller.
I'm not doing that.
Why not?
I'm a Blossom.
It would be...
unseemly for me to admit
that I made a play
for someone as...
inappropriate
as Ethel Muggs.
Then why do it
in the first place?
I don't know.
Cheap thrills, I guess.
What the hell, Jones?
You disgust me, Julian.
People like you
make my stomach churn.
You're rich.
You're entitled.
You strut around the world
like you own it.
And then you take
advantage of people
like my friend, Ethel.
So you're going to do
the right thing
for once in your life.
Julian gave a statement.
Ethel's free to go, right?
Yeah. She's no longer
an active suspect.
Though an adult is gonna need
to sign her out.
The Coopers are on their way.
They've agreed
to take her in again.
[Dr. Werthers]
My compatibility test,
or, uh, Cupid's checklist,
shall we say, consists
of only three questions.
First question.
Do you come
from similar backgrounds?
The Blossoms are descended
from European
barons and baronesses.
Um, my dad used to talk about
how Grandpa Artie and his wife
barely survived the Dust Bowl.
Very good.
Second question.
Are you close friends?
[scoffs] Um...
You know, I pride myself
on getting along
with pretty much everyone.
Hmm.
Last question.
Do you understand
the concept of marriage?
Uh... Um...
Marriage is not to be
taken lightly, Ms. Blossom.
And you, Mr. Andrews,
you must remain faithful.
It goes against our nature
as men, of course.
But...
a kind word, sympathetic ear
and a home-cooked meal
can go a long way
towards keeping
a wandering eye in check.
Have I clarified things?
[Penelope] Well, that is such
a relief to hear, Dr. Werthers.
Mrs. Andrews and I are elated.
Yes, we'll talk soon.
My best to Myrna.
The most wonderful news,
Mary, dear.
The children are compatible.
Well, frankly, I'm surprised.
You know, Archie and Cheryl
are so different.
Well, they both have that
glorious red hair, don't they?
[Toni] Hey, Fangs.
How's it hanging?
Not well, Toni.
Midge thinks that she
might be in trouble.
Oh, jeez.
Are you sure?
Not 100%, but, yeah,
pretty sure.
Okay, well,
first things first.
We need to confirm that Midge
is, in fact, pregnant.
Here's what we're going to do.
You, me and Midge
are going to meet
at the biology lab
at school tonight at midnight.
That'll give me enough time
to gather the supplies
we need to make our own test.
Can you dig it?
Big Daddy?
[sighs]
[piano music playing]
Kev, can we talk?
[door closes]
I went to the Dark Room
last night,
and I saw you and Clay there.
[scoffs] Yeah, I don't know
what you think you saw,
but Clay and I were just
kidding around.
No.
No, you weren't.
How long have you and Clay...
[sighs] Last night
was the first time.
After you broke up with me,
I went to the gym and...
just was bawling
my eyes out and...
Clay was in the locker room
and he just heard me,
and he came
and just talked to me and...
I'm sorry.
I know this must be
throwing you for a loop,
but just believe me.
If I had known what...
I... I was, I wouldn't
have wasted your time.
I'm not going to pretend
that I understand most of this.
But our relationship
was not a waste of time.
At least not to me.
[bright pop music playing]
[both slurping]
Well, I guess it's happening.
Mr. and Mrs. Andrews.
So, it seems.
Cheryl, are you... Are you sure
you really wanna
go through with this?
Would it really be that bad?
To be married to you?
No. Oh, heck, no.
I just... I wanna
get to know you better.
And through that process,
maybe I'll get to know
myself better too.
I think it's easy
to figure out your path
when someone's
walking alongside you.
Word around school is
you wrote Veronica
a beautiful love poem.
Maybe you could
find it in your heart
to write one for me.
Yeah, yeah. Sure I can.
[jazz music playing]
To small victories.
Hear, hear!
Though Ethel's not out
of the woods just yet.
No, but she's in a better place
than she was two hours ago.
[Jughead clears throat]
We make a good team, Nick.
Yes, we do, Nora.
[chuckles]
So, after dinner,
what do you think
about walking me home?
Oh, shucks...
I was actually planning
on staying here tonight.
At the diner?
Why?
Sheriff Keller
and his goon squad
trashed my train car.
Oh.
Well...
do you want to stay
at the Pembrooke?
[both chuckle]
No, no. I'm...
I'm allergic to silk sheets.
You're in luck, then.
Because we only
have sheets made
from the finest
Egyptian cotton.
Well, I wouldn't
wanna crowd you.
Please. There's an entire
wing of the apartment
I haven't even set foot in.
Really, I insist.
-[frog croaking]
-I'm confused, Toni.
How will any of this stuff
tell us whether or not
I'm pregnant?
It's a simple process.
I'm going to inject
some of your pee
into our friend here.
And if you're pregnant,
it's gonna cause
a chemical reaction
in the frog, causing it
to lay eggs overnight.
Will it hurt the frog?
No, it's quick and painless.
Promise.
Okay, I got Midge's pee
in a cup in a bag here.
So why don't you two
just wait outside
and I'll be out in a jiffy?
[frog croaking]
Well, Midge,
you're definitely preggers.
There's like,
400-500 eggs in there.
Oh, my God.
All right.
Fangs, Midge, listen up.
Do you two love each other?
-Yeah, we do.
-Completely.
All right. Fangs, you're going
to have to clean yourself up.
Wash the grease
out of your hair,
put on a button-up shirt
and go ask the Klumps
for Midge's hand in marriage.
I'd do anything for Midge.
But no way will her folks
give us their blessing.
Well, you're gonna
at least have to try.
And maybe they'll surprise you.
But, I wouldn't tell them
that Midge has a bun
in the oven just yet.
[plates clanking]
Good morning.
What's all this?
Well, I woke up early.
I figured I'd make you
a little breakfast
as a show of gratitude.
Little?
My typical breakfast
consists of half a grapefruit
and a cup of coffee.
I feel like I'm at
the Polo Lounge
having Sunday brunch.
How did you sleep?
Were the sheets to your liking?
I slept like a log.
But I'll admit,
I do feel a bit like
Little Orphan Annie in here.
Which makes me, who?
Daddy Warbucks?
Should we walk
to school together?
I'm skipping school today.
I have to go to the pound
and spring Hot Dog.
And then I have to fix up
my train car.
Well then, I'll skip too.
Why don't you focus
on getting Hot Dog
and I'll focus on
sprucing up your train car?
[Betty] Wait a minute.
You and Cheryl
didn't go all the way?
But now you two
are getting married?
I know. It's confusing.
It's lunacy, Arch.
Why don't you just tell
your mom the truth,
so you don't have
to do any of this?
Cheryl's in trouble, Betty.
And I want to protect her.
And it's weird to say,
but if I can save her
from something,
it might help me...
I don't know.
Figure out my purpose in life.
But do you love her?
-I could.
-[sighs]
I mean, according
to Dr. Werthers,
love grows over time.
He showed us a graph.
It starts when you're 17
and it peaks when you're 21.
I mean, that's when you
really start loving someone.
Arch, there's a difference
between saving someone
and loving someone.
What if the love never grows?
Archie. My father
has requested a sit-down
with us after school.
I trust you can
accommodate him.
-I'll be there.
-Wunderbar.
I'll let him know.
Betty.
You're a wonderful guy, Arch.
And it's really sweet
that you wanna help Cheryl.
But marriage is forever.
It's the rest of your life.
[Clifford] So very happy
to hear that you passed
Dr. Werthers' evaluation.
I suppose you're both wondering
what happens next.
Well, we were thinking
of a small ceremony
at Niagara Falls.
Don't be asinine, Cheryl.
You're going to be married
by a judge at Thornhill.
And I will set Archie up
with a part-time job
at the Naval factory.
And you'll both graduate
high school, of course.
And college as well.
That's a waste
of time and money.
After high school,
you, Archie, will enter into
the Blossom Management
Training program.
And once that's completed,
we'll start you on full-time.
Cheryl will help her mother
manage Thornhill,
eventually learning how
to run the estate herself.
Why? It's not as if
we're gonna live here.
Certainly you will.
Where else are you gonna live?
Well, Cheryl and I haven't
talked about it yet, sir,
but I was thinking we could
move into my parent's house.
Cheryl? In that hovel?
[jazz music playing]
Wow!
I barely even
recognized you, Fangs.
How did it go with the Klumps?
It went horrible.
They had a conniption.
Forbade me from
ever seeing Midge again.
Yeah, I was afraid
that was gonna happen.
Midge is rich.
She's white,
her parents love her.
And on top of it all, you're
a greaser wannabe rockstar.
Oh, jeez.
What do I do, Toni?
You do exactly
what the Klumps say.
Stay away from Midge.
They don't know she's pregnant.
You got four months before
she starts to show.
Which means we have
four months to make you into
a Ritchie Valens-type
rock star.
Huh?
Once you become rich and famous
and undeniable,
you'll re-propose to Midge
and they'll have no choice
but to give you their blessing.
You're in love.
Like a Romeo and Juliet
kind of love.
No matter what,
you and Midge will be together.
Well, do you fellas approve?
Wow! You really
are like Daddy Warbucks.
I consulted with some of my set
decorator friends out West.
I could have done more,
but time was very limited.
Are you kidding?
It's like the Orient Express.
Without the murder, of course.
Of course.
You know, Jughead,
you and Hot Dog
are more than welcome to stay
at the Pembrooke.
Um, golly, uh...
I appreciate the offer.
I'm just a creature of habit.
As is Hot Dog.
But thank you for everything.
This is... Gosh.
My pleasure.
All right. Well, I will
leave you boys to it.
Bye.
Do you wanna explain
this to me?
What were you doing in my room?
Cleaning it.
Now tell me,
why do you have this book?
[sighs]
I was reading it, Mom.
To try to make
some sense of my life,
since everything that you
tell me is backwards
and nonsensical.
Watch your tone, little miss.
A girl your age should not
be reading this filth.
Well, then when, Mom?
And it's not filth.
It's just the truth.
Where did you even find this?
[Ethel] It's mine.
It was at my house.
That's where Betty found it,
Mrs. Cooper.
I ordered it from a catalog
through the mail.
Oh, Ethel. Why am I
not surprised?
It doesn't matter
where I got it.
And I'm not done
reading it yet.
Betty. Young lady!
["Who Do You Suppose" playing]
♪ Who do you suppose ♪
♪ I really love ♪
♪ I'm thinking of ♪
♪ Who do you suppose ♪
♪ I dream of ♪
♪ Both day and night ♪
[Archie] Cheryl,
I can't go through with it.
After that crazy talk
with your dad,
this whole plan is suddenly
feeling really wrong to me.
I understand, Archie.
I do.
I demanded too much of you.
Asking you to lie,
to marry into my life,
my family.
That's my cross,
and my cross alone, to bear.
No, no, but it
doesn't have to be.
Because, I have another plan,
Cheryl. A better one.
What do you mean?
-What if we elope?
-[chuckles]
Go out West.
You could get away
from your family.
I could get a job on a ranch.
Or be, I don't know...
A folk singer?
-A what?
-A folk singer.
All I'm saying is, out West,
we can find ourselves.
Be whoever we want to be.
Imagine it, Cheryl.
You'd be free from whatever's
weighing you down here.
If only it were that easy.
It can be.
We just have to do it.
Okay.
Okay, let's try, Archie.
[Betty] I read more
of my book, Kev.
Including Chapter 20,
about men like you.
And I wanted to say
that I think you're so brave.
Swell to the last.
And here's your pin back.
I thought maybe
you could give it to Clay.
[chuckles nervously]
That's not mine.
It's your mom's.
What are you talking about?
When we were having
our troubles, she gave it to me
to give to you
to take the pressure
off of our relationship.
You went to my mom for advice?
No, she...
She reached out to me.
I hope that's okay.
Toni Topaz.
What are the odds?
I was actually just
about to come find you.
To say goodbye?
You can't do it, Cheryl.
Running away with Archie
would be a huge mistake.
You don't understand
my situation.
You think you can run away
from Riverdale, your family.
But you can't outrun yourself.
Who you are.
What makes you think
you know me better
than I know myself?
I was you.
Do you love him?
Archie...
Archie is a great person.
With the best heart.
And he's nothing
like my family. So...
I see. [sighs]
So you hop on a bus with a boy
and move across the country.
But...
eventually, you're gonna
have to look at yourself
in the mirror and face
who you really are.
Otherwise,
you'll just wither away.
Mom, where's Ethel?
Why, she's gone, dear.
Gone? Gone where?
I called my friend Janet
at Social Services,
and she thought
it would be best
that we send Ethel
to The Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Mom, the nuns there
are bonkers.
They do experiments on people.
They do not, Elizabeth.
That rumor has been debunked.
It's what's best for Ethel.
Trust me. I know
I'm right about this.
Is that what you said to Kevin
when you told him to pin me?
What on earth
are you talking about?
Did you give this to Kevin
and tell him to pin me, Mother?
To settle me and my urges down?
I may have given
some advice in passing.
Oh, come off it, Mom.
What are you so afraid of?
Is it... Is it Ethel?
Is it that book?
Is it me? What is it?
You know,
I'm here to protect you
from dangers that you don't
even know are coming your way.
But one day you will,
and you'll thank me for it.
I really doubt it.
I burned it.
Your sex book.
So you won't be reading
it under the covers anymore.
[scoffs softly]
["Young-At-Heart" playing]
♪ Fairy tales can come true ♪
♪ It can happen to you ♪
♪ If you're young at heart ♪
Wait, I got us bus tickets.
Or, are we taking
your convertible instead?
I'm so sorry, Archie, but...
I can't go out West with you.
This has been the most
beautiful pipe dream with
the most wonderful guy
a girl could ever ask for.
But that's all it is.
A fantasy.
You've been a true gentleman,
but I have to face the music.
I can't keep running
from all my problems.
At least, not this one.
-Cheryl--
-Archie, someday you are going
to make some girl very happy,
and she is going to want
to go with you to California.
Unfortunately...
that girl isn't me.
But maybe, she lives
right next door to you.
-You mean--
-Maybe you should write Betty
one of those sweet poems
of yours.
["Unchained Melody" playing]
Cheryl.
Shouldn't you be halfway
to Frisco by now?
I decided not to leave
with Archie, for many reasons.
Oh, yeah?
I don't know
where I go from here.
Well, why don't you start
by reading this book?
See if anything in it
resonates with you.
Will you do that?
Not for me, but...
for yourself.
♪ Are you still mine? ♪
♪ I need your love ♪
♪ God speed your love ♪
[paper rustles]
♪ To me ♪
[Mary] Archie, can you
come in here
for a minute, please?
Uncle Frank.
What are you doing here?
Your mom called.
Caught me up on everything.
Sounded like I needed to come
to town to knock some heads...
starting with yours.
All I know is
what they've told me,
that Ethel was staying
at some home
for wayward children
with a bunch of nuns.
Called
The Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
[Jughead exhales]
Are you okay?
No.
No, I feel like I failed her.
That I failed Ethel.
You didn't.
You fought hard to save her,
Jughead, and you did.
You did save her.
♪ Are you still mine? ♪
♪ I need your love ♪
♪ I...
I need your love ♪
-Wowie.
-[chuckles]
You can say that again.
♪ God speed your love ♪
♪ To me ♪
[song ends]