[ALARM CLOCK RINGS, THEN STOPS]
[JUGHEAD] This is the story
of two teenage boys
living under the same roof.
They go to the same school,
they think about the same things,
mostly cars and girls,
but very different passions drive them.
On a normal, typical morning,
the first thing these two boys do
is go for a run
through the still asleep town.
For Reggie, the run is a warmup
before he turns
to his true love, basketball.
For Archie,
it's a different kind of warmup
before putting pencil to paper.
Mind you,
today isn't a normal, typical morning.
It's the day after Halloween.
When a car full of Bulldogs drove
off a bridge and into Sweetwater River.
Team captain Julian Blossom
had been behind the wheel.
All the Bulldogs most likely
would have drowned if not for Reggie,
who pulled them from the water,
one by one.
But Julian Blossom was unconscious,
hovering between life and death.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
Even as Frank Andrews was doing his best
to calm down an enraged Clifford Blossom.
I knew bringing that punk in
was a bad idea.
It's his fault, it had to have been,
and I want him off my team.
Mayor Blossom, we're still
piecing together what happened,
but it's my understanding
that it was Julian behind the wheel.
You know what I do know?
That that thug has been trouble
since the day he got here,
and I want him gone.
You shouldn't be thinking
about the team right now.
You should focus on your son.
Everything else can be sorted out later.
[JUGHEAD] The Bulldogs weren't the only
Halloween tragedy that night.
The milkman
had tried to murder my bud, Ethel Muggs.
It was the same milkman
that I saw leaving my house
after he killed my parents, sheriff.
I wrestled the knife out of his hand,
and then...
It was self-defense, sheriff.
In case you're getting any funny ideas.
Well, at least all our questions
have finally been answered.
Are you joshing us?
Now I have even more questions.
Should I go to the station
and make a statement?
No. That won't be necessary.
This strikes me as an open-and-shut case.
Open and shut?
Sheriff, whoever this maniac is,
killed Ethel's parents,
killed Mr. Rayberry,
and tried to bump off Ethel.
If you have all the answers, who is he?
Huh? Who is the milkman?
I will get to that.
Maybe his fingerprints are on file
at the office,
but in the meantime,
we need to get Ethel back to the Sisters.
- No.
- [JUGHEAD] No. No, no.
The Sisters were abusing Ethel.
She'll come with me.
She needs to be
in the care of an adult, Jughead.
Well, that may be so, but not the Sisters.
[PHONE RINGS]
Frank, Archie. Do you have any news?
Jughead, slow down.
What is this about Ethel?
What?
Ethel, dear.
Mary and I have been
discussing everything,
and we've made a decision.
Given everything that's been going on,
we both think that it might best
if you stay with the Coopers.
What...? Again?
No. The last time
that I stayed with Mrs. Cooper,
she sent me to that horrible place.
Oh, honestly, Ethel.
Sending you to the Sisters
was more Mr. Cooper's idea.
So let's get you settled
in my sewing room.
Come along, dear.
If you hadn't been there,
those Bulldogs would've drowned.
You saved their lives, Reggie,
even Julian.
- You're a hero.
- I'm no hero.
When I realized I was the only one
who'd gotten free from the car
and kicked to the surface,
I knew that I had to
dive back down there...
and get everyone out.
Even in that moment,
I knew that if any of those guys died...
especially Blossom...
that I'd be blamed for it.
They would've locked me up
for the rest of my life.
Or done worse than lock me up.
Good morning.
I'm heading to school now, Ethel,
if you wanted to walk with me.
- Sure.
- Don't be ridiculous, Elizabeth.
I'll be driving Ethel
to school this morning.
My mom is such a phony-baloney.
She sent Ethel away
to the Sisters of Quiet Mercy,
and now she's playing nice with her
and treating me
like I'm some unwanted guest.
I tell you, Vee,
I have half a mind to run away.
You don't have to sell me
on the pain of phony parents.
And I'd invite you to stay with me
at The Pembrooke, but truth be told,
I've been living at the Babylonium
ever since my parents
locked me out of our apartment.
What? You're living at the movie theater?
Veronica Lodge is nothing more
than a common squatter.
Let me ask you,
have you tried breaking back in?
I know that this is a difficult time,
but I did wanna share, aloud,
a poem that one of you
turned in last week.
It's titled, "Phantom."
They tell me I'm solid
They pat me on the back
They see a son
A student
A team player
They see a boy like any other
But I look in the mirror
And there's no one there
Just smoke and mirrors
And I do not know how to be solid
Any thoughts, class?
It was beautiful.
[KEVIN] Yeah.
That was incredible, Clay.
I agree, but I didn't write it.
No, it was not Mr. Walker's poem.
It was Mr. Andrews' work.
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
I wish you'd speak up more
in class, Archie.
Based on this poem,
it's clear you have a lot to say.
All right, fellas, listen up.
We're scheduled for our big game
against Stonewall Prep this Friday night.
But after recent events...
we've decided to name a new captain
while Julian, God willing, recovers.
And that captain...
will be Archie.
[FANGS] All right, Archie.
Now, let's all take a knee
and say a prayer
for our Bulldog brother in distress.
We're so happy
to have you back with us, Ethel.
Yes, I admit, it's quite the reversal.
But you proved your sanity
by single-handedly
dispatching that, uh, drifter.
A drifter?
Who said that the milkman was a drifter?
Sheriff Keller, if I'm not mistaken.
It's obvious what happened.
This drifter, his mind was poisoned
by the dreck Pep Comics publishes
and he was inspired
to go on a murderous rampage.
Much like the original comic book.
Then he must've stolen a milkman's uniform
and begun killing
to satisfy some insane bloodlust.
[WHISTLES]
Well, that does makes perfect sense.
Except, why would he kill Ethel's parents,
and then Brad Rayberry,
and then try to get Ethel herself?
Do you really think
that a drifter would do that?
Yes, don't drifters usually move on?
Drift.
Neither of you
are in a position to theorize.
We have told you exactly what happened.
Now, I hope that you both finally see
the very real danger...
in what comic books pose to society.
- Uncle Frank?
- Hey, Archie.
[SIGHS] I, uh... I'm honored
to be named captain of this team,
but shouldn't it be Reggie?
He's our strongest player by a mile.
Well, that may be so, Archie, but...
this wasn't my call.
Clifford Blossom wanted you to step up.
And given the fact
that he sponsors the Bulldogs,
I thought it best to respect his wishes.
Clifford Blossom's
had it out for Reggie since day one.
The Bulldogs
are the mayor's pride and joy.
My strong advice...
leave this one alone.
But I'm glad you came to see me.
There's something I wanna give you.
Is that...?
Your dad's captain's patch.
I know he'd want you wearing it
for your first game as team captain.
Okay, Uncle Frank.
I'm leaving.
I'm going to stay with my friend Veronica.
It'll just be the two of us
in her apartment
doing whatever we want.
When have you not, Elizabeth?
["SEE SAW" PLAYING]
Where did you learn how to do that?
Pick a lock with a bobby pin?
Don't laugh,
but my Tracy True Teen Detective Handbook.
Laugh?
Betty, I love those books.
Okay. Question.
How quiet do we have to be in here
so as not to alert...?
His name is Smithers.
And we can be as loud as we want
when we're in the apartment.
It's just when we're going
up and down the back staircase
that we have to be mindful.
I told the boys that too.
What boys?
Archie and Reggie?
God, no. I actually wanna have some fun.
So I invited Kevin and Clay
to come over
after closing up at the Babylonium.
Father, I just got back from the hospital.
Please tell me the rumors
about basketball season continuing
whilst Julian languishes
are just that, rumors.
[CHUCKLES] You're brother's
always been a dunce.
He made his bed, let him lay in it.
As for the season, yes, Cheryl,
it will continue as scheduled.
It must.
Are you truly so desperate
to relive your glory days as a Bulldog
that you would forsake your own son?
Yes, I was a Bulldog.
And I'd do anything
to go back to those days again.
When I first realized
that a winning team can unite a town...
[CHUCKLES] You give the people that,
they'll follow you anywhere.
I certainly won't be shaking my pompoms
while my brother
hovers between life and death.
Oh, yes, you will.
You will put on your little happy face,
and you will cheer your little heart out,
until your spoiled pink lungs bleed.
Or you'll suffer
a fate worse than Julian's.
- [GASPS]
- Do I make myself clear?
♪ I'm gonna wash that man
Right out of my hair ♪
♪ I'm gonna wave that man
Right out of my arms ♪
♪ And send him on his way ♪
♪ Don't try to patch it up ♪
[ALL] ♪ Tear it up, tear it up ♪
♪ Wash him out, dry him out ♪
[ALL] ♪ Push him out, fly him out ♪
♪ Cancel him and let him go ♪
[ALL] ♪ Yeah, sister ♪
Sing it, Betty.
♪ If the man don't understand you ♪
♪ If you fly on separate beams ♪
♪ Waste no time, make a change ♪
♪ Ride that man right off your range ♪
♪ Rub him out of the roll call ♪
♪ And drum him out of your dreams ♪
[ALL] ♪ Oh, ho ♪
♪ If you laugh at different comics ♪
♪ If you root for different teams ♪
♪ Waste no time, weep no more ♪
♪ Show him what the door is for ♪
♪ Rub him out of the roll call ♪
♪ And drum him out of your dreams ♪
[ALL] ♪ Oh, ho ♪
♪ Oh, ho ♪
♪ We went and washed that man
Right out of our hair ♪
♪ And sent him on his way ♪
[ALL LAUGHING]
- [VERONICA] Care for a top-off?
- Yes, please.
Thank you, Vee.
This rum is so sweet and yummy.
Isn't it? I'll say this about my parents.
They keep
their liquor cabinet well-stocked.
Kev, this is so much more of a kick
than when you and I were going steady.
Oh, I agree.
And speaking of dating,
how was your Halloween
with Archie and Reggie?
With everything that happened,
I forgot to ask.
It seemed like something
was percolating with Archie,
and we did kiss, but then...
I'll be honest, I thought you and Reggie
might have made a love connection.
Well, now that we're talking about
both Archie and Reggie...
Kevin, Clay.
You fellas are always
in the boys' locker room together.
Tell us, who's packing the most heat?
Veronica!
- Uh...
- Hard to tell.
Oh, come off it, we all know how it goes.
It's after gym class.
You're having a steam.
You're snapping towels.
Are you seriously telling us
that neither of you
has ever cast an eyeball their way?
I will say that both Archie and Reggie...
both have a lot to be proud of.
I am not surprised.
I felt as much with Archie.
Okay. But, uh, the real story
coming out of the boys' locker room...
Yes. Julian Blossom?
- No.
- Fangs Fogarty?
[BOTH] No.
Dilton Doiley.
[BOTH SCREAM]
- No.
- It's always the little ones.
Well, to Dilton Doiley.
And all the boys of Riverdale High.
[ALL] To all the boys.
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- [BOISTEROUS ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHERYL]
Now that you've met our starting lineup,
please give a big Riverdale welcome
to the man who's going to lead us
to certain victory
against the Stonewall Stallions,
and our new team captain...
Archie Andrews.
[CHEERING]
Are you okay, Cheryl?
I'm fine. Just doing as is demanded of me.
Captain Andrews, will you please
say a few words to your loyal fans?
- [BOY] Yeah, take us to victory, Archie!
- [GIRL] All right!
- Um... [CLEARS THROAT]
- [MICROPHONE FEEDBACK WHINES]
Uh, the fact is,
I'm not really great with words.
But, uh...
[MICROPHONE WHINES]
It was nice, what you said in the gym.
Come on, Mrs. Thornton. I was awful.
Well, it might not have been
the Gettysburg Address, but...
it's hard to speak off the cuff like that.
However, when you write,
you do so with passion,
clarity, heart.
Well, that's swell of you to say,
but we both know that I'm not...
No, no. Stop right there.
I know putting pencil to paper
is not as exciting
as being captain of a sports team, but...
But I assure you, it can be.
And I hope you'll think about
putting as much energy into your writing
as you do into basketball someday.
Holy hell, freckles.
From what I've been hearing,
you survived those crazy nuns,
took out a killer, and cleared your name.
That's not bad for a teenybopper.
Not bad at all.
Thank you, Mr. Fieldstone.
I'm really just jazzed to be back.
Well, let's get you
drawing another story ASAP. Hmm?
- Jughead here will write a script for you.
- Oh, golly, we'd love that.
I am looking at the dream team.
So pitch me. Sky's the limit. Name it.
Anything you wanna do.
Well, in that case, I would love to do
a sequel to The Milkman Cometh story.
I think that we could
just make something...
Anything but that.
Forget the milkman, the milkman is dead.
You literally killed him. He's old news.
Well, Ethel and I were discussing
that The Milkman Cometh is still one of
your best-selling issues of all time.
With everything that's happened,
why not capitalize upon it?
Because the heat's on us right now.
Everybody's talking about
the latest editorial
that quack Werthers wrote.
Hell, even the AP picked it up.
We gotta be circumspect.
For a little while, at least.
So give me a story about a zombie,
or a goblin,
anything but a milkman, capisce?
From now on,
consider me lactose intolerant.
As Coco Chanel allegedly said,
"The best cure for a hangover
is spending money on new clothes."
It sounds better in French,
but the point still stands.
Are you girls
finding everything all right?
Mrs. Andrews, these pieces are stunning.
- Your taste is très magnifique.
- Thank you.
Could you please have these two dresses
sent over to The Pembrooke?
Of course.
- And yours too, Betty?
- Yes, please.
You're staying there as well?
Yes, ma'am. But don't worry,
my mother is copacetic with it.
Copacetic.
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
What the hell? They've got Peppy.
- Give our mascot back.
- Hey, simmer down, red.
You'll get your chance
to win him back on the court.
Of course, Mantle there, he's a choker.
Yeah, you put him under pressure
and he cracks.
That's how it was
when he played for us at Stonewall.
And dollars to donuts, he's gonna fold
like a sheet again this weekend.
Shut your mouth before I give you
a freaking knuckle sandwich.
Save it for the game.
We're real sorry to hear about Julian.
Such a tragedy.
But, hey, you know, we were thinking
of getting a wager going with you chumps.
But Stonewall
doesn't play for food stamps.
I know these turkeys. I played with them,
so I know how to beat them.
First up, Weston Wallis.
Has legitimate skills, but can't
sink a shot from outside the key.
Fangs, it's your job to keep him there.
That way,
he'll be tossing up air balls all night.
Nothing I dig more
than humiliating a rich boy.
- Consider it done.
- Good man.
Next up, Tank.
Looks like Boris Karloff,
but he panics when you crowd him.
Archie, that's your target. Stay on him
like the paint on the side of a barn.
Andrews, you with us?
He's a barn. I'm paint. Got it.
Righteous.
What's eating you?
Is it because Peppy got dog-napped?
Don't worry. We'll get him back.
Guaranteed.
It's not that. It's...
I feel like an imposter.
I shouldn't be the captain
of this team, Reg.
You should be the captain.
I mean, you're made for it.
Heck, it's your dream.
I don't think about that kind of stuff.
As far as dreams, I don't have any.
I have a plan.
To win the game this Friday night,
and then the game after that.
And to keep on winning until I go pro.
You got your eyes on the prize.
And you know what you do to get it.
I wish I could say the same about myself.
Can't you, captain?
I play basketball...
because it's a way for me
to feel close to my dad.
Not because it's my passion.
So, what's your passion?
Cars?
Girls?
You wouldn't believe it if I told you.
Hey, we talked about this.
Didn't you hear Mr. Fieldstone?
We got an ixnay on the ilkman-may.
I can't.
I can't, Jughead.
What gives?
Is it really so important
to do another milkman story?
You know, since this whole thing started,
no one but you has believed me.
People were telling me
that I was delusional,
or that I flipped a lid,
or that I killed my parents.
To the point
where I started to doubt my sanity.
And now the milkman is dead.
And everybody is still trying to tell me
what happened and how it happened.
Why? I don't know.
But I do know that I'm so tired...
of people telling me what I went through
and what I experienced.
I wanna tell my story.
Or at least a version of it.
Even if it's just in a comic book.
Well, hey, that makes a lot of sense.
And you'll draw the heck out of it.
We just have to figure out a creative way
to have our cake and eat it.
Without a glass of milk, of course.
[CHUCKLES]
This particular shade of pink
is Grace Kelly's favorite.
It's from the most fantabulous makeup shop
on Larchmont Boulevard.
My mom used to take me,
and we'd do exactly this.
She'd paint my nails right before bedtime.
My mom stopped tucking me in
after I got my gift from Mother Nature.
She said that I was now a woman
and didn't need to be coddled.
It's funny,
I practically ran away from home
and she...
doesn't seem to care.
Will you look at us, 16 years old,
living without our mothers.
Effectively orphans.
- Can I tell you something, Vee?
- Of course, Bee. Anything.
I feel so different
from everyone else in my family.
Sometimes I wonder if I was adopted.
- Is it just you and your parents?
- I have an older sister, Polly.
She left Riverdale
as soon as she turned 18.
Do you ever talk
to her about how you feel?
She's so busy.
Well, if you were adopted,
your family is the luckiest on earth.
Because you, Betty Cooper, are aces.
Not to mention beautiful to boot.
You know, if we're divulging
our deepest, darkest secrets,
I've always had
this paralyzing fear that...
That I was a mistake.
Unplanned.
And that my mother and father
never stopped resenting me for that.
I mean, they were fine having me around
when I was a little doll
they could dress up however they wanted.
But when I finally became old enough
to have my own mind,
with my own thoughts...
it was, "Bye-bye, Veronica."
Let's make a pact.
To never grow up
to be anything like our parents.
You know who I do think
are a happy and healthy couple?
- Kevin and Clay.
- Ah.
Aren't they the dreamiest?
I'm so happy for them.
Me too.
I'm also slightly jealous.
On some level,
it must be easier for two boys to date
than a boy and a girl.
None of that
battle-of-the-sexes stuff to navigate.
Fun fact, I read
in Dr. Kingsley's book that 81% of girls
experiment with other girls
before they turn 18.
Isn't that shocking?
Sounds about right to me.
I mean, I've kissed a girl before.
I won't say who, but you would know her.
Oh, my gosh.
Have you ever?
No, I haven't.
But I've thought about it.
It's only natural.
With whom?
With you.
Is it okay that I said that?
I'm glad you did.
Do you...? Do you wanna try it?
Me too.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KNOCK ON DOOR]
- Miss Veronica, we're coming in.
Smithers.
I stand corrected, Mrs. Andrews.
You were right about the squatters.
A mother's intuition always is.
Okay, girls,
you need to tell me everything.
Julian.
I know we don't always get along, but...
I love you.
Call me crazy,
but I miss your grating voice.
I miss your horsey laugh.
[SOBBING] Brother, dear.
Please come back to me.
If not for your own sake, then for mine.
I beg of you.
Oh, geez, would you stop it
with the waterworks, sis?
You're embarrassing both of us.
Julian.
You told a guy in a coma
he has a horsey laugh?
I'm gonna remember that.
Alice told you what?
"I'm not your mother anymore."
Unspeakable.
A mother disowning her own child.
And, Veronica, your parents evicted you?
Via telegram, via Smithers.
You poor things.
I knew something was wrong.
But don't worry,
I'm going to fix everything.
[FEATHERHEAD] Are we worried the Mantles
may try to take legal action against us
or the school board?
[CLIFFORD] Oh, don't be daffy, man.
They'd never find a lawyer
to represent them in a case like that.
Even if they did, they couldn't afford it.
- [FEATHERHEAD] You're right, Mr. Mayor.
- [CLIFFORD] Yeah, well, in any case,
uh, tell me a little bit more
about the Mantle boy's replacement.
Difficult keeping it hush-hush, Mr. Mayor,
but we just finalized the papers.
Your new ringer from Boston, K.O. Kelly,
will transfer to Riverdale High
as soon as next week.
Once Mantle gets us
that win against Stonewall,
we'll just swap him out for a normal,
red-blooded American lad.
A real one.
One that's just as good a player,
but more like us.
I will send that Mantle packing.
Of all the no-good,
rotten things in this world.
What kind of mother
disowns their own child?
When you have a child, do you know
what your middle name becomes?
Sacrifice.
I mean, we mothers were put
on this planet to nurture our children.
And here I thought
Penelope Blossom was bad.
You can bet your bottom dollar
I said the same thing to Hermione Lodge.
That you should both
do everything in your power
to right these horrific wrongs
and to regain your moral footing.
And you had best pray that you can
repair the damage that you've done.
Here you go, sweetie.
Oh, so am I your daughter again?
Of course. You and Ethel are.
[CHERYL] Archie.
Cheryl, I heard the good word
from the bird about Julian.
It is truly a miracle.
But I need to talk to you
about something else,
namely Reggie
and my father's nefarious plans for him.
[REGGIE] They're planning what?
After we play Stonewall,
Clifford Blossom is gonna cut you
and bring in some goofball ringer
from Boston named K.O. Kelly.
How much you wanna wager
the new ringer
is a few shades lighter than me?
Look, I'm in knots about this, Reg.
What do you wanna do?
I wanna finish
what I was brought here to do.
I wanna lead the Bulldogs
to their first championship in a decade.
- And I wanna do it as captain.
- That's what I want too.
Same with all the guys on the team.
So let's see
if we can make it happen for you.
What do you think, Mr. Fieldstone?
It's not about a milkman.
It's about a mailman.
- In case that wasn't obvious enough.
- Hmm.
It's subversive.
But, uh, it's kind of cheeky,
and I like that.
Says something without being ham-fisted.
It's...
Well, I don't know
how to tell you this, but, uh...
I think it's brilliant.
Oh, gee. Thanks, Mr. Fieldstone.
- We tried other things.
- We just kept circling back to, uh...
The mailman. Yeah, I get it.
It's a pretty neat work-around,
I must admit.
But Werthers and the powers that be
will not be as tickled as I am.
If we publish this, it's gonna
thicken the storm that's coming.
And believe me,
a storm is coming like the wrath of God.
A storm is coming.
Well, the way I see it
is we have two options.
We either bury our heads in the sand
and pray the storm will pass over us...
But like you,
I don't really see that happening.
...or, we run headlong into the thunder
and thumb our noses at it.
Jughead, you are wise beyond your years.
- You know that?
- Shucks.
What do you think, girl genius?
I vote we thicken this milkshake.
Ah, to hell with it.
I've always been a
"thumb my nose at the world" kind of guy.
Bernie, call up the printer.
We got a comic book to publish.
Shouldn't you be resting up
before the big game, boys?
I want you at your best.
We know what you have planned, sir.
We're here to give it to you straight.
We're not letting you replace Reggie
with another player.
I'm turning over my captainship to him.
It's what he deserves.
You don't have the authority, Andrews.
Not even your uncle does. Only I do.
Well, in that case,
if you don't make Reggie captain
for the rest of the season, then I walk.
Me too.
And if Archie and Reggie walk,
we all walk.
We're a team.
We stand together.
- [BOY 1] We're in this together.
- [BOY 2] We all go.
I'm guessing it'd be pretty embarrassing
for the mayor of Riverdale
to derail a championship season
out of, what, spite?
Let me make one thing
abundantly clear to you boys.
I do not take kindly to threats.
This isn't a threat, Mr. Mayor.
Just laying out your options.
So, what will it be, sir?
[PHONE RINGS]
- Hello?
- Phew.
It's you. I was so worried
your mom was gonna pick up.
Veronica, that is so strange.
I was just about to call you.
Well, I was only calling to say good night
and that... I miss you.
- What were you calling about?
- The same.
Great minds.
I love you, Bee.
I love you too, Vee.
Say, were you gonna go
to the big game tomorrow...
against Stonewall?
I almost forgot. I guess I am. You?
I suppose so.
You wanna sit together?
That way you can explain
all the esoteric rules to me.
The few I picked up as a River Vixen.
Fab.
What should we wear, do you think?
Before we head out, is there
anything you'd like to say, captain?
Just thank you. I know the only reason
Mayor Blossom rubber stamped me
is because the way
you fellas supported me.
No one's ever done that for me before.
Also,
um...
my folks made the trip from Duck Creek.
To watch my first game as captain.
So...
- Let's win this for Reggie's folks.
- That's right.
And for Peppy!
- [ALL] For Peppy!
- [ALL BARKING]
Hey.
- Don't even give them a second to breathe.
- Count on that.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANNOUNCER] From the opening tipoff,
the Riverdale Bulldogs,
led by Team Captain Reggie Mantle,
dominated the Stonewall Stallions,
who broke school records in points,
rebounds, and assists.
Indeed, all the Bulldogs
treated friends, family, and neighbors
to a night they won't soon forget.
Playing bravely
in honor of their teammate Julian Blossom,
who, as we understand it, is on the mend.
While proving beyond any shadow of a doubt
that this was the team,
led by Mantle the Magnificent,
that could take Riverdale
all the way to the state championship.
At the final buzzer,
in a show of good sportsmanship,
the defeated Stallions shook hands
with their victors at center court
before returning the statue
of Riverdale's beloved mascot, Peppy.
So how's it feel?
MVP and record-breaker?
I'm not gonna lie,
I'm happy my parents got to see me win.
They were so proud of you, Reg.
They were on cloud nine.
You earned it.
Which is why I, uh...
I wanted to give you something.
Your dad's captain patch?
Archie, I can't.
I want you to, Reg.
It would mean a lot to me, and to him.
I'll honor him, I promise.
And then I'll give it back to you
at the end of the season.
So you, uh, sticking around
on the team or what?
Well, I guess. Maybe for a little while.
I gotta watch your back.
What about writing poems?
That's what you love to do, right?
That's your passion, isn't it?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I'm not sure the world's ready
for Archie Andrews, beatnik poet.
Maybe.
Eh, maybe not.
[JUGHEAD] For a brief moment,
they were two teenage boys...
friends, practically brothers,
on the cusp of pursuing
very different dreams,
unaware that a storm was coming,
as Mr. Fieldstone said.
- [THUNDER CRASHING]
- Like the wrath of God, it was coming.
And that all of us
would be smashed to pieces by it.