[VERONICA] Dear Girl Next Door,
I'm not usually one to gripe
or seek advice from strangers,
but I'm sick of living in a world
that doesn't take me seriously
as a young businesswoman.
Did you know
I can't even open a checking account?
[TONI] Dear Girl Next Door,
I know and love who I am.
I'm Black, I'm bold, I'm beautiful,
but it's frustrating to live in a world
that doesn't celebrate me
for being those things.
[CHERYL] Dear Girl Next Door,
with every breath I take,
I'm living a lie, forever worried
that I'll reveal my true self
to an intolerant world
that won't let me love who I want to love.
[MIDGE] Dear Girl Next Door, I feel like
I'm sitting on a ticking time bomb.
And it's only a matter of time
before the world stigmatizes me
for being a woman of loose morals.
[EVELYN] Dear Girl Next Door,
or should I say Little Miss Busybody?
What makes you think
you have all the answers anyhoo?
[ETHEL] Dear Girl Next Door,
I know I should be grateful
for the things I have,
but it's hard
when everything around me is beautiful
and the world's constantly reminding me
I'm not one of those things.
Gosh. Ethel, that's a beautiful sketch.
Is that for art class?
She's finishing up the sign-up sheet
for Miss Riverdale Teen Queen pageant.
Your mom asked me to be her assistant.
Mm. Is it really time
for that embarrassing cattle call again?
Yes, it is.
But this year, first time ever,
we're going to be broadcast live
on national television
right out of the RIVW studios.
Whoop-de-do.
I hope you don't expect me to compete.
Oh, no, of course not.
Why would you wanna participate
in anything so glorious and wholesome
and all-American
as Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
when you're already holding the crown
for Miss Grumpy Pants U.S.A.?
And I'm sure you're not interested
in any of our wonderful prizes this year.
- Like, say, a new car.
- I don't have a driver's license.
- A Hollywood screen test.
- Not interested in the slightest.
Or a scholarship
to whatever college accepts you.
The pageant's giving away scholarships?
Since when?
Since we're gonna be live
on national television.
But I understand, you're not interested.
Ethel, she is beautiful.
But why don't we change her
from a blond to a brunette?
She'd be much more likable that way.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
What do rules say about outside designers?
Edith Head has been dying
to design a bathing suit for me,
and Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
would be a divine showcase for it.
Oh, Vee, please tell me
you're not signing up for that.
I already did, Betty.
Imagine the publicity it'd bring
to the Babylonium if I won.
- It's a business decision.
- But it objectifies girls.
I mean, wearing a swimsuit and heels
at the same time?
What about that peep show you did
with Archie? Was that objectifying?
Yes. Well, that was between me and Archie.
And he was in his underwear too.
What I wouldn't give.
How about flashing your panties
on live television?
That was my decision, on my terms.
Look, beauty pageants can certainly
be seen as objectifying women
if you choose to look at them
solely through that one lens.
What other lens is there?
What's that saying?
"Beauty is in the eye of the beholder"?
Speaking for myself,
I love being beautiful.
Not for the drooling approval
of some fuddy-duddy judges.
I refuse to give them any power over me.
I decide if I'm beautiful or not.
And I am, as are we all.
But doesn't it bother you
that beauty pageants
pit girls against girls?
There's a way around that.
We gals just need to make a pact.
No matter who wins, we all win.
And no catfighting or backbiting.
Except against Evelyn Evernever,
who was the first to sign up, annoyingly.
Toni, you're doing it too?
Trust me, Betty,
I feel the same way you do.
But this is the first year that
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen is integrated.
Even though there's not
a snowball's chance in hell
those stuffed-shirt judges
will give me the title,
I'll make sure I show the country
one Black woman competing for the crown.
And if I do win, don't worry.
I'll call out the Miss America pageant
for the fact that all its contestants
must be of good health in the white race.
My parents sponsor
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen, of course,
so it'd definitely raise a few eyebrows
if I didn't compete.
Though,
if I do win the title again this year,
I would use my platform differently.
Advocating for the more
disenfranchised teens in this town.
You sure you should be competing, Midge,
you know, in your delicate condition?
Won't you be wearing high heels for hours?
What if you trip?
You're the sweetest
for worrying about me, Fangs, but...
this might be the last time
I get to do anything like this.
Just...
dress up and be a 16-year-old girl.
Compete for some silly tiara
like it's the only thing that matters.
What I said before, ice it.
You go compete your heart out
on that stage, baby.
If those judges got eyes in their head,
they won't look at those other wannabes.
Because you're the hottest mama
with the classiest chassis
in the whole town, by a mile.
All right. Now that it's just us,
selfishly, of course I think it'd be a gas
if we were all part
of Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
- So I'm gonna go out on a limb here...
- I think I know what you're going to say.
Let me ask you this, Betty.
If your mom wasn't hosting the pageant,
wouldn't you be competing
for those ginchy prizes?
Imagine if you got that scholarship.
It could be your ticket to freedom.
You could go
to whatever school accepted you.
On your own terms,
not at your parents' whims.
- Someplace like...
- Sarah Florence or Smith College.
Mm-hm.
So you have thought about it.
I knew it.
["THERE SHE IS, MISS AMERICA" PLAYING]
♪ There she is ♪
♪ Miss America ♪
♪ Your ideal ♪
♪ The dream of a million girls ♪
♪ Who are more than pretty... ♪
[ALICE] Well, well, well,
if it isn't the latest and greatest
aspiring Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
Yes, Mother, I signed up.
Are you overjoyed?
No. Actually, I'm not, Elizabeth.
I would like to know
what your nefarious plan is.
Do you plan on winning the crown
and then pulling the entire temple down
around you,
make some kind of feminist statement?
No. I do not wanna
pull the temple down around me.
To be honest, it'd be nice
to win that scholarship money.
Oh, please, Elizabeth.
You get straight A's.
If you so choose to go to college...
Which I'm not recommending.
I would much rather you go
to finishing school.
...you're gonna be able
to get an academic scholarship.
Don't try and bamboozle me into thinking
that you care about the scholarship.
What would you like me to say then?
I'd like you to say that you actually want
to be Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
for the joy and satisfaction of it.
You know, I was Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
back in my day.
I know.
Everyone knows.
The night I was crowned,
it was the greatest night of my life.
I thought I could do anything,
be anything.
You know, well, it's silly, but I thought
that I might grow up to be a stewardess
and travel the world,
see glamorous places.
Wait, you wanted to be a stewardess?
That I did not know.
- Hmm.
- What happened? Why didn't you do it?
Well, I married your father, of course.
And then I had your sister,
and then I had you,
and I gave up my silly dreams
of becoming a stewardess.
- Can you imagine?
- Yeah.
I can.
How fab that would have been for you.
Traveling to all those places,
meeting glamorous people.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, Betty,
whatever your reasons are,
I think
this is gonna be wonderful for you.
Imagine if you won. That would be
the greatest accomplishment of my life.
This is so exciting.
I can't wait to rehearse with you, girl.
Wait, we have to rehearse?
Yes, of course.
I have to guide you girls
through this entire process.
And mind you,
this is not just glitz and glam.
This is rigorous, hard work,
like going into battle.
So I want you to get a good night's sleep.
I don't wanna see any shadowy bags
under those eyes in the morning.
A Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
does not walk, she glides.
That's what I wanna see from you.
Gliding, gliding, gliding.
Focus.
We wanna block out everything
and only concentrate
on being the most poised,
the most refined,
and the most elegant we can be.
Appearance, posture, carriage, character.
All these elements go into the making
of a Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
We must carry ourselves
with the dignity of English royalty.
Our categories are evening gowns,
vim and vigor,
bathing suits, point of view,
and the ever most important
talent competition.
It's all about showing how well-rounded
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen is.
That's all fine and dandy,
but I don't need some creepy old men
telling me how well-rounded
my backside is.
I know how shapely I am.
- Toni.
- Greaser garbage.
Preppy troll.
[ALICE] Miss Topaz, really.
As Miss Blossom would tell you,
being Miss Riverdale Teen Queen,
you serve as an ambassadress for Riverdale
for the entire year of your appointment.
Why, you must be the female embodiment
of all things good and decent
in our little town with pep.
In fact, "Pep" should be your middle name.
All right, one more hour of posture work
and then we will go down
to Mrs. Andrews' dress shop
and have you fitted for gowns.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING AND CHEERING]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Ethel Muggs, as the winner of this year's
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen pageant,
can you tell us what you're feeling
at this exact moment?
Gosh, Mrs. Cooper.
I guess I'm really just wishing
that my parents were alive to see this.
Oh, but, Ethel, they are.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING AND CHEERING]
[ETHEL] Mom?
Dad?
Ethel, as our newly minted
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen,
are there any other dreams
that you're looking to fulfill?
Now that you mention it,
a lot of people don't know that I paint,
as well as draw comic books,
and I'd be so jazzed
to have an original Ethel Muggs hanging
in a real gallery or museum.
Ethel,
I have got some great news for you then.
Your beautiful self-portrait
is going to be on display
at the Guggenheim Museum.
Oh, my gosh, the Guggenheim?
[ALICE] Yes.
Ethel, this is your night
and your night alone.
Is there anything else
that would make it even more special?
Well... I think
it would just be the ginchiest thing ever
if Jughead Jones were my boyfriend.
Oh, Ethel. Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
has the pick of the litter,
but if it's Jughead Jones you want,
then Jughead is yours.
[ETHEL] Jughead?
- Are you really my boyfriend?
- Of course I am.
You've always been my best gal.
Beautiful.
Ethel?
Ethel.
Sorry, what was that, Mrs. Cooper?
You did make an appointment
at the dress shop, I hope.
Mm-hm.
[MARY] Look at all these gorgeous girls.
You know, back in the day, I competed
to be Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
all through high school.
- Against you, Alice, if I'm not mistaken.
- You always gave me a run for my money.
And you always won.
Oh, it's funny.
I really thought
that being Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
would be a stepping stone
to doing something important with my life.
Like, I don't know,
being the First Lady or something.
Well, there's nothing more important
than being a wife and mother, Mary.
Maybe for our generation, Alice,
but I feel like these girls
could do anything they want,
be anything they want.
No disrespect to Mamie Eisenhower,
she's an icon,
but do you girls ever think
we'll have a female president?
- I wouldn't vote for a woman.
- Or a Black president for that matter?
Man or woman.
Think about how much change
would have to occur for that.
It'll happen. In our lifetime, I bet.
Now, now, I think it's important
to manage one's expectations.
- Don't you think, Mary?
- Of course.
Oh, Ethel, can you make sure
you pin Betty's dress
all the way around the hem?
Okay.
Midge, let's look at this fit on you.
[ETHEL SOBBING]
Ethel.
Are you crying?
Sorry. I won't get any tears
on your dress, I promise.
No, no, what's the matter?
Nothing. You're just so beautiful, Betty.
You and all the other girls
are just so beautiful.
I think we might need
to let this out just a tiny bit.
[EVELYN] Midge, you better start
cutting back on those desserts,
otherwise that cute boyfriend of yours
might decide you're too much to handle.
Evelyn, why don't you do us all a favor
and take a long walk off a short pier?
I'm just gonna go get my measuring tape.
Midge, dear, why don't you and I
have a little chat later, huh?
Just between us.
[BETTY] Ethel, what were those waterworks
at the dress shop about?
Did something happen?
No.
Nothing.
I guess I just wish
that I could be competing with you all.
Ethel, you're so beautiful.
- Why aren't you competing?
- I couldn't.
You've heard what your mom said
about being Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
She's supposed to
embody the best of the town,
be Riverdale's ideal girl.
That's not me, Betty.
I'm the girl whose parents were murdered.
I'm the girl who's quiet
and likes comic books
and draws creepy pictures.
No one in their right mind
would crown me Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
I know what my mom has been saying, Ethel,
but straight from the fridge, you...
You're such a wonderful, beautiful person.
You've overcome so much adversity
in your life,
more than any other girl in Riverdale,
and that is inspiring.
You are inspiring.
You have more pep in your little finger
than the rest of us do
in our whole bodies combined.
And you have every right to be competing,
just as much as the rest of us.
No.
I couldn't.
Really, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said anything.
♪ So now I lay me down to cry ♪
♪ Why did I tell my love a lie? ♪
So, Midge, how far along are you?
And no fibbing, please.
I recognize that glow.
Girls, I appreciate you gathering
for an emergency meeting before school.
Now, some of you may know,
Midge Klump is no longer with us.
- What? What happened? Did Midge die?
- Oh, no, no, she's still alive.
But regrettably, she is no longer eligible
to compete for Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
And moreover, she will no longer
be a student here at Riverdale High.
She will continue her studies
at the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
- But, Mrs. Cooper...
- And I assure you she's doing just fine.
Really, girls,
this is the best thing for her.
When you see her again
in six or seven months,
you will see that she is right as rain.
Six or seven months? What, is Midge...?
Also, this is a good time to remind you
that we must treat our bodies as temples.
Temples that must be protected
against any kind of defilement.
On that note, we will see you back here
for some good, clean fun this afternoon.
Okay? Very good.
I just don't understand.
Why would Midge be sent away?
I thought you were supposed to be smart.
Midge has a bun in the oven.
- Shut your pie hole.
- It's the worst-kept secret in town.
Second worst, after you two.
This wouldn't be the first time
a girl's been sent away to hide her shame.
Sadly, this is standard practice
in Hollywood.
- Midge has nothing to be ashamed of.
- [EVELYN] Says you.
She let a greaser paw at her
like a dirty rag.
You're cruising for a bruising,
you square.
Okay, wait.
So Midge and Fangs have actually...?
Yes, Betty.
Just once, or multiple times?
From the way those two
would look at each other,
I'm guessing
they were doing the deed on the reg.
If you must know,
Midge loves Fangs and Fangs loves Midge.
And if it wasn't
for her classist, racist parents,
- they'd be together right now.
- Quite the cautionary tale if you ask me.
No one is, you goon from Saskatoon.
I'm just... I'm wondering how Midge
could have ended up getting...
Uh...
No, I understand how it happened.
I'm just wondering if they were using...
If they were using protection.
Good question.
Midge said they were, but once it slipped.
- That's what Fangs told me too.
- See, this is why they ought to invent,
- I don't know, a pill or something.
- A what?
A pill.
Like a monthly pill that girls can take.
That protects them from... accidents.
Even happy ones.
Because let's face it,
we're the ones who have to live
with the consequences, not the boys.
They get claps on the back
while we bear the burden,
while we're stigmatized.
- Poor Midge. Her life is just...
- [CHERYL] Her life is not ruined.
Midge is one of my Vixens.
I won't let this destroy her.
Except you're no longer a Vixen,
and neither is Midge.
- Who did let you sit with us?
- I wonder if Fangs knows about this.
If he doesn't now, he will soon.
The whole school will.
- Then I should find him, talk to him.
- I'll come with you.
Betty, what are you thinking about?
Just how quickly
your entire life can change.
How one night
can decide everything for you.
You were quiet in the lounge, Ethel.
I keep thinking about Midge
at the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
It's awful what's happening to Midge.
We will figure out a way to help her.
But in the meantime...
I also think this presents an opportunity.
- What do you mean?
- There's an open spot now
to replace Midge in the pageant,
and what better girl to do it than you?
- Do you really think that, Betty?
- I do.
It almost feels like your destiny now,
but only if you want to, Ethel.
I do. But what about your mom?
There's so much that needs to get done,
and she still needs an assistant...
I have someone in mind for that.
They took Midge?
I'm gonna go out there to that convent,
I'm gonna bust Midge out of there.
She doesn't belong in that place.
They do experiments on those kids,
give them psychedelic drugs and stuff.
The last thing anyone needs
is you going in half-cocked.
Kidnapping Midge
after she's already been kidnapped once
will only make things worse.
We need more information.
Midge's parents know she's pregnant
because Mrs. Cooper forced it out of her,
but they may not know
that you're the father.
We should endeavor to keep it that way
so you're not arrested.
- Or worse.
- What am I supposed to do? Huh?
- Bupkis?
- We stick with the original plan.
You write a hit song,
you get a gold record,
and you become undeniable
to Midge's parents.
Focus on getting ready
for when you and Midge get reunited.
Look, my parents have made
many charitable donations to the Sisters,
so I will work on setting up at least
a phone call between you and dear Midge.
But you have to listen to Toni.
And, Fangs, remain calm.
Calm. [SNAPS FINGERS] Okay.
Beautiful.
What's going on in here?
I'm just getting Ethel all caught up,
but she has perfect poise, honestly.
- And doesn't she look to die for?
- Getting caught up on what, exactly?
Oh, didn't you hear?
Ethel's replacing Midge in the pageant.
- And she already knows all the routines.
- That is wonderful.
Um, but who's gonna be my assistant?
Here's your java, Mrs. Cooper.
Just the way Betty said you liked it.
Three sugars, extra cream.
Can I speak to you in the hallway?
Sure, Mom.
A few more laps and then we'll brainstorm
some ideas for the talent competition.
I knew you were gonna try to undermine me.
How am I trying to undermine you?
Midge dropped out,
or more likely was forced out by you.
- Now, what's wrong with Ethel competing?
- What's wrong?
Ethel does not represent the ideals
of Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
- Not by a country mile.
- Why? She's not pregnant.
No. No, she's not,
but she has an unsavory history.
Are you talking about what happened
with her parents, or something else?
Whoa. You are awful.
I am here to protect the office
of Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
I am not gonna let you turn this
competition into one of your crusades.
And whether you believe me or not,
I am also
and especially trying to protect Ethel
from the scrutiny
that Miss Riverdale Teen Queen demands.
I'm sorry, but over my dead body
is she going to compete.
Mom, Ethel should be
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
She needs and deserves it
more than the rest of us.
Think about it for one second, okay?
Ethel is an orphan. This scholarship
may be her only chance to go to college.
- No!
- Mom.
That is final. Ethel is a lovely girl,
but this is not a charity,
it's a competition.
And since you made this mess,
you're the one that's gonna tell her
that she has to withdraw, not me!
[TONI] What's the trouble now?
Well, I got Ethel
to sign up for the pageant,
and no surprise, my mom blew a gasket.
She's not letting Ethel compete
in Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
- Even though there's an empty slot.
- Oh, dear.
And why doesn't she want Ethel
to drop a nickel and then participate?
It's more of the same.
Ethel doesn't represent
the ideal blah-blah-blah.
My mom is nuttier than
a Christmas fruitcake, but I'm in it now.
And I don't wanna be the one
to tell Ethel that she doesn't...
represent the very best of Riverdale.
Imagine what winning would do for her.
Imagine the doors it would open.
Not just in high school,
but for the rest of her life.
Honestly, Ethel's got
as much chance of winning as I do,
but we're with you, Betty.
What should we do?
I'm open to ideas, ladies.
I vote we stand together, link arms,
and demand Ethel gets a chance to compete
or we all withdraw.
Quote it. I'm in, sisters.
This pageant's nowheresville without us.
Okay.
- I'll go talk to my mom.
- [VERONICA] Hold the line.
Thinking it through,
maybe this is one of those times
you go around your mom
to someone who might be more inclined
to listen to reason... or threats.
- Someone like my dad?
- Exactly.
And maybe
you shouldn't go in alone, either.
Maybe you go
with a more seasoned negotiator
who won't get bogged down
in messy, sticky family dynamics.
Like moi.
[BETTY] Ready?
- [VERONICA] Mr. Cooper.
- Hi, Dad.
Hey, ladies, what's the good word?
May we bend your ear about a few,
let's call them competition parameters,
that we and our fellow pageant contestants
have been discussing?
And what would those parameters be?
The first being Ethel Muggs
must be allowed to participate.
Let me just stop you girls right there.
I've already gotten an earful
about this from Mrs. Cooper.
And I'm afraid
that there is just no wiggle room.
- But...
- I'm sorry, girls, truly.
But there is a lot riding on this pageant.
And how we present ourselves to the world
is of the utmost importance, Veronica.
It's funny, Mr. Cooper, I've been doing
research on TV ad spending, for kicks,
including how much money
a live television event can bring in.
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen is going to be
huge for RIVW, we all know that.
We all want that.
Also, we're guessing you've already sold
all your commercial spots, am I right?
Which means you're on the hook,
and you can't cash those checks
unless Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
airs without a hitch.
What exactly are you two driving at?
Only that you might find yourself
in a precarious position
if all your teen contestants suddenly
decided to pull out of the pageant.
Which we will, Dad, if you don't fix it
with Mom so that Ethel can compete.
Betty, I...
[SIGHS]
Okay, fine. I'll see what I can do.
Thank you, Mr. Cooper. That's fantabulous.
And one more thing.
We want the swimsuit promenade
cut from the pageant.
What? Why?
That is the judges' favorite segment.
I'm sure.
But frankly, there's just no justifying
that outdated and plainly sexist aspect
of the competition.
Especially considering
all our judges are men,
and two of them are faculty members
at our school.
Don't you concur, Mr. Cooper?
Why do you constantly
undermine me, Harold?
And especially on the day of the pageant?
- But I don't...
- Put a sock in it!
You always undercut me. Always.
Which is especially galling
because I have spent the best years
of my life cleaning up after your messes.
- Alice, I'm not trying to undermine you...
- So, what if Ethel wins?
And some nosy Brenda Starr takes it
upon herself to look into her past?
What happens then, Hal?
To us? To our family?
Sweetheart, please, calm down.
Oh, do not tell me to calm down.
It doesn't matter
if Ethel competes or not.
You know who the judges are.
There is no way that Ethel is going to be
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
You're making a mountain
out of this molehill.
You made it a mountain, Hal.
Now, come help me with my necklace.
And another thing, mister,
I want more on-air time.
- Thirty seconds is not long enough.
- They're not fighting about me, are they?
[ALICE] The people want to see me.
- They need to see me.
- No. Not at all.
They're just nervous
about the pageant being live this year.
Last-minute jitters.
Trust me, once the cameras start rolling,
they'll be fine.
But clue me in.
Have you decided on a song
for the talent competition yet?
[DRAMATIC ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL JINGLES]
Archie, it's time for
the evening gala promenade.
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming.
This reminds me of county fairs back home.
We used to have Miss Duck Creek pageants,
complete with butter-carving competitions.
Can't believe they cut the bathing suits.
Do you wanna see your sister
prancing around like a bathing beauty?
It's kind of pervy.
Jones, don't you have
another comic book to write?
- As a matter of fact, I don't right now.
- Pop, can you turn it up?
- Kevin's about to sing.
- [HAL] Welcome back
- to Miss Riverdale Teen Queen 1955...
- [CLAY] Thanks, Pop.
...live from the RIVW stages.
And now, would you please welcome
Mr. Kevin Keller,
who will serenade us
during our evening gown promenade.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
♪ Some enchanted evening ♪
♪ You may see a stranger... ♪
First up, our reigning
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
I give you Miss Cheryl Blossom.
- ♪ Across a crowded room ♪
- [AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
♪ And somehow you know ♪
Miss Betty Cooper.
♪ You know even then ♪
♪ That somehow you'll see her ♪
[MOUTHING] Chin up.
♪ Again and again ♪
[HAL] Miss Evelyn Evernever
and Miss Ethel Muggs.
♪ Some enchanted evening ♪
♪ When you find your true love ♪
♪ When you hear her call you ♪
Miss Veronica Lodge.
♪ Across a crowded room ♪
♪ Then fly to her side ♪
- [WHISTLES]
- ♪ And make her your own ♪
And finally, Miss Toni Topaz.
♪ Or all through your life ♪
♪ You may dream all alone ♪
♪ Once you have found her
Never let her go ♪
♪ Once you have found her ♪
♪ Never let her go ♪
Let's hear it for Mr. Kevin Keller.
But most especially, our lovely ladies.
Don't they look just swell?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING AND APPLAUDING]
Gorgeous.
[HAL] And that was Miss Veronica Lodge
on the tightrope.
Wasn't she the loveliest
of lady daredevils?
- Wow.
And now, performing the original song
"Who Will Love Me As I Am?"
to end our talent competition,
here is Miss Ethel Muggs.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
♪ Like a fish plucked from the ocean ♪
♪ Tossed into a foreign stream ♪
♪ Always knew that I was different ♪
♪ Often fled into a dream ♪
Come on.
♪ I ignored the raging currents ♪
♪ Right against the tide I swam ♪
♪ But I floated with the question ♪
♪ Who will love me as I am? ♪
Hot diggity. Ethel's got a set of pipes.
More than that. She's got star quality.
Sheesh, is there anything
this girl can't do?
I think I'm in love.
♪ Could we bend the laws of nature? ♪
♪ Could a lion love a lamb? ♪
♪ Who could see beyond this surface? ♪
♪ Who will love me as I am? ♪
♪ Like a clown whose tears
Cause laughter ♪
♪ Trapped inside the center ring ♪
♪ Even seeing smiling faces ♪
♪ I am lonely pondering ♪
♪ Who would want to join this madness? ♪
♪ Who would change my monogram? ♪
♪ Who will be part of my circus? ♪
♪ Who will love me as I am? ♪
♪ Who will ever call to say
"I love you"? ♪
♪ Send me flowers or a telegram? ♪
♪ Who could proudly stand beside me? ♪
♪ Who will love me ♪
♪ As I am? ♪
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Yeah!
Wow!
Whoa, man!
Well, it has been a spectacular evening,
and everyone is a winner.
But now it is time
for our judges to decide
who will be the next
Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
Fifty cents says it's Veronica.
Who knew she was an acrobat?
Well, I don't know. Betty's delivery of
the Gettysburg Address was stirring stuff.
As long as it's not my sister.
If there's justice, it'll be Ethel.
We should've made the musical about her.
Looks like our judges
have made their decision.
And as you can see, my lovely wife Alice,
a former Miss Riverdale Teen Queen
herself, has joined me for the verdict.
I must say, you look absolutely wonderful.
- Doesn't she look wonderful, folks?
- Oh, stop it. Stop it.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
Thank you, dear.
This is my favorite night of the year,
even more than Christmas.
Because tonight,
one of these lucky girls' lives
is about to change forever.
-[HAL] And the winner of a brand-new car,
-[DRUM ROLL]
a Hollywood screen test,
a college scholarship,
and the title
of Miss Riverdale Teen Queen 1955 is...
[DRUM ROLL STOPS, CYMBAL CRASHES]
Ethel Muggs, everyone.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING AND CHEERING]
Ethel Muggs
is Miss Riverdale Teen Queen 1955!
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Smile, dear. The world is watching.
- Hi, sweetheart. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
[ALICE] Yes.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
- Fifty cents! You owe me 50 cents!
- You said Veronica!
It's incredible.
[DINGS]
Hey, Pop. Cheryl said I should be
expecting a call any minute.
[PHONE RINGING]
You go right ahead, young man.
Hello? Midge?
Fangs, honey bun.
It's so good to hear your voice.
I know, baby. I miss you.
Me too. It happened so fast, Fangs. I...
I still can't believe it.
Mrs. Copper talked to my mom
and the next thing I knew,
I was in the car
being driven to the convent.
- What are we gonna do?
- Same thing we talked about.
You just... You just have to stay strong
while you're in there.
I will. You know I will.
And trust me when I say,
we're gonna get through this, Midge.
And we're gonna be a family.
And we're gonna get married,
come hell or high water.
You believe me, don't you?
Of course I do.
With all my heart and soul.
That's my girl.
Oh, Fangs, I love you.
I love you too.
[SOBBING]
Mom?
I was just going to get some milk.
Is everything okay?
Is this sour grapes
because Ethel won and I lost?
You think you know everything,
don't you, Betty? Open it.
Wait, Ethel didn't win?
That's right.
Your father and the judges were furious
when I read her name instead of yours.
But what could they do?
They couldn't contradict me.
It would have been an embarrassment
to them and the station.
Such are the hazards of live television.
I don't understand. You...
You wanted Ethel to win after all?
Maybe...
Maybe I truly believe that Miss Riverdale
Teen Queen can change lives.
Even a life
as broken and hopeless as Ethel's.
Or maybe I just didn't want you to win.
I guess you'll never know.
But know this, Elizabeth.
Even with all your do-gooding
and grandstanding, Ethel would have lost.
Her life is gonna be better because of me.
You remember that.
No matter what happens next.
You can say whatever you want to me, Mom.
Downplay.
Equivocate.
But you did a decent thing for once.
And I may not understand the reason why,
but I'm choosing to believe
that, deep down,
you are a kind, caring, good person.
You think so, do you?
I do.
And I love you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
♪ The hands of time keep turning 'round
Around and round ♪
♪ I'm here alone... ♪
[BETTY] Dear Monica Posh...
Dear Sandy Sapphire...
Dear Coral Peasbottom...
Dear Bitsy Block...
Dear Carrie Carryon...
Dear Edith Cups...
First, let me begin by saying
you are not alone in this world.
And though it may not
feel like it today...
[TYPEWRITER DINGS]
there is a hope for a better tomorrow.
In fact, we girls are that hope.