[CREATURE GROWLING ON-SCREEN]
[WOMAN SCREAMS ON-SCREEN]
[JUGHEAD] One distinct advantage
of dating an owner of a movie theater
is getting to see flicks
with my pals for free,
which is why every Tuesday night
we would gather to watch whatever latest
Atomic Age fright-fest was playing,
little imagining
that we would soon be walking
into our very own real-life
science-fiction-tinged B-movie.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
There, suddenly,
was a melting man coming towards us,
looking like a wax statue that had been
left out in the sun too long.
At which point the cavalry
suddenly arrived.
[GUNFIRE]
Sheriff Keller would soon be claiming
the man was a vagrant,
suffering from a rare case of...
Wait for it... leprosy.
But that didn't jibe with what
I overheard Ethel say to Ben Button.
He's wearing the same uniform my dad did
when he worked at the maple factory.
[JUGHEAD] Once again, there was
something rotten in the town of Riverdale.
And if I was going to get
real answers this time,
I'd have to hunt them down myself.
Luckily, I knew for a fact
that the town coroner, Dr. Curdle,
was a fan of Pep's horror comics,
which were hard to come by now
unless you had
an inside connection like me.
Oh, yes.
These are quite marvelous, Mr. Jones.
Worthy of a quid pro quo.
Keen-o. So clue me in on what you know
about that mysterious melting man.
How did he end up looking that way?
He was suffering
from acute radiation poisoning.
[WHISTLES]
Jeepers. Nuclear or atomic?
And where would he get
radiation poisoning?
I couldn't say. Unfortunately,
I didn't have much time with the body
before Mayor Blossom claimed it
and whisked it away.
The melting man, as you call him,
was an employee
of the mayor's maple factory,
is my understanding.
That stinks like a rotten fish.
Ethel, are you ready to walk to school?
Betty, are you sure you don't want
your mom to drive you and Ethel to school?
Under no circumstances.
Ethel, come on. We're gonna be late.
[ALICE] Don't worry, Hal.
One day, it'll be raining cats and dogs,
and she'll finally let me give her a ride.
Mm, no, I won't.
Ethel, Veronica, and I signed up
for driver's education at school,
so pretty soon
I'll be driving myself wherever I want.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Great news from Coach Parsley
over at Camp Evans.
You are in, Reggie.
- No fooling, coach?
- In where?
Only the best summer basketball camp
for high schoolers in the country.
That's wonderful news.
Congratulations, Reggie.
What about you, Bill Shakespeare?
What are your plans?
No summer camp for poetry, is there?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
There will be plenty
for Archie to do in town, Frank.
He can pick up his old job at Pop's
or help me down at the dress shop.
Ah.
You hear that?
You can work at your mom's dress shop.
[FRANK CHUCKLES]
I'll bet you wish
you didn't quit the team now.
Let's motor, sis.
Train's leaving with or without you.
[MILITARY BEAT PLAYING]
And who, pray tell, was that?
- You enlisting, Dad?
- Don't be asinine, the both of you.
That was General Taylor from Washington.
He was delivering unto me, uh...
Well, a gift.
Come into my study.
I want you to see it.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What godforsaken creature is that?
This is Moloch, Cheryl.
An ancient pagan deity
who can only be appeased
through child sacrifice.
You should keep Moloch in mind,
should you be inclined
to give me any more grief.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
[JUGHEAD] Ethel.
I don't mean to open old wounds,
but that melting man
outside the Babylonium...
What about him?
You told Ben that he was wearing
the same uniform that your father did
at the Blossom maple factory.
I was just wondering
what your father did there.
He was a janitor. Why?
Did he ever get sick?
My mom sometimes said
that he started drinking
to help deal with the chronic pain
he felt in his stomach and his joints.
And also because he was losing his hair.
Golly.
But why are you asking me about this?
I can't say for certain,
but the fact that your father
and the melting man,
and Mr. Rayberry,
now that I think about it,
all worked at the Blossom maple factory
and all bit the linoleum in,
shall we say, bizarre circumstances...
I don't think that's a coincidence.
The Blossoms are hiding something,
and I'm going to find out what,
so I can get us, you, me, Mrs. Rayberry...
some closure.
What?
What is it?
Jughead, I appreciate what you're doing,
but I'm trying to move on with my life.
I'm applying for my driver's license.
I got my car that I won
as Miss Riverdale Teen Queen.
I'm going steady with Ben. Hi.
You're going steady with our Ben?
Ben Button?
In any case, I'm trying to put the past
where it belongs. Behind me.
Class, finish taking your seats.
Mayor Blossom and Principal Featherhead
asked me to show you
this informational film
about what to do in the event
of an atomic bomb detonating in Riverdale.
[NARRATOR ON-SCREEN]
Now we must be ready for a new danger,
the atomic bomb.
You will know when it comes.
There is a bright flash.
Brighter than the sun.
If you are not ready,
it could hurt you in different ways.
It could knock you down hard
or throw you against a tree or a wall.
It is such a big explosion
it can smash in buildings
and knock signboards over
and break windows all over town.
[ARCHIE] Jeepers, that atomic-bomb movie
really gave me the zorros.
It should have. That dumb movie
was telling us to duck and cover,
as if flying glass
is going to be the biggest of our worries.
In truth, most of us wouldn't
likely survive an atomic explosion.
What are you playing at, Jug?
Have any of you seen
the newsreels from Japan?
If a bomb drops on or near Riverdale,
all of us are vaporized
in less than a nanosecond.
Not to mention the radiation
we'd all be exposed to
even if we manage to survive
the initial detonation.
Well, I know what I'd do
if a bomb were heading our way.
I'd sequester myself
in The Pembrooke's sub-sub-basement.
It's like a little underground city
down there.
You'd be invited, Juggykins.
[GROANS]
I would seek shelter
in the abandoned Blossom mines.
They've stood strong
since before the Revolutionary War.
Isn't it dark and cold
down in those mines?
Hmm. Why, yes, Tony, it is.
I would have to find some way
to stay cozy and warm.
[REGGIE] I'd head to Duck Creek.
We've got a well so deep
no bomb or radiation could reach it.
Well, why stop at Duck Creek?
If we hear these sirens,
I'm hopping in my hot rod,
I'm grabbing my mom,
and I'm heading out West.
There's no way these radiation clouds
are going to cross the Rockies.
Out West sounds nice.
Sure does.
You can't outrun an atomic bomb, Archie.
No matter how fast your hot rod is.
Guys, I read somewhere
that if you are inside of a refrigerator
when the big one hits, you're safe.
But then you're inside a refrigerator.
Yeah. What would you do
about food and water?
I'd be in a refrigerator.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
I'm not holing up anywhere.
Come on, guys,
we can't let this bomb get us down.
In Nevada, where the U.S.
does most of its atomic testing,
people have bomb shelters
in case something goes wrong.
That's what it'd take to be truly safe.
A lead-lined underground bunker.
[BETTY] If Russia wanted to bomb us,
wouldn't they target larger cities
like Los Angeles or New York?
People who live in the sticks, like us,
we don't actually have to worry
about nuclear attacks, do we?
Mm. I wouldn't bet the farm on it.
An atomic bomb could drop anywhere,
even here in Riverdale.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
It says,
"Make rope and wrap around the rope."
Whatever that means.
[ARCHIE] Say, what are you fellas up to?
Trying to tie a sailor's knot
and failing miserably.
A sailor's knot? I can show you how.
Don't you remember
your Adventure Scouts training?
The rabbit goes out the hole,
around the tree,
back through the hole again.
You should get a nice loop.
What are you practicing this for?
You do realize, if the bomb hits,
there's not much
a sailor's knot can do for you.
Kevin and I are considering
joining the Merchant Marines.
Merchant Marines?
Wow, what is that,
part of the Navy or something?
No, it's a civilian job.
They pay you to work on a cargo ship
and travel around the world.
Archie, you might be keen on this. A lot
of great writers were Merchant Marines.
A lot of beats served too.
Ginsberg and Kerouac
both did time on the Seven Seas.
"Adventure awaits you on the open water."
I wouldn't hate
getting away from my uncle.
And seeing the world, having adventures?
That would enrich my writing.
That sounds super swell to me.
- And I do love tying knots.
- There's a recruiter coming tomorrow.
You can ask him questions
and hear what he has to say.
Ladies, you are the drivers of tomorrow.
As such, it is important to learn
to be alert, confident,
conscientious motor-vehicle operators.
- Stop sign.
- [STUDENT GASPS]
Driving is not a right,
as many young men believe.
It is a privilege and a responsibility.
Upcoming left turn.
That's wonderful.
Let's bring our cars into "park."
And shake it out.
Very good. Excellent.
Now, your homework for tonight is to rest.
Because tomorrow
your true test of skills begins.
We will be getting
into a real working automobile...
to practice parallel parking.
[STUDENTS MURMURING]
[GIRL] That's too bad.
How was school today?
Anything interesting happen?
We watched a movie
that taught us what to do
if the Russians drop a bomb on us.
I'm thinking of joining
the Merchant Marines.
Well, as long as
you finish high school first.
When that day comes,
I hope you'll still consider college.
Wait a minute, Mary.
Merchant Marines sounds
like a solid, sensible idea.
Much better than going to some college
to pursue poetry.
The Merchant Marines would be a way
for me to pursue my poetry.
A lot of beats would join to learn more
about themselves or the world,
then to write about it.
You'd know that
if you ever cracked open a book.
- What was that?
- No one is joining anything tonight.
So can we please
just finish our supper in peace?
[JUGHEAD] Well, Dilton,
what's the occasion?
[DILTON] I...
I just came by because...
after the melting man
and that movie my dad showed in class,
I know you're unsettled.
Sue me.
I don't want to die in an atomic attack.
Yeah.
Except you don't have to worry, Jughead.
You're one of my best pals,
my comic-book buddy.
If anything bad were to actually happen,
I'd take care of you. You'd be safe.
Well, that's swell of you to say, Dilton.
But how would I be safe?
It's... It would probably be easier
if I just showed you.
[METAL GROANING]
Holy crap-ola, Dilton.
How does your family have a bunker?
My dad built it.
He says we're deep enough
to survive an atomic blast.
And any radiation after the blast.
Am I missing something?
Does your dad think
that Riverdale could be a target?
Dilton?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
What does your dad know that we don't?
Nothing for certain.
But about a year
before Ethel's folks were killed,
her dad showed up to our house.
With this.
Mr. Muggs wanted to see
if it was worth anything.
He figured since my dad
was a science teacher, he'd know.
- What is it?
- Palladium.
Mr. Muggs said he swiped it from work.
- The maple factory?
- I guess so.
He said Clifford Blossom
was sitting on a pile of it,
and doing something with it.
That's when my dad
started building this bunker.
Because Clifford Blossom was
or is doing something with palladium?
A secret something?
Worth killing for?
In its inert state,
palladium is basically harmless.
But in its purest state,
concentrated and compressed,
some scientists speculate
it could be more volatile than plutonium
and, if detonated,
more destructive than a hydrogen bomb.
This is starting to ring a bell for me.
[JUGHEAD] Not just a bell, in fact,
a four-alarm siren.
I'd recently had my nose in a story
about a palladium bomb
destroying a small town
by my former deceased mentor,
Brad Rayberry,
who, at one point,
worked at the Blossom factory.
Had he seen or heard something there
about palladium
that had inspired his story?
[SIREN WAILING]
That's the emergency siren!
As we were warned!
This is it! This is the big one!
[STUDENTS SCREAMING]
Jughead, duck and cover!
Jughead! Jughead, what are you doing?
Get under your desk! No!
Jughead! Get away from the...
[SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
Damn you and your fearmongering,
Jughead Jones.
[CLIFFORD IN RUSSIAN]
Everything is in readiness.
Project Moloch is almost complete.
[PENELOPE IN RUSSIAN]
It's unfortunate what happened to that man
who escaped from the infirmary.
[CLIFFORD] Yes, but we knew
there might be casualties. Sacrifices.
And his family will be taken care of...
[PENELOPE] Think of how it will be
when we return to the Motherland.
Triumphant. As heroes.
Our leaders will be pleased.
They promised me an appointment
in your government, don't forget...
[FLOOR CREAKS]
[GASPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
As a Merchant Marine,
you'll travel the globe
on the world's
most technologically advanced ships.
You'll work and train alongside this
country's best and brightest young men,
all eager to experience life
to the fullest.
Yes, son?
Would we have time
to explore places we'd be visiting?
Really get to soak them up?
This isn't a pleasure cruise.
Something you should all know,
no one is guaranteed a spot.
Cheryl. Hi-ho.
Has anything strange
been happening at your house?
Mayhaps. Why do you care?
I heard you mention those abandoned mines.
I wonder if they're close
to your family's maple factory.
The factory is practically
right on top of them, yes.
Okay. Look, Cheryl,
this is going to sound like gobbledygook,
but I believe
your father is up to no good.
I think he is involved
in the Milkman murders,
not to mention the melting man.
And I think that those mines
are actually palladium mines
and they're not abandoned.
There's no love lost
between my father and I.
I'm certain if he had the chance,
he would sacrifice me
to a pagan god named Moloch.
But to your point, he has been meeting
with an Army general
in his study recently,
and I did overhear him
and my mother last night
speaking what I believe was Russian.
Holy moly. Do you think
you can get in there and play gumshoe?
Just poke around, snoop,
see if you find anything incriminating?
[ENGINE STARTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[STUDENTS CHEERING]
[GIRL] Great job!
I'm very pleased to announce that
since all of you passed both the written
and practical portions
of your driver's education exam,
we'll all be taking a field trip to
the Riverdale Department of Motor Vehicles
at the end of the week.
But, girls, this is very important.
To obtain your legal license, you must
bring a copy of your birth certificate.
The DMV needs to make sure
none of you are Russian spies.
[STUDENTS CHUCKLE]
I was wondering why the light was on.
Let me guess.
This is for the Merchant Marines.
The recruiter said
everyone rows at least an hour a day
when they're out at sea to stay in shape.
So I'm just getting a head start.
Listen, about that.
Can we talk man to man for a minute?
I know I'm not your father,
but just so you know,
I want what's best for you,
just as he would.
What is that?
Your old man's dog tags.
He'd want you to have them.
Like he'd want you
to quit this Merchant Marines business.
Join the Army. Enlist. Just like he did.
You didn't know?
Your father wasn't drafted.
He volunteered for the Army.
He knew what being a real man
and a good American meant.
He believed there was no greater duty
than serving this country
and fighting for democracy and freedom.
You wanna be like your father, don't you?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah. I try to be like him every day.
Well, then drop this poetry nonsense
and join the Army.
Become the kind of man he'd be proud of.
The man I know is inside you,
fighting to get out.
And the best part about joining the Army?
You don't have to wait until graduation.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's see what you're hiding, Daddy.
A draft?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Good morning, honey. One waffle or two?
Uh...
Are those your dad's...?
Dog tags? Yeah.
- Uncle Frank gave them to me.
- Why would he have done that?
Well, I think I know, but maybe you
should sit down so we can talk about it.
Betty, can we talk for a second?
Sure.
Are things not hunky dory?
No, there's a problem.
Um, I don't have my birth certificate.
It's at my house.
- Where my parents...
- Don't worry. I'll grab it for you.
- Really, Betty?
- Sure. Yeah.
I'll book it there
before we go to the DMV.
You have any idea
where your birth certificate would be?
My mom had a crafting desk
where she kept important papers.
I bet you it's in there.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
- Did you find something?
- Did I ever.
- You were right.
- About what part?
Everything.
Snooping through Daddy's study,
I stumbled upon a secret panel
and found a bunch of these.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
- And matching uniforms to boot.
- Holy Toledo.
The Milkman must have been
working for your father,
doing his bidding.
- Are you in danger?
- No more than usual.
I also went to the mines.
You were right about those too.
They are palladium mines.
Very much not abandoned.
Meet me on the Thornhill grounds tonight
and bring your camera,
and pray an atomic disaster
doesn't befall us all before then.
What...? What...?
What was my dad paying the Muggses for?
So, Frank, Archie told me about
your little talk in the garage last night.
[FRANK] Did he, now?
What did he say?
A few things, but it sounded to me
like you used his father,
your brother, to try to manipulate my son
into joining the Army.
How dare you?
Especially when you yourself never served.
The Army is the best place for him, Mary.
It'll set him straight.
Let's not mince words.
We all know what this is really about.
It's you not wanting Archie
to write poetry.
He's on the road to ruin. He's...
- Well, he's lost.
- [MARY] He's not lost.
He's 17.
He's got his whole life ahead of him.
Whether that's joining
the Merchant Marines or the Army
or going to college to study literature
and poetry after he finishes high school.
But he'll be the one who decides his path,
not his bullying uncle.
[MARY SIGHS]
I can't have you here anymore.
It's time for you to move out.
- You called me here to help.
- Now she's telling you to hit the road.
Who's gonna be the man of the house?
- I am.
- Not that I need one.
I am the woman of this house, after all.
I'm the one who pays the mortgage.
I suppose I could shack up
with Tom Keller.
I hear he's been handed
marching orders recently.
Wonderful. That works out for everyone.
Betty. How you doing, kiddo?
Why were you two
writing checks once a month,
year after year, to the Muggses?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Because, Betty,
Mrs. Muggs was our housekeeper.
Those must have been payments for,
you know, services.
That doesn't make any sense.
Some checks are from two years ago.
If Mrs. Muggs were ever our housekeeper,
she hadn't been
for as long as I can remember.
Oh, and what's the story
behind this photo?
Who's that baby?
Because it's not me. And it's not Polly.
That's Ethel.
Why did the Muggses have a photo
of you holding Ethel as a baby?
Because the Muggses asked
if I would be Ethel's godfather,
and I agreed.
So why I haven't heard about this?
Why hasn't anyone?
[SPLUTTERS]
- I don't know. I...
- [ALICE] Stop, Hal.
Just stop.
It's over. Can't you see that?
You're Ethel's father, aren't you?
Why don't you go for a walk, dear? Hmm?
So that Betty and I
can have a little chat.
Mildred Muggs did clean our house
before you were born. That part is true.
And at some point, she and your father
started having an affair.
And I suspected it for a long time,
but it was confirmed when...
Mrs. Muggs got pregnant.
Your father admitted everything.
He was crying, apologizing.
He didn't know what to do.
I mean, if any whiff
of the scandal got out,
the consequences for the station,
for us, for our family...
So you stayed with him.
I had no other choice.
Yes, I stayed, but I handled it.
I made a deal with the Muggses
that if they raise the baby as their own
and keep our secret,
that we would financially support
the child until she turned 16.
Support...
Ethel, my sister.
Your half sister.
This is why you adopted Ethel.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
This is why you've been the way
that you've been with me...
wanting Kevin to pin me over Archie.
Why you were scared of me
reading Dr. Kingsley's book.
You were afraid of something
like what happened to you happening to me.
I just wanted
to give you a good, happy life.
Unburdened.
Safe, free of shame.
You've been obsessed
with presenting as the perfect family,
when all along...
this is what's been wrong, this...
secret, this shame.
Not what I've been doing.
Or what Polly did.
It was Dad's affair...
and your decision to stay with him
and pretend that everything was fine.
And for all my efforts...
I failed you.
[ALICE WEEPING]
As a mother, I failed you, and I'm sorry.
You didn't.
You did the best that you could.
You did what you thought was right.
But now...
we need to get Dad back here...
and we need to tell Ethel everything.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TV ANNOUNCER] Oh, Mija!
Starring Hiram Lodge...
If what you say is here is really here...
It is. You will see for yourself.
Wouldn't there be more guards?
I imagine my father
is trying to avoid undue attention.
That's a good point.
[JUGHEAD] And as Cheryl and I
were on the cusp
of uncovering one explosive truth,
Ethel was experiencing
emotional shock waves
after learning the truth about her life.
It explains things.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Why my parents were so sad,
why they fought all the time...
why I always felt...
like it was somehow my fault.
Oh. It was never your fault, Ethel.
Ethel...
Mrs. Cooper and I were discussing, and...
well, we'd like to...
We'd like to make things right
and formally adopt you,
show you that we could be a true family.
I appreciate that, Mr. and Mrs. Cooper.
It's kind of you to offer.
I don't think that's what I want.
What do you want?
To be happy.
To move on with my life.
To start over.
You enjoy my room
and don't get into too much trouble.
I won't.
And I'll see you at practice, coach.
Mary. I don't know how I'm gonna survive
without your chicken pot pie.
Oh, come on, Frank.
You know you'll always be welcome
at Sunday dinner.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, in that case, I will see you Sunday.
You. So you're the man of the house now.
I hope you're up for the task.
And, uh... I hope
you don't hold anything against me.
Of course not, Uncle Frank.
But just to be clear, writing poetry
doesn't make you any less of a man.
Some of the most beautiful poems
were written by soldiers in trenches
covered in mud
and the blood of their brothers.
Well, maybe that's my path.
Well, maybe not.
I guess we'll have to wait and see.
Mm-hm.
We have to show these photos
to Sheriff Keller.
Maybe.
Maybe not. For all we know,
Sheriff Keller is in on it.
Kevin's father? No.
He's just a dimwitted small-town sheriff
that's in over his head.
Still, now that we have proof,
it's better to be careful.
Veronica has FBI contacts
from when they investigated her father.
I'll see if she can give me
the names of those agents.
Good thinking, Sherlock Jones.
By the way, are you and Veronica
officially an item now?
- Shucks, I don't know.
- Talk about being in over your crown.
I'm holding my own.
Mm-hm.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
I'll get it.
Gentlemen. You're right on time.
They're having breakfast in Grand Hall.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Clifford Marion Blossom,
Penelope Pavlina Novikov Blossom,
you're under arrest
for treason, conspiracy,
and advocating for the violent overthrow
of the American government.
The FBI is shutting down
your Project Moloch.
[HANDCUFFS CLICK]
You did a bad thing, Daddy.
[JUGHEAD] Over the coming days, the world
would learn about the American capitalist
seduced by the Soviet sleeper agent.
Operation: Project Moloch
was to have been the next leg
of the arms race.
From the A-bomb
to the H-bomb to the P-bomb,
the palladium bomb.
The U.S. believed Clifford Blossom
was developing it for them,
when, in fact, his plan had been
to develop the P-bomb in Riverdale,
then deliver it to Mother Russia.
The FBI and the U.S. Army were credited
with foiling the plot against America,
which was fine by me, as I was busy
putting the rest of the pieces together.
Mr. Rayberry
must have glimpsed just enough
during his job at the Blossom factory
to grow concerned.
He warned us, as he always did,
with his brilliant, terrifying stories.
He might have continued
flying under the radar,
but then he started agitating
at Riverdale High,
invoking the Supreme Court,
spooking the powers that be,
prompting Mayor Blossom
to have his hitman,
aka the Milkman, kill him.
Ethel's folks
also paid the ultimate price.
Mr. Muggs had discovered that the Blossoms
were sitting on a stockpile of palladium.
That made him a threat,
one that needed to be eliminated.
Ethel didn't care so much
about the details,
but now that she knew the complete truth
of her life, she was ready, she said,
to finally start to hope again
for a better tomorrow.
Hey, Lovebug, you ready to peel out?
["WALKIN' YOU HOME" PLAYING ON JUKEBOX]
♪ The clock is smilin'
Like a long-lost friend ♪
♪ Another minute and... ♪
[DOOR OPENS, BELL JINGLES]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[ALICE] Are you sure about this, Ethel?
Moving to Hollywood?
Don't you worry, Mrs. Cooper.
I called ahead to my friend Peter Roth.
He saw some of Ethel's artwork
and got her a job as a storyboard artist.
And I've arranged for Ethel
to live with one of my girlfriends
at the most glamorous of buildings,
the El Royale.
Thanks again, Veronica.
My pleasure.
Give them hell, Ethel.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't forget to send us your address
so I can come visit you.
[ETHEL] I won't forget.
Thank you for everything, Betty.
Of course.
I'll miss you.
You always were the best partner in crime.
Thanks, Jughead.
Don't be too sad.
- We'll always have Pep Comics.
- Hopefully. We'll see.
You are going to be just fine.
I truly feel that.
I hope so, Mrs. Cooper.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[JUGHEAD] Ethel was the first of us to go.
To leave Riverdale behind.
There would be others soon.
All of the pieces were falling into place.
Project Moloch had failed,
but it was just about time
to find out if our town would be avoiding
an even greater cataclysm.
["NOTHING CAN STOP ME NOW!"
PLAYING ON STEREO]
[VOLUME INCREASES]
♪ Nothing can stop me ♪
♪ Now! ♪
[CHALK SCRATCHING]
[BELL JINGLES]