["Ain't That a Shame" playing]
[Jughead] Grief is a terrible thing.
When you've suffered a loss, as I had,
the death of my mentor
and literary idol, Brad Rayberry,
time falls into a slow, sad rhythm,
- and a moment feels like an eternity.
- [music slows, distorts, then stops]
Even as the rest of the world
continues to tick on.
[Werthers]
You will no longer be in the River Vixens.
Your mother and I believe it's
too sexualized an environment for you.
High school, in general,
is a highly sexualized environment,
wouldn't you say?
Is that how you see it?
A bunch of horny teenagers
trapped together like sardines
for hours upon hours...
How do you see it?
As an academic institution
meant to provide a safe environment
where students
can challenge themselves intellectually
without being morally
and physically compromised.
Oh, well, you obviously
haven't spent a lot of time in gym class.
You are here, Betty,
because you stripped
in front of your window
for your next-door
neighbor's pleasurement.
And then you flashed your underpants
on live television.
In short, you seem unhealthily
obsessed with sexuality.
The words that come to mind
are "nymphomaniac,"
"exhibitionist," "sexual compulsive."
What exactly do you want
to talk to me about, Dr. Werthers?
Well, given your recent behavior,
I'm curious,
what is your first sexual memory?
[buzzes]
I'm not sure that I remember.
In that case, how often, Betty,
would you say that you think about sex?
["Lollipop" playing]
♪ Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli
Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli, lollipop ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli
Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli, lollipop ♪
♪ Call my baby "lollipop"
Tell you why ♪
♪ His kiss is sweeter than an apple pie ♪
♪ And when he does
His shaky rockin' dance ♪
♪ Man, I haven't got a chance ♪
♪ I call him, lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli
Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli, lollipop ♪
♪ Sweeter than candy on a stick ♪
♪ Huckleberry, cherry or lime ♪
♪ If you had a choice, he'd be your pick ♪
♪ But lollipop is mine ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli
Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lolli, lolli, lollipop ♪
[Werthers] Betty? Betty.
How often do you think about sex?
I would say an average amount.
I need a number, Betty.
Well, according to Dr. Kingsley,
teenagers think about sex
every seven seconds.
That number is for teenage boys.
There is a very different barometer
for teenage girls.
Well, in that case, I would say
I think about sex all the time.
- What did you just write down?
- Never mind that.
Why do you think
you think about sex all the time?
I'm curious about how it feels.
I don't think that waiting until
I'm married to have sex makes sense.
- What about having sex for pleasure?
- Betty, sex is for married people.
So they can start families.
So then, what about the girlie magazines
that my dad keeps hidden
in his sock drawer?
Uh, I'm sorry?
Well, I remember last year,
we were going to church,
my dad asked me
to fetch him his cufflinks.
And when I went to look for them
in his sock drawer,
I found all of these...
girlie magazines.
Your father is not in therapy. You are.
- Well, maybe he should be.
- He's a grown man.
- I'm a child psychiatrist.
- I'm not a child, either.
Though actually I do think
that our conversations
are starting to
make me see things more clearly.
In what particular way?
Well, I'm just now realizing that...
I don't think I want to get married.
At least, not any time soon. Maybe never.
I want to make an impact on the world,
instead of...
or in addition to, just having a family.
["Puppy Love" playing over record player]
♪ Puppy love... ♪
[knock on door]
Knock, knock. Hi, sweetheart.
I got you something fun.
- [Betty] What are those for?
- [Alice] I was in the grocery store,
and I just thought the pictures
were so pretty,
I had to get you a few of them.
- Mom, I'm not even dating anyone.
- Oh, it doesn't matter.
A girl can daydream about her wedding,
can't she?
- Why are you bringing this up right now?
- Oh, Elizabeth.
I just know.
When I see you in that white dress,
standing at that altar...
it's gonna be the happiest day of my life.
Tickets.
Get your tickets to the Babylonium's
James Dean double feature.
["That's Alright" playing]
What's all this about James Dean?
As president of his fan club,
I, along with my fellow Deanizens,
have been waiting for East of Eden
to reach our little hamlet.
You're just in luck,
because we have in our possession
a print of East of Eden.
And why, pray tell,
should I go to the Babylonium,
when the screen at the Orpheum
in nearby Greendale is much larger?
As befits the stature
of my beloved Jimmy Dean.
Is the Orpheum giving you
and your "Deanizens" free passes?
On the condition that you spread
the good word about the Babylonium?
We want a robust crowd
to honor Jimmy's memory.
On the sacred ground
of James Dean's grave,
I will deliver my fan club,
the Vixens, and the Bulldogs.
Excellent.
But don't worry about the Bulldogs,
I'm extending that invitation myself.
Personally.
Batten down the hatches, boys,
because the Babylonium
is going to do boffo business
this weekend. I can feel it.
But why are we giving out
tickets for free?
I'll let you in on the dirty secret
about the movie theater business, Kevin.
We make most of our money
from popcorn and soda sales.
And, uh, what was all that
about inviting the Bulldogs?
They're our hometown heroes.
Of course they have to be there.
All the Bulldogs,
or just one in particular?
[clears throat]
[Bulldogs shouting]
Oh! Check it out, Bulldogs.
If it isn't Miss Twinkletown herself.
It's "Tinseltown."
As a fan of the Bulldogs,
I wanted to personally
offer you free passes
to our James Dean double feature
at the Babylonium.
Comped tickets are in your lockers.
And you, Reginald?
Shall I save you a seat beside me?
I mean, surely you know what Jimmy Dean
used to do in high school, I hope?
What's that?
He was a basketball star, Reggie.
Just like you.
["It Happened" playing]
♪ It happened... ♪
[chattering]
Here you are.
- That'll be 25 cents.
- Okay.
Or you could treat me to a milkshake
after the show.
- You just keep on shooting, don't you?
- You keep passing me the ball.
Okay, sure, let's do it.
Take it.
- Meet you back here?
- All right.
Now get in there
before you miss the coming attractions.
Veronica.
Kevin, guess who's got a date
with Reggie Mantle tonight after the show?
That's swell, but Clay's got a situation
in the projection booth.
I don't know what happened,
but the print we received from the studio,
we can't play it.
What? Why?
It's been overexposed.
- How many reels are like this?
- That's the thing, all of them.
We've got a sold-out house.
[chattering]
Welcome to the Babylonium.
[cheering]
We're so excited to have you all here.
So quit bashing our ears
and play the damn movie.
[audience] Yeah!
[boy] Yeah!
Due to some unforeseen
technical difficulties,
I regret to inform you
we are unable to screen
our James Dean double feature tonight.
I knew it.
[booing]
[Veronica] However...
However, we are working on the problem
and are rescheduling said double feature.
That's all very well and good,
but we, the proud members
of the James Dean Fan Club,
Riverdale Chapter, demand a refund.
Immediately.
[all chanting] Refund! Refund! Refund!
Refund?
You all got free passes.
Including you, Cheryl.
True, but we did spend
all this money on popcorn and soda
to consume during the double feature,
which is no longer happening.
[audience clamoring]
I would be more than happy to provide
each and every one of you
with a voucher
for any snack of your choosing.
We don't want your stupid vouchers,
we want our money back.
- [all] Yeah!
- What a fake-out!
It's like Jimmy Dean died all over again!
All right. All right.
All right. Calm down.
Calm down. You can present your receipts
at the concession stands
for a full refund.
Yeah, right!
Hey!
Reggie.
I'm so sorry.
As much as I'd be delighted
to split a milkshake with you...
- You've got a business to take care of.
- I do.
The Babylonium's hanging on
by the most gossamer of threads.
I figured as much.
I'd happily take a rain check.
Yeah? Sure.
Yeah, just let me know
when's a good time for you.
Okay.
I've never heard
of such a thing, Mr. Roth.
A venerated studio like yours
sending out unplayable prints
of a major release like East of Eden?
[Roth] I'm as baffled as you, Miss Lodge.
At any rate, please accept
our deepest apologies for this mishap.
I'll accept your apology,
but what I really want
is a pristine copy of East of Eden.
And what I want is audiences
in Riverdale to see this picture.
I do. It's a wonderful picture.
But I'm afraid
that there are no more available prints.
You sent me a defective product.
How is this my problem?
Miss Lodge...
Veronica. May I call you Veronica?
You are the theater owner.
It's always your problem.
You'd know that if you weren't so green.
"Green"? Let me assure you...
I'm so sorry, but I need to let you go.
I'm having lunch at the Polo Lounge
with Monty Clift,
but good luck to you.
How does a major studio run out of prints
of their biggest release of the year?
I don't know.
But luckily,
they're not the only studio in town.
[swing music playing]
It's time to work the phones, boys.
- [phone rings]
- I have Pasadena Pictures.
Nicky. Veronica Lodge.
No, Nicky. I'm in exhibition these days.
The Babylonium in Riverdale.
Listen, my customers simply
don't have time for that Steinbeck yawner.
I need something exciting,
something fresh.
Do you have any available prints
of To Catch a Thief?
I'm hearing great things
about Hitchcock's latest.
Word around town
is that Oklahoma! is a masterpiece.
What about this Night of the Hunter
I keep reading about?
- It's RKO.
- [man 1] Be that as it may, Miss Lodge.
We've already booked
our picture at the Orpheum.
Unfortunately, Riverdale isn't a market
we're interested in cultivating.
Silver Shield Studios.
[man 2] Sorry, but we're being particular
about how we're
distributing musicals this year.
Superior.
[man 3] Furthermore, all of our
current releases demand larger theaters.
Please, don't call us again.
But, sir, you used to send us
your movies every week. What changed?
[man 4] I don't do business with underage,
would-be impresarios.
Especially not when I'm trying to get
into business with their parents.
But good luck to you, Miss Lodge.
You'll need it.
[sighs] Well, there you have it, boys.
I and the Babylonium have been blacklisted
by every major studio in Hollywood.
Why, though?
[sighs]
If I had to hazard a guess, my parents.
I've been waiting for this since
I bought the theater out from under them.
My last call confirmed it, but honestly,
I suspected sabotage
from the moment we got that bad print.
What do your parents want?
To see everyone but themselves fail,
including their own daughter.
I'm sure they want
the Babylonium to shutter
so they can buy it from me at a discount
and turn it into a parking lot.
I have an idea.
So far, we've only tried
the major studios.
But there are a lot of smaller,
independent places out there.
They're scrappy,
and they don't play by the same rules.
Their movies don't have big stars
or budgets or prestige.
In other words, they're B movies,
but they're still movies.
Good idea, Clay.
Boys, if we're going down,
we're going down fighting.
Get me...
one of those smaller studios.
Tell me, Betty,
do you ever remember your dreams?
Sometimes.
Are your dreams sexual?
Well, then, tell me, Betty.
What is your most vivid
or frequent sexual dream?
[Betty] I guess it's the one
where I'm in biology class.
Only...
I'm the teacher,
tutoring one of my students.
[Werthers] Which student?
[Betty] It varies.
["Captured" playing]
♪ Captured in a moonlight that blinds me ♪
♪ And a magic that binds me
In a world... ♪
[Werthers] Yes, but most often?
[Betty] It's Archie.
[Werthers] And what occurs in this dream?
♪ A music strange to me ♪
♪ Beats its thunder, through and through ♪
♪ He's in love ♪
♪ This wondrous change in me ♪
♪ This enchanted dream come true ♪
♪ Captured
In this spell I'm enraptured... ♪
[Betty] And that's the part of the dream
where I realize...
♪ By the soul I've been captured... ♪
everyone's watching.
♪ By the magic of you ♪
This dream, and others like it,
do you ever share them with other people?
No, never. Just my diary.
What are you always writing
in that notepad of yours?
Notes, observations, thoughts to myself.
Kind of like a diary.
Tell me, Betty.
Where do you think this urge comes from?
The urge to be seen
in such a sexualized way?
It must titillate you,
make it more exciting for you.
I don't think it's just about
being seen sexually.
I think it might be more
about being seen... period.
In what respect?
Being seen.
As a person...
with autonomy.
And desire.
And self-determination.
Go on.
I'm wondering if my interest
in understanding sex
is really more about
understanding myself...
who I am.
I mean, what better way to understand
a person than to understand their desires?
Including your own.
- It'll just be a few minutes.
- Thanks, Pop.
[swing music playing over speakers]
Hey, Holden Caulfield.
Have you ever heard of a movie
called The Crawling Eye?
Yeah. Came out a couple of years ago.
Story was kind of a mess,
but the monster was cool.
I loved it.
Mr. Rayberry loved it too.
Why do you ask?
Because after calling every minor
independent studio in La-La Land,
it's the only movie I can get
to play at the Babylonium.
Why don't you just do
what William Castle did?
That name dimly rings a bell.
He's a producer, director.
His movies are just okay,
but they all came with a kind of gimmick.
Like for The Tingler, filmed in Percepto!,
he put buzzers under the audience seats,
and when the monster, The Tingler,
appeared on screen,
he would buzz the people
and give them an electric shock.
That sounds dangerous.
Just a mild shock, but it worked.
People went nuts for The Tingler.
I get it.
Sell the gimmick, not the movie.
I can do that.
[Alice] Oh, good. She's home.
Hello, dear. I'm so glad you're home.
What's going on?
You remember Reverend Lowe
from Riverdale First
Reformed Presbyterian Church.
My, how you've grown
since the children's choir, Elizabeth.
He's going to hear your confession.
And perform an exorcism,
if need be, right?
[Alice chuckling]
Conf... Uh, confession?
Why would I need to confess?
What are you doing with my diaries?
Did you read them?
Elizabeth, I had to.
They were prescribed to me.
- By Dr. Werthers?
- I would rather not say.
You... You broke into my room
and stole my diaries
because my psychiatrist told you to?
Good grief, Mother.
I suspected you and Dr. Psycho
were talking about me.
But breaking and entering?
If you are so hot to trot
to talk with Dr. Werthers,
why don't you come to therapy with me?
It might help you.
I am an adult woman. I don't need therapy.
[scoffs]
Elizabeth? Elizabeth.
Breaking and entering.
What do you write down
in that notepad of yours?
Breaking and entering.
Okay, Dr. Werthers.
Let's see
what you've been writing about me.
Come on, this always works
in the Tracy True books.
Gosh, you're an even bigger bookworm
than I am.
Pop says you've been glued
to this booth for two days,
getting ink on your nose.
Uh, yeah, you might say
I'm spending time with a friend
before saying goodbye.
Oh. Well, sorry to interrupt,
but have you heard of this book Lolita?
Holy moly.
Where did you get this?
I borrowed it from a friend.
What can you tell me about it?
Well, it's Nabokov's latest novel.
It's pretty salacious
according to The Paris Review.
It's about a relationship
between a professor named Humbert Humbert
and a young girl named Dolores Haze.
- How young?
- Twelve.
Twelve?
So it's a book for perverts?
Well, passing moral judgment
on a work of art is a slippery slope.
Have you read it yet?
That's what I'm about to go do.
Thank you, Jughead.
- Hey, Pop, can I get another one, please?
- Coming right up.
[ominous music playing]
[announcer on-screen] No one is safe
from its spell of destruction.
The cold, hypnotic stare
striking fear into the hearts of all,
creating a frenzied nightmare
for those who behold it.
And that, ladies and germs,
is the terrifying, titillating
new feature film The Crawling Eye,
playing at the Babylonium, one week only.
Not that I care to see such dreck,
but didn't that movie
come out a few years ago?
Perhaps, but this is a re-release
in stunning 4D.
Mm, don't you mean 3D?
Oh, no. 3D is so 1952.
This is 4D, Cheryl.
A new fourth dimension of terror.
Time is the fourth dimension.
Do you mean time?
Shut up, Dilton.
4D is a novel, visceral experience,
unlike anything you've ever encountered
at the movies before, guaranteed.
My associates are handing out
little novelty reminders,
which are redeemable at the candy counter
for buy-one-get-one-free Milk Buds.
Now, remember, boys,
after you completely cover your balls
with a layer of newspaper,
let them dry before applying the next one.
I'll handle the paint job
when I get back from casting.
["Shake Around" playing]
[speaking indistinctly]
Just the two strapping he-men
I've been looking for all my life.
Hope you can make it
to The Crawling Eye tonight.
Not as audience members,
mind you, but as performers.
As part of my revolutionary 4D experience.
Veronica, we're not actors.
What would we have to do?
- Yeah, what, exactly?
- Not much.
All told, it would probably be
about two minutes of work,
for which you'd be handsomely compensated,
of course.
♪ When you get a funny feeling
Like a rockin' and a reelin'
♪ Shake around ♪
Ah. Ms. Cooper.
You haven't forgotten about
our standing appointment, have you?
No, I didn't.
But I won't be attending
our session today.
Instead I have some very interesting
reading to finish tonight.
But don't worry, doctor,
I'm sure tomorrow
we will have plenty to discuss.
♪ You gotta move a little, baby ♪
♪ Then you kick around a little, baby ♪
♪ You gotta slow it down a little, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause when the record
Starts a-groovin'... ♪
Cheryl, so glad you could make it.
Before the movie, you may
wanna take out a life-insurance policy.
You know, in case you die of fright.
Pathetic.
Otherwise, we have a nurse on duty
should you merely faint.
I am extremely disappointed in you, Midge.
Now, let's see what this 4D
you've been ballyhooing is all about.
And believe me, if it disappoints,
I will be demanding a refund again.
[dramatic music playing on-screen]
[man 1] If that cloud starts to move
before I get back,
take the car up, understand?
- [man 2] What about you?
- [man 1] Do as you're told!
[whispering indistinctly]
[giggles]
[girl crying on-screen]
[film audio distorts]
[man 1] Steady.
Steady. To your right.
- Visual on.
- Ready.
Bombs away.
[all screaming]
["Flying Saucer Rock & Roll" playing]
♪ Well, the news of the saucer
Been a-flyin' around ♪
♪ I'm the one
Who ought to seen it over the ground ♪
♪ Come outta hidin'... ♪
[screams, then laughs]
♪ Little green men
Taught me how to do the bop ♪
♪ They were three-foot high
They hit a few bars ♪
♪ Brought a rock 'n' roll
All the way from Mars ♪
♪ Flyin' saucer rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ I couldn't understand
A thing they said ♪
♪ But the crazy beat
Was a-stoppin' me dead ♪
[all chanting] Go, eyes, go! Go, eyes, go!
You care
to explain this novel, Dr. Werthers,
which I found in your desk?
Breaking into my office,
stealing my property...
- So you admit it's yours?
- Of course it's mine.
By reading about Lolita's mind,
I was hoping
to better understand yours, Betty.
You're comparing me to Lolita?
Well, she, too,
is a sex-crazed young woman.
Dolores Haze is a 12-year-old girl.
And she is not sex-crazed,
she is being coerced against her will,
much like I am, doctor.
So let me tell you
what I learned from reading Lolita.
You are a kissing cousin
to Humbert Humbert, only creepier.
And it is completely inappropriate for you
to be asking me all of these questions
about my sexual fantasies and experiences
behind closed doors,
manipulating our conversation,
feverishly writing down
every word that I say,
doing God knows what
with that notebook of yours at night.
You think I'm obsessed with sex?
I think you're the one
who's obsessed with sex, doctor.
Dangerously so.
And I don't think
you're reading Lolita for research.
I think you're reading it for pleasure
and some sick gratification,
and I no longer feel comfortable
being alone in a room with you.
[dramatic music playing]
[chattering]
[swing music playing]
Excuse me.
Guess word got out, huh?
I'll say.
Our 7:00 show is already sold out.
Well, boys,
we've got a genuine hit on our hands.
Ready to play to a full house tonight?
That's what we wanted to talk about.
Veronica, we did this
as a personal favor to you,
and we were happy to, once.
But this can't be a regular thing.
I'll say this.
You two sure know when to ask for a raise.
Because I respect your moxie,
and your balls...
I'll pay you $2 per show going forward.
Veronica, we can't do it.
We have basketball practice.
We have games.
Seems to me like you're playing hardball,
not basketball.
But here's the thing.
You're not the stars.
Those eyeballs are the stars.
You want to squeeze me,
I'm not interested.
I'll get Kevin and Clay to do the gag.
You can leave your balls with them.
Yes, Reginald?
I was thinking.
Maybe after tonight's show
we can try that date again?
I would,
but did you see that crowd out there?
I have to get on the phone with Variety
and whip this buzz into a story.
The Crawling Eye is going
to change everything for the Babylonium.
Yeah.
But I'll tell you what.
Come by tomorrow and we'll see.
Okay.
Well, I think I've heard
just about heard everything now.
Just got off the phone with Dr. Werthers
and he wants to end his sessions with you.
Great. The feeling's mutual.
To which I told him
under no circumstances
is he to give up on you.
Mom, why?
Because he's going to fix you.
Whatever is wrong with you,
he is going to help me fix it.
There is nothing wrong with me.
I wish you would stop trying
to convince me otherwise.
- Who are you calling?
- Dr. Werthers. I'm calling him back.
Put the phone down.
If you want to help me, then talk to me.
Really, just talk to me.
Stop playing this stupid game
of telephone with Dr. Werthers.
Fine. What would you like
to talk about, young lady?
Everything.
Starting with how unhappy I think you are.
Unhappy? Me?
You must be.
You don't know
what you're talking about, young lady.
No, you're right, I don't.
So please enlighten me.
Tell me why you'd rather foist me off
to some quack psychiatrist
than just be honest with me,
your own daughter.
What happened?
Things didn't always
used to be so fraught between us.
Something must have happened.
If this is what you're getting
out of the sessions,
then maybe you're right,
we should end them.
You once told me
that you were afraid for me,
afraid of what the world might do to me.
But why does it seem
like you're afraid of me?
- Oh, Betty...
- Please.
Just talk to me, Mom. I'm...
I'm right here.
- I...
- [Hal] What is going on here?
Mom and I are having a conversation, Dad.
Can you please leave us?
Leave? This is my house.
And I heard the conversation
you were having, Betty.
Enough of it.
This woman...
is the most wonderful wife
and mother in the world.
And the way that you've been acting,
you don't deserve her.
- Dad...
- [Hal] Just go to your room.
And do me a favor and stay there.
And you think about
what you've put your poor mother through.
- What I've put her through?
- [Hal] Yes.
- When all she's done is sacrifice for you.
- How?
Somebody, please tell me how.
You know what?
Just go to your room, young lady. Now.
[door slams]
Mom.
Good morning, Elizabeth.
Mom...
I want us to figure out a path forward.
But it is not Dr. Werthers.
No, it's not.
I relieved Dr. Werthers
of his duties this morning.
And mercifully,
he's decided to not press charges
against you for breaking into his office.
That's good.
Everything that I have been
trying to do my entire life,
sacrificing for you,
protecting you, trying to help you...
It's obvious you don't want it.
So I'm stopping.
You have all the answers.
You know everything.
Seems to me
that you don't need a mother anymore.
Marvelous.
You don't have one.
What are you saying?
I am not your mother anymore.
And you can make your own damn breakfast.
You sure she knows I'm here?
It's been half an hour.
Her phone's been ringing
off the hook all day.
I'm sure she'll be down soon.
[Roth] I was surprised and pleased
to read about your
recent box office success in the trades.
I didn't even know
there was such a thing as 4D.
Yes, well, that's the kind of business
the Babylonium is doing these days.
So I was curious
if you might wanna reconsider
your decision not to let us screen
any of your new releases.
Oh, I'm sure we can work something out.
You know,
I've always been a fan of Riverdale.
Great town. Superb audiences.
It's like no place else, Mr. Roth.
So we'll get that print of East of Eden
for the weekend, I take it?
It's already heading your way.
Fab.
Looking forward
to a long, fruitful collaboration, Peter.
Can I call you Peter?
All right, Reginald,
sorry to have kept you waiting.
- Where's Reggie?
- He got tired of waiting.
Left those for you, though.
[pensive music playing]
[lock rattling]
- [Smithers clears throat]
- Smithers.
There seems to be
something wrong with my lock.
I'm afraid, Ms. Veronica,
the locks have been changed.
Your parents no longer feel that you need
or deserve their financial support
now that you're such a roaring success.
As soon as you have a new address,
I'm to move your belongings.
An eye for a crawling eye.
As for my address,
I already know where I'll be staying.
In the short term, at least.
[elevator bell dings]
[sighs]
["Start at the Bottom" playing]
♪ You've got to start at the bottom
If you're ever gonna reach the top ♪
♪ You've gotta watch all the seeds you sow
Don't let 'em go to pot ♪
♪ You've gotta live by the golden rule ♪
♪ Heed what they teach
In the Sunday school ♪
♪ Start at the bottom
If you're ever gonna reach the top ♪
♪ When Jacob climbed his ladder
He started at the bottom... ♪
[ticking]
[music continues over speakers]
♪ Start at the bottom
If you're ever gonna reach the top ♪
♪ You've gotta watch all the seeds you sow
Don't let 'em go to pot ♪
♪ You've gotta
Live by the golden rule... ♪
What can I get you this round, Jughead?
Chocolate, vanilla, strawberry?
[sighs]
I think just the check, Pop.
I've been re-reading
all of Mr. Rayberry's work,
and I've noticed some recurring themes.
Time passes.
Seasons change.
Life moves on, you know?
I don't know if I'm done mourning,
but I think I'm done wallowing.
Think I'm ready to move on.
I think he'd want me to move on.
I'm glad to hear it.
[siren wailing nearby]
[car door closes]
[door bells jingling]
Jughead, we're still working
the Rayberry suicide case.
We need your help if we're gonna solve it.
[Jughead] So much for moving on.