I don't have to remind you gentlemen
that this meeting never took place.
Of course not, Mayor Blossom.
Has Ethel Muggs been talking much
since she's been with the Sisters?
Not a peep.
Sister Woodhouse
has imposed a vow of silence.
- Very good. What about the PTA?
- [FEATHERHEAD] Parents are still upset.
It's all they talk about at our meetings.
"Who killed Mr. and Mrs. Muggs?"
As long as people
remain focused on this murder case,
the more precarious our grasp
of the situation becomes.
- What's the sheriff's office doing?
- Tom is trying to find this "milkman."
- And the murder weapon.
- Why is he doing that?
I have the murder weapon right here.
What are you getting at, Fredreich?
We have to stop
rehashing the Muggs murder case
and start making sure that
something like it never happens again.
Now, in my extensive research,
in case after case,
comic books are the influencing factor
in most incidents
of juvenile delinquency and teen violence.
They are a moral scourge, gentlemen,
and their creators criminal degenerates.
That's what the PTA
should be talking about.
Comic books, not the Muggs.
And I believe
I know exactly how to make that happen.
Well, look who strolls in
whenever his heart desires.
- What do you want, kid?
- I was just in the neighborhood.
- Where is everyone?
- All out with a stomach bug.
- I'm under more water than the Titanic.
- Can I help?
- I need a full issue.
- I can do that.
- Written by tomorrow morning.
- No problem, Mr. Fieldstone.
I'm fast, I'm a great speller.
Four stories, seven pages each,
zero margin for error.
I'll write them on spec.
If you like them, then great.
If not, there's plenty more
where that came from.
All right.
If you have trouble
coming up with some ideas,
take these springboards.
Talk them through with Bernie.
I will. I won't let you down.
Bernie!
Gosh, Bernie, all these stories
have been done to death.
- Aren't there any original ideas anymore?
- Says the teenager.
Bernie, you're a genius.
What about stories
about teenagers and high school?
Pep Comics
doesn't have any of those, right?
Uh... Al says he doesn't relate to them.
But teenagers do buy our books.
Well, shucks, me and my friends do.
What about a narrator
that's actually a witchy lunch lady?
Or a creepy janitor?
We can call it "Homeroom of Horrors." Huh?
- You think Mr. Fieldstone will bite?
- Sure. Give it a whirl.
There's my little tortured genius.
Think you could take a break
from writing the next great American novel
and take this glamor-gal
to go see a fun flick?
Diabolique is playing at the Babylonium,
and I know you don't mind subtitles.
Ooh. Could we go tomorrow maybe?
I'm on deadline.
Al has asked me to write
an entire issue by morning.
An entire issue?
Sounds like a bit of a coup for you.
Yeah, it is.
But it's also a lot of pressure.
Though if I do a bang-up job
on these pages tonight,
Fieldstone could ask me
to be one of his go-to's.
Okay. Okay, my French thriller about
murderous school teachers can wait.
But since I'm here, maybe I can help you.
- How far have you gotten?
- I'm almost done with my first story.
I'm all ears. What's it about?
Sports-themed.
Because what's scarier than gym class?
And it has a narrator,
like all of my yell­ yarns will.
Um, called the Key-Keeper.
I had one of the artists
at Pep Comics do a mock-up.
- It's pretty nifty, right?
- The niftiest.
Looks like a real charmer.
[KEY-KEEPER] Well, well, well.
If it isn't another problem child.
You're looking for a little mischief
and mayhem, aren't you?
Well, maybe I can be of some assistance.
I'm the Key-Keeper, you see.
The midnight custodian
of this schoolhouse of horrors.
Come along and let's wake the dead
with a real spine-twister, shall we?
I call this sordid little tale
"Keep Your Head in the Game."
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Every team has one.
The runt, the klutz, the pipsqueak.
On the Bulldogs basketball team,
that half-pint was Dilton Doiley,
who was short, near-sighted,
and uncoordinated.
At the end
of one particularly grueling practice,
Coach Kleats had the team
line up for free throws.
No one could leave
until everyone had made a basket.
But Dilton couldn't make a shot
to save his life.
Come on, Doiley,
get your head in the game.
Maybe you need a little motivation.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[KEY-KEEPER] Coach Kleats
had the other players start running laps
until Dilton sunk one lousy bucket.
You're a dead man, Doiley.
[KEY-KEEPER] Poor Dilton.
He would soon learn
the true meaning of the term "foul play."
What the hell is wrong with you, Doiley?
[STUTTERING] I... I'm sorry, fellas.
I'm trying my best.
Why are you even here
if you can't make one stinking basket?
I just wanted to be part of a team.
Then be the damn water boy.
Hmm. It's like what Coach Kleats said...
you gotta get your head in the game.
How...? How do I do that?
Maybe a night stuffed in a locker
will help you figure it out.
What? No, guys! Guys!
Guys, please! Please, don't do it.
No, please. Please, please.
You don't understand. Stop! I can't...
- Don't leave me here!
- Hey, maybe this isn't such a good idea.
Stuff it, Andrews
[DILTON] I can't be here alone. Please.
- Doiley's gotta learn.
- [DILTON] I can't...
He's gonna start pulling his weight...
or we're gonna murder him.
[JULIAN CHUCKLES]
No, don't go!
Please! Please, don't go!
Don't leave me here!
I can't do this! No! No! Please!
[KEY-KEEPER]
What these merciless jocks didn't know
was that Dilton Doiley
was born morbidly claustrophobic.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOOR OPENS]
So by the time the day shift found
and released Dilton the next morning,
Dilton had suffered
a complete psychotic break.
He was a changed man.
A mad man, you might say.
Hell-bent on revenge against the Bulldogs.
Then it was just a matter of lying in wait
for his teammates to reconvene
for basketball practice
later that afternoon.
Luckily, Dilton had the perfect hidey-hole
from which to pop out
and surprise his teammates.
After which, Dilton could dedicate himself
to perfecting his free-throw technique.
Gotta keep my head in the game.
- Gotta keep my head in the game.
- [KLEATS] Attaboy, Doiley.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KLEATS SCREAMING]
Gotta keep my head in the game.
[KLEATS] Help!
Good for Dilton. Those awful bullies
got what was coming to them.
Exactly. And you see, that's what nitwits
like Werthers just don't understand.
What exactly?
These so-called "degenerate comics"
are actually bite-sized morality tales.
Especially those that involve Julian
Blossom getting his head chopped off.
I mean, you joke, but it's true.
Yes, comics can be
over-the-top and bloody sometimes,
but in these stories,
people that break the rules get punished.
People who are cruel
to others get punished.
People who have lustful sex get punished.
Lustful sex, did you say?
- Tell me more about that, Juggiekins.
- [CHUCKLES]
I've got a tale for you.
And it starts, believe it or not,
on a dark and stormy night.
With a flat tire near an isolated mansion,
and a young, strapping man
in need of assistance.
[THUNDER RUMBLING AND CRASHING]
Yes? May I help you?
I'm sorry to bother you at this hour,
ma'am, but my hot rod got a flat tire.
- Must have ran over a nail or something.
- Oh, how dreadful.
And now, here you are stranded,
you poor dear.
Why don't you come inside?
You can use our telephone
to call a garage.
At this hour?
Oh, they'll be closed, ma'am.
Would it be too much trouble
if I stayed the night?
That way, in the morning, I can call
the garage and I'll be out of your hair.
I suppose.
But I'm afraid the storm
has knocked out our power,
but you can warm yourself by the fire.
Well, come in. Come in.
Oh, you look a fright.
[KEY-KEEPER] They say a picture
is worth a thousand words,
but I only need two for this one:
"Hubba, hubba."
[CLEARS THROAT]
Thank you for the tea, ma'am, it's...
I already feel better.
There's not much in this world
that a strong cup of tea
and a roaring fire can't fix.
And you're welcome
to stay in my guest room tonight.
Thank you, ma'am. That's very kind of you.
However, there are one or two
ground rules you must observe.
Of course. Of course. Anything.
Once you are in your room,
you must stay there all night.
And you must lock the door
and keep it locked for the entire night.
Any particular reason why?
Alas, yes. I'm not alone in this house.
My granddaughter lives with me,
and she's not quite in her right mind.
She has this compulsive craving
for intimate physical,
some might even say
inappropriate touching.
- Really?
- Oh, yes.
She's ravenous for it.
Can't keep her hands to herself.
Wow, that's...
I mean, that sounds... Wow.
She's even been known to sneak
into the bedrooms of strange young men
in the middle of the night
in order to get her fix, as it were.
Is...
- that your granddaughter?
- Mm-hm.
Yes, it is. She's beautiful, isn't she?
Well, it's getting late.
Let's get you settled, shall we?
[KEY-KEEPER]
Surely some rules were meant to be broken.
Especially when the consequences
might prove to be downright titillating.
[DOOR CREAKING]
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[CHERYL] You're here.
You came.
- Are you the old lady's granddaughter?
- Yes, I'm Cheryl.
I'm so glad you're here.
It's been so long
since I've gotten to touch... like this.
I sure am happy to be here too.
- Let me just light a candle.
- No. No.
- Oh.
- No.
What we're about to do
is best done in darkness.
Now kiss me.
And let me feel you.
[KEY-KEEPER] Avert your eyes, pervert,
and turn the page...
to a bright new day.
[NANA ROSE] How was your night, young man?
Did you sleep well?
It was incredible. [CHUCKLES]
Thank you again for the hospitality.
I, uh...
I saw your granddaughter, I think.
By the window.
So, what's wrong with her?
Some kind of mental illness?
Oh, Cheryl was once youthful and vibrant
like any young girl her age.
But she wanted adventure,
and I couldn't help but indulge her.
She took a trip to some tropical jungle
in some far-off place,
and unfortunately, while she was there,
she contracted a rare form of leprosy.
Leprosy?
Horrible, terrible, disfiguring disease.
Rotting her swollen flesh away,
and incredibly painful.
Now she can't be around other people
because it's so very contagious, you know.
But... I mean, you don't...
Oh, no. I was exposed as a child
and so I'm immune.
I don't suppose you...
Am immune? No.
Mercifully, she'll soon succumb
to the leprosy and die.
Which is why I do everything
in my power to ensure
that she relishes her final days on Earth.
[STAMMERING] Wait,
what do you mean by that?
It was no accident
that brought you here, young man.
How do you think
those nails got on to that road?
I did warn you.
I gave you a chance
to lock that door and be a good boy.
And now you're
almost certainly infected as well.
[CHERYL] After last night,
we're going to be together,
forever and ever.
'Til death do us part.
[SCREAMING]
Well, that was grotesque.
What was the moral there?
Don't trust creepy old ladies
and their nymphomaniac,
leprosy-ridden granddaughters?
Well, it's more of
a "curiosity killed the cat" message,
- I think.
- Ah.
Or, don't engage in heavy petting
in the dark with someone
if you haven't got proper protection.
You know, I'm hearing that
Archie and Cheryl broke up.
And that, in the end,
they didn't do much more than neck.
Oh, yeah? Well, who can keep up with
all the horny teens at Riverdale High?
I mean, what else is there to do?
It's why God created high school.
So there'd be a place where boys
could chase girls and vice versa.
Yeah.
I mean, girls will do just about anything
to get a boy's attention.
Including feigning an interest
in comic books, apparently.
[KEY-KEEPER] Every school has one.
The plain Jane with the ponytail mane.
The sweater-set waiting for better-yet,
whom none of the boys
seem to sic their sights on.
Bland Betty
was little more than an invisible girl.
Yes, my foul fiends, Betty's prospects
of landing a date were very grave, indeed.
So she followed the advice
of her favorite beauty mags.
And, now, how can I help you, hon?
I would like a new look, please.
Oh. What's giving you
the gringles, dollface?
I just feel so...
unseen.
All the girls at my school have beaus,
and it's just like I'm a...
ghost.
I need something else, something new.
Something amazing
that will get all the boys' attention.
Well, I gotta tell you, this ponytail,
it's doing you no favors.
But, but, but, I just came back
from my fabulous honeymoon abroad,
and there's this new hairstyle
that is all the rage in Europe.
Really? What is it?
It's called "The Beehive."
Beehive?
Sounds sophisticated.
Oh, it is.
So we tease up all your hair,
put in some extensions,
and then roll it all up into a dome.
Just like a hive.
A "hive" hive?
I know it sounds silly,
but wait till you see it.
All the girls in England and France,
they just love it.
And the boys, they're crazy about it.
And, on my mother's grave,
may she rest in peace,
you're gonna get all the attention
you've ever wanted and then some.
What the heck,
if it's good enough for the Parisians,
it's good enough for me.
Oh, smart girl.
You're gonna look so chic.
Now, there's just one thing.
Once we get your goldilocks
up into the hive,
you're not gonna be able to wash your hair
or undo it ever.
Oh, well, how do I maintain it?
With this hairspray.
Use throughout the day as needed.
Oh, well, my mom says I'm supposed
to wash my hair every other day
or at least once a week.
With all due respect to your dear mama,
I'm the professional.
And you do wanna look beautiful,
am I right?
["SHE'S SWEET" PLAYING]
[KEY-KEEPER] The next day,
an all-new Betty showed up at school.
Her coif climbed to such heights,
it rivaled the Tower of Babel.
And similarly, it got everybody talking.
All the boys went "goo-goo-gaga."
And as for the girls, well,
they were positively gangrene with envy.
♪ Her lips are so red
Her eyes are so blue ♪
♪ They sparkle like morning dew... ♪
[VERONICA COUGHING]
Watch where you're spraying, Betty.
You know that ridiculous hairstyle
will never change the fact you'll always
be a ponytail princess on the inside?
[KEY-KEEPER] Betty didn't care
what Cheryl and Veronica thought.
In fact, that was the first time
they'd spoken to her.
And once Betty
got that blush of attention,
well, she started needing it,
feeding off it.
The more hairspray she put in her hair,
the heavier and more shellacked it became,
and the more the boys noticed her.
Can I carry your books to class, Betty?
Aw, gee, thanks, Julian.
Hey, uh, Betty. Can I take you out
this Friday night, please?
Archie. I'll think about it.
[KEY-KEEPER]
And Betty stayed true to her word.
She didn't wash her hair or undo it, ever.
She even slept in her beehive,
putting more hairspray on
before tucking herself in at night.
And that's when
the very bad thing happened.
I swear, in all my years,
I've never seen a cuter couple.
She's a cool cookie now, isn't she, Pop?
What do you mean "now"?
Betty's always been a peach.
You're making me blush, Archie.
Hey, I'm a lucky cat.
I'm going out with the ginchiest girl
with the ginchiest hair at Riverdale High.
- ["I GOT STUNG" PLAYING OVER JUKEBOX]
- Mm!
Best song ever.
Come on, snake, let's rattle.
Okay.
♪ I got stung by a sweet honey bee
Oh, what a feeling come over me ♪
Betty, is everything all right?
Whoa, Betty.
Something's not...
Betty? Betty!
Betty.
Someone get some help.
Betty's having some kind of fit.
Someone call the hospital!
Oh, God, Betty.
[KEY-KEEPER] No one could guess
how a young girl like Betty,
so full of life, would just drop dead.
Then again, maybe the town's coroner
will have the answers.
So young.
So beautiful.
And what a fascinating hairstyle.
Hmm.
Oh, my.
What have we here?
No. No!
Please, no.
No. Anything but spiders!
[KEY-KEEPER] Turns out, Betty's hair
attracted more than just boys.
A black widow spider
had crawled into her tresses that night
and laid a batch of eggs
in that ginchy hive of hers.
And when those itsy-bitsy spiders hatched,
they chewed into her brain,
which is what triggered
Betty's deadly diner bug-out.
Poor, sweet Betty.
She had to learn her lessons the hard way.
Beauty is only skin deep,
and vanity kills.
"Beauty is only skin deep"?
"Vanity kills"?
Are these actually different lessons,
or variations on a theme?
And what's wrong
with wanting to look good?
Boys do the same thing.
They toss weights around
to turn themselves into he-men.
Uh...
At any rate, by my count,
you're down to your last story
and I still haven't had
a starring role in one.
Well, say, that's a notion.
Something romantic would be nice.
Or something
that focuses on female friendship.
Yeah. What if we did a flip
of the classic teenage love triangle?
One in which the girls don't go
at each other's throats and catfight.
Now you're singing my tune.
Presenting, my fourth
and final story of the evening.
A terror-tale
I'm calling "My Better Half."
Archie's a good egg,
but a half-wit
when it comes to decision-making.
He struggles with the most basic
of all multiple-choice questions.
Should he go for A, the girl next door?
Or, B, the rich starlet-socialite?
But, in a rare stroke of mad genius,
Archie chose C, both of the above.
So on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays,
Archie takes Betty out.
And on Tuesdays, Thursdays, and Saturdays,
he takes out Veronica.
The one downside
to this break-neck schedule
was that Archie would, on occasion,
collapse from sheer exhaustion.
But it was nothing
that couldn't be rectified
with a strong cup of coffee.
Or four.
But even for a strapping young buck,
six dates a week will wear a fella out.
That's why Archie
saved Sundays for himself.
To rest, recover,
and replenish for the week ahead.
Now, you might think Archie would try
to keep his relationships a secret,
but he didn't.
Betty and Veronica
knew he was dating the other.
Still, each girl
wanted Archie all to herself.
They're playing Double Indemnity
at the Babylonium tomorrow night,
if you want to play
a little back-row bingo.
Oh, I wish I could swing it,
but I got plans.
Meaning, you've got a date with Veronica.
When are you gonna drop
that vapid airhead?
Oh, please, don't get razzled.
Why shouldn't I?
Having to share my beau
with that smelly tomboy.
Don't I make you happy?
Of course you do.
Then why aren't I enough?
Oh, come on. It's not like that.
Hey, you guys are both so different.
But let me let you in on a little secret.
[WHISPERS] You're my favorite.
- Really?
Oh, Archie.
How do you do it, Andrews?
Two broads at the same time.
What's your secret?
All right, listen, 'cause I'm only
gonna say this once, okay?
You tell them what they wanna hear.
That, yes, I'm seeing other girls, but...
I'm only serious about you.
You feed them the same three simple words.
"You're my favorite."
Technically, that's four words,
"You're" is a contraction.
"You are my favorite."
- Four words.
- Shut up, Doiley.
We're learning from Don Juan here.
But don't you ever get...
exhausted?
Sure, but that's why
God invented Sundays, and coffee.
[BOYS CHUCKLING]
Things might've kept humming along as-is
until graduation day,
but the Good Ship Archie
was headed for an iceberg.
Valentine's Day,
which, this year, disastrously,
landed on a Sunday.
So, Veronica, who's the lucky guy
taking you out for Valentine's Day?
Archiekins, of course.
Keep dreaming. Archie is my date.
You know, Betty,
for a smart girl, you really are dense.
Archie is gonna spend V-Day
with his best girl.
And that's me.
- Says you.
- Says him.
Archiekins says the only reason
he spends time with you
is because you're a charity case.
First of all,
he hates being called "Archiekins."
Second of all, the only reason
he spends any time with you at all
is because your ego is so fragile,
he's afraid you might do
something desperate or crazy
if he breaks up with you.
He said I'm fragile?
Aw, as a Glamourge Egg.
Well, he told me you're so high-strung,
you sometimes take
your mom's sleeping pills to go to bed.
- He told you that?
- Mm-hm.
Sounds like someone's
been playing you two for fools.
[BOTH] That rat fink.
Archie, you have to choose right now.
Who's gonna be your date
for Valentine's Day?
And after you pick me, of course,
you need to end things with Betty,
permanently.
Ladies, ladies. Let's all calm down.
In fact...
neither of you
can be my date on Valentine's Day.
[BOTH] Why not?
'Cause I'm taking my mom.
You see, it's her first Valentine's Day
without my dad, and...
And, well, she needs me.
I hope you guys can understand.
Archie, of course we understand.
That's so sweet and thoughtful.
I'm sorry we pressured you.
Me too. It was her idea.
Well, you guys shouldn't have
to miss out on Valentine's Day
on account of me.
There must be some other guys
you can go out with.
Yeah, Betty. Find somebody else.
No.
No, it's really okay.
There's an extra-credit report
that I've been putting off, so...
As for me, Mademoiselle published
a recipe for an egg-white face mask
I've been dying to try,
so that'll keep me busy.
Okay, so you're both staying in
this Sunday night, then?
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
But when Sunday night rolled around,
Betty and Veronica
decided against staying in
and went on a Valentine's date together.
[DOOR OPENS, BELLS JINGLE]
So imagine their surprise
when who should walk in, but...
He wouldn't.
He couldn't.
[BOTH] That rat fink.
Wait.
Whatever you're about to do...
I have a much better idea.
Betty.
Veronica.
What's going on?
We were wondering how
your Valentine's date went with your mom.
Yeah. It was nice.
Quiet.
Why?
Well, because a night off
gave us a chance to reflect,
and since you've been
having such a hard time
deciding between the two of us,
we were thinking...
What If you had us both?
At the exact same time?
For a very, very special date.
Really?
[BOTH] Really.
Say no more.
I'll pick you both up tonight.
We'll head over to Lovers' Lane.
I know the perfect spot. Nice and private.
Actually, Betty had an interesting idea.
I was thinking
we could meet in shop class.
After hours, of course.
Why would we go there?
Don't you know?
It's soundproof.
And we plan on making a lot of noise.
[BOTH] Come, Archie. Join us.
Wait.
You're forgetting something.
Your coffee.
We took the liberty of brewing it
extra strong for you tonight.
Guys, I really don't think
I'm gonna need a boost tonight.
Now, now, no need to posture.
You'll want all your energy
for what we have planned.
Promise.
Cross our hearts and hope to die.
Mm.
[ECHOING] Everything all right,
Archiekins?
Yeah. No, I'm good. I just...
Someone's waking up, Vee.
[VERONICA] I think you're right, Bee.
Welcome back, handsome.
What's happening?
Apologies if you're experiencing
a splitting headache.
I wasn't sure how many of my mom's
sleeping pills to slip into your coffee.
Whatever it is,
I'm sure we can figure it out.
But it's already been figured out, silly.
Trust us, this is a perfect solution.
After all, a problem shared
is a problem solved.
Shall we, Vee?
[VERONICA] After you, Bee.
Wait, wait, wait. Wait!
Wait, hold on! Hold on!
[SCREAMS]
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
This won't hurt... much.
[IN UNISON] We just wanna double our fun.
[SCREAMING]
[JUBILANT '50S POP MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEY-KEEPER] Here, for the first time,
Betty and Veronica
are with their beloved Archie
on the same night, at the same time,
secure in the knowledge that
they'll never have to share him again.
Didn't I tell you he was a half-wit?
[KEY-KEEPER CHUCKLING]
[JUGHEAD] Well?
What did you think
of the tag-team twist at the end?
O. Henry, eat your heart out, am I right?
I have...
opinions.
Okey-dokey.
I'm detecting a pattern, Jughead.
The sexual politics
in most of your stories are...
troubling, to say the least.
Veronica, gosh.
You may be overthinking this.
These stories are just meant to be a gas.
For whom?
Not teen girls.
Not when you're depicting them like...
shallow, crazy killers.
Is that what you think of us?
No. Of course not.
The boys aren't great shakes, either.
So you admit you're demonizing women?
Veronica...
it's just a comic book.
Anyhoo...
I'm done now.
Why don't we catch that last showing
of Diabolique at the Babylonium?
- What do you say? My treat.
- I think...
I'll take a page from your last story...
and split.
What's going on?
Are we not copacetic anymore?
Of course we are.
I'm just tired, is all.
I'll catch you at school tomorrow.
Promise.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[JUGHEAD] And, as easy as that,
whatever soap bubble
Veronica and I had been in just burst.
Tomorrow, at school,
things would be different.
We'd no longer be the Marilyn Monroe
and Arthur Miller of Riverdale High.
We'd pass each other in the hall,
but she'd once again
be the beautiful socialite
and I'd be the Melvin
who writes comic books.
The kind that hopefully
weren't corrupting the youth of America.
[FEATHERHEAD]
"Don't be fooled by their name.
These publications are anything but comic.
In their pages, crime is glorified.
Acts of wanton carnality are celebrated.
Stabbings, and beheadings,
and disembowelings are commonplace,
vividly depicted,
and offered up to our children
like so much bubblegum.
And if anyone doubts the insidious effects
of this subversive medium,
let me stress what my extensive research
has proven time and again.
There is a direct and undeniable link
between gruesome acts of brutality
depicted in the pages of comic books
and similar acts of savagery
committed in real life
by the juveniles
who read these comic books.
Our children are being seduced.
By violence.
By sex.
By depravity.
Their innocence must be preserved
by any means necessary."
I congratulate you, Dr. Werthers.
That's a brilliant editorial.
The soon-to-be-forgotten Muggs murders,
small potatoes
compared to the threat to America
that you have outlined for us tonight.
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
I consider it my civic and moral duty.
That's why these so-called creators
of these dangerous
and morally reprehensible stories
must be held accountable,
and punished
to the full extent of the law.
[FIELDSTONE] I've been reading
your stories, Jones,
and I gotta say, I love them.
This is incredible stuff.
Thank you, Mr. Fieldstone. I, um...
- I needed a win today.
- How come?
Ah. Let me guess. Girl trouble?
Yeah.
I...
had this sweet thing going
with this one gal,
but then she read my comics, and then...
Well, she took it the wrong way.
I don't think she liked what I was saying.
I don't even know what that means.
But you busted your ass
to turn those stories around overnight.
And I think you deserve
a little something extra for that.
- A bonus?
- Oh, God, no.
What, are you nuts?
No, I'm thinking credit.
- Your name...
- On the cover?
God, no. A byline.
On the inside, but still.
It's my name in print.
Oh, golly, that would be incredible,
Mr. Fieldstone.
My friends would flip.
How does Jughead "Jugular" Jones
sound for a byline?
Oh. [WHISTLES]
- I'm crazy for it.
- Yeah.
Now, you listen to me, kid.
I don't know much, but do I know this.
Girls come and go, but your name in print?
That's a thing that'll make people
sit up and take notice.
[JUGHEAD] Little did any of us imagine
how prophetic Mr. Fieldstone's words
would turn out to be.