["Ain't That a Shame" playing]
[Jughead]
Grief is a terrible thing.
When you've suffered
a loss as I have,
the death of my mentor
and literary idol,
Brad Rayberry,
time falls into
a slow, sad rhythm.
And a moment feels
like an eternity.
-[music slows down]
-Even as the rest of the world
-continues to tick on.
-[clock ticking]
[Dr. Werthers] You will
no longer be in
the River Vixens.
Your mother and I believe
that it's too sexualized
an environment for you.
High school in general
is a highly sexualized
environment.
Wouldn't you say?
Is that how you see it?
A bunch of horny teenagers
trapped together like sardines
for hours upon hours?
How do you see it?
As an academic institution
meant to provide
a safe environment
where students can challenge
themselves intellectually
without being morally
and physically compromised.
Oh, well, you
obviously haven't spent
a lot of time in gym class.
You are here, Betty,
because you stripped in front
of your window
for your next-door
neighbor's pleasurement.
And then you flashed your...
Your underpants
on live television.
In short, you seem...
unhealthily obsessed
with sexuality.
Now, the words that
come to mind are
"nymphomaniac,"
"exhibitionist,"
"sexual compulsive."
What exactly do you
want to talk to me about,
Dr. Werthers?
Well, given your
recent behavior, I'm curious.
What is your first
sexual memory?
-[buzzes]
-[sighs]
[sighs]
I'm not sure that I remember.
Uh, in that case, um...
How often, Betty,
would you say that
you think about sex?
["Lollipop" playing]
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli
Lollipop ♪
[pop sound plays]
♪ Boom-boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli
Lollipop ♪
[pop sound plays]
♪ Boom-boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Call my baby lollipop
Tell you why ♪
♪ His kiss is sweeter
Than an apple pie ♪
♪ And when he does
His shaky rockin' dance ♪
♪ Man, I haven't got a chance ♪
♪ I call him ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli
Lollipop ♪
[pop sound plays]
♪ Sweeter than candy
On a stick ♪
♪ Huckleberry, cherry
Or lime ♪
♪ If you had a choice
He'd be your pick ♪
♪ But lollipop is mine ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli ♪
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli
Lollipop ♪
[pop sound plays]
[Dr. Werthers] Betty. Betty.
[record scratches]
How often do you
think about sex?
I would say an average amount.
I need a number, Betty.
Well, according
to Dr. Kingsley,
teenagers think about sex
every seven seconds.
That number is
for teenage boys.
There is a very different
barometer for teenage girls.
Well, in that case,
I would say
I think about sex...
all the time.
What did you just write down?
Never mind that.
Why do you think you think
about sex all the time?
I'm curious about...
how it feels.
I don't think that waiting
until I'm married to
have sex makes sense.
What about having
sex for pleasure?
Betty, sex is for
married people so
they can start families.
So then, what about the girlie
magazines that my dad keeps
hidden in his sock drawer?
Uh, I'm sorry?
Well, I remember last year,
we were going to church.
My dad asked me to fetch
him his cuff links and...
when I went to look for them
in his sock drawer,
I found all of these
girlie magazines.
Your father is not in therapy.
You are.
Well, maybe he should be.
He's a grown man.
I'm a child psychiatrist.
I am not a child, either.
Though, actually,
I do think that...
our conversations
are starting to make me
see things more clearly.
[sputters]
In what particular way?
Well, I'm just now
realizing that...
I don't think
I want to get married.
At least not anytime soon.
Maybe never.
I want to make an impact
on the world instead of...
Or in addition to...
just having a family.
[pop music playing on stereo]
-♪ Puppy love
That's what they say... ♪
-[knocking at door]
Knock, knock.
Hi, sweetheart.
I got you something fun.
[chuckles] What are those for?
I was in the grocery store
and I just thought
the pictures were so pretty.
I had to get you a few of them.
Mom, I'm not even
dating anyone.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
A girl can daydream
about her wedding, can't she?
Why are you bringing
this up right now?
[clicks tongue] Oh, Elizabeth,
I just know,
when I see you in
that white dress,
standing at that altar...
[sighs]
It's gonna be the
happiest day of my life.
[door bell dings]
[Veronica] Tickets.
Get your tickets
to the Babylonium's
James Dean double feature.
[rock music playing]
What's all this
about James Dean?
As president of his
fan club, I, along with
my fellow Dean-izens,
have been waiting for
East of Eden to reach our
little hamlet for months now.
Well, you're just in luck,
because we have,
in our possession,
a print of East of Eden.
And why, pray tell,
should I go to the Babylonium
when the screen at
the Orpheum, in nearby
Greendale, is much larger,
as befits the stature
of my beloved Jimmy Dean?
Is the Orpheum giving
you and your Dean-izens
free passes?
On the condition
that you spread the good
word about the Babylonium?
We want a robust crowd
to honor Jimmy's memory.
On the sacred ground
of James Dean's grave,
I will deliver my fan club,
the Vixens and the Bulldogs.
Excellent.
But don't worry
about the Bulldogs.
I'm extending that invitation
myself, personally.
Batten down the hatches, boys,
because the Babylonium
is going to do boffo
business this weekend.,.
I can feel it.
But why are we giving out
tickets for free?
I'll let you in
on the dirty secret
about the movie theater
business, Kevin.
We make most of our money
from popcorn and soda sales.
And, uh, what was
all that about
inviting the Bulldogs?
They're our hometown
heroes. Of course
they have to be there.
All the Bulldogs
or just one in particular?
[clears throat]
[Bulldogs cheering]
[Fogarty] Oh,
check it out, Bulldogs.
[Bulldog player]
Oh, look at this.
If it isn't
Miss Twinkle Town herself.
It's Tinseltown.
As a fan of the Bulldogs,
I wanted to personally
offer you free passes
to our
James Dean double feature
at the Babylonium.
Comp tickets
are in your lockers.
And you, Reginald?
Shall I save you
a seat beside me?
I mean, surely you know
what Jimmy Dean used
to do in high school, I hope.
What's that?
He was
a basketball star, Reggie.
Just like you.
["It Happened" playing]
♪ It happened ♪
[chattering indistinctly]
[Veronica] Here you are.
That'll be 25 cents.
Okay.
Or you could treat me
to a milkshake after the show.
You just keep on shooting,
don't you?
You keep passing me the ball.
Okay, sure. Let's do it.
Take it.
-Meet you back here?
-All right.
Now get in there
before you miss
the coming attractions.
-[cash register dings]
-Veronica?
Kevin.
Guess who's got a date
with Reggie Mantle
tonight after the show?
That's swell, but Clay's
got a situation in
the projection booth.
I don't know what happened,
but the print we received
from the studio...
We can't play it.
What? Why?
It's been overexposed.
How many reels are like this?
That's the thing, all of them.
We've got a sold-out house.
[chattering indistinctly]
Welcome to the Babylonium.
[all cheering]
We're so excited to have
you all here tonight.
So quit bashing our ears
and play the damn movie!
[all] Yeah!
Due to some unforeseen
technical difficulties,
I regret to inform you
we are unable to screen
our James Dean
double feature tonight.
-[crowd booing]
-I knew it.
However...
However, we are working
on the problem
and are rescheduling
said double feature...
That's all very well and good,
but we, the proud members
of the James Dean Fan Club
Riverdale Chapter,
demand a refund... immediately.
[audience chanting]
Refund! Refund!
Refund?
You all got free passes,
including you, Cheryl.
True, but we did spend
all this money on
popcorn and soda
to consume during
the double feature
which is no longer happening.
[audience clamoring]
I would be more than
happy to provide each
and every one of you
with a voucher for any
snack of your choosing...
We don't want
your stupid vouchers.
We want our money back.
-[all] Yeah!
-[Cheryl] What a fakeout!
It's like Jimmy Dean
died all over again!
All right, all right,
all right, all right,
all right.
Calm down. Calm down.
You can present your receipts
at the concession stands
for a full refund.
Yeah, right!
Hey!
[man exhales]
Reggie.
I'm so sorry.
As much as I'd be
delighted to split
a milkshake with you...
You've got a business
to take care of.
I do.
The Babylonium's hanging
on by the most
gossamer of threads.
I figured as much.
I'd happily take a rain check.
Yeah? Sure.
Yeah, just let me know
when's a good time for you.
Okay.
I've never heard of
such a thing, Mr. Roth.
A venerated studio like yours,
sending out unplayable prints
of a major release
like East of Eden?
[Peter on phone]
I'm as baffled as you,
Miss Lodge.
At any rate, please accept
our deepest apologies
for this mishap.
I'll accept your apology,
but what I really want
is a pristine copy
of East of Eden.
And what I want
is audiences in Riverdale
to see this picture.
I do. It's a wonderful picture.
But I'm afraid that there
are no more available prints.
You sent me
a defective product.
How is this my problem?
Miss Lodge.
Veronica.
May I call you Veronica?
You're the theater owner.
It's always your problem.
You'd know that
if you weren't so green.
Green?
Let me assure you--
I'm so sorry,
but I need to let you go.
I'm having lunch
at the Polo Lounge
with Monty Clift,
but good luck to you.
How does a major studio
run out of prints
of their biggest
release of the year?
I don't know.
But luckily, they're not
the only studio in town.
-It's time to work
the phones, boys.
-[phone ringing]
I have Pasadena Pictures.
Nikki? Veronica Lodge.
No, Nikki, I'm in
exhibition these days.
The Babylonium in Riverdale.
Listen, my customers
simply don't have time
for that Steinbeck yawner.
I need something exciting,
something fresh.
Do you have
any available prints
of To Catch a Thief?
I'm hearing great things
about Hitchcock's latest.
Word around town
is that Oklahoma!
is a masterpiece.
What about this
Night of the Hunter
I keep reading about?
It's RKO.
[man 1] Be that as it may be,
Miss Lodge,
we've already booked
our picture
at the Orpheum.
Unfortunately, Riverdale
isn't a market we're
interested in cultivating.
It's Silver Shield Studios.
[man 2] I'm sorry,
but we're being very particular
about how we're
distributing musicals
this year.
It's Superior.
[man 3] Furthermore,
all of our current releases
demand larger theaters.
Please, don't call us again.
But, sir, you used to send us
your movies every week.
What changed?
I don't do business with
underage would-be impresarios.
Especially not when
I'm trying to get into
business with their parents.
But good luck to you,
Miss Lodge. You'll need it.
[dial tone sounding]
[sighs] Well,
there you have it, boys.
I and the Babylonium have been
blacklisted by every
major studio in Hollywood.
Why, though?
[sighs] If I had to
hazard a guess,
my parents.
I've been waiting
for this penny loafer to drop
since I bought the theater
out from under them.
My last call confirmed it,
but honestly,
I suspected sabotage
from the moment
we got that bad print.
What do your parents want?
To see everyone
but themselves fail,
including their own daughter.
I'm sure they want
the Babylonium to shutter
so they can buy it from me
at a discount
and turn it into a parking lot.
I have an idea.
So far, we've only tried
the major studios.
But there are a lot of smaller,
independent places out there.
They're scrappy,
and they don't play
by the same rules.
Their movies
don't have big stars
or budgets or prestige.
In other words,
they're B movies,
but they're still movies.
Good idea, Clay.
Boys, if we're going down,
we're going down fighting.
[snaps fingers]
Get me...
one of those smaller studios.
Tell me, Betty, do you ever
remember your dreams?
Sometimes.
Are your dreams sexual?
Well then, tell me, Betty...
What is your most vivid
or frequent sexual dream?
[Betty] I guess
it's the one where
I'm in biology class, only...
I'm the teacher,
tutoring one of my students.
[Dr. Werthers] Which student?
[Betty] It varies.
["Captured" playing]
♪ Captured
In a moonlight
That blinds you ♪
♪ And a magic
That binds me ♪
♪ In a world... ♪
[Dr. Werthers]
Yes, but most often?
[Betty] It's Archie.
[Dr. Werthers]
And what occurs
in this dream?
♪ A music strange to me ♪
♪ Beats its thunder ♪
♪ Through and through ♪
♪ Is it love? ♪
♪ This wondrous change in me ♪
♪ This enchanted dream
Come true ♪
♪ Captured
In this spell... ♪
[Betty] And that's
the part of the dream
where I realize...
everyone's watching.
This dream,
and others like it,
do you ever share them
with other people?
No, never. Just my diary.
Hmm.
What are you always writing
in that notepad of yours?
Notes, observations.
Thoughts to myself,
kind of like a diary.
Tell me, Betty.
Where do you think
this urge comes from?
The urge to be seen
in such a sexualized way.
Well, it must titillate you,
make it more exciting for you.
I don't think it's just
about being seen sexually.
I think it might be more about
being seen... period.
In what respect?
Being seen... as a person.
With autonomy, and desire...
and self-determination.
Go on.
I'm wondering if my interest
in understanding sex
is really more about
understanding myself.
Who I am.
I mean, what better way
to understand a person
than to understand
their desires?
Including your own.
-[bell dinging]
-[Pop] It'll just be
a few minutes.
Thanks, Pop.
Hey, Holden Caulfield.
Have you ever heard
of a movie called
The Crawling Eye?
Yeah. It came out
a couple years ago.
Uh, the story
was kind of a mess,
but the monster was cool.
I loved it. [chuckles]
Mr. Rayberry loved it too.
Why... Why do you ask?
Because after calling
every minor independent
studio in La La Land,
it's the only movie
I can get my hands on
to play at the Babylonium.
Why don't you just do
what William Castle did?
The name dimly rings a bell.
He's a producer-director.
His movies are just okay,
but they all came with
a kind of gimmick.
Like for The Tingler,
filmed in Percepto,
he put a bunch of buzzers
under the audience's seats
and when the monster,
the Tingler,
appeared on screen,
he would buzz
the people and give them
an electric shock. [chuckles]
That sounds dangerous.
It was just a mild shock,
but it worked.
People went nuts
for The Tingler.
[chuckles softly]
I get it.
Sell the gimmick,
not the movie.
I can do that.
[Alice] Oh, good. She's home.
Hello, dear.
So glad you're home.
What's going on?
You remember Reverend Lowe
from Riverdale First Reformed
Presbyterian Church?
My, how you've grown
since the children's choir,
Elizabeth.
[chuckles]
He's going to
hear your confession
and perform an exorcism
if need be. Right?
[chuckles]
Confe...
[chuckles nervously]
Confession.
Why would I need to confess?
What are you doing
with my diaries? Uh...
Did you read them?
Elizabeth, I had to.
They were prescribed to me.
By Dr. Werthers?
I would rather not say.
You... You broke into my room
and stole my diaries
because my psychiatrist
told you to?
Good grief, Mother!
I suspected you and Dr. Psycho
were talking about me,
but breaking and entering?
If you are so hot to trot
to talk with Dr. Werthers,
why don't you come
to therapy with me?
It might help you.
[scoffs] I am an adult woman.
I don't need therapy.
[scoffs]
Elizabeth. Elizabeth.
Breaking and entering.
What do you write down
in that notepad of yours?
Breaking and entering.
[door closes]
Okay. Dr. Werthers.
Let's see what you've been
writing about me.
Come on.
This always works
in the Tracy True books.
Gosh. You're an even
bigger bookworm than I am.
Pop says you've been glued
to this booth for two days,
getting ink on your nose.
Uh, yeah, you might say,
I'm, um...
spending time with a friend
before saying goodbye.
Oh, well,
sorry to interrupt, but...
have you heard
of this book, Lolita?
Holy moly.
Where did you get this?
[clicks tongue]
I borrowed it from a friend.
What can you tell me about it?
Well, it's Nabokov's
latest novel.
It's... pretty salacious,
according to the Paris Review.
It's about a relationship
between a professor
named Humbert Humbert
and a young girl
named Dolores Haze.
-How young?
-Twelve.
Twelve?
So it's a book for perverts?
Well...
passing moral judgment
on a work of art
is a slippery slope.
Have you read it yet?
That's what I'm about to go do.
Thank you, Jughead.
-Hey, Pop, can I get
another one, please?
-Coming right up.
[exhales]
[man on screen]
No one is safe from its spell
of destruction.
A cold, hypnotic stare
striking fear into
the hearts of all,
creating a frenzied nightmare
for those who behold it.
And that, ladies and germs,
is the terrifying, titillating
new feature film,
The Crawling Eye,
playing at the Babylonium,
one week only.
Not that I care to see
such dreck,
but didn't that movie
come out a few years ago?
Perhaps,
but this is a re-release
in stunning 4D.
Mmm, don't you mean 3D?
Oh, no. 3D is so 1952.
This is 4D, Cheryl,
a new fourth
dimension of terror.
Time is the fourth dimension.
Do you mean time?
Shut up, Dilton.
4D is a novel,
visceral experience,
unlike anything
you've ever encountered
at the movies before.
Guaranteed.
My associates are handing out
little novelty reminders,
which are redeemable
at the candy counter,
for buy-one-get-one-free
Milk Buds.
[rock music playing]
Now, remember, boys.
After you completely
cover your balls
with a layer of newspaper,
let them dry before
applying the next one.
I'll handle the paint job
when I get back from casting.
♪ When the record
Starts to boop ♪
♪ And your body starts to move
Shake around, girl ♪
[all chattering indistinctly]
♪ And the cats
All start to stew
When they see my baby do... ♪
Just the two strapping he-men
I've been looking for
all my life.
Hope you can make it
to The Crawling Eye tonight.
Not as audience members,
mind you, but as performers.
As part of my revolutionary
4D experience.
-Veronica, we're not actors.
-What would we have to do?
Yeah, what exactly?
Not much.
All told, it would probably be
about two minutes of work,
for which you'd be
handsomely compensated,
of course.
[rock music continues]
♪ When you get up
On that feeling like you're
Rocking and you're reeling ♪
♪ Shake around, girl ♪
Oh, Miss Cooper.
You haven't forgotten about
our standing appointment,
have you?
No, I didn't.
But I won't be attending
our session today.
Instead, I have some very
interesting reading
to finish tonight.
But don't worry, Doctor.
I'm sure tomorrow
we will have plenty to discuss.
♪ Move little baby ♪
♪ Can you kick around
Little baby ♪
♪ You gotta slow it down
♪ 'Cause when the record
Starts a-groovin'
Let your body start... ♪
Cheryl.
So glad you could make it.
Before the movie,
you may want to take out
a life insurance policy.
You know, in case
you die of fright.
Pathetic.
Otherwise we have
a nurse on duty,
should you merely faint.
[shaker rattles]
I am extremely
disappointed in you, Midge.
Now, let's see what
this 4D you've been
ballyhooing is all about.
And believe me,
if it disappoints,
I will be demanding
a refund, again.
♪ And when the record
Starts a-groovin'
Let your body start a-movin' ♪
♪ Shake around, girl ♪
[enthralling music playing
on screen]
[man 1 on screen] If that cloud
starts to move this way
before I get back,
take the car up.
Do you understand?
-[man 2] What about you?
-[man 1] Do as you're told.
[eerie music playing]
[whispering indistinctly]
[girl chuckles]
[woman crying on screen]
[eerie music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[man on screen]
Steady. Steady.
To your right.
Visual on. Steady.
Bombs away!
[eerie music continues]
[audience screaming]
["Flying Saucer
Rock & Roll" playing]
[all screaming and clamoring]
♪ Well, I came out of hidin'
And I started to rock ♪
[Cheryl screams and chuckles]
♪ Little green men
Taught me how to do the bop ♪
♪ They were three-foot-high
They hit a few bars ♪
♪ Rocked around the Moon
All the way from Mars ♪
[girl laughs]
♪ Flying saucer rock n' roll
I couldn't understand
A thing they said ♪
[audience applauding]
♪ But that crazy beat
Just stopped me dead ♪
[audience clamoring]
You care to explain
this novel, Dr. Werthers,
which I found in your desk?
Breaking into my office,
stealing my property.
So you admit it's yours?
Of course it's mine.
By reading about Lolita's mind,
I was hoping to better
understand yours, Betty.
You're comparing me
to Lolita.
Well, she, too,
is a sex-crazed young woman.
Dolores Haze is
a 12-year-old girl,
and she is not sex-crazed.
She is being coerced
against her will,
much like I am, Doctor.
So let me tell you
what I learned
from reading Lolita.
You are a kissing cousin
to Humbert Humbert,
only creepier.
And it is completely
inappropriate for you to be
asking me all these questions
about my sexual fantasies
and experiences
behind closed doors.
Manipulating our conversation,
feverishly writing down
every word that I say.
Doing God knows what
with that notebook
of yours at night.
You think I'm
obsessed with sex?
I think you're the one
who's obsessed
with sex, Doctor.
Dangerously so.
And I don't think you're
reading Lolita for research.
I think you're
reading it for pleasure
and some sick gratification,
and I no longer feel
comfortable being alone
in a room with you.
[all chattering indistinctly]
Excuse me.
Guess word got out, huh?
I'll say.
Our seven o'clock show
is already sold out.
Well, boys, we've got
a genuine hit on our hands.
Ready to play
to a full house tonight?
That's what we
wanted to talk about.
Veronica, we did this
as a personal favor
to you, and...
We were happy to, once.
[chuckles]
But this can't be a...
A regular thing.
I'll say this.
You two sure know
when to ask for a raise.
Because I respect your moxie
and your balls,
I'll pay you $2 per show
going forward.
Veronica, we can't do it, okay?
We have basketball practice.
We have games.
Seems to me
like you're playing hardball,
not basketball.
But here's the thing.
You're not the stars.
Those eyeballs are the stars.
You want to squeeze me,
I'm not interested.
I'll get Kevin and Clay
to do the gag. You can leave
your balls with them.
[Veronica sighs]
Yes, Reginald?
I was thinking...
Maybe after tonight's show,
we can try that date again?
I would, but...
did you see that
crowd out there?
I have to get on
the phone with Variety
and whip this buzz
into a story.
The Crawling Eye is going
to change everything
for the Babylonium.
Yeah.
But I'll tell you what.
Come by tomorrow,
and we'll see.
Okay.
Well, I think I've heard
just about everything now.
Just got off the phone
with Dr. Werthers,
and he wants to end
his sessions with you.
Great.
The feeling's mutual.
To which I told him,
under no circumstances
is he to give up on you.
Mom... Why?
Because he's going to fix you.
Whatever... Whatever
is wrong with you,
he is going to help me fix it.
There is nothing wrong with me.
I wish you would stop trying
to convince me otherwise.
-Who are you calling?
-Dr. Werthers.
I'm calling him back.
Put the phone down.
If you want to help me,
then talk to me.
Really, just talk to me.
Stop playing this stupid game
of telephone with Dr. Werthers.
Fine.
What would you like
to talk about, young lady?
Everything.
Starting with how unhappy
I think you are.
Unhappy? Me?
You must be.
[scoffs]
You don't know
what you're talking about,
young lady.
No, you're right.
I don't, so please
enlighten me.
Tell me why you'd
rather foist me off
to some quack psychiatrist
than just be honest with me,
your own daughter.
What happened?
Things didn't always used to be
so fraught between us.
Something must have happened.
If this is what you're
getting out of
the Dr. Werthers sessions,
then maybe you're right.
We should end them.
You once told me
that you were afraid for me.
Afraid of what
the world might do to me.
But why does it seem
like you're afraid of me?
-Oh, Betty.
-Please...
Just talk to me, Mom.
I'm... I'm right here.
-I...
-[Hal] What is going on here?
[sighs] Mom and I
are having a conversation, Dad.
Can you please leave us?
Leave?
This is my house.
And I heard the conversation
you were having, Betty.
Enough of it.
This woman...
is the most wonderful wife
and mother in the world.
And the way that
you've been acting,
you don't deserve her.
-Dad.
-[Hal] Just go to your room.
And do me a favor
and stay there.
And you think about
what you've put
your poor mother through.
-What I've put her through?
-[Hal] Yes.
When all she's done
is sacrifice for you.
How?
Somebody, please tell me how.
You know what?
Just go to your room,
young lady. Now.
[door slams]
Mom.
Good morning, Elizabeth.
[sighs]
Mom...
I want us to figure out
a path forward.
But it is not Dr. Werthers.
No. It's not.
[clicks tongue]
I relieved Dr. Werthers
of his duties this morning.
[sighs]
And mercifully, he's decided to
not press charges against you
for breaking into his office.
That's good.
Everything that
I have been trying
to do my entire life,
sacrificing for you,
protecting you,
trying to help you...
[sighs] It's obvious.
You don't want it.
So I'm stopping.
You have all the answers.
You know everything.
Seems to me that you don't
need a mother anymore.
Marvelous.
You don't have one.
What are you saying?
I am not your mother anymore.
And you can make
your own damn breakfast.
You sure she knows I'm here?
It's been half an hour.
Yeah, phone's been ringing
off the hook all day.
I'm sure she'll be down soon.
[Peter] I was surprised
and pleased
to read about your recent
box office success
in the trades.
I didn't even know
there was such a thing as 4D.
Yes, well, that's the kind
of business the Babylonium
is doing these days.
So I was curious
if you might want to
reconsider your decision
not to let us screen
any of your new releases.
[Peter] Oh, I am sure we can
work something out.
You know, I've always been
a fan of Riverdale.
Great town, superb audiences.
It's like no place else,
Mr. Roth.
So we'll be getting
that print of East of Eden
for the weekend, I take it?
It's already heading your way.
Fab.
Looking forward to a long,
fruitful collaboration, Peter.
Can I call you Peter?
All right, Reginald.
Sorry to have kept you...
waiting.
-Where's Reggie?
-He got tired of waiting.
He left those for you, though.
[clears throat]
Smithers,
there seems to be something
wrong with my lock.
I'm afraid, Miss Veronica,
that the locks
have been changed.
Your parents no longer feel
that you need or deserve
their financial support
now that you're such
a roaring success.
As soon as you have
a new address,
I'm to move your belongings.
An eye for a crawling eye.
As for my address,
I already know
where I'll be staying.
In the short term, at least.
[elevator dings]
[sighs]
["Start at the Bottom" playing]
♪ You've got to
Start at the bottom ♪
♪ If you're ever gonna
Reach the top ♪
♪ You've got to
Watch all the seeds you sowed ♪
♪ Don't let 'em go to pot ♪
♪ You've got to
Live by the golden rule ♪
♪ Live what they teach
In the Sunday school ♪
♪ Start at the bottom ♪
♪ If you're ever gonna
Reach the top ♪
♪ When Jacob
Climbed his ladder ♪
♪ He started at the bottom... ♪
[song continues faintly
on jukebox]
What can I get you this round,
Jughead?
Chocolate, vanilla, strawberry?
[sighs]
I think just the check, Pop.
I've been re-reading
all of Mr. Rayberry's work
and I've noticed some
recurring themes.
Time passes,
seasons change,
life moves on, you know?
I... I don't know
if I'm done mourning,
but I...
I think I'm done wallowing.
I think I'm ready to move on.
I think he'd want me
to move on.
I'm glad to hear it.
[siren wailing in distance]
[bell dinging]
Jughead, we're still working
the Rayberry suicide case.
We need your help
if we're gonna solve it.
[Jughead]
So much for moving on.