[Jughead] The popularity
and cultural impact
of comic books in our time
cannot be overstated.
Superheroes were out, horror
and crime comics were in,
and me and my friends
were obsessed.
What the hell?
You've got to be kidding me.
Guys, you're not
gonna believe this.
Do you remember
when I submitted my story
to Pep Comics
and I received that asinine
form rejection letter?
Well, they stole my story,
and published it.
Stole it? You mean
word for word?
Well, not word for word,
but it's definitely my story.
Well, I should sue 'em, right?
Can you prove
it was your story?
Maybe start by
giving them a call.
Oh, shucks to that.
Pep Comics is right here
in town. I'm gonna
go pay 'em a visit.
Who's with me?
[xylophone chimes]
Good morning, Riverdalians.
Let's begin with the most
exciting news ever,
which is that the
entertainment committee,
chaired by yours truly,
is hosting its first
dance of the year.
Our annual sock hop
taking place this Friday night.
As is customary, no shoes will
be allowed on the gym floor.
So, boys, before you ask
your best girls out,
make sure that your
socks match and that
they don't have any holes.
In short, the whole event
is sure to be the bee's knees
and the cat's pajamas.
Tickets will be
on sale all week,
and you'll want to snap them up
early as I can now confirm
that Kevin and the Crooners
will be headlining.
See you all there.
[bell rings]
Hey, Veronica?
I was wondering if you wanted
to go to the sock hop with me.
That depends.
Can you cut a rug?
Are you a good dancer?
Oh, yeah, of course I am.
Well, I'm sure I believe you,
but I'm still going to need
a demonstration, daddy-o.
Toni Topaz. Here to buy your
ticket to the sock hop, I hope.
That depends.
Are you asking me out?
What? Why, of course not.
No, I'm...
I am hosting the dance.
I couldn't possibly
be saddled with a date.
Not to mention that you're...
And I'm also...
-Um, and girls don't--
-Don't what?
Dance with other girls?
Calm down, Peggy Sue.
No, I'm not buying a ticket.
My pal Fangs here
is a singer,
and we were hoping
that you could give him a shot
at playing at the sock hop.
You should add
him to the lineup.
And the Serpents
will be there in full force.
Hmm, and start a rumble
as greasers are wont to do?
No, thank you.
Kevin and the Crooners
will be performing,
as previously announced.
Well, we offered.
Good luck selling tickets
with that B-grade
barbershop quartet.
Later, Midge.
[phone ringing]
[door opens]
Okay, Bernie, who's the kid?
He's a writer, Al.
Says we stole
one of his stories.
All right, come on in.
Tell me your tale of woe.
So you're accusing me
of what, exactly?
Well, I submitted a story,
then you rejected it.
And then, surprise, surprise,
you ran a story
that was exactly like it.
Now, you might call that
a coincidence, but I...
call it theft.
Well, I hate to burst
your bubble, kid,
but, uh,
I got news for you.
There are no original ideas.
I mean, I get hundreds
of submissions every week.
It's all the same slop.
But the timing, the details.
Oh, you want proof?
These filing cabinets here,
they're filled with every
single story germ I ever had.
I got a backlog just waiting
to be farmed out
to any hack
who can string together
a semi-coherent sentence.
Waiting?
Like you're looking
for writers?
-Always.
-Well, I'm a writer.
If I wanted to be considered,
what would I have to do?
Well, first off, drop
the persecution complex.
Listen, take this log line.
Turn it into a seven-page story
by tomorrow morning.
And if it doesn't make me
want to puke, we'll talk.
[Archie] Thanks for helping
me out of this jam, Betty.
I panicked, told Veronica
that I can dance
when the truth is,
I got two left feet.
You remember when
I broke Midge's big toe
doing the bunny hop.
[chuckles] I do.
But don't worry.
We will start with something
simple and classic.
The twist.
[record scratching]
[instrumental
pop music playing]
Okay, so start just by
moving your hips
from side to side like this.
Try it.
-Like this?
-No, less of shoulders,
more hips.
Okay.
Like this? I can't...
No. Maybe you just need
to focus on slow dancing.
Everyone knows
how to slow dance.
["Be Mine" playing]
Okay.
One hand goes like this.
The other hand, here.
And then you just sway.
♪ For the rest of my life ♪
[Betty chuckles]
That's it?
Yeah, it's
pretty simple, right?
♪ I can put aside
My foolish pride ♪
♪ I'm begging you, please ♪
♪ Be mine ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ For the rest of my life... ♪
[door opens]
[gasps] And what
exactly is going on here?
Betty was just
showing me some moves,
Mrs. Cooper.
I'm giving Archie
a dance lesson.
-[music stops]
-He's asking out the new girl.
She's a celebrity
from Hollywood.
Goodbye, Archie.
Bye, Betty.
Goodbye, Mrs. Cooper.
Oh, thank your
sweet mother for agreeing
to chaperone with me.
Give me
your expert opinion, Ethel.
I can take it.
I'm so jealous of you, Jughead.
It's my life's goal to draw
a story for Pep Comics.
They... They work with some
of the best artists in the biz.
Oh, come on. You're as good
as any of those clowns, Ethel.
I'll tell you what. If I can
finish these pages
and really make them sing,
then I'll put your name forward
to Mr. Fieldstone tomorrow.
He's our editor-in-chief.
Really?
Jughead, that would...
That would be a dream.
-Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
-[chuckles] Well...
Let's see what he says first.
["Baby Let's Make
Some Love" playing]
-[engine whirring]
-Yoo-hoo! Sorry to interrupt.
Just wanted to make sure
that everyone had their
tickets to the sock hop.
Midge Klump? One
of my precious Vixens
with a common greaser?
Sacrilege!
You get out of that car
right this minute!
[Midge] Calm down! I'm coming.
[Cheryl] Go!
-[engine whirring]
-["Teenage Love"
playing on radio]
Is everything okay, Kev?
Yeah, sure.
Just a little...
preoccupied, I guess.
Thinking about what songs
you're gonna sing
at the sock hop?
Yeah. Yeah, and other things.
You know, you haven't
officially asked me
to the sock hop yet.
Oh, uh, well, I'm performing.
So I just kind of assumed
you'd come to, you know,
cheer me on.
Right, yeah, of course.
That makes sense.
Um...
What is it?
Don't you like kissing me?
Of course.
It's like I said, I'm...
I'm performing
and I don't want to risk
catching a cold.
It's always
something with you.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means we've
been dating for months
and we're still not
going steady.
You haven't even
pinned me yet.
How am I supposed to pin you?
I don't even
play a varsity sport--
Doesn't need to be
a varsity pin, Kev.
It can be any old pin.
Can be a ring, even.
Gosh, when did you become
such a sex maniac?
For your information,
the fact that I want
my supposed boyfriend
to kiss me once every blue moon
does not make me a sex maniac,
and I do not have
cold germs or cooties,
and I will definitely
not be cheering you on
at the sock hop.
Betty... Betty.
[Mr. Fieldstone]
Well, it's pretentious, clunky,
too much dialogue.
But it'll do.
Bernie, get in here.
Wha...
-Yes, Mr. Fieldstone.
-[Mr. Fieldstone]
We got a live one here.
Now, see who's available to
draw a seven-page zombie story
for immediate publication.
So, I'm hired?
A dollar a page.
Take it or leave it.
Yeah, I'll take it.
And, um, I know an artist,
an incredible artist.
Young, hungry, cheap,
loves monster movies.
A real fiend for gore.
Okay.
But I want those pages
tomorrow.
Yeah, you'll have 'em.
And, um...
Thank you for everything,
Mr. Fieldstone.
[piano playing]
[piano playing stops]
Sorry, um...
I... I didn't know
the music room
was reserved.
It's not. I was just
horsing around,
but you probably need it
to rehearse, I'm guessing.
Uh, my set
for the sock hop, yeah.
You're Clay Walker, right?
I am. Just
transferred this year.
And you're Kevin Keller.
Son of the sheriff,
dating the prettiest girl
at Riverdale High.
[chuckles softly]
I've done my research.
Uh, where did you
transfer from?
All over. My dad's in the...
Was in the military.
Cool. Cool.
Are you going to the sock hop?
I wouldn't have a date.
I don't know many people.
Unless, uh, you could think
of someone I should ask.
A lot of people go stag here.
It's nice to meet you.
Hey. Uh, so I did
a little brushing up
and I'm ready
for that demonstration.
How do you feel
about slow dancing?
Nothing better.
But upon further reflection,
I have no doubt
a Troy Donahue type
like you
can trip the light
fantastic, Archie.
So does that mean...
But, quite candidly,
I'm also entertaining
other offers.
What? Oh...
Wow, okay.
However, being my escort
demands more than mere dancing.
It also requires
scintillating conversation.
I need to know that you won't
be a bore at the sock hop.
So, why don't you
clean yourself up
and come by the Pembrooke
at 6:00-ish tonight?
I'll be wanting to discuss
politics, art, current events.
Dazzle me with your wit.
Okay?
Dazzle you. Okay.
Well, I should motor.
[Veronica] See you tonight.
Archiekins?
[clears throat]
I'm rooting for you, stud.
[exhales]
So they just do whatever
you say, is that it?
Hmm?
Oh, you mean boys? [chuckles]
Boys aren't
too, too complicated.
I wish I had your confidence.
Why don't you?
What do you mean?
I mean, I'm only just getting
my sea legs here in Riverdale,
but I can already tell
you're a catch, Betty.
A total Marilyn.
You and Kevin the Crooner
are going steady, aren't you?
Um, not officially.
We may even be on the rocks.
That's a shame...
for him.
Why don't you invite
some other boy to the sock hop?
Get Kevin all hot and bothered.
That's always fun, keeping
our beaus on their toes.
Surely there's some He-Man
at Riverdale High
you'd like to make time with.
Tickets. Get your
tickets to the sock hop.
Buy one, get one free.
You... Dilton Doiley.
-Why haven't you bought
a ticket to my sock hop yet?
-Uh...
For that matter,
why are some people
trying to return their tickets?
Um... It might be because
of the Serpents.
What about the Serpents?
What are they planning?
They said they were going to be
waiting in the parking lot,
and they're gonna throw
rotten eggs at anyone
who tries going to the dance.
Barbarians.
And who, pray tell,
is the one
making these threats.
Mostly that scary Toni girl.
Of course. It would be her.
Well, this means war.
Dismissed.
[Archie] Mom?
[chuckles]
Can you help?
[sighs] Hang on.
I might have something
that'll do the trick.
[Mary chuckles]
Oh, that's more like it.
I think I'll have to
let it out a little bit,
but other than that,
it fits perfectly.
It's a little old-fashioned,
isn't it?
Well, it was your dad's,
but he'd want you to wear it,
especially to your first dance.
[chuckles] Well, actually,
I need it tonight, Mom.
Yeah. Veronica asked me over.
You're taking her to the dance?
If I'm lucky.
She wants to give me
a test run, you could say?
I don't like the sound of that.
A bit haughty, isn't it?
It's not like that.
Veronica is from Los Angeles
and she's practically
a movie star.
Standards
are different out there.
-Aw, geez, Mom. [chuckles]
-[Mary] I'm fine.
It's just, seeing you
here in his suit,
it just brings back
so many memories.
[sighs]
You know, your father and I
went to the sock hop together.
He was such a romantic
and he wrote me
the sweetest poems.
I still have them somewhere.
Poems?
He knew how
to make a girl swoon.
This one, I think.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
[Archie] So, Veronica
invited me over to her
place tonight, and...
I need to impress her.
So don't laugh...
but I wrote her a poem.
I just need someone
to read it and just
tell me if it's crazy
to give to her.
Okay. Hand it over,
Walt Whitman.
Well, is it terrible?
No.
It's actually really sweet.
You have a poet's soul, Arch.
Who knew?
[jazz music playing]
[Cheryl] So this is where
the Serpents dwell.
I always imagined
it'd be something
more like a biker bar,
but this...
-This is--
-The Dark Room is
a coffeehouse for bikers,
beatniks and badasses.
Which begs the question,
what are you
doing here, preppy?
Better question.
Why are you so hell-bent
on ruining my sock hop
the same way
your slimy Serpent pal
tried to ruin
my virtuous Vixen?
Okay, Cheryl. You want people
at your dance, I dig it.
So I'll pitch it again.
Let my boy Fangs
blow the roof off the gym
and we'll pack the place.
For the bazillionth time,
I have already booked
Kevin and the Crooners.
Yeah, the Crooners
are doneskis.
Look, Fangs is about to play.
So why don't you order
yourself a cappuccino,
take a load off
and hear him play?
Maybe you'll change your mind
and you and I can
get better acquainted.
[elevator dings]
[knocks on door]
-Archie, you made it.
-Am I late?
Oh, not at all, lover boy.
We were just discussing
President Eisenhower's decision
to run for a second term.
And let me warn you,
the others are very divided.
[chuckles]
-I'm sorry. Others?
-Come. Come on in.
We're having aperitifs
in the parlor.
[boys chattering]
[Betty] Mom,
can I ask your advice
about something?
Well, of course, honey.
What is it?
I think I'm having
weird feelings about Archie.
Oh. What sort of feelings?
Like, stirrings?
When we were dancing,
I felt a flutter in my stomach.
Is it possible that
this fluttering is
a reaction to feeling
underappreciated by Kevin?
I hadn't thought
of it that way.
Which is why it's a good thing
that you came to me.
Holy hell, Ethel.
There is no way
that Mr. Fieldstone
doesn't hire you
after he sees these.
-You really think so?
-Yeah.
Even though I'm a girl?
[chuckles] If he doesn't,
I'll eat my own crown.
So, uh, Jughead,
the sock hop's tomorrow night.
It is?
What if we went together?
Like, for kicks?
Yeah, yeah, just for kicks.
Might be fun.
Could have a decent
spread, cookies and whatnot.
[knock at door]
Since when are boys
allowed in your room?
We're just studying, Mom.
Well, whatever you were doing,
you're lucky your father's
working nights
at the factory this week.
I was actually just leaving.
I'll see you
at school tomorrow.
Excuse me. Sorry.
So then I said,
"Sorry, Mr. Sinatra,
-but I think Elvis
sang it better."
-[all laughing]
[boy] Oh, no.
Archie, are you all right?
You've been quiet all night.
Yeah, I'm good.
I was just...
I was just taking it all in.
-Soaking it up.
-Like the sponge that you are.
[men laughing]
I see you're
admiring the painting.
-It's a--
-It's a Monet. Am I right?
Indeed. You have
a connoisseur's eyes, Julian.
I appreciate beautiful things.
Every summer,
my family goes on
an art-buying tour in Europe.
Archie, what do you
think of the painting?
[slurps]
Um...
It's beautiful and all, uh...
I guess I just prefer
an artist like Norman Rockwell.
Then again, I'm not
really an art tour
through Europe kind of guy.
-So--
-That's obvious from what
you're wearing, chump.
Where'd you get that suit?
Some thrift store?
[boys chuckling]
It's my father's suit.
And you better
shut your trap, Blossom.
Wasn't he buried in his suit?
Or did he have more than one?
He was buried in his uniform.
Well, I, for one, think
you look very striking, Archie.
And I like a bit of variety
in my men's attire,
as well as in my men.
So, who's up for charades?
You know, Veronica,
it has been
a real swell night,
but, uh... I think I'm just
gonna blow out of here.
If I stay any longer,
I might be liable to spill
someone's blue blood
all over your nice,
expensive things.
[door slams]
Good morning, Mrs. Andrews.
As you may know,
I'm Veronica Lodge.
Is Archie home,
by any chance?
He's at the grocery store.
Shopping? This early?
Archie told me everything
that happened last night.
Well, that's
actually why I'm here.
I feel terrible about it.
I didn't mean for things
to happen the way they did.
My Archie is not
some Hollywood playboy.
He's a simple boy. So simple
that he's mad at Julian Blossom
and himself for what happened
at your little soiree,
when you and I both know
who the real villainess was.
[scoffs] I mean,
what kind of person
auditions boys
to go to a sock hop?
Well, when your parents
are actors... [chuckles]
Sorry. That's not an excuse.
Listen, if you hurt my boy,
you and I are going to have
some serious trouble,
Little Miss Femme Fatale.
-[Alice] Thanks
for stopping by, Kevin.
-[liquid pouring]
-High Point?
-Okay.
So, Betty tells me
that the two of you
have had some
troubles as of late.
Would you agree?
I feel awful, Mrs. Cooper.
It's like... Betty wants
these things from me,
but I'm not sure
if I can give them to her.
It's perfectly normal
for girls Betty's age
to have certain... [inhales]
...expectations of
what their boyfriends
are willing to do.
May I make a suggestion?
I'm going to give you this.
You see, Betty
just wants to be pinned.
She wants to feel appreciated.
And then all of those...
feelings will settle.
But won't a pin mean
she'll expect more from me?
Oh, no. A pin
takes off the pressure.
You see, it's a symbol
for what every girl craves.
They just...
They just want a fella
that's going to carry
their books home from school
or take them to the movies
Saturday night
or call them on the telephone
before supper.
Is that all?
A pin is a promise, Kevin.
Don't tell anyone,
but this is the actual pin
that Mr. Cooper gave me
back in high school.
See, this pin
somehow answered a desire
that we both were feeling,
and then things were
fine and pure
from that point forward.
You're a good boy, Kevin.
And Betty is a good girl.
And I believe that this pin
will take care of everything.
[chuckles nervously]
Tickets. Get your tickets
for tonight's sock hop.
-Hurry up!
-You, four eyes.
Get your tickets to
the sock hop yet?
Uh... no.
Well, pony up, poindexter,
because my pal
Fangs Fogarty is performing.
And trust me,
you'll be kicking yourself
if you miss it.
I'll take one.
Five. I'll take five.
By the way, did you, uh,
break the bad news
to Kevin yet?
No. But I will.
Can you dig it?
[bell rings]
Putting aside the fact
that you were drawing
while Dr. Doiley
was lecturing,
in and of itself
a flagrant violation
of school etiquette.
Dr. Werthers and I are also
deeply concerned about
what you were drawing.
Where did the vision
for this come from, Ethel?
Your subconscious?
A nightmare? The movies?
They're for a story.
What kind of story?
A comic book.
That I'm on deadline to finish.
That's why I was drawing
in Dr. Doiley's class.
I'm... I'm trying to
get a job at Pep Comics.
They're based here in town.
I'm sorry, Ethel,
but your budding career
as an illustrator of
lurid comic books
doesn't remotely justify
this behavior.
You have a week's detention,
starting today.
[Archie] Veronica.
Archie. Hi.
Look, about last night...
I'm sorry I rushed
out of there like that.
I, uh...
I sincerely was going to
rip Julian Blossom's head off.
[chuckles] Well,
he would have deserved it.
And I'm mortified about
what he said to you.
I truly had a good time
getting to know you better.
Well, um, in that case,
if you haven't made
your decision yet,
I'm still keen on taking you
to the sock hop tonight.
I would love that, Archie,
but I've already
made my selection.
And...
I'm not going with anyone.
-What? Why?
-[Veronica sighs]
With so many excellent options,
it's simply impossible
for an it girl to choose.
Options like Julian Blossom?
[scoffs]
You know,
I don't get you, Veronica.
I mean, what was last night's
dog-and-pony show
all about then?
I mean, forget last night.
This entire week.
Making us... Making me
jump through hoops like that?
It was a game, Archie.
The queen of the hive
gets all her worker bees abuzz
and then flies away before...
Before anyone's
stung too badly.
[Betty] So, have you
made your pick yet?
Here's a late-breaking scoop
for Hedda Hopper.
Socialite Veronica Lodge
has decided to go stag
to the sock hop.
Well, what happened?
What about Archie?
I'm in the midst of
a rude awakening, Betty.
Turns out I've been
careless and thoughtless
with a lot of the boys
at Riverdale High.
Archie most especially,
and most undeservingly.
Did you not like his poem?
What poem?
Archie wrote you a poem.
Did he not give it to you?
Not that I know of.
Not that I deserve,
in any case.
Wait a minute. So who's Archie
going to the sock hop with?
No one, as far as I know.
I'll tell you
one thing, though.
Whoever does
end up going with Archie,
she is one lucky girl.
Hey, Betty,
can I talk to you
for a second?
It's important.
Sure, let's talk.
Cheryl bumped me
and the Crooners.
Fangs Fogarty's performing.
Apparently, he's God's gift
or something. [scoffs]
I heard. Kev, I'm sorry.
No, uh... I'm sorry.
Betty, I'm really...
I'm really sorry.
I was a dope.
And you are the most wonderful,
most ginchiest girl
in the world,
and I took that for granted.
That won't happen again. Um...
Betty Cooper,
will you go steady with me?
-Kevin...
-Things will be
different this time.
I promise. I...
I love you, Betty. I do.
And you make
my heart feel full.
So will you be my girl?
Will you go
to the sock hop with me?
Yeah, of course.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. [chuckles]
All right.
Um...
Uh...
-[chuckles nervously]
How do I...
-I'll... I'll do it.
Okay.
[Kevin, softly] All right.
[knock at door]
Guess who didn't show up
for her assigned detention?
The Muggs girl.
I'm concerned, Felix.
I... I think we should speak
to Ethel's parents.
God knows
what's troubling that girl.
Now, you want me to believe
that a girl, this girl,
generated these pages?
Yes, and she's currently
skipping detention
because of how badly she wants
to draw comic books for you,
Mr. Fieldstone.
[inhales] Well, young lady,
let me congratulate you.
These are the most putrid pages
I've seen in a long time.
And that's the highest
compliment I can give
any artist.
Freckles, you have
some real talent.
What's your name?
Ethel.
Thank you, Mr. Fieldstone.
Well, freckles,
you and boy wonder here
make a terrific team.
So, what are you,
boyfriend-girlfriend?
Uh, no.
We are just creative partners.
-But we are going
to the sock hop together.
-Ah.
[knock at door]
Smithers. I'm about
to put my face on.
My apologies, Miss Veronica.
But I was emptying the bins
and came across something
that I believe belongs to you.
What's this?
It seems to be a poem, miss.
Mom, Dad,
is everything all right?
We got called
down to your school.
They said you're acting
like some delinquent.
Drawing dirty pictures.
[Mrs. Muggs] On top of
staying up at all hours,
inviting boys into your bedroom
and now missing detention?
We did not raise
you this way, Ethel.
Maybe if you didn't
drink so much, Mom.
And maybe if you weren't so
miserable all of the time, Dad.
The hell did
you just say to me?
Never mind.
[Mr. Muggs] Where
do you think you're going?
I'm going to the sock hop
with Jughead.
-Over my dead body, you are.
-[door slams]
["Strange Love" playing]
♪ Doobie, doobie, doobie
Doobie, do, wha-wha ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Well, I don't know
what it could be ♪
♪ Something about you
That really kills me ♪
♪ Could it be
the way that you walk? ♪
♪ Or it could be
the way that you talk ♪
♪ Well, it's something
I can't explain ♪
♪ My love came down
Like falling rain ♪
♪ Ooh, baby
You thrill me so ♪
♪ I'll never let you go ♪
♪ All through my life
I have looked
for a girl like you... ♪
If it isn't Kevin of Kevin
and the Crooners fame.
Yeah, hardly.
Just plain old
Kevin Keller tonight.
I was sorry to hear
that tonight's lineup
had been changed.
Oh, easy come, easy go.
Supposedly, Fangs is an
out-of-this-world singer.
Yeah, and he sure is
easy on the eyes.
But I can say
the same about you.
Anyway, I was...
I was really looking forward
to seeing you perform tonight.
Maybe you can
give me a private concert
one of these days?
Yeah.
Um, look, Clay, uh,
Betty's waiting for her punch,
-so if you'll excuse me?
-Of course. Have fun tonight.
[amplifier hums]
Good evening, Riverdale High.
-Who's ready to rock 'n' roll?
-[audience exclaiming]
Well, in that case,
find somebody to hold on to...
because we're about
to shake things up.
♪ A wop bop-b-luma
B-lop bam bom ♪
[audience cheering]
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rooty
Tutti frutti, oh rooty ♪
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rooty ♪
♪ A wop bop-b-luma
B-lop bam bom ♪
♪ I got a girl
Named Sue ♪
♪ She knows just what to do ♪
♪ I got a girl
Named Sue ♪
♪ She knows just what to do ♪
♪ She rocks to the east
She rocks to the west ♪
♪ But she's the girl
That I love best ♪
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rooty
Tutti frutti, oh rooty ♪
♪ Whoo, tutti frutti, oh rooty
Tutti frutti, oh rooty... ♪
Told you Fangs was
the next Chuck Berry.
[chuckles]
I wouldn't go that far.
Come on, let's see your moves.
I'm fine supervising
from right here.
-Thank you very much.
-One boogie woogie
and I'll stop hassling you
if that's what you really want.
Fine.
But just one dance.
♪ She knows how to love me
Yes, indeed ♪
♪ Boy, you don't know
What she do to me ♪
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rooty
Tutti frutti, oh rooty ♪
♪ Whoo, tutti frutti, oh rooty
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rooty ♪
♪ A wop bop-b-luma
B-lop bam bom ♪
["Only You" playing]
♪ Only you ♪
♪ Can make all this
World seem right ♪
♪ Only you ♪
I got the poem
you wrote for me.
Or at least I think you did.
"A stolen look across the hall.
I hope she hears
my silent call.
Dreams of walks
through moonlit nights
with the girl more beautiful
than all the cosmic sights."
It's beautiful, Archie.
Um... It barely rhymes.
How do you feel
about a do-over?
Or, to put it in other words,
Archie Andrews,
may I have this dance?
I'm sorry, Veronica.
Maybe next time.
Will you excuse me?
Of course.
Veronica Lodge.
Julian Blossom.
Where have you been
keeping yourself?
Oh, I've been around.
Waiting for my moment.
You could do a lot worse,
you know.
[sighs]
[Veronica] Why not?
♪ And fill my heart
With love ♪
♪ For only you ♪
♪ Oh, only you ♪
♪ Can make all this
Change in me ♪
♪ For it's true ♪
♪ You are my destiny ♪
Boys and girls dancing
in chaste harmony.
Just as God intended.
Wouldn't you agree,
Ms. Blossom?
Yes, everything is
as it's meant to be.
♪ Only you ♪
♪ Can make all this
World seem right ♪
♪ Only you ♪
♪ Can make
The darkness bright ♪
Ethel?
Ethel! Ethel.
Ethel.
[Ethel breathing heavily]
Is this blood?
[voice shaking] Jughead...
Something terrible
has happened.
[Ethel sobs]
♪ Oh, only you ♪
♪ Can make all this
Change in me ♪
♪ For it's true ♪
♪ You are my destiny ♪