[Jughead] Some towns
are football towns,
some are hockey towns.
Riverdale High had
a so-so football team.
And in the dead of winter,
kids played hockey
on Sweetwater River
once it had frozen solid.
But at its heart,
Riverdale was
a basketball town.
Long past its heyday,
some would say,
which was when
the Riverdale High Bulldogs,
led by point guard
Fred Andrews,
were state champions
three years running.
[students groan]
-[buzzer sounds]
-[grunts]
[announcer] That's another
big loss for Riverdale.
[players cheering]
Hey, look, fellas.
We fought
the good fight out there.
We got the rest of the season
to dust ourselves off,
get back on top.
Not if we keep playing
like pansies.
You're all a bunch
of spineless,
pillow-soft chumps.
You're lucky my parents
still sponsor us.
We're a panic
and a half!
Cut the gas, Captain.
Nobody's jazzed
about what happened out there.
The Bulldogs?
We used to be unstoppable.
Back when your dad played,
they were the champs,
not the chumps.
Now, I know that you don't want
to spoil that legacy.
[door clangs]
[crickets chirping]
What did Mr. Blossom want?
I finally convinced
our lead sponsor
to let me recruit
an outside player.
A kid who knows
how to win games.
You know me, I'll take
any help we can get.
Who's the guy? A ringer?
No, he's a farm kid
out of Duck Creek.
6'3", 220 lbs.
Pure muscle, but fast.
What's his name?
Mantle.
Reggie "The Blur" Mantle.
-The Blur?
-'Cause you never
see him coming.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Well, gee, I wish
I had a little girl like you ♪
♪ Yes, gee, I wish
♪ Well, nobody, nobody
Knows what I would do ♪
You know, I've been thinking.
What if you and I went steady?
Went steady?
How would that work?
It's not like you can pin me
or like we can walk down
the halls holding hands.
I know, but it could
be just for us.
Our secret... only we know.
Unless you don't want to.
It's just kind of a thing
squares do.
You know? Go steady.
That's a fair point.
Anyway...
It's kind of like we're
already secretly going steady
if you think about it. So...
-[grunts]
-[birds chirping]
You sure I can't
give you a hand?
No, I'm good.
So you're from Korea?
My mom's Korean.
My dad was born here,
I was born here.
My Uncle Frank said you played
basketball for Stonewall Prep.
What happened?
You writing a book?
There's not much to tell.
I dropped out.
[Frank] I had a great chat
with your folks, Reggie.
We're all squared away
if you want to say
your see-you-laters.
All right.
Archie and Frank told me
that you grew up on a farm.
Yes, ma'am.
What was that like?
The farm's everything we have.
It's our family's legacy.
My dad came home from the war
with a chunk of shrapnel
stuck in his shoulder,
so, it slowed him down.
I couldn't let the family
business fall behind,
so I stepped up.
Pitching in as much as I can.
What about the GI Bill?
Doesn't the government
help you out?
The army doesn't
give us any money.
We're not considered eligible.
Well, we are. Why not you guys?
Why do you think?
That's terrible.
Mayor Blossom will make sure
your family's farm
stays afloat financially.
So you can just concentrate
on playing ball.
Thanks, Coach.
[Archie]
This is your cot.
Some more blankets
down the hall
if you get cold or anything.
Oh, I emptied a drawer.
If you need any more space,
I can make some...
Who is that?
Uh, that is my neighbor.
Uh, you'll meet her at school.
We're actually supposed
to be keeping our curtains
closed from now on.
[knock on door]
Betty, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Sure, Dad. What's the word?
Uh, well, I was talking
to Dr. Werthers.
He wonders if it
might not be prudent
to get you exercising more.
You know, to burn off
some of your excess energy.
He doesn't want me to go back
on Riverdale Grandstand,
does he?
No, no, no, no.
He, uh, he says too many
temptations there.
Hmm. Boys.
Well, he wondered if you...
If you might not fare better
spending more time
with nice, decent girls.
Hmm. Unlike Veronica.
Now, I've spoken
with Clifford Blossom,
and he's going to
arrange it all with Cheryl.
Cheryl? What does Cheryl
have to do with any of this?
Um, well, Dr. Werthers thinks,
and your mother and I
both agree,
you should join the Vixens.
[scoffs]
Well, you looked snappy
at the game, Topaz.
Never seen a wool sweater
filled out so nicely.
Thanks for the
apple butter, Lizzo.
[chuckles] And let me guess.
You and the queen
of the paper shakers
got chummy in the janitor's
closet afterwards?
More or less.
Nice work, if you can get it.
You figured out a good hustle.
You find these ripe cherries
knowing they're in the closet,
which means there's
a shelf life on them.
Can get what you want
and move on.
No fuss, no muss.
Look. I gotta boogie.
I'll catch you later.
[Tabitha] It's so good
to see you, Toni.
You too, Tabitha.
How's the tour with
Mrs. Till been going?
[sighs deeply]
Well, let me tell you,
she has been so strong.
So inspiring.
But the tour itself...
Going from town to town
and seeing up close
what some people are
capable of doing?
The inhumanity, the hatred.
-The racial injustice.
-I can only imagine.
Now give me the scoop.
What have you been
doing to keep busy?
Well... [sighs] Don't laugh,
but I'm a cheerleader.
You are?
That's fun.
But you are still writing
for the Blue and Gold, I hope.
Honestly, I haven't been
doing much writing lately.
No.
So Betty Cooper
is now a River Vixen?
Newly minted as of last night.
Much to my chagrin,
might I add.
And you now own the Babylonium.
The paperwork was
finalized this morning.
Right. And weren't you
the popcorn girl two days ago?
What can I say?
Veronica Lodge likes
to burn rubber.
Hey, gang.
Do you mind if we join you?
That all depends.
Are you going to introduce us
to your strapping flutter bum
of a new pal?
Hey. I'm Reggie Mantle.
I just got recruited
to the Bulldogs.
Ah, I suspected a tall
drink of water like you
was a sportsman.
Careful, Veronica.
You might get a ticket
for speeding.
Hi. I'm Cheryl Blossom.
My parents sponsor
the Bulldogs,
and I am the captain
of Riverdale High's
cheerleading squad, the Vixens.
So we'll be working
closely together.
What about you?
You a cheerleader?
I am. I'm Betty.
Nice to meet you, neighbor.
[Veronica and Kevin] Neighbor?
Reggie's bunking with us.
Yeah, he's gonna help
turn things around
for the Bulldogs.
Well, he's already
turned my day around.
[chuckles softly]
But fill us in, Reginald.
Where are you from?
What you do for kicks?
And do you like the movies?
There isn't a theater
in Duck Creek.
My family and I,
we don't have a TV set.
Oh, well, you must come
to the Babylonium here in town.
It's a movie palace I own.
I own my own business, yes.
[exhales]
Or if you're interested
in picking up some
part-time work,
I'm always on the hunt
for a few good men.
[Cheryl] You'll have
to excuse Veronica.
Clearly, she was raised
by wolves.
I appreciate
the, uh, invitation,
but I'm just here
to play basketball
and win games.
Speaking of, where's the gym?
[all] I could show you.
Come on. I'll take you.
[school bell ringing]
Don't I know you?
Weren't you the guy
who was supposed to help me
keep track of my homework
from afar?
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry.
[sputters] Tabitha, I...
I got preoccupied. I...
It's... It's okay.
It was actually much
easier to coordinate
with Principal Featherhead
than I anticipated.
So you are hereby absolved.
[sighs, chuckles]
Well, that's a relief.
So, tell me,
why are you so preoccupied?
Oh, I... I got a job.
I'm writing comic books.
Oh! How fun. What kind?
It's a broad range,
but I also got to meet
and start working
for a literary hero of mine,
Brad Rayberry.
Oh, my gosh.
I know Brad Rayberry,
I mean, not personally,
but I've read his books.
His stories.
You read science fiction?
I read across all genres,
including science fiction.
Say, would you want
to meet him?
Would it be an imposition?
No, no, not at all.
It's, um... negative
perspiration.
[both chuckle]
I'm sure he would love it.
Okay. Great.
[romantic music playing]
Veronica. Hey.
Kevin.
Don't tell me
you're here to see
Singin' in the Rain again.
I would think you'd have
the whole picture
memorized by now.
I do, and I'm not. I...
I'm actually here because
I wanted to see about
getting a job.
At school, you mentioned
you were looking for...
A few good men. Yes, I am.
Since I called it quits
with the basketball team,
I've been looking
for something to do,
and I love the movies.
Well, that's my
biggest prerequisite.
And you're already
pals with Clay.
I am.
Well, he's up
in the projection booth
even as we speak.
But maybe you could
help me with something.
Yeah, with what?
Well, between us...
I happen to think Clay is...
extremely dashing.
I've been dropping hints
that I'm interested
in something
more than a professional
relationship with him.
But so far, no bites.
Maybe you could help me
suss him out a bit.
Um, do you mean, like...
Like is he
seeing anyone,
that sort of thing?
Yeah, maybe.
Well, in that case,
when can you start?
[whistle blows]
All right, you turkeys.
Bring it in.
We have ourselves
a new player.
His name is Reggie Mantle.
So let's see what he can do.
We are going to split up
into two teams.
Julian, you're captain
of one team.
Reggie, you've got the other.
Everyone else, pick a side.
Come on, guys.
We can't have a game
if it's three against seven.
We'll take Doiley too.
That'll be enough.
The water boy?
[Reggie] Yeah.
-[Julian] What is this, a gag?
-Can it, Julian.
Dilton, you up for it?
Well, come on.
[upbeat music playing]
[cheering]
[boys gloating]
[boy] Yeah!
[Frank] Thirty-eight, all.
Anyone's game.
[cheering]
[grunts]
Let's go. Game point.
-[blows whistle]
-[cheering]
Yes! Yes!
[all cheering]
Guys, how about we get
some burgers at Pop's?
Reggie hasn't tried 'em yet.
Come on. It's our
post-practice tradition.
What gives?
Actually, I can't.
I got a bunch of homework
to catch up on.
No, Andrews, you're right.
It is tradition.
I'm hungry enough
to eat a horse.
Last one to Pop's treats.
[Reggie scoffs]
You can come too, pipsqueak.
[Cheryl] Gather around, Vixens.
Now that our team's roster
is finally complete,
and with my family's first big
booster event coming up,
it is time to assign each Vixen
to their respective player.
Wait. What do you mean,
"assign"?
It means that you show
your particular player
extra-personalized support
throughout the season.
Baking him cookies,
wearing his jersey,
helping him with his homework.
I, of course, will be paired
with Julian.
And Toni, you and Archie
will be matched.
As for our new star player,
I was thinking Betty
could be with Reggie.
[knocking at door]
Maybe we leave him a note
and try again tomorrow?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Hey, maybe we can
go catch a flick.
I think the Babylonium
is playing It Came
from Beneath the Sea,
and Ray Harryhausen
did the giant octopus.
[chuckles] Oh, um...
Yes.
I would love to go
to the movies with you.
[both chuckle]
Toni.
What's going on?
We need to get real, Cheryl.
What about?
I can't do this anymore.
The Vixens.
Is this about being paired
with Archie?
Would you prefer someone else?
No. I don't want to get
paired with anyone.
That's the thing.
Baking for my own
personal meathead
is not really what I want
my life to be about.
This whole thing just
doesn't feel right anymore.
It's not me
or who I want to be.
A cheerleader.
I see.
Toni, this doesn't have
anything to do with me
asking you to go steady,
does it?
[Toni] No.
But now that you mention it,
I'm not the settling-down type.
And I feel like
I've lost myself.
I don't know.
This whole square scene
isn't for me.
I need to
figure myself out.
I'm sorry, Cheryl.
I just need some space.
Can we do
a double-size popcorn,
a large cola with extra ice,
two packs of
the Senior Mints,
a Butterflinger, a pack
of those Mint Bogos,
Three Buccaneers
and a Skit-Skat?
Do you want anything?
Uh, no, I'm okay. Thanks.
That'll be 75 cents.
[Clay] Here you go.
Perfect.
Keep the change.
-Enjoy the movie.
-Thank you.
Well, isn't that fascinating?
[Clay] What?
Jughead and Tabitha
going to the movies together?
I find that interesting.
Don't you?
Could be they both like
science fiction flicks.
You know, Jughead and I
were entangled for
a New York minute.
What happened?
-I ended it.
-How come?
He's plenty handsome.
I suppose.
But between you and me,
he's a total oddball.
Lives in a train car too.
I prefer my men to be
a bit more continental.
Worldly.
With an air of mystery
about them.
I... I should skedaddle
to the booth.
-Get the next reel cued up.
-[Veronica] Of course.
But Clay...
Just think about picking up
what I'm putting down.
[door closes]
Uh, what did you get
for problem four?
You know, you don't
have to do this.
What do you mean?
Oh, helping you
with your homework
is one of my Vixen duties.
I'm also supposed
to discreetly find out
what your favorite
kind of cookie is,
so I can bake you a batch.
-You don't have
to do that either.
-Oh, but I do.
On the hush-hush.
It's sort of my
court-appointed punishment.
What do you mean?
Oh, I was ordered
to join the Vixens
to curb my unhealthy
physical urges.
Oh, you mean,
you haven't heard?
[exhales deeply]
Yeah, I sort of flashed
my underwear
on live television.
You know,
like Marilyn Monroe style.
Is that how come
you and Archie have to have
your curtains closed?
Oh, no... [sputters]
Archie and I...
Well, you'll probably
hear about it anyways.
We were basically caught
having a peep show
in our windows.
A peep show.
Yeah, if you can
even call it that. [scoffs]
You know what?
I should...
I should probably go.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
Nothing happened between us.
We didn't. No, we're not...
-I'm completely...
-[Reggie] Yeah.
Still, I'm living with the guy.
And we don't go in much
for peep shows
and flashing panties
in Duck Creek.
So, it's... This is...
Consider yourself relieved
of your, uh, Vixen duties.
-Okay?
-But I... I...
Reg, you, uh... You want
to grab lunch with us?
Thanks for the invite,
but I'm gonna pass.
Well, it wouldn't be
with the team.
It would be with
my other friends.
All the same, I'm good.
[basketball swishes]
[Toni] I want to try
something out on you cats.
Ever since Featherhead
refused to publish
my Emmett Till article
in the Blue and Gold,
I've been keen to start
a literary society for
Riverdale's Black students.
A club that publishes
a journal
focusing on Black voices
and writing.
I think that's
an excellent idea.
Yeah, I've been craving
a forum where
I can publish
my literary criticism,
poetry and short fiction.
And this is something that
you would do in addition
to cheerleading?
No, I gave that up.
What happened?
I joined the Vixens
for the wrong reasons.
It was because
I had a crush on a girl.
Cheryl Blossom.
But now that's over, so...
Anyway, I think
publishing this journal
could really make a difference
for the Black students
at Riverdale.
It would. Definitely.
But what happened with Cheryl?
On the level,
we're just so different.
She's rich, she's white,
she's a Blossom.
The whole thing,
it would just be impossible.
I mean, it's hard
but it's not impossible.
For Kevin and I,
we're also very different.
So everything's a conversation.
But he's up for getting
to know me and what
I'm all about, and vice versa.
I hear that, Clay,
but you're also both preppies.
So, at least you're starting
off on the same foot.
Fair enough.
I guess it all depends on
how much you like the person.
Kevin, you haven't
seen Clay, have you?
He's running late.
Had some stuff at school.
Can we chat about something?
Of course.
[sputters] It's just, it...
It seems like you're coming on
really strong with Clay.
I might be.
Clay would never say anything.
But is that really appropriate?
[clicks tongue] Oh, Kevin.
Don't be such a wet rag.
What's wrong with a little
workplace flirtation?
It's not like Clay
is even remotely interested.
He's not.
I know that for a fact.
Oh.
And why is that?
Because he's not attracted
to assertive women?
No, he's not attracted
to any women.
Neither am I, for that matter.
I knew it.
I knew you were both
secret friends of Dorothy.
You knew?
How?
You're both dreamy flutter bums
who can quote every line
of Norma Desmond's dialogue
in Sunset Boulevard.
If you knew,
why would you make
a play for Clay?
To test my hypothesis,
of course.
You lucky dog. He is a hunk.
Say, what are the chances...
Clay swings both ways?
Uh, he doesn't. We don't.
Double-checking, that's all.
[chuckles softly]
You're okay with this?
Absolutely.
Kevin, the only thing better
than having a hunky boyfriend
is having hunky friends
who are boys.
The thing is, I've always had
more fun going out
with Tony and Tab
than, say, Steve and Dennis.
Steve McQueen
and Dennis Hopper.
Don't worry,
we'll get you up to snuff.
[sighs]
Oh, Kevin, I'm so excited.
This hick town is finally
starting to feel like home.
[giggles softly]
[Frank] All right, fellas.
Huddle up.
Julian has an announcement.
Tomorrow night,
my parents are hosting
their annual Bulldog booster
basketball mixer.
This year,
it's also a fundraiser.
To build us a new gym.
Are the cheerleaders invited?
Absolutely.
So dress spiffy.
Okay? Coats and ties.
Make sure you shower.
[clears throat]
And, of course, we'll be
welcoming our newest Bulldog
to the family, I suppose.
You know, that Blossom mixer
may sound a little stuffy,
but they're always
a gas and a half.
Yeah, well, let me know
how that goes.
-You're not going?
-No, I can't be distracted.
The NCAA is giving out
scholarships for college,
and if I get one of those,
I'm made in the shade.
Reggie, no man is an island.
Can't you do all that stuff
and still cut loose a little?
Hell, Julian made it seem like
you're the guest of honor.
If that's what you heard,
you're a lot more naive
than I thought.
Why are you being
such a killjoy, Mantle?
Why can't you meet
anyone halfway?
Meet halfway?
Julian and those guys
haven't taken one step
towards me since I got here.
And you haven't heard
anything I've been saying.
Sophomore year, I was recruited
by Stonewall Prep.
And I was juiced to be there,
but I never belonged there.
And my teammates made that
very clear.
[boy exclaims] Oh!
You guys like rice,
don't you?
Is that enough to take back
to your farm, yellow-belly?
[boy laughing]
[Reggie] And that was day one.
During practice,
the other players
would foul me on purpose,
and they did whatever
they could to run me
out of there.
And guess what?
It worked.
So this time,
I'm not meeting
anyone halfway.
Not giving anyone an opening.
A chance to humiliate me
ever again.
All right?
All right.
Reggie...
I'm sorry that happened to you.
But we're not like that here.
Aren't you?
[students laughing, chattering]
Cheryl.
Toni.
-Hello.
-How are you?
[exhales] I'm being stoic
and strong for the sake
of my Vixens.
-How are you?
-Well, I'm petitioning
for a new club.
And you,
as Junior Class President,
are in charge of the student
council's financing.
I was hoping you could help us
secure some funding.
What kind of club is it?
It's a literary society
for Riverdale's Black students
to share their ideas,
stories and writings
with each other
and the student body.
A way to express ourselves
on our own terms.
That's a really wonderful idea.
I'll put the request
through today,
but Toni, everything has to go
through Featherhead, so...
I know.
And I appreciate you trying.
And if Featherhead
doesn't approve,
we'll make it work.
We always do.
Maybe a bake sale or something.
Well, I would contribute
my legendary cherry scones.
Toni, can I ask you a question?
Is part of the reason
you broke up with me
because I'm white?
There was a lot
of reasons, Cheryl.
All interconnected,
but that was part of it.
Yeah.
I will try my absolute best
with Featherhead.
I promise.
-[jazz music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
Fancy meeting you here.
Well, howdy doody, Betty.
And how's it going
being a paper shaker?
Oh, swell.
Werthers thought it would
help me burn off
some excess energy.
Grown-ups don't have a clue.
No, they don't.
Anyways, I don't think I'll be
a Vixen for much longer.
And why is that?
Once my mother finds out
that I've been assigned
a basketball player
to take care of,
she will flip her lid.
[Archie] Oh, crap.
Um, will you excuse me, Betty?
-I...
-I'll take it.
Thanks.
[Betty chuckles softly]
Archie. Your uncle's telling me
that you're sharing a room
with our, uh...
Our secret weapon.
Uh, you mean Reggie?
Yes, I am.
Well, as a former
Bulldog myself,
I do appreciate the sacrifice.
Well, it's no trouble at all.
I'm cranked to do it, really.
Well, I know I couldn't.
I mean, bunking with, uh...
We look upon him
as a necessary evil, Dennis.
A means to an end.
She's talking about winning.
The Bulldogs must be
champions this year.
The town needs something
to rally behind.
And you know, Frank,
when you suggested
bringing on a Korean prodigy...
[chuckles]
Well, I was skeptical.
But having seen him play...
[exclaims]
I now see how inspired
your thinking was.
Tell me something, Archie.
Does he, uh, actually
realize the opportunity
we're presenting to him
and his family?
He does.
He just doesn't want
to fall behind on his...
On his schoolwork.
Good for him. [chuckles]
But, uh, well,
we don't care about that.
We just need him
to be a loyal soldier
and bring us
our championship trophy.
He does that,
preferably with a smile
on his face,
there'll be no problems for us.
And none for his family.
If you'll excuse me.
-I'm gonna get some fresh air.
-Yeah.
Good stuff.
Well, Coach,
here's to a winning season.
[glasses clinking]
[Veronica] Reggie Mantle.
And here I thought
you weren't
a fan of the movies.
I didn't say that.
I said we didn't have
any theaters in Duck Creek.
I stand corrected.
And the fact that I might
have been here tonight
didn't influence
your decision, I suppose?
If I'm being honest...
Oh, I insist upon honesty
at all times.
Not at all.
Truth is, I forgot
that you worked at this place.
[chuckles]
I don't work at it.
I own it.
Now, what can I get for you?
[clears throat]
A small popcorn?
No butter. I'm training.
Here you go.
On the house.
Thanks.
How rude can you get?
Anyway, there's plenty
other fish in the sea.
True.
But take a powder,
Herman Melville,
because that
is the real Moby Dick.
[Tabitha] Wow, this is like
the Orient-Express.
[Jughead chuckles]
That's exactly what I said.
-Here you go. Yeah.
-Oh, thank you.
Um, I actually,
I brought you something.
Here.
This is for you to keep.
Darkwater: Voices from
Within the Veil,
by W.E.B. Du Bois.
-Du Bois. He is a sociologist
and a civil rights activist.
-Du Bois.
He's also one
of my favorite authors.
Wow, it's a great title.
Which one should I start with?
Well, we've established
that you're a fan
of science fiction.
-Mm-hmm.
-And though it's more
speculative fiction,
I would suggest a story
that Du Bois wrote
called The Comet.
-What's that one about?
-Oh, it's fantastic.
It's, um, it's about this comet
that hits New York City
and it kills everybody
except for two people.
A man named Jim
and a woman named Julia.
And it's sort of about this
unlikely relationship that
develops between them.
And what's really interesting
is that Jim is Black
and Julia is white,
and it's sort of
one of the first times
an interracial relationship
has been depicted
in science fiction.
Well, it sounds terrific.
-Yeah.
-I can't wait to read it.
Actually, I was thinking
that maybe we could
read it together.
Tonight. Aloud,
if you wanted.
Yeah, that sounds swell.
How was the mixer?
It was dullsville.
Honestly, you didn't
miss out on much.
Hmm. How were the cheerleaders?
All dolled up?
I don't really want
to talk about it.
Hey, I'm gonna grab a shower.
Okay, you lug nuts.
Coach is in a meeting,
so I'm running warm-ups today.
Everyone good with that?
In that case, let's play ball.
[upbeat music playing]
[boys chattering]
[grunting]
[Archie] Yeah!
[Julian] Come on.
Hey, banana boy,
pass me the ball.
Pass me the ball!
[boys] Whoa!
[boy] Man, come on.
[panting] Listen up.
We are not doing this crap.
If you haven't noticed,
Reggie here is our
strongest player,
our only shot at making
the playoffs this year.
So we're going to rise
to his level.
So if you don't want
to be chummy with him,
that's fine.
But the minute
we hit this court,
we are teammates,
fighting for each other.
If you can't get
on board with that,
the door's right there.
And that includes
you too, Captain.
I hope this will suffice.
Funds for your new club.
Thank you, Cheryl.
[chuckles] I'm shocked
Featherhead approved
a Black literary society.
He didn't.
Those funds were earmarked
for... something else.
But I believe your club
to be a much more
worthy endeavor.
Well, I won't ask
any more questions.
But thank you.
Of course.
I look forward to reading
your first issue.
Cheryl, wait.
Yes?
What are you doing
after cheerleading practice?
No plans. Why?
If you want,
maybe we could meet
at the Dark Room.
I would love that.
Do you mean to talk?
Yeah, about...
what it would mean
if we tried again.
I didn't sock Julian for you.
I know you don't need saving.
I did it for my own sake
and for the team's.
I didn't want to believe
you were right about this town.
But, hell,
maybe we are just as...
As messed up
as any other place.
I don't know. [chuckles softly]
Want to grab a burger
at Pop's on the way home?
Maybe we'll run into some
of the other fellows there.
Sure, if you're sure.
I am.
Just don't expect me to sit
with anyone or anything.
[laughs]
[Jughead] Tabitha and I
stayed up till dawn,
reading and discussing
Du Bois' stories.
The next day, I wanted
to tell Mr. Rayberry
all about my swell night,
so I went back
to his apartment.
[door creaks]
Wha... What happened?
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but Brad Rayberry is dead.
Wha...
[sputters] How did he die?
He, uh, killed himself.
Hung himself.
He left a note.
"I can no longer
continue living this way."
I'm sorry, Jughead.
I know that he was your friend.