[JUGHEAD] Things were dire.
My friend Ethel's parents
had been brutally murdered
the night of the sock hop.
And suddenly, Ethel and I
were the prime suspects.
You drew this picture, didn't you, Ethel?
And they're meant to be
your mother and father.
Yes, but it was a joke.
Then why did Mr. Jones
hide it under his mattress,
like a dirty secret?
And is this where your far-fetched story
about a killer milkman came from?
- A comic book?
- No. No.
I saw a milkman leaving my house.
Don't say anything else
until we talk to a lawyer.
You know, a picture
is worth a thousand words, Mr. Jones.
And these...
Well, these tell a very disturbing story.
Well...
Well, maybe they'll be more talkative
down at the station.
Jughead. What's happening?
They're railroading us.
[KELLER] Let's go, Jughead.
[GIRL] I just can't believe
that Ethel would...
Where do you get off, Andrews,
taking advantage of my sister?
Going all the way with her
at Veronica's make-out party.
Okay, first of all,
you encouraged me to date Cheryl.
And second of all, I didn't.
We did not go all the way.
That's not what Cheryl's saying.
Cheryl.
Why did you tell your brother
we went all the way?
We didn't. We kissed. That's all we did.
We did more than that, Archie.
I mean, Bela Lugosi
didn't give me this beauty mark.
Oh, okay. Okay.
We barely made it to second base,
so why tell Julian we scored a home run?
I can't explain it.
But by saying that we did,
it's helping me with a problem I'm having.
Just know
that by corroborating my story...
you'd be protecting me.
Protecting you? How? From whom?
My family.
Archie, please don't ask me
any more questions than that.
Anyway, it's just
a little white lie, right?
Really...
who is it hurting?
["THE IN-BETWEEN YEARS" PLAYING]
♪ These are the in-between years
We're going through... ♪
I wanna give this back to you, Betty.
[BETTY] That was fast.
Did you glean something from it, at least?
I think so. I think I know what you want.
And?
And I wanna wait until marriage.
Oh, I see.
Well, how about this?
I'm not okay
with you making all of the decisions
in this relationship, Kevin.
So, as far as I'm concerned,
we're not going steady anymore.
[SIGHS]
[TONI] Betty, what is it?
Why are you crying?
[SOBBING] Kevin and I broke up.
[SIGHS] Boys ruin everything.
What did he do?
Well, we were talking about
having a more physical relationship...
and an ultimatum was put down.
You wanted to wait 'til marriage?
No, Kevin said
he wanted to wait until marriage.
So I broke up with him.
Don't be ashamed of your desires, Betty.
More girls should do what you did.
Ask for what they want
from their supposed boyfriends.
What do I do now?
Well, how about you and I
go to the Dark Room and grab a coffee?
And, Betty?
Maybe this breakup
is exactly what the doctor ordered.
[VERONICA] How's poor Ethel doing?
I think she's in shock.
I can only imagine.
- What are they saying to you?
- Not much.
Just that they can only hold us legally
for 24 hours,
after which they either have to release us
or charge us.
But you were at the dance.
We were all there together.
If there were some way
we could prove the time
that Ethel's parents were killed,
it might be enough to clear me,
and I'd figure out a way
to exonerate Ethel.
Putting on my Nora Charles hat,
doesn't Riverdale have a coroner
that would've performed
an autopsy on the Muggses?
Every town has a coroner,
but I don't know who that is.
Let me find out.
I'll be back.
Hey, Veronica.
Nora Charles?
The Thin Man is one of my favorite films.
I had a feeling.
Mom? What's wrong?
Mrs. Blossom just came by.
Is it true what she's saying
you and Cheryl did?
How did this happen?
I don't really feel comfortable
discussing this.
You think I do?
Never mind.
Just go upstairs
and change into your suit.
Why?
Because you and I are going over
to the Blossoms' for dinner
to figure out a path through this mess
that you and Cheryl made.
[ELEGANT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
So how was your trip to Washington,
Mr. Mayor?
Oh, Mary, please. It's Clifford.
As for my trip? Well, it was, uh...
It was productive.
But...
to come home
to our fair town torn asunder...
Two murders.
And our young people in crisis.
The world has indeed gone sideways.
Joe was right.
Senator McCarthy.
So tell me, Archie,
what do you think of the Russia problem?
The Russia problem, sir?
The Russians.
Arming themselves against us,
infiltrating us,
undermining our very way of life.
Well...
Well, Russia is a big...
It's a massive problem, sir.
I mean, clearly.
You're a very smart young man, Archie.
You remind me of your father.
Fred was a decent, hard-working,
red-blooded American.
Thank you, sir.
Mary, after dinner,
I think we should adjourn to my study.
We have much to discuss.
[CHERYL]
I'm sorry I never got to meet your dad.
You must miss him a lot.
Yeah, he was... He was my best friend.
That is so sweet.
We used to go to the movies
almost every weekend.
Westerns. Those were his favorites.
Mine too.
And afterwards,
we'd go to Pop's for burgers.
We'd joke about riding out west
to California, to live on a ranch.
Being cowboys.
It's funny, I think about that a lot.
["UNCHAINED MELODY" PLAYING]
♪ Whoa, my love ♪
♪ My darling ♪
♪ I've hungered for your touch ♪
♪ A long, lonely time... ♪
All right.
First thing's first,
let's get you that decaf.
You know what?
Betty, let's go. You don't wanna see this.
See what? What are you...?
♪ ...can do so much ♪
♪ Are you still mine? ♪
Oh, my gosh.
According to the time of death
on that certificate,
Jughead was at the dance
when Mr. and Mrs. Muggs were murdered.
This doesn't account for Ethel's
whereabouts at the time of the murders.
That may be the case,
but you can at least release Jughead,
can't you?
I'm sorry,
but is that cell gonna unlock itself?
Because I'm a very busy teenager, sheriff.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
I think they were trying
to starve me in there.
I managed to get Ethel to open up.
She told you where she was
when her parents were killed?
Mm-hm. And her reluctance to fess up
makes sense too.
Turns out, she was doing
the car seat cha-cha with, get this...
Julian Blossom.
Ethel was waiting at the bus stop
to go to the dance
when Julian drove by
and offered to take her.
You going to the dance?
Come on. I'll give you a ride.
[JUGHEAD] He took her to Lover's Lane
and tried to put the moves on her.
As Ethel described it,
she welcomed it at first,
but Julian decided to get a little handsy.
[JULIAN GRUNTS]
Julian warned her not to say anything,
and that if she did,
he would call her a nymphomaniac,
make her the town laughingstock.
Of course,
we know what happened after that.
She decided to go home
instead of the dance.
Terrible.
I say we talk to Julian
at school tomorrow.
Ethel thinks ratting him out
will make things worse for her,
and she may be right.
So it's up to Julian
to do the honorable thing.
God help us.
[DOOR OPENS]
And where have you been, young lady?
I was just having coffee
with my friend Toni.
Hmm. Well...
Mrs. Keller called.
Did you break up with Kevin today?
Oh, Betty.
Why did you do that?
He is so upset.
He's devastated.
Mrs. Keller doesn't know where he is.
She's worried sick.
Kevin is fine.
I just saw him at the coffee house.
And rest assured,
he's found a shoulder to cry on.
A very manly shoulder.
And?
And, looking back,
that's been the problem with us
this whole time, Mom.
Kevin likes boys.
Oh, Elizabeth.
Here, honey. Come sit.
[ALICE SIGHS]
Even if he does, it's just a phase.
See, carnal passion like that,
it never lasts.
It will fade.
And then, eventually, he'll be ready to...
To what? To kiss me? To want to kiss me?
To marry you.
To settle down and start a family.
Mom, how could I possibly marry
and live with Kevin knowing the truth now?
You and Kevin,
you've been building a relationship
for two years.
I know.
And if he's going through
some kind of sexual identity crisis,
don't you owe it to him
to help him through it?
If only as a friend?
[LIGHT BUZZING AND FLICKERING]
Holy heck.
Hot Dog.
Where'd they take you, boy?
[GROANS]
That was torture.
Well, Mr. Blossom said
some nice stuff about Dad, at least.
Clifford Blossom
has always been a hypocrite.
And a war profiteer, and a draft-dodger.
How's he a war profiteer?
He sold maple syrup to the Army
at a premium during the Korean War.
I've always managed
to give the Blossoms a wide berth,
but now, thanks to you,
we'll be linked for the rest of our lives.
What are you talking about?
The Blossoms and I have had a long talk,
and we've decided that,
based on your actions,
the best thing to do would be
for you and Cheryl to get married.
Married?
Aren't Cheryl and I too young to do that?
Dr. Werthers will be giving you
and Cheryl a test tomorrow.
I have to take a test now too?
A compatibility test.
Cupid's Checklist, to make sure
that you and Cheryl are...
- Compatible.
- Yes.
And psychologically ready to get married.
[CLEARS THROAT]
- Mom, this can't be what you want for me.
- It isn't.
But if you're old enough to...
do what you did,
then you're old enough
to take responsibility for it.
Think of Cheryl's honor.
That poor girl's reputation
could be destroyed,
and I know you don't want that.
Gosh, Midge.
Are you sure?
I'm never late.
I'm scared, Fangs.
Don't worry, baby. I love you.
We're gonna figure this out. I promise.
[SCOFFS] What do you two want?
We know that you were with Ethel
before arriving at the dance.
Is that what Ethel says? [CHUCKLES]
She wishes.
You're a terrible liar.
If you already know the story,
why the third degree?
Because they're trying to bamboozle Ethel.
You were the only one with her
when her parents were 86'd.
So you can be her alibi.
But you need to tell the truth
to Sheriff Keller.
- I'm not doing that.
- Why not?
I'm a Blossom.
It would be...
unseemly for me to admit
I made a play for someone as...
inappropriate as Ethel Muggs.
Then why do it in the first place?
I don't know.
Cheap thrills, I guess.
What the hell, Jones?
You disgust me, Julian.
People like you make my stomach churn.
You're rich.
You're entitled.
You strut around the world
like you own it.
And then you take advantage of people
like my friend Ethel?
So you're gonna do the right thing
for once in your life.
Julian gave his statement.
- Ethel's free to go, right?
- Yes, she's no longer an active suspect.
Though an adult
is gonna need to sign her out.
The Coopers are on their way.
They've agreed to take her in again.
My compatibility test,
or Cupid's Checklist, shall we say,
consists of only three questions.
First question.
Do you come from similar backgrounds?
The Blossoms are descended
from European barons and baronesses.
Um, my dad used to talk
about how Grandpa Artie and his wife
barely survived the Dust Bowl.
Very good.
Second question. Are you close friends?
[CHUCKLES] Um...
You know, I pride myself on getting along
with pretty much everyone.
Last question.
Do you understand the concept of marriage?
Um...
Marriage is not to be taken lightly,
Ms. Blossom.
And you, Mr. Andrews,
you must remain faithful.
It goes against our nature as men,
of course, but...
a kind word, a sympathetic ear,
and a home-cooked meal
can go a long way
towards keeping a wandering eye in check.
Have I clarified things?
Well, that is such a relief to hear,
Dr. Werthers.
Mrs. Andrews and I are elated.
Yes. We'll talk soon.
My best to Myrna.
The most wonderful news, Mary, dear.
The children are compatible.
Well, frankly, I'm surprised.
You know, Archie and Cheryl
are so different.
Well, they both have
that glorious red hair, don't they?
[TONI] Hey, Fangs. How's it hanging?
Not well.
Toni, Midge thinks that she might be...
in trouble.
Oh, jeez.
Are you sure?
Not a hundred percent, but yeah.
Pretty sure.
Okay, well, first things first,
we need to confirm
that Midge is, in fact, pregnant.
Here's what we're gonna do.
You, me, and Midge are gonna meet
at the biology lab at school tonight,
at midnight.
That'll give me enough time to gather
the supplies we need to make our own test.
Can you dig it?
Big Daddy?
[SIGHS]
[PLAYING SOMBER MELODY]
Kev?
Can we talk?
I went to the Dark Room last night.
And I saw you and Clay there.
Yeah. I don't know what you think you saw,
but Clay and I were just kidding around.
No. No, you weren't.
How long have you and Clay...?
Last night was the first time.
After you broke up with me,
I went to the gym
and just was bawling my eyes out, and...
Clay was in the locker room,
and he heard me and came in,
and talked to me, and...
I'm sorry.
I know this must be throwing you
for a loop, but just believe me,
if I had known what... I was,
I wouldn't have wasted your time.
I'm not going to pretend
that I understand most of this...
but our relationship
was not a waste of time.
At least not to me.
[BARBERSHOP MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
Well, I guess it's happening.
Yeah, Mr. and Mrs. Andrews.
So it seems.
Cheryl, are you sure you really
wanna go through with this?
Would it really be that bad?
To be married to you? No.
No, heck no.
I just wanna get to know you better.
And through that process,
maybe I'll get to know myself better too.
I think it's easier
to figure out your path
when someone's walking alongside you.
Word around school is you wrote
Veronica a beautiful love poem.
Maybe you could find it in your heart
to write one for me?
Yeah. Yeah, sure I can.
To small victories.
Hear, hear.
Though Ethel's not out of the woods
just yet.
No, but she's in a better place
than she was two hours ago.
We make a good team, Nick.
Yes, we do, Nora.
So after dinner,
what do you think about walking me home?
Oh, shucks.
I was actually
planning on staying here tonight.
At the diner? Why?
Sheriff Keller and his goon squad
trashed my train car.
Oh.
Well, do you wanna stay at the Pembrooke?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
No, no. I'm allergic to silk sheets.
You're in luck, then.
Because we only have sheets
made from the finest Egyptian cotton.
I wouldn't wanna crowd you.
Please, there's an entire wing of
the apartment I haven't even set foot in.
Really. I insist.
- [FROG CROAKING]
- I'm confused, Toni.
How will any of this
tell us whether or not I'm pregnant?
It's a simple process.
I'm gonna inject some of your pee
into our friend here,
and if you're pregnant,
it's gonna cause a chemical reaction
in the frog,
'causing it to lay eggs overnight.
Will it hurt the frog?
No. It's quick and painless, promise.
Okay. I got Midge's pee in a cup
in a bag here,
so why don't you two just wait outside,
and I'll be out in a jiffy?
[CROAKING]
Well, Midge, you're definitely preggers.
There's like
four-to-five hundred eggs in there.
Oh, my God.
All right, Fangs, Midge, listen up.
Do you two love each other?
- Yeah, we do.
- Completely.
Fangs, you're gonna have
to clean yourself up.
Wash the grease out of your hair,
put on a button-up shirt,
and go ask the Klumps
for Midge's hand in marriage.
I'd do anything for Midge,
but no way will her folks
give us their blessing.
You're gonna at least have to try.
And maybe they'll surprise you.
But I wouldn't tell them that Midge
has a bun in the oven just yet.
[VERONICA] Good morning.
What's all this?
Well, I woke up early.
Figured I'd make you a little breakfast
as a show of gratitude.
Little?
My typical breakfast consists of
half a grapefruit and a cup of coffee.
I feel like I'm at the Polo Lounge
having Sunday brunch.
How did you sleep?
Were the sheets to your liking?
I slept like a log.
But I'll admit, I do feel a bit
like Little Orphan Annie in here.
Which makes me, who? Daddy Warbucks?
Should we walk to school together?
I'm skipping school today.
I have to go to the pound, spring Hot Dog,
then I have to fix up my train car.
Then I'll skip too.
Why don't you focus on getting Hot Dog,
and I'll focus
on sprucing up your train car?
Wait a minute.
You and Cheryl didn't go all the way,
but now you two are getting married?
- I know. It's confusing.
- It's lunacy, Arch.
Why don't you tell your mom the truth
so you don't have to do this?
Cheryl's in trouble, Betty,
and I wanna protect her.
And it's weird to say,
but if I can save her from something,
it might help me...
I don't know,
figure out my purpose in life.
But do you love her?
I could. According to Dr. Werthers,
love grows over time.
He showed us a graph.
It starts when you're 17
and peaks when you're 21.
That's when you really
start loving someone.
Arch, there's a difference between
saving someone and loving someone.
What if the love never grows?
Archie?
My father has requested
a sit-down with us after school.
- I trust you can accommodate him.
- I'll be there.
Wunderbar.
I'll let him know.
Betty.
You're a wonderful guy, Arch.
And it's really sweet
that you wanna help Cheryl,
but marriage is forever.
It's the rest of your life.
[CLIFFORD] So very happy to hear that
you passed Dr. Werthers' evaluation.
I suppose you're wondering
what happens next.
Well, we were thinking of a small ceremony
at Niagara Falls.
Don't be asinine.
You'll be married by a judge at Thornhill.
I will set Archie up with a part-time job
at the maple factory,
and you'll both graduate high school.
- And college.
- That's a waste of time and money.
After high school,
you, Archie, will enter into
the Blossom Management Training Program.
And once that's completed,
we'll start you in full-time.
Cheryl will help her mother
manage Thornhill,
eventually learning
how to run the estate herself.
- Why? It's not as if we'll live here.
- Certainly, you will.
Where else are you gonna live?
Cheryl and I haven't
talked about it yet, sir,
but I was thinking we could
move into my parents' house.
Cheryl... in that hovel?
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING ON DOUBLE BASS]
Wow.
I barely even recognized you, Fangs.
How did it go at the Klumps'?
It went horrible.
They had a conniption.
Forbade me from ever seeing Midge again.
Yeah, I was afraid that was gonna happen.
Midge is rich, she's white,
her parents love her,
and on top of it all,
you're a greaser wannabe-rock star.
Oh, jeez.
Well, what do I do, Toni?
You do exactly what the Klumps say.
Stay away from Midge.
They don't know she's pregnant.
You got four months
before she starts to show.
Which means we have four months
to make you into
a Ritchie Valens-type rock star.
- Huh?
- Once you become rich
and famous and undeniable,
you'll re-propose to Midge,
and they'll have no choice
but to give their blessing.
You're in love.
Like a Romeo and Juliet kind of love.
No matter what,
you and Midge will be together.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, do you fellas approve?
Wow.
You really are like Daddy Warbucks.
I consulted with some of
my set decorator friends out west.
I could have done more,
but time was very limited.
Are you kidding?
This is like the Orient Express.
- Without the murder, of course.
- Of course.
Jughead, you and Hot Dog are more
than welcome to stay at the Pembrooke.
Oh, golly.
I appreciate the offer,
I'm just a creature of habit.
As is Hot Dog.
But thank you for everything.
This is... Gosh.
My pleasure.
All right.
Well, I will leave you boys to it.
Bye.
Do you wanna explain this to me?
- What were you doing in my room?
- Cleaning it.
Now tell me, why do you have this book?
I was reading it, Mom,
to try to make some sense of my life,
since everything you tell me
is backwards and nonsensical.
Watch your tone, little miss.
A girl your age
should not be reading this filth.
Well, then, when, Mom?
And it's not filth, it's just the truth.
Where did you even find this?
[ETHEL] It's mine.
It was at my house.
That's where Betty found it, Mrs. Cooper.
I ordered it from a catalog
through the mail.
Oh, Ethel. Why am I not surprised?
It doesn't matter where I got it,
and I'm not done reading it yet.
Betty! Young lady!
["WHO DO YOU SUPPOSE" PLAYING]
♪ Who do you suppose
I really love? ♪
I'm thinking of? ♪
♪ Who do you suppose
I dream of ♪
♪ Both day and night...? ♪
[ARCHIE]
Cheryl, I can't go through with it.
After that crazy talk with your dad,
this whole plan is suddenly
feeling really wrong to me.
I understand, Archie. I do.
I demanded too much of you,
asking you to lie,
to marry into my life, my family.
That's my cross
and my cross alone to bear.
No. No, but it doesn't have to be.
Because I have another plan, a better one.
What do you mean?
What if we... elope?
Go out west?
You could get away from your family.
I could get a job on a ranch.
Or be, I don't know, a folk singer.
- A what?
- A folk singer.
All I'm saying is,
out west, we can find ourselves,
be whoever we wanna be.
Imagine it, Cheryl.
You'd be free from whatever
is weighing you down here.
- If only it were that easy.
- It can be. We just have to do it.
Okay.
Okay, let's try, Archie.
[BETTY] I read more of my book, Kev.
Including Chapter 20, about...
men like you.
And I wanted to say
that I think you're so brave.
Swell to the last.
Um, here's your pin back.
I thought maybe you could give it to Clay.
That's not mine. It's, um, your mom's.
- What are you talking about?
- When we were having our troubles,
she gave it to me to give to you
to take the pressure
off of our relationship.
You went to my mom for advice?
No. She reached out to me.
I hope that's okay.
Toni Topaz.
What are the odds?
I was about to come find you.
To say goodbye?
You can't do it, Cheryl.
Running away with Archie
would be a huge mistake.
You don't understand my situation.
You think you can run away
from Riverdale, your family,
but you can't outrun yourself,
who you are.
What makes you think you know me
better than I know myself?
I was you.
Do you love him?
Archie...
Archie is a great person...
with the best heart.
And he's nothing like my family, so...
I see.
So you hop on a bus with a boy
and move across the country, but...
eventually, you'll have to look yourself
in the mirror and face who you are.
Otherwise, you'll just wither away.
Mom. Where's Ethel?
Why, she's gone, dear.
Gone?
Gone where?
I called my friend Janet
at Social Services,
and she thought it'd be best
that we send Ethel
to the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Mom, the nuns there are bonkers.
They do experiments on people.
They do not, Elizabeth.
That rumor has been debunked.
It's what's best for Ethel.
Trust me. I know I'm right about this.
Is that what you said to Kevin
when you told him to pin me?
What on Earth are you talking about?
Did you give this to Kevin
and tell him to pin me, Mother?
To settle me and my urges down?
I may have given some advice in passing.
Oh, come off it, Mom.
What are you so afraid of?
Is it Ethel? Is it that book?
Is it me? What is it?
You know what? I'm here to protect you
from dangers that you don't
even know are coming your way.
But one day, you will,
and you'll thank me for it.
I really doubt it.
I burned it.
Your sex book.
So you won't be reading it
under the covers anymore.
["YOUNG AT HEART" PLAYING]
♪ Fairy tales can come true ♪
♪ It can happen to you ♪
♪ If you're young at heart... ♪
Wait. I got us bus tickets.
Are we taking your convertible instead?
I'm so sorry, Archie,
but I can't go out west with you.
This has been
the most beautiful pipe dream
with the most wonderful guy
a girl could ever ask for.
But that's all it is, a fantasy.
You've been a true gentleman,
but I have to face the music.
I can't keep running from all my problems.
- At least not this one.
- Cheryl...
Archie, someday you are going
to make some girl very happy,
and she is going to want
to go with you to California.
Unfortunately...
that girl isn't me.
But maybe...
she lives right next door to you.
- Do you mean...?
- Maybe you should write Betty
one of those sweet poems of yours.
["UNCHAINED MELODY" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Cheryl.
Shouldn't you be halfway to Frisco by now?
I decided not to leave with Archie.
For many reasons.
Oh, yeah?
I don't know where I go from here.
Well, why don't you start
by reading this book?
See if anything in it resonates with you.
Will you do that?
Not for me, but for yourself.
♪ Are you ♪
♪ Still mine? ♪
♪ I need your love ♪
♪ God speed your love ♪
♪ To me... ♪
[MARY] Archie? Can you come in here
for a minute, please?
Uncle Frank. What are you doing here?
Your mom called,
caught me up on everything.
Sounded like I needed to come to town
to knock some heads.
Starting with yours.
♪ I'll be coming home ♪
♪ Wait for me... ♪
All I know is what they've told me.
That Ethel is staying at some home
for wayward children,
with a bunch of nuns
called the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Are you okay?
No.
No, I feel like I failed her.
That I failed Ethel.
You didn't.
You fought hard to save her, Jughead.
And you did. You did save her.
♪ Are you ♪
♪ Still mine? ♪
♪ I need your love ♪
♪ I, I need your love... ♪
Wowie.
You can say that again.
♪ ...to me ♪