[ALARM RINGING]
♪ Please tell me it's Sunday
There's still one more fun day ♪
♪ Another day of summer, please ♪
♪ Give me one more day of fun
Not this bummer one ♪
♪ Why is life so cruel? ♪
♪ Today, I'm heading to school ♪
♪ The first day, the worst day
The same old teachers ♪
♪ Yapping in our ears ♪
♪ The worst day, the first day ♪
♪ But at least it's our senior year ♪
♪ It's finally here
I've waited so long ♪
♪ For this one day, Monday ♪
♪ I hope it won't go too fast ♪
♪ Last year was nothing but good times ♪
♪ Nothing but fun ahead ♪
♪ My final page in the yearbook
Come on, nothing to fear ♪
♪ Looking ahead and I can see ♪
♪ I'm a model A-student
I'll be perfect and prudent ♪
♪ Come on, world
I'm taking you on ♪
[BOTH] ♪ The first day, our first day
Monday, senior year ♪
♪ Riverdale, are you ready for me? ♪
♪ 'Cause this new girl is coming in hot ♪
♪ With looks and style
And brains and class ♪
♪ And money, well, I do have a lot ♪
♪ Mirror, mirror, on the shelf ♪
♪ Have I outdone myself? ♪
♪ Using Versace, Prada, Klein
Looking fine ♪
♪ I'm gonna tag him, bag him
Make him mine ♪
♪ Four years
Feels like I've done it before ♪
♪ Four years, feels like so much more ♪
♪ Four summers spent, so cruel ♪
♪ No more summer ♪
♪ No more summer school ♪
♪ Ready, set, and blast it
Stepping up, I passed it ♪
♪ And I'm taking my place ♪
♪ Kicking back with my pals
And finding myself ♪
♪ And finding pizza boxes under my bed ♪
[ALL] ♪ Lunchtime, so many more
Cafeteria ♪
♪ More burgers aplenty ♪
♪ More eating for
Twenty more minutes till breakfast ♪
♪ Eggs and bacon it
Making it all we can-wich ♪
♪ Sandwich ♪
♪ Bow down, freshies
I shan't repeat ♪
♪ All hail
Your new River Vixen queens ♪
♪ High school is a pyramid of mean ♪
♪ And we run the halls
So act accordingly ♪
♪ Tip-off, ready to score
Playing to win one more ♪
[ALL] ♪ Seniors, let's go! Go, seniors! ♪
♪ Last batch of high school prudes ♪
♪ Next year, it's college girls ♪
[ALL] ♪ College girls with attitude ♪
♪ Sophomore, junior
Soon you'll rule in the school ♪
♪ Partying supreme year, senior ♪
♪ Slam dunk, homecoming king, class ring ♪
♪ No-look pass, last shot, cue the band! ♪
[ALL] ♪ Varsity state champs ♪
♪ Most Likely to Be Year ♪
♪ Me year, my year, school year
I rule year ♪
[ALL] ♪ And our band on the stand ♪
♪ And my friends, amazing ♪
♪ Our song plays on the radio ♪
♪ These are the days ♪
♪ All our friends
Till the end come together ♪
♪ We'll make it, one day, Monday ♪
♪ Senior year ♪
Wow, that was incredible.
Was that not so incredible, Clay?
For a first sing-through,
that was the most monster.
You two wrote this song?
All the songs you'll be rehearsing.
This is a lot of music to learn.
For the first time ever,
Principal Featherhead is open
to doing an original musical this spring,
as opposed to, say, Oklahoma!
for the millionth time.
So Kevin and I decided
to write a show about, well,
all of us and our lives at Riverdale High.
But Featherhead needs to see
a workshop presentation
before he gives it the official go-ahead.
But why the heck
are we playing seniors in the show?
We're juniors in real life.
Well, senior year is just
so much more kicking for the storyline.
Teens on the cusp
of the rest of their lives.
But, dramaturgically,
I'm still the new girl?
- "Coming in hot"? Does that make sense?
- And why am I a bit player?
I'm the best singer in this damn school.
- Fangs is the best singer.
- I'm the best singer...
You're also Archie's understudy, Julian.
Don't forget.
And Archie is the main character.
You just said the show
was about all of us.
Yeah, and Cheryl and I aren't here
to play glorified chorus girls.
Everyone's gonna have at least
a solo line or two in the closing number,
which is all about,
wait for it, prom night.
[WHISTLES] And I am out.
I'm sorry, Kevin, Clay.
I cannot, in good conscience,
participate in this.
In my opinion, there is no lower art form
than American musical comedy.
I'm gonna back-window it too.
I got the looks for acting,
- but I'm not much for singing and dancing.
- Okay. That's fine. Not ideal.
Clay and I
will write you both out of the show.
In the meantime,
everyone else is dismissed until tomorrow,
except for Archie and Julian.
We are going to workshop
Archie's "I want" song.
So hang back, fellas, would you?
Traditionally,
the "I want" song in a musical
tells the audience
what our hero is searching for.
Their innermost dreams or desires.
[MUSIC STARTS]
♪ I just turned 17
I'm master of my scene ♪
♪ Still something
Sort of not completely cool ♪
♪ Guess I'm talking about
The problem that I got ♪
♪ When things get chilly
That is when I want them hot ♪
♪ It might sound silly
But it bothers me a lot ♪
[BOTH] ♪ Archie going left
Archie going right ♪
♪ Archie running any road
That he can find ♪
♪ Archie never making up
His All-American mind ♪
♪ Making up his All-American mind ♪
♪ I look at other guys
With fire in their eyes ♪
♪ They know the way
Their whole lives will play out ♪
♪ Me, I don't have a clue ♪
♪ Of what I'm gonna do ♪
♪ Or even what my story is about ♪
[BOTH] ♪ Think it's time
I make a big decision ♪
♪ Attack my problems
With a slick precision ♪
♪ Only then can I get rid of the vision ♪
♪ Of Archie going left
Archie going right ♪
♪ Archie running any road
That he can find ♪
♪ Archie never making up
His All-American mind, making up... ♪
- No, stop, stop, stop!
- What the hell, man? We were humming.
I don't wanna be a drip,
but it's super distracting
when my understudy is singing
literally at the same time as me.
Also, I'm not really
jiving with this song.
That's funny. I am.
Well, Archie, as we said,
this is your "I want" song.
It seems more like
an "I don't know what I want" song.
Not to worry.
We can figure something out. Um...
What do you want
your "I want" song to be about, Archie?
What do you, Archie Andrews,
want to do in real life?
What's your secret passion or dream?
I... want...
Who is Archie Andrews?
Do you even know what you want?
Is it romantic? Do you wanna date Betty?
Do you wanna date Veronica?
- Do you wanna be on the basketball team?
- Or do you wanna write poetry?
What is it? All of these things?
Well, I don't know.
But, yeah, I mean, maybe all of them.
No, I'm sorry, that doesn't work.
The "I want" song can only be about
one thing, or it confuses the audience.
It means you have
a poorly defined main character.
No biggie. Kevin and I can take
another stab at your "I want" song.
If I don't really know what I wanna do,
how are you gonna write a song about it?
Listen, we'll figure it out.
And you are gonna love it. I promise.
[SIGHS] Golly.
Is there anything more stressful
than workshopping a new musical?
- Especially one that's about your friends?
- If there is, it beats me.
But you're handling it all like a champ.
Especially given everything you're
going through at home with your folks.
Listen, the only reason
I'm getting through any of this
is because of how supportive
and incredible you are, Clay.
♪ Heaven sent me an angel ♪
♪ In my soul, a mystery unfolding ♪
♪ Nothing more than chances ♪
♪ I miss you yesterday ♪
♪ Collecting midnights ♪
♪ And the evening is gone ♪
[BOTH] ♪ The world so far away ♪
♪ When I stand with you ♪
♪ This ain't no ordinary feeling ♪
♪ This is love ♪
♪ Time takes a picture ♪
♪ And we vanish in the light ♪
[BOTH] ♪ This dream, this moment ♪
♪ All it wants is you ♪
♪ You came my way ♪
♪ And stole my heart ♪
♪ I wanna be your shelter ♪
[BOTH] ♪ The wonder of you ♪
♪ This ain't no ordinary feeling ♪
♪ This is love ♪
♪ Baby, this is love ♪
[SWING MUSIC PLAYING ON JUKEBOX]
I know who I'm hoping takes me
to the Valentine's Dance.
But who are you fuzzy ducks chasing?
♪ I'm not the kind of girl
Who's gotta twist and twirl ♪
♪ Every boy around my little finger ♪
♪ There's just one special guy
Who always catches my eye ♪
♪ In my heart, he always lingers ♪
♪ He needs a Betty
All set and ready ♪
♪ He and I make the perfect pair ♪
♪ Beware to a certain beauty queen
Who comes between us ♪
♪ The girl for him is me ♪
♪ I'm not the kind of girl
Who comes in second place ♪
♪ I don't sit and wait for a date ♪
♪ I serve it up on a silver plate ♪
♪ Somewhere chic and fun ♪
♪ If that doesn't work
I'll bring out the big guns ♪
♪ He needs a Ronnie ♪
♪ I bring it on
He and I are the perfect pair ♪
♪ Beware ♪
♪ Goody, goody ♪
♪ Why would he with you
When the girl for him is me? ♪
[BOTH] ♪ The boy is mine
Next Friday, Valentine's Dance ♪
♪ My chance of ending the chase ♪
♪ Can't hardly wait to be the one
Hot fun ♪
♪ Next Friday, Valentine, Archie's mine ♪
♪ P.S., I must confess ♪
♪ Archie met me at Pop's yesterday ♪
♪ He asked for a ride on my bike ♪
♪ He's looking at me in that certain way ♪
♪ I sped around all over town
Yesterday with Archie ♪
♪ I bet you heard my engine rev ♪
♪ Toni, please
FYI, Archie was at my house ♪
♪ Day before yesterday ♪
♪ There must've been a storm outside ♪
♪ 'Cause what do you know? ♪
♪ The lights went out
And me and Archie got close ♪
♪ His hand in mine
We had a good time ♪
♪ I pulled out my pom-poms
My moves were sublime ♪
♪ And Archie leaned in ♪
♪ The boy is mine
Tomorrow, Valentine's Dance ♪
♪ My chance of ending the chase ♪
♪ Can't hardly wait to be the one
Hot fun ♪
♪ Tomorrow, Valentine, Archie's mine ♪
♪ One boy plus four best friends ♪
♪ Pretty girls getting ugly ♪
♪ Scratch and fight
Kiss and hug me ♪
♪ Best frenemies ♪
♪ Me and my best frenemies ♪
Yowzah! So fun, right? What a bop.
A bop on the head, maybe, you twit.
Kevin, what is this?
We're all friends, not "frenemies."
- What does that word even mean?
- I invented it.
Is this how you see us?
Vapid, khaki-wacky girls
fighting over some guy
who doesn't have
any interest in any of us?
- Don't worry. We can work up a new song.
- No, we will.
We deserve a song with more depth,
written from our point of view.
Since when do you two write songs?
Oh, we're not gonna write it.
I'll get one of my Oscar
and/or Tony-winning pals to write it.
I'm thinking Cole Porter.
Also, not to pile on,
but this song was obviously intended
to be a Betty and Veronica duet.
Which you clearly
added us to at the last minute.
You did ask for more stage time.
You know what? I'm challenging you
to write something truthful.
Not just about Toni and I,
though that would be lovely.
But something more honest
about you two as well.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
All right. We heard your notes, Archie.
- I didn't really have any notes.
- And we wrote you a new "I want" song.
Strong musicals
always have a romantic core.
So that's why we decided
to focus on your quest for love.
My quest for love?
You wanna give it a whirl?
See how it fits?
Sure, jelly, let's roll.
♪ I've never been the type
To know for certain ♪
♪ I'm always looking for a better view ♪
♪ I'm wondering
What's behind that other curtain ♪
♪ I wanna have my cake and eat it too ♪
♪ All this talk about growing up ♪
♪ Well, I can't help feeling
A little stuck ♪
♪ Between wanting and needing ♪
♪ Living and dreaming ♪
♪ All I ever wanted was a love ♪
♪ That's so, so true, yeah ♪
♪ And I got two ♪
♪ I could have a penthouse in the city ♪
♪ Be in the suburbs with a picket fence ♪
♪ They're both so different
But they're both pretty ♪
♪ It's hard to choose
I guess it just depends ♪
♪ Sometimes I crave
A little cotton candy ♪
♪ Sometimes I wanna have
Some onion rings ♪
♪ They're both delicious
Please understand me ♪
♪ How can I choose
Between two perfect things? ♪
♪ Like wanting and needing ♪
♪ Living and dreaming ♪
♪ Gotta make a choice ♪
♪ But I don't know what to choose ♪
♪ 'Cause I want two ♪
I'm sorry, guys. Can we stop?
I just... I'm at sixes and sevens
by what you asked me last time.
I mean, who is Archie Andrews?
What does he really want?
That's why we focused your "I want" song
on choosing between Betty or Veronica.
It's not that simple.
I mean, that's not really the big question
that I'm wrestling with here.
In our musical or in real life?
[SIGHS]
Fellas, I'm sorry, but I have to step away
from this musical for a while.
For my own mental health.
It's too real, too raw.
And... I have to figure out
some major stuff for myself.
Really, Archie?
[CLAY] Good luck to you, Archie.
I hope you make the right decision
about whatever it is you need to decide.
[VERONICA] Excellent news, Bee.
I just got off with Cole Porter,
and he is willing to take a crack
at writing us a little ditty
for Kevin's musical.
Wow, I'm sure whatever Cole
comes up with will be the tops.
Much better than "Friday Valentine."
Betty, Kevin's royal shaft of a song
did bring up something
that's been eating away at me.
Oh, no. What is it?
You recall
when the Red Scare came to town?
- Yeah.
- Well, in a moment of weakness...
Archie and I kissed.
Do you like him?
I... I do.
But...
I like you more.
I feel closer to you
than anyone else in this town.
I've known Archie my entire life.
But I feel the same way.
Maybe this is the universe
telling us to swear off Archie
and focus on our friendship...
right now.
[VERONICA CHUCKLES]
So, Dad, how's the new cot?
More comfortable?
Oh, I mean, I'm used to it by now.
- How's your mother doing?
- All right, I guess. Considering.
- What about school?
- It's fine.
I'm working on that new musical
I told you about.
- The one about you and your friends?
- Yeah.
It's just a workshop right now,
but if Principal Featherhead digs it,
we'll do a full production in the spring.
I keep imagining you, me, and Mom
in the audience,
celebrating my opening night together.
Why don't you just come home, Dad?
Or just come to dinner?
Heck, one meal. It's all I'm asking.
So you can talk to Mom.
There's more to the situation
that you don't understand.
Like what? I want to understand.
It's adult stuff.
Serious stuff between your mother and I.
You, uh...
You stick to your musicals,
and your singing and dancing.
Thanks for coming back in, ladies.
We heard your feedback,
accepted your challenge,
and last night,
after a fraught dinner with my father,
Clay and I regrouped and cooked up
a new song for the four of us.
[CLAY] We wrote it from the heart.
About people like us,
who have to be careful about who we love.
We'll kick it off,
then you two feel free to join in.
We'll see what happens.
♪ Do you know what it's like ♪
♪ To be in love with you? ♪
♪ To have my heart still love you ♪
♪ When my mind knows it can't be true? ♪
♪ Do you know what it's like ♪
♪ To be in love with you? ♪
♪ Not to remember what my life was like ♪
♪ Before I first met you? ♪
♪ Do you know what it's like
When I lie in bed ♪
♪ And I think of you
And the things you've said? ♪
♪ How they're almost exactly
All the things that I've said too? ♪
♪ Oh, do you know? ♪
[ALL] ♪ I know I'll never find your loving
In anyone else ♪
♪ In anyone else ♪
♪ Though I'll try ♪
♪ Oh, and I'll try ♪
♪ And I know I'll never find your smile
In anyone else ♪
♪ In anyone else ♪
♪ Though I'll try ♪
♪ Oh, and I'll try ♪
♪ If someone were to come up to me ♪
♪ And say that they knew
How to love you better ♪
♪ I'd say, "Buddy, step into the ring
You're going down" ♪
♪ I'd fight a guy for you ♪
♪ I'd fight a girl for you ♪
[ALL] ♪ I'd fight myself
You know I would ♪
♪ If I thought it'd do any good ♪
♪ Oh, do you know? ♪
♪ Do you know what it's like
When I lie in bed ♪
♪ And I think of you
And the things you've said? ♪
♪ How they're almost exactly
All the things that I've said too ♪
♪ Oh, do you know? ♪
♪ How to look into your eyes? ♪
♪ To let go of your hand? ♪
♪ To start another life? ♪
♪ I just don't ♪
♪ Understand ♪
Kevin and Clay, wowza.
You completely captured the longing
of being in a queer,
interracial relationship in the 1950s.
Dare I say,
this is going to be extremely powerful
once we put it on stage.
Oh. Um, Clay and I wrote this song
for you and for us
to sing and enjoy in private.
It's... It's not gonna be in the musical.
- Why the hell not?
- Why not?
Riverdale's too provincial.
I'm under enormous pressure
from Featherhead
to deliver something that's mainstream
and commercial, and...
But maybe one day,
when the world's caught up to our song.
In that case, Kevin, Clay,
when the world does catch up
and this beautiful song
is included in your musical,
Toni and I will be there too.
But in the meantime,
we do enough play-acting in our real life.
[TONI] So with all due respect,
Cheryl and I would like
to be written out of Archie the Musical
until we can act
as our authentic selves in it.
[POP] Soup or salad?
Archie, what would you like
with your grilled cheese, soup or salad?
I...
I don't know, Pop. I...
I just... I don't know.
We'll just take both, Pop. Thanks.
All right.
You were saying?
Kevin's writing this musical about me,
and I don't know why.
The character he's writing
isn't the person I am.
He's got me picking between
Betty and Veronica in the show,
but for me, in real life,
the choice is actually
between basketball and poetry.
Ah. The classic conundrum.
You, my friend, are cutting a rug
on what Camus would call
an existential crisis.
A what now?
Your dilemma is real, Archie.
But it's not about having to decide
between basketball or poetry,
artist or athlete, Betty or Veronica.
No, it's...
Well, it's about having to make a choice,
any choice, right now, today,
that could affect the rest of your life,
and that's... scary.
Especially for a cube like you.
Jeez, Jug. You're right.
That is why I'm so unsettled.
And I'll stay unsettled
until I make a decision.
♪ 'Cause now it's time to take a stand ♪
♪ To pick a path, to be a man ♪
♪ Sometimes, you gotta choose ♪
♪ And give it everything you've got ♪
♪ You only get one shot ♪
♪ And you can't pick two ♪
♪ I can't pick two ♪
[POP] Here you go, Archie.
A grilled cheese sandwich
with a soup and a salad, as requested.
Thanks, Pop. But, uh...
I only want the grilled cheese.
And make it to go, will you?
I gotta have a conversation
with my uncle that can't wait.
I'll take the soup and salad. Thanks, Pop.
[JUGHEAD WHISTLES]
[ARCHIE] Uncle Frank,
I'm not gonna be
on the basketball team anymore.
I wanna focus more on my poetry.
Is that who you are now,
some kind of beatnik poet?
So you're just gonna bail on the Bulldogs
halfway through a season?
Well, I need you on the team.
You got Reggie, Uncle Frank.
I mean, he is the team.
Well, I can't approve of it.
I won't approve of it.
- You're gonna regret it.
- Well, maybe.
Look, Uncle Frank,
if I don't follow my heart,
I'm worried I might regret that even more.
Respectfully, I've made my choice.
[MRS. KELLER] Kevin?
Holy mackerel, we overslept.
- [MRS. KELLER] Honey, are you awake?
- Just... Window, window.
- Can I come in? Just for a quick chat?
- Just a second, Mom!
[WHISPERS] I love you.
Good morning, sweetheart.
Did you sleep okay?
Um, yeah, I did.
I'm just, you know,
anxious about the musical.
Oh. I can only imagine.
But I was thinking,
what do you say
the three of us have dinner tonight?
You mean, you, me, and Dad?
At Pop's.
We think it would be good for us.
A good step.
Yeah, let's do it. That sounds great, Mom.
Wonderful.
Now, you get dressed,
and I'll drive you to school.
So, Veronica, which one of your
famous Hollywood friends wrote this song?
Cole Porter did. As I knew he would.
And I trust you'll agree
it's worthy of our complexities.
♪ Have you ever caught a glimpse
Of your reflection in the mirror ♪
♪ And wondered if the person
That you saw was even you?
♪ Everyone applauding ♪
♪ It's a perfect presentation ♪
♪ Nobody would ever have a clue ♪
♪ They look at me and figure
She's a girl who's got it easy ♪
♪ I cruise through life
While Daddy feeds me with a silver spoon ♪
♪ But if they caught a glimpse
Of all my doubts and hesitations ♪
♪ Tell me, would they sing
A different tune? ♪
[BOTH] ♪ There's a universe inside ♪
♪ That no one else can see ♪
♪ A world inside ♪
♪ Where I'm alone with me ♪
♪ You can spend a lifetime
Looking deep in someone's eyes ♪
♪ And never see the universe inside ♪
♪ I'm scared to show what's underneath ♪
♪ I cover it with makeup ♪
♪ It's dark and petty, I know ♪
♪ But I need to be the best ♪
♪ And all they ever see
Is only part of the equation ♪
♪ Don't they realize I'm so much more? ♪
♪ If only I could find a way ♪
♪ To show them all
So they would say ♪
♪ "How we want to see
The real you shining" ♪
♪ Then I would never have to be
Afraid of nightmares or my dreams ♪
♪ So if you want me
You know where to find me ♪
- ♪ There's a universe inside ♪
- ♪ There's a universe ♪
- ♪ You must have one too ♪
- ♪ Inside ♪
- ♪ A world inside ♪
- ♪ Inside me ♪
♪ No one ever knew ♪
♪ I wish I noticed
But I never took the time ♪
♪ To look beyond the surface ♪
♪ And finally see
The universe inside you ♪
♪ Inside you ♪
♪ I hope that someday
Someone looks into my eyes ♪
♪ And finally sees the universe inside ♪
That was...
stunning.
What...?
What just happened?
Some kind of energy exchange, I think.
Yeah.
A seismic one.
[KEVIN] I don't know what to say,
but I completely felt
the pain of your isolation,
your desperate need to be seen.
Now that that's squared away,
I think we should talk about
whatever just happened during that song.
Okay. Yeah, super. We should.
It felt... primal.
I felt the same.
Charged and intense.
All this time, we've been thinking:
"When are we going
to climb Mt. Archibald?"
When in fact...
Maybe there are other more...
emotionally complex mountains to climb.
There you both are.
I've been looking all over
to tell you something.
I've been doing
some soul-searching, and, um...
I realized I've kissed both of you,
and I'm fond of you both.
[BOTH] "Fond"?
But I'm in a period of growth
and self-discovery.
So I'm gonna take a little time
and not kiss anyone for a while.
Or at least, I'm gonna try not to.
Okay, then.
Later, gators.
We've had a few speed bumps,
but now we're jumping.
The new Archie, Julian,
he's even better than the real Archie.
Kev.
We have to talk to you
about something serious.
The papers are signed, Kevin.
It's all been finalized.
Your father and I...
We're getting a divorce.
So that's it?
You're just...? You're calling it quits?
This isn't something
that can be fixed, unfortunately.
Sometimes, a man and a woman come to find
that there are too many differences
between them.
Sounds like you've got it all figured out.
- Oh, it's...
- Well, if you will excuse me,
we are presenting
to Principal Featherhead tomorrow,
so I've got a lot of work to do.
And, yeah, thank you for a swell dinner.
- Oh, no. Kevin?
- Kev.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Come on, everybody
Put your school books down ♪
♪ Come shake it up and feel all right ♪
♪ Summer's almost here
And it's Senior Year ♪
♪ Now it's party time at Riverdale High ♪
[ALL] ♪ No one's saying ♪
♪ The one thing's weighing
On everybody's mind ♪
♪ Sure is getting close to Prom Night ♪
♪ Shoo-bop, shoo-bop, ooh ♪
- ♪ We're getting ready ♪
- ♪ Shoo-bop, shoo-bop, ooh ♪
- ♪ So come along now ♪
- ♪ Are you ready for the greatest ♪
- ♪ Shoo-bop, shoo-bop ♪
- ♪ Night of your life? ♪
♪ I've been busy waiting ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't know what he's thinking
But I'm praying that he asks me soon ♪
♪ Don't wanna seem needy
I'm just hoping it'll be me ♪
♪ And I don't know what to do ♪
♪ With his cool red hair
He's beyond compare ♪
♪ I've been waiting my whole life ♪
[ALL] ♪ Archie ♪
♪ Waiting for Archie ♪
- ♪ Meanwhile, Jughead said ♪
- ♪ "I plan on staying in bed" ♪
♪ "Chowing down on burgers and fries" ♪
♪ Hey, Jughead, you're coming with us
To Prom Night ♪
♪ Hey, Arch! What have you been up to? ♪
♪ I've been writing an awesome song ♪
♪ Playing football out on the lawn ♪
♪ Got no worries, you know me ♪
♪ Everything is peachy keen ♪
- ♪ Shoo-bop, shoo-bop, ooh ♪
- [ALL] ♪ We've waited so long ♪
-♪ Shoo-bop, shoo-bop, ooh
-♪ We're gonna make it last ♪
- ♪ Are you ready for the greatest ♪
- ♪ Shoo-bop, shoo-bop ♪
- ♪ Night of our lives? ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
[LAUGHING] Bravo!
Very well-sung.
Mr. Keller, may I see you in my office?
Kevin,
I'll get right to it.
We're not going to produce
your musical this spring.
Well, why? May I ask why?
In this climate,
so soon after our brush with Communism,
we think it's better
to do something more traditional,
something people can get behind.
Furthermore,
original musicals are tough sells, Kevin.
I don't wanna say
that the drama club's funding
depends on your box office receipts,
but if you put up a sign
for Archie the Musical,
will people come?
I don't know.
But if you put up a poster for Oklahoma!,
I'm certain we'd have a complete sellout,
all three performances.
Well, everyone, congratulations.
We'll be like every other
high school in the world
and do Oklahoma! this spring,
so enjoy, um, singing about wheat.
Oh. Kevin, we're so sorry.
Are you sorry?
Because all of you nitpicked every song
that Clay and I wrote for you.
You questioned our vision at every turn.
Who knows? If you supported me even a bit,
we might've pulled it off, but you didn't.
Now all that time and energy and effort,
it was all for nothing,
so thanks for that.
Whoa. What snapped his cap?
That outburst
wasn't just about the musical.
Kevin was gonna give you
the lowdown after the workshop.
But, um, he recently found out
that his parents are getting a divorce.
That's why he's been pouring
everything he's got into this show.
[MRS. KELLER] I'm so sorry all of this
is happening at once, Kevin.
Mom...
it isn't my fault, is it?
I feel like...
all this fighting between
you and Dad started around...
when Betty and I were calling it quits.
No.
No, Kevin.
What's going on between your dad and I
has nothing to do with you...
or who you are.
You have nothing to feel guilty about.
Or ashamed of.
You are my son.
And I love you unconditionally.
[PLAYING CHORDS]
[HUMMING]
Hey, uh, Kev.
Uh, you got a minute?
Well, I wanted to say thanks.
Thank you, buddy.
For what, Archie?
I know I left you high and dry,
but working on your musical this week,
it made me take a long,
hard look at myself.
Forced me to make some decisions that...
well, that I needed to make.
Well, I'm glad some good came of it.
As I'm sure you heard,
we're not doing Archie the Musical.
Yeah, I did. I'm all broke out
with the blues about it.
I was looking forward to seeing
how the whole shebang would turn out.
And what was that you were playing before?
For the musical?
No, it's just something
I stayed up all night writing.
After my mom and I
had a long talk about stuff.
Well, come on,
will you keep playing it for me?
♪ An empty stage is set ♪
♪ For all of us ♪
♪ But never before ♪
♪ Has home felt so far away ♪
♪ 'Cause never before
Have I been without you ♪
♪ Friends forever ♪
♪ Never say goodbye ♪
♪ And through the years ♪
♪ Friends for always, you and I ♪
♪ Take a photograph, tuck it away ♪
♪ These are the times
These are the days ♪
♪ These are the moments of us ♪
♪ When we stand ♪
♪ On the edge of time ♪
♪ Don't you know I'm here ♪
♪ Holding on ♪
♪ With room to grow ♪
♪ Know that I'm waiting in the wings ♪
♪ So many memories are ♪
♪ Waiting in the wings
With happy endings ♪
♪ Since when has life
Been so much change ♪
♪ The buds don't show
When there's no rain ♪
♪ Since when has growing up seemed ♪
♪ Not so very
Not so far away ♪
♪ Since when
Since I sing without you ♪
[ALL] ♪ It's not the song
That saved our world ♪
♪ But it's the song whose melody ♪
♪ It keeps you in my heart ♪
♪ It brings you back to me ♪
♪ This is our song ♪
♪ It's not the song that saved our world ♪
♪ But it's the song whose melody ♪
♪ It keeps you in my heart ♪
♪ It brings you back to me ♪
♪ This is our song ♪
♪ It's not the song that saved our world ♪
♪ But it's the song whose melody ♪
♪ It keeps you in my heart ♪
♪ It brings you back to me ♪
♪ This is our song ♪