[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
How can I help, sheriff?
We're trying to get a hold
of Rayberry's family, if he had one.
Was there any next of kin
that you know of?
Shucks. Uh...
Actually, he might have had a wife.
Know her name or where she lived?
No. He was pretty tight-lipped
about his marriage.
He only mentioned it in passing.
But maybe he filled out
some forms at Pep Comics.
I could check with them.
Well, I'd appreciate it.
Let me know if anything turns up.
It's important we put this sorry mess
behind us as soon as possible.
[ARCHIE] You're dreaming, Reg.
Uncle Frank.
Will you tell Reggie that Marilyn Monroe
is much sexier than Elizabeth Taylor?
That no one on the planet
is sexier than Marilyn Monroe?
Sophia Loren,
Brigitte Bardot, Eartha Kitt.
And, yes, in my humble opinion...
Elizabeth Taylor.
Told you so.
What the frig?
You guys are itching for a switching.
I got a call from Principal Featherhead
last night, Archie.
Tells me your grade point average
is back up, B-plus. Like we agreed.
Yeah? So does that mean I get back...?
["LITTLE CRUISIN' STREET MACHINE PLAYING]
She's waiting for you in the garage.
♪ Sweet little cruisin' street machine ♪
♪ She's-a-lookin' kinda mean ♪
♪ Little cruisin' street machine ♪
It's all right, I'll clean up.
♪ Yeah, her front is slaggin' ♪
Wowza.
That is the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
I didn't know you had a hot rod.
I didn't know you liked cars.
I've always wanted one,
just could never afford it.
Well, neither could I.
[WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You should've seen this baby
when we found her at the dump.
She was a real junker.
My dad and I rebuilt her together.
- Must've taken months.
- Try years.
We finished it before he went off to war.
Sounds like you and your old man
were real tight.
We were best friends.
- Taught me everything I know about cars.
- And girls, I bet.
- Is this a straight-six?
- V8 with headers.
Louder and faster.
- Transmission?
- Three-speed automatic.
Okay. Most important question.
Can she lay rubber?
Now that I got my grades up,
why don't we play hooky and I'll show you?
[FIELDSTONE] Dead, huh? [CHUCKLES]
Ain't that a kick in the teeth?
Ah, you writers.
You all have your secret demons,
don't you?
It's a shame.
Talented guy.
Say, you wouldn't happen to know anything
about Mr. Rayberry having a wife,
would you?
No.
Just that he wanted us
to send half his salary
to a small town in South Carolina.
Maybe she lives down there.
- Do you have a name or an address?
- Just a post office box.
I'll have Bernie get it for you.
Thank you, Mr. Fieldstone.
You bet. Dead. [CHUCKLES]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
[CLAY] The thing I love so much about
what Ralph Ellison did with Invisible Man
is he took the broad idea
of existentialism
and applied it specifically
to the Black American experience.
Well, what struck me the most
was the novel's style.
It was almost like jazz.
Very improvisational.
No shock there.
Ellison was a jazz trumpeter
before he became a writer.
It influenced his work.
That said,
some of his literary criticisms
rubbed me the wrong way.
For instance, I love Zora Neale Hurston's
Their Eyes Were Watching God,
but he called it
a blight of calculated burlesque.
I can't help but think that's partly
because it was written about a woman
and by a woman.
See, I liked Hurston's book,
but I do see Ellison's concern, though.
She's writing us
as caricatures for a white audience.
Parts of Invisible Man really spoke to me,
but he was just so angry
and tortured all the time.
[CLAY] Ellison's speaking
to the larger truth of our existence.
It's not a book about day-to-day life.
It's about what it feels like
in the scope of our human experience
to walk around in our skin.
[MRS. GIBBS CLEARS THROAT] Hmm.
Well, I, for one,
am really digging this conversation.
So to touch on what Tabitha said,
what were our thoughts
on Their Eyes Were Watching God?
["YOU CAN'T CATCH ME" PLAYING OVER STEREO]
[REGGIE WHOOPING]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
♪ Baby, you can't catch me ♪
♪ 'Cause if you get too close ♪
♪ You know I'm gone like a cool breeze ♪
[FANGS] Hey.
How's my baby, and our baby?
Better now that Riverdale's heppest
budding rock star is here.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
I actually got some news.
I booked a gig in Centerville.
I'm not headlining, Ritchie Valens is.
But I did find out that there's gonna be
some music producers there
that are gonna be scouting for talent.
Fangs, that's fantabulous.
Where and when?
So I can put it in my book.
Actually, Midge, you can't come.
This show's
in the rough part of Centerville.
Heaven forbid something bad would happen,
like a rumble breaks out and you get hurt.
Plus, what if your parents find out
you're road tripping to the boonies
to see your deadbeat boyfriend
play rock 'n' roll?
I gotta be a rich and famous musician
by the next time I see them
or they'll never jive
with us getting circled.
But they will.
Okay?
[WHISPERING] Go get to class.
Okay, so get this.
According to Mr. Fieldstone,
Mr. Rayberry had half of his paycheck
sent to a P.O. box in South Carolina.
That's not something a man
who's planning to kill himself does.
Exactly, despite what Sheriff Keller
seems to believe.
Honest to gosh, Tabitha,
I'm half tempted to just sneak
into Mr. Rayberry's apartment
to figure out
who that P.O. box belongs to.
His wife, hopefully, but also
to see if I can find some evidence.
What kind of evidence?
That he didn't kill himself.
That he was the victim of foul play.
Would you maybe want
some company for that?
With all due respect to James Dean,
what if you had to choose between,
say, Marlon Brando or Paul Newman?
To marry? Paul Newman.
But if we're talking about just spending
one wild, reckless night together,
Marlon Brando.
Betty Cooper, you naughty girl.
By the way, I've been meaning to ask you,
are you using a new cold cream?
Because you're positively glowing.
No, just soap and water.
But my mom is making good
on her threat to stay out of my life,
and honestly,
it's like a weight has been lifted.
Well, good for you.
Look at us.
A couple of independent young women
unconstrained by the expectations
of society, our parents, and boys.
["PARTY TIME" PLAYING OVER STEREO]
♪ Well, hello, baby
Let's have a little fun tonight... ♪
Upon further reflection, Betty,
why deal in hypotheticals
when we have our very own Marlon and Paul
to play with here at school.
Reginald.
Oh. Hey.
I wanted to offer you a mea culpa
for not making our date
after things got busy at the Babylonium.
So I was hoping
you'd give me another chance.
- What's changed?
- Circumstances.
To paraphrase my friend Lauren Bacall,
a girl can't be all work and no play.
Here's the skinny.
I'm not scared of the chase,
but in my experience,
some people
don't really want to be caught.
Is that you?
Only one way to find out.
Andrews, uh, you doing anything tonight?
No. No plans.
Right on. Can I borrow your car?
I've got a date with Veronica.
I thought you were done
with her antics, Reg.
- Eh.
- Do you even have a driver's license?
Of course. I drove my dad's truck
to the farmer's market every weekend.
Don't gringle.
I'll be real careful with her. I promise.
Well, what the heck?
Sure, why not?
Like we learned in Spanish class...
[BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH]
- No fooling?
- I got nothing better to do.
Just look after her, okay?
Black Athena is everything
I hoped it would be, Cheryl.
I finally feel like I'm doing something
worthwhile and worthy, you know?
Yeah.
I happened to be walking by
your last meeting.
It... sounded tremendous.
It was.
Although Clay tends to monopolize
the whole conversation.
It's very clear
he has the hots for James Baldwin.
Who's that?
He's this real hep writer from Harlem.
One of my favorites.
Anyway, what's your tale, Nightingale?
To be honest, I'm really missing you.
Between me and the Vixens
and you and your new club...
we barely get to see each other.
When we do, it's three feet apart.
What do you say we catch a flick tonight?
I wish I could,
but I really need
to finish reading Native Son.
It's the next book that we're gonna
be discussing at Black Athena.
Okay.
Well, what if I came with you
to your next meeting?
And I wouldn't say anything.
Of course, I would just listen.
Tell you what.
It's the first few days,
and we're just getting started.
I just wanna make sure
that everybody feels comfortable.
Maybe towards the end of the semester
when Black Athena is more established.
All right?
Whatever you think is best.
Hi, Archie. How are you?
Betty.
Terrific.
- My uncle let me have my car back.
- I saw. The whole school did.
I'm assuming that means
your uncle's finally easing up?
He is.
Yeah. I'm out of the doghouse.
Well, in that case, I was wondering
if it might be time to go on our date.
Wow. I'd love to go out with you, Betty.
Swell.
Do you wanna pick me up tonight
at, say, 7?
Oh, crap.
I...
I lent my car to Reggie
so he could take Veronica out tonight.
That's okay. We can take the bus.
Oh.
The bus?
- Or walk.
- Walk?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Let's walk. That sounds romantic.
Okay.
Jughead.
Take a look at this.
Well, whoever's in the photo...
this was taken June 1948.
No, I think the woman's name is June.
And I think these are love letters
written to Mr. Rayberry
from a woman named June Simpson,
writing to him from South Carolina.
That's the same as the P.O. box.
Wait, so this is...?
Brad Rayberry's wife.
Secret or otherwise.
Hold on.
June Simpson.
She's in here
with an address and a phone number.
We have to call her
and let her know what happened.
She probably hasn't heard.
[LINE RINGING]
[JUNE] Hello?
Hi. Mrs. Simpson?
Who's calling, please?
Um, you don't know me.
My name is Jughead Jones.
I'm terribly sorry to be
the bearer of bad news, ma'am.
Brad Rayberry has passed away.
Who...?
Who is this, exactly?
Uh, I worked with Mr. Rayberry.
I'm one of his friends.
How did Bradley die?
I'm not sure.
He was found in his apartment in Seaside.
Did he suffer? Do you know?
I hope not.
I'll come as quick as I can.
This is the apartment on Magnolia Street?
Yes.
I can be there when you arrive.
In the meantime,
I'll just be tidying up his things.
Thank you. I appreciate that. Goodbye.
[CHERYL] Kevin, what happened?
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just floating on a cloud,
to be honest.
And what, pray tell,
brought on this state of bliss?
I just heard Clay perform his latest poem,
"Ode to Sidney."
He's like a magician, but with his words.
He is, indeed.
And where did this performance
take place, if I may ask?
At a meeting of Black Athena.
You went?
- You were allowed to go?
- Mm-hm.
Yeah. Clay invited me.
I mean, it's freedom, Archie.
Plain and simple.
A freedom of not feeling
my mother's breath on my neck,
- watching my every move.
- [CAR ENGINE ROARS]
It's like my life is suddenly
this open road before me,
and I've got both hands on the wheel.
Wheel?
What wheel? Who's got the wheel?
Me.
Oh, right.
[VEHICLE DRIVING IN DISTANCE]
Is everything okay?
I'm peachy. Yeah. I'm just...
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- Uh...
- Archie, if you want to call it a night...
- No, I don't.
I don't.
Not at all.
But I'm just wondering where Reggie
and Veronica are on their date.
I mean, where else is there
to go in Riverdale other than Pop's?
[ARCHIE CHUCKLES]
[SCOFFS]
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
So I heard through the grapevine
that Kevin attended
a Black Athena meeting.
Yeah.
Well, Clay was presenting a poem,
and he wanted to have his boyfriend there.
Mm.
Yeah, Kevin says
it was an amazing experience.
Life-changing, even.
- Okay, Cheryl. If you really wanna come...
- I do.
I... I would love to.
Okay.
Well, we're gonna be discussing
Native Son, as I mentioned,
so you can borrow my copy. I finished it.
Thank you.
I do not take this lightly.
I can't wait.
[ARCHIE] You had me worried sick.
Do you have any idea what time it is?
I thought you got into a wreck.
Kept imagining you in a ditch somewhere,
all mangled and bleeding.
Archie, cool your jets.
Where did you and Veronica go?
Look, after I dropped her off,
I didn't wanna come home,
so I hit the freeway.
- You did what?
- I hit the freeway.
I wanted to open her up a little,
see what she can do.
You took my car... out onto the highway?
Reggie, that car is my favorite thing
in the entire world.
Anything could've happened out there.
- Am I grounded?
- No.
But I sure hope
you dug your little joyride, Mantle.
Because that is your last time in my car.
Keys.
[FRANK] I heard you two fellas
going at it last night.
What kind of guy does that
to a supposed friend?
I mean, I built that car,
spark plug by spark plug,
with my dad, Uncle Frank.
Listen.
Your pops and I...
we shared a car growing up,
and we fought more about that damn jalopy
than Cain and Abel did about sheep.
But come on, Archie.
The kid's far from home.
He's far from his family,
everything he knows.
He grew up scraping by,
working his ass off
for things guys like us take for granted.
Can't you give him a break?
Well, how was the date? Worth the wait?
It was not stellar.
Archie was distracted the whole time.
How was it with you and Reggie?
Mixed.
Usually boys wanna go parking with me,
not cruising around town.
But straight from the fridge,
he, too, seemed preoccupied.
Kept glancing at his watch
like he had somewhere to go.
Hmm.
Maybe we should switch dance partners
and try again?
Or maybe we try a double date.
I know just the event.
Have you heard
about this big concert in Centerville?
Mm-mm.
All the hipsters
and hepcats will be there.
What say we give our beaus
a chance to redeem themselves
for being such unlicked cubs?
[TABITHA]
Their words are so beautiful, Jughead.
Describing how their love endured
despite everything they went through.
- What happened to them?
- From what I could piece together,
they got married in New York,
and then they moved to June's hometown
in South Carolina to start a family.
But there was an incident.
Their lives were threatened.
Oh, jeez.
White thugs threw a brick
through their window.
Burned a cross in their yard.
They went to the police
who threatened to arrest them.
Not the thugs.
Them.
That's horrible.
I saw things like that every single day
I was on tour with Mrs. Till.
In any case, the Rayberrys were terrified.
Not just for themselves,
but for the safety of June's family.
That's why Mr. Rayberry left.
And settled in Seaside. Yes.
I think the plan was
they were gonna save up enough money
to get June's family somewhere safe,
and then they were gonna go
live in Paris as expats.
But if they had such a clear plan,
why would Mr. Rayberry take his own life?
Unless, as you keep saying...
he didn't.
- Reg, wait up.
- What, you find a dent in your fender?
Look, I'm sorry about last night.
I lost my cool.
In that case,
I'm sorry for miscounting the tromps.
What can I say? I'm car crazy.
It's a disease.
[VERONICA] Oh, fellas!
Better clear your dance cards.
Fangs is playing a concert in Centerville,
and we wanna go,
so you're taking us on a double date.
First to dinner, then to the show.
Any questions?
For some of you,
this was perhaps your first time
reading Wright's harrowing
and thought-provoking novel.
Of course, it was my third.
Now, I obviously have a lot of thoughts,
but I wanna hear from y'all first.
The book asks,
where does responsibility lie?
While Bigger does kill Mary,
the young white daughter
of the rich Dalton family,
the story in my mind
remains a cautionary tale about, well...
- The dangers of white ignorance.
- [CLAY] Exactly.
Wright doesn't give us any easy answers.
That's what's so great about it though.
He looks at society as a whole
and how it works to keep us oppressed.
Bigger commits murder,
but his true crime
is stepping outside the box
that white society built around him.
I'll say it. Bigger was a stereotype.
Wright doesn't give him agency
to break the mold.
James Baldwin would agree.
And all roads lead to Baldwin.
Right, Clay?
[ALL CHUCKLING]
They do, Kev.
Cheryl, do you have anything to add?
Oh, no.
Um...
Only that this was
the most powerful novel I've ever read.
And that the family in the book,
the Daltons...
reminded me a lot of my own family.
In some unpleasant ways.
But I'm very glad to have read it
and to be learning more about it.
[JEREMY] Just out of curiosity,
is Native Son the only novel
by a Black author that you've ever read?
Yes, but I can't wait to read more.
You won't be shocked to hear, Cheryl,
that I maintain an ever-evolving syllabus
of Black authors I believe everyone,
regardless of who they are
or where they're from, should be reading.
I gave it to Kevin.
I'd be jazzed to share it with you.
- Thank you, Clay.
- Of course.
Now, moving on to Baldwin's essay...
[KELLER] Let me get this straight.
In your expert opinion,
Brad Rayberry didn't kill himself?
No.
What happened to him then?
Well, to put a fine point on it,
disguising murder as suicide
has been a gimmick in detective fiction
since the days of Arthur Conan Doyle.
Let me ask you this.
How well did you really know
your so-called hero, Jughead?
Well enough to know
he wouldn't take his own life.
Uh-huh.
Did you also know that he was
a card-carrying member
of the Communist Party?
[SCOFFS]
How about the fact
that he was a draft dodger
who protested the Korean War?
That he was a dope fiend?
Spent a month as a mental patient
at St. Vincent's in New York City.
This...
This is impossible.
Now, I'm no headshrinker,
but if you ask me,
someone who's got that many secrets...
well, it's a miracle
that he didn't take his own life sooner.
I'm curious to hear
how you thought the meeting went.
Better than I thought it would, actually.
I'm relieved.
I was worried people would feel
uncomfortable around you,
or that you would feel uncomfortable
around my friends.
They were, and I was.
Not so much uncomfortable as I was worried
that I wasn't going to say
the right thing at first, but then...
But then everyone settled in nicely.
It was really nice to have you here.
It was.
But I think you were right to be
so protective of Black Athena.
It's your club, your space.
I am so grateful
that I got to experience it
and that I got to see firsthand
what you're so passionate about.
But I think in the future,
I will just attend the more public events.
Well, we are hosting an open mic night
at the Dark Room next month.
I will be there, front row.
And maybe you can read
some more books off Clay's list.
Absolutely.
And maybe afterward,
we could discuss them together.
Well, I can dig that plan.
Also, what are you doing tonight?
Midge had mentioned
that there was a concert in Centerville.
Would you wanna go?
I am certain
I could make myself available.
[JUNE] This is the last letter
I received from Bradley.
Given the date,
he must have mailed it right before...
his passing.
In it, he wrote about finally
wanting to have his novel published.
He did? Really?
"If a publisher takes it,
we'll at last have the money we need
to buy your parents a place in the city
and move to Paris.
After everything we've been through,
I'm filled with such optimism
about our future."
Now, I'm not a detective like Miss Marple,
but that doesn't sound like
a man planning to take his life.
No. It sure doesn't.
Mrs. Simpson, Sheriff Keller told me
some things about your husband.
That he was a war protester,
and a communist.
And that he'd been to... an asylum?
Mm-hm.
And that's true.
But did he also tell you
that Bradley served in World War II,
and that he became addicted to opium
because of a war injury,
and that he checked himself
into St. Vincent's voluntarily?
And, yes, he attended
a couple of communist meetings
when he was young, and curious,
and suffering during the Great Depression.
That makes sense.
I'll tell you this.
My husband was an optimist.
Despite everything life threw at him,
even when he was working as a janitor
at the maple factory,
stuck on the graveyard shift,
he never lost his sense of humor.
He always believed
something better was around the corner.
If Mr. Rayberry didn't take his own life,
it means that someone else is responsible.
Do you have any idea who, or why?
The world can be a brutal place.
God knows who Bradley
might have angered or upset.
I've seen a lot of people
do horrific things in my day.
If you want to look into Brad's death,
young man, I won't stop you.
Take a gander. You won't believe
the bitchin' rigs on this one.
Serves us right
for stopping at the newsstand.
[ARCHIE] Classy chassis.
Check out the flip-top box on Page 13.
[WHISTLES] Whoa.
Fat city.
You know, Steve McQueen used to drive us
around Hollywood in his '53 Hudson Hornet.
And believe me, you've never heard
anything purr quite like that.
I've fixed up more
than a few V8s in my day.
My dad says I've never met
an engine I couldn't repair.
Damn, the plating on these rims.
[WHISTLES]
Cherry. I'd agitate the gravel
with those chromes.
Boys, aren't we gonna be late?
For the show?
We're still going to the show, I hope?
If we don't leave now,
we'll never make it on time.
You're right. We should boogie.
What are you doing?
Oh. I thought since we're late,
it'd be better if I...
Well, you drove on the way here.
It's my car. I'll drive.
Okay. Make sure you don't flood
the engine when you start it, 'cause...
I got it, Reg.
[JUGHEAD]
So, what's next for you, Mrs. Simpson?
I'm going to bury my husband
where we first met.
And then I suppose I'm going to see
about getting his novel published.
- Let us know if we can help in any way.
- I will, dear.
Bradley always loved comic books
since I knew him.
I'm sure he'd be happy for you
to continue adapting his stories.
I'd be honored.
And I'll talk to Mr. Fieldstone
about doing a tribute issue,
with the proceeds going to you.
That'd be much appreciated.
Tell me, are you two going steady?
- Who, us?
- Oh, no.
- I mean...
- Um, we're classmates.
- And friends, I would say.
- Good friends, good friends. Yeah, pals.
[JUNE]
Well, you two take care of each other.
That's important.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Arch, do you need a hand?
Unfortunately, Betty,
it seems as though someone goofed it
and forgot to fill up the gas tank.
So the problem is we need to get gas,
and we need to beat feet fast.
Considering the fact that I'm in stilettos
and Pop's is 5 miles back that away,
might I suggest you two cool it
and start walking
while we stay here and huddle for warmth?
[BETTY SIGHS]
Hey!
- Hey, hey!
- Hey!
[BOTH SIGH]
So I've been thinking, why don't you see
if Clifford Blossom can get you a car?
- Get bent.
- Why not?
Clifford Blossom
will do anything to keep you happy.
Star players get perks all the time.
No way. I don't wanna be any deeper
in that creep's pocket than I already am.
It's bad enough he's paying someone
to work on my dad's farm in my place.
Is that how you see me,
as a germ who's looking for handouts?
Aw, jeez.
You don't have to be so touchy about it.
What's the matter, Andrews?
Am I too uppity for you? Hmm?
Borrowing your car instead of waxing it?
Eating off
of your mom's nice dinner plates?
You're ringing up
the wrong area code, Reggie.
Then what? Am I forgetting my place?
You better knock
that giant chip off your shoulder.
Oh, yeah?
Maybe I ought to knock the one off yours.
Wait. Wait!
Submit.
Hello!
[BOTH] Cheryl?
And Toni Topaz and Midge Klump.
Are you ladies having car trouble?
We were on our way to see Fangs perform,
but we ran out of gas.
Right on. That's where we're going.
Well, hop on in. The more the merrier.
It'll be a blast and a half.
What about the boys?
With all due respect to those wet rags,
who cares about the boys?
[JUGHEAD] What an incredible lady.
Really makes you think.
Yes, about a lot of things.
Like?
Like, that I should go back on the road
with my folks.
As hard as the tour was... Is.
Yeah. I was wondering.
I was planning to take some time off
to rest, reevaluate.
But meeting June,
reading her letters to Mr. Rayberry,
not that I needed a reminder,
but it was one.
You're fighting for people to be free
and live their lives,
and to love who they want to love.
There's nothing more meaningful than that.
Well, maybe this time,
you'll actually send me my homework.
Yeah. Yes. Yes, I will.
Maybe I'll send you some letters too.
So, you boys wanna tell me what happened?
I was stupid enough to think I was
lending my car to someone I could trust.
Yep. And I was stupid enough
to believe someone
when they said we were Bulldog brothers.
[POP] I don't know about all that,
but if this is over some car,
I've got an abandoned jalopy in my garage.
Why don't you take it off my hands,
Reggie? You'd be doing me a favor.
That'd be incredible, Pop.
Bet they let you keep it in the Shop class
at the high school too.
- How's that sound to you boys?
- Great.
Swell. Thank you, Pop.
- Thanks, Pop.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Great, great. Go.
I want to come clean about something.
The night I took Veronica out,
I didn't go joyriding afterwards.
That's not why I got back late.
Oh, hold the line.
Well, where were you then?
I drove home to Duck Creek
to see my folks.
- [ARCHIE] How come?
- I was feeling homesick.
[ARCHIE] Why didn't you just tell me that?
I can't go around telling people
I miss my mom and dad.
I've never thought about it like this,
but I've always felt a little homesick
ever since my dad left for Korea.
- Yeah.
- It's the best way to describe it.
Homesick.
[SIGHS] Like I said,
he was my best friend.
I've never really had one since.
What about Betty?
And what's his name? Uh...
Beef Soup? Soup Can?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
- You mean Jughead?
- Yeah, Jughead.
I guess you can't really
talk V8s with him.
No, not really.
He's a good egg, though.
And Betty? She's...
Anyway, how's things
back home with your folks?
The same as always.
They're working hard, missing me, but...
they're happy I ended up
in a good home, with good people.
You're good people, Archie.
You too, Reg.
My dad would have got a kick out of you.
- Yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
Hey, you think the girls
are gonna go ape on us?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Uh...
Where are the girls?
[CHATTERING]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- [FANGS] ♪ Tutti frutti, oh rootie ♪
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rootie ♪
♪ A wop bop a loo bop a lop bop boom ♪
♪ Got a girl named Sue ♪
♪ She knows just what to do ♪
♪ I got a girl named Sue ♪
♪ She rock to the East
She rock to the West... ♪
I can't believe you came to my gig.
If you thought I was gonna miss
the biggest show of your career,
you've got a screw loose.
Thank God you're so stubborn, Midge,
because it turns out,
you were my lucky charm.
What's this, huh?
It's the business card of a music producer
from Phantom Rock Records.
[SCREAMS, THEN LAUGHS]
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rootie
Ooh! ♪
♪ Tutti frutti, oh rootie ♪
♪ A wop bop a loo bop a lop bom boom ♪
Holy heck!
That's in worse shape than mine
when we found it.
Careful. Watch what you say about Bella.
- Bella?
- Yeah.
I always dreamed about
having a car named Bella.
Well, Bella it is.
- You could use a hand souping her up.
- I could.
That's why I asked Betty.
- Betty?
- Hey, Arch. Are you helping out too?
Uh, yeah, I suppose.
I was telling Reggie you two missed
an incredible show last night.
Fangs, for sure, is the next big thing.
He blew the roof off the armory.
- Uh...
- Yeah?
- Can I have that one? Thanks.
- Yeah.
- What?
Oh, nothing.
Thanks.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Oh, hello.
You must be a friend of Mr. Rayberry's.
It's such a shame what happened to him.
May he rest in peace.
Thank you.
Well, I hate to impose. I'm Mrs. Martin.
I just live down the hall,
and I've run out of milk for my kitty.
I was wondering if there might be any
in Mr. Rayberry's refrigerator.
How strange.
I wonder what happened
to the milk bottles.
Milk bottles?
A few nights ago,
I heard the milkman making
an unusually late delivery
to this apartment.
The milkman? You saw him?
No. I was inside my apartment,
but I heard him.
[JUGHEAD] How do you hear a milkman?
[WOMAN] Well, the distinct rattle
of the glass bottles, of course.
My kitty heard it right away,
because it is just about
her favorite sound in the world.
Isn't that right, Miss Kitty?
[CAT MEOWING]