[JUGHEAD] Sixty-seven years have gone by.
It's the present day.
Since our last chapter,
teenagers have become adults,
gotten married,
raised children of their own.
Many have taken their last breaths.
This story tonight is about saying goodbye
to a town that was once lost in time.
But also goodbye to the people
who once lived in that town.
It starts near the end.
With a woman named Elizabeth Cooper.
She's 86 years old now,
resting in a small room
in her granddaughter's house.
She checks the obituaries every day.
You knew him in high school,
didn't you, Grandma Betty?
Seems like he was an interesting person.
He was.
We all were.
We had such marvelous adventures.
Oh. You wouldn't have believed it, Alice.
Well, that's it.
That means I'm the last of them.
Alice, honey.
I want to go back.
To Riverdale. One last time.
Before it's too late.
I'm forgetting more and more every day,
and I want to go back
before I forget everything.
Well, let's see how you're doing tomorrow.
If you're up for it, yes,
we can take a drive to Riverdale.
Thank you, dear.
[SIGHS]
[BELL JINGLING]
Hello?
[BETTY GROANS]
I must have fallen asleep.
I was going through our yearbook.
Trying to remember... [CHUCKLES]
- Remember what?
- Oh.
Everything, I suppose.
I'm going back to Riverdale tomorrow.
My granddaughter's taking me.
Though going through these pictures,
I just wish I could go back to how it was.
How we were.
You can, Betty.
You could pick a day, and I'll take you.
- Though it might be painful for you.
- Why should it be painful?
Because you won't just be living that day,
you'll be seeing yourself live it.
Still...
If you say we can, then...
I wanna go back to a day I missed.
The day everyone got their yearbooks,
senior year.
I had the mumps, and I had to stay home...
and I never got my yearbook signed.
I've always regretted that.
Then we'll start in the morning.
You just have to walk through that door,
and you'll have your day.
The day you missed.
Oh, my goodness, it's my room.
It's exactly like I remembered.
Hello, room.
Is that...?
Is that really what I looked like?
There were so many things I wanted
to change about myself back then.
Why? I was perfect.
We were all perfect.
My window. [CHUCKLES]
How many sunrises have I seen
out this window?
How many moons? How many times...?
How many times have I looked out
this window into Archie's?
In the thousands, at least.
Archie's about to have
a big talk with his mom.
About what he's gonna do after graduation.
[MARY] Hey, sweetie.
- Breakfast is ready.
- Thanks, Mom.
Hey, Mom.
I don't want to be a pest,
but I gotta let Vic know by tomorrow
if I'll be joining his crew on Monday.
It just doesn't make sense to me.
Driving around the country
with some dusty road crew,
pouring concrete, digging ditches...
Well, it's like President Eisenhower said
on the news.
I'll be building the highways
that help connect people and places
from coast to coast,
all the way to California.
It'll give me something to write about.
But you've written so many wonderful poems
in Riverdale.
Mom.
It's only gonna be three months,
and then I'll be back.
No, Archie.
No.
You'll get one look at the Pacific Ocean
and forget all about Riverdale.
Forget Riverdale?
Fat chance.
This will always be my home. Our home.
What?
You're just like your father.
He was full of wanderlust.
He always dreamt about
settling in the West.
He never did, but...
maybe you will.
With my blessing.
Thank you.
I love you, Mom.
I love you too, Archie.
I don't remember.
What happened to Mrs. Andrews?
[ANGEL JUGHEAD] She bought her dress shop.
And then one day,
a woman named Brooke came in.
They started a conversation,
and a few weeks later,
she moved into the Andrews house.
They stayed together until the very end.
Mrs. Andrews was always such a kind woman.
She once gave my mother hell
for disowning me.
[POLLY LAUGHING] Oh, stop.
[ALICE & POLLY LAUGHING]
Is that...?
[POLLY] We can't have the baby shower
outside in the middle of June.
- I'll melt!
- [ALICE] Please, stop being so dramatic.
We'll get those cute little paper fans.
Mom!
Polly!
You're alive!
And you're so young!
And you're talking again.
Elizabeth, what are you doing out of bed?
You have the mumps, young lady.
No. No, I feel fine, I'm going to school.
Mom...
You did it. You divorced Dad.
You became a stewardess.
Just like you dreamed.
Well, my dream was to see the world.
Not pass out peanuts on a puddle-jumper
to Poughkeepsie.
But life goes on.
No, wait, don't rush off, Mom.
Just... Can I...? Just look at me. Just...
Look at me.
For heaven's sake,
I'm looking at you, Betty.
And I'm seeing a girl who,
if she doesn't have the mumps,
better hurry up
so she's not late for school.
- Right. Of course. School.
- [ALICE CHUCKLES]
First...
I love you, Mom.
Oh.
I love you, Polly.
[SOBBING]
I'm so, so happy to see both of you again.
What in...?
Was my mom a stewardess for very long?
On the contrary.
One night, her pilot had a steak,
three martinis, and a heart attack.
And your mom took control of the plane
and flew it
from Riverdale to Poughkeepsie,
landing it safely.
That's right.
And one of the passengers on the plane
asked her to dinner out of gratitude
for saving his life.
And a few months later, they got married.
He offered to show her the world,
and she wrote you postcards
from everywhere they went.
Until one day,
the postcards stopped coming.
What about Polly?
She had her twins, Juniper and Dagwood.
She was very fulfilled.
She led a happy life with her family,
but she never got back to performing
as Polly Amorous.
I only ever saw Polly perform once.
At the Babylonium.
But I can still picture her.
She was such a star.
Are you ready?
To go back to school one last time?
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
Is this real?
Or a dream?
It's more like something in between.
But this is really what happened
on that day back in 1957.
Everyone is so young and beautiful
and carefree.
And they have no idea, do they?
How special this time is,
how quickly it goes by,
like the blink of an eye.
[VERONICA] Bee?
You're not supposed to be here.
Or did you have
some kind of miracle recovery?
Veronica!
[BETTY CHUCKLES]
Thank goodness!
This is too wonderful for words.
There's an ego boost
I didn't know I needed.
You should get the mumps more often.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Well, come on then.
The day has barely begun
and we're already behind.
There are about a million things to do
before the last bell rings.
We're getting our yearbooks today,
don't forget.
I can't believe it, Vee.
This is the last time we'll be walking
into Riverdale High ever in our lives.
Betty, we haven't even graduated yet.
It's too soon
to be swamped with nostalgia.
That said,
I'm feeling a little verklempt myself.
- I'll powder my nose. Catch you later?
- Yes. Later.
[INTERCOM CHIMING]
[TONI ON INTERCOM]
Attention, Riverdale High students.
- Toni.
- As your Senior Class President,
I'm reminding all students
to pick up their yearbooks
in the Varsity Lounge today.
One per student.
Now...
on a more personal note,
as we seniors look forward to graduation,
it's only fitting that I share
one final poem with you.
It's entitled "Dreams,"
by Langston Hughes.
Hold fast to dreams
For if dreams die
Life is a broken-winged bird
That cannot fly
Hold fast to dreams
For when dreams go
Life is a barren field
Frozen with snow
Students of Riverdale High,
we dreamed of a better school
for ourselves.
And with Principal Weatherbee's help,
we made it happen.
As some of us head out into the world,
please remember that we,
each and every one of us,
have the power
to make real and lasting change.
But we have to dream it first.
I remember these.
Articles about Rosa Parks
and the Bus Boycott.
Toni always made sure
that Riverdale High was in dialogue
with whatever greater issues
were affecting the country.
It's true. And that would continue until...
Don't.
Don't tell me what happened to Toni.
Please.
I don't want to know yet.
All right.
I won't
["YOU'RE GONE BUT STILL
IN MY HEART" PLAYING]
Ew. Barf. What are you doing here?
The word from the bird
is you have the mumps.
Back off, I don't want your lumpy cooties.
No. It's fine, Cheryl,
that was a false alarm.
Can I please get my yearbook?
And will you sign it for me?
Not right now, Betty.
As you can see, I'm busy. Later.
- But what if I don't see you again?
- You most certainly will.
As long as you're not germy.
I expect you at my and Toni's art show
opening at the Dark Room tonight.
And afterwards,
we're hosting a get-together at Thornhill.
- I'll be at both.
- Of course you will.
Now move along, Betty.
There's a line behind you. Toodles.
- Aw. Thanks, Fangs.
- No sweat, Betts.
Fangs is used to giving out autographs
now that he had a hit single
on the charts.
Baby, come on.
- "Pixie Girl" only made it to Number 8.
- That's a huge accomplishment.
And what finally got my parents to sing
another tune about us getting married.
- And wait till you hear his next song.
- Speaking of, we gotta motor.
I'm supposed to be
at the studio in half an hour
to lay down some tracks
before going on my summer tour.
Tour?
Six weeks on the road
with an all-star lineup.
A different city every night.
They've booked us a super boss tour bus
and everything.
Catch you later, Betty.
Bye.
It didn't work out like they'd hoped,
did it?
No.
Four weeks into his tour,
Fangs' bus was heading over
the Rocky Mountains
when one of its tires blew.
There were no survivors.
Poor Fangs.
He was the first one of us to...
pass away.
But...
that's his gold record over there.
It'll hang in this room
for as long as there's a Riverdale High.
What about Midge?
Well, thanks to Fangs' songs,
Midge and their daughter were
taken care of for the rest of their lives.
I remember.
I'm remembering more and more.
Hey, Betty, what are you doing for lunch?
It's a beautiful day.
Clay and I are gonna eat outside,
- if you wanna join us.
- Kevin.
It is a beautiful day.
I would love to join you and Clay.
Gosh.
I can't believe this is the last time
we'll ever have lunch together
at school, Betty. Can you?
I know.
Everything is going so fast, Kev.
And, Clay, I feel as if
I barely got to know you.
That'll change. Clay and I
are gonna be roommates next year.
Oh.
With me going to Columbia
to study literature
and Kevin going to NYU
to study musical theater writing,
it just made sense for us
to get an apartment together.
That's what we told our folks.
Well, my mom and Clay's dad,
they were swell about it.
Just asked us to be careful,
like they always do.
And we always are.
What happens to them?
Nothing awful, I hope.
No.
They lived a very spirited life
in the heart of Harlem.
[BETTY] Yes. I remember visiting them.
All they had to do was open a window,
and an entire universe
of music and art would pour in.
[ANGEL JUGHEAD] Clay became a
tenured professor at Columbia University,
and Kevin started an off-Broadway
theater company.
They saw and survived so much
from that apartment.
Kevin was 82 when he went to sleep
and never woke up.
Clay passed away a few weeks later.
He went out to enjoy some sun
in Central Park,
sat on a bench to feed some pigeons,
and that was that.
Hey, Betty? Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I was just thinking
about you and Clay, and how...
you two are soul mates.
Sorry. I know I'm being silly.
Well, um, speaking about soul mates,
what about you guys?
Have the four of you figured out
what you're gonna do yet?
The four of us? What do you mean?
Betty. It's us.
Clay and I, we know the truth.
But if you want,
even though it's the last day of school,
we're happy to keep up the ruse
that you're only dating Archie
and not the others.
The others?
Come on.
Don't tell me you've suddenly forgotten
you, Archie, Veronica, and Jughead
have been in a quad this entire last year.
A quad?
What are you so happy about,
Little Miss Mumps?
Oh. I'm just...
remembering where I was a year ago.
Feeling boxed in by my mother's
expectations and society's rules.
Fighting to have my voice heard.
Yes, yes,
we all read The Teenage Mystique.
And now?
And now, I'm remembering...
It's been a really fun year.
[SCOFFS]
Thank you for signing my yearbook, Reggie.
Anything for the gal
who helped me fix up Bella.
Gotta say though,
you and me could've had
one hell of a senior year
taking Bella up to Lovers Lane,
if only you'd chosen me
over Chowderhead Andrews.
I didn't choose Archie over you, Reggie.
Or over Jughead, for that matter.
Can you keep a secret?
One that only a handful of people know?
Yeah.
Turns out,
after Angel Tabitha's last visit,
I remembered what it was like
being with Jughead.
And being with Archie.
And Archie and Veronica remembered
what it was like being with each other.
But Veronica and Jughead
had just starting a thing.
And remembering all of that
sort of just took the pressure off of us
having to make a single choice.
So the four of us realized that we could,
and maybe should, just be...
together.
At the same time.
Are you saying that for the past year,
the four of you have been dating?
Each other?
It started innocently enough
with the four of us going on double dates,
me and Archie, Jughead and Veronica.
And then it kind of
naturally evolved from there.
Some nights,
Archie would sneak into my bedroom,
and Veronica would go home with Jughead.
Other nights, Archie would
spend the night at The Pembrooke,
and I'd go over to Jughead's.
And sometimes,
more often than you'd imagine,
I would find my way to Veronica's.
Okay. But you guys never thought
about bringing me into the mix?
Veronica and I talked about it, of course.
A flutter bum like you? But you were
always so focused on basketball.
Trust me,
I would've made the time, Goldilocks.
But speaking of that...
I'd better get back to it.
I'm so glad I got to know you, Reggie.
This you.
And I think you're destined for greatness.
You too, Cooper.
Did Reggie go professional?
Yes. The following year,
he played for Kansas State.
Then he got drafted by the Lakers.
During the off-season,
he would work at his family farm
until his folks passed away,
then he had to sell the land.
[BETTY] At which point, he started
coaching here at Riverdale High.
He was buried in Duck Creek,
next to his wife and his parents.
He had two sons,
who still run the used-car dealership,
Mantle Motors.
We go to the Babylonium next.
- [VERONICA] How's that absinthe, Betty?
- It's delicious.
It's just a bit early in the day for me.
Well, I want to prepare you,
because I have news.
That I haven't yet shared with the boys.
The final pieces
fell into place yesterday,
but I'm moving back to the City of Angels.
Los Angeles?
Why? How?
Josie McCoy's words
about taking over Hollywood
have been ringing in my ears
since her visit.
So I finally called my good friend
Peter Roth,
and asked about getting a job
working for him in La La Land.
I've done the small-town thing.
I've done the theater-owner thing.
And I now know what I wanna do next.
- And what is that, Miss Lodge?
- I wanna produce movies.
And run a studio someday, just like you.
I can't tell you how excited I am
to begin this next chapter, Betty.
To get in on the ground floor,
learn the ropes,
work my way up
to being a studio executive.
One of the gatekeepers.
Wow.
Sounds like an opportunity of a lifetime.
It is.
But I'm detecting something, Betty.
I'm so proud of you.
Of all the things you've done,
of all the businesses that you've started,
this move feels...
the most right.
I agree.
Like it was my destiny.
To be in the movies.
The only thing is,
California's so far away.
Betty...
It doesn't matter how far away we are...
we will always be in each other's lives.
I promise.
I always loved this theater.
It had a good run.
Lots of kids made out here.
Lots of gum under these seats.
And Veronica?
[ANGEL JUGHEAD]
The summer after graduation,
Veronica started as an assistant
at Silver Shield Studios.
But within a few years,
she was running the place.
She became known for her impeccable taste
and for taking risks on young, raw talent.
She won two Oscars and produced some of
the most iconic movies of our time.
Vee was buried
in the Hollywood Forever cemetery.
[SOBBING]
I visited her grave once.
And went to some of her premieres
before that.
She was such a force.
I wish...
I wish I had
kept in better touch with her.
With everyone.
All of us. We were so close.
Inseparable.
And then we just...
That's what today is all about.
Remembering.
And getting one more chance.
And no regrets.
- [CHATTERING]
- [CHERYL] Thank you for coming tonight.
This is the culmination
of a year-long collaboration
between myself
and my partner in all things,
Toni Topaz.
Our relationship is the most
thrilling thing I could've ever imagined.
We're always creating.
There's no separation
between our art and our love.
So please,
mingle,
enjoy the work,
and feel free to buy a piece, or two.
Also, I'll be sitting
at that table over there
selling a collected edition
of the first six issues of Black Athena,
Riverdale High's
acclaimed literary magazine.
It's sure to be a collector's item.
Thank you.
[CHEERING]
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
These paintings are incredible.
I should try to buy one.
In case you were wondering,
Cheryl had an incredible career
as a painter.
Her work was shown in galleries
and museums across the country.
Even a couple in Europe.
What about Toni?
Toni and Cheryl stayed together.
Moved out West together.
They settled in the Oakland hills,
in a Craftsman house,
where they lived as artists and activists,
and they had a son,
Dale, named after Riverdale, of course.
And how did they pass away?
Peacefully.
After living full, gorgeous, sexy lives.
[BETTY CHUCKLES]
What about Julian?
[ANGEL JUGHEAD] Bit of a lost soul.
After graduation, he enlisted,
served, and died in Vietnam.
He was 28.
Nana Rose?
[ANGEL JUGHEAD]
Reincarnated. Multiple times.
The Bee and Mrs. T got married.
Oh, them.
Frank Andrews and Tom Keller
were murdered.
[BETTY] By who?
A hustler they picked up one rainy night
named Chic.
What's happening over there?
[ANGEL JUGHEAD] Veronica has just told us
about her plans to go out West.
And we are not taking it well.
I wasn't there for that conversation.
No.
Well, you should be.
Might help cushion the blow.
What's the tale, Nightingales?
Why the long faces?
Ronnie just dropped an atomic bomb on us.
I told them my Los Angeles news.
Ain't that just the pits?
[VERONICA] Come on, boys.
I know we haven't been
talking about it lately,
but we all knew we'd be going
our separate ways after graduation.
Yeah, but now it just feels so real.
And... final.
Hey. Do we really wanna spend
what could be our last night together
acting like a bunch of wet blankets?
Senior year was amazing.
And incredibly fulfilling.
Not just physically, emotionally too.
Seriously, how lucky were we
to have been brought together?
Given the opportunity
to know and love each other
across not one, but two lifetimes?
We should be celebrating that,
not mourning it. Not yet, at least.
Betty's right.
The future can wait.
Tonight is about appreciating
everything we've been through.
And let me tell you,
we have been through a hell of a lot.
You know, I gotta say, if I had to live
through high school twice,
which we did...
I'm glad it was with you three yahoos.
I love you all so much.
Meeting you was the best thing
that could've possibly happened to me.
Heartbreaks and all.
And I'm so glad to be here
to say that to you tonight.
Hey.
Should we all take one last ride
in my hot rod together,
to Cheryl's after-party?
[DRAMATIC ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are the others?
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
Already inside.
- Why aren't you there?
- I can't.
I can't go in.
- How come?
- Because I know,
and you know,
[SOBBING] that this is the last time
that all of us will be together, ever.
- Betty...
- I don't want to say goodbye.
I just don't.
It will be too painful,
too much to bear, like you said.
It was a mistake to come back here.
I should be at home.
I should not be saying goodbye. It's...
That's life, Betty.
You say hello.
You walk alongside someone for a while.
And then you say goodbye.
That's the arc of a life, isn't it?
Every minute counts.
[DRAMATIC ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD PLAYER]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[ARCHIE] Okay.
As some of you may know,
I'm kind of a big-time poet now.
We know, Andrews.
You won't stop talking about it.
In any case, I wrote something
to commemorate our time together.
Aw. Are you gonna make us get the weeps,
Archie?
This is an ode to my best friends
And every good thing
That must come to an end
Tomorrow we won't see each other
In study hall
So here's a few memories for us to recall
And no, I won't be mentioning
The epic highs and lows
Of high school football
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
I grew up next door to Betty Cooper
Who everyone thinks is super-duper
[AUDIENCE CHUCKLES]
Just don't mutter the word "Tangerine"
'Cause it sets off her serial killer gene.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Veronica Lodge, always in pearls
There isn't a business
You haven't given a whirl
Funny to think you were never Prom Queen
Then again, you were once-upon-a-time
A human dialysis machine
I specifically asked Angel Tabitha
not to let anyone remember that.
Cheryl Blossom
You're as rich as a Rockefeller
You also kept your beloved Jason
Down in a cellar
But I'm glad to see
You and the Serpent Queen back together
Only thing, Toni, Southside's one word
So whoever designed your jacket
Is a terrible speller
Jughead Jones needs no intro
-He made his teacher jump out a window
-[ALL] Oh!
He thinks himself a private eye
Chained himself to Southside High
Do me next.
Kevin's voice is so beautiful
He belongs in a chorus
But he spends most of his time
Cruising Fox Forest
[CROWD LAUGHING]
Fangs, look at you now
You're a rockstar greaser
A long way from a cult member
Who stole organs to put in a freezer
[KEVIN] Yeah.
Last but not least, Mantle the Magnificent
Pound for pound
You're my closest equivalent
But there's that other Reggie
So how do we know you're even legitimate?
I'm gonna need to see
Some kind of birth certificate
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Not cool, Andrews.
You know I'm sensitive about that.
These are just some of our wild endeavors
But now we've come
To the end of our time together
It's truly one of
My life's greatest pleasures
To call you all my best friends
Forever and ever
[WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You weren't planning on leaving
without saying goodbye, were you?
I'm afraid it's time for me to go.
Oh.
Okay.
Well...
Tonight isn't goodbye, anyway.
I know we'll see each other again.
Maybe...
Maybe we'll even end up together.
I've always felt...
that it would be you and me
at the end of the road.
I mean, it started with us, didn't it?
A boy and a girl next door to each other.
That's a lovely sentiment, Archie.
But that's not what happens in the future.
No?
No.
Your mom was right.
You make it to California
and you don't look back.
Then you meet a sweet, strong girl
who makes you laugh.
And you settle down in Modesto.
Then you have a beautiful family.
You're a professional construction worker
and an amateur writer,
and you are so, so content
and happy.
And when you die...
you ask to be buried here in Riverdale...
[SNIFFLES]
next to your father.
Glad you went in?
I am.
But it reminded me...
there's one last person I want to visit
before we leave.
If we have time.
We do.
I just wanna get some flowers first.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
It was right after the beginning
of senior year that he...
Yes.
It was a terrible blow to the town.
At least it happened in his sleep.
What do you think happens to us...
when we die?
Well, I can't speak for everyone,
but for a man like Pop Tate,
I have a feeling he's probably
still doing what he loved best,
flipping burgers and mixing shakes,
and making people smile.
For the rest of eternity, I bet.
Strange to say, but I read your obituary.
In the paper.
It was lovely, Jughead.
Yours was a life well-lived.
As we used to say back in the day...
it was swell.
I put all my eggs in one basket.
Jughead's Madhouse magazine.
It became an institution.
[ANGEL JUGHEAD]
It was juvenile satire at best.
Just mocking all of the Sacred Cows.
People loved it.
And they still love it 70 years later.
It's mostly teens and kids who read it,
but I'm not gonna lie,
as far as legacies go,
I could've done a heck of a lot worse.
Do you think about that a lot? Legacy?
No.
Not too much.
Well, you should.
First it was The Teenage Mystique.
A self-published best-seller.
Then it was your advice column,
"Betty's Diary."
All I remember from those days
were the never-ending deadlines.
Then it was New York.
Freelancing and protesting.
There was so much
to be angry about back then.
Hmm. Still is.
The same fights.
But other people are fighting them now.
The younger generation.
Who grew up
reading the magazine you started.
She Says magazine.
The go-to source
for feminist and progressive causes,
exposing hard truths.
Still being published today, I might add.
As far as professional legacies go,
I could've done a heck of a lot worse.
Do you have any regrets
about not getting married?
None.
But I'm so happy
I adopted my daughter, Carla.
I loved being a mother.
And a grandmother.
That's my true legacy.
My family.
What about you?
Any regrets about not getting circled?
Sometimes.
I know it's impossible, but...
I wish that we could stay
in Riverdale forever.
With all of our friends.
As we were.
Young and beautiful.
Full of hope.
Bursting with love for each other.
I know it's not possible.
No.
It's not.
In fact, it's time to get you back.
I know.
I'm ready.
To face whatever comes next.
Oh, Grandma, look. We're nearly there.
Goodbye, town sign.
Goodbye, Sweetwater River
and all its mysteries...
[YOUNG BETTY] And Fox Forest
and its haunted trees.
Goodbye, Red Door,
and the secrets behind it.
Goodbye, room. Goodbye, window,
and Archie's room.
Goodbye, Pembrooke,
with your crackling fires
and sexy sleepovers.
Goodbye to cups of coffee
and late nights of writing,
and to maple syrup mornings
and spin-the-bottle parties.
Goodbye to buttered popcorn,
and double-features, and double-dates.
Goodbye to music and poetry and art.
Goodbye, Riverdale High.
Goodbye to basketball games
and pep rallies and dances at the gym.
Goodbye, lockers. Goodbye, Blue & Gold.
Goodbye, chalk dust, and bobby-pins,
and whoopee caps, and whoopee cushions.
Goodbye to friends, and feeling scared,
and Fourth of July camping trips,
and time capsules,
and time.
I wish... I wish there were more of it.
Goodbye, Riverdale.
It was wonderful getting to grow up here.
Grandma Betty, we're here.
Look, honey, she's asleep.
[ROBERT] I don't think
she's asleep, honey.
[BELL JINGLING]
[PENSIVE AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
["WE BELONG TOGETHER" PLAYING]
♪ You're mine ♪
♪ And we belong together ♪
♪ Yes, we belong together ♪
♪ For eternity ♪
♪ You're mine ♪
♪ Your lips belong to me ♪
♪ Yes, they belong to only me ♪
♪ For eternity ♪
♪ You're my, my baby ♪
♪ And you'll always be ♪
♪ I swear by everything I own ♪
♪ You'll always, always be mine ♪
♪ You're mine ♪
♪ And we belong together... ♪
Perfect timing, Betty.
We got you a shake.
Your favorite, strawberry.
Thank you.
♪ For eternity ♪
We'll leave them here, I think.
Where they're forever juniors...
forever 17.
Always grabbing a burger or a shake.
Always going to or coming from some dance.
Talking about school, the big game,
who's dating who,
homework,
whatever movie is playing
at the Babylonium.
You know, the moments that make up a life.
That's where they've...
Where we've always been.
In this diner, in this town...
in the Sweet Hereafter.
So if you happen to see that neon sign
some lonely night,
at the end of that long journey,
the journey that every one of us is on,
pull over, come on in, take a seat,
and know that you'll always
be among friends.
And that Riverdale
will always be your home.
Until then...
Have a good night.
[TYPEWRITER CLACKING]