[JUGHEAD] The popularity and
cultural impact of comic books in our time
cannot be overstated.
Superheroes were out,
horror and crime comics were in.
And me and my friends were obsessed.
What the hell?
You've gotta be kidding me.
Guys, you're not gonna believe this.
Do you remember when I submitted
my story to Pep Comics
and I received that asinine
form rejection letter?
Well, they stole my story.
- And published it.
- Stole it? You mean, word for word?
Well, not word for word,
but it's definitely my story.
I should sue them, right?
- Can you prove it was your story?
- Maybe start by giving them a call.
Oh, shucks to that.
Pep Comics is right here in town.
I'm gonna go pay them a visit.
Who's with me?
[XYLOPHONE CHIMES]
Good morning, Riverdalians.
Let's begin
with the most exciting news ever,
which is that the Entertainment Committee,
chaired by yours truly,
is hosting its first dance of the year.
Our annual sock hop
taking place this Friday night.
As is customary,
no shoes allowed on the gym floor,
so, boys, before you ask
your best girls out,
make sure that your socks match
and that they don't have any holes.
In short, the whole event is sure to be
the bee's knees in the cat's pajamas.
Tickets will be on sale all week,
and you'll wanna snap them up early,
as I can now confirm that
Kevin and the Crooners will be headlining.
See you all there.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Hey, Veronica.
I was wondering if
you wanted to go to the sock hop with me.
That depends. Can you cut a rug?
Are you a good dancer?
- Oh, yeah. Of course I am.
- I'm sure I believe you.
But I'm still gonna need
a demonstration, daddy-o.
Toni Topaz. Here to buy your ticket
to the sock hop, I hope?
That depends. Are you asking me out?
What? Why, I... Of course not. No.
I'm hosting the dance.
I couldn't possibly
be saddled with a date.
Not to mention, you're a...
And I'm also... Um, and girls don't...
Don't what? Dance with other girls?
Calm down, Peggy Sue.
No, I'm not buying a ticket.
My pal Fangs here is a singer
and we were hoping that you could give him
a shot at playing at the sock hop.
Add him to the lineup.
And the Serpents
will be there in full force.
Hmm. And start a rumble
as greasers are won't to do?
No, thank you.
Kevin and the Crooners will be performing
as previously announced.
Well, we offered.
Good luck selling tickets
with that B-grade barbershop quartet.
Later, Midge.
[PHONE RINGS]
[DOOR OPENS]
Okay, Bernie.
Who's the kid?
He's a writer, Al.
- Says we stole one of his stories.
- All right, come on in.
Tell me your tale of woe.
So you're accusing me of what, exactly?
Well, I submitted a story,
then you rejected it,
and then, surprise, surprise,
you ran a story that was exactly like it.
Now, you might call that a coincidence,
but I...
call it theft.
Well, I hate to burst your bubble, kid.
But I got news for you,
there are no original ideas.
I get hundreds of submissions every week.
It's all the same slop.
But the timing, the details?
Oh, you want proof?
These filing cabinets here,
they're filled with
every single story germ I ever had.
I got a backlog just waiting
to be farmed out to any hack
who can string together
a semi-coherent sentence.
Waiting? Like you're looking for writers?
- Always.
- Well, I'm a writer.
If I wanted to be considered,
what would I have to do?
Well, first off,
drop the persecution complex.
Take this logline, turn it into
a seven-page story by tomorrow morning,
and if it doesn't make me
wanna puke, we'll talk.
[ARCHIE] Thanks for helping me
out of this jam, Betty.
I panicked,
told Veronica that I could dance,
when the truth is I got two left feet.
You remember when I broke Midge's big toe
doing the bunny hop?
I do.
But don't worry, we will start
with something simple and classic.
The Twist.
[SWING MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD PLAYER]
Okay. So start just by moving your hips
from side to side like this.
Try it.
- Like this?
- No. Less of shoulders, more hips.
Okay.
- Like this? I can't...
- Um...
No. Maybe you just need
to focus on slow dancing.
Everyone knows how to slow dance.
[MUSIC STOPS]
["BE MINE" PLAYING ON RECORD PLAYER]
Okay.
One hand goes like this.
The other hand, here.
And then you just sway.
♪ For the rest of my life ♪
That's it?
Yup. It's pretty simple, right?
♪ I'm begging you, please ♪
♪ Be mine ♪
♪ Whoo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ For the rest of my life... ♪
[DOOR OPENS]
[GASPS] And what exactly is going on here?
- Betty was just showing me moves.
- I'm giving Archie a dance lesson.
- He's asking out the new girl.
- A celebrity from Hollywood.
Goodbye, Archie.
Bye, Betty.
Goodbye, Mrs. Cooper.
Oh, thank your sweet mother
for agreeing to chaperon with me.
Give me your expert opinion, Ethel.
I can take it.
I'm so jealous of you, Jughead.
It's my life's goal
to draw a story for Pep Comics.
They work with some
of the best artists in the biz.
Come on, you're as good
as any of those clowns, Ethel.
Tell you what, if I can finish these pages
and really make them sing,
I'll put your name forward
to Mr. Fieldstone.
- He's our editor-in-chief.
- Really?
Jughead, that would be a dream.
- Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Well...
let's see what he says first.
["BABY, LET'S MAKE SOME LOVE" PLAYING]
♪ Listen, sugar, honey ♪
♪ Listen to me ♪
♪ I need your loving
Now, can't you see... ♪
Yoo-hoo! Sorry to interrupt.
Just wanted to make sure that everyone
had their tickets to the sock hop.
Midge Klump?
One of my precious Vixens
with a common greaser!
Sacrilege! You get out of that car!
[MIDGE] Calm down. I'm coming.
Go!
["TEENAGE LOVE" PLAYING ON STEREO]
♪ A little quarrel... ♪
Is everything okay, Kev?
Yeah, sure.
Just a little preoccupied, I guess.
Thinking about what songs
you'll sing at the sock hop?
Yeah. Yeah, and other things.
You know, you haven't officially
asked me to the sock hop yet.
Okay. Um...
Well, I'm performing,
so I just kind of assumed you'd...
come to, you know, cheer me on.
Right, yeah. Of course. That makes sense.
♪ I love you so ♪
♪ But time will tell ♪
Um...
- What is it? Don't you like kissing me?
- Of course.
It's like I said, I'm performing,
and I don't wanna risk catching a cold.
It's always something with you.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means we've been dating for months
and we're still not going steady.
You haven't even pinned me yet.
How am I supposed to pin you?
- I don't play a varsity sport.
- It doesn't need to be a varsity pin.
It can be any old pin. Can be a ring even.
Gosh, when did you become
such a sex maniac?
For your information,
the fact that I want my supposed boyfriend
to kiss me once every blue moon
does not make me a sex maniac.
And I do not have cold germs or cooties.
And I will definitely not
be cheering you on at the sock hop.
Betty. Betty.
♪ Our teenage love ♪
Well, it's pretentious, clunky,
too much dialogue, but, uh, it'll do.
Bernie, get in here!
What?
- Yes, Mr. Fieldstone?
- We got a live one here.
See who's available to draw a seven-page
zombie story for immediate publication.
So I'm hired?
Dollar a page, take it or leave it.
Yeah, I'll take it. And I know an artist.
An incredible artist.
Young, hungry, cheap.
Loves monster movies,
a real fiend for gore.
Okay.
But I want those pages tomorrow.
Yeah. You'll have them, and, um...
Thank you for everything, Mr. Fieldstone.
[PIANO PLAYING]
Sorry, um, I didn't know
the music room was reserved.
It's not. I was just horsing around.
But you probably need it to rehearse,
I'm guessing.
Uh, my set for the sock hop, yeah.
You're Clay Walker, right?
I am. Just transferred this year.
And you're Kevin Keller,
son of the sheriff.
Dating the prettiest girl
at Riverdale High.
I've done my research.
Uh, where did you transfer from?
All over. My dad's in the...
Was in the military.
Cool, cool.
- Are you going to the sock hop?
- I wouldn't have a date.
I don't know many people.
Unless, uh...
you could think of someone I should ask?
A lot of people go stag, I hear.
It's nice to meet you.
Hey.
So I did a little brushing up, and...
I'm ready for that demonstration.
How do you feel about slow dancing?
Nothing better.
But upon further reflection,
I have no doubt
a Troy Donahue-type like you
can trip the light fantastic, Archie.
So does that mean...?
But, quite candidly,
I'm also entertaining other offers.
What?
Wow, okay.
However, being my escort
demands more than mere dancing.
It also requires
scintillating conversation.
I need to know
that you won't be a bore at the sock hop.
So why don't you clean yourself up
and come by The Pembrooke
at 6-ish tonight?
I'll be wanting to discuss politics,
art, current events.
Dazzle me with your wit, okay?
Dazzle you. Okay.
- Well, I should motor.
- See you tonight.
Archiekins?
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm rooting for you, stud.
So they just do whatever you say,
is that it?
Hmm?
Oh, you mean boys?
Boys aren't too, too complicated.
- I wish I had your confidence.
- Why don't you?
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
I'm only just getting my sea-legs
here in Riverdale,
but I can already tell
you're a catch, Betty.
A total Marilyn.
You and Kevin the Crooner
are going steady, aren't you?
Not officially.
We may even be on the rocks.
That's a shame, for him.
Why don't you invite some other boy
to the sock hop?
Get Kevin all hot and bothered?
That's always fun,
keeping our beaus on their toes.
Surely there's some he-man
at Riverdale High
you'd like to make time with?
Tickets. Get your tickets to the sock hop.
Buy one, get one free.
You, Dilton Doiley, why haven't you
bought a ticket to my sock hop yet?
For that matter, why are some people
trying to return their tickets?
It might be because of the Serpents.
What about the Serpents?
What are they planning?
They said they were gonna be
waiting in the parking lot
and they're gonna throw rotten eggs
at anyone who tries going to the dance.
Barbarians.
And who, pray tell,
is the one making these threats?
Mostly that scary Toni girl.
Of course. It would be her.
Well, this means war.
Dismissed.
[ARCHIE] Mom?
Can you help?
Hang on, I might have something
that'll do the trick.
[MARY CHUCKLES]
Well, that's more like it.
I'll have to let it out a little bit,
but other than that, it fits perfectly.
It's a little old-fashioned, isn't it?
Well, it was your dad's.
But he'd want you to wear it,
especially to your first dance.
Well, actually, I need it tonight, Mom.
Yeah, Veronica asked me over.
You're taking her to the dance?
If I'm lucky.
She wants to give me a test-run,
you could say.
I don't like the sound of that.
A bit haughty, isn't it?
It's not like that.
Veronica's from Los Angeles.
She's practically a movie star.
Their standards are different out there.
Oh, geez, Mom.
I'm fine.
Just seeing you here in his suit,
it just brings back so many memories.
Your father and I
went to the sock hop together.
He was such a romantic.
He wrote me the sweetest poems.
I still have them somewhere.
Poems?
He knew how to make a girl swoon.
- This one, I think.
- Yeah?
Mm-hm.
[ARCHIE] So Veronica invited me
over to her place tonight.
And I need to impress her.
So don't laugh...
but I wrote her a poem.
I need someone to read it
and tell me if it's crazy to give to her.
Okay. Hand it over, Walt Whitman.
Well, is it terrible?
No.
It's actually really sweet.
You have a poet's soul, Arch. Who knew?
[JAZZ BASS MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHERYL] So this is where
the Serpents dwell.
I always imagined it'd be something
more like a biker bar, but this is...
The Dark Room's a coffee house
for bikers, beatniks, and bad-asses.
Which begs the question,
what are you doing here, preppy?
A better question,
why are you ruining my sock hop
the same way your slimy Serpent pal
tried to ruin my virtuous Vixen?
Okay, Cheryl, you want people
at your dance, I dig it.
So I'll pitch it again,
let my boy Fangs blow the roof off the gym
and we'll pack the place.
For the bazillionth time,
I have already booked
Kevin and the Crooners.
Yeah, the Crooners are doneskis.
Look, Fangs is about to play,
so why don't you
order yourself a cappuccino,
take a load off, and hear him play.
Maybe you'll change your mind,
and you and I can get better acquainted.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Archie, you made it.
- Am I late?
- Oh, not at all, loverboy.
We were discussing President Eisenhower's
decision to run for a second term.
And let me warn you,
the others are very divided.
I'm sorry, "others"?
Come. Come on in.
We're having aperitifs in the parlor.
[BETTY] Mom, can I ask your advice
about something?
[ALICE] Of course, honey. What is it?
I think I'm having
weird feelings about Archie.
Oh.
What sort of feelings?
Like... stirrings?
When we were dancing, I felt...
a flutter in my stomach.
Is it possible that this fluttering
is a reaction
to feeling underappreciated by Kevin?
I hadn't thought of it that way.
Which is why it's a good thing
that you came to me.
Holy hell, Ethel.
There is no way that Mr. Fieldstone
doesn't hire you after he sees these.
- You really think so?
- Yeah.
- Even though I'm a girl?
- If he doesn't, I'll eat my own crown.
So, uh, Jughead,
the sock hop's tomorrow night.
- It is?
- What if we went together?
Like, for kicks?
Yeah. Yeah, just for kicks.
It might be fun.
Could have a decent spread.
- Cookies and whatnot.
- [KNOCK ON DOOR]
Since when are boys allowed in your room?
We're just studying, Mom.
You're lucky your father's
working nights at the factory this week.
I was actually just leaving.
I'll see you at school tomorrow.
Excuse me. Sorry.
So then I said, "Sorry, Mr. Sinatra,
but I think Elvis sang it better."
Archie, are you all right?
You've been quiet all night.
Yeah.
I'm good. I just...
Just taking it all in. Soaking it up.
Like the sponge that you are.
I see you're admiring the painting.
- It's a...
- It's a Monet, am I right?
Indeed.
You have a connoisseur's eyes, Julian.
I appreciate beautiful things.
Every summer, my family goes
on an art-buying tour in Europe.
Archie, what do you think of the painting?
Um...
It's beautiful and all. Uh...
I guess I just prefer an artist
like Norman Rockwell.
Then again, I'm not an
art-tour-through-Europe kind of guy.
That's obvious from what you're wearing.
Where'd you get that suit?
Some thrift store?
It's my father's suit.
And you better shut your trap, Blossom.
Wasn't he buried in his suit?
Or did he have more than one?
He was buried in his uniform.
Well, I, for one,
think you look very striking, Archie.
And I like a bit of variety
in my men's attire.
As well as in my men.
So who's up for charades?
You know, Veronica,
it's been a real swell night, but, uh...
I'm just gonna blow out of here.
If I stay, I might be liable
to spill someone's blue blood
all over your nice, expensive things.
[DOOR OPENS, THEN SLAMS]
Good morning, Mrs. Andrews.
As you may know, I'm Veronica Lodge.
Is Archie home, by any chance?
He's at the grocery store.
Shopping? This early?
Archie told me everything
that happened last night.
Well, that's actually why I'm here.
I feel terrible about it.
I didn't mean for things to happen
the way they did.
My Archie is not some Hollywood playboy.
He's a simple boy.
So simple that he's mad
at Julian Blossom and himself
for what happened at your soirée,
when you and I both know
who the real villainess was.
[SCOFFS] I mean, what kind of person
auditions boys to go to a sock hop?
Well, when your parents are actors...
Sorry, that's not an excuse.
Listen, if you hurt my boy,
you and I are going to have
some serious trouble,
Little Miss Femme Fatale.
[ALICE] Thanks for stopping by, Kevin.
High Point?
Okay.
So Betty tells me that the two of you
have had some troubles as of late.
Would you agree?
I feel awful, Mrs. Cooper.
It's like, um...
Betty wants these things from me,
but I'm not sure I can give them to her.
It's perfectly normal
for girls Betty's age to have certain...
expectations of what their boyfriends
are willing to do.
May I make a suggestion?
I'm gonna give you this.
You see, Betty just wants to be pinned.
She wants to feel appreciated.
And then all of those feelings
will settle.
Won't a pin mean
she'll expect more from me?
Oh, no. A pin takes off the pressure.
You see, it's a symbol
for what every girl craves.
They just want a fella that's gonna
carry their books home from school,
or take them to the movies Saturday night,
or call them on the telephone
before supper.
Is that all?
A pin is a promise, Kevin.
Don't tell anyone,
but this is the actual pin
that Mr. Cooper gave me
back in high school.
See, this pin somehow answered a desire...
that we both were feeling.
And then things were fine and pure
from that point forward.
You're a good boy, Kevin.
And Betty is a good girl.
And I believe that this pin...
will take care of everything.
Tickets.
Get your tickets for tonight's sock hop.
- Hurry up.
- You, four eyes.
- Get your tickets to the sock hop yet?
- Uh...
No.
Well, pony up, Poindexter.
My pal Fangs Fogarty is performing,
and trust me,
you'll be kicking yourself if you miss it.
I'll take one.
Five. Five. I'll take five.
By the way,
did you break the bad news to Kevin yet?
[CHERYL] No. But I will.
Can you dig it?
- [SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
- Putting aside the fact
that you were drawing
while Dr. Doiley was lecturing,
in and of itself
a flagrant violation of school etiquette,
Dr. Werthers and I
are also deeply concerned
about what you were drawing.
Where did the vision for this
come from, Ethel?
Your subconscious? A nightmare?
The movies?
They're for a story.
What kind of story?
A comic book
that I'm on deadline to finish.
That's why I was drawing
in Dr. Doiley's class.
I'm trying to get a job at Pep Comics.
They're based here in town.
I'm sorry, Ethel,
but your budding career
as an illustrator of lurid comic books
doesn't remotely justify this behavior.
You have a week's detention,
starting today.
[ARCHIE] Veronica.
Archie, hi.
Look, about last night...
I'm sorry I rushed out of there like that.
I, uh...
I sincerely was going to
rip Julian Blossom's head off.
Well, he would've deserved it.
And I'm mortified
about what he said to you.
I truly had a good time
getting to know you better.
Well, um...
in that case...
if you haven't made your decision yet,
I'm still keen
on taking you to the sock hop.
I would love that, Archie.
But I've already made my selection.
And I'm not going with anyone.
- What? Why?
- [VERONICA SIGHS]
With so many excellent options,
it's simply impossible
for an "it girl" to choose.
Options like Julian Blossom?
I don't get you, Veronica.
What was last night's dog-and-pony show
all about, then?
Forget last night. This entire week?
Making us...
Making me jump through hoops like that?
It was a game, Archie.
The queen of the hive
gets all her worker bees a-buzz
and then flies away before...
Before anyone's stung too badly.
[BETTY] So have you made your pick yet?
Here's a late-breaking scoop
for Hedda Hopper:
"Socialite Veronica Lodge
has decided to go stag to the sock hop."
What happened? What about Archie?
I'm in the midst
of a rude awakening, Betty.
Turns out
I've been careless and thoughtless
with a lot of the boys at Riverdale High.
Archie, most especially,
and most undeservingly.
Did you not like his poem?
What poem?
Archie wrote you a poem.
Did he not give it to you?
Not that I know of.
Not that I deserve, in any case.
Wait a minute. So who's Archie
going to the sock hop with?
No one, as far as I know.
I'll tell you one thing, though.
Whoever does end up going with Archie,
she is one lucky girl.
[ETHEREAL SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Betty.
Can I talk to you for a second?
It's important.
Sure. Let's talk.
Cheryl bumped me and the Crooners.
Fangs Fogarty's performing.
Apparently he's God's gift or something.
I heard. Kev, I'm sorry.
No, um...
I'm sorry, Betty.
I'm really, really sorry.
I was a dope, and...
You are the most wonderful,
most ginchiest girl in the world,
and I took that for granted.
That won't happen again. Um...
Betty Cooper, will you go steady with me?
Kevin...
Things will be different this time,
I promise. I...
I love you, Betty. I do.
And you make my heart feel full.
So will you be my girl?
Will you go to the sock hop with me?
Yeah. Of course.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
All right.
Uh...
[CHUCKLES] How do I...?
I'll... I'll do it.
Okay.
All right.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Guess who didn't show up
for her assigned detention.
The Muggs girl?
I'm concerned, Felix.
I think we should
speak to Ethel's parents.
God knows what's troubling that girl.
You want me to believe that a girl,
this girl,
generated these pages?
Yes.
And she's currently skipping detention
because of how badly she wants
to draw comic books for you,
Mr. Fieldstone.
Well, young lady, let me congratulate you.
These are the most putrid pages
I've seen in a long time.
And that's the highest compliment
I can give any artist.
Freckles, you have some real talent.
- What's your name?
- Ethel.
Thank you, Mr. Fieldstone.
Well, Freckles, you and Boy Wonder here
make a terrific team.
So, what are you, boyfriend-girlfriend?
Uh, no, we are just creative partners.
But we are going to the sock hop together.
Ah.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Smithers, I'm about to put my face on.
My apologies, Miss Veronica,
but I was emptying the bins
and came across something
that I believe belongs to you.
What's this?
It seems to be a poem, miss.
- Mom, Dad, is everything all right?
- We got called down to your school.
They said you're acting
like some delinquent,
drawing dirty pictures.
[MRS. MUGGS]
On top of staying up at all hours,
inviting boys into your bedroom,
and now missing detention?
We did not raise you this way, Ethel.
Maybe if you didn't drink so much, Mom.
And maybe if you weren't so miserable
all the time, Dad.
- What the hell did you just say to me?
- Never mind.
[MR. MUGGS]
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to the sock hop with Jughead.
Over my dead body you are.
[DOOR SLAMS]
["STRANGE LOVE" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Well, I don't what it could be ♪
♪ Something about you
That really threw me ♪
♪ Could it be the way that you walk
Or the way that you talk ♪
♪ Well, it's something I can't explain
An up and down like falling rain ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, you thrill me so ♪
♪ I'll never let it go ♪
♪ All through my life
I have looked for a girl like you... ♪
If it isn't Kevin
of Kevin and the Crooners fame.
Yeah, hardly.
Just plain old Kevin Keller tonight.
I was sorry to hear that
tonight's lineup had been changed.
Oh, easy come, easy go.
Supposedly
Fangs is an out of-this-world singer.
Yeah, and he sure is easy on the eyes.
But I can say the same about you.
Anyway, I was really looking forward
to seeing you perform tonight.
Maybe you can give me a private concert
one of these days?
Yeah.
Um, look, Clay,
Betty's waiting for her punch.
- So if you'll excuse me?
- Of course.
Have fun tonight.
Good evening, Riverdale High.
Who's ready to rock and roll?
[CROWD CHEERING]
In that case, find somebody to hold onto,
'cause we're about to shake things up.
- [SCATTING]
- [GIRLS SCREAMING]
♪ Tutti Frutti, oh Rudy ♪
[SCATTING]
♪ Got a gal named Sue ♪
♪ She knows just what to do ♪
♪ I got a gal named Sue ♪
♪ She rock to the east
She rock to the west ♪
♪ She's the girl that I love best ♪
♪ Tutti Frutti, oh Rudy ♪
♪ Tutti Frutti... ♪
Told you Fangs was the next Chuck Berry.
I wouldn't go that far.
Come on, let's see your moves.
I'm fine supervising from right here,
thank you very much.
One boogie-woogie,
and I'll stop hassling you,
if that's what you really want.
Fine. Just one dance.
♪ She knows how to love me, yes, indeed ♪
♪ Boy, don't know what she do to me? ♪
♪ Tutti Frutti, oh Rudy ♪
[FANGS SCATTING]
♪ Only you ♪
♪ Can make all this world seem right ♪
♪ Only you... ♪
I got the poem you wrote for me.
Or, at least, I think you did.
A stolen look across the hall
I hope she hears my silent call
Dreams of walks through moonlit nights
With the girl more beautiful
Than all the cosmic sights
It's beautiful, Archie.
Um, it barely rhymes.
How do you feel about a do-over?
Or, to put it in other words...
Archie Andrews, may I have this dance?
I'm sorry, Veronica.
Maybe next time. Will you excuse me?
Of course.
Veronica Lodge.
Julian Blossom.
Where have you been keeping yourself?
Oh, I've been around.
Waiting for my moment.
You could do a lot worse, you know.
[VERONICA] Why not?
♪ And fill my heart with love ♪
♪ For only you ♪
♪ Only you ♪
♪ Can make all this change in me ♪
♪ For it's true ♪
♪ You are my destiny ♪
Boys and girls dancing in chaste harmony,
just as God intended.
Wouldn't you agree, Ms. Blossom?
Yes.
Everything is as it's meant to be.
♪ Only you ♪
♪ Can make all this world seem right ♪
♪ Can make the darkness bright... ♪
Ethel?
Ethel?!
Ethel.
Oh, my God.
Is this blood?
[SOBBING] Jughead.
Something terrible has happened.
♪ For only you ♪
♪ Only you ♪
♪ Can make all this change in me ♪
♪ For it's true ♪
♪ You are my destiny... ♪