Last season on Dexter
The butcher bodies was submerged inside these heavy duty garbage bags
Did you here that
30 bags! Do you know what that means?
There might be a new massmurderer out there way worse than the icetruck killer
8 confirmed victims of the bay harbour butcher
That's what the press is callling whoever dumped those bodies offshore
Last thing Miami need is another serialkiller
Any idea who the FBI send in?
Some guy named Lundy
We have positive id's on all 18 of our complete bodies
All 13 was tried for murder or at least expected of murder
Bay harbour butcher give me one shot at putting a bullet in the fuckers head
- You realy feel that way?
- Yes that's the one thing to value a human life
Yeah but i think we had different homework assignments
Tell me the truth
are you an addict?
Yes, I happen to be Christine
- I'm Dexter
- Hi Dexter
There's my sponsor
So tell me exactly how full of shit are you
This woman see's me
Somehow she's able to make me feel ok about what I am
Yo're gonna tell me all your
deepest darkest secrets
Laura Moser. My mother was murdered
I never told anyone that before
Did you find out what happened to the men responsible for your mothers murder
Santos Jiminez.
went into witness protection
Where are you?
I've decided to look up
someone from my past
1972 !
You slaughtered her
and she sold cocain
she was a snitch for a cop
she was fuckin him
It seemed my foster father and my biological mother where having an affair
Did he blame himself for her death?
Is that why he took me in
or was he just using her
Was he using me?
There ain't no papertrail on the early years of Dexter Morgan
Your past is a bigger mystery
than fuckin Jimmy Hoffa
Back off
If Dexter files a complaint you will be took off the force
He's hiding something Maria I can feel it
I did some bloodslide analyses
You will find out what you want what I realy am
- You don't understand
- Well then make me
Who the fuck are you?
Pardon my tits
How could you do this to Rita and not to mention her kids
You and Lila stayed in a hotel together
It's over Dexter
I'm sure you've heard we have a suspect in the Bay Harbout Butcher case
Sergeant James Dokes
He had the slides?
Carefully hidden in the trunk of his car at the airport
Jesus christ Morgan
you're the Bay harbout butcher
You sure about that? You might want to check with Lundy
What's it gonna be Morgan? Kill me now or set me free
Don't worry i'll send the FBI your way soon enough
You're still gonna try to frame me
Mission accomplished
After tomorrow i'll be out of reach, permanently
You going somewhere?
Good bye Lila
Hey who's out there anybody out there
- What are you doing there
- His name is Dexter Morgan
I found out that he's the Bay harbour butcher
Please just open this gate
Oh hey your alive
Im ok
oh you
Dexter.
What the fuck are you doing
No turn that off you're insane
What where you thinking? are you insane!
I where just trying to bring us back together again
The Lila experiment is officialy over
Could have had it all Dexter
I've never been one to put much weight
in the idea of a higher power
but if I didn't know better I have to believe that some
force out there wants me to keep doing what i'm doing
You wanted to be close to me Lila?
This is the most I have to offer
You taught me to accept who I am
Thank you
The code is mine now
is mine alone
so too are the relations I cultivate
My father might not approve but i'm no longer his disciple
I'm a master now
an idea transcended into life
Our father
Ah life
Life is ritual
routine
control
and an essential part of that routine
regular oral hygiene
well
Few minutes that'll numb right up
So
how was your summer Dexter?
I went to the carnival
I even won a prize
Hope you stay away from all the sweet stuff
Nah ususaly i'm..good but sometimes i indulge
I also made it a point to meet new people
Can never have to many friends
Now this temporary crown is gonna go way into the back
So there might be some blood
Not a problem
You still have your boat?
Oh you bet!
That's the only place I can realy let everything go
That's great
We're gonna have you up and
out on that water in no time
For someone that needs to spend
his life pretending to be normal
I've been able to finaly settle in
to a nice, normal world
and Rita is the scafolding
that holds that world in place
What are you thinking
Life is good
Here you go buddy
Ok Ashter you're up
Mickey mouse, unicorn or starfish?
Just plain round panncakes Dexter
She's growing up
It starts with panncakes?
It starts when it starts
Hey Dexter
uhm, can you come to dads day
at my school tomorrow
Just tell me what to do
Bye Charlotte
Bye Mom See you Dexter Bye Mom
Get your bag!
You hear that?
Hear what
The calm
everything is sowing into place
for the first time in my life
I got these terrific kids
There's no longer any drama surrounding me
and I have this great
generous, gentle guy
Most normal people enjoy
a sacred pact with society
Live a good life and
society will take care of you
but if society drops the ball then
someone else have to pickup the slack
That's where i come in
Fred Bowman a.ka Freebo
kills two college girls in skates
on the state police screwup
otherwise known as Floridas catch
and release program
he does the deed, gets away with murder
and falls of the radar
everyone's radar but mine
You got a birthday coming up dad
What to get the man who had everything
How about...
Freebo?
Morning Dex
Dexter the doughnut guy
Part of my routine
but let the record show
im not the only one with a daily ritual
Angel Baptista, bearclaw
Vince Masuka. Lemon custard
better than sex
actualy it's not
Hey I need a favour
You think you could
proof an article i'm running for FQ
Forensics Quaterly.
Right. Yeah
The editor was stoked that i was the LFI
lead forensic investigator
on the BHB
Bay harbour butcher
- Hey
No biggie
i've been published before
Penthouse doesn't count
Hey! That letter was famous!
Death by pastry
You changed your hair
Makes you look younger
I don't want to look younger
By the way nice job on the Renaldi case
Yeah, well...
murder/suicide pretty straight forward
Oh but still the report was spot on right
All right
Quinn's been in homicide for two weeks and he noticed
Noticed what?
My hair
I changed my hairstyle for the
first time since I was eight
Ahh short...er, shorter
Quinn he is just showing off
his detective skills
Oh you think he thinks i'm a potential lay?
That is not happening
and as long as you're not noticing things
You also not noticed that i've given up men,
liquir and smokes for the last 27 days
this is you're remembering days birthday
Dad. Birthday. Right.
Blue room seven thirty like always
Tried calling you last night
I.. wasn't home
I also tried your cellphone
You're in the same pants that you
had on yesterday
and that's just a backup
when you keep a locker
I thought a part of your restructuring
of the department
was you staying out of our personal lifes
Anything you want me to know?
Know this I went out and
had a great time last night
and you should be happy for me
besides
since when do you care
Since this, follow me
Ok guys  listen up
I just got word from upstairs
that Angel will no longer be detective Baptista
in two days he will be
dectective Sergeant Baptista
Im sorry for all the red tape and the hoops
nobodye deserves it more than you Angel
When this is realy official
When i can trade this in for that goldbadge
Drinks are on me
Angel gets his wings
Do you know what this means?
Payraise?
No dildo it means he's my supervisor
which means i have a lock for my detective shield.
Where you going?
- Uh research
- Dex !
uh typos grammar
something to interfer whatever
Haircut
Yep
Time to get the lay of the land on Freebo
and his
pink house
What you need?
Freebo.
I need Freebo
And you know him how?!
He sells the best shit anywhere
Cmon man what you googled him or something
You know what fuck it there are other dokespots
Hey hey Come here don't walk away
all fuck you on me
- What?
- Ding ding
Looking to hold some product
Ordinary i don't accept new clientel
but i've had a desoltery in third quarter
Aw cmon!
Need a little more hook
before breaking into the pocket
You know I bought this tv for six grand
but i'll let you have it for three
More interested in squaring some tar
Oh another juppy turns to the dark side
I need a hit
Jesus Tegan im transacting here
One tube
Did you hear what I said
Fuck off Tegan
Fine I guess your dick will suck it self from now on
Stupid cunt gonna read a fine short term relationship
Catch my drift?
Yeah catch your drift
and im entirely confident you've earned
the privielege as being repurposed as fishfood
Narcotics raided this place at noon today
The drug rats wont return to their nest for a while
Plenty of time to
do what i have to do
Rough, you like it rough
Excuse me?
The sugar, you like the raw stuff
It's my job to notice things
Morgan, right?
Do I know you?
Your haircut it's cute
Alright who the fuck are you
Yuki Mato internal affairs
And?
You know a Joey Quinn?
Why?
Well, he started drawing our attention
back when he was in narcotics
He's in your orbit now
I don't know the guy except
he handles my paperwork
Would be realy cool if you could
get next to him you know
- Do a little recon
- Are you high?
No, never been
Well,
Yuki, that's not gonna happen
Cooperation with the IA has its upsides
in the department
Yeah maybe for Rosen
Ok.
Well it was nice to finaly meet you
In person you know
Bye !
So what is it you think Quinn did exactly
Uh-uh you don't get to blow me off
and still ask me questions
Loud music
cover of darkness
Perfect
No!
Freebo get back here!
Who are you?
Who are YOU?
Shit!
Yo Freebo man!
what the fuck happened back there
I went there to kill Freebo
and ended up killing a total stranger
I didn't kill someone I completely met before
Who's guilt I wasn't absolutely certain of.
I did something wholy inside the moment
and wholy outside the code
Something
spontaneous
Who did I just kill?
Freebo's doorman
I
am
fucked
Just a mater of time
before someone calls it in
Hey you!
Dexter, hey
I know it's not one of our regular nights but...
could you come over?
Uh sure everything ok?
Im just...missing you that's all
God you're on fire lately
Are you complaining?
Compliant
Where are you?
I'm right here
A safe place
God created pudding
and then he rested
Pudding of chocolate
mana from heaven
What are the kids gonna do
for desert tomorrow?
Tangerines
Dexter Morgan.
Yes im happy with my long distance provider
What the hell ever happened to
do not call three in the morning
Not in India
I have an insanely busy morning tomorrow so
i'll be gone before you and the kids wake up
Dexter you have been working such killer hours lately
Please hold me until you have to go
Just a mater of time
Morning sergeant!
How long for you to get to 180 Countant
Uhh 20-30 minutes
I got it Dex
You got what
Only the case that's gonna get me my shield
It's huge
Angel put me on it officialy on it
Huge?
Who the hell are you?
I bet you wonder who the hell he is
Who he is, is what makes this case huge
It's Miguel Prado
He's that ADA that's been on a mission
to put away as many bad guys as he can you know
"a safe Miami is the only Miami"
A safe Miami and we're all unemployed
Why does he look so familiar?
Cause he just made the
cover of Florida Magazine
Top prosecutor in the state
two years in a row
He and Laguerta go way back you know
that whole Cubano thing
Yeah the guy is Ramon Prado
Miguels middle brother
He's a lieutenant with the
sheriffs department
Made himself quite the reputation for being a law and order hard ass
and
Oscar.
Prado?
as in baby brother
So much for spontaneousity
What was he doing in a dump like this?
They're saying that he was a coach at a youth club
Came here to confront the scum bag
who was selling shit to his kids
Talk about the wrong place
at the wrong time
Tell me about it
Find anything?
Yeah...
dead guy with a hole in his chest
This window is cracked,
there's blood on the wall
Who shut these drapes?
Probably first on scene
Some dipshit review? still outside puking
So what do we got?
Signs of a majorly big struggle here,
there, everywhere
Single stabwound to the chest
You read my article yet?
Started it So far it is realy good
Awesome
Whoever did this
He's already wishing he was dead
Someone realy stepped on his dick with this one
There where so many lessions
in the wanted code of Harry
Twisted commandments handed down
from the only god I ever worshiped
One through ten
Don't get caught.
That I got covered
But killing someone without knowing if he's guilty
I'd love some help on this one
But my god is dead now
Mans best friend
right Dex?
Not today
Hey my sister says that LaGuerta
knows this Miguel Prado pretty well
Way back when when we...
Hey wazzup?
Way back when when we Mighuel was in
law school
and Maria was just starting in law enforcement
They hooked up
Hooked up?
Between us for Maria Miguel Prado
will always be the one who got away
Prelim has the victim
Oscar Prado 26 dead
Dead from a single stabwound to the chest
The deceast brother ADA Miguel Prado
informed the active scene that
Oscar went to confront one
Fred Bowman streetman Freebo
for selling drugs to some youth club kids
Morgan.
This Freebo is the same guy that killed those two co-ed's
in the Everglides and got away with it so
the way it looks Oscar Prado died a hero
Also our team found a shitload of...
substantial amount of drugs in the house
Any leads on his whereabouts?
That part of the neighbourhood isn't exactly
policefriendly but i'm staying on it
Talk to me about forensics
Evidence indicates this was no hit and run
It was a furious close end battle
Whoever..
Was it whomever?
Whoever's good
Whoever did this got in a lucky shot
or was realy good at handling a blade
According to the ME the aorta was
cleanly severed in one penetration
Not easy to do
Any luck finding the weapon?
It's not on either premises
We've checked roofs, sewers, trashbins
in a five blocks radius
Our conclusion the assailant took it with him.
Dexter what's the blood saying?
Pretty much what everyone else is
I have some second level on scene work to do
I get back to you ASAP
Give it to sergeant Baptista
Full disclosure
I've had a personal relationship with
the Prado family for many years
and it goes alot further than the whole Cubano thing
Sergeant
Stating the obvious lieutenant
I'd like Freebo for this
Me too
Morgan.
Yes mam
Hit the streets harder
Learn what you can learn
With all due respect lieutenant
if Freebo did this
he's not in Miami
I mean he's in the winds
We could sit around on our asses
and speculate on wherever we think
the prime suspect may or may
not be or we can actualy go and look for him
As a Miami prosecutor I have
dedicated my career to fighting crime
To make our streets safe
for everyone
Every family white, black, latino, asian deserves
the full measures of our devotion to their dignity
another crime has touched my family in
the most profound way imaginable
I grieve equaly for every
family that has been
visited with the same unimaginable
news that we have received today
Our beautiful city is a city of families
and the untimely taking of any of us touches all of us
My parents brought my brothers from....
Part of my ritual has always been
to get to know my victims
Confirming their guilt beyond all doubt.
Oscar Prado tried to kill Freebo
and he tried to kill me
No way he was there
on some noble youth club mission
He's got to be guilty of something
Aren't we all?
So I ask again
Who are you?
Two speeding tickets and an illegal u-turn
What about outside the code of Harry
Harry finds me in a pool of blood
Turns me into his own personal vendeta machine
and when he see's the monster he
created in action he kills himself
Death can drink to his honor on his own
Any luck in the land of reluctant witnesses
One house I play good cop
the next i play bad cop
I still can't get shit from anybody in that neighbourhood
You know what the
problem is right?
Wait Quinn let me guess
The cop part?
No they don't owe you anything There's no insentive
which gives the balance of power
weighing in their direction, right
Her let me give you one thing,
call this guy,
tell him you know me. Tell him you want to
cash in one of my coupons.
Coupons ?
Yeah he's a CI from my days in narcotics.
He got a hook in him and it's not
coming out aanytime soon.
What you want in return?
For you to remember that i did you a solid
Not even a thank you?
Thank you
Stop looking at my ass
Detective.
Officer. Your Anton?
In the flesh
You got something you want to show me?
Oh yeah I've seen him before
Realy? Where?
In the news
Isn't that the guy you let walk with those co-ed killers.
Now that there was some
fine piece of police work
You know him from the news paper
Yeah i think i saw him on CNN or something
Ok that's all you got?
Thats all you got
You know if you and Quinn's fucking with me
Im realy not in the mood
You know summer if you need something
for that temper I got a man down the street
that sells realy ?mellow weak?
to take that edge right off.
Well thank you but i don't take advice
from drugdealers so..
Drugdealers?!
Oh never that.
Drug user, occationaly
Strictly weed though officer,
strictly weed
Then how did you become Quinns snitch
I got caught up in a drugbust
Quinn told me if I blew the whistle on the bigger fish
I would stay out of jail
so i listened
attentively
Yeah well...
you know it never hurts
for an occational drug user
to have another friend
on the force
That's the thing officer
I got enough friends
Yeah well im out of here
Yeah you have a good one you hear
What about this Prado guy?
..and to determine the impact site.
The exact point where forces carry the body
You have to distinguish the geometric differences
between backspatter, satelite spatter,
misting and arterial spurting
- Groose!
- Shut up!
Ehm, you remember how before when
Caties dad was talking about being a surgent
Yeah
and sometimes how he has to cut into
bodies and there's blood
But he saves lives
Do you save lives?
Ok you know how there's good guys and there's bad guys?
So you catch bad guys?
Well not directly but I help
Do you have a uniform?
Eh, lab coat
A gun?
No
He got a badge.
A laminate
Well thank you so much for taking
time from your busy schedule Mr.Morgan
to come and talk to the children
Yeah it was a real learning experience
Looks like I realy got through to em huh
It would have sucked even worse today
if I didn't have a dad today
Thanks for inviting me buddy
If anyone should have father issues,
anger, rejection, abandonment it's Cody
and what does he do? He moves on.
How does that happen?
I was so bad you're crying?
No, no it's just something I always wanted
You being here for the kids
It felt so wonderfully uncomplicated
Hello?
Mr.Morgan this is Miguel Prado
I need to see you Right away
So much for uncomplicated
It almost looks like a piece of art
Thank you sir
but to me it's more like a story
Tell me that story Mr.Morgan
The encounter started over here
The scuff-marks on the linoleum,
the crumpling, the thrower-up, they all
have the directional followty that leads to..
Now this is where your brother and Freebo
he's my lieutenants prime suspect
But you know that
There was a brutal struggle
I got to say it looks like your brother fought like a hero
but he was overmatched and sustained
a fatal stabwound to the chest
Everything about the blood
suggests that your brother
bleed out almost instantly.
Did he suffer?
Blood never lies
So now i know how he died
Question is why
Well one more thing Mr.Morgan
Why would a blood spatter analyst
spend time searching the sheriff departments database
for information on my dead brother
Uhm...
Like you sir I wanted to understand what happened here
I felt that
knowing some details about your
brothers life help me make sense out of his death
In your line of work Mr.Morgan is it usual
for you to get so involved?
I just sounded like a prosecutor there, i'm sorry
It's not a problem sir
and no it's not usual for me to get so involved
but this one, this death got to me
It's just..
it seem so unreal..
he's gone
Yeah I know
So a man died Mr.Morgan and what's left a soul?
And what is that exactly?
I realy couldn't tell you
Because some people say
the soul lives on forever
I don't know
Which makes you a synic
It makes me a scientist
So noone you ever loved has died?
My father died when I was in my twenties
and you don't believe that his soul,
call it his lifeforce is still here somehow
living inside you?
Because I... I should have been there for him
You can't blame yourself sir.
It's easier said than done Mr.Morgan
Do me a favour
You realy want to get to know
my brother like you say
Come to his wake tonight
Come see how much and how,
how fully he was loved.
Ok
Taken enough of your day here,
thank you.. Dexter
This reports final?
Blood specimen's I collected all came back
belonging to Oscar Prado
Trace prints on and around the victim
all points to Freebo
Anyone out there talking?
Officer Morgan was hitting up the usual
firewall of clammed up witnesses
and eyewitnesses so I put her in touch with
an old CI of mine
hopefully she...
Hey Quinn that CI you put me on
was totaly useless for Freebo
Sadly it's not a perfect world
Yeah for all we know Freebo
is in like Nebraska by now
Well I guess you don't owe me
that favour then
How come he gets favours?
He doesn't
But what the CI told me about the victims
He wasn't some hero coach that
went into the hood and took one for the team
What do you mean?
Oscar Prado was into Freebo
for some serious cash
Now why would someone be into
i don't know a drugdealer for big bucks.
Because Oscar Prado
the pride of little Havannah
was a fucking junkie.
Thanks Maria
Good one Morgan
She's been in better moods
Yeah I didn't exactly brighten her day
No you didn't
Excuse me for doing my fucking job!
You see any other supercops coming
down here with any leads?
No Deb you're definitly amazing but you gotta
I know i know i know
Be aware of my surroundings
take the temperature of the room before I open my mouth
I know it's a bad habit I admit it
Well look on the bright side
now that you've given up men, boose
and cigarettes running your mouth
is the only bad habbit you have left
That's right
I'm a model of fucking perfection
You know what day it is today right?
How could I forget?
7.30 I buy your first drink
You wanted to see me? Hey Baptista
I need you to think about Debbie Morgans continued
involvement on the Oscar Prado case
You want me to throw her
under the bus
for what being a little overzealous
It's not about heal
It's about tact and sensitivities
It's also about the real world
This case is as high profile as it gets.
I... No Morgan is resourceful, intanatious
and usualy the right amount
of pain in the ass
But there's political ramifications
and my history with Miguel Prado aside
this case is just too big for her
Just say the word Maria
and I will follow your orders
Becoming a homicide sergeant is more
than just a bump in payscale
it's a quantum leap in responsibility
All part of moving up the chain
If i'll bounce her she'll hate me
Your her boss ? not her friend
It's up to you
Can I get another cranberry juice
That makes three problems down under
Geez I like the fucking taste ok
Miss you dad
My condolences
Thank you for coming
Losing my brother it's gonna
leave a pain in my heart
that I don't think ever gonna heal
You have a brother Dexter?
No just a one loud sister
What she said back at the station
It's ok I know my brother was a good man
but i can tell that he suffered
from the tragedy of perfection
Who doesn't
Oh indeed...
You attacked me with a knife
in a dopedealers house.
No Oscar you certainly didn't suffer
from the tragedy of perfection
Then why do this feel so wrong?
Why in your death are you still
so alive in my life
Did you know him well?
Not as well as I thought
Sorry
Cuervo black
Thanks
Harry
What the hell is that?
Cranberry Juice is that
gonna be a problem?
Not even close to a problem
but the taste is kinda funky
You know by the time my dad was my age
he already had his shield
Kinda why i'm here
I'm taking you off
the Oscar Prado case
I come up with grade a intel on Oscar Prado
and I get tossed of the case
for being a little loud?
In a nutshell
Did Maria put you up to this?
It was my decision
I'll tell you one thing Angel
I'm not letting anyone getting in the way
of me getting my shield
There's only one person in this apartment
that can get in your way
Who?
You
Can I get a real fucking drink please?
My sister still lives her life
trying to please her father
Me...
I'm following the lead
of an eight year old kid
I'm moving on
Thank you for last night
It was a nice surprise
This is where I wanted to be
Ah, again?
All I want is chocolate pudding..
and you
Not necessarily in that order
Morgan.
Where the fuck where you last night
Ritas
It wasn't Ritas night
Turns out it was
I called you
I know
And you ignored me?
Not you, Harry
Deb...
i'm in a whole other place when it comes to dad
I'm working out some personal stuff
You're such a fucking guy
What is this you got to kill your father
so you can become your own man kind of bullshit
Dad wasn't perfect
but he was there for you
- Deb wait
- What?
Im sorry I didn't notice your haircut
So what is it, is it too short
too young too dorky, what?
It's beautiful
Beautiful?
You just said beautiful
Yeah I did, cause it is
It's like you honored dad
for the both of us last night anyway
I had some help
You getting along with
the new boss man?
Aw fucker took me off the Oscar Prado case
and put me on this
Some dead end John Doe
A couple of ladies of the night called this in
Oh mother the Joz...
Could  you turn that thing off!
We'll work quietly
About half way through
your article Vince so far
it is very moving
Yeah I was trying to make second serie
chromosome analysis sexy
Glad you picking up on it
Strangled
There's no blood i'm the blood guy Why did you call me in
Because of this
Looks like our evildoer had an agenda
Maybe it's a tattoo or something
Dex I need to know if this was anti or post mortem
Tegan
Freebo's girlfriend
Looks like he's still in Miami
Hi there
- You talk to Morgan yet?
- Yep
How'd she take it?
There where curse words involved
You did good
Sergeant
Way to be
Thank you
There ya go Dexter
Good as new
Hold the elevator, hold..
Asshole,
Sorry, sergeant asshole
Ramos, Masuka, Quinn
Vamos we got some celebrating to do
You still drink after last night
A man has his needs You can go
back to your cute little Cranberry Juice
Nah taste like shit
I'm gonna have a Mohito
or ten
on you searge
Morgan!
You still have the wrong person?
There's a good reason why Quinn's of interest to IA
Understand me
when I say you have the wrong person I mean me
These people are more than just
badgenumbers to me They're my friends
They're my family
It's the sound of your shield calling for help
Harry said that what's inside me
would be there for ever
and that I wouldn't be able to change
He was half right
Killing Oscar Prado was a bell
I can't unring
I had moved on from my father
But i still need his code
Now more than ever
but it has to evolve
Become my own
Change is good
Hey you
Hey yourself
This music again?
Chocolate pudding again?
Shit
What?
I have done this before
What do you mean?
I'm pregnant
Subtitles by DIProgan