Dexter.S03E08.HDTV.XviD-LOL
English Corrections - UF
Previously, on Dexter...
We need to go after the root cause,
this bloodsucking,
soulless defense attorney
Ellen Wolf.
Has she ever actually killed anyone?
Keep an open mind about her.
Miguel's on his way over here right now.
I know one side of him.
Maybe there's more.
Missing evidence,
Witness intimidation,
jury tampering.
- You got proof?
- He's a bad guy. He's not a stupid guy.
I'm pregnant.
They say this part should pass soon.
This isn't some kind of
weird end run, is it?
Make me see how
sensitive you really are?
I'm not all that sensitive.
- Yeah, you are.
Someone loaned freebo some money
and is willing to skin
people to get it back.
Which is why I want to use
our C.I. more aggressively.
Wait. You mean Anton?
Yeah, we're gonna spread the word
that Anton knows where Freebo is.
You're gonna use him as bait?
Which means that the skinner
will be looking for me.
Am I being set up?
I found the fucking lead on the skinner case.
The skinner is using
tree-trimming as a
cover for surveillance.
He watches from the trees,
and when the time is right,
he grabs them.
I know what you did for me.
I will be your bait.
So you told Quinn I
was investigating him.
Hey, you're the one who fucked him.
Not my fault he didn't want an encore.
Cop's dead 'cause Quinn
cut all the wrong corners.
Next dead cop's on you.
What did it feel like to end his life?
Felt like justice.
We're like-minded.
Together we can make a difference.
It's said that everything is
connected to everything.
The butterfly effect.
You drop a pebble into a pond,
and the ripples radiate outwards,
touching and affecting everything.
Until finally a fish
grows arms and legs
and crawls out of the water.
And picks up a rock and smashes
the next two fish over the head.
And we have the first serial killer.
This is good pizza.
On television.
What channel's ESPN over here?
I think it's a big number.
Yeah, there you go.
And now we got Gary
going the other way.
Tryin' to get in.
No way. that's not a foul, man.
That was definitely
wrong what that guy did.
You're clearly not a
sports fan, are you?
Not really.
I'm more of a
National Geographic kind of guy.
Sharks, bears, the occasionally penguin.
You do have other interests, though.
Yeah, I suppose I do.
Speaking of which...
Uh, boundaries.
Eh, it's encrypted.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Trust issues.
Football.
See. you do know your sports.
This guy right here.
Billy Fleeter.
Should I know him?
Not yet, but hopefully, you will.
This was from maybe five years ago.
He never went pro.
Drug problem. turned to gambling.
Unfortunately, he wasn't very good at it.
More than once he's paid his debts off
to his bookies by working as an enforcer.
Breaking fingers?
Crushing skulls with a baseball bat.
I went after him
a few years ago, but...
I just couldn't get the evidence.
I had to tell the children of
a 70-year-old man
that he had just killed
that there was nothing we could do.
So here it comes.
Miguel wants me to kill him.
I don't want you to kill him.
No?
I wanna do it.
You.
I've let you do all of the
heavy lifting so far.
Now it's my turn.
I'm ready to get my hands dirty.
It's one thing to let Miguel
provide a little backup,
another thing to share
the reins with him.
I'm gonna need your help, Dexter.
Not a good idea.
Just, uh, think about it.
No, Dexter,
don't think about it.
The waffle is a lot like the pancake,
only square.
Why is it square?
Because it was invented
by Simon P. Waffle,
and he liked to stack
his waffles in boxes,
And that's just easier to do
if they're square.
You're making that up.
I'm hurt that you would even think that.
Oh, God, Dexter,
you're making a mess.
That's okay.
We'll clean it up.
It's not the point.
What is the point?
I don't know.
The point is not to
make a mess to begin with.
Rita's pregnancy hormones seem to be
ganging up on us this morning.
How come there are no
English muffins left?
Uh, I think you ate the
last one yesterday.
Waffle?
Uh, that's disgusting.
Cody, you need a haircut.
Let's see...
four, five, six more months
till she delivers.
Rita, are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
Right, I am starting a new job
and I'm planning a
wedding all by myself.
What can I do to help?
It's not like you can
pick out the deejay.
Last time I got into your car,
Your radio was tuned to marching music.
It helps me think.
And it's not like
you can pick the florist
or the caterer or even
the wedding bands.
I could pick the wedding bands.
Right.
Just like the engagement
ring you never gave me.
You said you didn't want one.
I don't want one.
Who drank all the orange juice?
Jesus Christ.
- What?
You have like no hot
water in your shower.
All right.
Yeah, I told you to wait, remember?
Well, I can't wait.
Some of us have jobs to get to.
I'm a musician.
I work nights.
Yeah, and what do you do
with the rest of your day?
You take a nap,
you watch cartoons.
Jack off.
Oh, I rarely watch cartoons.
Fucking hilarious.
Well, you better not be
writing any more songs about me.
Most ladies would be flattered.
Well, most ladies aren't cops.
Oh, right.
Right.
I gotta go.
You okay?
Come get these.
Yeah.
Freebo's dead.
And now there's a
tree trimmers' convention in here.
It seems random, but it's not.
The butterfly effect again.
Of course, it's an odd sensation
when you happen to be the butterfly.
And if I were to help
Miguel kill Billy Fleeter
who knows the effect
that would have on the world?
Is this the beginning
of a whole new level of friendship?
Is it the end of life as I know it?
Mr. King,
we met at the scene of our
second victim, is that correct?
Yes, that is correct.
Great. Have you ever worked at
any of these addresses?
No, no, see, these are city jobs.
I'm a private contractor.
Okay, well, I'm gonna need a
list of all of your employees.
I can get you a copy of my payroll records.
That would be a big help.
How soon do you need this?
Ten minutes ago would be great.
Very well.
Thank you.
Looks like someone got lucky last night.
Uh, let's just say
that Barbara and I have
taken it to the next level.
You know that now you've done the deed,
she's gonna be taking notes,
making a checklist of your every move,
to see if you're
relationship material, right?
That's not true.
Wait, is it?
Well, it's not like
we write anything down.
It's...more of a mental process.
Morning, Loo.
Third day in a row of this, huh?
Let's hope something shakes
loose on this. Come here.
Uh, I have a favor to ask you.
Shoot.
You know I got to go to
that peace officers...
...association thing tomorrow night.
You wanna-- you wanna be my date?
Maria, um,
thank you for the invite.
But I have plans.
And if I bail, I don't think
it's gonna go over too well.
Like that. Huh.
Okay. Good for you. Okay.
Relationships are complicated.
Letting Miguel kill
Fleeter would be a gamble.
This guy's a gambler.
Look where it got him.
Something to consider
when Miguel and I do
our research tonight at the casino.
How'd you find out about this place?
Research.
Always a first good step, right?
Move a little closer?
Tonight is just about watching,
learning his routine--
where does he go,
when does he go,
what does he do when he gets there.
Okay.
Later, we'll meet him.
We?
Yeah, we'll see how it goes.
Right now,
we don't want him to notice us.
We don't want anyone to notice us.
Cameras all over the place.
Number one rule of the code is
"Don't get caught."
Code? What code?
How much do I tell him?
It's just a series of precautions.
Learned where?
Common sense mostly.
A little more than that.
Well, my dad was a cop.
Right, right.
So he taught you...
- What cops look for in an investigation.
Oh, and so you work it
backwards from there, right?
Plus, I spend all day looking
at other people's mistakes.
You pick things up.
I'm sure.
Am I forgetting something, Dexter?
Was there one final lesson where I said,
"Go now,
far and wide,
and preach the code, my son"?
I don't think so.
So when you popped Anton
for drug possession,
was it just pot, or was it coke or--
What was it?
Uh, pot, I think.
Right. right, it couldn't have been
anything too serious,
Or you wouldn't have made him a C.I.
I guess.
You're just full of answers today.
I-I-I just busted guys
like him every day.
I don't remember,
and it's all written down somewhere.
Right. C.I. files.
Hello?
Hey, lazy, hope I'm waking you up.
Hey, lazy?
I haven't been to bed yet.
Look, I need your C.I. number.
I'm gonna file a status report.
What's a C.I. number?
Your assigned confidential
informant number.
It should be on your paychecks.
What checks?
Your paychecks from the county.
Hello. I don't get any paychecks.
Quinn always pays me in cash.
Oh.
Okay.
I'll get it from him then.
My client was supposed to
be sent to county yesterday.
Apparently he was,
but then they put him
on the next bus right back
here in the afternoon.
I've been chasing him
all over the place.
We shouldn't have those mix-ups.
Is it a mix-up,
Or is Miguel fucking with me?
Ever since I started looking into him,
he's been going out of his
way to make my job harder.
Well, you knew that was gonna happen.
Doesn't mean I can't bitch about it.
Oh, anyway, I should go see my client
and ask what perfectly
logical reason he had
for lighting his
ex-wife's house on fire.
Oh, I wanted to ask you.
Any chance you'd go to a
police charity function
with me tomorrow night?
Room full of cops?
I can't imagine anything more fun.
Shouldn't have asked.
I'm kidding.
I'd love to go.
Okay, next on your list, Mr. King,
Santiago Ramirez.
He no longer works for me.
That didn't end so well.
Why?
He was run over.
Uh, Mario Astorga.
Didn't I talk to him?
Yes, if you remember,
he's the one who
found the body of that man.
Right. Second victim.
Mario's one of my best foremen.
So he's a good guy?
What, he's not a good guy?
He has a temper.
He gets very angry.
Keep going.
I knew his family back in Nicaragua.
We're both from San Marcos.
But Mario had to leave.
Why?
The police were looking for him.
I heard he killed someone with a knife.
Do you know where I can find Mario?
I don't know where he lives.
But tomorrow,
he'll be at Bayside Park.
- You sure?
- I make the schedule.
Fleeter pays off his gambling debts
by eliminating people for his bookie.
A schoolteacher here,
a mother of two there.
People who can't settle their debts.
Sending a message to others--
"Pay up."
Do I help Miguel move forward on this,
or do I listen to Harry and shut it down?
Hey, you.
Yeah, I just heard a
love song on the radio
that reminded me of you.
Oh, that's sweet.
And it made me really angry.
So have you gotten
the wedding bands yet?
Um, I'm still doing my
research, but I'm on it.
I gotta go.
Hey, you know anything
about wedding rings?
Yeah.
Wedding rings and nuclear fission are
like my secret specialties.
Thanks.
Your brother's kind of a dweeb, huh?
You say anything more about my brother,
and I will kick your
fucking nuts down your throat.
That doesn't even make any sense.
So, hey, Anton doesn't have any priors,
you pay him in cash,
and I can't find him in the C.I. database.
Should be in there.
What are you hiding?
Anton is not officially a C.I.
What do you mean?
Come here for a second.
Look, it was just
easier for both of us.
I never filed an arrest report on him
so he has no police record.
I did him a favor.
Plus, it saved me the
hassle of all that paperwork.
You have got to be fucking kidding me.
We used him as bait.
He was putting his life at risk,
and he was
under no legal obligation to help us.
No, no, no, there was just
no paperwork, that's all.
Not to mention the fact
that because he's not officially a C.I.,
there's no end date to when
he's done working for us,
so you can just string him
along as long as you want to.
What are you getting so upset about?
What, are you in love with the guy?
No, I'm not in love with him.
But you're sleeping with him.
Jesus Christ,
do you know what kind of a
bonehead mistake that is?
Sleeping with an informant?
I mean, it's that kind of judgment'll
screw up your career.
He's not an informant.
You just said it.
But you didn't know.
Either way, it makes you look stupid.
No, you don't get to
lecture me, asshole.
Anton could so easily
file a huge lawsuit
against the police department
once he finds out
how you fucked him over.
Yeah, if someone told him.
Of course I'm gonna tell him.
You'll sell out a cop for
some dope you're fucking?
That's not half as bad
as being responsible
for another cop dying
because you don't like
to play by the rules.
What?
Yuki told me.
You don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
Despite Harry's warnings,
here I am with Miguel,
outside Billy Fleeter's house.
If I'm gonna stop this,
it's gonna have to be soon.
Are you sure you want to do this?
It's breaking and entering.
But you know that.
Yes, I do.
Let's go.
Here, put these on.
Forensics guy who always
has latex gloves on him.
No one would ever think twice, huh?
I guess you're right.
I don't want Miguel to see
how easy this is for me.
Uh, you want me to try?
No, I think I--
I got it.
So what are we looking for?
Proof.
That he's guilty.
We know he bludgeons people to death,
so look for something... bludgeony.
Uh, this looks like it's
been knocked around some.
Hold it up.
Purple?
Ergo...
Blood.
How easy is this?
I'll test it against the
blood of his alleged victims.
Let you know later today.
You know it takes me two days
to get a search warrant,
then another day to catalog evidence,
and then, a week before I
can get the lab results.
This is definitely the way to go.
We also need to make sure that
he's likely to kill again.
Why is that?
It's just one of the rules.
One of these days I'm
gonna make you sit down
and write out all these
rules for me, but okay.
He--he kills whenever he needs money.
That's how he pays off his
debts to the bookie.
Dex, I've tried a lot of
these gamblers before,
and they all keep records.
They're like anal about their numbers.
There's got to be like a ledger
around here somewhere.
Maybe there's a hidden
wall safe or something.
We're talking about the man
who leaves his murder weapon
in an umbrella stand.
Yeah, you're right.
What if we don't find anything?
Then we don't move forward.
Leave it, Dex.
Just put it back.
You can stop this right now.
Call it off.
Why should I call it off?
I didn't teach you the code
to share with your buddies.
I taught you the code to keep you alive.
You don't get to have friends, Dexter.
Nothing good can come out of this.
Hey, Dex, you know what, I don't think
we're gonna find anything here, man.
Look at you.
It's my life, dad.
30 grand in the hole.
I think we know how he's
gonna pay that off.
So, look, we moving forward?
Yeah, moving forward.
If the blood matches.
I can't believe we are just now
sending out invitations.
This is so last minute.
It's okay.
There's plenty of time.
And Dexter's no help.
Do you know,
I asked him for menu suggestions--
Do you know what he says?
I don't know.
Steak. He says steak.
Yeah, that's great, Dexter.
That's really great.
We'll start with a steak appetizer,
followed by steak salad,
followed, of course, by a steak,
and then, of course,
it'll all be topped off
by a steak fucking cake.
Rita.
What?
The envelope.
You're making a mess.
Why don't you stuff for a while?
And I'll do the addresses.
Okay.
I've got big news.
Yeah, about the skinner?
No, about you.
You're free.
Oh, yeah, ever since Abe Lincoln.
I mean from the police department.
You're no longer a C.I.
Hold on, wait a second.
The way Quinn explained it was,
if I play ball,
it would knock down my felony possession
to a misdemeanor,
and if I worked hard enough,
it would go away all together.
Well, it's gone away.
Hmm, how's that?
Clerical error.
The necessary papers were never filed,
so there were never any
charges for you to work off.
Wait, so I've been doing all this
shit when I didn't have to?
Just be glad you don't
have to do it anymore.
Well, thank you.
And I want to put
protective detail on you.
What?
No. No, Debra.
- Anton.
- Listen.
You said I'm free,
so I'm free of this.
So we should celebrate.
Dinner tonight.
Mm, no, I'm working tonight.
How about we celebrate now?
I've got to go back to work.
Tomorrow.
Breakfast.
Perfect.
So I'm guessing we got a
blood match, huh?
That's why we're here.
Life vests?
We can't exactly load up the cart
with axes and machetes, now can we?
Exactly right.
So, um, have you given any thought
as to how you want to do this?
Mm-hmm.
Small caliber gun to the head.
Then I walk away.
That happens all the time.
Guns make noise.
And they leave
evidence behind-- bullets,
casings, powder residue.
Not to mention the body.
Okay.
You don't want to create a crime scene.
It's where experts like me
gather evidence against you.
Okay, okay, I get it, I get it.
What do you suggest?
Up close and personal.
Hey, in case we have to tie anybody up.
I'm gonna put together
a starter kit for you.
Hey, you got better.
Yeah, what do you know?
What better place to gamble on Miguel
than a room full of games of chance?
Where slot machines go to die, huh?
And at least one gambler.
I think that's it.
Now we pick up Mr. Fleeter.
You ever drop a quart of milk?
Watch it spread over the
whole kitchen floor,
The mess it makes?
There's six quarts of
blood in the human body.
This isn't gonna be pretty.
There's no shame in backing out.
Dex, after 14 years of filing briefs,
trying cases,
and dealing with bullshit...
...this is all gonna look
nice and neat in comparison.
I have been to some lame-ass rubber chicken
dinners in my day, okay. I know, I know.
A no-host bar is punishment enough,
but no bar at all is cruel.
And unusual.
All right,
I'm buying the first round.
Thank you.
That's pretty.
Gift from my first husband.
Nice, nice.
You're handsome.
Dire ethanol emergency here.
What'll it be, ladies?
Uh, cuba libre for this one.
Gracias.
And a double scotch
neat soda back pour moi.
Very nice.
Easy.
Oh, and who was that guy, that--
that suit and haircut
sitting next to you
that wouldn't shut up?
Oh, the, um, the senior liaison
for the greater mi--
who knows?
I don't know--
what's sad is that this is
the only social event
I've been to in six months.
Oh, that doesn't qualify
as a social event.
Okay.
Can I get you anything else?
Yeah, how about a foot massage
with those big,
gorgeous hands of yours?
They're kind of cold from scooping ice.
Hmm, but you're hot.
Cheers.
- Nothing shy about you, huh?
- No.
Well...
...after a pair of empty marriages,
I realized the secret to
long life and happiness is,
well, chocolate and flirting with
young, hopefully hung men.
Sounds fattening and dangerous.
- Oh, but so fun.
- Hmm.
Which, clearly,
you're not having enough of.
- I am.
- Hmm.
Look, believe me,
I've had my fun.
You need to be raising
hell and breaking hearts.
- I need to be?
- You need to be.
The skirt-wearing days
do not last forever.
We all end up old and in the way.
I tell Miguel to be inconspicuous,
and what does he do?
He shows up looking like the unabomber.
I've got my work cut out for me.
Oh, close game, close game.
Yeah, good deed.
Good game, huh?
No, it's not a good game.
Good game is when they don't
beat the fucking point spread.
Oh, you got a little money riding on this?
A little bit.
Shit.
Sorry.
Not half as sorry as
somebody else is gonna be.
Here we go.
Buenas noches, Patron.
Hey, who was that guy?
Uh, I don't know.
Some guy.
How do you know him?
I don't.
Dex, sometimes people recognize me.
It's off.
We're not doing this.
We need to take down the kill room.
No, no, Dex,
let's just wait.
No one ever goes in that room there.
You saw.
Tranquilo, huh?
We decide tomorrow, okay?
We'll see.
Anton.
Me again.
Waiting on you still.
The way I figured it,
you gigged until closing,
and then you went home and
smoked some of that herb
that you keep in your cereal box.
And now, like all self-indulgent,
vaguely adolescent musicians,
you are sleeping in till noon--
and I'm okay with that.
Okay? I'm okay with that.
As long as you're alone.
Okay, okay.
Too much caffeine.
A dutch farmer sees his crop fail.
No money to his name,
he takes a job working on a boat.
An unseasonably strong wind
blows him to Indonesia.
He drops a bean into the soil.
And voila, 400 years later...
Java.
Everything is connected.
Hello?
Dex, wanna hook up for breakfast?
I'm buying.
I would, Deb,
but I'm already freshly bageled.
What are you doing up so early?
Trying to be a good fiance.
Rita made me vice president in
charge of wedding rings,
so I'm off to the jewelry store.
And what do you know about
buying women jewelry?
Zero.
Less than.
Jesus, Dex.
Look, I'll meet you at that
place on second street
at 10:00, okay?
The wedding band has to
match the engagement ring,
so what does that look like?
She said she didn't want one.
My God, you just get dumber every day.
How do you survive in this world?
Of course she wants one.
How am I supposed to know that?
You're such a Y-chromosome cliche.
Just buy her a beautiful, romantic,
I love you with all of my
heart fucking engagement ring.
And Dex,
size matters.
Can I ask you something
non-jewelry-wise?
Go for it.
Okay, hypothetically...
...let's say that
this guy has to work
with this girl,
but he fucking hates doing it,
and too bad 'cause he
has no fucking choice.
And?
And one thing leads to another...
...and this hypothetical guy...
...starts having sex with
this hypothetical girl.
Hypothetical sex?
Real sex.
Really real sex.
But then the guy is told
that he no longer has to work
with this girl, and poof,
he just disappears.
You know.
Thin air. Adios.
So I'm wondering, is it possible
if Mr. Hypothetical never really
was all that into this girl?
And he was just getting it on to,
I don't know, pass the time
or satisfy primal urges or whatever?
Sounds perfectly reasonable to me.
What the fuck do you know?
That one.
I gotta go sit in a hot car and
wait for a suspect.
Hey, Anton...
...what the fuck?
Call me.
I can bring Mario in myself.
Let you get all the credit
for catching the skinner?
No fucking way.
We don't know he's the skinner.
Closest thing we got.
That was really fucking unfair
what you said yesterday.
Well, is it true?
That a cop died because of you?
It's not that simple.
Try me.
Yuki Amado was my
partner in narcotics.
There was another detective
on our team, Stewart.
He made a bad judgment call and
shot an unarmed coke dealer.
I remember that.
Paralyzed him, right?
Then Stewart went on a bender
until he finally swallowed
his own bullet.
How does Yuki make that your fault?
Because Stewart had a
problem with crystal meth.
And I knew it.
And rather than bust him,
I tried to protect him.
So it is your fault.
Listen to you.
Everything is so black and white.
You could have stopped him.
Yeah, sure, if I knew what I knew now.
But that's not the way things work.
I'm sorry.
You're just making excuses.
Yeah, of course I'm making excuses.
Don't you?
I mean, how else do you sleep at night?
Who the fuck said I sleep at night?
Then you must be killing yourself
over hooking up with Anton, huh?
Yeah, it was probably a mistake.
I think he lost all interest
once he realized he was free.
Not so black and white, is it?
Mario.
Mario Astorga?
Fuck!
I'm guessing he didn't want to
come in for questioning.
He made a run for it.
Interview two.
What's his story?
So far, he hasn't said a word.
Ah, you keep at it.
And you check with Nicaraguan
authorities on priors.
We're just waiting to hear back.
I'm never gonna get out of here.
I gotta call Barbara and
cancel our dinner.
Oh, she's not gonna like that.
I mean, it--
it's work.
I'm not here.
Leave a message.
Hello, Barbara.
This is sergeant Angel Batista.
Angel to you.
How are you?
Good I hope.
So I have to cancel
our dinner tonight.
And I am deeply,
deeply apologetic.
And I hope that you will
let me make it up to you
in whatever possible way
you wish things made up
to you in.
Oh, I can tell
by that look on your face,
you're trying to figure out
how to tell me something
I don't wanna hear.
Calling off the kill.
It's over.
Really, Dex?
Just because some guy
recognized me in a bar?
No one is ever gonna
make that connection
once Fleeter disappears.
I'm not taking that chance.
'Cause that's not the
way you do things. right.
No, it isn't.
Tell me about that.
What are you asking?
I wasn't gonna bring it up before,
but I'm guessing...
...you've been doing this for a while.
Freebo wasn't your first.
Was he?
How many, Dex?
Okay, you know what,
it doesn't matter.
I will respect your privacy.
But I just don't understand
why are you not gonna help me here?
Just because we--
we broke this little rule from your code?
Come on, Dex.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
You never should have
asked me to help you.
You're not ready.
I'm not--
or is it you that's not ready?
Because we could have dealt with this
Fleeter problem like three times already,
and you keep throwing up all of these
roadblocks with all this code bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
Oh, come on.
Keep telling yourself that, Dex.
Come on, it's like wearing a
fucking strait jacket, man.
No, Miguel, it's just the opposite.
If I didn't have the code,
the darkness--
I could stand here and tell you
another story about my abusive father,
but what I haven't told
you about is the time
that I kicked the shit out of him
and knocked him down a
flight of stairs.
And I really enjoyed it.
That was the first time in my life
that I've ever felt...
...powerful like...
...like I was in control of--
of something.
And ever since then,
I've been trying
to--
to get that feeling back again.
So when you talk to me about...
...the darkness inside of you...
...I understand.
I really do.
I just want to let some of mine out too.
I know you understand that.
You know what, Mr. Astorga?
Maybe I should have
opened with my closer.
Meaning?
We know about the incident in Managua,
the one where you stabbed a cab driver.
He touched my sister.
Sadly, he survived.
That's a heartbreaking story.
Still you are an illegal guest
of our country.
- Immigration's on the way.
You're gonna be on a
plane before the sun comes up.
But I have a son.
He was born here.
He's a U.S. citizen.
He's my life.
Your boy's a U.S. citizen?
Yes.
Then he stays.
Maybe your wife too.
We don't know yet.
But we do know is if you keep
stonewalling us on this skinner case,
you are gone on a one-way ticket.
No matter what you try to do to me,
the facts ain't changing.
'cause I don't know anything
about anything.
Then why would George King
suggest otherwise?
Senor King said I knew something?
In a word?
Yup.
And senor King will be very disappointed
to hear you're calling him a liar.
No!
Please.
What are you so afraid of, Mario?
Yeah, what'd this guy do to you?
What can he do to you?
Please.
Send me back to Nicaragua.
Alone?
Si. Yes.
Alone.
We mentioned George King's name
once and he turns to jell-o.
Scared to death of him.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Yeah, King jobbed us.
I'm gonna issue a bolo for him.
Hello?
Shit.
Who was it?
Uh, me.
I was checking to see
if my phone was working.
Barbara never called me back.
I think I ruined it.
Sorry.
Dating sucks.
Yeah.
Well, I'm outta here.
Still no George King,
but we put the word out.
Barbara.
You got my message.
Yup. been listening to it all day.
Makes me laugh every time.
It's pretty bad, huh?
Um, the worst.
I'm glad I amuse you.
Not half as glad as I am.
Hey, did they finish already?
They never even started.
What do you mean?
Where's Anton?
He never showed.
- Why?
- I don't know.
They waited an hour.
They called.
Doesn't answer.
Thanks.
What the f--
Poetic.
Are you ready?
I am.
Thank you.
Thank you for this.
For letting me in.
For showing me the way.
Look at him.
Look at him trying to figure it all out.
What the fuck?
We're here because of them.
Those lives that you destroyed.
Who are you?
We're justice.
Hey, man, I was just doing what I had to do.
As are we.
I've always done the deed alone.
Never stood outside.
Been a witness to this moment.
The moment of truth.
Can Miguel go through with it?
Can he step out of the cocoon and fly?
How do you feel?
Fantastic.
Shouldn't we get him out of here?
As bonded as we may feel,
there are still things
I can't share with Miguel.
I got it.
No, it's--it's too much work.
Leaving no trace is my
area of expertise.
Yeah, but, Dex--
Get home before Sylvia starts to
wonder where you are.
I mean it.
Okay.
I'm going.
Not a good idea.
That would be against your code, huh?
Sorry.
Anton, you in there?
Hello, Anton?
Oh, God.
Shit.
Trimmed trees.
The skinner's been here.
You were wrong.
It went well.
Maybe.
Who knows?
You can't admit it.
He did good.
That was never the issue, Dex.
I was only thinking about you.
Of course.
You've set something in motion here.
Everything Miguel does from
now on is connected to you.
It's a lot of responsibility
teaching him what you just did.
A heavy burden.
It was too much for me to bear.
I hope you're a stronger man.
You're still up.
I can't sleep.
I hope it's okay.
My God.
It's--
it's perfect.
Dexter, God, you've been such a
saint through all this.
I don't know
how you've put up with me.
If you need me to help out
with more of the wedding stuff--
- No.
No, it's...
...it's the hormones.
I go crazy when I'm pregnant.
Tell me about it.
That's not true.
You should just get out while you can.
Just run for your life.
I won't.
I promise.
It's like I have this
monster living inside of me,
and I don't know how to control it.
Maybe I can help you out with that one.
It's so beautiful.
It's been said
that a butterfly can flap
its wings in Brazil...
...and set off a storm in Florida.
I'm taking the chance that's
not entirely true.
Original Subs from tvsubtitles.net
English Corrections - UF