Let's get something straight.
This, the chemistry, is my realm.
I am in charge of the cooking.
Out there on the
street, you deal with that.
As far as our customers go, I don't
want to know anything about them.
I don't need to see them.
I don't want to hear from them.
I want no interaction with
them whatsoever.
This operation is you and
me, and I'm the silent partner.
You got any issues with that?
Whatever, man.
No matter what
happens, no more bloodshed.
No violence.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync: µ°¸â »ð¼ý
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Breaking Bad
Season 01 Episode 06
Walt?
- You all right?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah. I'm okay.
You know, honey, you-- you
really don't have to
look, I like being here with you.
Yeah.
I'm only saying that, you know, I'd be okay
with it, really, if-- if you want to go.
You know, actually, it would make me feel a
little better knowing that you were there
when Walter jr gets home from school.
Okay.
All right.
- So you'll call me when you're finished?
- Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Uh, and have you been
in touch with Elliott?
Because, uh, I haven't
seen a check from him.
- Yes, I-- I got it.
- Really?
It came, yeah.
Yeah, it-- it came last week, and I put it
right into my credit union account, so--
Taken care of it.
Good.
So we're good. We're good
could you not deposit this until monday?
Thank you.
Call if the discomfort's too much.
Otherwise, we'll see you next week.
Yeah.
Chemical reactions involve change
on two levels: Matter and energy.
When a reaction is gradual,the
change in energy is slight.
I mean, you-- you don't even
notice the reaction is happening:
For example, when rust collects on
the underside of a car. All right?
But if a reaction happens quickly,
otherwise harmless substances
can interact in a way
that generates enormous
bursts of energy.
who can give me an example
of rapid chemical reaction?
Hint, hint.
Right here.
Like an explosion?
Yes. Good.
Explosions.
Explosions are the result of chemical
reactions happening most instantaneously.
And the faster reactants--
I.E., Explosives
and fulminative mercury is
a prime example of that
the faster they undergo change, the
more violentthe explosion.
So... explosions.
Okay, listen. Why don't youstart reading on
your own from the top of chapter 7, all right?
Mr. White, you okay?
I got it, mr. White.
Don't worry.
You got kids to teach.
Thanks, Hugo.
He's starting to lose weight, which
is, uh, tough to see that
you know, to feel the difference
when I put my, uh, arms around him.
Can I talk?
Of course.
Walt...when, um, when you don't let me in,
when you don't tell me what's going on,
I think it's like I feel like you
don't even want me around sometimes.
No.
And-- and-- and
recently these afternoons,
when-- when you're
coming home so late
and we're just left
wondering where you are.
Y-yeah, dad.
What's up with that?
Walt, is there anything else you're
holding back from your family?
Now's the time to share.
Well... I, uh...I--
I like to be alone--
I mean at times, and
it's not about you, really.
It's just that sometimes it feels better not to
talk at all about anything, you know, to anyone.
Alone time can be helpful for some types.
Maybe knowing what you
do when you're alone
might make it easier for your family to be
more accepting of whatever it is you do alone.
Well... I-- I like to go on walks a couple
of times a week, maybe more, after work,
and, uh, I really enjoy the nature
you know, the cacti, the
vegetation, that kind of thing.
And that's really very therapeutic.
Yo! You okay?
- Did you breathe that ----
- No. I'm just dizzy. I--
come here. Sit down, sit down.
I'm burning up.
Take this off.
Sit down. Get some air.
Oh, god.
Oh, this--
here.
yeah?
Yeah, that's better.
When were you going to tell me?
Tell you what?
Cancer.
You got it, right?
How did you know?
My aunt had one of those...
dots on her to target the radiation.
What is it, in your lung?
I'm your partner, man.
You should have told me.
That's not cool, okay? Not at all.
What stage are you?
3a.
Gone to your lymph nodes.
Your aunt.
H-how bad was she when they caught it?
Bad enough. She didn't last long.
How long?
Seven months.
I get it now.
That's why you're doing all this.
You want to make some cash for
your people before you check out.
You got a problem with that?
You tell me. You're the one that looks
like you just crawled out of a microwave.
You going to be able to finish the batch?
Yes.
All right.
No.
You do it.
Me?
Yeah.
What happened to your mad skills?
Go on. Here.
You do it.
You can do it.
If you have any questions, I'll
be right out here.
The next time, put an ice
pack on your head during chemo.
My aunt said it
helped with the hair loss.
What's this?
Christmas?
This the one we found way out
in the boonies, the cook site?
Holy----.
What?
Lab says they pulled up an imprint of some
old writing that used to be on the inside.
Old magic marker or something.
Yeah? What's it say?
"Property of J.P. Wynne chemistry lab."
That's walt's school.
we were supposed to start at 3.
I'm out there making fat stacks, man.
Chill.
Hey. Prepaid cell phone.
Use it.
How much is this?
26 big ones.
Is that all?
$26,000?
Uh, no, that's 26 hundred,
and your share is 13, minus
25 bucks for that phone.
How much meth did you sell?
Nearly an ounce.
Last time I checked, there
were 16 ouncesto a pound.
What did you do with the rest, smoke it?
Yo, I've been out there all
night slinging crystal.
You think it's cake moving a
pound of meth one teenth at a time?
Why are you selling it in
such small quantities?
Why don't you just sell the
whole pound at once?
To who? What do I look like, scarface?
This is unacceptable.
I am breaking the law here.
This return is too little for the risk.
I thought you'd be ready for
another pound today.
You may know a lot about chemistry, man,
but you don't know
jack about slinging dope.
Uh, well, I'll tell you, I know a
lack of motivation when I see it.
Oh,my--
come on. You've got to be
more imaginative, you know?
Just-- just think outside
the box here.
We have to move our
product in bulk, wholesale, now.
How do we do that?
What do you mean, to, like, a distributor?
Yes. Yes. That's what we need.
We need a distributor now.
Do you know anyone like that?
Yeah, I mean I used
to until you killed him.
So who took krazy-8's place?
Some guy named Tuco.
A bad ---, from
what I hear.
Tuco, okay. So then just go talk to Tuco.
Right. Like "hello, sir.
"Hey, I know you don't know me,"
but would you be interested in a
felony quantity of methamphetamine?
" Well, yes, but maybe with a
little more salesmanship, perhaps?
You just don'tget
it, man. This guy's O.G.
What--what
does that mean?
Ah,-----, look, he's
upper level, man.
He's not going to do business
with some dude he doesn't know.
Okay, you just don't understand
the way it works.
You can't just bum rushsome high-level
ice man and start cutting deals, okay?
It's risky.
You need an intro.
You need someone to vouch.
Well, who introduced you to krazy-8?
Emilio. That's only because I
knew himfrom, like, third grade.
We can't talk to Emilio, either, because
all right, all right, all right.
Look, I'm telling you, Mr.
White, it's too risky. Okay?
I mean, we're making money.
Why can't you just be
satisfied with the way it is?
Oh, come on! Just growsome!
Wait till monday again?
Yes, please. Thank you.
Mr. White.
Thank you, Hugo.
Knock-knock.
Oh, hey.
How are you feeling, Walt?
Good.
Yeah.
Are you up for having a visitor?
Hey, buddy.
Hank.
Well, let me know if
you need anything, huh?
I will. Thank you, Carmen.
No problem.
That chick's got an
--- like an onion.
Makes me want to cry.
So what-- what are
you doing here?
Well, I had some questions I wanted
to run by you-- work-related.
You feeling okay? I
could come back later.
No, no, no, no. I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
What do you mean work-related, though?
Do you recognize that?
No.
That was used to cook meth.
Found that on some indian
land about 40 miles from here.
Old label on the inside used to say...
J.P. Wynne chemistry lab.
Really?
I don't understand how
that came from here.
Well, I was hoping you
could help me with that.
We found it near an abandoned car
belonging to one of our snitches.
A snitch?
Yeah, one of our confidential informants.
Went missing a while back.
No body yet, but we're pretty
sure he's, you know, chk-chk.
Probably chopped up in little
pieces and fed to the buzzards.
Anyway, you, uh-- any respirators
like that go missing lately?
No. No. No, I mean, not that I know of.
I'll need to take a
look at that inventory.
Sure. Sure.
I got a list hanging on the wall.
You mind if I take a
look at your store room?
Not at all, no.
Be my guest.
So who's got keys?
Well, the science faculty, the staff, Carmen,
the vice principal has the master, and me.
How about students?
Uh, no, no.
No students have keys.
I should hope not.
My question is do any little ----
know where you keep them?
Uh, I don't-- I don't think so. No.
I mean, besides, I keep them right
here in my pocket anyway, so
walt, look, I know they're your students,
but, uh, do not underestimate them.
Big mistake.
Are there any other respirators?
Uh, no.
Because I'm counting six.
Uh, inventory says eight.
Uh, glassware looking a little sparse.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
You're missing a couple of
erlenmeyer flasks at least.
Uh...oh, yeah.
A 5,000 milliliter round bottom.
Meth heads love to brew in this, baby.
Going to answer that?
Uh, no, it's just-- no, I don't-- I won't--
maybe it's Skyler.
She's in trouble or something.
I mean,----.
Don't ignore it on my account.
Answer it. Come on. I got stuff to do.
- Ah, jeez.
- Okay.
Hello.
What's up, Mr. W?
Uh, speaking.
Oh, bad time to talk?
Absolutely.
All right, so just listen.
You know that guy we were talking about, Tuco?
Turns out my boy skinny Pete was in the
same cellblock with him over at Los Lunas.
So we got our in.
We're hauling a pound to the dude right now.
Okay, then.
Well, thank you-- thank you very much for calling.
My doctor is very solicitous.
Hey, look, buddy, the last thing I want
to do is get you in hot water,
but some meth monkey had a
feeding frenzy in here, okay?
You got to keep a better watch over your turf.
I-- I will. All right.
We don't want people to start
wondering about you, right?
Right. No. Right. Absolutely not.
So you're sure you're tight with this guy?
Two nuts in a ----, yo.
Yo,man, I'm skinny Pete!
Maybe this isn't such a good idea, yo.
Come on.
Atta man. That's what's happening.
Yo, Tuco's expecting us.
No need, man. Me and Tuco go back.
Tuco. What's happening, my brother?
Sick crib, yo.
You been keeping it real since you been sprung.
What's it been, like a year?
This your boy?
Yeah-- Jesse, the dude with the glass
I was telling you about.
Hey, man. Yeah, I've heard a lot about you.
Break out the ice.
Take a bump.
No worries, man. I'm no cop.
I said hit it.
All right.
This kicks like a mule with his
-----wrapped in duct tape.
Where'd you get it?
I cooked it.
Who you working for?
No one, man.
I mean, I have a partner that I cook with, but
That's it.
All right.
We got a deal.
See? I told you Tuco would hook you up.
Cool.
I haven't said how much.
All right
How much?
35 large for the pound.
Well, you're a little light, ese.
It's all right. Don't sweat it.
It's all good.
It's good. Walk. Get out of here.
What about the money?
You'll get it.
This is a consignment operation.
You want me to float 35 g's?
You don't trust me?
No, no. Hey, it's not-- it's not that, man.
It's just, you know, I don't--
I don't do business that way.
Tough ----! The deal is done!
You said this was cool.
Get money for meth. Cash up front.
Don't front, dude. Tuco's good for it.
I don't need your punk ---to vouch for me!
Come on!
Oh, come on!
All right, you brought
me some really clean crystal.
Do you really want your money up front?
Up front.
Nobody moves crystal in the
south valley but me,-----!
good morning, Hugo.
Don't mind if I call you Hugo...
Hugo.
We've never had a crowd on the street like that.
Is that uncle Hank?
Holy ----.
Uncle Hank's arresting Mr. Archuleta.
Hugo, is that--
this doesn't make any sense to me at all.
I got two words for you: Background check.
How about that?
555-0 to the 1 to the 7 to the 8,
representing the abq.
What up? Leave it at the tone.
Where the hell are you?
Call me back.
- Hey, Walt.
- Yeah.
Uh, Hank's about to deal.
Okay. I'll, uh, I'll be right there.
All right. Let's see what the turn brings us.
You're looking good, Walt.
You-- your color's better.
Yeah?
Thanks.
He's actually on the pretty strong stuff now.
Dr. Delcavoli's trying to talk him into
taking some timeoff from work, but
well, actually, I just talked to Carmen this morning,
and they're getting a substitute for a few weeks.
Really?
I just didn't have a chance to tell you.
Sorry.
Your bet, tough guy.
Check.
Uh, yeah. Check.
Check's in the mail.
10 million.
Red's 25 million. Blue's 10.
Well, then 25 million because that's how I roll.
Hey, uncle Hank, why were you arresting
Mr.Archuleta the other day?
He's a pretty cool guy.
Well, uh, turns out that he has a record.
Yeah. Couple of possession beefs.
We figure he was the guy that was stealing
your school's chemistry gear.
I mean, you know, he had a key.
Fit the profile.
When we searched his truck,
we found a big old fat blunt,
which goes to prove old huge
Hugo ain't so cool after all.
It's-- it's to you, Walt.
Yeah, I-- I'll call.
You know, I can't believe the school system
didn't know about this guy's record.
I mean, that's pretty scary.
How could something like that just
slip through the cracks?
I don't know.
I mean, for what it's worth, Hugo just
doesn't strike me as the thief.
Yeah, well, nothing personal, Walt,
but you wouldn't know a criminal if he was
close enough to check you for a hernia.
Now, that said, we got a search warrant,
and we toreold Hugo's house apart.
Turns out he's a major league pothead.
But, uh, but he didn't raid your chemistry set.
You hiding something?
I'm in.
And the river card.
Yeah, I got nothing. I'm out.
I'm out.
When old "holes in her purse" bails,
you know you're in deep.
Looks like it's you and me, buddy.
What's going to happen to him? Hugo.
Oh, he-- well, I mean, he's going to
lose his job, like he should.
Probably spend a couple months in county,
as it's not his first rap.
I'm waiting.
You going to man up,
or you're going to ---- out?
Hank.
What? Sorry.
I'm all in.
No.
You bad, bad, bad, horrible liar.
What are you smoking there, huh?
You got a heart?
You got the flush, don't you?
Nope.
Not falling for it, buddy. I fold.
Talk about anti-climactic.
Your cards couldn't have been that bad.
Come on.
Oh, my god.
- You threw away an ace
- what are you doing?
- And a cowboy, for
- don't do it. What?
Oh... a handful of nothing.
Who is this?
I was dialing Jesse Pinkman.
Well, where is he, then?
You the guy?
Yeah, I'm the guy.
How is he?
Got some busted ribs and like that.
Got messed up pretty good.
I was all like"----, Tuco, chill, ese."
I don't know what got into him. Seriously.
Oh, he's out, man, way out.
They got him doped up big-time.
So you're the cook, huh?
Yo, I didn't catch your name.
Tell me about this Tuco.
Tell meev erything about him.
Good morning.
Would you pass the butter, please?
Bad ---, dad.
You tuco?
I want to talk to Tuco,
and I'm not leaving until I do.
What's your name?
Heisenberg.
Okay.
Have a seat, Heisenberg.
I don't imagine I'll be here very long.
No?
All right.
Be that way.
It's your meeting.
Why don't you start talking and
tell me what you want?
$50,000.
Oh, man!
50 g's?
How you figure that?
35 for the pound of meth you stole and another
15 for my partner's pain and suffering.
Partner.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that little -----.
So you must be daddy.
Let me get this straight.
I steal your dope, hmm?
I beat the ---- out of your mule boy!
And then you walk in here,
and you bring me more meth?
Whoo, that's a brilliant plan, ese.
Brilliant.
You got one part of that wrong.
This is not meth.
Are you ------- nuts?
You want to find out?
No-doze, gonzo, calma!
Calma. Calma.
Ah, yeah, you got -----.
I'll give you that.
All right. All right.
I'll give you your money.
That crystal that your partner brought
me I sold faster than $10 --- in tj.
What say you bring meanother pound next week?
Money up front.
All right.
Sometimes you got to rob to keep your riches.
Just as long as we got an understanding.
1 pound is not going to cut it.
You have to take 2.
Orale.
Hey.
What is that ----?
Fulminated mercury.
A little tweak of chemistry.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: µ°¸â »ð¼ý
Proudly Presents