- Huh?
- Hello.
♪ Supervillain,
ahead of his time ♪
♪ Incredibly handsome
genius, criminal mastermind ♪
♪ But now he's all cleaned
up and fighting crime ♪
♪ A superhero that
you stream online ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it feels good
to be good this time ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it's Megamind ♪
♪ Rules! ♪
Ah! 27 seconds and counting!
- Our time's running out!
- Okay
Dentist.
No! Stop guessing "dentist"!
Come on, Chum.
It's scary, it's got a
big mouth, little arms
-Oh! I
know! A shark, but with arms!
A shark but with arms?!
That's your guess?!
A T-Rex, Chum! It was a T-Rex!
- Sorry, not sorry.
So this is like regular
"Guess That Thing,"
but with electric shocks.
Yeah, painful ones!
Well, except for Chum.
The wattage is pretty
calming on his circuits.
It thure is, Kreiko.
This is how we do game night
at the lair, dear Roxie!
Now, are you ready
to guess that thing?
Let's do this!
- Megamind: Uh, okay!
This thing is... Um...
Oh, sorry. My brilliant
brain keeps thinking of.
Old English synonyms you
couldn't possibly know.
Try me. I'm
no Yorkshire raggedy fishwife.
Oh. I've never heard that one.
- I-I made it up! Keep going!
- Okay!
Remember one time when I
was evil and captured you?
This is what I dangled you over
- by the thinnest of strings...
Uh, genetically
modified piranhas!
- Mm, no, the other time.
- Quicksand!
- No, no! A different time!
- Bear traps!
- Yes! I dangled you over a pit of bear traps!
- Whew.
- That was close.
Almost as close as
you got to those bear traps.
Piranhas? Bear traps?
You guys have the
weirdest friendship ever!
I think we have a
perfectly normal
villain-turned-hero-
slash-reporter-turned-mayor camaraderie.
There's nothing normal
about that sentence at all.
I admit our relationship
is a bit unconventional,
but it's kinda like those videos
where a koala is
friends with an eel.
Okay, yeah, it is kinda weird.
Christina: Couldn't agree more.
But I would replace
"kinda" with "very,"
and I'd replace
Megamind with anyone.
Sorry. Polls say voters prefer
a mayor with normal friends.
You're still here?
Don't you turn back into
a bale of hay at sundown?
The mayor's work is never done.
We still have to finish
the municipal operations
facility's budget.
Guess the mayor's work is
never interesting either.
Hey, man, it's game
night at the lair!
You leave your
manners at the door.
- Whoa.
Sorry, guys. I gotta head home.
Already? It's way
before your curfew!
I have to work on an
extra credit project.
If I don't build a robot
that can throw a tennis ball,
my science teacher
will flunk me.
If it's a robot you need,
you're more than welcome to use
all the high-tech doodads
the lair has to offer.
Really? I can use
all your cool stuff?
Oh, Mr. Schlurg-Peterman might
give me extra-extra credit!
- Wait. Bennett Schlurg-Peterman?
- You know her teacher?
We were
inseparable at summer camp.
They didn't even need
to tie us together
- for the three-legged race.
- So, why aren't you hanging out
with this everyday card-carrying
member of the teachers union
instead of these
stinking weirdos?
- Hey!
- Yipe! Aaah...
Man, I haven't seen
Bennett in years,
but we used to have so much fun.
Like bear trap, piranha fun?
Different in that it was
a more... normal fun.
Yeah, we must be talking about
a different Schlurg-Peterman.
Schlurg-Peterman?
Sounds like a law firm
- that represents haunted toys.
- Chum: Mm...
Or that noise Chum's making.
- Schluuuuuurrrrrrrrrrrg.
Burp McSchlurp Esquire?!
Ritchi Von Coconut Cannon?!
- It's really you!
- I can't believe it!
My science classroom's
down there.
It's really not that exciting.
Not exciting? To see where
my dear Keiko fills her mind
with test tube wishes
and double helix dreams?
I mostly doodle.
Well, now you can
skee-doodle on home.
I want to experience this solo.
Are you sure this isn't about
Roxie and Mr. Schlurg-Peterman?
I said skee-doodle.
Please. What could some
boring normie-normal ton
have to offer
friendship-wise over moi?
♪ Camp Frog Ear!
Camp Frog Ear! ♪
♪ If we could, we'd
stay all year! ♪
Huh?
Megamind! What a surprise!
Uh, Bennett, Megamind.
Megamind, Bennett.
Schlurg-Peterman.
Ah, just reminiscing
about summer camp here
with ol' Coconut Cannon.
Yikes. Insulting her
stringy coconut-like hair?
Not so nice, Bennett.
I have stringy hair?
Oh, we called her Coconut Cannon
because of her killer throwing
skills on the dodge ball field.
Not as killer as
your air muffins
on Wet Chili Wednesdays.
You
know, in prison,
I invented a snack called
"toothpaste bites."
Yes, I know.
Oh! Our
secret handshake!
How have we not done that yet?
Excuse me, Roxie?
Remember when I trapped
you on a hot air balloon
with tarantulas?
- That was fairly enjoyable...
- One, two, three.
Both: And pinky! Wazoo! Cronch!
- Bennett: I can't believe we remembered it all!
- Roxie: Oh, I know!
- Oh...
- Chum: Oh, Sir.
- Did you use a taquito as a chocolate milk straw again?
Oh, this is a different
kind of agony, Chum.
Like longing mixed with sadness
mixed with feelings
of inadequacy.
Keiko: Sounds like
someone's jealous.
You know, 'cause you
and Roxie are a thing?
We're not a "thing."
Why? Did she say something?
I just figured you guys
were deeply in love,
but pretend to be too
busy to realize it
because you're both terrified.
That's how hero
relationships normally work.
It's complicated, Keiko.
And I am not jealous!
I'm sure my tummy has
nothing to do with the fact
that the goodest thing
that ever happened to me
has replaced me with
her old camp buddy,
and they share nothing
but warm fuzzy memories!
Just wondering,
have you told Roxie
you think she's the goodest?
Which is adorable, by the way.
I grew up in a prison, remember?
I'm new to the
whole friend thing.
- Um, hello? Standing right here.
Oh, Chum, I adore you,
but you're more of
a vestigial limb
or a helpful ghost
haunting me for life.
- I'll take it!
- Oh, you don't understand
the pain I'm in.
When I was young, I
never even got to play
- a decent game of...
- Robot: Throw!
- Ow!
It's actually called
"catch," but yes.
My robot actually works!
And just in time for dinner.
Try not to be jealous, okay?
So you don't have an old
camp buddy. Who cares?
You're Megamind. You can
do literally anything!
Huh...
Keep an eye on my
pal here, will you?
- Hm...
Pal
That's it!
Maybe it's time I
make a pal of my own!
Come, come, little robot.
♪ Her pants got eaten
by a crocodile ♪
- Oh yeah.
Ooh! Remember when we
snuck into the cabin
where they kept all
the confiscated candy?
I've never thrown
up so many colors in my life.
Oh. It's nothing. City social
media account tagged me.
Happens all the... Wait.
"Our mayor with her
oh-so-normal teacher friend.
Hashtag relatable."
- Christina...
Hey! That's us!
I am so sorry about this.
I don't normally have
paparazzi, I swear.
It must be weird being
friends with adult me.
I'm cool with it. It feels like
- the most normal thing in the world.
Megamind:  Yes!
And I have a feeling
those normal feelings
are about to change.
Oh!  You
guys come here, too?
Roxanne, Bennett,
I'd like you to meet
my old camp buddy,
- Pal-3000!
Ollo! We were bunkmates
at Camp Turkey Neck.
Oh, the friendship
memories we shared.
What? You don't really
expect us to believe
this scraggly hunk of metal
is an old friend of yours?
- Your words make me sad.
- I am sad now. Hm...
I programmed him to be very
in touch with his emotions.
Not advanced AI so much as
a simple copy-paste
of my own heart.
I thought you said
you met at camp.
It was a day camp, and that
day happened to be today.
And while Pal-3000 may
indeed be made of metal,
he and I have just as
strong a bond as you two.
Actually, I might even
argue that we have
an even stronger
bond than you two!
It's not a competition.
Perhaps, but you know
what is a competition?
- Limbo!
Come on, limbo!
Who will crash to the
ground on their spine first?
- Oh!
- S-So, what's
the deal with you and him?
It's complicated.
I'd say he's not
normally like this,
but my nose would start growing.
Like Pinocchio!
Because you'd be lying!
You got it!
Shall we finish?
- Enough limbo.
Time for Camp Turkey Neck Cheer.
Brilliant idea,
robo pal of mine!
- Who's in the neck?
- I'm in the neck!
My neck of the woods?
Your neck of the woods!
Both: Turkey Neck! Turkey
Neck! Gobble, gobble, gobble!
Ha-ha ha-ha! Memories good.
Shared memories better.
- Come on, guys! Gobble!
- You don't have to... Ah!
- Gobble, gobble!
- Ow!
No! This is the
opposite of normal!
Where is my robot?
- Uh,
have you checked the lair?
We're in the lair!
He's due today!
- Dah! I need to stress scroll.
Why is my science
project wearing a hat
and throwing donuts
at Megamind?!
Oh, food fight!
Just like old times!
- Oh no!
- Hey, come on, cut it out!
- Look out! Gonna get ya!
- Ha! Throwing food at you!
- So sorry about all this.
- Eh, it's not your fault.
We'll try again soon. Yeah,
I'm gonna make a run for it.
Watch out, Pal-3000!
You're about to get
a face full of jelly!
- Oh...
Here comes that
awful feeling again.
Ha-ha!
You just got
Pal-3000'ed in the face.
- You stole my science project?!
No, I borrowed your
science project.
The robot isn't even yours?!
No, it's not!
You can have him back.
Turns out, it wasn't
enough to relieve me
of my churning tummy anyways.
Plus, I think Roxie may be
a tad displeased with me.
If you could fill a city
bus with a tad, then yes.
- It's been fun, Pal-3000,
but our lifelong hour of
friendship has come to an end.
- Pal-3000: Mm.
- Run along now.
I'm truly sorry, Roxie.
L-Let me get these sprinkles
out of your stringy hair.
Come on, science project.
We have my academic
future to save.
-Pal-3000:
Processing... Processing...
Not science project.
Pal-3000 is Megamind's
best friend.
But, Megamind is no longer
best friend to Pal-3000.
Then, Pal-3000 must
find new Megamind
to be best friend.
I think my homework's
freaking out!
Uh...
Must find new Megamind.
- Must fight new Megamind.
- Must find new Megamind.
Megamind!
Not Megamind.
Uh, think you
could drive faster?
Speed is relative, Keiko.
- This is not
the time for relaxation.
We've got an
emotionally unstable
and potentially dangerous
robot on the loose!
Must replace Megamind.
Must find new Megamind.
- Megamind. Not Megamind.
- Hey! What are you doing?
- Throw!
Whoa!
- Friend: Dude, you okay?
- Pal-3000: Ha-ha ha-ha. Memories good.
- Shared memories better.
Feeling melancholy.
Hm. Want to journal.
Roxie: He just tossed that
civilian like a rag doll!
Megamind: Uh, yeah,
so I may have reinforced
his metal body
with space alloy
and made him 1,000 times
stronger than a human.
- What?!
Oh, sure. It sounds crazy now,
but what if we were in
a tug-of-war contest?
Not Megamind! Throw!
- Not Megamind! Throw!
- Not Megamind!
- Throw!
Unbelievable! All of this
just because you were jealous.
What? This is all because of
that diabolical
Schlurg-Peterman.
Bennett?! What did he do?
I don't know, but
for some reason,
I don't like the guy!
Again, all of this
could have been avoided
if you both just clearly
defined your relationship.
Both: It's complicated,
Keiko!
Pal-3000: Not Megamind.
Not Megamind. Not Megamind.
- Not Megamind.
You gotta do something!
- Nice knowing you, Pal-3000.
No! I still need him
for my science grade!
Ugh. It's gonna be absolutely
impossible to tame him.
Just pretend to be
his friend again,
so we can make him go to school.
- Not Megamind...
- I'd rather not. He's so needy.
It can make him so
unpleasant to be around.
Sounds like someone I know.
Yeah. Bennett, am I right?
Not Megamind! Not Megamind!
Not Megamind!
Not Megamind.
Not Megamind. Not Megamind. Not...
Giving him what he wants is
the only way to stop this,
and what he wants is you.
- Megamind...
Gah. Can't you just make
do with a lower GPA?
Colleges care far more about
extracurriculars, you know.
If I don't get extra
credit, I fail.
If I fail, my mom won't let me
hang out at the lair anymore.
She won't let me hang
out with any of you!
I should
step it up then.
But, if I pull something doing
the Turkey Neck Cheer again,
- I expect foot massages from all of you.
- No!
- Absolutely not.
- I got first dibs!
- Not Megamind. Not Megamind.
Yoo-hoo! Pal-3000!
- My bestest friend.
- Megamind!
- Ha ha ha.
You look hungry.
Uh...
Trust fall!
Oh, no.
Pal-3000: Throw. Catch.
Throw. Catch.
- Throw. Catch.
Lead him over here!
Uh, why don't we go this way?
More friendship fun to be had.
There? Processing.
- Processing. Analyzing new data.
Megamind led me to girl who
called me science project.
Ultimate betrayal detected.
Engage tantrum protocol.
- Hey!
- Calm down! It's okay!
- Megamind will not leave Pal-3000.
This friendship is
officially toxic!
Aah!
- Megamind!
- Sir!
Up, where nobody can stop us.
Ha-ha!
Ah, this
will all be fine.
- Woo!
Ah!
We don't need gun
for friendly fun.
Oh, blast that magnetic alloy!
That I added. Why must
I always overachieve?
- What do we do?!
- I don't know! Chum,
- I forget. Can you fly?
Nah. The space alloy I'm
made of is super heavy.
- Yow!
That's it! If the
orb calms Chum,
and they're made out
of the same stuff...
You are thinking
of other friends.
- Mm-mm-mmm!
Ah! Of course not!
Uh, come here, you huggable
pal! Let's play a game.
How about Guess That Thing?!
Not with Roxanne, but
with you, my real friend.
Oh, a game? Yes, please!
Guess That
Thing! On game night,
we all had to play with these
small, round, dangerous things.
- Remember?!
- Game night does not compute.
The electrified orb!
No! No! Not the orb of calmness!
We have to throw it to
Pal-3000 to save Megamind.
- Soon, they'll be too high up. This is our one shot.
Can't you throw it
up there? For Sir?
I can't!
You'll have to! For Sir!
- Come on, Coconut Cannon.
You got this.
- Hey, Pal-3000!
Catch!
- Catch! My favorite game.
- Megamind: Chum, grab it!
Oh, my
beautiful orb!
Pal-3000: Ah... Taking nap now.
I may not have
thought this through!
- Chum!  I'll do it.
- Decelerate! To slow their fall!
Ah. I see you paid some
attention in science class.
Breathe. Aim. Shoot.
O... kay.
Good... aim... Roxanne...
Nope! No time for your
decelerated thoughts!
I got a class to pass!
Okay, Pal-3000.
Throw the ball.
Hum... I will never be
Megamind's best friend.
What's the point?
What's the point of
anything, anyway?
Mr. Schlurg-Peterman, you saw
what Pal-3000 is capable of!
Ooh, sorry. Rules are rules.
Unless he throws
that ball, you fail.
Look, Pal-3000. I made
you to be my best friend.
But I saw today that you
can't just make a friend.
You can't force someone to
feel how you want them to.
Friendship is more
like a game of catch.
It's give and take.
And today, I was
a real ball hog.
I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry I was
going to throw you off
the top of a skyscraper.
That's oka... Wait, what?
Oh, hey, someone give
me that ball to throw.
- Throw!
- Robot: Catch.
Keiko: Whoa!
Don't be surprised. I
am up to my eyeballs
in extra-credit robots.
- A lot of kids are failing.
- Analyzing. A new friend.
Conclusion, vastly
superior to Megamind.
Vastly superior?
I don't like that.
Recognize a good thing?
Robots: Ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha...
Alright, Keiko.
You now have a B-.
Yes! Can we have another
game night to celebrate?
- Of course!
- How about 8:30?
- Absolutely.
- Roxie! You in?
Oh, we were gonna
finish our meal.
I guess I'm cool with
you two hanging out.
Oof!
Puddles of poodles, that hurt.
Pal-3000: My bad.
Uh...
- A giraffe on a sailboat!
- Lasagna! The War of 1812!
These are all horrible guesses!
- Roxie. Where's Bennett?
Turns out, we don't have a lot
in common beyond camp memories.
And sure, you and I have
some not-so-fun memories,
but who cares?
We have all the time in
the world to make new ones.
Like today, when I saved you
from being thrown
off a building.
Or when you shot that De-Gun
at me with perfect aim.
I've never been so decelerated.
O-Or when that robot tossed
that guy into the garbage!
That was actually very scary.
And how about that
throw, Coconut Cannon?
Oh, stop.
- Uh, you do know that's still counting down, right?
That is quite calming.
- Ow!