- Huh?
- Hello.
♪ Supervillain,
ahead of his time ♪
♪ Incredibly handsome
genius, criminal mastermind ♪
♪ But now he's all cleaned
up and fighting crime ♪
♪ A superhero that
you stream online ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it feels good
to be good this time ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it's Megamind ♪
♪ Rules! ♪
Roxanne: Yes, I am
aware of the damage,
and we're working on it.
Were you aware that we're
giving away a free coffee
to anyone inconvenienced
by a Megamind battle?
- Let me in, Christina!
- Oh, no, no, no!
We have a very strict
no nuisance policy!
According
to my nuisance detector,
you're actually the nuisance,
and your readings
are off the charts!
- You let me go!
- Congratulations, guys.
You're both
nuisances! Let him in.
I... Ah!
You did that on purpose.
She's crazy busy
dealing with the people
mad at the damage you caused
playing hero out there,
so make this quick.
Ah-chnoo-sance!
That was
not a real sneeze.
Roxie, I have some
tech that will help us
keep Metrocity safer than
a baby in bubble wrap.
I'm happy you're excited
about your invention,
but I'm slammed today.
I swear, I don't think I could
handle just one more thing.
- Lady
Doppler : Attention!
This is an evil weather alert!
Good morning, Metro City!
- Ooh! Lady Doppler...
- Shh!
I have a forecast for today.
Dark and stormy over
the mayor's office.
The map says sunshine.
She always was
terrible at weather.
And for Roxanne Ritchi,
the tattletale former reporter
who got me fired
all those years ago,
- 100% chance of revenge!
She's good.
Hey, just because I'm
a hero doesn't mean
I've lost my appreciation
for quality treachery.
She shot lightning at me!
And, yes, I did get her fired.
But now, I have to
arrange a bodyguard,
cancel public appearances,
probably build a bunker.
There, there. Relax your boo-tay
on that ergonomic chair, Roxie.
Stopping baddies is
my bag. Fear not!
It's easy for you
to say, "Fear not."
You're walking around all
safe with a pew-pew ray gun.
It's more of a
chick a-pow ray gun.
But, my wits protect this
city more than my weapon.
Which brings me to the
purpose of my visit.
- My new gadget.
Ow!
Huh? What the?
I look... like... you.
- Why do you look like me?
- Switcheroo microchips!
The hottest new crime-stopping
tech from yours truly.
And sound like
me. I-I sound like you!
It's a twist on the
disguise generator.
Explain any scenario in
which this would be useful.
It's... great for a
good bamboozlement.
Can't you just turn it off?!
It's more of a wear-off thing.
How long does it last?
- A few days, tops.
- Days?!
I'm the mayor! I have people
waiting to see me now.
Don't be such a nervous Nadine.
How hard is it being
mayor of Metrocity?
First, it's
pronounced Metro City.
- Second, don't let the intercom scare you.
Christina : Madam Mayor, the
gentleman from the parking garage is here.
Great. He's already upset about
you blowing up his garage.
Why? The jaywalker's getaway
car was parked there.
So were a thousand other cars!
I won't apologize
for being thorough.
You will do exactly as I say.
This stays hush-hush.
If anyone finds out,
it'll seem like I'm not
in control of the city.
- And that's the last... Whoa. Whoa!
Oh...  Your
head is so big.
It's like balancing a
turkey on a toothpick!
You need to find me a
new place to park cars!
Just park them in the park.
It's right there in the name.
- I'm allowed to do that?
- I do it all the time.
It's not like there's
a law against it.
Roxie-As-Megamind: There's
absolutely a law against it!
He can't park cars
in the public park!
Is this thing on?
- Yes, it's on.
- Huh?
The things I say under
my breath are not for you.
Roxie-As-Megamind: Your
request is not possible.
Your request is not possible.
Roxie-As-Megamind: Thank
you for stopping by.
Thank you for stopping by.
Really? That's it? Can I
give him a muffin or something?
- I'd like a muffin.
- No muffin.
I withdraw my offer of muffins.
Figures. I had a feeling
you'd do nothing for me.
If I remember to vote,
It won't be for you.
Let me tell you something I
learned in the few seconds
I've been mayor. People
like to hear "yes."
It's all that "no" stuff
that makes you unpopular.
No wonder you're stressed
out all the time.
This should be an easy job.
The job would be a lot
easier without all of your
swing-by-the-seat-of-your-pants
antics.
Now, you're attacking
pants antics,
the one sport I'm good at!
Give me this pew-pew ray gun,
and I'd do 10 times
the saving you do
with half the damage!
Ha! Maybe a 13%
reduction. At most.
O-Okay... Uh,
there are more angry people
here who wanna complain to you.
- Let them in.
- Get rid of them.
The mayor isn't
really feeling well,
and we thought maybe
she should rest.
I've made a remarkable recovery!
Christina, send in
the complainers!
Don't you have to
present Keiko Morita
with the Citizen Heroism Award?
I don't see that here.
That's because the defender
of the city gives that medal.
You must be getting
our schedules confused
- for no real reason at all.
- You heard the mayor!
- Playtime is over! Move it!
- But... But...
- Let's go, let's go! Brilliant retort, as always.
- Do nothing. Say nothing.
Ugh, and let her wallow in
the hatred of her citizenry?
No. I will make Roxanne Ritchie
the most popular mayor
in Metrocity history!
Are you speaking
in third person?
Maybe. Megamind does it,
and he's way cooler than you.
- Roxie-As-Megamind: Metro... AH.
Metrocity is fortunate enough
to have someone
as brave as Keiko
among its citizens.
Or ci-tie-zens.
And let's not forget the
importance of a good mayor
'cause you've got one. She
can be overlooked, you know.
She's really doing
everything she can
about all the
damage. Or de-mage.
Anyway, for her bravery
in helping stop
the Doom Syndicate,
I present Keiko Morita
with this award.
- Let's hear it for her, Metrocity!
Roxanne?
No. I'm Megamind.
Keiko: I appreciate
you taking time
from throwing darts
at the mayor's picture
to give me this award.
He does that?!
Aha! You are Roxanne!
Okay, okay.
He tried some
switcheroo tech on me,
and it's not wearing off.
And how is that a bad thing?
Oh, I'd love to be
Megamind for a day.
Chasing bad guys, zapping
stuff with the pa-pow ray gun.
Oh, you know what? We should
totally stop some crimes!
No! I need to get
back to my office.
He's at my desk,
looking like me,
and I have to make sure he
doesn't do any mayor stuff!
You could do that,
or you could not be
a totally lame person
and stop some crimes!
- Yeah, but...
- Hear me out.
This could also help
Megamind's web channel.
I need some content where
he's a little more personable,
and that comes naturally to you.
Thanks, I get it, but we
shouldn't press our luck.
- Also, his pants are really tight.
I've got a
super-wedgie going on.
So sorry I'm late, Sir.
I was trying to butter toast
with some very cold butter.
- Oh, it's fine.
- No, it's not!
I'm a terrible sidekick.
Oh. Um, you know, I
don't say this enough,
but I appreciate you.
Sir? Are you okay?
- Maybe we should check your temperature.
Officer : Attention, all
units. Purse snatching in progress.
Shall we pursue, Sir?
Oh, I don't think
that's a very good...
Dude! You gotta spend
time in Megamind's shoes,
- see how it feels.
- Uh,
pretty sure he does
that every day, Keiko.
I guess this could be a chance
to prove that it is
possible to save the day
without causing so much
pain-in-the-mayoral-rear damage.
- Plus, I get
to fire the pew-pew ray gun.
I thought we agreed it was
more of a chick a-pow ray gun.
Oh, uh, sorry, Sir. I
know you hate this song.
I don't, actually.
Just yesterday,
you said it was the national
anthem of throwing up.
Well, I've changed
my mind. It's catchy.
Makes me wanna dance
in my too-tight pants.
- Turn it up.
- Okay, then!
- Can I get
a "waka waka woo" up in here?!
♪ Waka waka woo ♪
- Mayor's office.
You want to place a giant snow
globe in the art district?
In the middle of the street?
In the middle of summer?!
- I can't think of a single reason why not! Yes!
- You've got the mayor.
Parking enforcement
is overwhelmed?
- Well, I say yes to giving them the day off!
Dog lovers wanna hold a
rally in the city square?
- That's a big yes!
Cat lovers wanna hold a
rally in the city square?
The more the merrier!
Y-E-S spells yes!
Whee!
I need to
hit the gym more!
Please stop! I have
a rock in my boot!
Uh-oh. Getting the pukies.
I'm never
gonna catch this guy.
Time for old pew-pew!
- Wh-Whoa! Whoa! Ah!
Huh?
- Chum.
What do you think is the best
setting on this right now?
You're asking my opinion, Sir?
He turned down the next block!
Chum, cut him off! I
need a good ending.
- Roxie-As-Megamind: Ha, ha!
- Huh?
- Got you!
- Oh...
See ya!
Woo! What a rush!
And I have to say, I don't
think we did that much damage.
- Ooh, we did much damage.
Now, give us a pose and a line.
Um...
Remember, I did
not do this alone.
It took all three of us to
stop this purse snatcher.
He was very fast.
A Megamind who takes direction.
This is a dream!
Hey-hey!
You know what is going
to send Roxanne's...
Uh, I mean my approval
ratings through the roof?
Showmanship!
♪ Bing bop, biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo ♪
♪ Bing bop, biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo ♪
♪ My polka dot llama
likes to play ♪
♪ He runs all night ♪
♪ And sleeps all day ♪
♪ When I get lost,
he knows the way ♪
♪ And this is what
he has to say ♪
♪ Bing bop, biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo ♪
♪ Bing bop, biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo ♪
♪ My llama loves
the circus ring ♪
♪ He jumps around,
bing bong bing ♪
♪ Eats hay all day like a king ♪
♪ And this is what
he likes to sing ♪
♪ Bing bop, biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo... ♪
Doppler: I promise, your
next public appearance
is going to be electrifying!
Oh, Megamind.
Have you always been this
strong, smart, and appealing?
Thank you for
sending my popularity
- into the stratosphere!
Anchor : Megamind
has been at it again.
- Citizens are fed up. The meal?
Megamind's excessive
destruction.
He turned me into
a bullion cube.
My doctor says I'm not
supposed to be a bullion cube.
What in the name
of Darwin's donut?
- She's ruining my rep! Roxie!
- Come in.
- I'm here.
We're just stuck in some
sort of traffic nightmare.
What exactly have you
been doing out there?
It's taken a lot of work
to make you popular,
and you're destroying
the city in my name?
I am not... Wait.
What do you mean,
make me popular?
Have you been mayoring?
Funny story.
I might have made
some appearances.
- Appearances? As in more than one appearance?
And maybe changed
some parking laws.
Ah!
Did you approve of that gaudy
art snow globe I kept rejecting?
Apparently, people
love giant things
where they're not
supposed to be.
- I don't get it either.
- Hey, move it!
- Get outta the road!
I gotta get to work here!
There's a war brewing
outside, ma'am!
You said dog rally,
not cat rally.
Dogs aren't smart
enough to rally!
This is preposterous.
Why can't you all get
along? Like cats and dogs!
We should get you
back inside, ma'am.
I'm reaping what I've sown.
Things are coming back
to bite me in the butt.
- I've created a monster. And other clichés!
- Roxie-As-Megamind: What's happening?
- So, listen. Sure,
I did some mayoring wrong, and
now they all hate me or you.
W-We're gonna
have to fix this.
The people need to hear from
their calm, collected mayor.
Megamind-As-Roxie: I don't
know how to quell the masses.
Remember, they're
looking for leadership.
First, get a podium
in front of you.
Now, give a speech
that's stern but fair.
Citizens of Metrocity.
Start acting civilized
or feel my wrath!
- No!
Do not threaten the citizens.
Oh, good. Lady Doppler
just showed up.
Didn't you say you'd handle her?
Sorry. I got distracted by
the whole becoming you thing.
Good news is she's after me now,
so you're it.
Fine. You calm the mob.
I think I've spent
enough time in your shoes
to keep this weather
witch at bay.
Roxie,
they're staring at me
with their ordinary
eyes. What do I say?
Megamind! Your girlfriend
shoulda worn a raincoat
'cause a blizzard's
coming to City Hall!
A raincoat for snow?
Do you even know
what weather is?
A raincoat for snow?
Do you even know
what weather is?
That was for
Doppler, not you.
Hey, Doppler, here's
a forecast for you.
A butt-kicking front coming in
with a 100% chance of defeat!
You're getting some
great lines in on Doppler,
but I need great lines, too.
- Feel my thunder!
- Ah!
- Oh!
- Hello? Hello?!
Not ideal.
You do realize that was
lightning, not thunder, right?
Catch me if you can.
We can't let her
get to Megamind!
She's already gotten
past you, Sir.
- Way past, in fact.
- Uh, I meant Roxanne.
- Let's go!
- Hello? Hello?
I gotta say something.
Citizens of Metro... Ci... ty.
I think you're all wonderful.
And marvelous! And
really cool and stuff.
- The end. And mic drop?
Not one more step.
I got you, Gail.
Really?
Womp, womp. Oh, what
happened to you?
You used to be better than this.
- Pathetic!
- Christina: Okay, okay!
Everyone, just calm down!
- Ma'am,
I advise you to open your
mouth and let words come out.
What would Roxanne do?
She wouldn't vaporize
anyone, so that's out.
She would also say "no" a lot.
Ollo... Hello. How's it going?
- Okay, okay.
You're mad because I used
to say "no" too much,
and now, I've said
"yes" too much.
What I've learned is there's
a time for each of those,
and now is a "no" time.
Like no division.
We can all work together
to make things easier.
- Eh, I don't know about that.
- She's not wrong.
What about no
fighting? That's good!
If you're a dog lover, don't
fight with the cat lovers.
They're just like you,
only they prefer to love an
animal that actively hates them
and goes to the bathroom
in a box in their home.
The point is,
we're all the same.
We're all weird, but,
you know, a-a good weird.
And if we can all imagine
walking in each other's shoes,
maybe we can learn to appreciate
and respect each
other's weirdness.
Then, none of us are
weird! We're just us.
- Metrocity!
We interrupt this boring
speech for a weather alert.
An earthquake's a-comin'!
An earthquake isn't weather.
- Why is everybody on my case today?
Roxie is in
danger. Let's go!
You go. I'm sure it'll be easier
to defeat Lady
Doppler without me.
That doesn't sound
like you, Sir.
Yeah, we're gonna need
confident Megamind back.
But my pew-pew ray gun is
busted.
Pardon my language,
but gun shmun.
It's your wits that
protect the city, Sir,
not your weapon.
Well, as Keiko knows,
I'm not quite feeling
like myself today.
But even if you're feeling
like, oh, say Roxanne today,
you know that Roxanne is
at least as smart as you.
Huh.
You're right.
I am as smart as Roxanne.
Not sure I understand, but
I agree with the message!
You're the master of
plans and schemes.
I'm certain you can
come up with a way
to contain Lady
Doppler's weather attack.
Contain the
weather... That's it!
The mayor may have
been terrible today,
but she gave us just the tool
we need to defeat Doppler!
Plans and schemes!
That's my Sir!
You're about to
lose in a landslide!
That's clearly a tornado.
And again, landslide?
Not weather!
I'm exhausted
correcting this woman.
Aw, unfortunately, there's no
time for an official recall.
Let's just skip to the
part where you're ousted!
Looks like the sky
is clearing up.
Didn't I already defeat you?
You destroyed my
gun, not my mind.
Nothing a change in
weather pattern can't fix.
Ah!
Chum! Snow globe!
Yes!
I think I'm gonna
be sick!
Doppler out.
That's a wrap, everybody!
Outstanding work.
Specifically the saving me part.
I even had a cool line!
Looks like the sky
is clearing up!
Crowd: Megamind!
Megamind! Megamind!
It sounds so beautiful.
Like angels.
You calmed them down
all on your own.
That's great.
They were chanting your
name earlier, I swear.
Looks like Metrocity
loves us both once again.
Bring it in, team.
I love this new
in-touch-with-your-feelings Sir.
Let's not get too used to it.
Maybe just special occasions.
Roxie: Thank you!
Now, I hate to be
a "mayor downer..."
Get it? Like major...
Never mind.
Parking rules are back in effect
and fines will be doubled.
- I gotta move my car!
- I can't afford a ticket!
Thanks for the opportunity, Sir.
- From now on, this song will be ours.
♪ Bing bop, Biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
No, no, no, no. Not the
national anthem of throwing up!
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka
woo, my llama... ♪
- Your
ever-changing personality remains
a wonderful mystery to me, Sir.
♪ Bing bop, Biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo ♪
♪ Bing bop, Biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo ♪
♪ Now, a cow can moo, moo! ♪
♪ And a dove does coo, coo! ♪
♪ And a ghost goes boo, boo! ♪
♪ But this is what my llama
says with a giggle or two ♪
♪ Bing bop, Biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo ♪
♪ Bing bop, Biddy
biddy bing bop ♪
♪ Zing zoo, waka waka woo! ♪