(neon buzzing)
- (line straining)
- (grunting)
- Huh?
- Hello.
(screams)
(theme song playing)
♪ Supervillain,
ahead of his time ♪
♪ Incredibly handsome
genius, criminal mastermind ♪
♪ But now he's all cleaned
up and fighting crime ♪
♪ A superhero that
you stream online ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it feels good
to be good this time ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it's Megamind ♪
♪ Rules! ♪
[beep, static]
Citizens of Metrocity,
I need your help!
I've been kidnaped by one
who I used to call friend.
And now, they're torturing
me ever so cruelly!
Calm down, Captain Hysteria.
I wanted to surprise you for
all the hard work you're doing.
Don't you like surprises?
I have no problem
with surprises.
It's just the ones that come
out of nowhere and surprise you.
So, you just don't like
surprising surprises.
(groans) The tension
is unbearable!
Just let me guess what
it is. A bigger statue?
Plutonium? A bouquet of puppies?
Tell me. Wait! Don't tell
me. I retract that! Tell me!
- Okay, before you explode.
- (sighs)
Ta-da!
- (gentle music playing)
- (gasps)
Sweet, shimmering Shangri-La!
I know you've become a fan
since Chum helped
revamp the place, and
(excited panting) Oh... Okay.
Ooh! I want that one!
No, I want that one!
Oh, so many choices!
Well, who says you gotta choose just
one? (Laughs) - Megamind: Mr. Donut!
Roxanne, it's Mr. Donut!
Did my outfit give it away?
(laughing)
You're witnessing a
master at work, Roxanne.
Look! He juggles donuts as
well as he deep fries them.
Mr. Donut: Yeah, I do!
Ho ho ho ho!
- Ho!
- Whoa!
Oh! (Gasps) The precision!
- Then you are gonna love this!
- (gasps)
Who's this beautiful creature?
That is our new Megadonut.
My tribute to the
city's greatest hero.
You, sir, are an artist.
Who would have imagined?
A few weeks ago,
this place was just
another greasy diner.
But whether it's
week-old soup or donuts,
whenever fate points
me in a new direction,
I dive in 100%!
Well, this donut is about
to 100% dive into my belly.
Well, since you hate
surprises so much,
maybe we'll skip the next one.
Tell me what it is! I beg you!
Easy! I have arranged
for Mr. Donut
to give us a little tour.
Mr. Donut: Usually, I like to
keep my baking process a secret,
but I think I can
make an exception
for the defender of
Metro City. Follow me.
Ah-ah, I almost forgot.
No eating in the kitchen.
This'll give you time to digest
the seven donuts you
had on the way over.
Fine
(brainbots beeping)
Business is booming!
Though, it would be nice
to spend a little more time
with the wife and kids.
Psst! Hey, buddy. What
are you waiting for?
- (dreamy music playing)
- Don't you want to take a bite?
(whispers) Of course.
I want nothing more!
Mr. Donut: Did
you say something?
(conveyor belt rattling) - (normal)
Uh, I-I said, "Please tell us more."
This is all just the beginning.
Got some big plans
for expanding.
First across town, then
across the country.
Before you know it, Mr. Donut's
gonna take over the world!
Megadonut: Ollo...
My sweet, gooey
flesh is yearning
for those pearly chompers.
Ugh, you're clearly just
my donut-loving imagination
playing tricks on me.
And here's the secret
to the whole operation.
My famous sticky glaze.
You've saved my Metrocity twice.
Surely you deserve one bite.
That is airtight
logic. Ah... (grunts)
(quietly) You have the
self-control of a puppy
around a sloppy toddler.
He said no eating.
Roxanne, both you and the
donut make good arguments,
except if I listen to
you, I get nothing.
(both struggling)
- (tense music playing)
- (slow motion gasp)
(splat)
(both gasp)
(both sigh)
And you'll find this
interesting. The vat actually
(screaming)
- (dramatic music playing)
(Megamind, Roxanne gasp)
We have to save him!
No donut baker dies on my watch.
(triumphant music playing)
(squishing)
(Roxanne yelps)
- Mr. Donut!
- (squishing)
- Are you okay?
- (sighs)
I think I slipped on jelly.
But how could that
have happened?
Both: Uh...
(siren wails)
All his vitals are fine.
- He's just really sticky.
- (stethoscope snaps)
I guess he could
just hold on to that.
I think now would be a good time
to apologize to Mr. Donut.
You're the one who
grabbed my arm!
Fine. We'll do this together.
(gentle music playing)
Mr. Donut, we owe
you an apology.
Roxanne's blatant rule-following
caused me to squirt the jelly.
(weakly) I'll pay
you back for this.
That's not good.
What did he say?
Everything okay?
Actually, I'm afraid
things have gone
- from bad to evil.
- (dramatic crescendo)
Whoa! Oh!
- (static)
- Citizens of Metrocity,
you're about to see something
rarely captured on film.
The origin of a supervillain
out in the wild.
Roll it!
(weakly) I'll pay
you back for this.
- Ah, ha!
- (grunts)
What are you up to?
- Mr. Donut is the nicest person ever.
- Oh, really?
Do nice guys admit their
plans for world domination?
- Exhibit A.
- (beep)
Mr. Donut's gonna
take over the world!
(dramatic sting)
Is your head also
filled with jelly?
He just meant that he wants
to expand his business.
His business is badness,
and Mr. Donut is all in.
- Exhibit B!
- (beep)
- But whether it's week-old soup or donuts...
- Megamind (dubbed): Or evil!
- (beep)
I dive in 100%!
(Megamind laughs evilly)
That's not even his evil
laugh. That's your evil laugh.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
(on video) Chum, how
is my evil laugh?
You're assuming he's
going to turn evil
because he fell
into a vat of glaze?
That's crazy.
Crazy like a fox in a lab coat.
Because it's based on
something called science.
- (typing, beep)
- He's right, Roxie.
A hero accidentally
creating a nemesis
by causing them to
fall into something
is a well-known villain
trope going back to the '50s.
Name one example where someone
literally created a nemesis
- by knocking them into something.
- Keiko: Got it.
"Top 10 times where someone
literally created a nemesis
by knocking them
into something."
Ugh, the internet's the worst.
Behemoth fell into a volcano,
the Cosmetologist fell
into a tub of mascara,
Leopardman fell into a cage of
baby leopards, and... Ooh! Look!
This one has a video link.
(baby leopards growling,
snarling cutely)
All: Aw!
Chum, you worked with Mr. Donut.
What's your impression?
Oh, he was a great boss.
Although, he did demand
100% from his workers.
Sounds like a villain to me.
Also sounds like every
boss at every job ever.
Gotta side with them, Roxie.
This guy's hitting
all the signposts
that lead to major villainy.
Which is why I'm
going to do something
no hero has done before.
Stop a villain before
they even become one.
Chum! You and I are going
to check in on Mr. Donut
and see if can get
back on his good side
before it turns into a bad side.
He's overreacting.
People don't just switch
from good to bad. Ooh!
What do you say you and I
launch our own investigation?
Hold on. You want me to
do real detective work?
Think you're up for it?
Up? I'm on the dang
roof! But wait.
What if I'm right about
Mr. Donut being bad,
and you're wrong
about him being good?
A real detective uncovers the
truth no matter where it leads.
But let's say loser
buys the winner donuts!
My glucose is rising already.
(grunts)
I sure appreciate you and Chum
stopping by to repair the place.
It's the least we could do.
So now, there's absolutely
no reason to turn evil ever.
- What?
- I said, "Look at that!"
- Better than ever.
- Uh, not exactly, Sir.
Can't get the heating element
to work on the glaze vat,
and it's gonna take about
a week to get the parts.
A week? How am I
gonna make the donuts?
Fear not. I have
just the solution.
- Brainbot, fetch me the laser gauntlet.
- (brainbot whirring)
♪♪
Now, just point your
hand at the vat and fire.
(whirring, zap)
Whoa! What do you
know? It's working.
I tell ya, I don't know
how to thank you guys.
Well, you can thank us
by just staying the
wonderful person you are
and not changing anything about
your personality and life goals.
There you have it,
citizens of Metro
(static) - I hate to
toot my own horn... Chum?
- Toot, toot!
- I mean, seriously,
how many heroes do you
know who've actually
stopped a villain
before they became one?
Sir, we're having a
little difficulty.
(static)
- It's all the glaze I fell into.
Not only is everything
sticking to me,
I still can't get
my costume off.
You probably just need
a little mega muscle.
- (upbeat music playing)
- (straining)
Get my back into it. (Groans)
- My front into it, too.
- Mr. Donut: Oh no.
I gotta be at the
bank in 10 minutes.
(grunts) Go to your appointment.
Chum and I will
fetch some tools,
and we'll get that off
you when we come back.
It's no big deal, and certainly
no reason to resort to villainy!
- Whoa!
- Who's blue, has two thumbs, and stops criminals
before they even know
they're evil? This guy!
I've never seen such an
orderly conspiracy board.
That's because I've been looking
into Mr. Donut's background,
and it's spotless!
He doesn't have an evil bone
in his donut-shaped body.
Not so fast, fellow detective.
- Think you might have missed something.
- Reporter: Breaking news.
We're live as a
donut-shaped villain
is robbing Metro City Bank.
How could he turn evil? I
gave him a laser gauntlet!
Why would you give a man
you thought could turn evil
a gauntlet that shoots lasers?
You know my hindsight is
questionable, Roxanne.
Thought I reached him in
time, but evil works fast.
Luckily, justice is fasterer.
- Let's go, Chum.
- (triumphant music playing)
I'm gonna tail them. If
you're taking donut orders,
- I'm a bear claws kinda gal!
- Oh!
(tense crescendo)
- (people yelling)
- (laser whirring)
♪♪
Okay, Mr. Donut.
Your days of villainy
have come to an end!
Oh, Megamind, am
I glad to see you!
The glove you gave
me keeps firing!
Also, things keep
stickin' to me!
So you're not robbing the place?
Of course not!
I came here for
my expansion loan,
- and when I went to hand over my forms...
- (whirs)
(citizens screaming)
Oh, there's still time.
He hasn't turned down
the path of evil.
Quick! Let's get it off him!
♪♪
- (struggling)
- (zapping, people screaming)
Watch out!
Everyone, remain calm!
Mr. Donut: Oh, sorry!
Ah! That hurts.
- (people screaming)
- A stethoscope-wielding villain
the media has dubbed
Dr. Glazer Donut
has taken over Metro City Bank.
This is shocking footage
taken as Megamind and Chum
engage the donut-shaped
physician fiend
- in hand-to-hand combat.
- (grunts)
- (siren wails, stops)
- Whoa!
Ugh! We just bought
that patrol car!
- (people screaming)
- Megamind: Almost got it!
(Chum, Megamind yelp)
Ah! (Groans)
Chum: Mr. Donut?
Sir! He's out cold!
Officer (on megaphone):
Come out with your hands up!
We have to get him out of here!
Quick, to the Invisible Car!
(beeping)
- (blast)
- (crowd screaming)
♪♪
We gotta hide Mr. Donut.
He'll want revenge for sure
if I accidentally get him framed
for a crime he didn't commit.
(straining)
(car revving, roaring)
Guys, wait!
(grunts) Huh?
"Opera, pay, mega"?
Oh, I found a clue! I'm
like a master detective.
Oh, wait. I have no idea
what these words mean.
But I do know where
he wrote them.
- (door creaks)
- Ah, here we are.
I once used this abandoned
life preserver warehouse
as a hideout while the
lair was getting fumigated.
You'll be safe here while
Chum and I clear things up.
(woozy) Okay, I got a
few quick questions.
Who am I, who are you,
and what's goin' on?
(gasps) Must've been
that bump on the head!
Okay, quick recap. I'm
Megamind. This is Ol' Chum.
Stay here and try not
to think about revenge
and world domination.
- Call if you need anything.
- (door slams)
Whoa. Feel like I need to rest.
Those life preservers look cozy.
- (intimidating music playing)
- (winches whining)
- (grunts)
- Well, what do we have here?
Someone trying to steal
our appropriately
nautical-themed villain hideout.
What?
Whoa! Guys! It's
Dr. Glazer Donut!
That who I am? A
doctor who's a donut?
We're the Go Fish Gang!
And we're huge fans.
We saw you rob the
Metro City Bank,
and it was brilliant!
I did? And it was?
And your whole getup!
A doctor who's also a
donut that shoots lasers?
- Just terrific!
- I shoot lasers?
(zap, blast)
Whoa! I guess I do.
Such a fresh, original
concept for a villain!
We're about to pull
off a job of our own.
And it would be an honor to have
Metro City's newest
bad guy with us.
Oh...!
- (picking lock)
- What's taking so long?
You're making us
look like amateurs
in front of Dr. Glazer Donut.
It's so much pressure
with him watching me work!
Hey, show us how it's
done, Dr. Glazer Donut.
- You mean you want me to...
- (zap)
- (blast)
- (dust settling)
That was absolutely my bad.
And your bad is
absolutely awesome.
(laughter)
Hey, you're really good at this.
Where'd you get
your start, anyway?
Uh, I seem to remember.
Megamind knocking me
into a vat of glaze?
Sounds like a classic
nemesis origin story to me.
That's fate telling you that
you were born to be a villain.
And when fate points
you in a direction...
You dive in 100%!
Exactly. A villain like you
could take over the world.
Taking over the world!
Yeah, I remember
wanting that, too!
Stick with us,
and we'll make all your
evil dreams come true.
(maniacal laughter)
Hey, Dr. Glazer Donut, let's
hear your maniacal laugh.
(maniacal laugh)
- (laughter building)
- (dramatic crescendo)
(stops laughing)
(overlapping accolades)
♪♪
He has amnesia?
- And you just left him there?!
- He's someplace safe.
He doesn't know that. He
doesn't know anything now!
Oh, the more I try
to help the man,
the more likely it seems
he's going to become
my greatest enemy.
Look, we can try and
do our best for others,
but ultimately, it's
up to each of us
to decide who we are
and what we wanna be.
And personally, I don't think
there's even a sprinkle of
evil in Mr. Donut's heart.
One sprinkle of evil,
courtesy of this blue buffoon.
Reporter (on video): This
just in, new villain sensation
Dr. Glazer Donut has robbed
the Metro City Pearl exchange
- with the Go Fish Gang.
- (nervous whimper)
- Gang: Dr. Glazer Donut! Dr. Glazer Donut!
- (Mr. Donut laughing)
(laughs)
Now, for our next crime,
we should do
something really big.
As an evil donut doctor,
my prognosis for Megamind
- is death by sugar-glazed villainy.
- (dramatic sting)
Hey, love your thinking, but
Megamind's a hard guy to trap.
Not if we get him to come to us.
You, sir, are an artist.
(dialing)
Hello, Megamind?
Mr. Donut! Have you
joined the Go Fish Gang?!
Of course not!
But they've taken me hostage.
They're using your old
warehouse as their hideout.
Is there no evil
originality anymore?
Just stay calm. We're
heading right over.
(quiet tense music playing)
(yelping)
Sorry. Thought you
were Dr. Glazer Donut.
I got your message.
What's this clue you
wanted to show me?
Take a look. You can
just make out the words
"opera," "pay," and "mega."
- The rest is torn.
- Oh! Oh!
I've always wanted to do this!
Find the pad he wrote this on.
♪♪
Here's a little trick I
picked up when I was a kid
and had a detective agency
with my stuffed animals.
Aw!
Operation Payback Megamind?
(gasps, sighs) Mr. Donut
does want revenge.
(clang) - We're here to
rescue you, Mr. Donut.
- Ah!
- Ah! Whoa!
(whirring)
Mr. Donut: Well, well, well.
Looks like we got a
walk-in appointment.
Hope you got full coverage.
Mr. Donut, how could you?
What would the donuts think?
Ah-ah! The name's
Dr. Glazer Donut.
And, unfortunately for you,
the prognosis is
- a sweet, sugary demise!
- (dramatic crescendo)
Bank robbery, faking amnesia.
It must all be a trick
to get Megamind to
lower his guard! (Sighs)
Guess I did help
create a villain.
- (gasps)
- We gotta hide!
(grunting, yelps)
(tense music
playing, crescendos)
(click)
- Attack!
- (both grunting)
Mayor Ritchie?
What are you doing here?
We could ask you the same thing.
This is my husband's store!
We just came in to
help him prepare
for Operation Payback Megamind.
- Ha! I knew it!
- (Roxanne yelps)
♪♪
Roxanne: Huh?
Keiko: "Thank you,
Megamind, you deserve it"?
Wait. Operation Payback is a
surprise party for Megamind.
For saving his life!
What else would it be?
I think Megamind might
have... accidentally
turned your husband
into a villain.
You mean my Melvin?
You might be the only one
who can get through to him.
Alright, Megamind. Time
to sleep with the fishes.
- (beep)
- (gasps)
Sharks, to be more precise.
(snarls)
And to officially welcome
Dr. Glazer Donut to the family,
- we're going to let him send you both to your doom.
- (laser whirs)
Mr. Donut: It's
time to end this.
We have been enemies
a long time, Megamind.
Actually, no, we
haven't! We were friends!
I do remember...
He's just trying to stall you!
Oldest hero trick in the book.
Mr. Donut, I know exactly
what you're going through.
My entire life came down
to one single decision.
What kind of person did
I really want to be?
Do you want to be the
reviled Dr. Glazer Donut,
or the beloved Mr. Donut?
- (whirring)
- (door opens)
Melvin? What's going on here?
- (laser whirs down)
- Claire?
This isn't you. You're
not Dr. Glazer Donut!
You didn't even go
to medical school!
Your name's Melvin
Feinberg. You make donuts,
and you're good at it!
You're a terrific husband,
a wonderful father,
and you're better than this.
She's right, Mr. Donut.
Your donut skills are
meant for good, not evil.
Oh, enough jibber-jabber.
- Blast him, Dr. Glazer Donut!
- (whirring)
(yelping)
The name is not
Dr. Glazer Donut.
- It's Mr. Donut!
- (Chum and Megamind yelp, grunt)
(groans) That could've been
more thought out on your part.
No one throws back
the Go Fish Gang.
- Ah!
- Stand aside, Mr. Donut.
- This is our job.
- No, no.
I helped create this mess
and I'm gonna help fix it.
100%.
That's my Melvin!
(grunts)
A master of pastry
arts, and brave.
(yelling)
(grunts)
Whoa!
Ha! Is that the best you got?
- (cracking)
- (yells)
- (grunts)
- (unspooling)
♪♪
Yo! Whoa!
Looks like I landed a big one!
(screaming)
Help!
(yelps)
Looks like I'm the
one who got away!
Do-nut leave now.
I got a baker's dozen
reasons you should stay!
(grunting, groaning)
- Cool!
- Yeah, you did it, Dad!
Hey, my little munchkins!
Guess we caught the "hole" gang.
You know, like donut
holes! (Laughs)
I stepped on the nice
moment, didn't I?
According to Megamind,
Mr. Donut was working undercover
to help him nab the
notorious Go Fish Gang.
- Job well done to Metro City's newest and unlikeliest hero.
- (siren wailing)
Another tray for my
favorite customers.
(sighs) Great to see Mr. Donut
back and better than ever.
And not only that,
I figured out a way to spend
more time with the family.
Here you go.
- There's nothing better than free labor.
- (kicks)
And family togetherness.
I think maybe there's also
a lesson to be learned
- from all of this.
- That reminds me!
I just want to
say to all my fans
that I think Mayor Ritchi
has learned a valuable lesson
about assuming the
worst in people.
Hey! I was on his side.
For a majority of the time.
The important truth is
the kind of person we are
comes down to the
decisions we make.
For example, right now,
I'm regretting the decision
to eat 20 donuts.
Come on, big guy.
What's one more bite?
How could I ever disappoint you,
my little delicious
blue friends? (Chomp)
♪♪