(neon buzzing)
- (line straining)
- (grunting)
- Huh?
- Hello.
(screams)
(theme song playing)
♪ Supervillain,
ahead of his time ♪
♪ Incredibly handsome
genius, criminal mastermind ♪
♪ But now he's all cleaned
up and fighting crime ♪
♪ A superhero that
you stream online ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it feels good
to be good this time ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it's Megamind ♪
♪ Rules! ♪
(whirring)
- (screaming, grunts)
- (zapping)
- (groaning)
- Lady Doppler: Always a pleasure
making a fool outta
you, Megamind.
And thanks for the isotopes.
You mean these isotopes?
Who's the fool now?
- (laughs)
- (whirs)
Pierre: It would appear
you are Monsieur Fool!
- (laughing)
- (Megamind groans)
- (Megamind panting)
- (clang)
- (groans)
- (clicking, whirring)
Time to spin this in my favor.
(zap)
(yelps)
(woozy grunting)
Looks like someone skipped
a well-balanced breakfast.
- (whoosh)
- (grunts)
I just have coffee. Dark blend.
(maniacal laugh)
Come on, Megamind. You got this.
Okay, I don't got this!
Nighty-Knight: Around
and around you go!
Oh, wait. I got it!
Ah! My eyes!
(yelling, grunts)
Ah!
Don't fall asleep on the job!
Megamind: Know this.
I will not rest until
I get those isotopes!
But first, maybe
a quick power nap.
(snores)
As per your ordinance,
we have slept (clears throat)
swept this city clean.
- And the isotopes?
- That I lost,
mostly because we were sweeping,
but I will not rest until
I've recovered them,
- Roberta.
- Roxie.
I'm Megamind. You're
Roxie, Roberta.
- Uh, is his brain broken?
- How would we tell?
(snoring, grunts)
You've been chasing
villains all night.
You should go to bed.
Hopefully a right-side-up one.
Heroes don't rest.
Now, I really have to
get back to the lair.
Keiko: Um, this is
your lair, buddy.
Ah, yes, of course.
Thank you, Chum.
(snoring) - If Megamind
doesn't get some rest,
he's gonna have a
complete Mega-meltdown.
And those are never
pretty. But not to worry.
I'll have him shipshape
on the good ship Shipshape
- in no time. (Laughs)
- I know you will, Chum.
- (groans)
- He really needs some rest.
Ma'am, you have a full day
of wall-to-wall meetings.
Keiko, Chum, this has been
a confusing waste of time,
per usual.
Well, you and I should
be able to handle things
while Megamind rests
and recuperates.
I've got his beloved
binky right here.
First of all, he uses a binky?
Like a little baby?
Don't tell him I told you.
But, yes, it does
help him relax.
That's a fun fact our followers
don't need to know about.
Anyway, it's a school day, bro.
I'm only here for
the toaster pastries.
Oh, but he's in pretty
bad shape, Keiko.
I don't know if I can
take care of him alone.
(groans, snores)
I'll come back right
when school is out
and give you a
hand. But, come on.
You're Chum. You've got this.
- (musical beeping)
- (gasps)
Izzy Iggy, lead
singer of Facemelter,
is doing a show in town!
Sir's gonna want
tickets for sure.
- (click)
- (rock drum beat playing)
I love this song!
♪ Put your hands up
high, grab the air ♪
♪ Clap your hands, like
you just don't care ♪
♪ Stomp your feet on
the cement floor ♪
♪ Do the robot now, open... ♪
- (turns off music)
- Chum,
I cannot let myself
be distracted
by the smooth sounds and
velvety voice of Izzy Iggy!
There's work to do!
(snores) - Sir, you
should be in bed relaxing.
Here, take your binky.
Oh, I don't need to relax,
and I don't need my binky.
What I need is to
create a simulation
of every possible move the
Doom Syndicate could make!
This will keep me a good
six to seven steps ahead.
- Okay...
- But not only that, I need to create a simulation
of every possible move the
Doom Syndicate could make.
This will keep me a good
six to seven steps ahead.
Ooh! A butterfly!
How did you even get in here,
you silly little bug fairy, you?
(sighs) He may not know
it, but this Izzy Iggy show
is exactly what Sir needs
to recharge his batteries.
"Remaining Izzy tickets only
available at the box office."
Huh...
He'd probably be fine by himself
if I stepped out
for just a second.
(wheezing laugh)
Although I don't agree
with your politics,
that is too funny, Butterfly.
Or maybe not.
How can I get those
tickets and care for Sir?
Oh, I could really use an
assistant of my own today.
Huh...
Alright, cloning machine.
Let's make another
me to watch Sir
- while I grab those tickets!
- (beep)
- Just need a little DNA.
- (whirring)
♪♪
(gargling)
Sir could use a little
more attention than usual,
so I'll adjust the
new me just a skosh.
I'm already smart enough,
so let's trade some
intelligence for persistence.
(zapping, whirring)
(exciting music playing)
(electricity fizzling)
Oh, very handsome!
I shall call you Chum Two.
Must be because I'm too
ready to serve, Sir!
(laughs)
Well, I'm glad I didn't
skimp on my witty repartee.
(snores)
- (thump)
- Ah! Stop hitting me!
Okay then. Try to
get him to rest
while I'm off on my
errand to help him,
you know, rest.
Oh!
Uh, in case it rains
on your journey.
- Well, thank you!
- And here's your lunch.
Oh, I should be back in a jiff.
Ah-ah! No one's ever been
sorry they brought a lunch.
I never thought of it that way.
Or actually, I suppose I did.
(laughs)
I can't say why,
but what I'm seeing makes me
believe the Doom Syndicate
is building a giant
radioactive banana.
Diabolical! Hey!
What the?!
No rest is for the wicked, Sir.
And you are not wicked. Anymore.
- Here we go. And...
- (chair creaking)
What are you... It
doesn't recline!
- Not with that attitude.
- (snaps)
Whoa! (Grunting)
Explain yourself, Chum!
Chum Two: Oh, my apologies, Sir.
Allow me to relax you.
(muffled yelling)
(spits)
- Would you please go away?!
- (sighs)
I'm letting Sir down.
Not Sir would be
so disappointed.
How do I make up for
two disappointments
when there's just one me?
- (curious music playing)
- Huh.
- (line chatter)
- Clerk: Next.
Good day, employed citizen.
I would like to purchase
two tickets to the
Izzy Iggy show, please.
It's a lottery.
Is that like, "It's a vibe"?
Clerk: No. It means
I give you a number,
and then we'll randomly
call out numbers,
and those people
will get a chance
to buy the two
remaining tickets.
14? My lucky number!
That's the age I was when Sir
first said "thank you" to me.
Congratulations.
Wait over there.
And next!
♪♪
Tuna? I hate tuna.
- Other me should know that.
- (dialing)
Lair of Megamind!
This is Chum Two.
I just wanted to check in.
You gave me tuna,
which I do not eat,
and I was worried that
adjusting your personality
- might have been...
- Chum Two: Please hold!
Wait, wait, wait! Don't
put the hold music on!
(rock drumbeat playing)
♪ Put your hands up
high, grab the air ♪
♪ Clap your hands, like
you just don't care ♪
- Whoa!
- S-Sorry!
I-I can't help but follow
instructional song lyrics.
(nervous laugh)
- (grunts)
- Christina Christo!
(sighs) Chunk, right?
Chum, actually.
I'm just here getting
Izzy tickets for Megamind.
Well, Roxie asked me
to get two tickets
for her and Megamind.
She said she wanted
him to relax.
At a metal show? So weird.
Well, since I'm already
getting tickets for him,
you should probably call Roxie
and tell her Chum is on it.
I'd call myself, but I'm
on hold with... myself.
No, no, no. When she asks
me to do something, I do it.
That's why I'm the best.
I would never leave
anything in the hands of,
- well, you.
- I have never let Sir down,
so I kind of feel like
I can handle this.
Driver: Nice moves, weirdo!
Thank you! Can't resist
instructional songs!
(sighs) I'm obviously too
flawed to keep Sir relaxed,
- but that can be fixed.
- (beeping)
One perfectionist
Chum coming up!
(zapping)
♪♪
(sighs) Perfect!
(beeping) - I'm writing an
extremely complicated code
that should ensure the
Doom Syndicate never again,
um...
(sighs) I forget
what, but trust me!
It's gonna be the hottest thing
since sliced beds.
- Much too close to the screen, Sir.
- Ah!
You'll damage your eyes.
Oh, and look at this
unkempt workspace.
(beeping)
My code!
That was really
complicated and important!
I think.
Killing germs is important, Sir.
I have no use for a clean freak.
I need someone who is
passionate about stopping crime.
Passion, you say?
I can do that, Sir!
- Oh, 'scuse me.
- (whirring)
(beeping)
(electricity fizzling)
Let's do this!
(gasps) What is this?
A crime simulation?!
Um, yes.
If I can cut the Syndicate
off here, they'll be trapped.
Yes! I'm on the edge of my seat!
- The tension is electrifying.
- (triumphant sting)
Right...
And so, if we
defeat them here...
We'll be heroes!
Yes...
But if I don't make
it here in time...
The world may end! No, no, no!
- (screaming)
- (smashing)
What are you doing?!
These markers
represent human beings!
How could you be so insensitive?
More sensitivity. Got it, Sir.
(whirring, beeping)
(zap)
(Chum clone whimpering)
What's the matter now?
I tried to make you toast,
but I hurt the toast instead!
- (sobbing)
- Uh...
- There, there.
- (wailing)
The toaster was just on
the wrong calibration.
It could be fixed.
You should be happy, dear Chum.
Happy? Okay, Sir.
- Calibration?
- (whirring, zap)
Is my de-gun
properly calibrated?
Oh! The de-gun!
Are we gonna use
it to stop crime?
That would be so fun!
Okay...
When do we fight bad guys,
and how much fun will
that be? Scale of 1 to 10?
You know what you should do?
You should work on the, um,
- Invisible Car!
- Oh, yes! Yes!
(laughs) It's the best day ever!
How am I supposed to work
with all this insanity?
I think Chum might need a nap.
What do you guys think?
Chums: We think you
could use a nap.
Why am I hearing
more than one...
Chums?
Chums: Hello!
- What is going on here?!
- (dramatic crescendo)
Ha! You, a better
assistant than moi?
For the 10th time,
I'm not an assistant.
I'm her chief of staff.
Then why are you fetching
concert tickets? Hmm?
Okay, fine. I sometimes
do assistanty things,
but when I do, I am far better
than you could even dream.
I can assist circles around you!
In fact, watch as I use
my superior assisting
to ensure I win this lottery.
Excuse me, good sir.
May I interest you in
my assisting services
in exchange for
your lottery number?
Well, I was supposed to
buy iguana food today...
♪♪
Chum: Here you are, sir!
That was impressive! (Laughs)
Deal's a deal.
Looks like the
superior assistant
just doubled his chances
of getting the
tickets for his boss.
You best not think
you can best me.
I can do better than best you.
Well, then. Time for a good
old-fashioned assist-off.
(yawns) - Half-caff,
light cream, two sugars,
stirred twice, and
hot, but not too hot.
Amazing! Now, I can
work on my essay.
- (yelps)
- Speaking of which,
a complete history
of Pompeii! And look.
Graphs.
- (dogs barking)
- (gasping) Here you go.
Tiger did his business,
Spuds tired herself out,
and Dino sniffed out a fire.
- Thank you. Whoa, whoa!
- (dogs barking)
♪♪
(brushing)
- And spit, please, sir.
- (spits)
Tooth brushing! Will
wonders never cease?
I know what will turn that
blue frown upside down!
- Tickle fight!
- (laughing)
I love that idea so much,
I'm going to marry it!
With Sir's blessing, of course.
(sobbing) Idea weddings
always make me cry!
Sir, if we have the
ceremony here at the lair,
it's a tax write-off!
(Chums chattering)
Hey, I'm back! Just
like I promised... Whoa!
Chums: Keiko, everything
is under control!
Keiko! I just realized
what's going on here!
I'm dreaming!
- I'm very sure you're not dreaming.
- (mystical music playing)
And since we're
positive I'm dreaming,
I can do whatever I want!
Whee!
I never felt so free!
- (whooping)
- Lemme make a wild guess here.
Chum made a clone
because he needed help,
and that clone made more clones.
And now, Megamind has
no concept of reality
because he's having a
complete Mega-meltdown!
No!
Well, actually, yes.
(alarm blaring)
(news music playing)
Anchor (on TV): Things are
growing dangerous downtown
- as a now 40-foot Behemoth rampages through Metr...
- (static)
Oh, this dream is
only getting better!
I get to battle a
40-foot Behemoth
with my unlimited dream powers!
To the Invisible Car!
- Chums: Coming, Sir!
- You four stay here.
I'm gonna be his dream sherpa
and make sure he stays safe
and doesn't try anything stupid.
I'm gonna destroy Behemoth
with electric beams
from my eyeballs!
Dream power!
- You will never stop us from assisting our Sir!
- (yelps)
(grunts)
- (Chums yell)
- (crashing)
- (rumbling)
- (straining)
- (grunts)
- (clang)
That'll do.
Ah! Tell me you're normal Chum!
I just wanted to say
tweedle-dee dinglee-deedledee!
Because it's so fun to say
when you're happy like me!
(laughing) Yeah!
Oh, definitely not normal Chum.
Listen up. This is my dream,
and I want to make
fighting Behemoth
be as fun as a dream
can make possible!
I know what's fun! We'll get
the new improved Invisible Car
and sneak up on Behemoth!
It'll be like a surprise party!
I don't think that's a...
Wait, that's actually
not a bad idea.
- And... voilàà!
- (car whirring)
(electric guitar riff)
This is perfect!
This is a disaster.
Okay, real talk.
You're heading to
battle with Behemoth,
and you do not have
magic dream powers!
Oh, you're way more fun
in real life, Keiko.
I'm flying in my dream!
- Whee!
- (engine roars)
- Oh no!
- (Behemoth roars)
- Make the car invisible.
- Aw, but I wanna see
if we can make Behemoth
smile at its pretty colors!
We can stop it with the
dream power of happiness!
- No!
- Yes, we can.
(honking)
- (roars) Ooh.
- (smash)
Pretty car.
(stomping) -Aw, it
worked! We made him smile.
Behemoth smash pretty car!
- (roars)
- (screaming)
Megamind: I never felt
nauseous in a dream before!
- (laughs)
- It's not a dream!
Don't worry, bummer dream Keiko.
My electro-vision
will blast Behemoth!
(aggressive humming)
Oh, please end well.
Please end well.
(banging) - Chum clone:
Sir! Let us help you!
I will rescue you!
Strike me down! Sir is
out there in danger!
And he doesn't even
have his binky!
(gasps) The perfect
plan to help Sir.
I know it will come to us if
we just put our heads together!
Put our heads
together... (gasps)
What if we use the
cloning machine
to combine our molecules,
lower all our attributes,
and maximize strength,
making one gigantic us!
- (clang)
- (whirring, zapping)
- (smash)
- (stomping)
I'm coming, Sir!
(dramatic crescendo)
(muffled stomping)
- Hi, Roxanne!
- Hi, Chum.
- Take that! And that! (Grunting)
- (Behemoth laughs)
- Who tickle Behemoth?
- (clang)
Megamind? (Growls)
Huh?
I'll save you, Sir!
(gasps, panting)
- Whoa!
- (air whistling)
- (stomp)
- A great big Chum! Keiko!
Isn't this the most
wonderful dream?!
You know what? I'm gonna
give in to the crazy.
- This kicks butt!
- You just relax, Sir.
I'll handle this.
- (yells)
- (Behemoth grunts)
- (smash)
- (grunts)
Everything's giant
monsters these days.
Where's the remote? (Grunts)
- (rumbling)
- (Behemoth roars)
- (smashing)
- (screaming)
Shh! Sir is trying to nap!
(both yell)
(smash)
(muffled struggling)
Ha! He did it! Megamind did it!
Megamind: Yes. Thank
you. You're all welcome.
He destroyed the streets again!
I can't get to work!
Even in my dream,
when I win, I lose.
This city will be
the death of me.
(sucking)
This city will be
the death of him?
I have to act fast. I must
(smash) destroy the city
before it destroys Sir!
- Whoa! Ho!
- (clatters)
- (muffled destruction)
- (muffled crowd screaming)
- (muffled roar)
- (muffled stomping)
- Huh?
- (dramatic crescendo)
Hm.
I'd be happy to help
anyone with anything!
I'll do twice her anything
- and be three times as happy about it!
- (grunting)
Clerk: And the
final number is...
♪♪
- 14.
- (gasps) That's me. I win!
I'm the best
assistant in the city!
Ha, ha! Yes! Told
you! In your face!
- (smash)
- Huh?
- (people screaming)
- (grunting)
- (stomp)
- (gasps)
I think Megamind might need
some top-notch assisting
right about now. You
take the tickets.
If I'm gonna lose, at least
it's to another assistant
and a really good one.
- (panting)
- (dramatic crescendo)
(sleepy groaning) - Oh, my. Looks
like my plan went a little haywire.
He's finally resting, so
you kind of did your job.
- (snoring)
- Sir...
- It's time to wake up, Sir.
- Oh, Chum.
- (relaxing music playing)
- I had the craziest dream ever.
There were so many yous,
but not in a good way.
- Then, a giant you wrestled a mountain in the street.
- (smash, people screaming)
Actually, it was real,
Sir. It all happened.
We're too late!
Until the city is flattened,
I don't think this MegaChum will
follow a single instruction!
That's a great idea, Sir!
There's one kind of
instruction no Chum can resist!
- (crowd screaming)
- MegaChum: Sorry!
Apologies, everyone.
Nothing personal.
Just have to destroy
everything real quick
before you become
the death of my Sir.
(heavy metal song playing)
What is that?
(song blasting on radio)
♪ Raise your hands
like a crazy mutt ♪
♪ Be mellow, don't
crush Mr. Donut ♪
- It's working, Chum! Keep going!
- Got it!
♪ Gently place the
cars on the ground ♪
♪ Don't scare the
people and turn around ♪
♪♪
♪ Run away with a
nice smooth motion ♪
♪ Make a bee-line for
the deep blue ocean ♪
Instruction songs?
The funnest songs in
the whole fun-a-verse!
♪ Wade in slow so
you do not drown ♪
♪ Bend those knees
and sit on down ♪
♪ Now dunk that head
with no concern ♪
♪ And swim away and
don't you return ♪
(song ends)
You know, this old man guitar
music's starting to grow on me.
Chum! (Panting)
- I think you should have these.
- Really?
You put our dumb
competition aside
to do some phenomenal assisting.
- And you saved the city.
- (snoring)
Oh, Sir will be so
touched that you...
I didn't do it for him.
Us assistants have
to stick together.
(heartfelt music playing)
(clink)
Megamind: You did
a great job, Chum.
I'm quite proud. But remember.
One Chum has always
been enough for me.
Um, Sir?
(groggy): That's my
little fish monkey.
(kiss, laugh)
Operation Mega Meltdown
was only a partial success.
We've got the hairbrush,
but the binky's not here.
Machiavillain (on phone):
(sighs) I would need a crayon
to put this into simpler terms.
The binky is the key
to my entire plan.
(sighs) It's so hard to
find quality assistants.
But, I guess if you want
something done right,
you have to get someone
else to do it yourself!
(maniacal laugh)
(Izzy Iggy singing)
♪♪
♪ Not to repeat myself ♪
♪ But free will is a lie ♪
♪ Free will is a lie... ♪
Huh!