- Huh?
- Hello.
♪ Supervillain,
ahead of his time ♪
♪ Incredibly handsome
genius, criminal mastermind ♪
♪ But now he's all cleaned
up and fighting crime ♪
♪ A superhero that
you stream online ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it feels good
to be good this time ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it's Megamind ♪
♪ Rules! ♪
Megamind: You've met
your match, evildoer.
For I, Megamind,
am the hero of Metrocity!
And you will feel my
steely justice
with the force of a
an angry llama!
Ol' Chum: Oh, nonsense. I
think you're improving, sir!
That's way better than attacking
their mothers personally!
I'm clueless, Chum!
Now that I'm a hero, I
want to inspire the people
the way Metro Man did!
Being a villain and
stoking fear is a breeze,
but how do I conjure
awe and eyes-agogginess?
Do I need to exercise?
- What about flossing?
Sir, robbery in progress
at Everything City!
Ha-ha! Move over, bad
breath and sensitive gums!
There's crime to be stopped!
Let's go! Hurry it up!
This isn't Some Of It City.
- Fork over everything!
Villain, beware! For I
am the white knight of...
Dude Monkey: Bananalamadingdong!
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Woo! Yeah!
Hey, Dude Monkerinos!
Your happy hometown
Dude Monkey here.
Shall we schtop another crime?
What is that thing?
- Hyah!
- What?!
Let's can this tuna fish!
- Oh, my!
Did I do it again?
I schtopped a crime!
- Say, Bananalamadingdong!
Post that on your sosh
and you'll get
beaucoup engagements!
- Thanks!
- What? Megamind?
Oh, must have beat
him to the scene.
Sorry, Mr. Atric.
Hey, can I call
you Geri?
JK, bro! I'm Dude Monkey!
Say 'sup to my Dude Monkerinos!
- 'Sup?
- Remember to like and subscribe
if you think the city
needs a fresher fighter
than this horse-and-buggy
bagpipe head!
Bananalamadingdong!
What in Hades'
hamper just happened?
What just happened was awesome!
You've been a hero
just a short time,
and already, you're influencing
strangely charismatic youngsters
to defend the city!
Perhaps I'm more
inspiring than I thought.
As mayor, I don't
have actual control
over the sun.
Yes, well, I have a
lot on my plate today,
but I promise to absolutely
look into it, Senator.
- Huh?
- Ollo... Ow!
Whoa!
My brilliant blue noggin!
You know, you're not
a villain anymore.
You can use the front door.
But a monitor? Really, Roxanne?
Sorry. Muscle
memory. I'm a little on edge.
Just found out the Doom
Syndicate escaped from prison.
They escaped already?
I must say, the former
villain part of me is proud.
But the hero part of me
is incredibly frustrated
- with our prison system!
You'd think they'd lay low,
but I guess Nighty-Knight
couldn't resist Taquito Tuesday
at Dos Muchachos Picante.
Can't blame him. Their
tacos are delightful,
but if he pops his
Halloween head up again,
I have just the
treat for his tricks!
Hey, can I ask another favor?
Ma'am, do not offer
Megamind the aquarium gig!
Well, well, if it isn't
Christina Christo,
the Secretary of Party Pooping.
It's Chief of Staff, actually.
My job is to make sure
Roxanne can get reelected.
Something you don't
seem to care about.
What's this gig she
doesn't want me to have?
So they're having a grand
re-opening of the aquarium
and want me to
make an appearance?
To warn baddies
against another attempt
at the diamond-encrusted
koi fish, no doubt.
It says "hero," not
live-action blueberry.
- Ha!
- Gimme that!
I'm looking for ways
to be more inspirational,
and nothing inspires citizenry
like a bombastic speech
- at a relaxing, fish-filled...
- Ah!
- Got it! Ma'am,
he's the one who destroyed the
aquarium in the first place.
If you want to save a fish, you
gotta break a few aquariums.
- That's mine!
- Give it to me!
- Megamind: Gimme!
Great. You both owe
a tree an apology.
Christina, we've
got to use Megamind.
He's Metro City's
best and only hero.
Not anymore. There is
a new hero in town,
and his name is Dude Monkey.
The petty crime stopper who
was totally inspired by moi?
Why hire a second-rate wannabe
when you can have a
first-rate is-a-be?
Roxanne: He makes a
good point. Christina,
send word to the aquarium board
that I'm recommending Megamind.
Fine.
Nee-nuh nee-nuh nee-nuh!
- Roxanne: Kids,
no ice cream unless
you stop fighting.
Both: I will when you
admit I'm the favorite.
Jinx. Double jinx. Triple jinx!
Enough! Go play outside.
Mama's gotta work.
- What about that icèd cream you promised?
- Megamind: Wanna look my best for the aquarium gig.
Time to get my blue bod ripped
with some hardcore
physical fitness.
Chum! A little help!
Faster, Chum. I
wanna feel that burn.
You got a big problem, Double M.
I know. Chum is
horrifically out of shape.
Your problem is Dude Monkey.
Shall we schtop another crime?
- Ooh! A video! Can I watch?
That chimp chump is no
threat. He looks up to me.
He's proof that my aim to
inspire Metrocity is working.
Good luck inspiring people
when this guy's trolling you.
What's with
this troll business?
They've been
extinct for decades.
Trolling means he's trying
to humiliate you online.
- Sorry, Mr. Atric.
Hey, can I call
you Geri?
JK, bro!
Geriatric means old.
We don't want this
guy to take your place
as defender of Metro City by
defining you as out of touch.
This video has a
quarter million views!
It must have aired on
the 6 o'clock news.
Oh, you're serious?
Uh, I-I'm actually
gonna ask this.
Have you ever heard
of the internet?
Yes, I've heard
of the "onternet."
I'm just not onterested.
It's a passing fad, like fidget
spinners or paying your taxes.
Okay, well, in that case,
welcome to the Information Age.
- You're about 30 years late.
This is a television.
- True!
- Wasn't a question.
But was I right?
Can I get a point?
- Sure.
- One to zip.
Back in the age when people
used to live in caves,
this is how they'd
get their news.
True! Ha-ha, all tied up.
But the internet connects to
every computer on the planet.
- You guys know that, right?
- No, we do not.
But I do know I'm right
about us not knowing,
so another point for Chum.
Keiko: Not something
to be proud of.
So, with the Internet
and social media,
you can put out a story
and send it anywhere
and to everyone instantly!
They call this going viral.
I went viral on Metrocity once.
Gave everyone dance fever.
I should get 10 retroactive
points for that, honestly.
- Fine.
- What, does that mean I win?
Sure. You're the grand champion
of learning about the
internet way too late!
- Yes!
- No!
Now, listen. Dude
Monkey is engaging
in a social media showdown that
you're losing by not showing up!
He's telling a
huge-gantic audience
that you're a ding-dong so
he can steal all your fans!
- That settles it, Keiko.
Make me virulent
on the onternet.
I'm looking at this
internet thing,
and it's hilarious! Look!
This cartoon baby is dancing
just like a grown-up!
That meme is older
than my teacher,
and she knits.
: Ollo,
fans. I am here,
talking into the camera
as if I were talking
to you in person.
Thanks to the magic
of the onternet.
Maybe need a catchphrase.
Something like,
"Villains are red,
heroes are blue.
Stop robbing that bank,
or feel my kung fu!"
Or, you know, I'll think
of something later.
Sir! Have you seen
this unusual fellow
- who sings about rain made of...
- Chum!
- Okay, Chum,
you gotta stop watching
old Internet stuff
while we're filming.
And Megamind, be
more natural, dude.
You're moving your arms
like a floppy inflatable
- at a used car lot.
- Keiko,
I'm unfamiliar with
the glare of a lens.
I'm more of a live
performance guy.
You know, theater!
Treading the boards!
Well, I'm certainly bored,
but this is for a web channel,
not Shakespeare in the Park.
- Just move your arms normal.
- So, more like...
Hello, my biggest
fans! Megamind here.
Perfect! We'll go with
that. Roll camera.
: Hello,
my biggest fans!
Your little fannies
will shake as you worship
the splendor that is...
Keiko: You're doing the arm thing
again and saying weird stuff.
: Ugh! I don't know
what you want from me, Keiko!
Actually, maybe just
do something heroic.
Heroic opportunities don't just
walk out into the street and
Or sometimes they do.
DeGravity should do.
Ha-ha! Um, citizen?
What are you watching that
had you so distracted?
Dude Monkey.
- Whoa! You watchin' my vids, bud?
- What the?!
Oh, wow! It's
really Dude Monkey!
You're such an inspiration.
Can I get a selfie?
How about a self-photograph
with the hero who,
- you know, saved your life?
- Nah, I'm good.
- Say, "Megamind's cheugy!"
Say, "Megamind's cheugy!"
Keiko: I'll just
edit that stuff out.
- We will beat Dude Monkey
to an onternet pulp
with this video, right?
This rescue was awesome!
Once people see this, they're
gonna be all, "Who-Monkey"?
- We're just gonna upload and wait.
Ooh! I got a view!
- That was from you watching it.
Be patient. Your
fans will find you.
I gotta head home.
My mom's super strict
- about my 9 p.m. curfew.
- Another view!
- Keiko: Also from you!
Oh...
- Come on, come on...
- A new meme!
- Ah! How many views?
Oh. False alarm.
It's just an old
one with new words.
Only 100 views?
Why haven't I
become a virus yet?
I know it hasn't
exploded overnight,
but you need to be patient.
We need to build
something unique to you.
The video where that monkey
man does the troll to me.
- How many does that have?
- A couple more.
- Yeah, a million more.
It's as if I don't exist!
I'm far from
inspirational. I've become
unpopular.
- Your fans will find you. We just need...
- Thank you, Keiko,
but I know how to handle this.
Chum, we've got a
"Class Me" emergency.
The only thing that will
get me out of this spiral
is a whiz-bang appearance
at a fish museum!
The kids will love it!
Yeah, my heart's racing already.
You know, I have some great
ideas for this aquarium gig.
- Hyah! Woo!
- Ow!
Really wanna see your face
when she tells you this.
Go ahead, ma'am.
The aquarium board is
made up of people
with terrible taste
who are kind of leaning
toward Dude Monkey.
No! Any dude or any monkey,
but not him!
You gotta see his
latest, though!
Dude Monkey: Dude Monkey
stops crime with a meat-sicle!
Hey! My wallet!
'Sup, Dude Monkerinos!
Pretty much gonna declare myself
Metro City's greatest hero.
Crime is poppin', but Megamind
is
a-prune juice shoppin'!
- Thanks, Dude Monkey!
- I schtopped a crime!
Hey, quick, shout out
to my primo sponsor,
Mr. Minion's Meat-sicles,
the official meat-sicle
of Dude Monkey.
Yumalamadingdong!
I can't believe
he has a sponsor!
- Why don't I have a sponsor?
- You got me.
I think a wart removal cream
would be blessed to have you.
Hilarious, Christina.
Hey, that guy is charismatic,
but he's no Megamind.
I'll keep fighting for you.
I'll make it easy. If Dude
Monkey's catching fire,
I'm gonna become a
crime-stopping megaton bomb!
That's a metaphor for having
an engaging web channel,
not a threat.
Ma'am, they've
spotted Nighty-Knight!
That aquarium board
will change their mind
when I bring
Nighty-Knight to justice
and knock Dude
Monkey's web channel
on its weird monkey butt!
I've been studying what
makes Dude Monkey so popular.
If this is the hero
Metrocity wants me to be,
then so shall I be it!
- Hey, radical duderoos.
Megamind here. Crimes a-poppin'!
- Dang.
- Help! Help!
Scope that! Crime
much, am I right?
You'll L-O-L as I
trick-shot these handcuffs
right on Nighty-Knight's wrists.
- Hey! That's my fishbowl!
- Hm.
- Oh, I think you just missed his wrist, sir.
By which I mean entirely.
- We gonna let him steal meat-sicle carts?
Nah. Crime stopping rocks!
- Ow!
- Crime-a-Doodle-Don't!
Hizzle, cowpokes.
Just call me Dead-Eye Blue
because when I take
my shot at baddies,
I never miss.
Backslash rad!
- Guard: He's got the blueprints!
Ha-ha! Well, howdy,
Nighty-Knight!
- Ah!
- Ah! Chum!
It's like all-new memes,
but with that special
homemade flavor!
Keiko! I demand you
burn all copies.
I should come off
as inspirational,
not as some bumbling buffoon.
Come on! It's funny stuff!
Your fans are gonna see this
and mash that subscribe
button so hard,
you could serve it with gravy.
Keiko, I'm
repositioning you.
I'll be taking over
advising myself,
and you'll organize
my jazz albums.
But you don't have
any jazz albums, sir.
Then this should
be easy for her.
But you don't even know how
to post or log on or stream!
- Jazz albums!
Imagine her telling me I
don't know what I'm doing.
Now, to get rid of these videos.
- Gonna upload them right into the trash.
Hasta la vista, videos!
Sir, I think you may
need to see this.
Dude Monkey : Yo, yo,
yo, yo, yo, Dude Monkerinos!
Just got a call from
the mayor's office.
I've been requested to
appear at the grand reopening
of the aquarium!
And you know what?
I beat Megamind for the gig!
Now I'm gonna dance all over
this picture of Megamind
until a-millio eyeballs
are on this stream!
Bananalamadingdong!
He's still dancing
after two hours.
Incredible.
I need a 30-minute nap after
eating three chicken wings.
- Well, well, well.
On my way to the hospital.
My back is lousy
with stab wounds.
I'm truly sorry about
the Dude Monkey thing.
It was out of my hands.
What fun is having
my friend as mayor
if I don't get
everything I want?
I was elected to be
the mayor of the city,
not just my friends.
And the city wants Dude Monkey,
which I agree is
dumb.
Dumb-ocracy. Am I right?
You can't unspoil my sour mood
with mayoral dad jokes, Roxie.
- Christina: Mm! Mm!
Hey, come on!
Bananalamadingdong.
I possess super intelligence,
otherworldly handsomeness,
and selfless humility.
Yet, I am felled by
a bananalamadingdong.
You uploaded your blooper reel?
I hope the answer is no.
The answer is yes.
It is up, and it is
huger than a luger!
You're getting
Dude Monkey numbers
and netting more
subs every second.
Ow! Crime-a-Doodle-Don't!
Oh, terrific.
The whole city must
be laughing at me.
Just look at the comments.
Little Terry Sasko says,
"I love that Megamind
messes up just like me.
In a weird way,
that's inspiring."
Inspiring? Well,
that's what I want,
but this feels like
what I don't want.
This is what your channel needs.
Everyone wants to be a hero.
So when a hero makes a mistake,
that's fun to see because
everyone makes mistakes.
If you wanna inspire your fans,
we need to show them
everything, warts and all.
Maybe you're right.
And perhaps I was a little
harsh on you earlier.
You think?
I'm promoting you back
to your previous position
as my adviser of all
things onternetty.
Do I get a raise?
- I wasn't paying you before.
- I had to try.
You know, I find
it a little fishy
that Nighty-Knight would want
to steal a... Wait a second!
- Nighty-Knight!
Oh, I'm a fool for not
seeing this earlier.
I was so focused on
being onternet cool,
I let him slip
through my fingers!
We have to stop him!
But it's impossible to know
where he'll strike next.
No, it's not, Chum.
Nighty-Knight is making a play
for the diamond koi fish.
Sir, don't you think you're
jumping to conclusions?
No! Keiko, bring up my bloopers.
- Hey! That's my fishbowl!
Pause it! He's
stealing a fishbowl!
Perhaps he wants an
unconventional candy dish.
Keiko, run it.
Backslash rad!
- Pause!
Now, zoom in! There!
The blueprints for the aquarium!
Please. Who doesn't have those?
Megamind: He's going to sneak
himself in inside a meat-sicle cart!
Maybe we should focus on what
Nighty-Knight is actually up to.
- Keiko, enhance audio.
Nighty-Knight: My darkly
dark plan to steal
the diamond-encrusted koi
during the reopening ceremony
will be a... drowning success.
Okay, I'm convinced. The
"muahaha" did it for me.
To the aquarium!
Alright now! Now the D-Monk's
gonna upchuck some smarts
all over you Monkerinos!
Aquariums
are like superheroes.
They both are things
people like to look at,
and also both things that
make people happy, too.
- Please give me good news.
Like, a meteor is
heading this way,
so I don't have to
listen to this speech.
Nighty-Knight's coming
for the koi fish!
If you see a meat-sicle
cart, clear it out.
Dude Monkey: Lungs like
humans do. They have gills.
We need to clear
out all meat-sicle carts.
Security. We need help clearing
out the meat-sicle carts.
Hey!
Eternal doom awaits all who
come between Nighty-Knight
and his fishy bowl of... doom!
Let's schtop a crime!
Dude, awesome costume!
Alright, let's do this
just like we practiced.
Some light sparring, and then
I totally crush you. Ready?
You dare talk confusingly
to the Duke of Darkness?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, Brad!
We so do not have
the budget for this!
Wait. You're not Brad.
You're really
Nighty-Knight!
Crowd: Run! It's Nighty-Knight!
- Hey, guys.
Welcome to "Megamind's Rules
For Defending Your City!"
How do you like that title,
Keiko? Is it onternetty?
So onternetty. I think
you're starting to get this.
By the way, where is Dude
Monkey in this moment of need?
Bad Guy Brad: Oh...
Here you are, dude!
Dude, you were supposed
to stage the heist
like we rehearsed!
I don't know how to
stop real criminals!
Dude, you just got
ousted as a fraud.
Dude!
I had a feeling Dude
Monkey was a phony.
I assure all you
former Monkerinos,
as Metro City's defender,
I will never lie to you.
- Yoo-hoo! Wannabe spooky dude!
- Nighty-Knight: Megamind!
Your pathetic
attempts to foil my
Wha...
- Pretty chill, homeboy.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, please, no! You're too much.
- But it is fitting.
I appreciate the applause,
but I also really need
you to like and subscribe!
Sir! I made my own meme!
- Pretty chill, homeboy.
Ol' Chum: I think
you've gone viral, sir!
I look positively infectious!
Guard: Megamind!
Someone just stole a genetically
altered starfish from the lab!
A what?
My quest was darkly bountiful,
most vile one.
The starfish.
Able to regenerate its
body if it loses a limb.
This holds the genetic
key that will allow me
to rise to power once again!
Soon, I will remind Megamind
how good it feels to be bad!