- Huh?
- Hello.
♪ Supervillain,
ahead of his time ♪
♪ Incredibly handsome
genius, criminal mastermind ♪
♪ But now he's all cleaned
up and fighting crime ♪
♪ A superhero that
you stream online ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it feels good
to be good this time ♪
♪ It's Megamind ♪
♪ Oh, it's Megamind ♪
♪ Rules! ♪
Machiavillain: I am born anew!
You've served me well,
my sad, pathetic little puppies.
And now, as we're
about to deliver
our devilish main course,
it's time for the flourish!
As I once told my
little blue pupil,
the key to supervillainy is
presentation!
- Thank you.
Thank you. N-No,
you're too kind.
Ooh! I almost forgot
how beautiful I am.
You look great.
I said I almost forgot,
but your sniveling
platitude is noted.
When you're reborn, it's like
you're seeing and smelling
and hearing everything
for the first time.
Music! I need music!
I said music.
Something with style,
not ear torture.
Oh... Mm...
Pardon, but was zere
a point to all of zis?
Yeah. When do we get to the
part where we destroy Megamind?
Trying to simply
destroy Megamind
is where you've all failed.
We need to do more than that.
We have to destroy who
he thinks he's become.
- It's time to
put Metro City's hero
to the test!
We're here at City Hall Plaza,
where citizens are gathered
to celebrate Comet Day.
Can you believe it?
The Metro City Comet.
This only happens once
every hundred years!
Yeah, that's... something.
A whole day of
festivities are planned
with Mayor Roxanne
Ritchi presiding.
Hooray for the mayor!
I know her!
- We all know her, Chum.
- Excuse me,
but somebody doesn't seem
to be in the proper spirit
to watch a 10-mile-wide
chunk of ice, dust,
and small rocky particles
pass by the Earth.
Sorry, I-I just got a
lot on my mind today.
Well, Dr. Chum's advice clinic
just happens to be open!
- Come on, let's rap.
- Uh, okay.
It'd be easier if I just
come out and say it,
so hold any comments
and questions
for after I'm done
getting it all out.
You got it.
I kind of gave
Megamind's binky away.
You gave Megamind's binky away?!
A-Ahem. Sorry.
That was a comment,
and I apologize. Please, go on.
- To Machiavillain.
Machiavillain's back?!
Oops. That was a question.
I'm really bad at this.
But we need to tell Sir
as soon as possible!
It was my mistake.
I need to be the one to
tell him. Promise me, Chum.
- Oh boy.
Not too late to get someone
a little more surprising
as our surprise guest.
Even you have to admit,
people love Megamind.
People also love
playing with baboons.
That is, until nature
takes its course.
Well, my blue guy
hasn't let us down yet.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's my proud duty
to introduce today's
guest and my good friend,
- Megamind.
- Crowd: Megamind! Megamind!
- Megamind! Megamind...
Where is he?
I slept like a
handsome log last night.
Oh, Sir, you're just in
time to see your entrance.
Wait a second. You're supposed
to be at the comet ceremony!
That was today?!
I have to get down there!
Chum, where's my good
cape? The black one!
- It's with all the other black ones.
- Megamind: Got it!
Ahem.
I know you're in a hurry,
but I need to tell
you something.
Keiko, I'm already
late for an event
and what's sure to be an
epic Roxanne brow-beating.
It really can't wait!
- Keiko, I really don't have time for...
- Well, well, well, if it
isn't my formerly prized pupil.
- Machiavillain!
It can't be. I
thought you were...
Machiavillain : Defeated?
Destroyed? Didn't I teach you
that it's impossible to keep
a truly bad villain down?
I'm here to find inspiration
for my next evil project.
And here you are, my megamuse.
Well, maybe you haven't heard,
but I'm not a villain anymore.
Yes. I can't tell you how
disappointed I was to hear
that you're now batting
for the losing team.
Justice might lose a
game here and there,
but we make up for
it in the off-season.
The off-season is
for exhibition games,
but this is the finals,
and I'm heavily favored to win.
It doesn't matter
if you win or lose!
It's how well you play the game!
Then, why even
bother keeping score?
Because! Uh...
- Ha-ha! Gotcha!
- Goh!
Chum, what's happening?
It's almost as if Sir
is at a loss for words.
Blast him!
He knows sports metaphors have
never been my strong suit.
Machiavillain: I came here
to help you, Megamind.
You're caught in an
upward spiral of goodness,
and I came to drag you back
down to where you belong.
Where life is simpler,
and you don't have to think
about things like rules
- or setting a good example for the kiddies.
- Huh?
Get to the point, Machiavillain.
Machiavillain: I came
to offer you a choice.
Return to villainy and be
welcomed back with open arms,
or continue this
heroic silliness
and face the ultimate challenge.
I choose heroic silliness!
Then know this.
What happens next is on you.
And now, it's time
for evil's favorite game show...
Audience : "Who
Wants To Save A City?"
The rules are simple. Megamind,
you have one hour to
pass three heroic trials
hidden throughout the city.
For each, you'll be given
only one clue to its location.
If you stop all three,
I will leave in peace!
If you lose, it will mean
utter destruction of Metro City.
Are you ready to see
how good of a hero
- you really are?
- Ready, set, go!
Time's wasting, Sir!
Keiko, stay here.
Machiavillain is
the most dangerous
individual I've ever known.
Oh, yeah? Well, I owe
that guy some payback.
- Payback?
- I mean...
I just don't like bullies.
Sir, I think we
need to tell Keiko
the truth about Machiavillain.
You're right, Chum,
but I need to be
the one to tell her.
- Promise me.
Why does everyone trust
me with their secrets
when I hate keeping them?
Roxanne : You better have
an amazing non-sleep-related excuse
- for not being here.
- Roxanne,
I don't have time to apologize.
We're in the midst of a
deadly game of cat and mouse!
- Ready for the first clue?
How on Earth did
you hack my watch?!
Clue number one.
The world is your oyster,
but when is it in
your living room?
Hm. Clock's ticking!
- Ciao!
Ugh, first sports,
now shellfish trivia?
He's hitting all my weak areas.
Keiko: The world
is your oyster...
The Oyster Nebula!
It's a space cloud,
but also part of
the Metro Comet's route.
We learned about this in school.
Okay, but then where do
living rooms come in?
Must be something
everybody has in theirs.
Not alligator pits, not
particle accelerators...
Wait! Televisions!
And the comet is being broadcast
live from the observatory!
- Step on it, Chum!
- You got it, Sir!
- Hm. Nothing looks to be amiss, Sir.
Megamind: That's
what worries me.
Keiko, you're with me.
So, this Machiavillain guy.
Uh, yes. He taught me everything
I know about being evil.
But, I wanted to tell you...
Yeah, you told me already.
But, did I tell you
I had to defeat him
to become a supervillain?
Yes! You kicked his butt
once, so you can do it again.
- But, I really...
- Actually, the truth is...
Does that guy seem
a little off to you?
- Almost as if he's...
Hypnotized!
Bonjour, Monsieur Megamind!
Pierre Pressure!
I thought I smelled snails.
It's escargot.
I had them for lunch,
and they were magnifique.
He must be planning
to use the newsfeed.
With everyone at the plaza
watching the ceremony,
he could hypnotize all
of Metro City at once!
Ze poisson-companion is correct!
- Your show's
about to be canceled.
Zat pea-shooter might
work on one Pierre,
but what about...
Pierres: Multiple Pierres?
Oldest villain
trick in the book.
You zap the one in the middle!
- Piece of cake.
- Keiko: More like 100 cakes!
I can't find the middle
if they don't stay still!
Sir, may I recommend
the De-Gun's new
rapid-fire setting?
Right!
Ha, ha!
Take that! Whoa!
- Look out!
- Take cover!
What happened? Was I victorious?
Looks like you
debilitated him, Sir!
Vive la France.
Keiko: Also looks like you
debilitated the telescope.
- Ollo?
Don't "ollo" me.
First, you don't
show up to the event,
and now, the comet feed is down,
which I'm assuming has
something to do with you!
- Oh, bravo!
Sorry, Roxie. Gotta take this.
Time for clue number two.
What a villain seeks
to rule over all,
when it is lost,
darkness will fall.
- Much success to you.
He says that, but I'm
not so sure he means it.
The first part of
the clue is easy.
Villains always
seek the same thing.
- Power.
- A spa day!
I mean, power! You're
probably right, Sir.
But, what kind of power
could make darkness fall?
- Roxanne : It's the power station!
- You're still here?
- Roxanne: Still here!
And who was that
you were talking to?
Thanks for the help,
Roxie. We'll explain later.
- Floor it, Chum!
- Huh. Everything looks quiet here.
Lady Doppler: Beware
of a flash flood
of lightning!
You're just in time to see me
destroy Metro City
with its own power!
Keiko, you distract Doppler
with some trash talking.
- I've got an idea.
Hey, Doppler! You know
there's no such thing
as a flash flood of
lightning, right?
Well, if it isn't
Megamind's kid sidekick.
Why don't you go back
to the clubhouse?
Adults are talking.
Yet, I'm the only one
not in a funny costume.
You're making me rethink
my no-zapping-kids policy.
I've seen your aim.
I ain't sweatin'.
- Oh, you little...
- Time for a fish-monkey fry.
- Thirsty?
Water and electricity
don't mix, do they?
- Time to bolt!
- Ah!
I just wanna thank our sponsor
for today's festivities.
- Mr. Minion's Meat-sicles.
Power's out across the city.
It's gonna be one of those
crazy Metro City days, isn't it?
How's that for a flash flood?
Nice callback, Keiko.
Unfortunately, it looks like
the city's entire power grid
is fried, Sir.
The good news is
we're two for three.
Yes, it's been a lot
easier than expected.
Which is not like
Machiavillain at all.
Oh, what an
inspirational testament
to the power of teamwork.
It's now time to play
for the fate of the city!
Clue number three. You've done
well and played like a whiz.
As for the last location,
it's where your heart is.
I believe the old saying goes,
"Home is where the heart is."
He's going after the lair.
With the grid shut down,
so is our security system!
Ugh!
The smell of goodness
in here has to go.
Nighty-Knight: Ahem! Megamind's
computer isn't going to work
with the city's power out.
The lair's emergency backup
generators should be kicking in
in three, two, one.
Brainbot: Intruder
alert. Intruder alert.
Intruder alert...
Nighty-Knight: Uh, sir?
Now, all that was once
Megamind's belongs to me.
Brainbot: Intrud...
A much better color on you.
- Fly, my pretties!
Go make some mischief.
Chum: What's going on?
Machiavillain must now
have access to the lair!
He's turned the
brainbots against us!
Keiko: Not just us! They're
committing crimes all over the city!
- We've
got to shut them down fast!
Sir, the brainbots
are controlled
by the lair's
transmitter antenna.
If we can knock it out...
It'll turn off all
the brainbots at once!
- Why are
there so many menus in here? Ah!
- Found it!
- The remote to the laser satellite!
Brilliant, Sir!
The satellite fires
with pinpoint accuracy.
I should be able to
take out the antenna
- while leaving the rest of the lair intact.
- Machiavillain: Well, Megamind.
Thank you for playing,
but I'm afraid
you've lost the game.
Au contraire, mon frere.
You see, I've learned a few new
things since Villainy Shool.
- The bad guys always lose.
- We did it!
Oh, Megamind.
While you were distracted
with the brainbots,
I reprogrammed your
targeting system!
- Instead of
destroying the transmitter,
your laser knocked
the comet off course,
causing it to head
straight towards.
- Metro City!
Everyone, remain calm!
Megamind will know what to do!
I have no idea what to do!
I'm sure all hope
isn't lost, Sir.
Oh, really? Did you not notice
the giant comet about
to obliterate the city?
It just seemed like something
I should say right now.
I mean, look at that thing.
- It's huge.
It's a hero problem way
above my power grade.
Oh, Machiavillain played
me like a blue fiddle.
No! He can't win!
Can't you just beat him
like you did last time?
Time to tell her the
whole story, Sir.
I never intentionally
defeated Machiavillain.
- What do you mean?
- When I was a student,
I accidentally left
the gamma chamber on
while heating a burrito.
I came back from an errand
to find Machiavillain's entire
fortress burned to ashes.
I'm not proud of it,
but I took credit for
destroying my master.
And on that lie, I went from
being an ordinary villain
to a super one.
There's gotta be something
you haven't thought of yet.
Can't we just use the satellite
to re-divert the comet
away from the city?
It takes too long to
warm up between shots.
What about the De-Gun?
It's not powerful enough.
I'd have to, I don't know,
run it through the
cold fusion generator
of the Invisible
Car or something,
but that's still a long shot.
A long shot is still a chance!
- Crowd: Megamind! Megamind!
We're here to save the day,
but we're going to
need everyone's help.
Let's move like we have
a porpoise, people.
Crowd: Megamind! Megamind!
- He's gonna do it!
- You can do it!
Kick that flying rock's butt!
Hey, comet!
- This one's for the dinosaurs.
Ah!
You have a plan B, right?
That was B through Z.
- I'm sorry. I failed, Roxanne.
Since this is the end,
there's something I
regret never telling you.
What is it?
You are...
Machiavillain:
Fear not, citizens!
- Machiavillain is here!
My binky?
One moment while I take care
of this small problem of yours.
- Ah-ha!
Citizens! From this day forward,
you will fear no more!
- Metro
City's true hero has arrived.
- Finally,
a real hero to save us!
Oh, Sir.
We've been looking all
over the city for you!
I'm just
admiring the symbolism.
It's my own fault,
thinking for a moment I was
smart enough to beat him.
Actually, it's my fault.
Oh, that's nice of
you to say, but...
No, it's literally my fault!
That's what I've been
trying to tell you!
I gave Machiavillain your binky.
Why would you do that, Keiko?
When you wouldn't train me,
I wanted to prove myself.
I pretended to join
the Doom Syndicate
to find out what
they were planning.
Machiavillain tricked
me into stealing it.
The binky is the last thing
I have from my home world.
It's a source of unlimited power
that I don't even
totally understand.
I wouldn't blame you if you
never wanted to see me again.
I'm nothin' but trouble.
Megamind: That's the
last thing I want.
Machiavillain tricked us both.
Besides, I've always had
a soft spot for trouble.
Oh. A press conference
just started.
Machiavillain :
I regret to inform everyone
that it was Megamind
who is responsible
for this near catastrophe.
Yes, it appears that he's
returned to his old evil ways.
- Behold!
- First, he
neutralized the observatory,
which would have acted as
an early warning system.
- Then, he
destroyed the power grid
to disable any
emergency response.
- Next, he unleashed
his brainbots upon the city,
giving him just the
distraction he needed to use
his own satellite
to divert the comet
- right toward Metro City.
Oh, it's all lies! All of it!
Machiavillain's specialty.
Now, now. I know how
shocking this must be.
It's never easy to see someone
so noble fall from grace.
Perhaps our courageous mayor
will have comforting
words for us all.
Though I question with my
whole heart these accusations,
the evidence is overwhelming.
I have no choice but
to declare Megamind
public enemy number one.
It's over. Machiavillain's won.
Not quite yet, Ol' Chum.
We still have one
card left to play.
We have to find...
- Metro Man.