You can do this.
You have reached Walter White.
Please state your name...
...number, and the reason for your call.
Thank you.
Third try.
Walt, if you're there, please pick up.
I really wanted to do this together
but I can hear him getting up.
It's not like I can keep him
from seeing the thing.
So, I'm sorry, but I've waited
as long as possible and I...
I guess I'm gonna have to go ahead
without you.
So call me.
- Hey.
- Hey. Happy birthday, sweet 16.
Thanks, Mom.
Of course,
I thought you might sleep through it.
So since it's almost, oh, noon...
...I think your first big birthday
decision is breakfast or lunch?
- Pancakes?
- Pancakes it is.
Oh, could you do me a favour?
I forgot to get the paper.
Can you grab it for me?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Surprise.
It's from me and your dad.
It's pretty slick, huh?
Yeah. Thanks, Mom. It's... It's great.
I really did a lot of research...
...and, I don't know,
this car just really stood out to me.
It's got a ton of great features,
power everything, solid engine.
It's really roomy so you can,
you know, carpool with all your friends.
And, of course,
it is safe because I'm still your mother.
And it has a CD player...
...so you can listen to tunes
while cruising around.
So you know what? Breakfast can wait.
You wanna take it for a spin?
Maybe later. I'm kind of starving.
Yeah, okay. Well, let's...
Let's get those pancakes going.
Saul, he's here.
Bad idea. This is a bad idea.
Saul?
Send him in.
Mr. Beneke. Saul Goodman.
Thank you for coming down.
- Hey.
- Yeah, hi.
Have a seat, please.
I...
I don't understand why I'm here.
- Something to do with my creditors?
- Creditors? No.
I'll cut right to the chase, Mr. Beneke.
I have some bad news.
Nothing but lately.
Your Great-aunt Birgit passed away.
I'm sorry, who?
Apparently she passed away
in Diekirch, Luxembourg.
And this was- Wow, eight years ago.
I just assumed you two were close,
given that...
Well, maybe this is good news.
Birgit left behind a sizeable estate...
...of which you, Mr. Beneke,
are the primary beneficiary.
What?
She had no immediate relatives
so the estate's just been sitting...
...while the folks over in the EU
searched for a living heir.
Well, I don't know of any relatives
in Luxembourg.
Definitely no one
who would name me in their will.
Well...
Well, here we go. She left no will.
So that's probably why it took so long.
They traced the inheritance
to your father.
But having passed- My condolences.
- You are the next in line...
...to the tune of $621,552.33.
And when does Don Eladio arrive?
Let's see how the cook goes first.
Who's the chemist?
Is this a joke?
He's asking if you're the chemist.
I'm one of them.
Okay, we've all met.
Let's get to work.
Where's the phenylacetic acid?
Please show him the phenylacetic acid.
We synthesize it ourselves.
All the ingredients are here.
They synthesize their own.
What?
I don't do that.
What's the problem?
Look, I get my phenylacetic acid
from the barrel with the bee on it.
That's how I know how to do it.
Mr. Pinkman was under the impression
that the phenylacetic acid...
...would already be synthesized
upon his arrival.
Any sophomore chemistry
student can make it.
What kind of amateur
have you brought us?
- What's he saying?
- We're working it out.
This is ridiculous.
I'm not letting some infant...
...who can't even synthesize
phenylacetic acid...
...teach me my business.
Tell this asshole if he wants to learn
how to make my product...
...he's gotta do it my way.
The right way.
I speak English.
So you understand
what "asshole" means.
Now, go get me my phenylacetic acid,
asshole.
How long is it gonna take
to get him what he needs?
I don't know. I have no idea.
Several hours, at least.
I can wait. Gives us time to talk
about the state of this lab.
Don't you have standards?
I mean, this place is disgusting.
All right, we're gonna scour every vat,
every tank, every cook surface.
We clean up every possible source
of contamination. And then we cook.
Who do you think you are?
I'm the guy your boss brought here
to show you how it's done.
And if this is how you run your lab,
no wonder.
You're lucky he hasn't fired your ass.
Now, if you don't want that to happen...
...I suggest you stop whining
like a little bitch, and do what I say.
Clean up!
You have reached Walter White.
Please state your name...
...number, and the reason for your call.
Thank you.
Dad, you there?
I'm outside. Are you okay?
I know you're home, your car is here.
You missed my party which feels like
something's gotta be really wrong.
I... I'm gonna have to call 911.
I don't know what else to do.
Dad?
Come in, if you're coming in.
What happened to you?
What happened?
I got into a fight.
What do you mean, a fight?
Like-? What fight?
Are you gonna talk to me here?
What are you doing?
- I'm calling Mom.
- Don't do that.
Look, I...
I appreciate that you're concerned,
but I'm fine.
Just do not call your mother.
Why not?
Because...
...I was gambling.
If you tell your mother, I just -
I will never, never hear the end of it.
So please.
Can we just keep this between us?
Would you do that for me?
Just... Just keep it to yourself.
I don't understand.
How'd you get into a fight?
And with who?
I made a mistake.
It's my own fault.
- I had it coming.
- Dad...
...it's okay.
It's all my fault.
I just...
I'm sorry.
Dad.
Come here.
Come on. Dad, it's okay.
No. Hey, hey, no.
- It's okay. Come on, please. It's okay.
- No.
Look at me. Look at me.
It's okay. It is. Come on.
Come on.
It's-It's okay.
Hey.
How was your birthday?
Good. Get some rest.
Okay.
The new car...
...did you drive it here?
Yeah.
That's good.
You like it?
Sure. I do.
It drives great.
That's good, Jesse.
Yes.
- Yes.
- Well done.
The first of many.
Yeah? What's that mean?
You're staying.
You belong to the cartel now.
You can't come to my work like this.
You're too recognisable.
Your face is plastered on every
bus bench within a five-mile radius.
Celebrities have to get their cars
washed just like everybody else.
I wouldn't have come
if it wasn't important.
- Okay?
- What is it?
Well, I went ahead and met
with your Mr. Beneke. Right?
Which, I will say again,
loudly and for the record, bad idea.
Yes, but it is better than prison,
correct?
Marginally. Which is why I disbursed
the funds as you requested.
All right, good.
Yeah. I can't believe
he actually bought it.
Great-aunt Birgit. What?
But you called it. People see zeroes
dance before their eyes...
- ...it's like highway hypnosis.
- So, what's the problem?
Let's just say, you and I don't
wear the same rose-coloured glasses...
...where Johnny Fabulous
is concerned.
So I kept an eye on his bank accounts,
and pulled his credit report.
If you would, note the time on that.
Three fifty-four p.m. yesterday.
- Three hours after leaving my office.
- He bought a Mercedes SL550.
He's actually leasing it,
but he put 4500 down.
He's gonna pay 1830 a month.
Fully loaded.
He even got the heated steering wheel.
But that's upwards of 6300
that won't be going to the IRS.
I just thought you might like to know,
loath as I am to say, I told you so.
Where is he now?
Hey.
How you doing?
Good.
How are you?
I'm fine, but your mother
is going to be worried sick.
I called her last night.
Oh, God.
I told her
I was spending the night at Louis'.
It's cool. So...
How are you?
I'm fine, son. I...
I...
Well, I...
I took these painkillers
that I had leftover from my surgery...
...and I made the brilliant decision...
...to wash them down
with a couple of beers.
Not my most sterling moment,
I admit.
But I'm fine.
I wish I could take back last night.
It was your birthday.
- This shouldn't be on your mind.
- It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
I'm your father,
and I don't want last night to be...
I mean, you really...
...can't think of me like...
Like what?
I don't understand.
My father died when I was 6.
- You knew that, right?
- Yeah.
He had Huntington's disease. It's...
It destroys portions of the brain...
...affects muscle control...
...leads to dementia,
it's just a nasty disease.
It's genetic.
Terrified my mother
that I might have it...
...so they ran tests on me
when I was a kid, but I came up clean.
My father fell very ill when I was...
...four or 5.
He spent a lot of time in the hospital.
My...
My mother would tell me
so many stories about my father.
She would talk about him
all the time.
I knew about his personality...
...how he treated people...
...I even knew how
he liked his steaks cooked.
Medium rare.
Just like you.
I knew things about my father.
I had a lot of information.
It's because people
would tell me these things.
They would paint this picture...
...of my father for me.
And I always pretended
that was who I saw too.
Who I remembered. But it was a lie.
In truth, I only have one real...
...actual memory of my father.
It must have been
right before he died.
My mother would take me
to the hospital to visit him.
And I remember the smell
in there, the chemicals.
It was as if they used up...
...every single cleaning product
they could find in a 50-mile radius.
Like they didn't want you
smelling the sick people.
There was this stench
of Lysol and bleach.
I mean, you could just feel it
coating your lungs.
Anyway, there lying on the bed...
...is my father.
He's all...
He's all twisted up.
And my mom...
...she puts me on her lap.
She's sitting on the bed next to him
so I can get a good look at him.
But really, he just scares me.
And he's looking right at me...
...but I can't even be sure
that he knows who I am.
And your grandmother is talking...
...trying to be cheerful,
you know, as she does...
...but the only thing
I could remember...
...is him breathing.
This...
This rattling sound.
Like if you were shaking
an empty spray paint can.
Like there was nothing in him.
Anyway...
...that is the only real memory
that I have of my father.
I don't want you to think of me
the way I was last night.
I don't want that to be the memory
you have of me when I'm gone.
Remembering you that way...
...wouldn't be so bad.
The bad way to remember you
would be the way...
The way you've been
this whole last year.
At least last night you were...
You were real, you know?
- Bye.
Somewhere you should be?
Well, basically
it was a temporary hiatus.
But you give us two weeks, we will
be up and running 100 percent.
All right, you talk to your people
and get back to me, okay?
- Hi.
- Yeah, thanks, Tanya.
Okay. You bet.
Say hi to the kids for me.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Nice surprise. What's up?
Just thought I'd swing by,
see how things are going.
Well, things are...
Things took a turn. It's kind of crazy.
Oh, yeah?
The universe is telling me something.
I got some good news.
Some very good news...
...and I'm getting the business
going again.
I figure we haven't been down long...
...so we should be able to get most
of our old contracts back. Sit.
Oh, thank you. That's -
Gosh, that's...
That's wow.
How is that even possible?
Well, I got a very unexpected
cash infusion.
I guess someone's
looking out for me.
I guess so.
Is that yours, outside?
Yeah, well, you know...
...I can't be driving a piece of crap.
You got to present
that successful image.
Right. So the IRS stuff.
That's resolved?
Yeah, it's in progress.
So you paid them?
Well, not yet. But I will.
When?
Well, it's not that simple.
Here's the thing:
I never had proper legal counsel.
So I was thinking...
...I should hire someone good who can
maybe hammer out a better deal.
There will never
be a better deal, Ted.
The deal is you pay
your back taxes...
...you pay your penalty
and you don't go to prison.
That's a good deal. So...
Let's keep our priorities straight.
Well, my priority
is getting my business back.
And putting my employees back on the
payroll so they can pay the mortgages.
Right. But I think
your employees would agree...
...that you need to get
your financial situation in control...
...before you can help them.
Boy, the IRS
got you on commission?
I'm just saying that,
though I really understand...
...the temptation
to restart the business...
...maybe the universe is telling you...
...that you need to pay what you owe.
Skyler...
...this is my money.
Why are we having this conversation?
You're no longer a part of my life.
A decision you made, by the way.
So I don't understand
why you're hectoring me about this.
- Ted, this affects both of us.
- No it doesn't.
I'm telling you to drop this.
You need to use that money
to pay your bill.
By the end of this month.
Which you promised
the IRS in writing that you would do.
It is that simple.
Okay.
Okay, duly noted.
What does that mean?
Does that mean yes? Because
I really need a yes here, Ted.
All right, Skyler,
I'll tell you what it means. It means...
...in the most respectful way possible,
there's the door.
And I'm inviting you to, you know...
And thank you for your concern,
but I'm done talking about this.
From whom exactly do you think
you got that 600,000, Ted?
Great-aunt Birgit?
That was you?
Yeah.
What is this shit?
I don't get a vote?
I'm supposed to just
stay down here forever?
I promise you this:
Either we're all going home
or none of us are.
Now settle down.
On your feet.
Gustavo.
I'm so happy...
...you finally came to your senses.
May I present the cook.
This is your new employer.
You address him as Don Eladio.
It's a term of respect.
Hello, young man.
He doesn't speak
a word of Spanish, does he?
And he's no chemist...
...I'll tell you that.
I don't care if he's a pig farmer.
He cooks better meth than you do...
...with all your fancy
college degrees.
And this one will have
plenty of time to learn Spanish.
What's in there?
A gift?
Gustavo, you're so generous.
It's a token of respect.
In honour of our renewed friendship.
Let's see what's in here.
No, impossible!
Zafiro Añejo!
Look at this.
Even the bottle is a work of art.
It's perfection!
Perhaps...
...it's too good to share.
What do you think, Gustavo?
It's yours to do with as you choose.
I choose...
...to drink it!
Careful.
That's beautiful stuff.
If you spill a drop...
...I'll cut off your hand.
Come on, hurry up.
Gustavo.
Welcome to Mexico.
Now you say:
This one's an addict.
To work, he must be sober.
None for you!
Enough business!
Bring the girls!
No. No, no, I don't...
Gustavo.
Cheer up, man.
Gustavo...
...I'm not angry.
I had to spank you.
But what choice did I have?
Look, once every 20 years...
...you forget your place.
There's no place for emotion in this.
You of all people should understand.
Business is business.
If you'll excuse me.
- Where are you going?
- To use your bathroom.
If I may.
Miguel!
Show Gustavo the pisser.
And make sure he doesn't get lost.
Hurry up.
Make yourself useful. Find a gun.
Don Eladio is dead!
His capos are dead!
You have no one left to fight for!
Fill your pockets...
...and leave in peace!
Or fight me...
...and die!
I hope to hell that works.
Take him.
Keys.
No. No.
Okay. Okay.
Hey. Hey, you still with us?
Go.
Kid, get us out of here, kid.
Come on.