- Are we done?
- Listen, I--
This attack on my brother-in-law,
I don't know what it means.
Please.
I fear for my family.
I'm sure they'll be fine.
I'm told the assassin that survived
is gravely injured.
It's doubtful he'll live.
Now, thank me and shake my hand.
- Thank you. Thank you again.
- You're quite welcome, Mr. White.
Guys, guys, hurry up.
- Can we go now?
- Upstairs, come on.
What's happening?
Eight forty-three.
Time of death, 20:43.
Burn in hell, you piece of shit.
One of the gunmen died
at the scene.
The second succumbed to his wounds
earlier this evening.
Agents with the DEA and FBI...
...in conjunction with APD are working
with Mexican law enforcement...
...in an attempt to identify
the deceased suspects. Both--
I can give you the highlights.
Your nephews grew impatient.
They continued to press me
for my permission to kill Walter White.
When I wouldn't give it, they settled
instead for DEA Agent Schrader.
But a phone call was placed...
...to Agent Schrader
moments before the attack.
Thus giving him the upper hand.
Marco was shot in the face
and died instantly.
Leonel lingered for several hours.
The warning call to the DEA agent...
...Juan Bolsa
may have some insight...
...into who placed it.
Yesterday,
federales raided his hacienda.
And in the confusion,
Juan was shot dead.
An accident, perhaps.
A mistake made by his own men.
Though we may never know.
At any rate,
I thought you should hear it from me.
This is what comes
of blood for blood, Hector.
So is this the loud one?
What?
No. This is the PET/CT scan.
Positron emission tomography.
They've paired that
with computed x-ray tomography.
Quiet. No magnets.
Right, okay.
Yeah, thanks.
I'm still pretty new at this.
One minute,
I'm starting a new business...
...my wife and I
are thinking about kids.
Walk into a doctor's office
and suddenly ...
- I mean, life as I know it--
- Excuse me.
Yes. I'm waiting
to hear a progress report...
...on the thing we discussed,
so call me.
Anyway, so for me,
that's been the biggest wake-up call.
Letting go, giving up control.
You know, it's like they say,
"Man plans and God laughs."
That is such bullshit.
Excuse me?
Never give up control.
Live life on your own terms.
Yeah, no,
I get what you're saying...
...but cancer is cancer, so...
To hell with your cancer.
I've been living with cancer
for the better part of a year.
From the start, it's a death sentence.
That's what they keep telling me.
Well, guess what?
Every life comes
with a death sentence.
So every few months,
I come in here for my regular scan...
...knowing full well
that one of these times--
Hell, maybe even today.
--I'm gonna hear some bad news.
But until then...
...who's in charge?
Me.
That's how I live my life.
This residue here is why we descale
with cool water...
...from the walk-in
and not water from the tap.
Do it again, please.
Pollos Hermanos, where something
delicious is always cooking.
Yes, detective.
Yeah.
- Gustavo, thanks for coming.
- Pleasure.
- How's Kathi?
- Much better, thank you.
- And you know Hank Schrader?
- Yes, indeed.
- And Steve Gomez?
- How was your meal?
Agent Schrader and I had a chance
to catch up at one of my restaurants.
I'd eat there every day
but I wouldn't fit through the door.
- Well, should we get started?
- Yeah.
- I'd like to record this conversation.
- Of course.
The DEA is working on an investigation
which may overlap with my own...
...so I've asked them to sit in.
Gus, we all appreciate your coming
in here to talk to us...
...but you have the right
to have an attorney present.
Oh, well, I can't see
how that would be necessary.
But then,
I have no idea why I'm here.
So you wish to continue?
Please. I'm very anxious
to find out what this is all about.
Sir, your fingerprints were found
at a crime scene.
Really? That's surprising.
A drug-related homicide.
Gale Boetticher's apartment.
So you knew the victim?
Fifteen years ago, I established
a chemistry scholarship at UNM.
I named it
after Maximino Arciniega...
...a dear friend of mine
who died young.
Gale was a recipient
of this scholarship.
He was perhaps one of three dozen.
I see.
And Mr. Boetticher graduated in ...
-1999.
- That sounds right.
And you kept in contact with him
over all this time?
Oh, no. I hadn't seen Gale for years
until I ran into him a few weeks ago.
- Ran into him where?
- At the restaurant.
Well, "ran into" isn't quite accurate,
as I assumed...
...he came by to re-establish contact
with me. We caught up briefly.
He invited me to dinner
the following night and I accepted.
It was perhaps a week later
when I read about him in the paper.
- Drug related, you said?
-It's a good possibility.
The paper made no mention of that.
I assumed
that it was a random crime.
So after years with no contact,
he shows up in your restaurant...
...and invites you to dinner?
- He wanted money.
- Gale Boetticher asked for money?
- He didn't say that.
He spoke in terms
of a vague investment opportunity.
But it was my suspicion, yes,
as to why he invited me into his home.
He was a very, very talented chemist,
but for reasons I never understood...
...he was more interested
in taking shortcuts...
...than what would or could have been
a very promising career.
Personal shortcomings
notwithstanding...
...he was a warm, gentle person...
...and I thought a lot of him.
At any rate,
I declined his business offer...
...and after
what was a very pleasant meal, left.
Can you tell us where you were...
...on the night of Wednesday the 23rd
at around 8 p.m.?
- Not an accusation, just a question.
- No, I understand. Let's see.
Twenty-third.
I was at a fundraiser
at Presbyterian Hospital.
I was there from 7 to about 10.
Anyone else?
Sorry, yeah. Just one other thing.
Is Gustavo Fring your real name?
Is it my real name?
I know you're a Chilean national...
...but there are no records of you
ever living there.
Really?
I mean, records show that you
immigrated to Mexico in 1986...
...and years later, you were granted
an entry visa to the United States.
But there's no record of Gustavo Fring
ever having existed in Chile...
...which I find, I don't know, strange.
Well, no, really, it isn't.
Pinochet's government
was guilty of many sins.
First and foremost
were human rights abuses.
But it was also notoriously unreliable
at keeping records.
I'm sure if you keep digging,
you'll find me.
Okay, I think that's it, Gus.
Thank you.
I hope that I was of some small help.
- You were, absolutely. Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
Good to see you again. Oh, no.
- No, please, please. Don't get up.
- Thanks.
Gentlemen.
So are we buying?
This thing with his name?
What are you thinking?
Sure, the record-keeping
in South America's hit or miss.
I mean, we run into that all the time,
right?
But we usually find something.
Before '86 this guy's a ghost.
If State Department wasn't satisfied,
they wouldn't have naturalized him.
Well, maybe,
but he emigrated from Mexico in '89.
State just wasn't as tough
on background checks pre-9/11.
I don't know what this has to do
with the case at hand.
I was curious when his print showed up
at Boetticher's apartment.
For me, the scholarship explains it.
I'll admit to a certain degree of bias.
This man has been a longtime friend
of DEA.
But that being said,
I thought his story was credible.
Well, I agree.
I think it was a good story.
Still, why are we hearing it now?
What do you mean?
Well, like you said, he's a-- This man
is a big law enforcement booster.
He's reading the newspaper and sees
that someone he had dinner with...
...someone he thought a lot of
was murdered.
He reads this
and he doesn't make a phone call?
Didn't call you
or one of his other cop friends...
...to share his connection with the case
or ask about the investigation?
We can't predicate
a criminal investigation...
...on a person
not making phone calls.
What do you think, Tim?
Well, I wanna follow up
on the scholarship, the alibi...
...but my overall impression?
I believed him.
Nice touch. Birdbath.
- Hey, tiger, how's it hanging?
- Good.
Yeah, so very nice.
What's the damage?
Twelve hundred a month.
I did a lot of research.
- That's a pretty good deal.
- You kidding me? That's a great deal.
Speaking of which...
...that's for the week.
Plus there's a little extra in there
for any move-related incidentals.
Thank you.
- Hey, champ, how's the new school?
- Good.
I loved school when I was your age.
Seesaws, story time,
chasing girls with sticks.
It wasn't until the fifth grade
that I found out she liked me too...
...but by then her family had moved
to Scottsdale, so ...
- Carpe diem, okay?
- Okay.
All right. Good boy.
So you'll thank Jesse again
from both of us?
You got it.
- So is he-- How's he doing?
- Jesse?
He's good. He's busy.
How is it?
Space, lots of light. it's--
Little garden outback. it's nice.
And Brock? How's he doing?
Hey, look, I don't mind
dropping checks off every week...
...like Ed McMahon...
...but if you wanna know
how they're doing...
...why don't you go see for yourself?
I'll catch you later.
- Hey, you gonna need a ride home?
- No.
Great.
Anyway,
I'm proud for not losing my cool.
Plus, it shows our crew
that I will support them...
...if a customer's being rude.
You're really taking to this whole
be-your-own-boss thing.
Yeah. I guess I am.
Actually...
...I'm thinking about making the move
up to management.
Jesus. Corporate America, look out.
Excuse me,
I would be a vast improvement.
No one in Kleinman's entire front office
knows about giving an x-ray...
...which is just...
Hey, Dad, whatever happened
with your scan?
Did you get the results back?
Yeah, I did...
...and I'm still in remission.
So you're all gonna have to be stuck
with me for a while longer.
Cheers, buddy.
What about you, Hank?
How you feeling these days?
You know, getting there.
The other day, he had a big powwow
with all the DEA muckety-mucks.
What was that about?
Nothing. Just a dead-end.
He won't tell me, either.
Apparently, it's all very hush-hush.
Hey, Walt, do me a favour?
Marie's working tomorrow
and there's a gem and mineral show...
...opening at the fairgrounds.
I wondered if you could give me a lift?
Yeah. Sure.
I had a collection of my own
in high school.
I mean, nothing fancy.
Just entry-level beryls and garnets...
...one passable black tourmaline.
- Turn right here.
- Okay.
But I did have one piece of morganite
that was very special.
It'd been heat-treated,
so it had that classic cast to it.
That rose, almost salmon hue,
you know?
Hey, Walt,
there's no rock show, okay?
I just said that so Marie wouldn't freak.
Here. Take a right here.
Freak about what?
Hank, where are we going?
Are you hungry?
We're not here for the chicken.
Kill the engine.
All right.
You ready
for your mind to be blown?
Sure.
Gustavo Fring, remember him?
He came to the hospital
after the shooting. Put up the reward?
He sponsors the DEA Fun Run
every year. You've met him?
Yeah, the Fun Run guy. Yeah.
That guy, yeah. What about him?
Well, I suspect" I can't prove it,
mind you, but I suspect...
...the man's a drug dealer.
Yeah. Methamphetamine.
I mean, honest to God,
I really believe...
...that this guy may be one
of the biggest movers in the southwest.
Remember Gale Boetticher?
- That sad sack from the karaoke tape?
- Yeah.
And you said that he didn't strike you
as being the boss-man type?
That there was a bigger guy
out there.
- Hank, that was just speculation.
- Doesn't matter. It made me keep at it.
And guess what I find?
Chicken Man's fingerprints
at Boetticher's murder scene.
- So we bring him in--
- You think that Gustavo Fring...
...killed Gale Boetticher?
Probably not.
These guys usually get a dunce
to pull the trigger, right?
But his fingerprints being there
was enough to bring him in. So I--
So you brought him in to the police?
Right. He sits down to talk with us,
the problem is that--
What did you ask him?
What did he say?
Walt,
will you let me finish my story here?
Sorry, I'm just
interested, you know?
All right. Whatever. So we bring him in
and he proceeds to kick our asses.
Okay? He's got an explanation
for the fingerprints.
He's got an alibi for Gale's murder.
He's got reasons for everything.
This guy
is Terms of Endearment convincing.
So he's not guilty?
Yeah. As far as DEA
and APD are concerned, he's not.
Officially, Fring's not a suspect.
But I'm telling you...
...something deep down says
he's my guy.
Just gotta prove it.
Hank, why are you telling me this?
I need a favour.
What favour?
You see that Volvo station wagon
over there?
The guy drives a 10-year-old Volvo.
It's brilliant.
Anyway, listen...
...what I need for you to do...
...stick this on it.
GPS tracker.
Wifey thinks hubby's screwing around
on her but she wants to be sure?
Stick this on the car--
This part here, it's a magnet.
--And see where he goes.
Cool, huh?
Two eighty-nine from SkyMall.
It's not live-view,
so we gotta come back later...
...and take it off
and stick it in the computer.
Still, a pretty amazing time
we're living in.
Hank, isn't that illegal?
I mean, isn't there some sort
of unlawful search and something--
it's known as extralegal.
But trust me, it's our little secret.
Look, it's easy, okay?
Here's what you do.
You untie your shoelace
and you head toward the restaurant.
You're walking past the car...
...look down and, "Hey, darn,
my shoe's untied." Okay?
Now, when you bend down
to tie your shoe...
...you stick this into the wheel well.
- Then you go inside and I don't know--
- Hank, I don't feel good about this.
I know that this kind of thing
is outside your comfort zone--
No, I mean it. This is a mistake.
Walt,
I need you to help me out here, okay?
This is really important to me.
Are you gonna make me beg?
Come on. Just stick it in there.
Yeah.
Just act normal.
May I help you?
I-- I--
Sir, may I help you?
I didn't do it. See?
- I didn't do it.
- Do it.
Do it.
May I help you with your order?
What the hell is he...?
Just made sure it was secure.
Hey, where's my soda?
Just kidding. Let's go. Let's go.
Yes, that one.
I swear to God, I thought I was driving
the man to a gem and mineral show.
All of a sudden he has me
pulling into your restaurant...
...and telling me
that he's investigating you.
Look, you and I,
we've had our differences...
...but I would never--
Look, my brother-in-law,
evidence-wise, has nothing.
He's operating on pure conjecture.
And no one, not one person
that he works with...
...thinks that you are anyone other
than an owner of a fast-food chain.
But if something were to happen
to Hank?
That would only draw their attention
to you and therefore, to me, as well.
We have a mutual interest
in resolving this without violence.
I will make sure
that he discovers nothing.
Jesse!
What? Oh, hey.
Don't wait to be, like, invited.
Are we alone?
- So where do we stand?
- Where do we stand on what?
Where do we stand with the thing
that you were supposed to do?
I assume you haven't done it.
You didn't lose it, did you?
You would tell me if you lost it, right?
Oh, Jesus.
Asshole. You're creaming
to get it done, go do it yourself.
If he didn't see me coming
like he's some kind of ...
All right, look.
Our timetable has advanced.
You have got to make this meeting
happen this week.
Tomorrow. Tonight, if possible.
Oh, tonight. What are you, high?
My brother-in-law,
my DEA agent brother-in-law?
He's onto Gus.
Did you hear what I just said?
My brother-in-law is onto Gus.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got it,
your brother-in-law. Okay, I'm thinking.
Look. So, what if this is
like math or algebra?
We add a plus douche bag
to a minus douche bag...
...and you get, like,
zero douche bags.
I've got some math for you.
Hank catching Gus
equals Hank catching us.
Hank, he's relentless, all right?
He won't quit.
Yeah, well, he's got nothing,
is all I can say.
- How would you know that?
- Because he's still above ground.
Think a dude like Gus would let
your boy anywhere near him?
He'll break out his box cutter
on his sorry gimp ass.
So you haven't even seen him
since that time at the diner?
Okay.
Think. All right.
They've got to be figuring
that we've talked.
So you need to tell Mike that you
are worried about Hank's investigation.
Okay? Hank already knows
who you are, by the way.
And besides, you actually did kill Gale,
so there's that.
This is all good fodder for you
to request a sit-down with Gus...
...so you can discuss
what you would say for questioning.
Okay? Now, you just say
that you want to be--
No, that you need to be able
to be properly coached.
Then, when you're near him...
...you put this to use.
Mike's just gonna tell me
to shut my mouth if I get busted.
- He ain't gonna set up no meeting.
- Well, then insist on it, damn it!
Act panicked.
Gus' ass is on the line.
He'll meet with you
if he thinks you're a liability.
No. He will waste me
if he thinks I'm a liability.
You know what?
Whatever, man.
I'm gonna take a piss.
I think you got a phone call.
Anything important?
- Yes?
- I did some digging around.
- And?
- Neither the DEA...
...nor the APD considers you
a person of interest.
Schrader is looking into you
totally on his lonesome.
- A voice in the wilderness.
- Does he have resources?
Just him, his credit card
and his chauffeur Walter.
He'd be committing career suicide if he
were to mention you to Merkert again.
- No warrant for that tracking device?
- No.
The guy has gone totally maverick.
He's Miss Daisy with binoculars.
We watch our backs,
we don't throw him any bones.
He'll never make a case.
- What about Chile?
- If! can't find any trace before '89...
...I seriously doubt Schrader can.
Seems to me
the bigger problem is the cartel.
Now, we can handle them
if that's all we've got on our plate.
But dealing with both Schrader
and the Mexicans at the same time?
If he happens to be watching
when they make a move...
...it could be the perfect storm.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
I don't know how many grandmas
and grandpas we got.
Is there a couple of them
in viewing land?
Well, it's "The Grandparent's Polka."
Hello, Hector.
The cartel has given me
its ultimatum.
To which I've said no.
DEA Agent Schrader, he's a concern.
He's looking into my past.
Is today the day, Hector?
Gustavo, sit down.
You're making me nervous.
It's a good plan. Trust yourself.
Everything is going to be okay.
Are you crazy?
The boss is gonna rip your balls off!
What, you gonna tell?
And you?
They ain't gonna say nothing.
They like what they see.
You're not going to offer
our guests anything?
Who says they're guests?
If the boss wants them to drink...
...they drink.
So...the Chicken Brothers.
I like your restaurant.
Dark meat and white meat?
Don't look like no brothers to me.
At last!
The master chefs!
You two ...
That chicken you cook ...
I swear, it has got to be the tastiest
chicken in all of Mexico.
Thank you, Don Eladio.
It's a great honor.
Max is the chef.
The compliments are all his.
Gustavo is too modest.
There'd be no restaurant without him.
Well, however you two do it, keep it up.
Your chicken, it's so...zesty.
Piquant.
But it does not taste
like a Mexican style.
It's a recipe I learned in Chile...
...which I've modified a bit
for the Mexican palate.
I bet we like a little more chili
than you Chileans.
We Mexicans like a good hard kick!
So...if your partner is the chef...
...then who are you?
Don't tell me you are just the taster!
I handle the business operations.
Gustavo is a brilliant businessman.
Es el businessman.
Good, good.
But tell me something.
That chicken, so fabulous...
...so excellent...
Besides that, what else
do you have on your menu?
We have several side dishes.
Rice. Beans.
Sometimes we prepare
a carnitas entrée...
...if we come across fresh beef
in the market.
Anything else?
Come on, be honest.
There is nothing else you offer?
A little taste of something else?
Something on the side?
Because when I send my men
to your restaurant...
...they come back
with more than just chicken.
They come back with drugs.
Regresan high.
You are selling them narcotics.
Methamphetamine.
With all due respect, Don Eladio.
I didn't sell it to them.
I gave them samples.
Samples.
Some businessman.
I gave them samples to give to you.
To introduce you to our product.
Don Eladio, Gustavo meant no offense.
But he...that is to say we...
...could think of no other way
to get your attention.
We want to work with you, Don Eladio.
I know all about methamphetamine.
That's poor man's cocaine.
Only bikers and hillbillies use it.
There's no money in it.
May I, Don Eladio ...
I am a biochemist by training.
The methamphetamine we make
is much superior...
...to the so-called biker crank
you know of.
It is crystallized, like glass.
Purer.
And the chirality of the molecule...
...its very structure, is different.
The narcotic effect is far more potent.
This product is the drug of the future.
It'll triple your profits.
Perhaps quadruple.
They're not only good cooks...
...they're great at shoveling manure.
Right now, you deal almost exclusively
with cocaine.
But the coca plant can't grow
in Mexico.
You are no more than middlemen...
...for the Colombians.
They cut you a percentage for
smuggling across the border.
But the lion's share
of the profits goes to them...
...despite your assumption
of all the risk.
This new crystal methamphetamine ...
it's stronger,
more addictive than cocaine...
...which means
it will move in higher volume.
But most importantly,
it's completely artificial.
We can show you
how to manufacture it...
...right here in Mexico.
And you keep all the profits.
My men do like your product.
Hector, what is wrong with you?
Why did you not get glasses
for our guests?
Go on.
You are quite the talent.
I bet you learned cooking
from your mama. isn't that true?
But...what about the chemistry?
I studied at the University of Santiago.
Gustavo paid for my education.
Oh, really?
I have degrees in both biochemistry
and chemical engineering.
With minimal capital investment...
...we can set up
a factory-grade laboratory for you.
Train your own people
to manufacture large quantities...
...of highly pure methamphetamine.
Fantastic!
Tell me one thing, though.
If you're the cook ...
Why do I need him?
Señor?
You.
Businessman.
Why should I negotiate with someone
who doesn't respect me?
Who insults me by dealing
under my nose without my permission?
Who manipulates me into a meeting...
...in front of my own men?
What do I need you for?
Don Eladio. Please.
I didn't sell anything.
I apologise if you are offended...
...by my method
of obtaining this meeting.
I merely took the initiative.
I meant no insult.
Don Eladio,
Gustavo didn't mean to offend.
I know Gustavo like a brother.
He's an honorable man.
The most loyal man I have ever known.
He rescued me
from the Santiago slums.
He made me the man I am today!
Gustavo is a genius.
He will make you millions!
Just find it in your heart to forgive him
this one small mistake.
Please...
He's my partner.
I need him! I swear to God!
Look at him.
You did this to him.
Now, look at him.
Listen to me.
The only reason you are alive
and he is not...
...is because I know who you are.
But understand ...
You are not in Chile any more.
My advice ...
Stick to chicken.
Look at me, Hector.
Look at me.
Maybe next time.