- Number 17, please.
- That'll be fine, thank you.
Goodbye. Thank you so much.
Hello, Fawlty Towers.
Oh, hello, Mr Hawkins.
- I've arranged your car for 2:00.
- Thank you.
Well, you did say today, Mr Hawkins.
- You do accept cheques?
- With a banker's card, yes.
Well, we have to cancel the order then.
Yes. No, no, 5:00 will be fine.
Goodbye.
Polly, Brenda can't start till Monday.
Would you mind doing
the rooms until then?
- Oh, no. I could do with the money.
- Oh, good.
There you are.
Thank you, Mr Yardley.
Oh, hello. Can I help you?
- Yes...
- Girl,
would you give me change for this, please?
In one moment.
I'm just dealing with this gentleman.
- Yes, Mr Thurston...
- What?
- I was wondering...
- I need change for this!
In a moment.
I'm dealing with this gentleman.
But I have a taxi driver waiting.
Surely this gentleman wouldn't mind
if you just gave me change.
- Do you?
- No, no. Go ahead.
- There you are.
- Thank you.
Can you tell me
how to get to Glendower Street?
Now, I've booked a room and bath
with a sea view for three nights.
- Glendower Street?
- Yes.
You haven't finished with me.
Missus...
Mrs Richards.
Mrs Alice Richards.
Mrs Richards,
Mr Thurston.
Mr Thurston, Mrs Richards.
Mr Thurston is the gentleman
I'm attending to at the moment.
What?
Mr Thurston is
the gentleman I'm attending...
Don't shout. I'm not deaf.
Mr Thurston was here before
you, Mrs Richards.
But you were serving me!
I gave you change,
but I hadn't finished dealing with him.
Now, Glendower Street...
Isn't there anyone else in attendance?
Really, this is the most appalling service!
What a good idea!
Manuel, could you lend Mrs Richards
your assistance in connection
with her reservation?
Now...
I've reserved a very quiet room
with a bath and a sea view.
I specifically asked for a sea view
in my written confirmation,
so please make sure I have it.
Qué?
- What?
- Qué?
- K?
- Sí.
C?
KC?
KC? What are you trying to say?
No, no, no, no.
Qué: What.
K-watt?
Sí. Qué... What.
- C.K. Watt?
- Yes!
Who is C.K. Watt?
Qué?
Is he the manager, Mr Watt?
- Manager!
- He is?
Ah, Mr Fawlty!
- What?
- Fawlty!
What are you talking about,
you silly little man?
What is going on here?
I ask him for my room,
and he tells me
the manager's a Mr Watt, aged 40.
No. No, no. Fawlty.
"Faulty"? What's wrong with him?
It's all right, Mrs Richards.
He's from Barcelona.
The manager's from Barcelona?
No, no, no. He's from Swanage.
- And you're in 22.
- What?
You're in room 22.
Manuel, take these cases
up to 22, will you?
Very nice stay, Mr Fawlty.
Ah, glad you enjoyed it.
Polly, would you get Mr Firkin's
bill, please?
When will we see you again?
Oh, not for a few weeks.
You're not by any chance
a betting man, Mr Fawlty?
Er... Well, I used to be.
Only there's a very nice little filly
running at Exeter this afternoon.
- Really?
- Dragonfly.
Ah.
- Dragonfly?
- Yeah.
It's well worth a flutter,
but pay the tax on it before...
Oh, delighted you enjoyed your stay.
Very nice.
Hope to see you again before long.
- There you are.
- Thank you.
Goodbye, Mrs Fawlty.
Goodbye, Mr Firkin.
A satisfied customer.
We should have him stuffed.
Oh, Mr Fawlty,
3:00, Exeter, Dragonfly.
Right?
Yes, good luck!
Jolly...jolly good luck with it.
Morning, Major.
Good morning, Fawlty.
Yes, dear?
What was that about
the 3:00 at Exeter, Basil?
Oh, some horse
he's gonna bet on, I expect.
You're looking very spruce
this morning, Major.
- St. George's Day, old boy.
- Really?
Got a horse, have you?
What's his name?
Did you catch it, dear?
Dragonfly, Major.
- Going to have a flutter, Fawlty?
- No, no, no, no, no.
No, Basil doesn't bet any more, Major.
Do you, dear?
No, I don't, dear, no.
That particular avenue of pleasure
has been closed off for me.
And we don't want it
opened up again, do we, Basil?
No, you don't, dear. No.
The great warning-off
of May 8th, yes.
Good old Saint George, eh, Major?
Well, he killed a hideous
fire-breathing old dragon, didn't he?
Ran it through with a lance, I believe.
Mr Fawlty! Mr Fawlty!
Is Missus...room no like.
She want speak to you. Is problem.
Ever see my wife making toast, Polly?
Why... Why'd he kill it anyway, Fawlty?
I don't know, Major.
Better than marrying it.
Marrying it?
But he didn't have to kill
it, though, did he?
I mean, he could've, uh,
just not turned up at the church.
Good morning, madam.
Can I help you?
- Are you the manager?
- I am the owner, madam.
- What?
- I am the owner.
I want to speak to the manager.
- I am the manager, too.
- What?
I am the manager as well.
Manager. He manager.
Oh, you're Watt.
I'm the manager!
- What?
- I'm the manager!
Yes, I know. You've just told me.
What's the matter with you?
Now, listen to me.
I booked a room with a bath.
When I book a room with a bath,
I expect to get a bath.
You've got a bath.
I'm not paying £7.20p per night, plus V.A.T.,
for a room without a bath!
Here is your bath.
You call that a bath?
It's not big enough to drown a mouse.
It's disgraceful!
I wish you were a mouse. I'd show you.
And another thing.
I asked for a room with a view.
Deaf, mad, and blind.
This is the view as far
as I can remember, madam.
Yes, yes, this is it.
When I pay for a view,
I expect something more interesting than that.
That is Torquay, madam.
That is not good enough.
Well, may I ask what you
were expecting to see
out of a Torquay hotel bedroom window?
Sydney Opera House, perhaps?
The Hanging Gardens of Babylon?
Herds of wildebeest
sweeping majestically...
Don't be silly.
I expect to be able to see the sea.
You can see the sea.
It's over there between
the land and the sky.
I need a telescope to see that.
Well, may I suggest
that you consider moving
to a hotel closer to the sea?
Or preferably in it?
Right.
Now, listen to me.
I'm not satisfied, but I've decided to stay here.
However, I shall expect a reduction.
Why, because Krakatoa's
not erupting at the moment?
Because the room is cold,
the bath is too small, the view is invisible,
and the radio doesn't work.
No, the radio works. You don't.
What?
I'll see if I can fix
it, you scabby old bat.
- I think we got something then.
- What?
I think we got something then!
What are you doing?
Qué?
Madam, don't think me rude,
but may I ask,
do you by any chance have a hearing aid?
A what?
A hearing aid!
Yes, I do have a hearing aid.
Would you like me to get it mended?
Mended? It's working perfectly all right.
No, it isn't!
I haven't got it turned on at the moment.
- Why not?
- The battery runs down.
Now, what sort of a reduction
are you going to give me on this room?
- 60% if you turn it on.
- What?
My wife handles all such matters.
I'm sure she will be delighted
to discuss it with you.
I shall speak to her after lunch.
You heard that all right, didn't you?
- What?
- Thank you so much.
Lunch will be served at half past 12:00.
Manuel! Manuel!
Are you going to the betting shop today?
- What?
- Oh, don't you start!
You go betting shop today?
Oh, sí! Betting shop, sí!
Now, I want you to put this
on this little horse,
Dragonfly, but... Big secret.
Sybil no know.
No, no, it's lovely.
It's just a bit buttery with my skin.
I think I need something more... more...
Topazy, for my colouring,
you know, more tonal.
Have you got...
Have you got Cosmopolitan there?
Page 42, you see Burt Reynolds?
Well, there's a girl standing behind him
looking at James Caan.
That sort of colour.
Mm.
Lovely. All right, I'll be in at 11:00.
- Oh, Polly...
- Hmm?
I've got to check the laundry.
Could you keep an eye on reception for me?
Sure.
Polly, Polly, where Mr Fawlty?
I don't know. What's the matter?
I have money for him.
He win on horse,
but big secret, shh!
Mrs Fawlty, shh!
Well, give it to me. I'll give it to him.
Good afternoon, Miss Gatsby.
Good afternoon, Miss Tibbs.
Good afternoon.
First they give me
a room without a bath,
then there's no lavatory paper!
Would you like some of ours?
We keep an extra supply.
Yes. Would you like some of ours?
Hello! Girl, there's no paper in my room.
Why don't you check these things?
That's what you're being
paid for, isn't it?
- We don't put it in the rooms.
- What?
We keep it in the lounge.
In the lounge?
I'll get you some.
Do you want plain ones,
or ones with our address on it?
Address on it?
How many sheets?
Well, how many are you going to use?
Manager!
Just enough for one? Tell me.
Manager! Manager!
Yes? Testing... testing...
There you are. I've never met
such insolence in my life!
I come down here
to get some lavatory paper,
and she starts asking me
the most insulting,
personal things
I've ever heard in my life!
I thought she wanted writing paper.
- I'm talking to you, Watt!
- Watt?
Are you deaf?
I said I'm talking to you.
I've never met such insolence in my life.
She said people use it in the lounge.
- Yes, she thought...
- Then she starts asking me...
- No, please listen...
- appalling questions about...
I can explain. No, you see,
she thought you wanted to write.
Wanted a fight?
I'll give her a fight, all right!
- No, no, no. Wanted to write!
- What?
Wanted to write. On the paper.
Why should I want to write on it?
I'll have some sent up
to your room immediately.
Manuel!
That doesn't work either.
What were you saying just now?
- Turn it on.
- What?
Turn it...
Turn it on.
I can't read that.
I need my glasses.
Where are they?
They're on your head, Mrs Richards.
I've lost them.
They're the only pair I've got.
I can't read a thing without them.
Excuse me!
- Now, I had them this morning...
- Mrs Richards...
When I was buying the vase...
I put them on to look at it,
and then I had them at tea time...
Mrs Richards!
Your glasses are there!
There? Who put them in there?
No, no, no! On your head!
- What?
- On your... Look,
on...
I'm sorry about that, Mr Fawlty.
Manuel asked me to give this to you.
Oh! Thank you, Polly, and, Polly...
Not a word to the dragon, eh?
- No.
- Right.
Oh, Manuel,
get some loo paper, muchos, for 22.
Uh, twent... Sí.
Are you blind?
There were on my head all the time.
Didn't you see?
- Yes.
- Didn't God give you eyes?
Yes, but I don't use 'em,
'cause it wears the batteries out.
Send my paper up immediately.
What's all that?
22.
Evening, Terry.
Do you like Cavaliera Rusticana, Terry?
I've never had it, Mr Fawlty.
You're in a good mood, Mr Fawlty.
Had a little bit of luck on the gee-gees.
Not a word to the "trouble and strife," eh?
♪ Oh, de Camptown Ladies sing this song
♪ Doo dah, doo dah
♪ Camptown racetrack five miles long
♪ Doo-dah doo-dah day
♪ Goin' to run all night
♪ Goin' to run all day
♪ Gonna bet me money on the bobtail nag...
♪ I did it my way ♪
Can't stand Frank Sinatra.
You make me feel so young. Rubbish.
You seem very jolly, Basil.
Hmm?
You seem very jolly.
Jolly?
Yes, jolly. Sort of... Happy.
Oh, happy. Yes, I remember that.
Not that I noticed, dear, no.
I'll report it if it happens, though.
Well, you look happy to me, Basil.
No, I'm not, dear.
All that dancing about,
singing and rubbing your hands.
Just my way of getting
through the day, dear.
The Samaritans were engaged.
I thought maybe you were in love. Hah!
Only with you, light of my life.
Or had a bit of luck or something.
Did Mr Hawkins deliver the tonics, Terry?
Yes, he did, Mrs Fawlty.
Manuel! Manuel!
Oh, your horse, it win! It win!
Shah! Shah! Manuel...
You know nothing.
You always say, Mr Fawlty,
but I learn.
- What?
- I learn, I learn.
- No, no...
- I get better!
No, you don't understand.
- I do!
- No, you don't.
I... I do understand that...
Shah! Shah!
You know nothing about the horse.
I know nothing about the horse.
Yes.
Ah.
Which horse?
What?
Which horse I know nothing?
My horse, nitwit!
Your horse, nitwit?
No, no, Dragonfly!
- It won!
- Yes, I know!
I know it won, too!
I put money on for you.
You give me money,
I go to betting shop...
Yes, I know, I know!
Why you say I know nothing?
Look, look, look...
You know the horse?
Uh... Nitwit or Dragonfly?
Dragonfly! There isn't a horse called...
You're the nitwit!
What is "wit-nit"?
It doesn't matt...
I could spend the rest of my life
having this conversation!
Please, please try to understand
before one of us dies!
I try.
You're going to forget everything
you know about Nitwit.
No, no, Dragonfly.
Dragonfly! Yes!
Sí, sí, sí.
Eventually.
What?
Uh, at the end.
No, no, no, forget it now!
Now?
Well, pretend you forget!
Pretend?
Well, don't say anything to anyone
about the horse!
I know that.
You tell me that this morning!
- Basil...?
- So don't do it again!
Yes, dear?
It's Mrs Richards.
A fatal accident?
She's had some money stolen.
Oh, Mr Fawlty,
I tell Polly.
That's all right, but don't tell anyone else,
not even me! You know nothing!
- Basil?
- Yes, dear?
You've got to help me handle this.
She's in a frightful state.
I can't get a word in edgewise.
She's had £85 taken from her room.
I said we'll search everyone,
but she insists we send for the police.
What do we do with someone like that?
She just keeps on!
Mrs Richards, how very nice to see you!
Are you enjoying your stay?
There's no need to shout.
I have my hearing aid on.
Mrs Richards,
I've explained to my husband...
I've just been up to my room.
£85 has been taken from my bag,
which I had hidden under the mattress.
Oh, yes?
It's a disgrace!
I haven't been here a day.
- What sort of staff do you employ?
- Mrs Richards...
If you knew anything at all
about running a hotel,
this sort of thing wouldn't happen!
Well, what have you got
to say for yourself?
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
I haven't got it turned up enough.
Basil!
I said I suggest...
Oh, my head, my head!
Has it come away?
Did you bang your head?
Yes! Yes!
Oh, dear. Let me have a look.
You'd better go and lie down
before something else happens.
Shut up!
Why don't you call the police?
We will, the moment
we've searched the rooms.
My money's been taken!
Yes, yes, I know. Try not to speak.
Is this a piece of your brain?
£85.
Take my arm.
I don't need your arm, thank you.
I can get down the stairs
perfectly well by myself.
Down the stairs?
Don't stop when you get to the basement.
Keep straight on.
Give my regards to the earth's core.
Are you sure you can manage?
And if you give us any more trouble,
I shall visit you in the small hours
and put a bat up your nightdress.
Well, that was fun, wasn't it?
The odd moment like that,
almost worth staying alive for, isn't it?
It's nice to share a moment like that,
isn't it? It's what marriage is all about.
I know. I read it on
the back of a matchbox.
Basil, sometimes...
Seriously, Sybil, do you remember
when we were first...
manacled together?
We used to laugh quite a lot.
Yes, but not at the same time, Basil.
That's true. That was a warning, I guess.
Should have spotted that, shouldn't I?
Zoom! "What was that?"
"That was your life, mate."
"Oh. That was quick. Do I get another?"
"Sorry, mate, that's your lot."
Basil.
Back to the world of dreams. Yes, dear?
What are we going to do?
Give it another 15 years?
- About the money. Do you...
- Aw, she's left it in her room,
or eaten it or something.
We'll get Manuel to go through the room.
Polly can check the lounge...
- I saw Polly with money just now.
- Well, there you are.
Quite a bit, too.
She was counting it in here.
Well, it's probably hers.
No, she's been very short lately.
I'll ask her...
Well, you can't.
You can't just ask her like that.
- Why not?
- It would be terribly rude,
asking someone if money is theirs.
That would be so embarrassing!
Rubbish, Basil.
Hello, Fawlty Towers.
Polly Sherman?
Yes, certainly, I'll get her straightway.
Hang on.
Polly!
Terry, where's Polly?
In there.
- She saw you with the money!
- What?
She saw you counting
the horse money!
She's just coming...
Oh, hello, dear.
Here she is. Found her in here.
As I was just saying, Polly,
my wife would like a word with you
about a slightly delicate matter.
It's not delicate, Basil. Don't be silly.
He thinks it's embarrassing
for me to ask you
about that money I saw you with
earlier on in the office.
I wondered if someone had handed it in.
Mrs Richards has lost some.
The money? In the office?
You were counting it, weren't you?
Did someone hand it in?
Oh, no.
No, it's mine.
Yours?
I won it.
You won it?
On the horse Mr Fawlty got a tip on.
I hope you don't mind, I...
No, no, not at all.
I didn't know you bet on the horses, Polly.
Oh, I don't.
Only I was in the town,
and I passed the betting shop,
and I thought, "Well, why not?"
Well, why not indeed?
Jolly good question, eh, dear?
Pity you didn't let me
put something on, really.
You realise how much we would've won?
£75 for a £5 stake. Still, you know best.
Those were the odds, were they, Basil?
Yes, that's right, dear. 14-1.
I listened in on the wireless
just to make sure it had triumphed.
Enjoy your winnings, Polly.
- Thank you.
- Polly.
- Yes, Mrs Fawlty?
- What was the name of the horse?
The name? Uh...
I've gone blank.
- Birdbrain!
- Birdbrain?
No, no, that came in third.
Uh...
Fishwife!
- What?
- No...
No, not that. Small...
Fly! Fly!
Flying Tart!
No, no, no, it got off to a flying start,
and it's name...
was Dragonfly!
Thank you, Polly.
If I find out the money
on that horse was yours,
you know what I'll do, Basil.
You'll have to sew 'em back on first.
- Ah, Major!
- 6:00, old boy.
Oh, so it is. Uh, Major...
Can I offer you, uh...
Oh, very decent of you. Just a quick one.
Going to a memorial service.
Ah.
Tie's a bit bright, isn't it, Major?
- What?
- For a memorial service?
Oh, I didn't like the chap.
One of those. Know what I mean?
- Cheers.
- Uh, Major...
Could you do me a favour?
Well, I'm a bit short myself, old boy.
No, no, could you look
after some money for me?
I won it on that horse.
Only Sybil's a bit suspicious, you see?
She goes through my pockets some nights.
Oh, absolutely. Which horse?
- Uh, Dragonfly.
- When's it running?
No, it ran today. I won that on it.
Oh. Well done, old boy.
No, could you keep it?
No, I couldn't do that,
very decent of you...
No, could you keep it just tonight?
It's Sybil, you see? Secret.
Ah, a present.
Sort of, yes.
Don't mention it.
Mum's the word.
I'll get it from you in
the morning and bank it.
Understood, old boy.
Cheers.
There you are, Mr Mackintosh.
- Good morning, Mr Fawlty.
- Good morning, ladies.
Hello. Fawlty Towers.
Watt!
I didn't say anything.
Have you called the police yet?
Excuse me, I'm trying
to take a telephone call.
Have you called them yet?
- Yes, yes, we have.
- When are they going to be here then?
As soon as possible.
They're very busy today.
Busy. Humph!
Lot of bloodshed at the Nell Gwen
Tea Rooms last night. Hello?
Certainly, yes. Mrs Richards?
Mrs Richards! Sorry.
Telephone for you.
- Here.
- Yes?
What's this for?
- Uh, telephone calls?
- But I haven't made any.
- Uh... Cigarettes?
- I don't smoke.
There's nobody there.
Hello? Yes, yes, I know she is.
Yes. It's your sister!
Well, what is it for?
Umm... Drinks?
Drinks? Me?
We've been cut off.
Hello?
Look, you tell me, and I'll tell her.
Even the phones don't work.
Your sister says you've had an offer
of £87,000 for your house in Brighton.
87,000? Give it to me.
Don't be a fool, Stephanie.
92,750 I said, and I'm not taking
a penny less. You tell him that.
Why don't people listen?
Well?
Well, let's scrub that 32p then, shall we?
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Oh, thank you very much.
Oh, Major! Major! Um, can I have it now?
- What, old boy?
- The money.
The money I gave you last night?
What... What is all this about?
You remember I gave you some money
just before you went
to that remembrance service?
- Remembrance service?
- Yes.
I don't remember that, old boy.
It was for a chap you didn't like.
- You know, he was one of those?
- One of those what?
Well...
- Pansy?
- Yes.
Which one?
No, no, no, no.
You were in your best suit.
Was I? Oh, yes, of course!
I went to the theatre, of course!
- No, no...
- Yes, yes, with Winnie Atwell, yes.
Winnie Atwell?
Well, Marjorie Atwell then, Marjorie.
I always call her Winnie because...
Well, because she looks like Winnie.
She's not black.
Black? Churchill wasn't black.
Look, look, look,
I gave you £75. You put it in there.
What do you mean by telling me
you called the police?
You've done no such thing.
Your wife's just told me
you're still searching the rooms.
Well, I thought she'd called them.
You lying hound!
- Mrs Richards...
- Go and call them now, immediately.
Mrs Richards, we will,
the moment we've searched...
Right. I shall call them myself then.
Couldn't we just wait until...
I've never seen such a place!
All right, Mrs Richards.
Would you like to use
the office phone?
What?
In here. Thank you.
Basil! Get the key and check her room.
Right.
I found it, Fawlty!
It was in my pocket! Yes, in my new suit!
- Major, shh!
- In here, you see?
- Stuffed right down.
- Can I have it?
I don't know how it got there,
you, see, because I make a point
of keeping my money in my hip pocket.
Yes, please! Please!
- What, old boy?
- Can I have it?
Oh, yes, yes, the money.
Yes, yes, of course.
Good God, it's gone!
No, no, in there!
- Basil?
- Here it is!
- What's that?
- I found it, Mrs Fawlty.
The money.
Oh, that's marvellous! Mrs Richards!
- What?
- We found your money.
- No!
- The Major's found your money.
- No! N...
- What?
Thank you so much, Major.
There you are.
I told you it would turn up.
What is it, Basil?
Bit of luck, eh, Fawlty?
It's £10 short.
Oh, dear.
It's not!
£10 short?
Oh, my God!
Don't worry, we'll have a whip round!
Basil, stop!
What's he doing now?
What on earth do you
think you're doing?
I'll look for the missing £10 immediately,
Mrs Richards.
- Where exactly did you find it, Major?
- In my pocket.
- In your pocket?
- Yeah, yeah. Not this suit. In my new suit.
Would you mind if I popped up
and had a look?
No, no, not at all.
I'll see if I can find it.
Won't be a moment.
Uh, it's in with the, um, the, uh...
- Did you say it was in your pocket?
- Yes, yes.
What was it doing in your pocket?
Can I explain?
You're not explaining anything.
You're completely loopy.
Mad as a March hare!
Yes, yes, I am.
Yes, I am completely loopy.
That's why I gave him
the money to look after.
You see, there's been a mistake.
That money there is in fact mine.
- Yours?
- Yes, as the Major will confirm,
you see, I was saving it up
for a present for my wife.
That's why I couldn't say
anything just now,
but I gave it to the Major last night...
What rubbish! This is my money.
- No, the Major will verify what I've said.
- Hmm?
- Could you verify that, Major?
- What, old boy?
Hush... The money.
I gave you last night,
for my wife's present?
I gave it to you
- just before you went to the theatre?
- The theatre?
Well... Yes. You... You remember?
That money I won on the horses!
A horse?
Why are you whispering?
What are you saying?
- He says he won it on a horse.
- Won it on a horse?
Shah! It doesn't matter!
Do you remember me giving it to you?
Oh, think! Please think!
What was the question again?
Oh, the money, the money! Do you...
Manuel! Manuel!
You remember I had some money yesterday?
The money I won on the horse?
Oh, sí.
Tell Mrs Richards.
Tell her I had the money yesterday.
Ahem-hem!
I know nothing.
What? What?
- No, no...
- Nothing.
No, no, forget that!
I forget everything. I know nothing.
- You can tell her!
- No, I cannot.
Yes, yes, tell her!
Tell her. Please! Please!
Tell her. Tell her!
Tell her! Tell her, or I'll kill you!
Oh. Ha ha!
No, I know nothing.
I am from Barcelona.
I'm not listening
to any more of this rubbish!
I'm going to finish my breakfast,
and when I come back,
I want the rest of my money.
Give it to her, Basil.
I can't find it. Give her 10 from the till.
Right!
What are you doing?
I'm going to give her
the shirt off my back, too!
You see? I know nothing.
I'm gonna send you to a vivisectionist.
Now...
Good afternoon, Mr Fawlty.
Good afternoon.
You got a Mrs Richards staying here?
- Yes.
- Oh. Ah, well,
only she bought this yesterday,
asked us to deliver it.
The thing is,
she left some money behind.
Keeps it in this.
95 quid. Look.
The cleaner found it this morning.
Almost threw it in the bin. Lucky, eh?
Is she around?
Nope. I'll give it to her.
Oh. Thanks, Mr Fawlty. Goodbye.
Mm... Mwah!
We found her money!
Where?
She... It doesn't matter.
I'm £10 up on the deal!
£10 up?
Yes, it's 95... Even if I give her 10,
I'm still 10 up!
Polly, for the first time in my life, I'm ahead!
I'm winning!
Hello, Mrs Richards.
How lovely to see you.
Your beautiful vase that you bought
yesterday has just arrived. Now, remind me,
the money that you have there,
is it yours or mine?
I told you. It's mine.
You're absolutely sure?
Yes, I am.
- But you're still £10 short?
- Yes.
Polly, give Mrs Richards this, would you?
What's that?
This is mine.
What's that, Basil?
- It's mine.
- What?
It's the money I won on the horse.
Oh, yes, right. Polly asked me
to put it in the safe for her.
So, that's all sorted out,
and this is your money, Polly.
And this is your beautiful vase,
Mrs Richards.
Fawlty!
You did give me that money!
You won it on that horse!
Aah!
That cost £75!
Oh, I am sorry, Mrs Richards.
We must pay you back. There you are. One...