(bellowing)
Yee-haw-ho-ho!
(school bell ringing)
(bears growling)
(whistle blows)
♪ The Simpsons 26x09 ♪
I Won't Be Home for Christmas
Original Air Date on December 7, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(playing "Jingle Bells")
(playing bluesy riff)
♪ ♪
(growls)
(snarling)
(squawking)
(cats yowling)
(Cat Lady jabbering)
D'oh!
(bicycle bell jingling)
(grunts)
BART: Ay, caramba!
(groans)
Carrot.
(humming)
You are about to see
the worst half-hour
of television ever.
All righty then.
♪ ♪
Okay, R3, let's
serve up some soup.
(whistling)
May the sauce be with you.
Oh, since when is soup sauce?
This is so non-canonical.
You have every right
to be furious.
Oh, it's as bad
as I remembered,
and I haven't watched
it since yesterday.
Horrible, yet enthralling.
Hooray!
A card from Dr. Hibbert.
(gasps)
Phew.
Oh.
(bird squawks)
I'll be right home, honey.
I just got to lock down
the reactor for the evening.
Tight as a drum.
See you soon.
Bart, hold the ladder still!
(gasps)
(grunts)
Oh!
Wish Homer was here.
Simpson!
(gasps)
Mr. Scrooge!
Time for your holiday gift.
Ooh!
In your name, a donation has been made...
(groans)
...to the Salvation Army.
Also, you will be visited
by three spirits tonight.
No, wait. That's my schedule.
Smithers, We need to cancel
the 10:30 spirit.
Yes, sir.
(Marge humming)
MARGE: Hello.
HOMER:
Heading home, baby.
Nothing's gonna stop me now.
(shrieks)
(groaning)
Maybe a drink
will help me with my driving.
Man, those things go off quick.
♪ Yo. ♪
(guitar plays country melody)
(metal guitar plays)
♪ Ah! ♪
VIN SCULLY:
...and the baseball exclaimed
as it flew out of sight,
this ballpark is shorter
in left field than right.
Martinez swings and misses.
Yes! I'm recording this
during a game.
Since the United States
government
declares this man
to be Santa Claus,
this court will not dispute it.
Few people know that verdict
was overturned in the sequel.
(chuckles)
I better be heading
home to my family.
Enjoy your evening
with your wonderful...
uh... neon sign.
Yeah, last year I broke it just
so the repairman would come.
But I'll be fine.
Hey, um, you gonna be okay?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Super! (crying)
It's just that...
you know, I lost my ma
at Christmas.
(sighs)
She took me to a mall,
and I never saw her again.
But I'll never forget that image
of her bolting
for the parking lot.
Okay, okay.
I'll stay for one beer.
Oh, great, great.
But don't do it out of pity.
Pity! Pity! Have pity!
Look, I'm wrapped
around your leg here!
Please! Please! Please!
But I promised Marge.
Now I'm sitting on
your shoulders! Please!
Okay, okay!
(Homer groans)
(grunts)
Mom, where's Dad?
I don't know.
Aw, it's Christmas Eve, man!
We do not want
to set a precedent
for fat guys
being late tonight!
(grunts)
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night... ♪
(laughs)
I'm happy on Christmas Eve.
And for once it's not
'cause some drunk
left a wallet on his stool.
Uh-oh, this is
starting to hurt.
(grunts)
And now, Homer, it's only fair
that I give yous a gift.
I'm gonna set the clock
in the bar to the correct time.
HOMER:
Hey, what the...
(gasps)
I am so late!
Whoa, whoa.
It's the night before Christmas!
Stop stirring, you!
(grunts)
(ticking)
One night.
The one night of the year
I want Homer home
with his family,
and he can't even do that.
Christmas is a great time
to dump him.
If you do it now, you won't have
to watch the Super Bowl.
(tires squealing,
car door closing)
Homer Simpson!
(gasps)
I never thought I'd say this
to someone I cared for,
much less my husband,
but I'm saying it now.
I don't want you here
on Christmas!
Marge, think about
what you're saying.
It's Sir Isaac Newton's
birthday.
Out now!
Yeah? Well, good luck
assembling all those
toys without me!
We already did it.
(shrieks)
The ghost of Marge Future!
HOMER:
She'll forgive me.
MARGE:
Should I forgive him?
HOMER:
Especially this time.
MARGE:
Maybe not this time.
HOMER:
I mean it's Christmas.
MARGE: With his marriage
in this much trouble,
he's got a lot
of thinking to do.
HOMER: I wonder if there's birds
on the moon.
(sobbing):
I miss Marge.
I wonder if Lou suspects
that I was his Secret Santa.
What kind of a cheapskate
gives you
one corncob holder
for Christmas?
(chuckles)
Moe, what are you doing?
♪ Good King Wenceslas
looked out ♪
♪ On the feast... ♪
JAPANESE MALE VOICE:
Voice too poor for karaoke.
Shutting down.
Bye now.
Oh, my God.
Santa brought me
just what I asked for!
(laughs)
Hmm. "239."
Who's he fooling?
Hmm... Hmm.
Hmm!
Mm-hmm.
Hey, pal. Can't believe you have
to work Christmas Eve.
Well, if you're here
for a last minute gift,
we have a cell phone
holder that fits
no cell phone
made after 2002.
And, uh, Kwik-E-Nog.
Nog stands for
"Not Okayed by Government."
Maybe Marge would forgive me
if I won the lotto.
Give me a scratcher.
D'oh!
Give me another one.
(groans)
D'oh!
Give me another one.
(groans)
D'oh!
Give me another one.
(groans)
D'oh!
Give me another one.
(groans)
D'oh!
Give me another one.
Oh please, stop! Stop it!
My religion prohibits me
from taking advantage
of a fool more
than ten times.
This thing basically
has no winners.
Yeah, but doesn't
the money goes to schools?
You have been to our schools.
What do you think?
Welcome to Bring Us
Your Toilet Paper night.
Don't worry,
none goes to Willie.
Don't need it.
I got me Starbucks napkins!
You know, ironically, in
India, they did use the money
for schools and they
had fantastic results.
Aw, thanks
for your honesty, Apu.
Is there any other product
in the store
you'd like to warn me about?
Well, uh...
those hot dogs began
life as Twinkies.
(sizzling)
Wow.
(pop, crackling)
(groans)
Christmas Eve.
The one night a kid
wants to go to sleep
is the one night he can't.
I can't have another cocoa.
My pee is starting to
smell like a ski chalet.
(door opens)
Oh, thank God you're here.
I need to get to sleep.
Tell me the story
of jazz again.
Well, the story of jazz starts
with the tresillo,
the most prevalent
duple-pulse rhythmic cell
in sub-Saharan African music.
But the rest will have to wait.
Bart, Bart,
I hear Mom sobbing.
And I don't know where Dad is.
If it helps, I made you a card.
Bart, this is the year
I've got to nail Christmas.
I don't want to be a jaded
ten-year-old like you!
Ah, yes.
I remember Christmas Eve
when I was eight.
MARGE: Why do you always wait
till the last minute
to put up the lights?
HOMER:
I don't want to ruin the magic.
And I certainly... Aah!
(gurgling)
Next year
this is
your job.
(electrical crackling)
(grunting)
Ooh!
Hmm, they say a boy never
gets over seeing his dad
in a Santa suit getting hanged
and electrocuted
on Christmas Eve.
I'll help you, kid.
(sighs heavily)
Mom, I'm just a kid,
but I say if Dad isn't
here Christmas morning,
that's the kind of thing
families never recover from.
Hmm.
Lisa, sweetie,
I'm tired of being a pushover.
You're not a pushover.
You can't smoke.
Just chewing
on the wood.
Okay then.
(clattering)
(groans)
Eh, how you doing there?
Uh, your front
door was locked,
So, uh, rather than
call or knock,
I, uh, came down
your chimbley there.
(coughs)
Moe Szyslak, you didn't
climb down our chimney
just to say
"Merry Christmas."
(coughing)
(clears throat)
Midge, it's one minute
till Christmas,
and if I'm ever gonna be
a good guy, it's now.
All right, here I go.
I'm the one that kept Homer
from coming home,
'cause, uh, well, I was lonely.
(gasps)
Yeah, that's right--
me, Mr. Party Pants.
So, uh, so don't hold
it against Homer, eh?
Oh, my poor Homie.
This is what
I was hoping for.
For it not to have been
completely his fault.
Thank you, Moe.
(mumbling):
Huh?
I'm sorry, Marge,
I'm sorry,
but it was Christmas, and
we were under the mistletoe.
That's lettuce caught
in a spider's web.
All right.
I've got
to call Homer.
(buzzing)
(beeps)
D'oh!
What gives? Don't you get
Showtime Extreme?
(groans)
No answer.
Let's go find
your father.
What?
I never give up hope.
Neither do I.
Even the anchor store's closed.
("Someday at Christmas" plays)
♪ Someday at Christmas ♪
♪ Men won't be boys ♪
♪ Playing with bombs ♪
♪ Like kids play with toys ♪
♪ One warm December
our hearts will see ♪
♪ A world where men are free ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ Someday at Christmas... ♪
Any uplifting
holiday movies?
Well, let's see.
We've got a film about
a nutty professor...
Ooh.
...with advanced
Alzheimer's.
D'oh!
Seth Rogen and Jonah Hill...
Yeah?
...in a concentration
camp drama.
D'oh!
And a cute model...
Ooh!
...airplane that
lost its propeller.
Um, I guess I'll take
the concentration camp one.
And a Merry Christmas
to you, sir.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Well, if I got to spend
Christmas Eve alone,
at least no one will see me.
Hey-ya, Homer!
(barking)
Ah, just 'cause you're here
shouldn't make you sad.
This is my 17th Christmas
alone in a movie theater.
This is my family.
The guy with
the smelly pants,
the lady that carries
empty cans in a PBS tote bag.
Ugh, what if I left now and gave
you guys my popcorn and soda?
(cat meows)
Wow, Homer, you have
a very generous side.
Can I borrow,
like, $10,000?
Flanders?
What are you doing here?
Christmas is
my busy season.
Sold three pairs of
scissors this month.
Two came back.
Say, Flanders,
with all the hard luck you've
had, how do you stay so happy?
And don't say
"Jesus."
Well, sir, our good Lord and
my boys are all I've really got.
All Edna left me was
wonderful memories
and some
ungraded papers,
which I'm still working
my way through. (sniffles)
Flanders,
are you crying?
Ah, just snowflakes
on my mustache.
Listen, could I buy
a left-handed, uh...
I don't know,
eyelash curler?
Sure, but y-your eyelashes are
long and luxurious already.
Are you just buying this
to be nice?
Uh, maybe.
Oh, Homer, unto us this
day, a neighbor is born.
But why?
Because jerk-ass Homer
has become ass-jerk Homer.
Well, that curled my
lashes, but good for you.
(chuckles)
You're all right,
stupid Flanders.
You're all right.
Well, this is a whole new
relationship for us.
We'll be friends
in this life and the next.
HOMER:
Whoa, he's getting serious.
Is this what I really want?
(whimpering)
My best friend is
a great runner.
I made everyone happy but me.
Some Christmas.
(sobbing):
Feliz navidad.
(wind whistling)
(vehicle approaching,
tires screeching)
Abe Simpson, please.
Visitor for
Abe Simpson.
You came!
You came to see me!
(Bart grunting)
Aw!
Easter came early
this year.
I thought we were just
gonna ask if he'd seen Homer.
I'm afraid we've
awoken a needy giant.
Visitors!
Let's brew some weak tea and
talk about the good ol' days!
Make them turn
the TV to CBS!
("Hark! The Herald
Angels Sing" plays)
(electrical crackling)
Well, with all that you
folks have experienced,
I think we could enjoy listening
to a little of your wisdom.
The problem with
Puerto Ricans is...
No casual racism.
(snoring)
(muttering)
What the...?
The Nutcracker.
Every child's favorite
Christmas character.
Is this a dream?
Not a dream.
I work at the mall.
And it's closed, so scram.
Man, you are a nutcracker.
But I've learned
something tonight--
you know how everyone hates
being with their family on Christmas?
Uh-huh.
Well, being without them
is worse.
Can you find it in your wooden
heart to give me a break?
All right, listen,
pal, uh...
you want to go
to a party?
(dance music plays)
What are you
doing here?
Halloween merchandise goes
on sale December 26, man.
("O Holy Night" plays)
Well, he's not in
the neon sign store.
Lady, buy a sign
or go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to find my husband,
and nothing's open.
Well, there is
a party here.
Hey, is your husband into
people dressed like food?
Where is this party?!
(electrical crackling)
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
Is that girl really doing that?!
Mm, load-bearing wall.
(whoops)
(moans)
Ho, ho, ho!
This party's great,
but all I wish is
that I was drinking a beer
with my kids right now.
MARGE: Homer?
Hmm?!
Homie, I'm
your present tonight.
And the present is that
I'm not gonna always assume
that you screwed up.
Because I realize maybe
there's a good explanation
for what you do.
Or a crazy one that's
pretty entertaining.
Oh, Marge,
you found me!
You always find me.
Now we just have to find your
car in the mall parking lot.
I thought I had one of
those chirping keys.
Oh, well, I've been
faking the noise.
'Cause you deserve
the best.
(imitates car chirp)
You didn't have
to do that.
I love you
just the same.
(imitates car chirp)
(moaning)
Thank you magical creatures
of the mall!
You have all taught me
a Christmas message
I'll never forget--
the place to get drunk
is at home.
("Dance of the Sugar Plum Fairy"
plays)
All right, I'm
sick of waiting.
Bart, you know you
can't open a present
till Mom and
Dad wake up.
(scoffs)
It's 9:10 a.m.
I know what they're doing--
they're up in bed
watching the re-broadcast of
the Hollywood Christmas Parade.
Oops, my finger slipped.
Oops! So did mine.
(laughing)
Oh, I got a baseball glove.
I got a chemistry set.
I want yours.
Merry Christmas,
son.
Uh, don't you mean
"Happy Birthday"?
It's two presents.
Um, walkie-talkies don't
count as two presents.
God.
I mean, you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
JESUS:
Idiot.
Behold, our
miracle of birth.
Each birth is followed
by another birth
just seconds later.
(grunting)
What the?!
This isn't Halloween.
Shh!