(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(grunting)
♪ The Simpsons 26x08 ♪
Covercraft
Original Air Date on November 23, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(snoring)
(groans)
(humming)
Well, if ain't
my next-door neighbor,
King Toot.
Moe.
How many times I
got to tell you
not to throw your trash
in my Dumpster?
Oh, come on, Szyslak.
I got to make space in the store
for my new side business--
a tanning salon that secretly
has cameras in the beds,
which feeds into my Web site,
www.tancams.com.
That is registered.
Yeah, sounds great.
Maybe then you could afford
to rent your own Dumpster.
I like my current deal.
Free. Of. Charge.
(grunting)
I'll eat your hair!
You call that a testicle kick?
(tires screech)
All right, you two, break it up.
Drive on, asphalt cowboy,
or I'll squeeze his brain out
like an edamame.
Eh, uh, a what?
Those beans you eat
before your sushi comes.
Oh, salt peas.
I call them salt peas.
Look, Officer, after 20 years
of being neighbors,
tempers sometimes flare up.
Moe's a good guy.
No, no, no, it's my fault.
I'm a hothead.
I ain't got no beef
with you, Toot.
(whispering): You better stay
out of my Dumpster.
I've also been
stealing the catalogs
out of your mailbox.
(punching,
instruments clattering)
(grunting)
(screaming)
It's my Dumpster!
(screaming continues)
(both growling)
And that's the
terrifying tale
of how the Quebec Nordiques
became...
the Colorado Avalanche.
Oh, no!
King Toot's is closed!
Dad, you're going to have
to take me to...
the big box music store.
Look at all
these monstrosities.
HOMER: Lisa, how many times
have I told you
to bow down
to our corporate overlords?
(Lisa groans)
(doorbell dings)
Hmm.
It's like some kind
of guitar central.
Hmm.
(groans)
Hmm. Hmm.
Midlife crisis
at 12 o'clock.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let me guess, dude.
You're an axman; you're
looking to score a new blade.
Stig.
(chuckles) You've got a name
that's not a name.
So what's your poison, bro?
Les Paul?
Straight up Gibson?
No, no, no, classic Strat,
am I right?
Oh, I don't have what it takes
to play guitar.
I mean, I'm no Joe Walsh
in the brains department.
(chuckles) Who is?
Look, you don't have the weak,
womanly fingers
of a guitar princess.
You, my friend,
have the muscular stumps
of a bass man.
Try this on.
(note plays loudly)
What the rock?
(chuckles)
Now that was a lick.
I did a lick?
Keep them coming.
(notes repeating)
Yes, now bob your head.
Bob it, bob it, bob it.
Dude, usually it takes years
to learn such neck confidence.
Now check this out.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
I'm amazing.
Dude, you're already
one of the greatest bass
players of all time.
Okay.
Now... Oh, how are you set
for stage lights?
I'm not set at all.
Ooh, what about gels?
This is embarrassing
to admit, Stig,
but I haven't even thought
about gels.
(Marge humming)
(bass playing loudly)
(gasps)
(screams)
What is that racket?!
Music!
Beautiful music!
What?!
Beautiful music, baby.
The bass guitar?
This doesn't really
seem like you.
Sure it is.
You know I've always loved
laying things down.
Grooves are just the latest.
(groans)
I feel a powerful connection
to the history
of famous bass players.
Like what's-his-name
from The Who.
Or that guy from Led Zeppelin
who wasn't Page,
Plant or Bonham.
Those are the only two
I know for sure.
It's so cool to have
another musician in the family!
Oh, yeah, and you know what
the great thing is about music?
It's so easy.
Uh, well, to truly master
an instrument
you'll need years of...
So easy.
(bass playing)
(gasping)
(siren wailing)
(gasps)
(groans)
Oh!
Ooh!
(groans)
MARGE:
I can't take it.
All Homer does
is play that stupid bass.
Doink, doink, doink, doink,
doink, doink, doink.
You're not alone, Marge.
A man gets older,
has a career, a few kids,
and suddenly there's a hole
in his life
that can only be filled
by jamming.
For my Julius,
it was the drums.
Timothy has
that awful guitar.
Kirk just loves his keyboards.
I never knew
so many women suffered
from extramarital jamming.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God.
What if all the dads
jammed together
in a dad band?!
That way they would play
their horrible music
in one garage at a time.
Marge, you're a genius!
This menu was right--
good things do happen
at 'Zerz.
♪ 'Zerz! ♪
(cymbals clattering)
I don't know, guys.
I'm not sure
I'm feeling this.
The bass is kind of known
for being a solo instrument.
What were
our wives thinking?
We probably don't even like
the same tunes.
On the count of three,
everyone say
their favorite kind of music.
One, two, three...
ALL:
Hard-driving rock!
(gasping)
Dads, let's jam!
(rock song playing)
Garage bands rule!
(gasps)
I almost forgot
the most important thing.
(rock song playing)
(song ends)
Great practice, guys.
What do you say we give
it another six hours,
then call it a day?
APU:
Excuse me,
but my wife told me about
your get-out-of-the-house band.
And, uh,
perhaps you need a singer?
Oh, yeah, Apu,
I'm sure you're
a great singer.
But the balance of the band
is really delicate right now,
and we're not really looking
for a world music vibe.
No disrespect to world music.
I love world music.
No, no, I will sing
the classic power ballad
"Hopin' for a Dream"
by my favorite band
from the 1980s, Sungazer.
(clears throat)
Okay, here we go.
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I wish that
I could fantasize ♪
♪ Pull a dream right
out of the air ♪
♪ Take a chance,
turn it into a prayer. ♪
That sounds nothing
like terrible,
terrible world music.
Why is your voice different
when you sing?
It is because of all the years
I spent at the Kwik-E-Mart...
(rock song playing)
...where classic rock anthems
were piped in
on a never-ending loop.
The endless repetition
drove many clerks to madness.
The only way to maintain
my sanity
was to sing along
until it seemed like
our voices were one.
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
♪ Hopin' ♪
♪ Focus like a laser beam ♪
♪ I'll keep fighting
till I want something great ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream. ♪
(song ends)
Guys, are you feeling this?
Are you feeling this?
I'm feeling it.
I'm definitely
feeling it.
I felt something earlier,
but I was afraid to bring it up.
I think we all
felt something.
We are more than just
a garage band
desperate to do anything other
than hang out with our families.
We are now a cover band.
And we shall be called...
Covercraft.
Because we play covers
and this is our craft.
And it sounds
like Hovercraft.
That was not my intent.
Okay, Covercraft, hands in.
Cover...
ALL:
Craft!
R-O-K-C.
(carnival music playing)
(instruments tuning)
Okay, this crowd is
about to experience
the special magic
of the cover band,
the thrill of live music
without the fear
of hearing anything new.
Hmm?
(sighs)
Apu, what's wrong?
What if, what if
I am no good?
This is the
Cabbage Festival, man.
I-I don't know if
I can face that crowd!
(groans)
Buddy, buddy.
Think of it this way:
you're not singing
in front of all those people,
you're alone
at the Kwik-E-Mart
in the middle of the night.
You just wear this onstage,
and everything will be fine.
(gasps)
My uniform!
All alone at the Kwik-E-Mart.
♪ ♪
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I wish that
I could fantasize ♪
♪ Pull a dream
right out of the air ♪
♪ Take a chance ♪
♪ Turn it into a prayer ♪
♪ Girl, you know
I want to be the guy ♪
♪ With a hunger
burning deep inside ♪
♪ Tonight I wish
upon a falling star ♪
♪ To discover what
my yearnings are... ♪
Everyone loves you, Dad.
You could become
a famous rock star!
Well, son,
I do have the talent.
My mind is full of ideas
for great songs I could write...
down the names of
and then cover.
But then I remember:
I'm just a regular guy,
jamming with my buds.
Oh, sweetie.
This band has brought out
the best in you.
Yeah, you really get that
it's all about the music.
Yep.
It's all about the music.
And it would take a pretty
unforeseen development
to change that.
Pretty unforeseen...
Gentlemen, I think we've found
what we're looking for.
HOMER: Guys, I really need
your honesty here.
At the Squidport
Senior Jamboree...
was I too in
the pocket?
(Covercraft members gasp)
KIRK: Freddy Freeman,
Shredder Stevens,
Nick Delacourt and
Peter D'Abbruzio--
you're four of the five guys
from Sungazer!
But where's your lead
singer, Grant LeDavid?
Uh, he passed away.
How?
(whispering)
What kind of erotic
asphyxiation?
(whispering)
Oh...
Apu, you're
the only man
on the entire
Internet
who's got the pure
Sungazer sound.
Will you be our
new lead singer
and join us on
our stadium tour?
Uh...
Oh! Ooh.
I think I can
answer for Apu.
He's flattered,
but the small-time
success of Covercraft
is all that any of us
have ever wanted.
Uh, actually, I...
Apu has a rich life
here in Springfield:
a store full of
great products,
a lovely
him-type wife,
and eight super kids:
Anoop, Sandeep,
Nabendu, Gheet,
Pria, Uma,
Poonam, Sashi...
Shut your mouth,
I want to do it!
I want to be a singer
for a real rock band!
SHREDDER STEVENS:
Sun...
ALL:
...gazer!
Gotta say, I'm
kind of jealous
of Apu getting
a break like that.
Not me.
I'm nothing but happy
that our friend is headed
for fame and fortune.
APU:
Tonight we play Las Vegas--
and the theme of
the casino is circus!
Circus!
Ha!
(whimpers)
I want his fame
and fortune so much!
Why must the Lords
of Rock be so cruel?!
(laughing)
Sammy Hagar?
You're not dead.
Damn it!
I told you those jalapeño
poppers had too much breading!
Sorry,
Señor Hagar.
Nah, nah, nah,
it's cool, man.
I went to rock star heaven.
And there was this great back
patio with this sweet fire pit.
If you had the right
wristband-- which I did.
(laughs)
News story in aisle three?
Local clerk,
Apu Nahasapeemapetilon,
is a dead ringer
for a dead singer.
He's living the rock star dream
as front man for
'80s chart-toppers
Sungazer on their Last Final
Hell Re-Freezes Over
Ultimate Good-bye
For Serious This Time
Never Again Part Two
of Question Mark Tour.
Apu and the band appeared
on Saturday Night Live
as the punch line
in a game show sketch.
What's a game show?
Something you make
sketches about.
KENT BROCKMAN: It looks like Apu
won't be playing
the Cabbage Festival ever again.
Dad, you shouldn't
be jealous of Apu.
Remember, it's all
about the music.
I'm not jealous.
I'm envious.
Jealousy is
when you worry
someone will take
what you have.
Envy is wanting
what someone else has.
What I feel is envy.
Hmm.
Wow, he's
right.
You know what?
Apu leaving is
the best thing
that ever happened
to this band.
We're gonna be
like Genesis
after Peter Gabriel left.
You mean more popular
but not as good?
Phil Collins-era Genesis
is not as good, huh?
"No Reply at All,"
"Land of Confusion,"
"Throwing it All Away,"
"Illegal Alien,"
"I Can't Dance," and I'm sure
I don't need to mention...
"Invisible Touch"!
Hmph!
(Covercraft plays)
(grunts)
You know, we really could
use a new lead singer.
You know, I've been
known to sing a little.
What? So you can also get
famous and bail on us?
You're out of the band!
Well, you can't
just kick him out.
Oh, so you're sticking
up for Yoko here?
Looks like I've got
another Yoko on my hands.
How can there be two Yokos?
Yoko! Yoko!
Yoko! Yoko! Yoko!
All you Yokos
are out of the band!
(grumbling)
Are you okay?
Do I sound okay?
You sound great!
Your licks are really... juicy.
They're not juicy.
My licks are dry.
Dry and scratchy
like a cat's tongue.
You didn't join a band
to become famous like
in Almost Famous.
You loved playing music
with your friends.
That was enough
to make you happy.
Well, it's not enough anymore.
When something great
happens to one person,
everyone else's life
gets a little worse.
Look it up, it's called physics.
Apu is a good man.
He sent over front row tickets
and backstage passes
to his show at
the Costington Center.
Oh, you mean he
generously invited us
to come watch him
be a rock star?
Stop feeling
sorry for yourself.
Your friend had a wonderful
thing happen to him,
and you are coming with us
to share in his talent.
I'll never have
a per Diem.
You don't know
what a per Diem is.
Still want one.
Hmph.
Apu wouldn't be able
to sing a note
if I didn't help him get
over his stage fright
with his Kwik-E-Mart shirt.
(gasps)
Backstage pass,
you just became
a payback rage pass.
Look at all this rock star
dressing room stuff.
What a sellout.
Cheese plate...
oh, sorry, cubed cheese plate.
Lemon tea, probably
for his throat.
Mm-hmm!
Let's see how he performs
in front of all those people
without his magic-people-
performing-in-front-of shirt.
(door opens, Homer gasps)
But, Mr. Shredder,
you promised me
after we played my hometown
I could have a day off.
I also promised
I'd kick heroin.
Hmm?
But the tour is
so hard on my family.
My octuplets are being raised
by roadies and bodyguards.
This is
not proper.
Look, Apu.
For 25 years
we wasted money
on women, drugs
and guitars with
live fish inside.
And now we want
to keep it going.
You signed a contract
for a three-year,
57-country tour
at union scale--
no per Diem.
(gasps softly)
You're in the band.
Oh, well, I guess it's showtime.
(gasps)
Homer?
I'm sorry, Apu.
I thought you were
living your dream life,
so naturally
I wanted to ruin it.
But now I know things stink,
so I'm okay with it.
Oh, what is
the point?
I am trapped like a Kwik-E-Mart
hot dog on a roller.
Kwik-E-Mart hot dog, eh?
You want every hot dog
in the store?
Every one?
Okay...
- Yeah! - Yeah.
- Oh!  -Yeah!
FORUM ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
Tucks Medicated Pads presents...
Sungazer!
(cheering) Yeah!
All right!
Uh, people?
I am sorry to report
that all the original
members of the band
have been struck down
by a mysterious case
of hot dog poisoning.
(groaning)
Rather than refund your money
or reschedule the show,
we have a surprise for you.
Get ready to rock with a group
that is truly all about
the music-- Covercraft!
♪ ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
♪ Hopin' ♪
♪ Focus like a laser beam ♪
♪ I'll keep fighting ♪
♪ Till I want something great ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
(audience cheering)
♪ Hopin' ♪
♪ To someday,
somehow have a goal ♪
♪ I'll keep fighting
till I want something great ♪
♪ I'm hopin' for a dream ♪
♪ Hopin', hopin', hopin' ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
♪ Hopin' ♪
♪ Dreams are great
or so it seems ♪
♪ If I never find one
I guess that's okay ♪
♪ I'm hopin' for a dream... ♪
♪ Hopin', hopin', hopin' ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream, oh... ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
So there I am, on Easter Island,
and the heads ask me
to play them a song.
I say, "Why me, heads?
You've heard the music
of the universe itself."
And they say, "Sammy,
your stuff rocks
just a little harder."
That's when I wake up.
I'm in the Springfield
Elementary parking lot,
doing a buck fifty-five
in my Ferrari 512 Boxer.
I was cornering so hard,
I blacked out
from the Gs, man.
They say I ran over
the groundskeeper.
Probably get life in prison.
But I got a plan to escape,
using only this harmonica
and some guitar picks
with my face on 'em.
Who's with me on this?
(Hagar laughing)