♪ Two... two, three... ♪
Ooh. Wiggle in.
Get comfortable.
Hey, a couch is a couch.
Ooh, yeah.
Yes, there, you see?
Oh, yeah!
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
That's so...
Whoo-hoo!
♪ The Simpsons 26x06 ♪
Simpsorama
Original Air Date on November 9, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Uh, students,
each one of you
has been assigned
the mandatory honor
of contributing
to the Springfield time capsule,
where your arcana
will lie dormant
until the 31st century.
And...
By the time you finish talking,
we're gonna be
opening this
damn capsule.
Right. Time capsule.
Nelson, give me something.
I brought a picture of my dad.
He's still at large...
in my heart!
I brought
my lucky rabbit's foot.
I can have good luck
without it.
Ow!
Wish we could put this moment
in the time capsule.
Consider it done.
Uh, how about you, Bart?
Let me guess-- you forgot
to bring something.
I'm offended you think I forgot.
Let's see.
Ta-da!
Listen, boy, this
is the only legacy
you'll ever leave.
Better make this count.
My sandwich!
And so a thousand years from now
this capsule will be opened
by some future Mayor Quimby.
That-that could be
anyone's ooze.
There.
And now,
to help secure the jazz vote,
Lisa Simpson will
play her saxophone.
Even God hates jazz.
A mysterious electrical storm
is currently wreaking havoc
with our studio.
But I'm not one
of those brainless dolts
who mindlessly reads
a teleprompter-er...
error 401 backslash backslash
colon reset C-drive
shutting down.
What the hell was that?
Probably just another piece
of America's space junk
falling out of orbit.
Remember when this country
didn't suck?
'Cause I don't.
Homer, I think there's
someone downstairs.
Relax, Marge.
It's probably just Homer
coming home late from Moe's.
Hmm.
Ooh, the eyes in that picture
are following me!
Uh, that's a mirror.
Isn't all great art
kind of a mirror?
We'd better send the dog down.
Come on, here's your chance
to protect us, boy.
Come on. C...
Aah!
Stupid dog.
Ow!
Ow.
We'll have to set
a trap, Bait--
I mean, Bart.
All set.
When he starts gnawing at you,
I'll whack him with this broom.
Hmm.
Ooh!
Don't drink
my loved ones!
Oh! Bite my shiny metal ass!
A robot!
With a catchphrase!
Hey, Homer, you gonna kiss him
or kill him?
All right!
Tether-boy!
Okay, so,
what are you?
Must be a secret
government project.
Whoa, what do
I look like, a narc?
My name is Bender,
and I come from...
the future!
Prove it. What happens to
Homer Simpson in the future?
I don't know.
You die?
Oh... my... God.
He's telling the truth.
I have to take you
to our civic leaders.
Hey, hibachi head,
how are you gonna pay for that?
Uh, let me just
transfer some, uh,
electronic hyper-
credits into your
register here.
Ding-da-ding-
ding-ding-ding-
ding-ding!
Ooh, and, uh, another round
for my friends!
Ding-da-ding-ding-
da-ding-ding.
Hey,
this blade rummy is all right.
He's a big spender,
plus he fixed the jukebox.
I think
they had a thing going.
♪ Oh, baby,
what you done to me... ♪
I hate it when
they get quiet.
Listen, uh, I know
you're a robot
and incapable
of emotion...
It's true.
I'm empty inside!
Uh, look, I just want to
ask, can we be friends?
You're the only guy I know
with less hair than me.
Sure. That's why
I came to your time--
for all you know.
For all we know!
D'oh!
A, uh, strike!
A totally legitimate strike!
Yeah!
Hey, uh, what's the robot
version of bro-Mance?
Ro-Mance.
You future guys have a word
for everything... pal.
You know, they look
a little similar.
Yeah. Like the guy
who designed Bender
just took a
drawing of Dad
and stuck an antenna on it.
A little lazy,
if you ask me.
Regardless, I see
no reason to believe
that Bender is
from the future.
Robotic technology today
is very advanced.
Oh, really?
Can your modern-day robots
do this?
It's not my birthday--
although Maggie's
is pretty soon.
I can't do "Maggie."
The Gs look like sixes.
This is the robot who claims
to be from the future.
Can your present-day robots
do this?
Uh, no, no,
they cannot.
Not sure why they'd
want to-- gorbid.
Now, why are
you here?
What is your mission,
uh, so to speak?
I don't remember.
Man, this guy doesn't
ask permission--
he just goes
right in you.
Eh... aha!
Bender's mission protocol
is definitely intact.
It just requires
a delicate procedure
known as "unplug and re-plug."
Because that fixes everything.
I remember why I'm here!
To kill Homer Simpson!
My ears are burning.
Not yet, but they will be.
A boxing glove!
But we bowled together.
Aw, I can't do it.
What stopped you, Bender,
Asimov's Three Laws of Robotics?
You think robots care
what some hack
science fiction writer thinks?
I killed Isaac Asimov
on the way over here.
Well, Isaac somebody.
What the...? My ass
is about to project something.
You don't have
to announce it.
Just do it quietly
and blame the dog.
Bender,
we've just regained contact.
Have you killed Homer Simpson?
Uh, yep.
Killed him good.
If Homer's dead,
why are the creatures he begat
still here
and multiplying out of control?
What the...?
You lied to
me, Bender!
Homer Simpson's
still alive!
Come on, Bender,
stabbity-stabbity.
Wait! Stop! Why must
you kill my dad?
Especially when cheeseburgers
are doing the work for you.
Homer Simpson must be
eliminated immediately.
The creatures destroying
New New York have his DNA.
The monsters are stealing
our office supplies!
That's inexcusable!
Gah!
Um...
Hello, robot.
Looks like everyone gets
a turn to say something.
This concludes my turn.
We sent Bender back in time
to kill Homer
before the monsters
could evolve from him.
Apparently, this was too heartless
a task for a robot.
Leela, can you handle it?
In a New New York minute minute.
Ow!
Right in my language center!
Professor, y-you're
a fellow man of science.
Maybe if we teamed up,
we could, uh,
figure something out.
Okay. Eh, but remember, to
me you're incredibly stupid.
Oh, and the annoying
girl may be helpful.
Meanwhile, Leela, take Homer
and explore this time period.
Find out why people would
ever pay for "freemium games."
I'll explain.
Okay, it starts free,
right?
Then you visit
your friend's game,
and he's got this awesome candy
mansion...
Get a load
of those freaks!
And you're like, "99 cents?!
You bet I'd like one!"
And that's why I owe
Clash of Candies $20,000.
Here we are.
Marge, I'd like you
to meet Leela and Fry.
Oh, don't mention her eye.
Don't mention her eye.
Don't mention her hair.
I... am so pleased
to meet you.
Nice to be hair.
Oh, Lord.
Professor Farnsworth,
I'm dying to know
how you got here.
Was it a time machine?
Little girl,
time machines are
physical impossibilities.
We teleported
through a singularity
that I quantum entangled
to Bender
under the guise
of fixing his collar.
Yes, but how
did Bender get here?
With a time machine.
But you just said that...
Sample's ready!
Kill all humans.
Start with Flanders.
Good news, everyone!
That means it's bad.
The human DNA
in the creatures
was only
half Homer's.
The other half came from...
someone else.
Oh, so we can kill
that person instead.
Maybe they're evil
and deserve it.
Or have one of those
annoying voices
that gets on everybody's nerves,
with the adding extra
noises for no reason.
Myveen.
Bloingy.
And the other person is...
Oh, who's that?
It's me.
Wait a minute. We don't
have to kill you.
Oh, well, that's better.
We just have to kill
all your children.
Or just one of them.
If you can figure out which
one sired the killer rabbits.
We interrupt this hologram
to bring you an
important bulletin.
The horrific creatures
destroying New New York
have begun
metamorphosing.
Eat my shorts!
Ay, caramba!
What a surprise.
It's Bart.
Wow,
I'm doing the same jokes
a thousand years later.
Ay, caramba!
But how did a mere boy
destroy the future?
Well...
Let this be a lesson.
Never throw meaningless crap
in a time capsule.
That's it! All we have to do
is dig up the time capsule.
And bury Bart in the hole.
I thought people
in the future
would be more full
of peace and love.
Like in Epcot Center.
In our time, Epcot Center
is a work farm for the weak.
Oh, but it's
not as crowded
as the slave labor camps
at Universal Studios.
We're here.
My bowling buddy.
Hey!
You can't dig that up
for a thousand years.
Plus, I wrote
my name there.
See?
Shmayday!
They got Scruffy!
Nope. They just
got my mustache.
But a life without a mustache
ain't worth livin'.
No!
That generator
powers the portal.
If they destroy it,
we'll be...
...sucked back
into the future.
Okay, head count.
One, two, three...
Where's Maggie?
Well, little meatbag,
it looks like it's
just you and me.
Stuck in a terrible past
where I know the result
of every horse race ever!
To the track!
I want that.
Well, you can't have it.
Why, you little...
Dad, it's me.
Prove it.
When's your birthday?
February 23rd.
Ha! February has no 23rd.
You...
Yes, it does.
Can you please just get us
out of this lousy future?
Actually, of all probable
futures, this is the worst.
It is, 'cause
my baby's not in it.
Motherly love.
Why did we outlaw that?
Madam, our mechanical friend
Bender is your portal home.
But we can't use him until
the generator is repaired.
Homer works
at a nuclear plant.
He can help us get home.
Oh, are you good
at your job?
I was voted employee
of the month
as an April
Fools' Day joke.
Why, you little...
Great.
You and Fry
can bumble around together
while the rest of us
give up and make peace
with our various deities.
As for me, I'm an atheist.
Oh, nobody's father,
who art nowhere,
I know you can't hear me,
completely ignore this prayer.
Nothing art thou and nothing
will thou ever be.
Jesus was just a man.
Amen.
Well, I shall stay here
for the decadence.
There's no debauchery like
end-of-the-world debauchery.
Your lips, my lips,
apocalypse, ooh!
I can't believe you're all
giving up without a fight.
Lisa,
we're just a package
delivery service.
And not a very
good one.
The only way to handle
the creatures
is to do what we do
to each year's
Super Bowl losers:
shoot them into space.
But we'd have to
round them up first.
Let me take care of that.
If there's one thing
I know how to do,
it's manipulate Bart.
You're nuts.
I've got a will of iron.
Okay, let's get going.
Dad, we have beer
in our time.
Hey, I haven't had a drink
in a thousand years.
There's a horse
called Bender's Bounty.
But my memory says
he died during the race.
That can't be true.
And way, way, way back
is Bender's Bounty.
Damn it!
Oh, chief, it
looks like a robot
killing horses
over there.
Oh, a 608...
Lou, can't you just
let me enjoy my day off?
W-Why are you dressed
in your uniform, then?
'Cause they're
the only clothes that fit me.
You happy? Happy?
Attention, goblins.
Madison Cube Garden is filled
with Butterfinger bars.
And people are laying
fingers all over them.
They're evolving. Wow.
That's a first for you, Bart.
Will you shut up?
Uh, did I remind you
to strap yourselves in?
You realize you're
cheering the death
of millions of my children.
Wow,
it's working.
I guess the instructions
were in English.
What the...
Whoa!
Hey, here's a souvenir photo of
you guys coming out of my chest.
Aw, I will treasure
this forever.
Lie detected.
Oh, my sweet baby.
Oh, feels like
you have a full diaper.
Ooh, um, I'll
change her.
Here's your cut.
Nice knowing you,
meatbags.
Have fun turning
to dust.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're the portal.
How are you gonna
get to the future?
The old-fashioned way.
Good night, friend.
You'll always have
a special place
here with us.
Thanks, pal.
Look at this mess.
It would have
disintegrated upon entry
if someone hadn't turned off
the atmosphere last night.
I like it cold
when I'm sleeping.
Besides, these horrible
Earth creatures are delicious.
The Johnsons will be here
for dinner any minute.
What happened
to the handsome man I married?
I ate him, remember?
Here they are.
Uh, hmm...
Hope we're not
interrupting anything.
I can't take any more.
I-I can't
take it.
Well, perhaps the one of you
that is female
should go console her.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Two... two, three... ♪
♪ Simpsons in the future ♪
♪ Space jokes flying
through sound ♪
♪ What are those tubes? ♪
♪ I wonder what ♪
♪ Ice cream's like now ♪
♪ Maybe it's hot ♪
♪ Or some new temperature
they invented. ♪
That's it, we're done.
Shh!