D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(screams)
(door slams)
(laughs)
(whistle blows, crowd cheers
on TV)
(retches, groans)
♪ The Simpsons 26x02 ♪
The Wreck of the Relationship
Original Air Date on October 5, 2014
(laughs)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(groaning, grunting)
(Bart laughs)
Well, it wasn't easy,
but we managed to watch
every "testicle fail"
video on the Internet.
Now to leave a great comment.
LOL.
That's gotta hurt.
Oh... I guess there's
nothing left to do
but go outside and play.
Wait-- a sponsored link.
MILHOUSE: Ooh!
A trailer for
Project: After Party.
The long-awaited sequel
to Project: Party.
(gasps)
That's a red band trailer.
We're not old enough
to see that.
Sure we are. I just have
to enter my birthday.
January 1, 1900.
No movie's so dirty the oldest
man in the world can't see it.
Well, they did everything
they could to stop us,
but we hacked through anyway.
NARRATOR: They thought the party
was over.
After party!
♪ ♪
(gasps)
Brief nudity!
I thought we installed
parental blocking software
on all our computers.
I don't know
what that stuff blocks.
Mammogram appointment.
(alarm blares)
I told you
to clean your room
and instead you're
watching chest videos.
Look at all those bowls
of half-eaten cereal.
The cereal on the
bottom gets soggy.
I know how cereal works.
Now clean your room.
Why should I?
It's just gonna get dirty again.
I'm in charge.
You do what I say.
I'll get to it
when I get to it.
That better not mean
what it means when I say it.
(squishing)
D'oh!
That boy has no respect
for my authority.
Maybe you two are more similar
than you'd like to admit.
We're not similar.
I love being told
what to do by someone
who's wise in the ways
of the world. Love it!
Here's what I would do:
in the middle of the night,
clean Bart's room for him,
then, in the morning,
thank him for cleaning his room.
You poor woman.
Dealing with Bart
has turned your mind
to ketchup water.
You rest.
I'll be the boy's father now.
I'm done.
I'd like it if you ate
a little more broccoli.
Eh, I'm not feelin' it.
Your mother said
eat your broccoli.
Why do I need
to eat broccoli?
So that you can grow up
healthy and strong, like...
Randy Quaid.
Yeah, Randy Quaid.
He's very healthy.
Look, I'll drink
another glass of milk.
(scoffs)
Milk. That's for babies
and old guys who can't
sleep at night
because of what they did
in the war.
Broccoli.
Hey, what if I eat
the broccoli?
I love the stuff.
(chuckles)
You eat a sundae.
Marge, get Lisa a sundae.
You are not
leaving this table
until you eat
that broccoli.
And I'm going to sit
right here until you do.
(scoffs)
You'll never out-sit me.
Oh, really? You think
your skinny butt
can sit on that hard,
wooden chair longer than
El Gordo?
(gasps)
The sit is on.
Eat your broccoli.
No.
(snoring)
(alarm rings)
Read your broccoli.
No.
They've been
at it all night.
I know, but
they're not gonna
waste a whole
Saturday inside.
(phone rings)
Mm-hmm?
Homer, where are you?
Our fantasy football draft
is about to start.
(gasps)
Today's our draft.
I've got to pick
a good fantasy team.
When I lost last year,
they made me do something
so humiliating...
Jeebus loves Tebow.
(Homer whimpers)
And so the fat man caves.
If you need me, I'll be up
in my room eating cereal.
Half a bowl of cereal.
Marge, I want you--
my wife-- to draft
my fantasy football team.
(all gasp)
I-I don't really
know that much about the...
My team name is
"Somewhere Over the Dwayne Bowe"
and my password
is "Annoyed Grunt."
Draft with God, honey.
Eat your broccoli.
(panting)
Martin's been secretly
taking self-defense
courses,
and now he's
beating up Nelson.
MARTIN: Hi-yah!
NELSON: Ow. Ow. Whoa. Aah!
His fat fists
are a blur.
I've never seen
moves like that.
KEARNEY:
And never will again.
Sounds like quite a match.
And here's your ticket
to a front-row seat.
No. No.
I'll never eat those
filthy mini-trees.
Today, I wear the vest.
Haw. Haw.
(groans)
Now I am never eating
that broccoli.
Homie. Homie,
the fantasy draft just ended.
I got you five kickers.
It is called football, right?
You are definitely
eating that broccoli.
(Homer and Bart growling)
This has got to stop.
If you don't go to work,
you're going to get fired.
I can get another job.
Who wouldn't want to hire
a man who won't back down?
I could be a prison warden
or a Southern anything.
I've got an idea,
but I'll need
that broccoli.
(blender whirrs)
These two fruit smoothies
look and taste exactly the same.
One of them, however,
has the broccoli blended in.
Bart picks one of the smoothies
and drinks it--
maybe he had the broccoli,
maybe he didn't.
No one knows,
so neither of you has given in,
and this horrible impasse
can come to an end.
Uh, works for me.
I'm in.
Oh, thank God.
Hmm...
Oh, no, the broccoli.
(annoyed grunt)
You did that on purpose!
You lick this table clean!
Come on. Lick it.
(grunting)
(both grunting, groaning)
(both grunting)
Come on, now,
you can still lick it.
Oh, I'm afraid Homer
and Bart's problems
are beyond our power to solve.
There's only one thing
left to try.
(snoring)
(both grunt)
(all grunt)
(whispers):
And, lift.
Put my sack back on.
I'm trying to sleep.
(both snoring)
(grunts)
Hmm?
(gasps)
Where are we?
I don't know.
Eat your broccoli.
No.
We're on an old-time boat.
We've been kidnapped.
(chuckles):
Not kidnapped, shanghaied.
Oh.
My name is
Captain Bowditch.
Your wife signed you up
for a week at sea,
where you'll live like sailors,
eat like sailors
and use therapeutic techniques
to solve father-son conflicts...
like sailors.
Hmm?
For there's no
better place
to solve relationship
issues than on...
The Relation Ship.
"Relation Ship."
It works two ways.
(laughs)
Pretty good.
Hey, lame ass,
Thanks to you, we're stuck
on a stupid therapy boat.
I'm the lame ass?
The only lame ass on this boat
is you and all
the other lame asses!
(both grunting, groaning)
Shouldn't we
do something?
We are doing
something.
We're empathizing.
I just know Bart and Homer
are best friends already.
I can feel it.
(computer dings)
Ooh, I'm getting a message
from your father's
fantasy football league.
I must
still be logged in as him.
Lenny used the "uck" word.
Mom, it's trash talk.
You know how guys say
mean things to their friends,
the way women say nice things
to their enemies.
Oh.
(computer dings)
Yikes!
Well I don't like
this trash talk.
And I'm gonna
do something about it.
Even if I have to bring in
the big guns.
Dear Lord, please help Homer's
friends understand
that make-believe
computer football is no excuse
for using the Internet
to be mean.
(phone buzzes)
(gasps)
Trash talk?
In church? No.
No, not here.
(phones buzzing)
MARGE (gasps):
It's everywhere.
And now, a moment of silence
for the victims
of the Shelbyville sinkhole.
(phone buzzes)
(Marge gasps)
The WI-Fi. The WI-Fi.
I've got to take out The WI-Fi.
She's under a lot of stress.
Her husband's at sea.
(bell dinging)
Ahoy, lads and dads.
It's never easy to talk about
your feelings
in front of strangers...
so we're going to sing
about them.
♪ Who wants to sing
about their feelings ♪
♪ Who wants to go first
and sing about their feelings ♪
♪ I'll go first
and sing about my feelings ♪
♪ I'm so happy to be singing. ♪
Now, Homer.
D'oh!
So, Cletus, Gitmo,
what brings you fellas
to The Relation Ship?
My daddy's
always overpraisin' me.
Aw, that's great honesty, son.
I'm so proud of you.
(scoffs)
Why won't you let me fail?
What about you,
Bart, Homer? Homer?
Lethargy, skin spots,
spongy gums--
this man's got scurvy.
But we've only been
at sea one day.
When's the last time
you had citrus?
I had a mimosa
at brunch a few years ago.
Well, Bart, while your father
spends the next few days
sucking out of
the lemon barrel,
you'll drink deep of the
hearty grog of empowerment.
What does that mean?
Mainly climbing.
Except for Wednesday night when
we project a movie on the sails.
But, really,
a lot of climbing.
(Gilbert and Sullivan's "We Sail
the Ocean Blue" playing)
Sheepshank, bowline,
clove hitch...
(Homer sucking)
Dad, look, I did a round turn
with two half hitches.
You lie!
(gasps)
Wait a minute.
Windswept hair, rugged tan,
rough, calloused hands.
You're enjoying
this, aren't you?!
So what if I am?
You're my son and you
will hate what I hate.
Angled parking. Lemons.
Kickstarters by famous guys
who already have lots of money.
And this boat!
I'm old enough to choose
my own things to hate.
And the things I like.
And I like being a sailor.
Betrayed by my worst enemy.
I never would have seen it
coming.
Why, Bart,
that's a perfect halyard cleat.
Just like you taught me,
Captain.
Over, under, over, under, over,
under, under, under, over, over,
over, over, over, over, over,
under, over, half hitch.
Well, the standard form
is under, over, under, over,
under, under, under,
under, under,
over, over,
under, under, under, under,
around, over, over, under...
Fathers, sons,
together we've made a lot of
progress on this voyage.
I learned
that left is called "port."
I finally got over
my sea sickness.
(retches)
Terrific, Homer. Just terrific.
But one sailor has truly taken
to nautical life.
I hereby award Bart Simpson
the post of midshipman.
(spits)
Wow.
So now I can give orders?
That's right,
Mr. Midshipman.
Wait a minute.
I'm his father.
He can't order
me around.
He's your superior officer,
so he can and will order
you around.
And what if I refuse?
Oh...!
I'm sorry we had
to discipline you.
On the positive side,
you won't miss out
on the father/son
hornpipe dance.
(playing accordion)
Oh, I hate
the Golden Age of Sail.
(whistles)
Officer on deck!
Seaman Homer, you're supposed
to be swabbing the deck.
Why should I?
It's just gonna get dirty again.
I'm in charge.
You do what I say.
Fine. I'll swab
whatever you say.
Look! I'm swabbing the deck.
I'm swabbing this giant tree
that the sail grows out of.
Ooh! I'm swabbing
the top of the ocean.
Ooh! Swab, swab, swab...
Hey! What the...?
Fantasy football has turned
every man in this town
into a trash-talking monster.
Oh, face it-- all men
live in a sad world
of profanity, boob jokes and
tired comedy references.
Más cowbell!
(laughter)
There's only one thing that
will shut these guys up.
You got to beat one of
them at fantasy football.
(dramatic, epic sports
theme music playing)
Then that's what I'm gonna do.
NARRATOR:
Game day.
As an icy mist rose
from a package
of defrosting hamburger meat,
desktop gladiator Marge Simpson
prepared to lead
her husband's team against
undefeated trash-talker
Moe Szyslak.
Mom did everything:
she checked injury lists,
scouting reports,
she even studied the tapes.
The tapes of The Real
Housewives of Tampa Bay,
where she watched star running
back Lakwando Demarius
get kicked out of his house
after buying his wife
the wrong color convertible.
That doesn't match my phone!
Lakwando's mind
won't be on the game.
And...
benched.
And now to make my big move.
Homer's team e-mailed asking
to start five kickers.
I was like, "Okay,
it's, uh, your funeral."
There would be no funeral.
High winds, unlocked by the
savage power of climate change,
allowed Marge's five kickers
to launch a long-range campaign
of three-point annihilation.
An 85-yard field goal?
You got to be kidding me!
Refresh, refresh.
But no amount of refreshing
could alter the facts:
Despite a breathtaking
ignorance
and a powerful dislike
of the sport,
a rookie housewife had defeated
a savvy veteran,
proving conclusively
that fantasy football
is basically just luck.
Ahoy, Midshipman.
I hope your voyage
on The Relation Ship
is proving interpersonally
fruitful.
I don't know. It's really hard
when someone
doesn't respect your authority.
Epiphany ho.
And I'm sure your father
has been doing some growing
and learning of his own.
♪ I found some booze
in another dad's bag ♪
♪ Drunk, drunk ♪
♪ Drunk on a boat ♪
Yi-yo-yu!
(grunts)
You don't need booze, Homer.
I went to sea because
I'm a recovering alcoholic.
But out here on the waves,
I no longer crave
the sweet, warm,
soothing flavors
of yummy, yummy rummy.
(gulping)
I love this boat!
With all its pullies
and flappies and...
Everything has a name.
You know what, Homer?
I've always wanted
to eat a parrot.
What's the big deal?
It's just like a green chicken!
Yeah...
NARRATOR: But fortune did not
favor The Relation Ship,
as the same winds that lofted
Marge's fantasy field goals
to victory now sent gales
of doom
toward this vessel of
questionable therapeutic value.
(thunder rumbling)
White lightnin' squall!
Why is the captain
just juggling?
Okay, o-okay.
I can do this. I can do this.
Someone count me in!
I said count me in!
Don't worry, I'll radio
the Coast Guard for help.
The therapy bears!
Look out for the therapy bears!
Oh...!
I'm a-comin', bears!
Don't stand there gawking
like a dang fool!
Do somethin', boy!
You criticized me!
That's all I
ever wanted, Daddy,
honest parenting.
CLETUS:
Aw...
Now I'm the ship's
highest-ranking officer.
It's up to me
to get us to shore.
Dad, we can make it
to harbor
if we can just sail
around that lighthouse.
Are you crazy?
We'll never make it!
Drop the anchor
and wait out the storm!
No, we need to sail.
I'm dropping the anchor!
Can't you just do what I say?
You've never done
what I say-- ever!
(booming, crashing)
(gasps)
(gulps, groans)
Now can we please respect
each other?
(booming, crashing)
Yes, son. We can.
Awaiting your orders,
Mr. Midshipman!
Put up the storm jib
and haul in the main sheet!
Aye aye, sir.
Another success story
for The Relation Ship.
(glugging)
(humming happily)
So, did your sailing adventure
help you work out your issues?
Does this answer
your question?
(sailor's hornpipe music plays)
Yar! Quite a
hornpipe Thar be.
But, uh, surely you would never
have gone on a sea adventure
without your old friend,
the Sea Captain.
Yar.
That's gonna hurt
for a long time.
Yar.
(Gilbert and Sullivan's "We Sail
the Ocean Blue" playing)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man