- 2020.
- THAT'S A STRETCH.
- FINE.
2024.
I WIN,
WE MOVE IN THERE.
I'LL TAKE THE WEST WING.
YOU TAKE THE EAST WING.
YOU CAN BE THE FIRST GENTLEMAN.
- ACTUALLY, THAT SOUNDS
KIND OF GREAT.
THANKS FOR COMING WITH ME
TO GET MY STUFF.
- HOW COULD I PASS UP
AN OPPORTUNITY
TO LOOK AT OUR FUTURE HOUSE?
- OH, JUST REMEMBERED.
I KIND OF GOT YOU
AN ENGAGEMENT PRESENT.
- IS IT A WAFFLE TOWER?
- I MEAN, IT'S A LITTLE BETTER
THAN THAT.
[background chatter]
- CLAUDIA WELDERS.
- UH, THAT--
HOW DID--
HOW DID YOU DO THIS?
- CALLED IN A FEW FAVORS.
- EXCUSE ME.
- A FEW HUNDRED FAVORS.
MR. VICE PRESIDENT.
BEN WYATT FROM
CONGRESSMAN MURRAY'S OFFICE.
- HEY, BEN. DAVE TOLD ME
YOU WERE GONNA BE COMING BY.
AND YOU MUST BE LESLIE KNOPE.
WELCOME. WELCOME.
- [laughs]
YOU'RE--MY NAME JUST CAME OUT
OF YOUR MOUTH.
- WELL, YEAH, IT DID.
- THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
THIS ISN'T REAL.
- NO, IT'S HAPPENING,
AND I'M DELIGHTED
TO HAVE YOU HERE.
ON BEHALF OF THE PRESIDENT
AND MYSELF,
I WANTED TO--
- OH, MR. VICE PRESIDENT,
I AM DEEPLY FLATTERED,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
THAT I COULD TAKE OVER
MADAM SECRETARY CLINTON'S
POSITION.
I MEAN--
- I'M CONFIDENT
YOU COULD DO THAT JOB
OR ANY OTHER, BUT--
- OKAY, I WILL.
- WELL, THE REASON
YOU'RE HERE IS I'M TOLD
YOU'VE DONE SUCH A GREAT JOB
IN YOUR TOWN
AND IN THE STATE OF INDIANA,
AND I JUST WANT
TO SAY CONGRATULATIONS
FOR YOUR PUBLIC SERVICE.
- AND I JUST WANT
TO SAY THANK YOU.
- WELL, YOU--
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
HEY--
Y-YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
- YOU'RE VERY HANDSOME.
- I THINK WE'RE ALL DONE.
- WELL, YOU'RE VERY NICE.
- OKAY. THANK YOU.
- THANK--
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- WELL--
OH, WELL, YOU WILL?
- THANK YOU,
MR. VICE PRESIDENT.
- Y-YOU'RE WELCOME.
- YOU DON'T LET ANYTHING HAPPEN
TO HIM, YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
HE IS PRECIOUS CARGO.
[triumphant music]
*
- YEAH, IT'S ACTUALLY THE SAME
ACCOUNTING FIRM I ALMOST JOINED
LAST YEAR, AND THEY GAVE ME
A GREAT PACKAGE--
THREE WEEKS OF VACATION,
MATCHING 401(k),
AND A PRETTY SWEET WINDBREAKER.
- WOW.
- I'M GETTING MARRIED,
AND I WANTED
A GOOD STABLE JOB,
SO I'M GOING BACK
TO ACCOUNTING.
SO JUST CALL ME BOND,
MUNICIPAL BOND.
YEAH, THAT JOKE KILLED
AT THE ACCOUNTING FIRM.
- WELL, WELL, WELL.
IF IT ISN'T MR. LOOKS
AND PROFESSOR BOOKS.
HE'S LOOKS.
- I GOT IT.
- OF COURSE YOU DO, BOOKS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WELL, FUN FACT: BEN JUST GOT
AN AMAZING ACCOUNTING JOB.
REGULAR FACT:
I HAVE TO GO TO A MEETING.
UN-FUN FACT:
MY UNCLE JUST HAD A STROKE.
WELL, I'M OFF.
- THIS IS ACTUALLY
A CRAZY COINCIDENCE.
I HAVE A NEW COMPANY
AND COULD USE YOUR HELP
ON THE MATH SIDE OF THINGS.
- OH, WHAT'S THE NEW COMPANY?
- WE SPECIALIZE IN MAKING STACKS
ON STACKS
ON STACKS ON STACKS.
- RIGHT.
PASS.
- I'M KIDDING.
IT'S A REAL IDEA.
SO GET THIS--
KIDS ARE ALWAYS GROWING
OUT OF THEIR CLOTHES,
SO THEIR PARENTS DON'T WANT
TO BUY 'EM NICE THINGS.
I'M GONNA RENT
MY UPSCALE CLOTHING
TO MIDDLE SCHOOL KIDS,
BECAUSE I DISCOVERED
I'M ROUGHLY THE SAME SIZE AS
THE AVERAGE PAWNEE 12-YEAR-OLD.
- THAT'S ACTUALLY
A REALLY GREAT IDEA.
- I KNOW. CAN YOU TAKE A LOOK
AT THE BUSINESS PLAN,
TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK?
- SURE. WHY NOT?
- AWESOME.
- WASHINGTON, D.C. HAS
MORE DOG PARKS PER CAPITA
THAN MOST CITIES.
PAWNEE ONLY HAS TWO DOG PARKS--
THIS ONE
AND THAT ONE,
WHICH IS ALSO
AN ACTIVE PARKING LOT.
- CAN YOU SAY
"PER CAPITA" AGAIN?
I WANT TO TAKE A PICTURE
OF YOU SAYING "PER CAPITA."
- STOP.
- I AM SO PROUD OF YOU.
NOW STAND NEXT TO THE SCREEN
AND THINK ABOUT
ALL THE STRONG FEMALE
ROLE MODELS IN YOUR LIFE.
- GROSS.
- APRIL CAME TO ME
WITH AN IDEA TO BUILD
A DOG PARK IN PAWNEE.
I RECOGNIZED HER POTENTIAL
A LONG TIME AGO,
AND SHE'S FINALLY
LIVING UP TO IT.
I MEAN,
I AM SO PROUD OF HER,
I COULD CRY.
AND...HERE WE GO.
ONE TINY CRITIQUE.
IF YOU DO WANT
TO BE TAKEN SERIOUSLY,
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO THINK A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT HOW YOU PRESENT YOURSELF.
- NO, THIS IS PUBLICITY
FOR ORIN'S
NEW PERFORMANCE ART SHOW.
HE'S AN ANIMAL
LIVING ON A HUMAN FARM.
AND YOU CAN GO AND FEED HIM
FROM YOUR OWN HAND.
- UGH,
THAT'S HORRIFYING,
AND SO IS ORIN.
YOU SHOULD NOT BE FRIENDS
WITH HIM.
- SO, AFTER REVIEWING
ALL THE OPTIONS,
I FOUND THAT THE BEST LOCATION
FOR THE DOG PARK
IS LOT 48,
THE ONE BEHIND ANN'S HOUSE.
- [laughs]
NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO PUT
A PARK THERE FOR FOUR YEARS.
SEE, THE THING IS, APRIL,
THAT LOT IS MINE.
I'VE BEEN DOING
SLOW, PAINSTAKING WORK
SO I DON'T WANT TO WHIP OUT
THE LEGALESE ON YOU NOW,
BUT I GOT DIBS.
WHAT WE ARE GONNA DO
IS WE'RE GONNA TAKE
YOUR ENTHUSIASM,
WE'RE GONNA BUNDLE IT UP,
AND WE'RE GONNA FIND A NEW PLACE
FOR A DOG PARK.
DOESN'T THAT SOUND FUN?
ONE, TWO, THREE, CHEESE.
GOOD GIRL.
- GOOD MORNING, ANDY.
[clears throat]
- OKAY, SOMETHING IS DIFFERENT
ABOUT MY COMPUTER.
AHA.
IT'S GONE.
[gasps]
A GAME IS THE FOOT.
SEE, PART OF THE POLICE ACADEMY
ENTRANCE EXAM
IS INVESTIGATING A CRIME.
SO ABOUT A MONTH AGO
I TOLD EVERYONE IN THE OFFICE
THAT, AT SOME POINT,
THEY SHOULD STEAL SOMETHING
FROM MY DESK
SO I COULD PRACTICE.
LET'S DO THIS.
WAIT, HEY, DID YOU GUYS
TAKE MY GLASSES TOO?
THEY GOT MY SUNGLASSES TOO.
- I WAS IN MIAMI
LAST WEEKEND.
I TOOK MY TALENTS
TO SOUTH BEACH.
- HOW DO YOU SPEND
YOUR TIME IN MIAMI?
MAYBE FENCING
STOLEN COMPUTERS?
- YES, I TOOK
YOUR GOVERNMENT COMPUTER
FROM INDIANA TO MIAMI
TO SELL IT
ON THE BLACK MARKET
FOR 150 BUCKS.
- HA-HA, YOU DON'T KNOW IT,
BUT YOU JUST GAVE YOURSELF AWAY.
- GOTTA SAY,
I'M IMPRESSED.
YOUR MISSION STATEMENT
MADE SENSE,
AND YOU DIDN'T USE
ONE R. KELLY LYRIC.
- YES.
SO YOU WANT TO BE MY CFO?
- WELL, I ALREADY HAVE A JOB,
BUT I'LL HELP
AS A FRIEND.
AS LONG AS YOU TAKE
WHAT I SAY SERIOUSLY.
I DON'T WANT ANOTHER
ENTERTAINMENT 720 DISASTER
ON OUR HANDS.
- YEAH, IT WAS A DISASTER.
TOO BAD
WE DIDN'T SEE IT COMING.
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'S MY FIRST MOVE?
- YOU KNOW, I THINK ANY
OF THE FOUR PREVIOUS LOCATIONS
WOULD WORK, BUT THERE'S
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS PLACE.
IT JUST HAS
A REALLY GOOD ENERGY HERE,
YOU KNOW?
LOTS OF NATURAL LIGHT.
- IT'S TINY AND AWFUL
AND LOUD.
AND IT'S ZONE 14B,
INDUSTRIAL WASTE CLEAN-UP SITE.
WE SHOULD TECHNICALLY BE WEARING
HAZMAT SUITS RIGHT NOW.
- IT SEEMS LIKE THE KIND
OF PLACE A SKA BAND WOULD GO
TO SHOOT HEROIN.
- COME ON, GUYS, THIS IS
A GREAT PLACE FOR A DOG PARK.
I MEAN, LOOK,
THERE'S ALREADY A DOG HERE.
- OH, MY GOD.
I HAD THAT EXACT DOLL
WHEN I WAS A KID.
THIS IS--
THIS IS TRAUMATIC FOR ME.
- WELL, I'M SORRY, BUT LOT 48
IS THE ONLY ONE THAT WORKS.
AND I'M DEFINITELY
BRINGING IT UP
AT THE NEXT
CITY COUNCIL MEETING.
- APRIL, PLEASE,
I BEG OF YOU,
I WILL DO ANYTHING
TO KEEP YOU FROM DOING THAT.
- OKAY.
SAW OFF YOUR PINKY TOE.
- NO.
- SHAVE YOUR HEAD.
- HAVE SEX WITH JERRY.
- NO.
- WELL, I TRIED
TO BE REASONABLE.
- I HAVE CREATED A MONSTER.
AND NOW I NEED
TO DESTROY HER.
WHAT DO I DO, JOE?
[impersonating Biden]
WELL, LESLIE,
LOOK INTO MY EYES,
TAKE A DEEP BREATH,
AND EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
[self]
THANKS, JOE.
GOD, HE'S GOOD.
- RON, THANK YOU
FOR AGREEING TO SEE ME.
- I DIDN'T. YOU JUST WALKED
IN HERE AND STARTED TALKING.
- I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR A HISTORY LESSON.
LOOK, I AM TRYING
TO REMOVE PARKING METERS,
AND THERE IS A GUY
IN PUBLIC WORKS
WHO'S BEING
A REAL THORN ABOUT IT.
- WHICH GUY?
- RICKY JORDACHE.
- NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
WHAT'S HIS DEAL?
- HE'S NEW.
HE USED TO BE A SLACKER,
BUT NOW HE'S REALIZING
HIS FULL POTENTIAL,
BUT AT WHAT COST?
HE'S SMART,
AND HE'S BEAUTIFUL,
AND I THINK OF HIM
IN MANY WAYS AS A DAUGHTER,
BUT THAT WOULD BE CRAZY
'CAUSE HE'S A MAN
AND HIS NAME'S RICKY.
HERE'S MY QUESTION.
HOW DID YOU USED
TO SLOW ME DOWN
WHEN I WAS BECOMING
TOO ME-ISH?
- SOMETIMES I'D JUST GIVE YOU
BUSY WORK.
I ONCE HAD YOU PUT TOGETHER
A BROCHURE
ABOUT DIFFERENT KINDS
OF INDIANA TOPSOIL.
- THAT SOIL BROCHURE
WAS NOT BUSY WORK.
I MEAN, PEOPLE STILL REFER
TO MULCH ADO ABOUT NOTHING.
- AND IF YOU WERE PARTICULARLY
AMPED UP ABOUT A PROJECT,
I'D TAKE YOU TO JJ'S
AND DISTRACT YOU WITH WAFFLES.
- THOSE WERE
DISTRACTION WAFFLES?
I THOUGHT
THEY WERE FRIENDSHIP WAFFLES.
- BREAKFAST FOOD CAN SERVE
MANY PURPOSES.
- BUT WHAT IF THIS PERSON,
THIS RICKY, WHO IS REAL,
DOESN'T LIKE WAFFLES
OR ANYTHING.
- EVERYBODY HAS SOMETHING
THEY'RE PASSIONATE ABOUT.
JUST FIGURE OUT WHAT IT IS,
EXPRESS AN INTEREST IN IT,
AND DIVERT HIS ATTENTION.
[The Farmer in the Dell plays]
*
- HOWDY, NEIGHBORS.
WELCOME TO HUMAN FARM.
HERE'S YOUR ANIMAL FEED.
PLEASE DON'T FEED THE ANIMALS.
- WOW, THIS IS REALLY,
REALLY COOL.
I LIKE THE STATEMENT IT'S MAKING
THAT, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE ALL IN CAGES IN A WAY.
- YEAH, IT'S ACTUALLY
ABOUT DEATH AND THE CITY.
- YEAH.
I SEE THAT NOW.
HI, ORIN.
- MS. WICKS,
IF YOU'VE READ OUR PROPOSAL,
YOU'LL SEE THAT AN ALLIANCE
BETWEEN RENT-A-SWAG
AND SWEETUMS COULD BE
MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL.
- WELL, I MUST SAY
IT'S A MUCH BETTER IDEA
THAN THE LAST ONE YOU HAD,
THAT GOURMET FRENCH FOOD THING.
- OH, MY ESCARGOT
DELIVERY SERVICE, SNAIL MAIL.
SO YOU WANT TO PARTNER UP
AND MAKE HISTORY?
I MEAN,
YOU'VE ALREADY MADE HISTORY
AS THE WORLD'S
MOST BEAUTIFUL CEO.
- I'M REALLY SORRY, CUTIE.
THE COMPANY'S LAYING LOW
RIGHT NOW
DUE TO A SMALL MISHAP.
- AH, YES.
THE SWEETUMS MOLASSES
STORAGE VAT EXPLODED,
RESULTING IN A SLOW-MOVING
ECOLOGICAL DISASTER.
- WELL, ALL PRESS
IS GOOD PRESS.
- NO, THIS WAS BAD PRESS.
A LOT OF HOMES
WERE VERY GRADUALLY FLOODED.
- PEOPLE DIED.
ACTUALLY, SPEAKING OF,
WE'RE STARTING UP
A NON-PROFIT FOUNDATION
TO RESTORE OUR NAME.
ANY INTEREST IN RUNNING IT?
- OH, I'M--I'M SORRY, YOU WANT
ME TO RUN YOUR NON-PROFIT WING?
- I KNOW THAT BOBBY NEWPORT
IS MY STEPSON,
BUT THE WORK YOU DID ON LESLIE'S
CAMPAIGN WAS AMAZING.
YOUR NAME IS ON OUR SHORT LIST.
- JUST TO CLARIFY,
IT'S A NO TO ME
ON ALL FRONTS,
AND YOU'RE OFFERING BEN A JOB?
- YEAH.
- COOL. COOL.
- BEEN LOOKING AT YOUR FILE
ALL DAY,
JERRY--
IF THAT EVEN IS YOUR REAL NAME.
- IT'S NOT.
MY REAL NAME IS GARY.
- WELL, GARY--IF THAT EVEN
IS YOUR REAL NAME--
SOMEBODY STOLE MY COMPUTER.
NOW, IF YOU'RE A CRIMINAL,
LOOK AT ME,
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME LEGALLY,
OR ELSE IT'S CONSIDERED
ENTRAPMENT.
- I'M SORRY, ANDY.
IT WASN'T ME.
- OH, MAN, REALLY?
- NO.
- OKAY.
OKAY, SO WE KNOW
IT'S NOT JERRY,
UNLESS HE WAS LYING TO ME.
I CAN NEVER TELL
WHEN PEOPLE ARE LYING TO ME.
HOPEFULLY THAT DOESN'T COME UP
IN MY POLICE WORK.
- I THINK WE SHOULD DO
MORE STUFF LIKE THIS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK PAWNEE
NEEDS AN AMAZING ARTS PROGRAM.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST DROP
EVERYTHING AND COORDINATE IT.
- I'M NOT STUPID.
- WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- IT MEANS THAT THE ONLY REASON
YOU BROUGHT ME HERE
IS TO DISTRACT ME
FROM THE DOG PARK.
YOU HATE THIS SHOW.
- I LOVE THIS SHOW.
- WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE PART?
- THE HEAVY-HANDEDNESS.
- [groans]
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I HAVE TO GO TALK
TO COUNCILMAN JAMM RIGHT NOW.
- WHY ARE YOU TALKING
TO COUNCILMAN JAMM?
- BECAUSE I TOLD HIM
ABOUT THE DOG PARK IDEA,
AND HE LOVES IT.
HE THINKS IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
HE'S GONNA SUPPORT MY MOTION
AT THE CITY COUNCIL MEETING
TOMORROW,
AND HE GAVE ME
A REALLY COOL DENTAL MIRROR
TO CHECK OUT MY MOLARS.
- OUR DISPUTE ASIDE,
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL WITH JAMM.
HE'S A SNAKE,
I'M TELLING YOU.
- YEAH, LIKE I SHOULD TRUST YOU
OUT OF ALL PEOPLE RIGHT NOW.
- MOO.
MOO.
- QUIET, WEIRDO.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE A SHEEP?
- NO.
YOU ARE.
- [whispers] OH, SHUT UP.
- TOM WOULD MAKE
A GREAT PROFILE FOR YOUR SHOW.
I MEAN, THIS IS A GUY
WHO'S LEARNED
THROUGH AN UNBELIEVABLE SERIES
OF BONEHEAD BUSINESS MOVES.
- NOT TO MENTION
IN THE LAST MONTH ALONE
THREE PEOPLE HAVE CONFUSED ME
FOR A SHORTER,
INDIAN RYAN GOSLING.
- IT'S INTERESTING,
BUT I THINK I NEED TO WAIT
UNTIL THE BUSINESS
HAS BEEN AROUND
FOR A FEW MONTHS,
MAKE SURE IT'S VIABLE.
YOU'RE THE GUY WHO RAN
THE CONGRESSIONAL CAMPAIGN
IN WASHINGTON, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- WHAT, ARE YOU GONNA
OFFER HIM A JOB?
- YES.
WE'RE LAUNCHING
A NEW POLITICAL CHAT SHOW,
AND WE NEED CORRESPONDENTS.
- OH, WELL, THANK YOU,
BUT I'M A LITTLE SHAKY
ON LIVE TV.
- THAT'S OKAY.
PEOPLE WANT AUTHENTICITY.
THINK ABOUT IT?
- DIDN'T YOU HEAR HIM?
HE STINKS ON TV.
HE SWEATS.
HE STUTTERS.
IT'S LIKE THE KING'S SPEECH,
BUT THE FIRST PART,
BEFORE HE'S FIXED.
- THAT WAS MY FAVORITE PART
OF THE MOVIE.
- WHAT IS HAPPENING?
- CHRIS TRAEGER.
- YUP.
HI, ANDY.
- I KNOW YOU DID IT.
- DID WHAT?
- [laughs]
DON'T PLAY STUPID
AND HANDSOME WITH ME.
YOU STOLE MY COMPUTER
SO THAT I COULD PRACTICE
FOR MY POLICE EXAM.
YOU'RE AS GUILTY
AS YOU ARE SEXY.
- ANDY, ANOTHER COMPUTER
WAS REPORTED STOLEN
FROM THE OFFICES
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE COURTYARD.
I DON'T THINK
THIS IS PART
OF YOUR POLICE TRAINING.
I THINK CITY HALL WAS ROBBED.
- I CAN'T TELL
IF YOU'RE LYING TO ME.
REALLY?
- I THINK.
- LIKE A REAL CRIME?
THAT'S EVEN BETTER.
- NEXT ORDER OF BUSINESS:
IT'S AGENDA ITEM 280B,
A MOTION TO CONSTRUCT
A DOG PARK
ON MUNICIPAL LOT 48.
- MS. LUDGATE,
YOU HAVE THE FLOOR.
- THANK YOU,
COUNCILMAN JAMM.
YOUR HELP
AND GENERAL NON-AWFULNESS
IS MUCH APPRECIATED.
LESLIE,
MEMBERS OF THE COUNCIL,
I BELIEVE THAT MUNICIPAL LOT 48
SHOULD BE A DOG PARK.
- BOO.
BOO.
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE THERE'S
CONSIDERABLE OPPOSITION TO THIS,
SO I'M SORRY,
MS. LUDGATE,
YOU SHOULD GO NOW.
- REALLY?
I JUST HEARD ONE HAG BOOING.
- LADIES, PLEASE,
LET'S KEEP THIS CIVIL.
- COUNCILMAN,
PAWNEEANS,
SATISFIED CUSTOMERS
OF JAMM ORTHODONTICS,
AS WE DISCUSS WHAT TYPE OF PARK
TO PUT ON LOT 48,
I HAD A THOUGHT.
HOW ABOUT NO PARK?
WHO HERE THINKS
PARKS ARE STUPID?
LET THE RECORD SHOW THAT
EVERYONE IS RAISING THEIR HANDS.
I HAPPEN TO KNOW FOR A FACT
THAT PAWNEE'S FAVORITE
FAST FOOD RESTAURANT, PAUNCH
BURGER, NEEDS A NEW LOCATION.
NOW, SEEING AS HOW THE FUTURE
OF LOT 48 IS OPEN
FOR DEBATE, I MOVE
WE SELL IT TO PAUNCH BURGER
FOR A NICE PROFIT.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO BE ASIAN
TO DO MATH THAT SIMPLE.
- YOU TOLD ME
YOU WANTED A DOG PARK.
- UH, PSYCH.
- THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU LIED TO ME.
- YOU JUST GOT JAMMED.
- I HATE
WHEN HE SAYS THAT.
- I TOLD YOU
THAT JAMM WAS A SNAKE.
- WELL, IT TAKES A SNAKE
TO KNOW A SNAKE.
- SO NOW I'M A SNAKE?
- YES.
YOU DECEIVED ME
FOR TWO STRAIGHT DAYS,
AND YOU EAT MICE.
- I DON'T EAT MICE.
- YES, YOU DO.
YOU'RE A MOUSE EATER.
MOUSE EATER.
- ENOUGH!
YOU ARE FRIENDS
AND COWORKERS.
IN THIS OFFICE, WE TREAT
EACH OTHER WITH RESPECT.
- HEY, APRIL,
HOW IS THAT DOG PARK COMING?
- GET OUT, JERRY.
- THIS IS PRIVATE!
- SORRY, GUYS.
- WE ARE NOT LEAVING HERE
UNTIL YOU TWO FIGURE THIS OUT.
RON, GUARD THE DOOR.
- YES, SIR.
- NO ONE LEAVES THE OCTAGON.
I DATED AN ULTIMATE FIGHTER.
IT WAS LIKE A THING HE SAID.
- WHAT'S THE PLAY HERE,
OFFICER?
YOU GONNA SET UP A PERIMETER,
MAYBE BUG A FEW PHONES?
OOH, I KNOW.
WE COULD PUT OUT
A DUMMY COMPUTER
FOR THEM TO STEAL,
FILL IT WITH EXPLOSIVES FIRST,
[clicks tongue]
BOOM, TAKE 'EM ALL OUT.
- YEAH, WE'RE NOT DOING
ANY OF THAT.
- ANDY, I LOVE YOUR ENTHUSIASM,
BUT WE DON'T REALLY HAVE
THE KIND OF MONEY TO LAUNCH
A MASSIVE INVESTIGATION.
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA FILL OUT
THIS STUPID REPORT
AND THAT'S IT?
AS A FUTURE COP,
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
I CANNOT LET THIS GUY GO.
- LOOK, MAN, THIS IS
WHAT MOST POLICE WORK IS.
JUST WRITING STUFF DOWN.
IT'S NOT SUPERHERO TIME.
IF IT SOUNDS BORING,
MAYBE YOU OUGHT
TO DO SOMETHING ELSE.
- MAYBE WE SHOULD FIND
THE PERSON
WHO STOLE
HIS POSITIVE ATTITUDE.
- HEY, MAN.
GET ANY MORE JOB OFFERS
SINCE I LAST SAW YOU?
- YEAH, BUT IT WAS
JUST A MANAGEMENT POSITION
AT URBAN OUTFITTERS.
I TURNED IT DOWN.
- I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
MAYBE I CAN'T HACK THIS.
MAYBE I SHOULD TAKE
A CUE FROM YOU
AND STICK
WITH MY BORING DAY JOB.
- WELL, MY ACCOUNTING JOB
ISN'T BORING.
- IF IT WAS
REMOTELY INTERESTING,
THERE WOULD BE A SHOW
ON A&E ABOUT IT.
THEY HAVE A SHOW
ABOUT STORAGE UNIT AUCTIONS.
- FAIR POINT.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE PASSIONATE
ABOUT THIS,
KEEP AT IT.
THINGS WILL TURN AROUND.
ALSO CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT TIME
THAT SHOW
ABOUT STORAGE UNITS IS ON?
- 9:30.
- [sighs] ALL RIGHT,
I'M GONNA HAVE TO FORCE THIS.
LESLIE,
MAYBE YOU WANT TO ADMIT
THAT YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
THE GREATEST ROLE MODEL.
- I DON'T CARE.
ORIN'S MY ROLE MODEL.
- APRIL, MAYBE YOU WANT
TO ADMIT
THAT YOU'VE BEEN
A LITTLE SELFISH
AND INCONSIDERATE.
- LOOK, ALL I EVER WANTED WAS
FOR YOU TO SHOW THE ENTHUSIASM
YOU SHOWED FOR YOUR DOG PARK,
AND, WHEN YOU DID,
I BLEW IT.
AND I'M SORRY.
- FINE.
I'M SORRY THAT I OUTSMARTED
YOU AT EVERY TURN.
- APRIL.
- AND I KNOW I HAVE A LOT
TO LEARN FROM YOU,
AND I'M SORRY
THAT I DISRESPECTED
YOUR STUPID DREAM.
- A LOT OF LOVE
IN THIS ROOM.
- I'M VERY, VERY SORRY.
- ME TOO.
- I LOVE YOU VERY MUCH.
- I LOVE YOU TOO.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS
IN FRONT OF HER.
- OKAY.
- OKAY, ANN,
SINCE YOU'RE SUCH A GENIUS,
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- NEITHER OF YOU WANT JAMM
TO WIN, NOR DO I,
BECAUSE I HATE PAUNCH BURGER,
BUT, IF THERE IS ONE IN
MY BACKYARD, I WILL EAT THERE,
LIKE, EVERY NIGHT,
AND THAT IS NO GOOD.
SO I SAY WE STOP PLAYING DIRTY
WITH EACH OTHER,
AND WE START PLAYING DIRTY
WITH JAMM.
- YES.
WE'LL HAVE TRIPLE-SEX WITH HIM.
- NO. I HAVE AN IDEA.
IT'S VERY UNCOOL,
BUT IT'S NOT ILLEGAL,
TECHNICALLY,
BUT IT IS A DICK MOVE.
- I LOVE IT.
- HEY, CAPTAIN.
STATUS UPDATE:
MY NEW SUSPECT--THE DUDE
WHO RUNS CARPET EMPORIUM.
THE WAY I FIGURE IT IS,
CRIMINALS LOVE TO WRAP THINGS
UP IN RUGS.
PLUS, HE YELLED AT ME WHEN I
TRIED TO UNROLL 'EM ALL, SO...
- ANDY, WHILE I APPRECIATE
YOUR DEDICATION
TO FINDING THIS CRIMINAL,
I THINK YOU MIGHT WANT
TO TAKE INTO ACCOUNT
WHAT THE POLICEMAN SAID.
- I MEAN, GOSH,
IF I CAN'T EVEN INVESTIGATE
BAD GUYS,
WHY BECOME A COP AT ALL?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHEN I GET BUMMED OUT,
I TAKE MY SHIRT OFF
BECAUSE THE BAD FEELINGS
MAKE ME FEEL SWEATY.
[groans]
YOU KNOW WHAT,
MAYBE I SHOULD BAIL
ON BEING A COP.
- CITY HALL NEEDS
A NEW PART-TIME SECURITY GUARD
FOR THE WEEKENDS.
YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
LOOK AT IT AS A WAY
TO FEEL OUT
WHETHER YOU WANT
TO BE A POLICE OFFICER.
BUT, KEEP IN MIND,
IF YOU TAKE THIS JOB,
YOU MUST KEEP YOUR CLOTHES ON
AT ALL TIMES,
EVEN IF YOU GET SAD.
- NO DEAL.
OKAY, I'LL DO IT.
- THAT A BOY.
- I'LL DO IT. I PROMISE.
AND I GET A GUN,
AND I CAN POINT IT
IN PEOPLE'S FACES.
- INCORRECT.
[dog barking]
- HEY.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
- OH, HELLO, COUNCILMAN.
THE DOGS ARE HERE
BECAUSE THERE'S NO DOG PARK
IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD,
AND THE KIDS ARE HERE
BECAUSE THERE'S NO HUMAN PARK
IN YOUR AREA.
THEY ALL NEEDED
A PLACE TO PLAY.
- MY FRONT LAWN?
- THAT'S RIGHT,
AND THEY'RE GONNA KEEP USING IT
UNTIL THERE'S
AN ACTUAL PARK NEARBY.
- HEY, HEY, LADY,
GET THAT THING OFF MY GNOME.
HE IS DRY-HUMPING
MY GARDEN GNOME.
STUPID BEAST.
- COUNCILMAN JAMM, WE JUST NEED
A LITTLE BIT MORE TIME
TO DESIGN OUR PARK.
AND, IF YOU PLOW THROUGH
AND IGNORE US,
THIS IS GONNA BE YOUR LIFE.
- I'LL CALL THE POLICE.
- YEAH, SIC THE POLICE
ON A BUNCH OF KIDS AND PUPPIES.
THAT'S A GREAT PHOTO OP.
- FINE.
GENTLEMAN'S AGREEMENT.
IN 90 DAYS,
WE'LL PUT OUR PLANS TO A VOTE.
WINNER TAKE ALL.
- DEAL.
- GREAT, NOW CALL OFF
THE ACTUAL DOGS.
I WANT THESE KIDS
OFF MY LAWN.
I WANT THAT HULA HOOP
OFF MY 'VETTE.
RIGHT NOW.
- HEY, JAMM.
YOU JUST GOT KNOPED.
AND LUDGATED.
AND PERKINSED.
- HA-HA.
NICE TRY.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
YOU JUST GOT JAMMED.
[door slams]
- OKAY, SO LET'S GET TO WORK.
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, DO YOU
NEVER JUST TAKE A SECOND
TO ENJOY THINGS?
- I JUST SAID,
"LET'S GET TO WORK."
HOW ELSE DO PEOPLE ENJOY THINGS?
- I KNOW YOU CHANGED
YOUR MIND LAST TIME
WE OFFERED YOU A JOB,
BUT WE ARE JUST THRILLED
THAT YOU CHANGED IT AGAIN.
- THANK YOU.
ME TOO.
- THIS IS OUR BEST OFFICE.
AS YOU CAN SEE
THROUGH THE WINDOW,
YOU HAVE A GREAT VIEW
OF THE BILLING DEPARTMENT.
HEY, SHARON!
- SHH.
- SORRY.
SHE'S FUN.
SO, PLEASE,
IF THERE'S ANYTHING WE CAN DO
TO MAKE YOU HAPPIER
IN YOUR NEW JOB,
JUST LET ME KNOW.
- OH, NO,
THIS IS GREAT, BARNEY.
THANK YOU.
BUT I HAVE TO QUIT AGAIN.
- WHAT--OHH!
IS THIS A CLASSIC BEN JOKE?
- NO.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
BUT I JUST DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS.
I NEED TO MOVE MY LIFE
IN ANOTHER DIRECTION.
- THIS IS DISAPPOINTING.
AGAIN.
MAYBE SOMEDAY WE'LL FIGURE OUT
THE MAGIC FORMULA
THAT GETS YOU TO WORK HERE.
- WELL, FORMULAS ARE MY FORMULA
FOR MOOLAH.
- [laughing]
TED, GET IN HERE!
BEN'S QUITTING AGAIN,
BUT YOU GOTTA HEAR WHAT HE SAID.
- LESLIE'S BEEN SAYING FOR WEEKS
I SHOULD DO SOMETHING
I LOVE,
AND SHE'S RIGHT.
AND I'LL HELP TOM OR MAYBE TRY
TO DO THAT TV THING
OR MAYBE WORK
FOR THE SWEETUMS FOUNDATION.
I DON'T KNOW.
LIFE IS SHORT.
WHY BE AN ACCOUNTANT,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, OTHER THAN THE STABILITY
AND THE HEALTH PLAN
AND THE ABOVE-AVERAGE PAY.
OH, GOD,
THIS BETTER WORK OUT.