- SUPPORT FOR PAWNEE
COMMUNITY RADIO
COMES FROM LISTENERS
LIKE YOU
AND FROM THE NEW FILM
THE SHADOWS OF SEVEN HEADS,
THE DRAMATIC TALE
OF AN ISRAELI SOLDIER
WHO FALLS IN LOVE WITH CONJOINED
PALESTINIAN SEXTUPLETS.
OUT SOON
FROM FOCUS FEATURES.
- WELCOME TO
"THOUGHT FOR YOUR THOUGHTS."
I'M YOUR HOST DERRY MURBLES,
SITTING IN FOR NINA JOPLIN,
WHO IS TOURING THE COUNTRY
PERFORMING A SPOKEN-WORD OPERA
ABOUT PEAR-SHAPED WOMEN.
MY GUEST TODAY
IS CITY COUNCILWOMAN
LESLIE KNOPE.
- IT IS A PLEASURE
TO BE BACK, DERRY.
YOUR SHOW LAST WEEK
ON DOLPHIN LACTATION
WAS JUST RIVETING RADIO.
DERRY, MY TEAM AND I
ARE TRYING TO BUILD A PARK,
AND WE NEED INPUT ON THE DESIGN
FROM YOU,
THE CITIZENS OF PAWNEE.
SO I GUESS I'M HERE
TO SEND OUT THE BAT SIGNAL.
- A BAT SIGNAL, FOR
LISTENERS WHO MIGHT NOT KNOW,
REFERS TO THE CHILDREN'S
CHARACTER "THE BAT MAN"
A STRONG GENTLEMAN
WHO FIGHTS CRIME NOCTURNALLY.
- THAT'S CORRECT.
WELL PUT.
THIS PARK IS GOING TO BE
A CELEBRATION OF PAWNEE
BY PAWNEE AND FOR PAWNEE.
SO, YOU KNOW,
SEND IN YOUR PLAN
OR YOUR RESUME...
AND QUICK.
PLEASE. HURRY.
THIS IS ALL GONNA FALL APART
IF YOU DON'T HURRY.
- COMING UP AFTER THE BREAK,
MOVIE REVIEWS
WITH KEN TUCKER
WHO IS FILLING IN
FOR DAVID BIANCULLI
WHO'S IN NEW YORK
FILLING IN FOR KEN TUCKER.
LESLIE, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO INTRODUCE THE NEXT SEGMENT?
- OKAY.
"NOW IT'S TIME FOR
'JAZZ PLUS JAZZ EQUALS JAZZ,'
"TODAY WE HAVE A RECORDING
OF BENNY GOODMAN
PLAYED OVER A SEPARATE
RECORDING OF MILES DAVIS."
[both recordings playing
simultaneously]
- RESEARCH SHOWS THAT OUR
LISTENERS LOVE JAZZ.
[simultaneous music continues]
*
[triumphant music]
- ALL RIGHT,
SO THIS IS A LETTER
FROM WHAT LOOKS LIKE
A FEDERAL PENITENTIARY.
"HERE'S A MODEL
"OF WHAT I THOUGHT THE PARK
COULD LOOK LIKE.
ALSO, I'M INNOCENT.
PLEASE FIND ME A LAWYER."
I'M GETTING KIND OF WORRIED.
I MEAN, WE HAVE NOT RECEIVED
ONE USABLE IDEA SO FAR.
- HANG ON.
LOOK AT THIS GUY.
"30 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE
"WITH A DEGREE IN ARCHITECTURE
FROM THE ROYAL DANISH ACADEMY
OF FINE ARTS IN COPENHAGEN."
- WOW! BEAUTIFUL FOUNTAIN.
PERFECTLY MANICURED SHRUBBERY.
THIS IS LIKE
PARKS DEPARTMENT PORN.
THIS GUY IS GREAT.
I DON'T CARE IF HE'S SOME
JUNKIE WAR CRIMINAL PIMP.
I AM NOT GONNA
CHANGE MY MIND.
- HIS NAME'S WRESTON ST. JAMES.
HE'S FROM EAGLETON.
- OH, I'VE CHANGED MY MIND.
I'M NOT BEING MELODRAMATIC
WHEN I SAY
THAT PEOPLE FROM EAGLETON
ARE SNOBBY AND EVIL,
AND THEY LOOK DOWN ON PAWNEE,
AND THEY WOULD MOST LIKELY
EXTERMINATE EVERYONE
WHO ISN'T FROM EAGLETON
IF THEY WEREN'T SO BUSY
BEING OBSESSED WITH THEMSELVES.
[exhales]
GOD, THAT WAS CLOSE.
SOMETIMES WHEN I RANT
ABOUT EAGLETON,
I FORGET TO BREATHE,
AND I PASS OUT.
NO. WE CANNOT HAVE
SOMEONE FROM EAGLETON
DESIGN A PARK FOR PAWNEE.
WE HAVE HAD A BLOOD FEUD
THAT HAS LASTED FOR 200 YEARS.
- WELL, WE DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF TIME,
AND HE IS THE FIRST
DECENT CANDIDATE.
SO LET'S AT LEAST
GO MEET THE GUY.
- YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
THEN WE CAN REJECT HIM
FACE-TO-FACE.
I LIKE YOUR PLAN.
- FRIENDS, FORMER LOVERS,
ACQUAINTANCES, JERRY,
I INTRODUCE YOU
TO THE FUTURE HOME OF...
RENT-A-SWAG!
- YIKES.
- MUCH LIKE WOMEN IN
'90s STAND-UP COMEDY ROUTINES,
TOMMY BE SHOPPING.
I STARTED A BUSINESS WHERE I
RENT MY FANCY CLOTHES TO TEENS
SO THEIR PARENTS DON'T HAVE TO
BUY THEM NICE THINGS
THEY'LL JUST GROW OUT OF.
SO IF YOU SEE
A 14-YEAR-OLD KID
WEARING A LOUIS VUITTON CRAVAT,
YOU KNOW WHO TO THANK.
ME.
AND LOUIS VUITTON FOR MAKING
SOME DOPE-ASS CRAVATS.
- SON, I LOVE WILDLIFE,
BUT IS A STORE
THE BEST PLACE FOR IT?
- HELP.
- THE PLACE NEEDS SOME WORK,
BUT THIS IS A GREAT LOCATION.
LOTS OF FOOT TRAFFIC,
NO METERED PARKING.
AND IT'S WELL WITHIN
MY FISCAL RANGE.
- GOOD USE OF THE WORD FISCAL,
TOMMY--VERY UP-SCALE.
- VERY IMPRESSIVE.
WATCHING YOU GIVES ME FAITH
THAT ANYONE CAN REINVENT
THEMSELVES.
- TOMMY TIMBERLAKE IS DEAD.
LONG LIVE THOMAS M. HAVERFORD,
RESPONSIBLE TYCOON.
- HELP.
I CAN'T MOVE.
- HE DESIGNED THIS PLACE?
WHAT A DUMP.
- BEN!
LESLIE. HI!
- HI.
- WRESTON ST. JAMES.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING.
- NO, THANK YOU.
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF OUR NEWEST PARK?
- EH. IN A WORD, UNDERWHELMING.
AND A LITTLE INCONVENIENT.
THERE'S NO TRASH CANS ANYWHERE.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH MY GARBAGE,
JUST THROW IT ON THE GROUND?
- THANK YOU FOR THE TRASH!
- MR. ST. JAMES,
I HAVE TO SAY,
THIS PARK IS INCREDIBLE.
- THANK YOU.
ITS OFFICIAL NAME
IS "FIVE MILE GROUNDS",
BUT WE LIKE TO CALL IT
"WIDE SMILES ABOUND."
- BECAUSE OF ALL THE SMILES
THAT OCCUR?
- [chuckles]
IT'S SO BORING.
- COME ON, I'LL TAKE YOU GUYS
ON A LITTLE TOUR.
- GREAT.
HE SEEMS SUPER-COOL.
- HE SEEMS COOL.
JUST YOU WAIT.
WELL, THEY ALWAYS
WINE AND DINE YOU FIRST,
BUT THE FACT
OF THE MATTER IS
EAGLETONIANS ARE,
WITHOUT EXCEPTION,
SNOBBY,
CONDESCENDING JERKS.
THIS IS THE PAWNEE SIDE
OF OUR BORDER WITH EAGLETON...
AND THIS IS
THE EAGLETON SIDE.
- AH.
UHH.
HEY, BABE, IT'S ME.
WILL YOU COME DOWN HERE, PLEASE,
AND KEEP ME COMPANY?
I'M SO BORED.
I NEED YOU.
- IF I COME DOWN THERE,
CAN I AT LEAST BREAK SOMETHING?
- OF COURSE, BABY.
ANYTHING. YOU KNOW THAT.
CHRIS GAVE ME
THIS GREAT JOB
AS A WEEKEND SECURITY GUARD
AT CITY HALL.
ONLY ONE PROBLEM--
IT'S A TERRIBLE JOB.
I DID EVERYTHING
I WAS SUPPOSED TO DO,
AND I WALKED AROUND
THE BUILDING FOUR TIMES.
ONLY 20 MINUTES
HAS GONE BY.
UGH! THOUGHT MAYBE
TEN MINUTES HAD GONE BY
SINCE I STARTED TALKING.
IT'S ONLY BEEN 15 SECONDS.
[deep sigh]
OHH...
OH, BABE,
THANK GOD YOU'RE HERE.
I GOT SO BORED, I STARTED
THINKING ABOUT EXISTENCE--
"DO I MATTER?
DO ANY OF US?
IS THERE A MASTER PLAN
IN THE WORKS, A GRAND DESIGN?"
JUST DUMB STUFF LIKE THAT.
- UGH! WHO CARES?
- [sighs] I THOUGHT BEING
A SECURITY GUARD
WOULD BE EXCITING.
NOPE.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
ISN'T THIS HOW ALL GREAT
BERT MACKLIN CASES START?
IT'S QUIET.
A LITTLE TOO QUIET.
- AS YOU CAN SEE, WE LIKE TO
KEEP THINGS QUITE IMMACULATE.
I REMEMBER WHEN PAWNEE
HAD THAT MASSIVE SEWAGE OVERFLOW
IN CIRCLE PARK--
WHATEVER HAPPENED WITH THAT?
- WE TOTALLY FIXED IT.
- WELL, EXCEPT FOR THE SMELL.
THE SCIENTISTS THINK IT'S GOING
TO LINGER FOR ANOTHER 40 YEARS.
- CAN WE JUST CUT
TO THE CHASE HERE?
WHY WOULD A FANCY
EAGLETON ARCHITECT LIKE YOU
WANT TO DESIGN
A TINY PAWNEE PARK?
- WELL, I HEARD YOUR PLEA
ON THE RADIO,
AND YOU WERE SO PASSIONATE
ABOUT THE PROJECT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF
IT'S A GIANT PARK LIKE THIS
OR A LITTLE TINY
POCKET PARK.
IT'S ABOUT THE PEOPLE.
WE'RE HERE TO SERVE THEM.
- HEY, MR. ST. JAMES!
- OH, OUR BALLOON ARTISAN
IS OUT OF BALLOONS.
EXCUSE ME.
- I HAVE CHILLS.
LOOK AT MY ARM.
- WHY ARE YOU SO CHARMED
BY HIM?
YOU'RE LIKE A SOUTHERN BELLE
WHEN RHETT BUTLER COMES AROUND.
- YES. RHETT BUTLER.
THAT'S WHO HE REMINDS ME OF.
OR BONO!
- WHAT?
NO ONE FROM EAGLETON
HAS EVER WANTED TO HELP
ANYONE FROM PAWNEE
FOR ANY REASON.
IN 1988,
WE WERE HIT BY A TORNADO.
WE ASKED EAGLETON FOR HELP,
AND THEY CLAIMED
THEY WEREN'T HOME.
AN ENTIRE TOWN
CLAIMED THEY WEREN'T HOME.
I DON'T TRUST THAT GUY
FOR A SECOND.
- LESLIE, LOOK WHAT WRESTON
COMMISSIONED
FROM THE BALLOON ARTISAN.
IT'S US.
- GREAT WORK, TEAM.
DONNA, YOU AND YOUR WORK
ARE RAVISHING, AS USUAL.
ANN, GREAT ORGANIZATIONAL
SKILLS.
- WOW. GENUINE PRAISE.
- IT'S A TIP I PICKED UP FROM
LEE IACOCCA'S AUTOBIOGRAPHY.
A SMALL CONNECTION BETWEEN
YOU AND YOUR WORKERS
HELPS BUILD LOYALTY.
JERRY!
HOW'S THE OLD TICKER?
- OH. WELL, UH,
THE REHAB IS GRUELING--
- GREAT!
GLAD TO HEAR IT.
YO, ROOMBA, DROP A BEAT!
- * HI HO, HI HO
- RENT-A-SWAG
IS GONNA BE THE OPPOSITE
OF ENTERTAINMENT720.
THIS IS MY LAST CHANCE.
IF THIS GOES DOWN IN FLAMES,
I WILL HAVE NOTHING
EXCEPT MY LOOKS.
I COULD ALWAYS PIMP MYSELF OUT
TO HOT OLDER LADIES.
I NEED TO REMEMBER THAT.
- MAY, 1817.
A SCRAPPY GROUP
OF FRONTIERSMEN AND WOMEN
ARRIVE AT A HARDSCRABBLE
CHUNK OF LAND
AND CALL IT PAWNEE,
INDIANA.
- WE OWE THEM
A DEBT OF GRATITUDE.
- MM. JUNE, 1817,
THE RICHEST AMONG THEM
TAKE ALL OF THEIR MONEY
FROM THE BANK
AND THEN FLEE UP THE HILL
LIKE COWARDS
TO FORM EAGLETON.
RECOGNIZE ANY OF YOUR ANCESTORS
AMONG THE MEANIES?
- ACTUALLY, LIKE MOST PEOPLE
FROM THE AREA,
I HAVE ANCESTORS
ON BOTH SIDES.
THAT'S WHY I THINK THIS RIVALRY
IS JUST A LITTLE SILLY
AND SELF-DEFEATING.
- YEAH, YOU MAY NOT KNOW THIS,
BUT LESLIE WAS ACTUALLY
BORN IN EAGLETON.
- DO NOT BLAME ME
FOR THE SINS OF MY MOTHER.
- LOOK, MS. KNOPE,
I'M REALLY TRYING HERE,
BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW
IF OUR WORKING TOGETHER
IS SUCH A GREAT IDEA.
- OH...RUNNING AWAY SO SOON.
TYPICAL.
YOU KNOW, SAY WHAT YOU WANT
ABOUT PAWNEEANS,
BUT WE NEVER GIVE UP.
- WE HAVE A MURAL CALLED
"THE MANY SURRENDERS OF PAWNEE."
- OH, LOOK WHO'S PAYING
ATTENTION TO ME NOW!
- OKAY. CAN I SPEAK TO YOU
PRIVATELY FOR A MINUTE?
- THE NAME IS SPECIAL AGENT
BERT MACKLIN.
TELL ME WHO YOU ARE,
WHO YOU WORK FOR,
AND DON'T BOTHER TRYING
TO LIE TO ME,
BECAUSE I'M AMAZING.
- [accent]
MY NAME IS JUDY HITLER,
AND I AM THE SPOILED
ONLY DAUGHTER OF ADOLF.
AND I'M GOING TO TELL MY DADDY
YOU WERE MEAN TO ME,
BERT MACKLIN.
HE'S NOT GOING TO
LIKE IT VERY MUCH.
SO UNTIE ME!
- NICE TRY, MISS HITLER,
BUT YOU HAVE SOMETHING
THAT I WANT.
WHERE'S THE NECKLACE WITH
ALL OF GERMANY'S WAR SECRETS?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT.
- I THINK YOU DO!
- I DON'T!
[thud]
- NOW, YOU GIVE ME
THAT WAR-ENDING NECKLACE,
OR I WILL RESORT TO TORTURE.
- FINE. I WILL SHOW YOU
WHERE IT IS, DAMN IT.
YOU'RE TOO GOOD, MACKLIN.
- DON'T YOU DO IT, HITLER.
DON'T YOU DARE
FALL IN LOVE WITH ME.
OH, HITLER, YOU SEXY BASTARD.
NO!
- YES!
- MM...MM!
AAH!
- I AM JUST FILLED
TO THE BRIM WITH QUESTIONS.
WHY ARE YOU USING
THIS WOOD?
IS IT MORE PLIABLE?
WHAT ARE THESE METAL LATCHES?
ARE THEY COPPER OR BRASS?
IS ONE BETTER?
AND IF SO, WHY?
- IF I TELL YOU, THEN YOU WON'T
HAVE LEARNED ANYTHING.
- [laughs]
ANOTHER IN A LONG LINE
OF LESSONS
FROM THE GREAT RON SWANSON.
MY THERAPIST,
DR. RICHARD NYGARD,
SUGGESTED THAT I TRY SOME
NON-EXERCISE-BASED HOBBIES.
SO I'VE BEEN STUDYING
WOODWORKING WITH RON.
I MADE THIS.
BEFORE I STARTED,
IT WAS BIGGER.
- HERE. I HAVE DESIGNED
SOMETHING VERY IMPORTANT.
WHY DON'T YOU START WORK
ON THAT RIGHT AWAY?
- YES, SIR!
- IT'S A FLIGHT OF STAIRS
THAT LEADS TO NOWHERE.
- WERE YOU LISTENING TO HIM
WHEN HE WAS TALKING ABOUT
SERVING THE PUBLIC
AND MAKING OUR COMMUNITIES
BETTER?
YOU KNOW WHO
HE SOUNDS LIKE, RIGHT?
- YES. IDI AMIN.
OR LORD VOLDEMORT.
- NO. YOU.
NOW, YOU'VE BEEN
VERY RUDE TO HIM,
AND YOU NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
- HA HA HA.
YOU ARE A LAUGH RIOT, BEN.
I AM NEVER GOING TO APOLOGIZE
TO SOMEONE FROM EAGLETON.
- ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU CAN KISS YOUR PARK
AND FOUR YEARS OF WORK
GOOD-BYE.
UP TO YOU.
COME ON. YOU CAN DO IT.
- I DON'T WANT TO.
- YOU CAN--
YOU CAN DO IT.
MR. ST. JAMES,
THIS HAS BEEN A STRANGE DAY.
BUT WE WOULDN'T
WANT TO LEAVE YOU
WITH THE WRONG IMPRESSION
OF PAWNEE.
- HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN HITLER?
- ANYWAY, WE WOULD LOVE
TO HAVE YOU DESIGN THE PARK,
AND IN THE SPIRIT
OF RECONCILIATION,
LESLIE WOULD LIKE TO
APOLOGIZE.
- I MAY HAVE ALLOWED
MY PREJUDICES,
MY TOTALLY LEGITIMATE
PREJUDICES AGAINST EAGLETON
AFFECT MY FEELINGS TOWARDS YOUR
INVOLVEMENT IN THIS PROJECT,
AND SO THEREFORE,
I WOULD LIKE TO SAY THAT I'M--
I'M...
I'M LESLIE KNOPE.
[laughs]
NO.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
I WANT TO SAY. OKAY.
[slapping face]
I'M...
SSS....
MY MOUTH IS KINDA DRY.
MY MOUTH IS DRY.
THIS IS CANADA DRY.
DRINK CANADA DRY
IF YOUR MOUTH IS DRY.
THAT'S NOTHING.
WHAT I WANT TO SAY IS
I'M S...
I'M SOR...
I'M SOR--
HE'S A HUMAN BEING.
YOU'RE A HUMAN BEING.
YOU CAN JUST--
JUST SAY--
I'M SOR--
- OH, MY GOD.
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY THAT I--
I'M SORRY, VERY SORRY,
THAT I WAS RUDE.
IT'S TOO SOON.
- YOU KNOW WHAT,
AS A GESTURE OF GOOD WILL,
I'D LIKE TO WAIVE MY FEE.
I'LL DESIGN THE PARK
PRO BONO.
- THANK YOU.
THAT'S VERY NICE OF YOU.
- I'VE BEEN WORKING UP
A LITTLE MODEL OF THE DESIGN.
WHY DON'T I BRING IT OVER,
AND WE CAN ALL
GO THROUGH IT TOGETHER.
- GREAT. AND THEN YOU CAN
COME TO OUR WEDDING.
- HUH?
- WHAT?
- IT'S IN MAY, AND WE HAVEN'T
PLANNED IT YET,
BUT SAVE THE DATE.
- [accent]
I WAS NEVER HERE.
- AH!
- AAH!
- WELL DONE, TEAM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE PLACE?
- DO YOU REALLY LIKE
THIS YELLOW PAINT?
I MEAN,
I KNOW IT WAS ON SALE,
BUT IT LOOKS A LOT
LIKE DRIED PHLEGM.
- FOR REAL, TOM.
THIS PLACE IS SAD.
I THINK ONE OF THE MANNEQUINS
TRIED TO COMMIT SUICIDE.
- I THINK WHAT'S IMPORTANT
IS WE ALL HAD A GOAL,
AND WE ACHIEVED IT.
- SO YOU LIKE THE PLACE?
- OH, NO, IT'S QUITE TERRIBLE.
- THIS IS THE BEST
I CAN DO FOR NOW.
AND I'M $46 UNDER BUDGET.
NOW I HAVE A SMALL TREAT
FOR YOU GUYS
FOR ALL YOUR HARD WORK.
PIZZA PARTY!
- ONE SMALL PIZZA
FOR ALL OF US.
WITH NO TOPPINGS.
- CHEESE IS A TOPPING, JERRY.
AND WHY ARE THESE LIGHTS
BLARING, BY THE WAY?
DOES SOMEONE HERE OWN STOCK
IN THE ELECTRIC COMPANY?
- IF THERE WERE MORE FOOD
AND FEWER PEOPLE,
THIS WOULD BE A PERFECT PARTY.
- [laughing]
- YOU CAN'T RUN, HITLER.
82ND AIRBORNE
IS EVERYWHERE!
HISTORY CHANNEL.
HO HO HO!
WHAT IS THIS?
A CHILD SPY,
SENT TO STEAL THE NECKLACE?
BERT MACKLIN, FBI!
FREEZE!
- I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
- YEAH, BAD CALL, BERT.
- OH.
OH, HEY, I'M JUST KIDDING,
BUDDY.
I'M JUST PLAYING AROUND.
MY NAME'S REALLY ANDY DWYER.
I'M A SECURITY GUARD.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- JOEY.
I WAS WITH MY MOM,
AND I GOT LOST.
- OH. WELL, GOSH,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I'VE GOTTEN LOST HERE
ABOUT 500 TIMES,
AND I WORK HERE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO
FIND YOUR MOM, HUH?
SHE'S NOT IN THERE,
I'LL BET.
LET'S TRY THIS WAY.
- HELLO?
MS. KNOPE, MR. WYATT?
WE'RE FROM
WRESTON ST. JAMES' FIRM.
- OH, HEY, COME ON IN.
WHERE'S WRESTON?
- HE'S ON HIS WAY.
HE WANTED US TO GET STARTED.
- AW! OH, WELL.
OKAY, I GUESS GO AHEAD.
- WE PRESENT
THE CROWN JEWEL OF PAWNEE
CONTAINING THE SIGHTS, SOUNDS,
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
SMELLS THAT DEFINE YOUR CITY.
- THERE ARE SEVERAL
DROOL BUCKETS
FOR YOUR MORE...
SLACK-JAWED CITIZENS.
WE ALSO HAVE FOOD TROUGHS
FULL OF CHEESEBURGERS
AND PUBLIC SHOWERS
WITH INSTRUCTIONS FOR THOSE
WHO'VE NEVER SHOWERED BEFORE.
- YOU HAVE FIVE SECONDS
TO GET OUT OF HERE...
OR I WILL RIP YOUR THROATS OUT.
- OUT.
NOW.
- OH, HEY, MY BACKYARD
IS BIGGER THAN YOUR PARKS.
[both laughing]
- LESLIE, STAY BACK, STAY BACK.
- I TOLD YOU THAT EAGLETONIANS
ARE AWFUL, TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
THEY CALL THEIR BOOGERS
PAWNEE CAVIAR.
- I'M ON YOUR SIDE,
AND I'M FURIOUS TOO.
BUT THIS JUST DOESN'T
MAKE SENSE TO ME.
I'M GONNA TALK TO WRESTON,
AND I'M GONNA GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
- ANY EXCUSE
TO TALK TO WRESTON.
WELL, I AM GONNA THINK
ABOUT A REVENGE PLAN.
I KNOW WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO.
WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT
WHERE HE LIVES.
WE'RE GONNA DRIVE
TO HIS HOUSE.
WE'RE GONNA SET IT ON FIRE
AND WATCH IT BURN.
- LESLIE, WE CAN'T DO THAT.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE CAN'T.
- ALL RIGHT, SO...
DOES THIS LOOK FAMILIAR?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- I WAS TALKING TO JOEY.
- JOEY!
- MOMMY!
- THERE YOU ARE.
OH, GOD, I WAS SO WORRIED.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU'LL NEVER KNOW HOW MUCH
I APPRECIATE IT.
- WELL, JUST DOING
MY JOB, MA'AM.
- THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME,
ANDY.
THANK YOU, TOO, MISS HITLER.
- WHAT?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WOW. YOU MADE THOSE LOSERS
VERY HAPPY.
- OH, NO, I DIDN'T.
BERT MACKLIN DID.
- NO...
- FBI.
- ACTUALLY,
- BERT MACKLIN KINDA MADE
THAT LITTLE BOY CRY.
- WELL, HE'S A ROGUE AGENT WHO
REFUSES TO PLAY BY THE RULES.
- SERIOUSLY, I THINK ANDY DWYER
MAKES A BETTER REAL COP
THAN BERT MACKLIN.
MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR BERT MACKLIN
TO HANG UP HIS SHADES.
- CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING
TO DRINK?
- ICED TEA, PLEASE.
AND CAN I ASK YOU,
HOW ARE THERE PALM TREES
HERE?
- WELL, EAGLETON LIES
ON TOP OF A HOT SPRING
WHICH CREATES
A MICRO-CLIMATE ZONE.
WE ARE...[chuckles]
TRULY BLESSED.
- GOD, I'M SO SORRY
I'M LATE.
- WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED,
MAN?
- I HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT STUPID PRANK.
IN FACT,
THAT'S WHY I'M LATE.
I WAS FIRING THE TWO PEOPLE
WHO WERE RESPONSIBLE,
AND I WAS ESCORTING THEM
OUT OF THE BUILDING.
- WELL...GOOD!
- FULL DISCLOSURE:
CERTAIN PEOPLE IN THE FIRM
WANTED TO PROMOTE THEM,
BUT I INSISTED THEY BE FIRED.
- IF YOU SWEAR TO ME
THAT YOU'RE SERIOUS,
MAYBE WE CAN SALVAGE THIS.
- I WOULD REALLY LOVE TO.
BUT WHAT ABOUT LESLIE?
I JUST DOUBT
THAT SHE CAN EVER GET OVER
THE BAD BLOOD
BETWEEN OUR TOWNS.
- I THINK YOU'RE WRONG.
LESLIE
IS A VERY FORGIVING PERSON.
- REVENGE!
HA HA HA1
THIS IS FOR PAWNEE,
YOU BUTT-FACED POMPOUS JERK!
WHOO!
I LOVE YOU, BEN.
PAWNEE FOREVER!
YOU WANT A STUPID TIE?
I'LL GIVE YOU A STUPID TIE.
HA HA!
WRESTON, SUCK IT.
NOW WE'RE EVEN.
- LESLIE.
- HUH?
- HE DIDN'T DO IT,
AND HE FIRED THE PEOPLE
WHO DID.
[cans clatter on ground]
[running footsteps]
- ATTENTION, PLEASE.
I'VE BEEN GOING OVER
THE BOOKS,
AND I'M MISSING $9.
NOW, I'M NOT ANGRY
AT WHOEVER TOOK IT.
JUST COME FORWARD.
YOU'LL BE SERVED
WITH A LAWSUIT,
AND WE WILL MOVE ON
WITH OUR LIVES.
- HEY, BUDDY, LET'S GO GET
SOME BREAKFAST, OKAY?
- FINE. IT WAS YOUR IDEA,
SO YOU'RE PAYING.
YOU'RE DRIVING.
I'M NOT CHIPPING IN FOR GAS.
- OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
- I'LL HAVE
THE PANCAKE BREAKFAST.
OH, LET ME ALSO GET
12 EGGS, UNCOOKED,
AND SOME TOAST.
20 SLICES, UNTOASTED,
IN A ROW IN A BAG.
- YOU WANT A CARTON OF EGGS
AND A LOAF OF BREAD.
- YEAH, JUST THE PANCAKE
BREAKFAST IS FINE.
- DON'T OFFER TO PAY
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE CHEAP.
- LISTEN, MAN, I KNOW YOU DON'T
WANT TO REPEAT THE MISTAKES
OF ENTERTAINMENT 720,
AND THAT'S GREAT,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA NEED
A LITTLE BIT OF THE OLD TOM
TO MAKE THIS BUSINESS WORK.
- NO. THAT TOM RUINED
EVERYTHING.
- YES, HE DID,
AND THAT TOM MADE YOU
A HORRIBLE BOYFRIEND
AND A TERRIBLE EMPLOYEE
AND DROVE YOU TO BANKRUPTCY.
- ARE WE NEARING THE POINT?
- BUT YOUR SWAGGER
AND YOUR SHOWMANSHIP
AND YOUR CONFIDENCE
IS PART OF YOU,
AND IN SMALL DOSES,
IT CAN HELP.
YOU CAN'T HAVE RENT-A-SWAG
WITHOUT THE SWAG.
- I BARELY HAVE ENOUGH CASH
TO GET EVERYTHING SET UP.
- I KNOW.
TAKE THIS.
WE ALL CHIPPED IN.
USE IT TO SPRUCE UP THE STORE.
AND IN RETURN YOU CAN GIVE US
LIKE ONE SHARE OF STOCK
IN THE COMPANY.
- LIKE A MINI PUBLIC OFFERING.
"SMORT", ANN.
SMORT.
THIS IS A CAUSE
FOR CELEBRATION.
WAITER! EIGHT STRIPS
OF BACON, UNCOOKED,
IN A SEALED PACKAGE.
- I CALL IT
THE PAWNEE COMMONS,
A CELEBRATION OF PAWNEE'S
HISTORY AND PEOPLE.
- A WAMAPOKE-THEMED
PLAYGROUND...
GOOD TRUCKS
FROM LOCAL RESTAURANTS,
LI'L SEBASTIAN FOUNTAIN.
I MEAN, IT'S PERFECT.
- THANK YOU.
- I CAN'T SEE MYSELF
FIGHTING YOU
ON MORE THAN
60% OF THESE IDEAS.
- I'D EXPECT NO LESS.
I'M JUST GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
I'VE NEVER MET TWO PEOPLE
MORE PASSIONATE
ABOUT THEIR HOMETOWN.
- OH, I'M ACTUALLY FROM
MINNESOTA.
- WHY DO YOU KNOW SO MUCH
ABOUT PAWNEE?
- WELL, I'M IN LOVE
WITH A WOMAN FROM HERE.
A STRANGE, PASSIONATE,
GOOFBALL OF A WOMAN.
- [giggles]
ME. HE'S IN LOVE WITH ME.
- I'M SORRY TO SEE YOU GO,
MACKLIN.
YOU DIDN'T ALWAYS
PLAY BY THE RULES,
BUT DAMN IT,
YOU WERE A HELL OF AN AGENT.
- TODAY I SAY GOOD-BYE TO
THE ONLY LIFE I'VE EVER KNOWN.
- WELL, SOME OF THE BOYS
CHIPPED IN
AND WE GOT YOU...THIS.
IT ISN'T MUCH, BUT IT'S
SOMETHING TO REMEMBER US BY.
- 40 YEARS UNDERCOVER.
I NEVER EVEN MET MY FAMILY.
- WHAT?
- AND THIS IS ALL I HAVE
TO SHOW FOR IT?
TOTALLY WORTH IT.
- IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE
SERVING WITH YOU, SON.
- IF YOU EVER NEED ME,
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND ME--
IN BED NEXT TO YOU,
PROBABLY HAVING SEX WITH YOU.
[triggers cock]
[21 gun salute]
[shell casings clatter]
[gunshots,
casings clattering]
[gunshots, clattering]
- WELCOME TO THE NEW
NEW RENT-A-SWAG
NOW WITH 30% MORE SWAG.
I USED THE MONEY
YOU GUYS GAVE ME
TO ADD A LITTLE FLAIR,
AND I TOOK EVERYTHING
I OWN IN MY HOUSE
AND BROUGHT IT HERE,
EXCEPT FOR MY BED.
I BASICALLY LIVE HERE NOW.
- I HATE ALL OF THIS,
WHICH PROBABLY MEANS
IT'S GOOD FOR YOUR BUSINESS.
- RON, MY WOODWORKING PROJECT--
IT'S FOR DISPLAYING SHOES!
-YES. THAT WAS ALWAYS
THE PLAN.
- ALL RIGHT,
RENT-A-SWAG TEAM,
I HAVE ONE MORE LITTLE
SURPRISE FOR YOU--PIZZA PARTY!
PART 2.
- OH, WOW!
TWO PIZZAS.
AND TOPPINGS!
- ONLY ON HALF.
I'M NOT ZUCKERBERG.
EAT UP, CHUMPS.