- We need the river
for access.
- What about the other area
downstream?
- We can't afford them both,
Simeon.
- Well, we've got to.
If anyone else
starts prospecting,
we'll have lost
all that we've done
over the last six months.
- There.
That's my share for the claim.
- I'm off at first light.
I should make Pretoria
in four days.
- And be back in ten, eh?
- And in six months...
we'll be rich.
Good night, Gerrit.
- Good night.
- Who the hell are you?
- Stella de Zuigder.
And you?
- Lee.
Simeon Lee.
How long have I been here?
- This is your third day.
You'd have died in half a day
if we hadn't have found you.
- Thanks.
I was, uh, mauled by a lion.
- Yeah, I know.
I took the bullet out.
- All right.
My partner attacked me.
- That's what diamonds do
to people, eh?
Don't worry.
They're safe.
And your map.
It's a bit bloodstained,
though.
- Do you, uh...
live out here
all by yourself?
- My father got tired
of trying to marry me off.
- Simeon?
Simeon?
Simeon!
- Happy Christmas.
- And to you, sir.
Thank you very much.
- Well, that's
the last decent meal I'll get
till the New Year I expect.
- You are not looking forward
to your Christmas,
Chief Inspector?
- We're going to Mrs. Japp's
family in Wales.
- Ah.
- If they start singing again...
- I shall think of you,
Chief Inspector,
as I sit down
to my simple repast.
For Poirot,
it will be a quiet Christmas,
with my radio perhaps,
a book,
and a box of exquisite
Belgian chocolates.
- Well, listen, Poirot.
Think of me on Christmas morning
when you open this.
- Oh, thank you very much,
Chief Inspector.
- Merry Christmas, Poirot.
- Merry Christmas to you.
- Oh, yes, of course.
There we are, my dear.
- Thank you, sir.
- And a very happy Christmas
to you.
- And to you.
- Thank you.
- All right, all right,
I'm not a child.
Bring them in.
- Mr. Simeon Lee?
- Yes.
Have you got them?
Get out.
Get out, all of you!
- Beg pardon.
Voilà.
- Can I help you?
- Yes, Monsieur Dicker?
- Yes.
- Monsieur Dicker,
my radiator, it has gone cold.
And there is a--
- The boiler is broken, sir.
- Well, then the boiler,
it must be repaired.
- It will be
after Christmas, sir.
- After Christmas?
That is most unsatisfactory.
- Unfortunately,
I can't do anything about it.
- I don't--
- I cannot get ahold
of a plumber, sir,
until after the holidays.
- I see.
I see.
- I'm sorry about it,
but there's nothing I can do.
- Au revoir, Monsieur Dicker.
Oh, non.
Yes?
- Hercule Poirot?
- Yes, it is I,
Hercule Poirot, who speaks.
- I need a detective
to come and stay here
in my house for Christmas.
- Non, monsieur, I...
- Don't say no just like that.
Hear me out.
Superintendent Sugden
of the Shropshire Police
recommended you.
- I do not know him.
- I don't care
if you don't know him.
He knows you.
My life is in danger.
- Have you received
any threats, Monsieur...
- Lee.
Simeon Lee.
Ah, well, you'd have to be here
to understand.
- Tell to me if you please,
Monsieur Lee,
does your house have
the central heating?
- What?
Yes, of course.
- Very well.
Poirot will be there tomorrow.
Give to me, if you please,
your address.
- Help the needy at Christmas.
- Thank you so much, sir.
Thank you.
- Madam?
Help the needy at Christmas?
Oh.
- Are you ready to order, sir?
- Yes.
Thank you very much.
But please to tell me,
what is this
brown Windsor soup?
- Well, sir, it's soup...
from Windsor.
- I see.
Then I will have
this brown Windsor soup,
followed by the...
and a side order of lamb,
separate...
- Okay if I share your table?
- Of course.
Well, I'll be glad
to get out of London,
I don't mind telling you.
Oh, it's a terrible place.
- But you are English, no?
- Been abroad for years.
What about you?
- I am Spanish.
- Did you see
any of this, uh,
civil war business
over in Spain?
- I saw a bomb drop.
And it blew up a car.
- That didn't upset you?
- One is alive for a time
in this world, yes,
and then one is dead.
And one's friends are sad,
and one's enemies rejoice.
- Don't you believe
in forgiving your enemies,
señorita?
- No.
I do not.
If I had an enemy,
I would cut his throat,
like this.
I wouldn't like to be
your enemy, señorita.
- But it does not look very...
délicieux.
- Well, sir,
it is brown Windsor soup.
- What, um,
brings you to England?
- I am going to stay
with my English relations.
They are very rich, I think.
They live in a big house
called Gorston Hall.
- Good God.
- What is it?
- You must be Jennifer's girl.
- My mother's name was Jennifer.
- I'm Harry Lee.
Jennifer was my sister.
Do the family know
you're coming?
- Oh, yes.
- That's more than they do
with me.
- He's playing God
as he always does.
It's the role he enjoys most.
- Well, I think
it's extremely boring.
- Well, boring or not,
it's our duty to be here,
Magdalene.
Moreover, it enables us
to save considerably.
- But we shouldn't have to
scrimp and save like this.
Well, can't you make your father
give you some more money?
- He upped my allowance
last year.
- And what happens when he dies?
- The bulk of his money
comes to Alfred and myself.
- Isn't there another brother?
- No.
No, no.
Harry left years ago.
We don't talk about him,
incidentally.
A very disreputable character.
- Well, your father's not
all that reputable, George.
- What on earth
do you mean by that?
- When he gets me alone,
he makes me feel
quite uncomfortable.
The things he says.
- Yes, yes.
Well, one has to make
allowances.
- It isn't only
the things he says.
- At Father's age,
with his health being so bad...
- Must you always
give in to him, Alfred?
- He's a very old man, Lydia.
- Then he'll get older
and more tyrannical.
But why must we have George
and Magdalene for Christmas?
- Father hasn't seen George
for a long time.
He's very good to us,
you know, Lydia.
- Oh, Alfred!
Magdalene's going to be
frightfully bored, anyway.
- Well, why George has to go
and marry a girl
20 years younger than himself,
I shall never know.
He always was a fool.
- I suppose she's been
quite a help to him
in his constituency.
- What is it, Horbury?
- Beg pardon, sir.
Is it convenient
if I take the car?
Mr. Lee has asked me
to go to the station
and meet some more guests.
- Some more guests?
- Wait a minute!
Come in!
- We have just seen Horbury,
and he says that--
- Ah, Lydia, my dear.
What a nice color you've got.
- He says there are to be
more guests for Christmas.
- Just straighten
my legs for me,
would you, my dear?
It's a terrible thing
to get old, Lydia.
- Who are these people
that are coming?
- Well, first of all,
there's my old friend
Hercule Poirot.
- Who's he?
- A friend.
And then there's Pilar.
- Pilar?
- Pilar Estravados,
Jennifer's girl,
my granddaughter.
- But you didn't tell me.
- It's going to be
a grand Christmas!
All my children round me.
There, now, Alfred.
There's your clue.
Guess who the other visitor is.
- But you haven't got
any more...
- Your brother, Harry,
of course.
- What do you think
of the spats?
And the patent leather shoes?
- Just the thing
for a weekend in the country.
And those mustachios
must have enough wax in them
to keep Madame Tussauds
going for a fortnight.
- Miss Estravados?
- Yes.
- Mr. Simeon Lee sent me
to meet you.
Mr. Harry Lee?
- Sure.
- I'll put your bags
in the boot.
Mr. Poirot?
- Are you a friend
of the old bastard Simeon?
- I am a friend of Mr. Lee, yes.
- There's no good
you calling him Mr. Lee, chum.
There'll be more Mr. Lees
than you can shake a stick at
at Gorston this X-mas.
And I'm one of 'em.
Harry Lee's the name.
- Hercule Poirot.
- Pardon?
- Poirot.
Hercule Poirot.
- French, eh?
- Non.
- I'm her long lost uncle.
Tell him your name, Pilar.
- Pilar Estravados.
- You two should get on,
being foreign.
- Alfred, the car's arrived.
What are you doing?
- I'm writing a note to Father,
protesting in the strongest
possible terms--
- A note!
Whatever good do you think
notes are going to do?
Bless my soul.
If it ain't Tressilian!
How are you, Tressilian?
- Mr. Harry!
- Still here, eh?
- Miss.
- Still the same ugly old dump.
- You don't look very tough.
- Hercule Poirot is a detective,
not a bodyguard, monsieur.
- Oh, is he?
Got a brain, has he?
Well, good thing somebody has.
All my sons are
complete nincompoops.
I've probably got better sons
scattered all over the world,
born on the wrong side
of the blanket.
My family hate me, you know.
- It is not hard to see why,
Monsieur Lee.
- They're frightened of me.
- It is often the way
with men who are old and rich.
- Well, anyway,
I'm going to make
an announcement this evening,
and then they'll have
good cause to hate me.
What do you want?
- You wanted to see
Miss Estravados, sir.
She's outside.
- All right.
One more minute.
- What is it that you wish me
to do here, Monsieur Lee?
- Keep your eyes open.
Keep your ears open.
- Bien.
What am I looking for?
What am I listening for?
- You'll know when it happens.
- Tressilian is taking
your bags to your room, sir.
- Thank you.
- I've been
a very wicked man, Pilar.
What do you think
of that?
- The nuns say
all men are wicked.
- Nuns?
But I don't regret it.
I've enjoyed
every moment of it.
I've cheated,
and I've stolen, and I've lied.
And the women!
Are you shocked, Pilar?
- Why should I be shocked?
Men always desire women.
That is why wives are unhappy
and go to church and pray.
- You are the devil's brat.
- Oh, you like me to sit here
with you, Grandfather?
- Yes, I do.
It's a long time
since I was close
to anything as young
and beautiful as you are.
It warms my old bones.
Ah, but you don't fool me.
Don't think I don't know
why you sit here
listening to me droning on.
Money.
All right.
I'll show you something.
I just got these yesterday
from the company museum
in Pretoria.
These are
the first diamonds
I ever took
from my first mine.
- But they are little pebbles;
that is all.
- They are uncut.
That's how diamonds are
when they're found.
- Well, why do you
not have them cut?
- Because I like them
like this.
It all comes back to me.
The sunshine,
the oxen,
and the smell of the veldt
and the quiet
of the evenings.
- It is unfortunate
that these so-called Republicans
have forced him to take
the action he has taken.
But take it from me,
Generalissimo Franco
has right on his side.
- Well, yes,
it is always reassuring
to hear the opinion
of an expert on these matters.
- Can I top anybody's glass up?
- You're very tanned.
Have you spent time
in South Africa too,
like your father?
- Only a year or two.
I've been
in Argentina mostly.
Well, apart from
my time in Macao.
- I'm afraid I've been
absolutely nowhere.
- Could I have a word, Lydia?
I'm sorry.
- Excuse me.
- I've remembered
who this Hercule Poirot is.
He's a detective.
- The police?
Oh, surely not.
- He's one of those
private detectives.
- But why should your father
want to...
- Excuse me, sir.
- What is it, Horbury?
- Mr. Lee is ready
to see you all now.
- Come in!
Hello.
Is that you, Charlton?
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry to trouble you
at home,
but it is rather urgent.
I want you to make
a new will for me.
Yes.
Sit down.
I won't be long.
Yes, well, you see,
it's some time
since the other will was made,
and things have changed.
No, no, no.
I don't want
to spoil your Christmas.
Come over on Boxing Day
or the next day, yes, yes.
I shan't be dying just yet!
Good-bye.
You're all looking
very glum.
What's the matter?
Harry.
I'd have known you anywhere,
even after all these years.
Your taste in clothes
hasn't improved, I see.
- Good to see you, Dad.
You're looking well.
- Fortunately,
I did not ask you all up here
for the pleasure of seeing
your smiling faces
but because I want to say
that we have to reorganize
things a bit
now that we have two more people
living in the house.
- What do you mean?
- Pilar will make her home
with us here, naturally.
And Harry is home for good.
- Harry's coming to live here?
- What's wrong with that,
old boy?
- Harry is my son too,
you know, George.
Of course,
it is going to mean
cutting back a little
in other areas.
Your allowance, for instance,
George, will have to go.
- You can't do that, Father.
You don't understand how heavy
my expenses are already.
- Oh?
Well, let your wife
do her bit then.
She could make
her own clothes.
Even my wife could make
her own clothes,
and she was one
of the most stupid women
it's been
my sorrow to meet.
- You've no right to talk
about our mother like that.
- Right?
Right!
You've no rights, any of you.
You're just a set
of namby-pamby weaklings!
Has any of you produced
one grandson for me?
No!
- Hold hard, Dad.
- I'm just sick to death
of the lot of you.
Get out!
Get out, all of you!
- What's got into him?
- Go to hell!
- I blame you, Alfred.
You've had
charge of him here.
- What are you talking about?
- I think there's a case for
getting a doctor in right away.
- A doctor?
There's nothing wrong
with him.
- He's clearly
not of sound mind.
Two doctors, isn't it?
- Ladies, shall we?
- Shall I announce you,
superintendent?
- That's all right, Tressilian.
Mr. Lee's expecting me.
- Come and have some coffee.
The gentlemen will be
through in a minute.
- Over here?
- It's wonderful
that you could come, Pilar.
- It's wonderful for me
to meet my uncles and aunts
and this grand house.
- After seven years?
- But I've got these blokes
chasing me for cash!
- I was having a word
at a cocktail party with Buffy,
and you know he has
the ear of the PM.
- Who was it?
- Mr. Sugden.
Superintendent of police.
Watch what you're doing!
- I'm sorry, Mr. Tressilian.
- You've got no right
to go touching things.
- What did he want,
this police superintendent?
- He's collecting
for the police orphanage.
- Oh?
And did he get anything?
- I'm sure he did.
- We'll be having more snow
tonight, I shouldn't wonder.
- We'll be cut off again,
if we're not careful.
- Good night, ladies.
- Going to the pictures?
- I expect so.
- It's coming from Dad's room!
- It's locked!
It's locked!
Dad!
- We're gonna have to break
the door down.
- Don't be a fool.
It's made of solid oak.
- Quick!
Battering ram!
- What's going on?
- One, two, three!
- Try again, harder.
- What does this mean?
- What was that terrible noise?
- One, two, three!
Again.
One, two, three!
- You've got to put
some more effort into it.
- One, two, three!
One more should do it.
One, two, three!
- Dad!
- Excuse-moi, monsieur.
- I've forgotten my book.
- I didn't know
whether to open it, sir.
- What's going on?
- Something's happened
upstairs, sir.
- Superintendent, I was just
going to telephone the police.
I would've used
old Mr. Lee's phone,
but they told me
not to touch anything.
Oh, dear.
- What?
- It's old Mr. Lee, sir.
Mr. Simeon,
he's been killed!
Murdered!
- My God, what a shambles.
Nothing must be touched.
- All right.
I want this room cleared.
- Who are you?
- Police.
Superintendent Sugden.
- You got here very quickly.
- Would everybody
please wait downstairs?
Excuse me, miss.
Nothing must be touched
or disturbed.
- She knows that.
- You picked up something
from the floor just now.
- I did?
- It's in your hand now.
Please give it to me.
Ah.
You must be Mr. Poirot.
- Superintendent.
- Lucky we had a detective
here on the spot.
- Perhaps.
- Stay in here, would you?
- Look!
- Don't touch it.
- It is where he kept
his diamonds.
They have gone.
- What are you doing here,
Poirot?
- I've come to rescue you,
mon ami.
The Superintendent Sugden was
going to call in Scotland Yard
in any case,
so I suggested that,
as you were just
across the border...
- Well, it must have been
the work of a lunatic.
- That's your theory, is it?
- Isn't there some mental home
in the vicinity?
A homicidal maniac.
- How do you suppose
this homicidal maniac
gained admittance
to the house, Mr. Lee?
The only door that wasn't locked
was the kitchen door,
and the kitchen staff didn't see
any homicidal maniacs.
- Well...
- Pardon.
- No, come in, Mr. Poirot.
- I have the Chief Inspector
Japp with me, superintendent.
- Japp?
- Oui.
- From Scotland Yard?
This is a pleasure indeed,
Chief Inspector.
- Thank you, sir.
- I expect you're used to this
kind of thing, Chief Inspector,
but murders are few
and far between
in this part
of the country.
- I imagine so, sir.
- Well...
I was just about to ask
Mr. George Lee
the crucial question.
- Oh, yes?
- Which is, of course,
Mr. Lee,
where were you
at the time of the murder?
- I was in here...
on the telephone...
calling my agent
in Westeringham,
as a matter of fact.
- So you were actually
in this room
when you heard
the noises from upstairs?
- The crashing about
and screaming.
Yes.
- Mr. Poirot tells me
these diamonds
have gone from the safe, sir.
- Yes, I'm getting a few more
men in from Shrewsbury
to do a thorough search
of the house and grounds.
But the theft of the diamonds
may not be
as indicative as it seems.
- Forgive me,
but I don't understand,
superintendent.
- Mr. Lee telephoned me
yesterday afternoon.
He wanted me to come over
and see him at 8:15.
Made a special point
of the time.
What's more, he told me
to tell the butler
that I was collecting
for some police charity.
- Ah.
- Well, Mr. Lee is an important
person in these parts,
so I did as he said.
He told me that
several thousand pounds' worth
of uncut diamonds
had been stolen from his safe...
he thought.
- He thought?
- He said they definitely
were missing
but that only two people
could have done it,
and one of them
might have done it as a joke.
- I have yet to meet anybody
in this household,
superintendent,
that has even the most
rudimentary sense of humor.
- He didn't happen to name
these people, did he, sir?
- No, he didn't,
Chief Inspector.
But it's odd.
He wanted me
to go away
and come back again
in about an hour.
Said he'd have
a clearer idea then
about if he'd been robbed
or if it was a joke.
I can tell you,
by this time,
I was getting
pretty fed up with Mr. Lee.
- But of the two people
that he suspected,
is it possible that one
could be a servant
and the other
a member of his family?
- And if it was family,
he didn't want
to drop them in it?
- Well, yes.
Perhaps my visit
was just meant to put
the frighteners on them.
- So you left?
- Yes, I did.
It wasn't worth my while
going all the way home,
so I went
and sat in the car.
I was just on my way back--
I was to use
leaving the orphanage
subscription book behind
as an excuse--
when all this hell
broke loose.
- What's been going on in here?
- Simeon Lee was a man who
was shrunken, old, and frail,
n'est-ce pas?
And yet all this.
It signifies,
do you not think so,
Chief Inspector?
- Looks more like
a five-star riot
than a simple throat-cutting.
This door was locked, you say?
- Yes.
- May I?
- There are no prints on it,
apart from the old man's.
- Ah, you observe
the little scratches
at the end of the barrel,
Chief Inspector?
- It's been turned
from the outside,
using long-nosed pliers.
- But why, mon ami?
So that we would think
that Simeon Lee
locked the door himself
and that it was suicide?
That is a suicide most strange,
n'est-ce pas.
Who hurls around the room
all the furniture
and then screams
before he commits the act?
- Suppose Mr. Lee
put up more resistance
than the murderer expected
and made such a racket
that he had to get out quick
before he had time
to put the room to rights.
- He couldn't have got out
through the window?
- All bolted shut.
- This one isn't.
- But it's locked in
that position for ventilation.
- But is it not a possibility
that Simeon Lee
did, in fact, commit a suicide
but wanted it
to look like murder?
- Why would he do that?
- Because Simeon Lee was a man
most vengeful, Chief Inspector,
and had not a great love
for his family.
- Blimey.
- Superintendent,
what was it
that Mademoiselle Estravados
picked up from the floor
in the room
of Monsieur Simeon Lee?
- Oh, last night?
- Oui.
- Here.
In detective stories,
it's the sort of thing
that solves
the whole mystery.
What do you think?
- A little wooden peg.
And a little rubber ring.
- Keep them if you like.
If they've got anything
to do with the murder,
I'll retire
from the police force.
- No, no, no, no.
I would not deprive you
of them, mon ami.
Tell me, what was it
that made you recommend me
to Monsieur Simeon Lee?
- I didn't.
- Ah.
- What time was it
you went out last night?
- Just after 8:00.
I went to the cinema
in Oswestry.
It's only ten minutes
on the bus.
- Anybody see you there?
- I was with a young lady.
- Oh, yes?
What's her name?
- Doris Buckle, sir.
She works in the United Dairies
at Markham Road.
I didn't have anything
to do with this, sir.
- What can you tell us
about the diamonds
Mr. Lee kept in his safe?
- Nothing, sir.
They arrived
the day before yesterday.
Mr. Lee said they came from his
old company museum in Africa.
It's not very pleasant
when the murder happens
in a house.
- Nobody said it was.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Can I help you?
- No, no, thank you.
I'm just looking.
- Christmas presents, is it?
- Oui.
- For the wife?
- Uh, no, no, no.
No,
if you please, monsieur,
I should like to buy the present
for a good friend.
- With a sense of humor,
I dare say.
- Well...
- Bulb-operated hairy spider?
- Oh!
No.
Thank you.
- My three-in-one packet
of itching powder,
ink blot,
and stink bombs?
- No, no, no.
No, you see, my friend,
he is a policeman.
- Oh.
He won't be wanting
the Sherlock Holmes
detective set then?
- I do not imagine so, non.
- Cigars?
- Exploding?
- Jamaican.
- Ah!
Bon.
Bonjour, Madame Lee.
Bonjour, monsieur.
- Good morning, Mr. Poirot.
- Pardon, madame, but I do not
understand that which you do.
- Oh, it's just
a hobby of mine:
miniature gardens.
Um, this one's a desert oasis.
And this will be
an Italian vineyard
when it's finished.
And this is a Japanese garden.
Do you see all the stones?
- C'est charmant.
- Mr. Poirot,
why did my father-in-law
ask you to Gorston?
- To tell you the truth,
madame, I am not sure.
He told to me
that his life was in danger.
- But from whom?
- He did not specify.
- There is somebody
I don't trust.
Horbury's only been
with us a year and...
- Tell me, madame.
At the time of the murder,
your husband,
he was in the dining room
with Monsieur Harry?
Where were you?
- I was in the drawing room
having coffee.
- So you were alone?
- No, no,
the Spanish girl was there.
No, no, she wasn't.
She went out
a couple of minutes before.
First, Magdalene went,
and then Pilar went.
- So you were quite alone?
- Yes, I suppose I was.
- And tell me,
who was the first to arrive
at the door
of your father-in-law?
- I was.
- It's locked!
It's locked!
- And you saw there
no other person,
no other person
who came out of the room?
- Of course not.
- Tell me, Monsieur Lee.
I have to, I'm afraid,
ask the questions
most obvious
as well as
the subtle ones.
Did you know
the combination of the safe
belonging to your father?
- No.
Nobody did.
But it would have been
easy enough to discover.
You must find out who did
this awful thing, Mr. Poirot.
You must find out!
- Very violent sort of blokes,
these Africans.
- Europeans do not figure
too badly
in the arts of violence,
Chief Inspector.
- But it gives you the creeps,
this place, doesn't it?
- You are too sensitive,
mon ami.
- That's true.
- Chief Inspector...
- What is it, Poirot?
- We know
of two possible motives
for the murder
of Monsieur Simeon Lee.
One is a simple case
of the theft of the diamonds.
- And the other's
old Simeon's will.
Did someone want him dead
before he could make
the changes he was threatening?
- Précisément.
- No, no, no, no.
You'll go in-off
if you do that.
Now, grip the butt
of the cue firmly...
and...
- Ah, good morning.
Mr. Harry Lee,
I presume?
- And who are you?
- Chief Inspector Japp,
Scotland Yard.
- Ah, brought in the big guns,
have they?
- I'd like a word
with Miss Es-trah-vados.
- Estra-vah-dos.
- Yes.
In private.
- Don't let them bully you, kid.
- Now, then, Miss Estra--
- Vados.
- Estravados.
Quite.
You understand English
all right, do you?
- My mother was English.
I am really
a very English person.
- Is your passport English?
- It is Spanish.
- We'd better have a look
at that, if you don't mind.
- It's in my luggage I think.
- So your grandfather sent
for you to come from Spain,
and you arrived here yesterday;
is that right?
- Yes.
- Tell me, mademoiselle,
when you--
- Sorry; I was looking
for Sergeant Coombes.
Please, don't let me interrupt.
- When you first met
your grandfather,
what did you think of him?
- He was very, very old.
He had to sit in a chair,
and his face was all dried up.
But I like him all the same.
I think that
when he was a young man,
he must have been
very handsome.
Like you.
- There you are, sir.
- I think I'd better go
and find Sergeant Coombes.
- Now, these diamonds
that have been stolen...
- They were not like diamonds,
just very ugly little stones.
- So he showed them to you,
did he?
Didn't give you any of them,
I suppose?
- No.
But I thought
that one day he would,
if I was very nice to him
and came often
to sit with him,
because old men--
they like very much
young girls.
- Tell me, mademoiselle.
Who do you think
stole them?
- Horbury.
- Why do you say that?
- He has the face
of a thief.
His eyes go so...
from side to side,
and he listens at doors.
- Where were you when the crime
was committed, Miss Estravados?
- I went up to my room.
I remember the butler
had just brought in the coffee.
But I wanted
a clean handkerchief,
so I went upstairs.
I was sitting
at my dressing table,
repairing my makeup.
And then far away,
I heard a scream
and everybody running,
and so I went too.
- I see.
So you were all by yourself,
up in your bedroom,
when Simeon Lee died?
- Yes.
Yes, I was.
- Here, Sergeant!
- Empty.
- Whose room is this?
- It's that member
of Parliament's
and his wife's.
- You know what I think, Poirot?
- Non, Chief Inspector.
What is it that you think?
- I think this murder
was done by a woman.
That's what I think.
- And why is it
that you think that?
- Right.
- Merci.
- Simeon Lee was
a frail, old man, yes?
- Monsieur Simeon Lee was a man
of the frailness extreme, oui.
- Then how do you account
for the furniture in his room
being knocked about
all over the shop like it was?
I mean, he couldn't have put up
much of a struggle
against a man, could he?
But against a woman...
- Ah, Chief Inspector,
you have been thinking again.
I have warned you
of this before.
- Oh, well.
- But you know, seriously,
Chief Inspector,
all of the family,
the women included,
they will have alibis
for the time of the murder.
- Well, the lovely
Magdalene Lee's
is pretty flimsy,
and it was her luggage
we found the diamond case in.
- If I'd stolen the diamonds,
do you really think
I'd be stupid enough
to leave the box
in my own luggage?
- Would you tell us
where you were
at the time of the murder,
Mrs. Lee?
- In the drawing room.
- In the drawing room
with Mrs. Lydia Lee?
- Um...no.
I'd come in here
to telephone.
- Was anybody
in the room with you?
- No.
It was a private call.
I was alone.
- How long were you in here,
Madame Lee?
- What's it got to do with you?
- Just answer the question.
- How should I know?
15 minutes?
20?
You know how long it takes
to put a call through
in the evening.
- It was a trunk call then?
- Well, of course it was.
You don't honestly think
I'd know anybody
in this godforsaken dump,
do you?
- Well, one of them's lying.
The lovely Magdalene
can't have been
in there alone
making a phone call,
the same time
as her husband was
in there alone
making a phone call.
- Exactement.
Perhaps we should tax them
with this together,
Chief Inspector.
- Here's another thing
I've been thinking, Poirot...
- Boy!
On the desk in my room,
you'll find my spectacles.
- In your room, madam?
- There's something not quite
English about this murder.
- Comment?
- This throat-slitting.
Not quite our style.
What'll you have then, Poirot?
- Well, that's very kind of you,
Chief Inspector.
A glass of dry white wine.
- Wine?
- A Muscadet, perhaps?
- Well, they might have
some cider.
- Hello, Hercule.
How are you doing?
Let me buy you a drink.
- Non, merci.
The Chief Inspector Japp
is already buying me one.
- So...it was
the glamorous Magdalene
had the diamonds all the time
I hear.
- Uh...the leather box
but not the diamonds.
- Ah.
- Ah, Mr. Lee,
I've been looking for you.
- Well, you only had to look
in the nearest pub.
But tell me, though.
What do you think
of the opening times
in this country?
- Sit down for a minute.
Good health.
What made you decide
to return to England
after all these years?
- I thought the fatted calf
would make a welcome change.
No, my father wrote to me
a year or so ago,
suggesting that I came home,
so I came.
- And, Monsieur Alfred,
how did he feel
about your return?
- Alfred's always been
jealous of me.
You see, he was the good,
stay-at-home,
stick-in-the-mud son.
- Mm.
Tell me, Monsieur Lee.
What do you think was
the purpose of the confrontation
that your father had
with his family
before dinner last evening?
He wanted to see the fur fly.
He was watching us
like a cat
to see how we reacted.
- What changes in his will was
he thinking about; do you know?
- I imagined...
shall I say, I hoped...
the change would be
to the benefit
of your humble servant.
Pilar, too,
I wouldn't be surprised.
- You got any theories
about this murder, Mr. Lee?
- I don't understand it at all.
I mean, that door was locked.
It took some doing
to break it open.
And there was no one
in the room but Dad.
Nobody could have got out
through the window.
- The door was locked
from the outside.
- No, key was on the inside.
- You noticed that,
Monsieur Lee?
- Well...
I do notice things.
It's a habit of mine.
I, um...
I must get back
to my friends.
- I've been feeling
very queer.
Very queer indeed.
- It is indeed
a business most odd.
- Oh, dear, it gave me
quite a turn, it did,
when I went into the hall,
and there was this strange man
standing there.
And Mr. Harry's voice said,
"Still here, Tressilian?"
Alive.
The same as ever.
- It must have been
a feeling most strange.
- It seems sometimes
as if the past
isn't the past at all.
It seems to be, the bell rings,
and I go to let someone in--
doesn't matter if it's
Mr. Harry or Mr. George
or Superintendent Sugden even.
But I'm saying to myself,
"But I've done all this before."
- That is most interesting,
Tressilian.
- Yes, well...
I'd just like to check
some times with you,
Mr. Tressilian.
When the noise started upstairs,
Mr. George Lee was telephoning.
Can you confirm that?
- Oh, somebody telephoned, sir.
Yes, the bell rings
in my pantry here.
If anybody lifts the receiver
to dial a number,
there's a faint noise
on the bell here.
- Hmm, and about
this fellow Horbury, the valet,
he was definitely
out of the house
by a quarter past 8:00?
- It was a bit before that,
I'd say, sir.
It was just after
the superintendent arrived.
I remember particularly
because he broke a coffee cup.
- Horbury broke a coffee cup?
How was that?
- He was just lifting it up,
admiring it, like,
and I happened to mention
that Superintendent Sugden
had arrived,
and he just dropped it.
- Did he, indeed?
- Sit down, will you?
- I prefer to stand.
- Very well.
It's about these telephone calls
on the night of the crime.
You put through a call
to Westeringham,
I think you said,
Mr. Lee.
- To my agent
in the constituency, yes.
- Your call went through
at 7:56 exactly.
- Well, I couldn't say
the exact time.
- Ah, but we can,
you see, Mr. Lee.
Your call was put through
at 7:56 and ended at 8:09.
Your father was killed,
Mr. Lee, at about 8:15,
so I must ask you for
an account of your movements
during those six minutes.
- Well, the exchange
must have made a mistake.
Well, I may have just
finished telephoning.
I think I debated
making another call.
- You would hardly debate
whether or not
to make a telephone call
for six minutes.
- Are you doubting my word?
- We do like these questions
answered, Mr. Lee,
in a murder case.
- I don't like your tone,
Chief Inspector.
- I'm sorry for that, Mr. Lee.
Mrs. Lee, I think you said
that you were telephoning
when the alarm broke out
and that, at that time,
you were alone in the study.
- Telephoning?
You didn't telephone
from here.
- Didn't I?
Um...I don't know.
I was so upset.
- Well, you stated that--
- George,
don't let them bully me.
You know
if people shout at me,
I can't remember
anything at all.
I'm so upset.
- I won't have my wife
treated like this!
It's disgraceful.
She's a very sensitive woman.
I warn you:
I shall have a question
asked in the House
about the bullying methods
of the police.
- She'll be back.
- In about five minutes,
I should say.
- When she's worked out
a story, eh, Poirot?
- You know, Chief Inspector,
this case--
it certainly gives one to think,
n'est-ce pas?
- It gives one to think,
all right, Poirot.
- Puh!
Stop it!
- Oh!
Look at it, poor thing.
It's what I picked up
in Grandfather's room.
He must have had a balloon too,
only his was a pink one.
- You seen a ghost
or something, Poirot?
- Chief Inspector, I might
just have done precisely that.
- Good-bye, sir.
- Good-bye, and merry Christmas.
Ah, Madame Lee.
- Monsieur Poirot.
- Hmm?
- Funnily enough,
I want a word with you.
I can trust you, I know,
Mr. Poirot.
You look so kind.
You see, there's--
this doesn't have to go
any further, does it?
I mean, you don't have to tell
that awful policeman?
I wanted to telephone somebody.
A friend of mine.
A man.
And I didn't want
George to know about it.
I know it was wrong.
- I do not judge, madame.
- No.
Anyway, I went to telephone
after dinner,
when I thought George would be
safely in the dining room.
- After seven years?
- But I've got these blokes
chasing me for cash!
- And when I got there,
I heard him telephoning,
so I waited.
- And where did you wait,
madame?
- There's a little place
for coats and hats and things
just by the door.
And I slipped back there
where I could see George
come out of the study.
Only he didn't come out.
And then I heard all the noise,
and I heard Mr. Lee screaming.
Anyway, it would be
very, very awkward for me
to talk about this
in front of George.
You do see that,
don't you?
- Here, Poirot!
- At the back of the house!
- Listen to this.
- Good afternoon, sergeant.
- Sir.
- Tell Mr. Poirot
what you just told me.
- Well, sir,
the superintendent asked me
to make a few inquiries,
like, about any reason
that Horbury might have
for being a bit careful
about the police.
- Did you find any reason,
sergeant?
- That he did,
extorting money under threat
in Bedfordshire,
modified blackmail.
The case couldn't be proved,
so he got off.
- Yeah, but he
could not have possibly
have committed the murder.
His ladyfriend says
he was at the cinema,
and everyone agrees that
he left the house before 8:00.
- Yes, I know.
Blessed infuriating.
Tell him the other thing,
Coombes.
- Well, sir, we also made
an inquiry or two
about Mrs. George Lee.
- Ah.
- Magdalene Jones, as she was,
when she was living
with a Commander Jones
down in Hambledon,
passed her off
as his daughter,
only she wasn't.
- And before that,
she was Madeline Potts
of Willesden.
She left with most
of the commander's savings
and debts all over Hampshire.
- Huh.
Thank you very much, sergeant.
I do not think that that one
is as simple as she seems,
Chief Inspector.
On the night of the murder,
she said that she went
to telephone a man, hmm?
But she overheard
her husband on the telephone
and concealed herself
until he finished.
- Well, it sounds like
about her dap.
What are these blooming things,
Poirot?
- Ah, now, these are
the miniature gardens
of Madame Alfred Lee.
- What's the point of having
a miniature garden?
I mean, you can't do
anything with it, can you?
You can't take a deck chair out
and sit in it.
- They are art, Chief Inspector.
See here?
This one is a vineyard italien.
And this one is
the garden Japanese.
- Well, it's just stones,
isn't it?
I mean, I know the Japanese
are peculiar, but...
What are you looking at?
What is it?
It's a stone.
Very nice.
- Nicer than you think,
Chief Inspector.
- Little frog's been doing
his Christmas shopping.
- I want to see
what he has brought for me.
- Steady on!
- Oh, it's not for me, I think.
- What the devil is it?
- It is an imitation moustache.
- I knew that thing of his
couldn't be real.
- What is it?
- We'd like a word, Mrs. Lee,
if that's convenient.
- Oh, yes, all right.
I'll come out.
I'm sorry.
Alfred's resting.
He had very little sleep
last night.
Would you come through here?
This is his mother's old room.
It hasn't been touched
since she died.
- Tell me, madame,
your husband,
he was very attached
to his mother?
- He adored her.
- We were wondering
if you can explain these.
- What are they?
- Uncut diamonds, Mrs. Lee.
We found them
in your Japanese garden.
- My dear Chief Inspector,
if I'd stolen the diamonds,
I would have just dug a hole
in a flowerbed somewhere
and buried them there.
Have you still
really no idea
who could have done
this awful murder?
- We got more idea
who didn't do it.
- Oh, please, God,
let it be a stranger,
not a member of the family.
- It might be both.
- What do you mean?
- It might be
a member of the family
and at the same time
a stranger.
It is merely a little idea
that has occurred
to the mind of Hercule Poirot.
- The official reading
of the will
generally takes place
after the funeral
of the deceased.
However, as that will not now be
until after the inquest,
I have been asked to give you
the bare bones
of Mr. Simeon Lee's
testament now.
- Asked by whom?
- Interested parties, Mr. Lee.
The main provisions of the will,
which was made ten years ago,
are quite simple.
Half Mr. Simeon Lee's property
goes to his son, Mr. Alfred Lee.
The remainder is divided equally
between his other children.
- Alfred's struck lucky again,
as per usual!
Half the old man's fortune!
- You ought to think
yourself lucky
my father left you
anything at all.
- Well, I don't think
I need to go any further.
- What about Pilar?
- Miss Estravados
is not mentioned in the will.
- Doesn't she get
her mother's share?
- Jennifer Estravados,
if she had lived,
would, of course, have received
her equal share
with the rest of you.
As she is dead, the portion
that would have been hers
goes back into the estate
to be shared out between you.
- Then...I have nothing?
- Oh, my dear, the family
will see to that, of course.
- I think she ought to get
Jennifer's whack.
- Well, I really must be going.
Good-bye, Mrs. Lee.
Anything I can do,
please consult me at any time.
- I agree with Harry.
I think Pilar is entitled
to a definite share.
I mean, this will was made years
before Jennifer's death.
- The law is the law,
I'm afraid.
We must abide by it.
Yes, we're all
very sorry for Pilar,
but as George says,
the law is the law.
- My dear, this must be
very unpleasant for you.
Would you please leave us
while we discuss the question?
- Yes.
Yes, very well.
- Well, gentlemen,
you've heard what you came for.
This is family business now.
You really are a skinflint,
George, aren't you, huh?
- At least I'm not a sponger.
- You have battened on Dad
these last 30 years!
- As an elected member
of his Majesty's Parliament--
- Can we please discuss this
sanely and quietly?
- Yes.
Jennifer only died
last year.
I am sure that when Simeon sent
for Mr. Charlton,
he intended to make provision
for Pilar in a new will.
I think we should carry out what
we can assume were his wishes.
- I agree.
- Certainly not!
The whole thing's preposterous.
- Considering George is
the only person in this family
who has done anything
in the world,
I think it's shameful
his father left him so little.
- Well, that's clear enough.
Of the family, Alfred and I are
in favor of the motion.
George is against.
The ayes have it.
- There isn't any question
of ayes or noes.
My share of my father's estate
is mine absolutely.
I shall not part
with one penny of it.
- So who profits
by the fact that Simeon Lee
didn't have time
to alter his will?
- All of them,
except the Spanish girl.
- So we can cross her
off the list then?
- Yes.
Well, maybe.
- No!
I will not!
- It's your right, Pilar,
your blood right!
- You speak like that!
That is why
I cannot do it!
- But it's not a matter
of charity; it's justice!
- You have all
spoiled everything.
I am going away.
Now.
At once.
You will not be troubled
by me no more.
- Now, the matter
of your passport, Miss--
- Go to hell!
- What's going on?
- It's a family matter.
I'm sorry.
Alfred and I had agreed
to settle a third
of our share
of the estate on her.
She refused to take it.
- She is still alive.
- Good morning, Tressilian.
- Good morning, sir.
- Merry Christmas.
- Oh, thank you, sir.
- Hercule, have you heard
how the girl is this morning?
- Merry Christmas to you,
Monsieur Harry.
Yes, Mademoiselle Estravados,
she sleeps peacefully.
She has, I think,
the clavicle that is broken.
- Mm, yes, yes, I heard all that
from the doc last night.
But I mean, who would want
to do such a thing?
- Ah.
Excuse me.
- What have you got to tell me
then, Poirot?
- It is most interesting,
Chief Inspector.
I went into the room
of Mademoiselle Pilar.
I opened the drawer,
and I took out her passport,
and, Chief Inspector...
- What's the meaning
of all this?
- Merry Christmas, Maggie.
- Good morning.
Please to come in now.
Please to make yourselves
as comfortable as possible.
Mademoiselle...Estravados
has something
that she wishes to say to you.
- You think I am your niece,
Pilar Estravados.
That is not so.
- I don't understand, Pilar.
- I would not have told you,
not ever,
but for the money.
To come here and pretend
and cheat and act,
that was fun.
But when Lydia said
that the money was mine
and that it was only justice,
it was not fun any longer.
I am sorry.
Pilar was killed
when I was traveling with her
in her car in Spain.
And I had not much money
and nowhere to go,
and I thought,
"Why should I not go to England
and become rich?"
And when it began, it was fun,
wondering if I could--
- This is preposterous!
This is criminal!
Getting money
by false pretenses!
- Well, she didn't get much
from you, old boy, did she?
So...I'm not
your uncle anymore, eh?
- I'm afraid it's rather
more serious than that.
If she could lie about that,
she could lie about anything.
I'll tell you
what I think, Miss...
what's your name?
- López.
Conchita López.
- Very well, Miss López,
I'll tell you
what I think happened.
When Mr. Lee found
that the diamonds were missing,
he sent word for you
to come and see him
immediately after dinner.
You did so,
and he accused you of the theft.
You denied it.
- No!
This is not true.
I left the drawing room
after dinner.
I came up here to my room.
I wanted a clean handkerchief.
But then I thought
I would go and see the old man.
I thought he would be pleased.
But when I turned out
onto the stairs,
I saw that someone else
was there at his door.
I slipped back into the corridor
in case the person
turned around.
I did not want them to think
that I was...
I don't know the word.
- Ingratiating yourself?
- Yes?
- No.
Go on, Pilar--
Conchita.
- I heard those horrible noises,
crashes, screams.
And when the people
came running,
I came out at the end
and joined them.
- Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
This is all very airy-fairy.
You say you saw someone standing
outside Simeon Lee's door.
Who did you see?
- I do not know who it was.
It was too dimly lit to see,
but...
it was a woman.
- Rubbish!
She's just saying anything
to get off the hook.
I always said an outsider
killed my father.
- In my opinion,
Simeon Lee, your father,
he was killed
by his own flesh and blood.
- One of us?
I deny that.
- Oh, yes.
There is a case against
every person in this room.
- Nonsense.
Balderdash!
- Et bien.
I will begin with the case
against you,
Monsieur George Lee.
- Now, wait a minute!
- You had no love
for your father.
You kept on good terms with him
for the sake of money.
On the day that he died,
he threatened to cut down
your allowance.
But you knew that when he died,
you would probably inherit
a sum most substantial.
And there is your motive.
- I never heard such--
- After dinner,
you went to telephone.
This telephone call
lasted 13 minutes.
You could then have easily
visited the room of your father
and killed him.
Afterwards, you left the room,
turned the key from the outside
in the hope
that the whole affair
would look like
that of a burglar.
But you omitted,
in your panic,
to make sure that the window,
it was left open
to support
this burglar theory.
And that was stupid,
but you are,
you will pardon me
for saying so,
rather a stupid man.
But, you know,
many other stupid men
have become criminals.
- How dare you speak
to my husband like that!
- Ah, yes.
Then there is,
of course, Madame Lee.
She also had a motive.
She is, I think, in debt.
And the tone of the remarks
made by Simeon Lee
would have caused her
some uneasiness.
- Roger, you know this...
- She also has no alibi.
She said she went
to the telephone,
but did she, in fact,
make a call?
And in any case, we only have
her word for what she did.
- I suppose it's our turn now.
Now, how do you suggest
that dear Alfred
killed his beloved father
when we were both together
in the dining room at the time?
- Et bien, that is very simple,
monsieur.
You and your brother are on the
terms very bad, n'est-ce pas?
Oh, that is well-known.
But let us suppose
that these bad terms
were all part
of a clever plot.
Let us suppose
that you and he
had got together
some time before.
And then comes
the night of the murder,
which, together,
you have planned so cleverly.
One of you remains
in the dining room,
talking out loud
and quarreling,
to make it appear
as though there were
two people in the room,
while the other brother,
he goes upstairs
and commits the crime.
- I mean,
I don't think you understand.
You devil!
- But what if it was not a woman
that Mademoiselle López saw
outside the room of Simeon Lee?
What if Mademoiselle López
is again lying,
but this time
to support a man
of whom she has grown
rather fond?
- Now, look!
- No, you're wrong.
It was me that Pilar saw.
- You, Lydia?
- I can't believe
I've been such a coward,
to keep silent
just because I was afraid.
- I think you'd better
tell us now, Mrs. Lee.
- I'd been thinking all evening
about the unpleasant scene
we'd had with Simeon
before dinner.
When Pilar--
I'm sorry, Conchita--
left the drawing room,
I decided to go up
and see him.
I was going to be firm
with him.
I was going to tell him
that Alfred and I were leaving.
- Lydia!
- Yes, yes, I was!
I'd had enough humiliation,
Alfred.
I knocked
on Simeon's door.
There was no answer.
I knocked again.
Still no answer.
I tried the door handle.
And the door was locked.
Then those terrible noises
started inside the room.
I stood there, paralyzed.
And then Alfred
and the others came running
and battered down the door,
and we saw inside the room.
And there was no one there.
Just Simeon lying dead.
There was no one else there.
Do you understand me?
And no one had come out.
- And all this time,
you've said nothing.
- No!
Because if I had,
there is only one thing
that you could have thought:
that I had killed
my father-in-law.
- Non, non, non, non, madame.
When you heard those screams
most awful,
when you heard the sounds
of the struggle,
Simeon Lee was already dead.
- Already dead?
What do you mean,
already dead?
- Did I not tell to you,
Chief Inspector,
that I thought
I had seen a ghost?
The first intimation
I had of this
was when I visited
the shop in the village.
And the owner of this shop,
he is a fellow most jovial,
n'est-ce pas?
He delights in
the childish pranks and...
how do you say, la blague?
The practical tricks.
- You're not trying
to tell us
that this was all
a practical joke?
- Non, non, non, madame,
not a joke,
but a trick most deadly.
The killing itself was simple.
Our murderer sets the scene.
The diamonds are taken
from the safe,
which had already been opened
by Simeon Lee.
As much furniture as possible
is piled in the center
of the room like a tower.
Then a strong,
thin length of cord
is tied around this tower.
The two ends of the cord
are then passed
through the narrow gap
in the window
and allowed to drop
to the ground below.
The door, it is locked
from the outside.
The stage, it is set.
Our murderer walks
casually away,
waits a little while,
then returns to the wall
below the window
and takes up the slack
on both ends of the cord.
And now, at last,
the perpetrator has prepared
the final element
in his ruthless plot.
- But the scream?
The terrible scream?
- Ah, yes, of course,
the dying screams
of Simeon Lee,
the cry of a man
in mortal agony,
a soul in hell.
Monsieur Harry Lee
came closest to it
when he described that sound
as that of the killing of a pig.
And it was here that
my friend in the village shop
unwittingly played his part.
- Morning.
- In that establishment
most eccentric,
the owner sells
long pink bladders,
which have painted
on them faces.
These are called Dying Pigs.
They are blown up
like a balloon,
and the little wooden peg
is placed in one end
to prevent the escape of air.
Our murderer had placed
in the room
one of these balloons
and had attached the cord
to the little wooden peg.
His plan accomplished,
our murderer then pulls
the remains of the Dying Pig
out through the window,
leaving behind only
the little wooden peg
and a telltale fragment
of the balloon.
But you know,
the most valuable clue
in this case
was uttered quite unknowingly
by the butler, Tressilian.
He said that he felt strange.
He said that he felt
that things were happening
that had happened before.
And it was one
very simple occurrence
that gave to him
this feeling most strange.
It was when he met
Monsieur Harry Lee,
when Monsieur Harry Lee
first entered the house.
Bless my soul.
If it ain't Tressilian!
- Mr. Harry!
- And when you look at the face
of Monsieur Harry Lee,
you can see why.
- What the devil do you mean?
- In the face,
Monsieur Harry Lee
closely resembled his father.
But the similarity
is quite striking
when one observes the portrait
of Monsieur Simeon Lee
in the sitting room.
En effet, all of the men
in the Lee family
have a likeness
that is most strong.
- All right, Poirot.
All very clever,
no doubt.
But who is this murderer
we keep hearing about?
- Ah, the good
Chief Inspector Japp
always the one to make Poirot
stick to his task.
Et bien, Chief Inspector,
in order to answer
your question,
it is necessary that we make
a short journey.
Suivez-moi.
- I hope you know
what you're up to, Poirot.
- Bonjour, Madame de Zuigder.
We would like to see your son,
if you please.
- Oh, God.
- This was indeed the death
of an evil man.
Remember the reputation
of Simeon Lee?
How he broke
the heart of his wife
because of his numerous affairs
with other women?
Remember, also, his boasts
of the illegitimate sons
that he had sired.
A man born,
you will pardon me, madame,
on the wrong side
of the blanket
can nonetheless inherit
the features of his father:
his pride,
his patience,
and his vengeful spirit.
- It was my revenge,
my pride, my vengeful spirit.
And I did not inherit it
from Simeon Lee.
I got nothing
from Simeon Lee,
nothing.
- And you waited.
You and your son
followed Simeon Lee,
and you waited.
- 40 years.
- You instilled into your son
your own rage.
- I saved Simeon Lee's life.
And he used me,
and he stole from me,
and he deserted me
and my child.
- Your son changed his name,
settled down to a career,
and he also waited.
Nothing in this life was
so important to either of you
but the total destruction
of Simeon Lee.
- Simeon Lee earned his death
as he earned nothing else
in his whole life.
He was a...
- Come in, superintendent.
- What's going on?
- And now you can see it,
can you not, Chief Inspector?
You can see why Tressilian
felt so disoriented.
- What's all this about?
- The extent
of his disorientation
did not fully dawn upon me
until I purchased
from the village shop
the false moustache
and attached it
to the portrait of Simeon Lee
in the sitting room.
The likeness...
it was extraordinary.
- You're saying
I look like Simeon Lee?
- You are like Simeon Lee
in almost every respect.
- None of that!
- You resemble very closely
your father!
And also,
like your father,
you are prepared to wait years,
if necessary, for your revenge.
And your revenge
is indeed terrible.
And so you embark
on your ingenious subterfuge...
Weaving the intricate web
of deception
that will make the murder
which you have committed
appear to have been perpetrated
by an innocent member
of the household,
while you yourself
were absent.
You make sure
that Tressilian notes well
your exit from the house.
- We'll be having more snow
tonight, I shouldn't wonder.
Good night.
- Good night, sir.
- You stop halfway
down the drive...
wait long enough to distance
yourself from the crime
in the minds of the family...
And then return to the house.
Once beneath the window,
you activate
the mechanism most crude
that creates the hideous sound
of a murder
that you had
already committed.
And then,
to further your alibi,
you find an excuse to actually
come back into the house.
- I've forgotten my book.
I want this room cleared.
- In this way,
you are fortuitously present
to investigate your own crime.
- These are mere ravings.
Unsubstantiated ravings.
- Non, non, non, non,
superintendent.
Also like your father,
you are prepared to stop
at nothing to achieve your aim.
As the investigating officer,
you are perfectly placed
to put the diamonds
where you know
they will be found...
And to do the same
with the black leather case.
In this way, you sought
to incriminate the innocent...
And worse.
Mademoiselle López
had given to you already
one very nasty moment.
- I think that
when he was a young man,
he must have been
very handsome.
Like you.
- You knew,
which we did not know,
that she meant that literally.
- I think I'd better go
and find Sergeant Coombes.
- She saw the likeness.
And then...
she made the discovery
of the balloon.
- It is what I picked up
in Grandfather's room.
He must have had a balloon too.
- Suddenly, you were afraid.
You thought that she might put
the two and two together.
And from that moment,
the fate of Mademoiselle López,
it was sealed.
- It was indeed fortunate
for her
that at your first clumsy blows,
she screamed,
and you were forced to leave
the task unfinished.
- Madre de Dios!
- Harold Sugden,
I am arresting you
on a charge
of the willful murder
of your father, Simeon Lee.
- May his soul rot in hell.
I'm sorry, Mother.
- We did well, Harold.
- Come on.
Let's get it over with.
- Who were you going
to telephone then?
- My dressmaker.
- At 8:00 on the night
before Christmas Eve?
- Why did old Simeon ask you
down here in the first place?
- Ah, because
Superintendent Sugden
wanted an expert witness
to the proceedings
to prove that he could not
have been involved.
So he asked Simeon Lee
to invite me.
- But Sugden said he didn't.
- That is because
he did not want us to know
that he'd been in contact
with Simeon Lee before.
- Mr. Poirot,
Chief Inspector Japp,
must you go so soon?
- It is with regret, madame,
but we have to catch the train.
Monsieur Lee.
- Mr. Poirot, I wanted
to thank you so very much.
- Non, non, non,
pas de tout, madame.
It is a sad thing, non?
To meet like this
and at Christmas.
Au revoir, mon amie.
- Monsieur Poirot!
I wanted to say good-bye
and to thank you.
- Mademoiselle López.
And might I suggest that,
in the future,
you maintain your own identity?
It will cause, I am sure,
much less of the complications.
- Harry and I are going
to Paris.
- She knows she'll be safe
with an old man like me.
- I'm sure she will,
Monsieur Harry.
- Good-bye.
- Oh, yes?
- Merry Christmas,
Chief Inspector.
- Oh, Poirot,
you shouldn't have.
- I have not yet thanked you
for my present.
- I hope you like them.
- Oh, I do
very, very much indeed.
Such wonderful colors
and such workmanship.
- Emily's been knitting away
at those blessed gloves
for months.
- Ah, well, you must tell to her
how much I thank her
and how much her skill
it is appreciated.
- I will.
I will.
You're not going
to wear them now, then?
- Non, non, non, non, non,
non, mon ami.
These must be kept
for best, huh?
I shall wear them only
when I go to church.