- Hi, everybody.
So how's everybody doing?
Okay?
- Uh, let's see. Amber?
- 'Here.'
'And John?'
- Hi, John.
- Uh, Lauren.
- Here.
'Hey, Lauren.'
Uh, Daniella.
Last name is Usher. Hi.
Uh, Stephanie Pratt.
Is she here?
Hyo Jun?
'Ah, yeah.'
And you're Stephanie, yeah?
- Yeah. Sorry.
- 'Okay.'
'The first day, it's difficult
for some people'
'so just try to relax
and enjoy the process.'
♪ We gonna start a revolution ♪
♪ Every day a new solution ♪
♪ Gonna smash and break
right through the mold ♪
♪ Every time gonna
find a new way ♪
♪ And we gotta start a new day ♪
♪ Gonna leave you decked up
in the hall ♪
♪ Yeah ♪♪
One second.
- Hi.
- Hi, I'm Whitney.
I'm here to see Kelly Cutrone.
Um, hold on one second.
Um, just give me one second.
She's finishing up
on a phone call.
Okay, cool. I'll just...
Make sure that everybody
transfers to you
at that other extension.
(Stefanie)
'Oh, okay.'
(Kelly)
'It's ten after 5:00.'
'Is Whitney here yet?'
- Yeah.
- 'What is she doing?'
- 'Standing in the hallway?'
- Yes.
(Kelly)
'You can bring her in,
'cause I wanna'
'go to this music meeting.'
- Okay.
- 'Okay?'
Oh, okay, great.
Can you bring her in?
Because I have to go.
- Hi, there.
- Hi, how are you?
- Crazy here today.
- I know, I was noticing.
Well, you know, we're doing
all these fashion shows here
and then we're
setting up Paris
we're setting up Los Angeles.
So one of these things is
we're gonna be working
'a lot with a brand
from Australia.'
- Sass & Bide.
- That's awesome.
So I'll just give you
a quick brief, they're here
'and their show's in the main
tent at Fashion Week tomorrow.'
So here's the problem.
Normally, when people start
we like to give them
all the rules.
- Which come in this book here.
- 'Okay.'
We don't have time for that
today, so what we're gonna do is
we're gonna take you up,
and you're gonna run the fitting
- 'with Sass & Bide.'
- Okay.
Alright. And then just so you
know you have to wear black.
I don't know if you noticed,
but everybody wears black.
- Okay. Will do.
- 'Okay?'
You're willing to do
whatever it takes?
I'm definitely willing to do
whatever it takes.
That's always
been my work ethic.
Okay, I hope so,
'cause people say that
when they're in that chair
all the time.
- I'm sure.
- Okay.
Let's go meet the designers.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Okay?
- So, this is our fifth floor.
- Wow, look at that color.
Which is kind of going kooky.
- Uh-huh.
- Isn't it great?
- A lot of great clothes.
- 'It's awesome.'
This is Whitney, our new
employee in our LA office.
- Hi.
- Sarah Jane, Heidi.
- Hello. How are you?
- 'Sass & Bide.'
Which you will be working
with them tonight.
Because I have to go.
We have another event.
'But you're gonna stay
with the girls.'
I'm just here for
whatever you guys need, so...
- Okay? I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay. Right.
Good luck.
It's gonna be a long night.
We usually stop working at
about...3:00 in the morning.
- 2:30, 3:00.
- 'Okay.'
[rock music]
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ That you say no sir ♪
♪ And now it's a big blur ♪
Use the reflect tool here.
And then drag it, and I have
the exact opposite of the side.
'So, for those of you that'
'weren't too good in matching'
'your, um, sides
in flat sketching'
'this is a perfect way,
it'll give you an exact sketch.'
And I have, like, three times
the amount of closet space.
- Yeah.
- Which is unbelievable.
Oh, my gosh. You know Stephanie,
Spencer's sister?
She just wrote me
"You won't believe who's
in my computer class."
- Okay?
- Lauren.
Oh, my gosh.
She must be freaking out.
Why are they taking class
together... What class?
I don't even know
what to write her.
Oh, my God, that's so crazy.
Go say hi.
I'm telling her to go say hi.
(trainer)
'And you just hit print...'
'...and it usually prints
right away.'
'And if we ever have
any trouble with it'
'we just call the technicians'
'and so you don't have to worry
about, uh'
'something happening.'
Oh, my God.
Lauren just texted me.
Stephanie Pratt is
in her computer class.
- Poor Lauren.
- She's freaking out right now.
(trainer)
'I didn't say this, but bring
your jump drives in next week.'
'Okay, I'll see you next week.
Take care.'
[rock music]
So we're gonna have to
figure out a way to print
all of the looks,
put that on the models
and it'll just
help the dressers.
- Yeah, to put it on exact.
- So that we can have a visual.
Yeah.
It's the most wearable one
I've got.
Just saying, um,
I just think it might be
'a bit racy with the bottom,
everything's so tight.'
You're worried that it doesn't
look ready to wear?
Well, sometimes you'll
get comments
that something
is not as wearable
to, like, who's gonna wear
tights, like, you know.
Oh.
- You'd wear this, wouldn't you?
- Yeah, I mean, I would.
But I think that you also
wanna show the pants
because I-I don't know
you've done
on all the other models, but...
None... No other ones show it.
So maybe it would be nice
just to have one
to actually show what they look
like and how they actually fit.
Could you just do one more
walk for us, do you think?
I mean, people that are gonna
be wearing these pants anyways
are gonna wear it like this.
Like, someone who can't
wear it like this
aren't gonna buy them anyways.
- 'That's a good point.'
- So...
I mean, I think, I like,
I like it.
'Well, let's keep you in that.'
'Now, we'll get a photo.
Thanks.'
- Thanks, Whitney.
- You're welcome.
♪ 'Cause the world is
what you make it ♪
♪ And now you're good ♪
♪ Just like I knew you would ♪
♪ You get up when you fall
and you'll do it all for good ♪
- Hey.
- Hey. How was work?
I'm tired.
Okay, what's up with your
text message, first of all?
Okay, when I sat down,
she wasn't there. She was late.
And they called roll,
and the woman called her name
and I was like, "What?"
Was she sitting by you?
Yeah, she was like two seats
away from me.
Like, there was one person
in between us.
'Like, seriously, come on.'
I'm sorry,
but it's kind of funny.
It's just really, really random
that she would be in your class.
Put her in, like, a lecture
hall, it'd be so chill.
I would never even see the girl.
I'm in a class of, like, 16.
Well, just 'cause she's in
your class doesn't mean, like...
No, I know, I'm totally,
I just, I hope
she just leaves me alone
is my only thing.
What a great way to start
your day off.
'I know.'
[chuckles]
[instrumental music]
♪ To my enemies ♪
♪ Those were the best days
of our lives ♪
♪ When our hate
made us feel so alive ♪
♪ So wrong it's right ♪♪
Hey, Lauren.
I just wanted to say I'm really
sorry about yelling at you.
I didn't mean to be a bitch
to you, you have to understand
the last time I saw you,
you literally screamed
in my face for no reason,
you know?
I know, I just see them upset
and I see they're not
friends with you...
But why they... What did I do?
I mean, I-I don't
even wanna get into it.
You don't have to.
He's a jerk sometimes.
If anyone knows, I know.
- Okay. Well, I appreciate that.
- I'm really sorry.
I'm just gonna, like, stay out
of whatever's going on.
I know that you're trying to be
a really good friend to Heidi
and I appreciate that,
because I'm really protective
of my friends, too.
Well...
So I don't have
anything against you.
I don't dislike you,
I just...
- Okay.
- Don't wanna get yelled at.
[Stephanie laughing]
It'll never happen again.
I'm really sorry.
Well, I appreciate
your apologizing.
- Alright.
- Thanks.
♪ Made it on my own ♪
♪ I'm okay ♪
♪ Out on my own ♪
♪ Don't you see?
I'm alright ♪
♪ You know that I made a place
to call my home ♪
♪ 'Cause I've tired so hard ♪
♪ Yeah for so long ♪
♪ Don't you see
it's okay ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll be okay
I made it on my own ♪♪
Okay, models, if you're dressed,
come line up over here.
'If you're dressed,
let's line up.'
- Hi! Okay.
- 'Hi. You're gonna come...'
Yeah, well, basically,
what's happening
the clothes are all
set up over here.
They're already in order.
They're being seamed
as we speak.
Really quickly, how did every
thing go with their fittings?
She said it went great
last night.
(Heidi)
'Yeah, yeah, no, it was good.'
Oh, yeah, it was wonderful.
'What happened with
the legging thing?'
We went with your choice
on the leggings?
Oh, yeah, we were nervous
about the butt showing.
Did she know what
she was doing?
Yeah, yeah, she did.
She got it.
(Whitney)
'As soon as, um, Kelly goes
to director's booth?'
All your models will be lined
up, and you'll be pushing them.
And so Kelly will say,
"Go for the next."
You're gonna say the girl
the-the model's name and say,
"Daria gone."
Is Whitney on clear-com?
Yes, I'm here.
Alright, let's go dark.
We're ready to start.
'We're starting.'
'Go for the first girl, Emily.'
Let's go.
Go. First model gone.
[upbeat music]
♪ Wake up ♪
♪ You're losing ground ♪
Go for the next girl.
♪ Wake up ♪
♪ We'll turn things around ♪
♪ Right and right again ♪
Cue, Whitney, go for Veronica.
Go. Veronica gone.
(Kelly)
'There you go, babe.
Go for Tatia.'
(Whitney)
'Tatia, go, Tatia, Tatia.'
- It's out of order.
- Totally out of order.
What the...is going on?
Stop it.
Stop getting out of order.
Now, who do you have with you?
Um, we have Hollis.
- Go for Hollis.
- 'Hollis. Hollis.'
- Hollis, Hollis, go.
Go, go, go.
Hollis gone.
Alright, they're fine.
♪ Wake up ♪
Okay, go for Alexandra.
Alexandra, go.
- Alexandra gone.
- Thank you, Whitney.
(Kelly)
'They're alright.
Do we have one more?'
'Go for the next model.'
Last model gone.
[all cheering]
[crowd applauding]
[indistinct chatter]
Alright, alright, bitches!
Done, done, done!
So I just want to tell you that
I'm really happy with what
you did with the pants.
You have a voice, and I think
your voice is meaningful.
- Okay, good.
- And the designers liked it.
- So I think that's great.
- Good.
So when you get out to LA
I mean, your role
is gonna really increase.
I think your training
at Teen Vogue is like
you've really built
upon that now
So we're gonna expect a lot
from you, just so you know.
I hope so, yes.
No, after this, this was
so exciting for me.
I mean, I had so much fun.
Alright, good.
You did a great job.
- I'm proud of you.
- Thank you.
[instrumental music]
♪ I'm free ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I have arrived ♪
♪ I'm so alive ♪
♪ I'm free ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm on my own ♪
Okay, green.
Yeah, be careful
not to get it...
- 'All over me?'
- 'All over you.'
This is supposed to be
like fun painting
not disastrous painting.
I don't think
we can handle this.
- Oh...
- Here.
- Thanks.
- Uh-huh.
And, uh, yeah, just don't paint
the wood thing.
I really like this color,
P.S.
Yeah, me too.
This is the color I had
when I lived with...her.
- Lauren?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
- 'So how's school going?'
'I'm doing so bad
in this class.'
It's so hard.
I hate computers.
'You have class with Lauren.'
I don't even know
what to say to that.
Have you seen her?
Yeah, I sit, like
a person away from her.
Maybe you guys
should like pass notes
and become friends.
I mean, the class is,
like, eight weeks
and I did apologize.
I just like, I told her I'm just
gonna stay out of...your fight.
[upbeat music]
♪ I see you like
jumping down ♪
♪ You're still still
hanging around ♪
♪ My feet back on the ground ♪
♪ So I can run away ♪
(Lauren)
'I don't care
that she apologized.'
There's still something
I just don't trust about her.
I don't trust her, either.
Imagine if you had
a brother or sister who was like
did really mean things
to people, you know?
Would you want people to think
you were bad, too?
Yeah, but you don't know
everything about her, either.
- I know.
- Just keep your guard up.
- Be careful.
- I-I don't need a guard.
I'm not like, putting
any trust in her.
I'm just being nice to her.
She's a nice girl.
Just don't put yourself
in any vulnerable positions.
- I won't.
- You're smart about that.
You know what to say and what
not to say, you know?
I don't know. I mean, what's the
girl gonna do to me, you know?
[instrumental music]
[rock music]
I don't know,
I guess that, um
like, Lauren and Stephanie
are talking now.
- Kind of awkward.
- I mean...
Like, she can hang out
with whoever she wants...
...but it just doesn't really
make sense that she's...
She can be friends
with Stephanie
who is Spencer's sister
but she can't be friends with me
because of Spencer.
It's a little weird, yeah.
I mean, and it's weird
for Stephanie, it's like...
You've been here
for the past year.
- You know what's happening.
- Yeah.
What does Spencer have to say
about this whole thing?
Does he know?
I mean, I'm sure
he's not gonna like it.
♪ Who's the fool? ♪
♪ You think that you're cool ♪
♪ I'm not giving up
on my way to the top ♪
♪ I feed the fire with fuel
you are my soul ♪
♪ Now who's the played
and the player? ♪
♪ I am the great betrayer ♪
[humming]
So, what's going on
with you and Heidi?
I think relationship vacation
turned into, um...
End?
I should be asking you.
I don't know,
I don't talk to her.
Well, I just, like,
I'm sick of choosing sides.
Don't bitch about being on sides
'cause you're not on my side.
You're so immature.
Do you think I can just
eat in peace without...
You're so lame.
You're so homeless and so lame.
'You're a real candidate
for Heidi.'
Pretty Heidi...loser Spencer.
I don't even hear anything
you say. It's just...
You really don't wanna know
what she thinks about you?
Nope.
So you're just gonna
live here and never
talk about your feelings
with me?
I can't tell you anything
'cause I can't trust you.
I tell you one thing,
you tell, uh, Heidi
I tell you another thing,
you could tell LC.
Next thing, next thing, you'll
be telling Brody things
and then...everybody I don't
want to know things
will know things, so...
I just can't trust you,
that's the problem
so I can't say anything.
I don't know why
you can't trust me.
'Why do you think?'
You go to school with LC
and you go to the clubs
with Heidi.
Well, I'm always here
to help you.
'Cause number one,
I am your sister.
[rock music]
So, yeah,
I totally quit smoking.
- Congratulations.
- I know.
Now I can, like, breathe
when I walk up stairs.
Oh, yeah, that too.
And you'll live longer.
- Right?
- The whole no-cancer thing.
- That's good.
- I know.
If I can only stop going
to tanning beds.
(Lauren)
What'd you get on the test?
I got a "B."
- 'I know. I'm totally excited.'
- Good! That's good.
I'm totally gonna put it
on the fridge.
Really?
I feel like if I did that,
Audrina'd make fun of me
I'd probably do it anyways.
I live by myself, so I
can do that kind of stuff.
I thought you lived
with your brother.
Oh, yeah.
Trying to forget about that.
[chuckles]
- He's so annoying.
- Sorry.
Like, I try to talk to him,
and he's just like...
He's saying he doesn't
trust me now, but, like...
Why?
He was like,
"Well, you go to school
"with Lauren
and you're best friends
with Heidi."
He was like, "You're just, like,
in between all of it."
I was like, "I know, I don't
wanna be in between all of it."
He can't hate you for being
a nice person. That's silly.
It's like treading on thin ice
coming home every day.
- That kind of sucks.
- I know.
It's not really fair.
Spencer and Heidi
it's like their word
or nothing.
Yeah, sounds fun.
[Stephanie laughing]
Wait, are you even allowed
to talk to me?
I'm not kidding. I don't wanna
get you in trouble.
Then I'll be like, "We're doing
homework," or something.
- For our computer class?
- I'm serious. I know.
I'm serious.
But when they do find out
it's not gonna be pretty.
[pop music]