It's cool.
- Hi.
- 'Hi.'
It looks amazing.
- It's gorgeous.
- It should be fun.
So, you're gonna work backstage.
and you're gonna do
front of the house.
And front of the house
is really horrible.
'We're gonna have to try
and figure out the front row.'
It's gonna be a little bit
chaotic because it's not seated.
We're gonna give front-row cards
to the young kids
'and we want them to really have
a great time tonight.'
How are we announcing
the beginning of the show?
- You're gonna tell us.
- Okay.
'You're running
the show tonight.'
It's-it's really important,
obviously, for "Teen Vogue."
It's our one big party.
And I am counting
on you, Whitney
to make this a success.
I want the show to start
on time, promptly at 9 o'clock.
- 'No screw-ups.'
- Right.
- Alright.
- Okay.
[instrumental music]
- Ah!
- Hey! Ooh! Are those for me?
I just saw these
at the reception. Yeah.
- There's a note too.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, they smell so good.
- Aren't they beautiful?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh!
"You're the greatest thing
that ever happened to me.
"Happy 21st birthday.
To a hundred more birthdays
together. Love, Spencer."
Oh, that's really sweet.
We have to do something.
- Do you wanna, like, do lunch?
- Yeah, perfect, let's do lunch.
We'll catch up and have lunch.
Yeah, so maybe, like,
one o'clock or something?
- Perfect. I'll be here.
- Okay.
Okay, thanks, Kimberly.
[instrumental music]
(Audrina)
'Tonight, I'm going
to Viper Room with Justin.'
We're going to see
this band called The Ruse.
- The Ruse?
- Have you ever heard of them?
- No.
- 'It's like alternative rock.'
We've heard so much about them,
so we're like, "that's cool."
I mean, if they're good,
maybe I'll bring their CD back
and give it to Samantha.
- Are they not signed?
- 'I don't think so.'
I want to meet the band
and, like, check it out and see.
So, is this a date?
Are you guys dating?
Have you decided yet?
I guess you could call it
a date.
You just can't put
a label on it.
It's a Viper Room date.
[laughs]
That's its own genre of date.
[instrumental music]
I cannot believe
it's my 21st birthday!
I know. That's so exciting.
I have to order
a glass of wine or something
'cause it's my first time.
I've been so excited
to turn 21 for so long.
- I know.
- I'm, like, the last one.
Twenty-one was like
a huge, like, pivotal year
'cause you're just getting
into, like, your 20s
and you're starting to, like
figure out more, like,
who you are and...
From 20 to 21, I think it's been
my biggest growing year so far.
Like, so much has happened.
- My life has changed so much.
- Yeah.
I feel like I should be turning
25 right now, you know.
So, what are you doing
for your birthday?
I think tonight Spencer's
just taking me out
for a surprise dinner.
'So wait, it's your 21st'
'and you just want it
to be with Spencer?'
You know, it's about,
like, me and Spencer.
It's not like, "Oh, my
this is gonna be
the biggest moment of my life."
It's, like, I don't know,
I hope, you know
it's one of them,
but it's not like...
Being with him is the best part
you know,
and that's the bottom line.
Yeah.
[instrumental music]
We have to stuff 1500 gift bags
by seven o'clock?
We need some more help,
for sure.
On the walkie, you have to
let me know who's coming in.
I will. I would like
to see the list.
People bring their little
entourage with them
and they want to sit with them.
I'm nervous that
I'm gonna get my ass whipped.
I'm just dying to know exactly
how many VIPs
they're planning on seating
over there.
There's like 12 seating areas.
Doesn't the first row
of chairs count too
as front row or no?
No.
We'll lie and say it's front row
to the people sitting there.
I'm nervous. I hope I can get
everyone seated on time.
[rock music]
(Jennifer)
'You have not seated
a fashion show before.'
- Is that right?
- I haven't.
Okay, the thing that's tricky
about this event is that
it's not assigned seating
like a normal fashion show.
'So it's kind of gonna go
off the cuff.'
Okay.
You have to seat about
390 people in 15 minutes,
alright?
'You're gonna do this.
This is gonna be fun.'
It has to happen in 15 minutes.
The show's got to go off
at nine o'clock.
You're most likely gonna be
the person
that we come to and say
"Whitney, what's going on
backstage?"
So, you've got the back
of the house
and you've got the front
of the house.
- Right.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Good.
Alright. Thank you.
'Remember, I'm on seven,
and you're on one.'
So if you need me, go to seven
and tell me to go to 11.
Okay. This is so confusing.
- Really?
- I can handle it.
- Seven, one.
- 'Yeah, yeah, yeah.'
- Great.
- Okay.
Wait, where are you going?
'Um, I think people
just got here.'
- 'So I'm going.'
- Okay.
'Are they letting people
in yet?'
- 'Definitely.'
- 'Okay.'
Alright, do we have to check
anything else out?
No, I think...
I mean, unless you want to.
You are welcome to...
Have you seen outside yet?
- '...go outside.'
- No.
- Let's see outside.
- Alright.
'Alright, we're gonna start
pulling girls to dress them.'
'Do one of you girls
want to come?'
We need five at a time.
Ready? Let's go.
[indistinct shouting]
Are these actual
all movie stars?
(male #1)
'Yeah.'
I mean, if you're okay
with it...
No, let's move them faster.
(Whitney)
'It is now 8:40,
and we're running a little late'
just because the red carpet's
taking a long time
and, like, our main people
aren't here yet.
- 'Okay.'
- 'Okay?'
(Lauren)
'Okay, so, I just heard the
red carpet is taking forever.'
Yeah, we're gonna wait.
Okay, so, now they're saying
we're shooting for a 9:30 start.
- 'Really?'
- Yeah.
So it's pushed back a half-hour.
- That late?
- Yeah.
[instrumental music]
Isn't this fun, like, working
at a record label
to get to go and do this...
Scout bands?
♪ So take this sorrow ♪
♪ Let it swallow you ♪
♪ Shake this sorrow ♪
♪ Let it swallow you ♪♪
[cheering]
Thank you.
[indistinct chattering]
- I'm Audrina.
- Nice to meet you. How are you?
Hey, buddy. Nice to meet you.
- 'What's your name?'
- Mark.
Mark, nice to meet you.
Are you guys signed?
'No, we're actually working
on different stuff now.'
You are. I work for Epic.
- If you guys have a CD...
- Do you really?
- You guys are really good.
- 'Cool. That would be great.'
Are you guys gonna
go out tonight?
We were thinking about it.
We're not sure what to do.
We're doing a little after party
for a few people
like, literally right
down the street at One.
One. I've been there once.
They have really good food.
Let's go have a drink,
and then we'll walk down.
[rock music]
Can I get a sparkling water
and a flat water?
You should check her ID.
She's 21.
Whoo!
Surprise. Happy birthday.
Oh, you shouldn't have
done this!
I am so mad at you!
Oh, I cannot believe
you did this.
I'm about to die!
They said it's the
brand-new one out.
Only out for like a week.
Oh...my...gosh!
[laughs]
[squeals]
This is what I like.
The bling in the chain.
[gasps]
I love you! I love you!
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you! Thank you!
This is my favorite present
I've ever gotten in my life.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
It's too far!
- Celebrate! Whoo!
- I am.
- What's that face?
- No face.
Would you like
a little more wine?
- You seem a little serious.
- No.
Would you like some more?
- It's great.
- What?
- I'm having a great time.
- Me too.
[rock music]
Let's open the doors.
Let's go.
Does everyone know where
they're supposed to be?
- Are you good?
- I'm good. Yeah.
It looks fantastic.
Look at the mob.
- Now there all filing in.
- Where are all our seaters?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Where are the seaters?
Lauren for Whitney.
'Where are the other seaters?'
We need the people that are
seating the show other than us.
- Right.
- Come on.
'Sit right behind
these people.'
Okay, I'm just gonna have you
come over here.
Sorry.
Whitney!
Do you have a front-row seat?
Come on over here.
Okay. This is your table.
Okay? Cool.
Okay.
You guys are right over here.
(Lauren)
'Whitney, there's not supposed
to be anybody sitting there'
'and there are two people
sitting there.'
You got to keep that area clear.
You guys can sit in either
of these back ones
if you want. Yeah.
Whitney, can you go to 11?
That one in the hat
always crashes every party.
Right here?
He's not allowed
in ever usually.
Right here, sitting right
in front of us?
- Really?
- Find out from Carlos.
He's a crasher from way back.
- Wanna to take your seat?
- I think we need to start.
- Right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
I think that...
Hold on, hold on...
For who? Oh, hi, yes. Um...
[indistinct chatter]
I don't think you can hear me
on this.
- No, it's out right now.
- Oh, well, there you go.
How close are we to being all...
Um, like, honestly,
a couple minutes.
Sit down. I want them
to roll up the carpet.
Alright, let's get off
the aisle.
- We're good?
- Are you good?
Okay.
Nice job, Whit.
Way to crack the whip, baby.
My gosh. I just started
putting people...
That's what you got to do.
You just got to roll with it.
Yes. Let's go, ladies.
Lauren!
Lauren's right there.
Should I tell her we're good?
- Go, we're ready to go.
- We're good.
'Yeah. We're good.'
No, wait, wait,
we're bringing Hilary Duff in.
- We're not ready.
- Tell Lauren to wait.
Okay. Erik, they're all good.
Suzy? Suzy?
- They're good.
- Yeah?
They said we're ready
to start.
Alright, you guys.
Hi, are you there?
Corina, Will.
Lauren?
- We're going.
- Lauren?
- Have we started going?
- Yeah.
Alright, here we go.
[instrumental music]
We're just waiting
on Hilary Duff.
Erik, wait, they're seating
Hilary Duff right now.
Okay, you guys,
stay in your positions.
We're just waiting
for one person?
She's coming in right now.
I see her.
'Okay, she's here.'
- They're good to go.
- Alright, you guys.
Make this show...hot.
[instrumental music]
I'm gonna go do one more.
Right behind each other,
you guys.
We got, like, two more to go,
and then we're doing the finale.
[music continues]
[audience applauding]
- Aah! Good job, guys!
- Thank you so much.
Whoo!
Good job, everyone.
[rock music]
- What do you guys want?
- Let me get some drinks.
I'm gonna get one of those,
I think.
- Which one?
- The Naughty Schoolgirl.
- 'J.D., red wine...'
- Naughty Schoolgirl.
- 'Naughty Schoolgirl?'
- Yes.
'I love that. That's good.'
[laughter]
I now know why
it's the Naughty Schoolgirl.
- 'There's actually a sucker.'
- There's a lollipop in there.
- Dip it.
- Cheers, everyone.
- 'Thank you, guys.'
- 'Cheers.'
'To guys with
The Naughty Schoolgirl.'
It's really good.
This is my new favorite drink.
I'm actually from Orange County.
Oh, okay.
Southern California,
born and raised. Yeah.
Always.
Hey!
- What happened over there?
- I don't know.
Yeah.
- Oh, that was so good.
- What?
- Justin.
- Is that his name?
Okay. Good.
That's all that matters.
- We'll hang out.
- Yeah, yeah.
It was nice meeting you.
It was nice meeting you
as well.
(Audrina)
'Hey.'
- You getting ready?
- Yeah.
Nice meeting you.
See you soon. Thank you.
(male #2)
'Pleasure. Pleasure.'
Bye! Come on, Justin.
[instrumental music]
- Did people like it?
- Did you have fun?
What are you hearing out here?
I didn't have fun,
but I thought it was amazing.
- It looked amazing.
- 'I thought it was amazing...'
- 'Did it look good?'
- Yeah, it looked great.
It looked great!
- You enjoyed it?
- Yes! I thought it was great.
Are you hearing good things
from all the guests?
- Yes. The show was amazing.
- Really?
Every year should be
a different designer.
Different designer
and a different location.
- Yeah.
- Good work!
- You did it.
- Yay! Done!
- Those guys were nice.
- Yeah.
The one was a little too touchy.
The tall one.
- He liked you.
- He kept grabbing me.
He wanted you.
Yeah, but I'm going home
with you.
That's why we work
so well together.
Yep, this is a very important
wish. Do not rush it.
I'm just so glad this year,
like, last year it was so crazy
and it was a big party
and all this drama
and Audrina trying to come over.
And, like, this year,
I'm with the love of my life
and it's so, like,
much easier and low-key.
This is what I want, you know.
Long day.
You feel good about it?
It was perfect. It couldn't
have gone any better.
Yeah, we've come
a really long way
since first
young Hollywood party.
Nice job, boss lady.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[theme music]