- 'How was Vegas?'
- Brody kissed me.
What?
You guys would be
quite the couple!
I fought with Audrina
a little bit in Vegas.
You did?
What were you fighting about,
Justin Bobby?
- Justin was rude.
- That's not okay.
I know, honestly, this was me
and Audrina's first fight too
in, like, the two years
we've known each other.
It is because we live
together now, and that happens.
You live together.
You're best friends.
You do so much together.
It's bound to happen, you know?
[cellphone beeps]
- Random.
- What's random?
- Jen Bunney just texted me.
- Jen Bunney?
- Weird!
- What does she want from you?
She says, she needs
to talk to me.
She just said,
"I need to talk to you"?
"I really need to talk to you."
Wow.
She probably wants
to smooth things over.
Are you ready to talk to her?
You guys have a lot
of catching up to do.
[instrumental music]
Hey!
Painting toes?
Yes.
What's wrong?
'Jen Bunney just texted me.'
She wants to get lunch.
'It kind of got me
thinking about stuff.'
I just feel like I'm-I'm
have kind of been just
like, overstepping
and being too judgmental
'like the way I've been
treating you with Justin.'
It's hard because
I'm a very stubborn person.
And I don't like to admit
when I'm wrong.
Mm-hm.
'But, I just feel really,
really bad.'
And, like, at this point, even
though it's been so far along
like, I'm still really
broken from last year.
And it's like,
I'm still dealing with all that.
And I think that
I'm just so scared
for anyone to go through
the same thing.
Look what I did last year,
where's it's like
I'm trying to think that
I'm being a good friend
and, like, I made my
roommate move out.
Like, she couldn't even
live with me.
And it's like,
I'm trying not to do it again.
And I don't want it
to happen again.
So I'm just,
you have to help me, though
because if I'm, like
being annoying
you just need to tell me
to shut up.
Just be like,
"Lauren, shut up."
You're,
like one of my best friends.
I just don't wanna push
anyone else away.
And I need to just
basically shut up
and be happy for you
when you're happy.
- So, I'm really sorry.
- 'It's okay.'
- Apology accepted.
- Thank you.
[instrumental music]
I just talked to Audrina
and apologized already.
- You did?
- Yeah.
For, like, for Vegas?
Just for...
...the whole stupid
Justin thing.
Justin's a loser. Whatever.
(Lauren)
I think I'm just kind of over
fighting with people right now.
(Lo)
This store is adorable!
- 'Really cute!'
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, it's connected...
- Where'd you just get that?
Well,
how do I wear this, exactly?
Like this.
Ooh! I like! I want!
What are you doing today?
Um...
...I think I'm gonna go
to lunch in a little...
...to meet Jen just 'cause
she's been texting me
'and I'm gonna go talk to her.
And then I don't know.'
Buns?
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
I just don't understand
what she wants.
I don't know. To fix things.
I really don't know.
It's just, she hurt you
pretty bad once
and I don't want to see that
happen to you again.
It won't because...trust like
I had in her before
is something you have to earn.
- You know what I mean?
- I know. It's not that.
It's just, like, I know that you
had a really hard year.
And in my eyes,
it's not...totally worth it
for you to, like,
throw yourself back
in to what made you upset
in the first place.
I'm not throwing myself
back in.
I'm just going to lunch
with her.
I know. I know. I know.
I just...
- Thanks, Mama Lo.
- I don't wanna see you upset.
- Okay?
- I'm not upset. I'm fine.
I know, but I love you
and I don't want to...
I don't want that mean girl
to be mean to you again.
[instrumental music]
- Hey, you wanted to see me?
- 'Yeah.'
Have a seat.
So, tell me what happened
this weekend.
Um, I had Elodie covering
for me on Friday
and she was like,
"Oh, yeah, it's fine.
'Don't worry.
I'll totally be there."'
Elodie never showed up.
And so, I raced over there,
and I got there right away.
Okay,
so, bottom line is Elodie
doesn't work here
anymore and you do.
So, if you're gonna have
somebody cover for you
what I need you to do
is you have to communicate
with me, or Jennifer, or
somebody on the team so we know.
You have responsibility.
Y-you fought for this position.
You have to live up
to everything you promised me
and everything you said that you
would do for this job, okay?
You have to be 100%
on your game.
You can't let
your home life interfere.
your personal life interfere.
This isn't a nine-to-five job.
This is a career.
'You have to learn
from your mistakes to grow'
and know that it can happen
once, it can't happen twice.
- Right. I'll make sure.
- Okay.
Perfect.
That's what I want to hear.
- Great. Thanks, Brent .
- Alright.
[instrumental music]
- 'Hi.'
- Hi!
- How are ya?
- 'Good, how are you?'
Good.
Thank you.
What's new?
I've just been working,
going to school.
- I started school again...
- 'Where, FIDM?'
- Mm-hm.
- That's pretty.
- Where'd you get it?
- What?
Your diamond.
Oh, it's a friendship bracelet.
A friend gave it to me.
So...
...how'd you hold up
with that whole...
...rumor situation?
Not very well.
I really wanted to, like
call you
and make sure you were okay.
It wouldn't have been
the right time.
But, I knew that, I knew
it wasn't the right time.
- Well, thank you.
- Thank you.
So, what's up?
'What'd you wanna tell me?'
Uh.
'So, I had lunch with Heidi
recently.'
Uh.
'You know the whole
sex-tape thing?'
I think
she thinks that Brody...
...is responsible
for the rumors.
I don't know.
'I really don't know.'
I don't wanna get involved.
Why would Brody start
rumors about me?
I've been friends
with him all along.
I don't know.
I know you don't.
I don't believe it though.
I think it only
makes sense for her
to blame it on
every other person.
[instrumental music]
- Hi.
- Laundry day?
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
Good.
I just had lunch with Jen.
How did it go? It's good?
Yeah, I mean...it's fine now
like, I'm obviously not
mad at her anymore.
What did she say? She just...
I guess, um,
she just recently had lunch
with Heidi,
and Heidi was like
"Brody was the one who
said everything about Lauren.
Like, I didn't have anything
to do with it."
Heidi acted like she had
nothing to do with it?
But, worst of all,
she's, like, blaming Brody
who's been my friend all along.
I'm like, Brody's my friend.
Brody has never been the one
to start trouble ever, right?
No.
It makes me mad
that Heidi's going around
saying that about Brody.
Why would she say
that Brody was doing it?
Looks, like, 'cause
she's blaming every person.
I'm gonna see him
at dinner, though
'so I'm gonna ask him about it.'
'That's good.'
- We'll see.
- 'Yeah.'
It's good,
whatever happens, happens.
Truth and time tells all.
That's what Justin said.
[instrumental music]
I still can't believe Brent
said anything to you.
That's totally not your fault.
If you get somebody to cover...
I didn't know that Elodie
quit that day.
She was just trying
to snipe you out.
I can't believe she was so
mad about the job, like...
I mean, the bottom line is
if Elodie
was supposed to have the job
Brent would have
given it to her.
- 'It's not my fault.'
- Wha wha wha.
- 'Yeah.'
Lesson learned.
Can't depend on anybody.
[instrumental music]
(Audrina)
'This is way better than Vegas.'
(Justin)
'See, I can do these things.'
It's just when it gets staticky.
You don't like
a lot of people around.
I can't deal with it.
You might want to go
on that side.
You're stripes.
[chuckles]
Was that it? Oh!
Me and Lauren
had a talk the other day.
- You did?
- Yeah.
She felt bad 'cause she felt
like she was interfering
and being too controlling.
- She was.
- 'Yeah.'
I just told her, like,
I'm gonna do what I want.
It's my life,
and I appreciate her concern
but, like, stay out of it.
You know, like,
give me my space.
But she apologized.
She said sorry.
And, like, she's happy for me
and she's gonna try
to not butt in anymore.
I think things should be
happy and blissful
and just mellow.
- Like it is now?
- Yeah. That stuff...
I mean, you know
how I feel about that.
It's just, like, why?
'Who has the patience
and, uh, life's too short.'
I don't know,
I think maybe something between
her and Brody
will spark up again.
- I won!
- You're amazing.
I love it. Good game.
- Two to one.
- Alright.
[instrumental music]
Whoa! Whoa! Alright!
- How are you?
- Good to see you.
Good to see you too.
You look stunning...as always.
I had so much fun in Vegas.
I wanna back.
That was fun, wasn't it?
That night that
you crawled into my bed
'my rotating bed,
and then said that...'
You asked me to stay and come.
Oh, you, no.
Cheers.
- Cheers to...
- True friends.
I agree. True friends.
[laughs]
So, what else? Talk to me.
Um, I did want to talk
to you about something.
Do I need a sake shot
for this one or what?
So, I went out to lunch
with Jen Bunney.
I guess she still
speaks to Heidi
and that, um,
she basically said that
Heidi blamed every reason
I was upset with her on you.
She said that you spread
every one of those rumors.
She's lost her mind.
They both have.
If that's what
she's going around saying
she's completely lost her mind,
'cause it's not true.
But you won't look at me
and tell me
that you know they did it.
I try to stay away from that.
I just need you to be
honest with me.
And if I knew something
like that about you
I would tell you,
because you're my friend.
Now,
I'm stuck in a bad position.
I understand that,
but it comes down
to wrong and right.
Obviously in this situation,
he's wrong.
And that's just plain and
simple. It's easy to see, but...
Then, why won't you look at me,
and tell me they did it?
[sighs]
- 'Lauren.'
- What?
I know 100% fact
that they did it.
Thank you.
[instrumental music]
(Whitney)
'What up, yo?'
Did you go out last night?
No, I went to sleep
at like ten o'clock.
- 'What'd you do?'
- Well, I went to dinner.
- Who'd you go with?
- I just went with Brody.
Oh, how was that?
Uh, it's the first time
he finally admitted to me
that he knows that Spencer
said all those things about me.
No way!
'Cause, he would never
admit it to me before.
I mean, first he was probably
trying to have his back
and now that they're
not friends anymore...
'Here's the thing
about Brody is that...'
...he even, like, when
he's not your friend anymore
or if he breaks, you know,
he breaks up with someone
'he never really
says bad things about them'
'which is something
I really like about him.'
That's a great quality.
And so, I was like,
you know, "Brody
"I'm not accusing you
of anything
'"but you know
they're out there saying that'
'you're the one saying
these things about me."'
So, then that sparked.
So, then he was finally
like, "You know what
like, I didn't wanna
have to tell you but, yes
I know for a fact he did it."
Oh, man.
Do you think that Heidi
was involved at all?
I mean, I feel like
there's a possibility that
he may have done it,
and then she knew
and then just kinda
went along with it.
So, Jen needs to know
to stop spreading rumors.
Well, I'm gonna text her
and let her know.
And set the record straight.
[instrumental music]
- Hi!
- Oh, look how cute you look!
- How are you?
- Hi, Bunney.
- What's up?
- Nothing much.
Getting some lunch.
What's been going on?
Any, any anything?
I don't know. Same old stuff.
Life.
- What's wrong? Are you okay?
- Yeah!
You seem, like,
stressed or something.
Actually,
I went to lunch with Lauren
and we talked about
everything.
And we're fine.
I mean, I love that you're
friends with Lauren again.
I think you should be friends.
I thought the whole thing
was silly.
I thought, you know...
So you do wanna be friends
with her again?
If we can put this whole
thing behind us, you know?
I, I mean, that would be amazing
if you guys could just...
...end the drama, but it's just
such a sticky situation.
You know what I mean?
It's not a little thing.
It's not like someone
kissed someone.
It's like someone put something
in front of millions of people.
But, I feel like
I have to, like tell you
Brody told Lauren that
you know,
you and Spencer did it.
I mean, obviously he's gonna
say that, it's not...
You really,
really, really didn't?
- You really didn't?
- You think I did?
- No. I'm think...
- You think I did.
Okay, I would think that
you would know better.
I meant Spencer.
- What?
- Are you sure Spencer?
- Yes, I'm sure Spencer.
- That's all I was asking.
It's, just like, a question.
'Cause I was told that.
I think it's funny that you're
coming and blaming me for it.
- I'm not blaming you.
- But, you're coming at me...
No, no, I just asked.
I'm just gonna,
like, bring it up.
When you say no, that's that.
It's done.
[instrumental music]
Should we get the check?
Can we get the check?
[music continues]
Hey.
Aah! How was, uh...
Did you have work today, yeah?
No, I had lunch
with Jen Bunney.
Wow, those are always fun,
aren't they?
'I mean, Jen was telling me
that Lauren was saying'
"Brody says it was all Spencer
who spread the sex-tape rumors"
and blah, blah, blah.
He's such a little bitch.
I told Jen, I was like,
"How could you ask me that?
"Like, really,
I've been your friend through
"all this and Lauren hasn't been
talking to you.
And all of a sudden, like,
out of nowhere, you know."
It's great that they made up.
I'm really happy for that.
- 'But, like...'
- He's so shady.
I just think it's so sad
that they're blaming you,
right?
'Spencer.'
[instrumental music]
[theme music]