- 'Hi.'
- Hi.
Um, I'm here to see Audrina.
She's gonna be
in the Epic Digital
which is straight ahead.
- And it's on the first floor.
- Okay.
- Right through those doors.
- Great, thank you.
(Heidi)
'This is so cute.
It's like a real cafeteria.'
This is our little
hangout spots.
Do you eat here every day?
Not every day,
there's like, um...
there's a couple places
down the street.
But they usually
have good food here.
'So nice to, like, relax and be
able to have, like, a lunch...'
I know I've been going nonstop.
Like, you don't know how nice
it is to be able
to talk to you again.
You know, it's like we were
friends for a long time
and then all this stuff happened
that had nothing to do with us.
It had to really do
with Lauren and Spencer.
I know and then somehow
all of us,
it became part of all of us.
And I was acting like,
"What have I...
This is none
of my business, like..."
- 'Right.'
- You know.
I'm really, like,
gaining myself again
and I'm gaining, like,
hanging out with girlfriends
and, like...
Okay, you know what?
'I really need
a girls' night out.'
'No boys, no Spencer.
Will you come?'
♪ Gotta let it go
Gotta take control ♪
♪ You know I'm about
to lose my mind ♪
♪ Gonna break away
I've had all I can take ♪
♪ You just run out of time
Gotta let it go ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Excuse me.
- Hi.
- It's, like, models in here.
- I know, I know.
- Oodles of models.
- Is Kelly here?
- She is.
I don't know, she's some...
She goes, like, in and out.
- Oh, is she upstairs right now?
- I think so.
Okay, so here's
what's happening.
Put your stuff down
over here and then
I'll tell you what's going on.
Bianca Gomez,
how old are you now?
- 'Nineteen.'
- Oh, my god.
You look so cute
in that lingerie.
- Great.
- Hi, Kelly, this is Lauren.
- The helper.
- Hi, I met you before.
- I've met you before.
- How are you?
I did meet you before.
I'm well.
- Is she our helper?
- Yeah.
She is?
Alright, Lauren.
- You wanna cast with me?
- Sure.
You and Whitney, get ready.
Here we go.
- We'll start from there.
- Okay, go ahead.
Straight down.
Uh, Lauren, um...
Whitney, can you
Polaroid these two girls?
Alright.
One, two, three.
- What's your name?
- 'Courtney.'
- Courtney.
- Courtney with a C?
- Thank you.
- Alright.
(Kelly)
'We've got another one, Lauren.
Don't get too comfortable.'
'Oh, my god.
Okay, I think he's perfect.'
'Lauren Conrad, where are you?'
- Getting paper clips, gettin...
- Okay.
I need to book these models.
You guys have that done?
Oh, my god.
You guys are so slow.
Let's sit over here
really quick
I'm gonna bump Jess,
I mean, I know
you don't wanna move,
but you're gonna have to move.
(Kelly)
'Can you guys grab
a couple chairs?'
Just to have, like, a little
crash course...really quickly.
(Jessica)
Can we spare Lauren
to maybe call?
Julia wants to make sure
that the models...
No, you could do that.
We're gonna book
these models over here.
Lauren, pull up a chair
over here.
(Lauren)
'Okay.'
["Stranded"
by Caitlyn Taylor Love]
♪ Nowhere to go all alone ♪
♪ Lost in the middle
of nowhere ♪
♪ Stranded stranded
nowhere is feeling like home ♪♪
(Spencer)
Oh, perfect time.
I'm just cutting your half.
- Thank you, but I'm leaving.
- Where are you going?
Oh, my god, did you use all
the turkey for
your one sandwich?
No, this half is for you.
This half is for me.
- Where are you going anyways?
- I'm going out in Hollywood.
I'm sure you are.
Going to a nightclub?
- Uh, yeah.
- What club would that be?
- It's a S Bar.
- Is Heidi going?
- Umm...
- So I'll take that as a yes.
Don't wait up.
Have fun, coach potato.
[door shutting]
[upbeat song]
[song continues]
(Audrina)
It feels so weird
me meeting Heidi here.
(Chiara)
'Was the last time
New Year's Eve with Lauren?'
Yeah, over there.
'Doesn't matter what I do'
'someone's gonna be mad.'
- Hey...
- Hi, hey.
I'm so glad you're here.
[club music]
What's going on?
'Oh, my god,
you have to hear this.'
[laughing]
[song continues]
It's so crazy to see
how much goes into it.
You know, you think that you
just, like, slap on an outfit
and just, like, throw them out
there, it's so not like that.
This is like a dream job.
I'm so stoked for you.
'It'd be so cool
to work here with you.'
I know.
Well, if you impress Kelly
maybe she'll hire you.
Hey, you guys, I wanna...
Hi.
I wanna go over
a couple things.
First of all, for the shows,
it's just best
to wear all black no boobies.
- You know, just straight black.
- Am I doing shows?
I'm gonna need you
to help us because...
Yeah, I'm open all week, I just
didn't know what I was doing.
Tomorrow really is gonna be,
all hell's gonna break loose
so, I really need you to get
a good night's sleep tonight.
It's gonna be a big day,
alright?
[reggae music]
♪ Woo ♪
♪ Shake shake shake ♪♪
♪ I been a long time ♪
♪ Been a long time
searching for you ♪
Ha ha. Oh, my god,
I didn't know that.
I don't think
you should go there.
They're taking shots?
- That's right.
- They're talking shots?
You are insane.
Oh, and you guys were standing
over there like, oh...
Oh, really?
I'm not like,
"Oh, blah, blah, blah."
Hi...they're here.
[indistinct chatter]
[instrumental music]
♪ Can you hear me on your own? ♪
♪ Can you feel? ♪
- Good morning.
- How are you?
- Doing laundry.
- 'It's a laundry day for me.'
- Umm.
Where did you go last night?
Um, I went to S Bar after work.
Heidi and Stephanie were there,
like girls' night out.
'So then we're sitting there
talking, Spencer shows up'
and he's with all these girls
'and, like, Heidi kept
looking over there'
'and Stephanie's like,
"Oh, my god."'
'Like, what,
what are you gonna do?'
Why wouldn't she just
go up and say hi?
Wasn't the guy like her fiance?
'Because, like, he knew that'
she was doing a girls' night
with her girls
and, like, she's like, I bet
he knew where I was coming
and he's just, like,
stalking me and coming here.
But, like, if you're in
a relationship with someone
you can't walk up to them
and be like, "Hey?"
I guess they're on
relationship vacation.
- I don't know.
- Thing is...
And this is just me
being me that, um...
it would not surprise me
if Heidi or Spencer
tried very, very hard
to become friends with you
'because they really
don't like the fact that'
'I get along with Stephanie.'
Umm.
- I know.
- Cool.
It was surprisingly gross that
how many girls were on him.
He probably pays them.
No girl would willingly
touch that scum.
Whoa, where'd that come from?
[cackling]
'Okay, I have to go get ready.
I have Kelly's show today.'
[chuckling]
♪ 'Cause feel I really feel
I feel alright ♪
♪ If something brings you down
I'm leaving it behind ♪
♪ I'm letting it go
let it go let it go yeah ♪
♪ I'm livin' in the moment ♪♪
Alright, here's what
I need you to do.
I want you to push
like a mother hen
just from the back,
both of you.
Call these people out.
- Here's the microphone.
- Okay.
Get all the models
I'll show you how to do it.
Girls, we don't have time
for this, let's go.
- Out, out...out on the runway.
- Let's roll.
That's how you do it,
just like a...
like a sheepherding dog, okay?
Anyone that looks tall
with her hair done.
Okay, models, everybody,
to the runway!
- Models.
- Models out to the runway!
Okay, okay.
'All the girls out
on the runway.'
'Whitney,
get the seating chart.'
- I have it.
- Guys, wanna come out more?
She's gonna demonstrate for you.
(Kelly)
'Whitney, can you just go
backstage really quickly'
and ask does she wanna go
to red backstage lighting
then change to the purple for
the first look and copy that?
- Okay...yeah.
- Does she...?
She wants to know,
when she's finished talking
is she wants it to start red
and then change to purple
when the first girl comes out.
- Alexia wants to know?
- Kelly wants to know.
The light, the lighting red?
Red to purple? Okay.
[chatter]
- I'm...
- 'I can get some jelly, if...'
(Whitney)
Yeah, no, no, I'm sorry,
did you wanna
start red
or did you wanna start...
First look red
and then change to purple?
- Or do you wanna start purple?
- 'Start red.'
- Right, okay.
- Starting red.
Starting red, we're gonna go
with the original red?
Okay, good...the backstage
is gonna go deep red.
Go deep, can I see a red,
so I can lock it in?
Let's bring the other
houselights down.
Okay, perfect!
Okay, girls, you're gonna go
line them up from the back.
- Okay.
- 'Alright?'
- Yes.
- 'Alright, don't * * * up.'
♪ Look to the sky ♪
♪ The dreams you want
aren't far behind ♪
♪ You feel it ♪
[instrumental music]
♪ Look to the sky ♪
So I'm changing the layout
maybe a little bit.
I want to switch this one
out to here
and move this cabana out
completely, which...
- Alright.
- We have a week, so...
It's perfect.
Are you okay?
I haven't seen you all day.
I know, I've been kind of
hiding out a little bit.
I had, like, the worst night
in my life last night.
- At S Bar?
- 'Yeah.'
I thought I was having,
like, girls' night out.
- 'And then Spencer shows up.'
- Yeah?
And he doesn't come over
and say hi.
Like, he doesn't even
acknowledge my existence.
And then he's
surrounded by, like
a group of girls
and taking shots with them.
'I was so sick
and I wanted to kill him.'
- Why would he do that?
- I've never felt so betrayed.
Was he trying to do some
childish display of him
being angry with
the fact you guys are...
Or he's over it, you know.
He's not over it,
if you're over it
then you don't do
something like that.
It's so hard seeing him
with other girls though.
How can you love
and hate someone so much
at the same time?
[instrumental music]
♪ I don't wanna let it
slip away ♪
♪ The way it feels to run ♪
♪ And so it feels
when I just stay ♪
♪ I have been
beautifully wounded ♪
♪ I'm beautifully wounded ♪♪
[phone ringing]
(Spencer)
'Well, look who it is.'
What are you doing?
- 'What are you doing?'
- I am just at Bolthouse.
Do you wanna come by?
[indistinct]
I think we need to talk.
'Uh, yeah, when should I come?'
Uh, whenever you can make it.
- 'I'll be there soon.'
- Alright, bye.
[key tone beeping]
[upbeat music]
(Emily)
'In about 15 minutes,
we're gonna start the shows.'
You're gonna be
backstage with me
and you're gonna help me
push the models.
And then Lauren's gonna help
with the model lineup.
Those models that came in late,
we've got to get them
into first look,
so that we can start the show.
(Whitney)
'Alright, guys,
let's get in order.'
'If models are done changing,
please send them up front.'
'We're gonna start lining up.
Michelle!'
I just did a lap
and no one caught it.
- Michelle! Okay.
- 'Alright.'
- Lauren!
- Two minutes left.
(Lauren)
'Guys, is everyone lined up
and ready for first look?'
What time is it?
Is everybody lined up?
- We're ready.
- 'Are we ready?'
Okay, yoo-hoo!
Let's do this good.
'Roll out.'
♪ Sun comes down
for a holiday ♪♪
(Kelly)
'Tell the girls to smile
when they come out.'
Smile, everybody.
♪ Saturday and your ♪
I'm sorry, what did you say
your name was?
Devin, great.
- Great job, Lauren.
- Great job.
Heather, come right here.
Right here, step up, step up.
'This is Amanda.'
- 'Heather.'
- 'Okay.'
We need Michelle.
Where's Michelle?
Michelle, we need you!
- 'Where's Michelle?'
- 'Right here, right here.'
Come right here.
♪ Till I'm down
on the dance floor ♪
Okay, everybody,
get in order for finale!
One, two, three,
go for the girls.
Everybody, go!
Everybody go!
[crowd applauding]
- Nice job on the music, boys.
- Whoo!
[cheering]
- Thank you so much.
- Come here, I owe you.
♪ There's just something
about you ♪
♪ That makes me feel
the way I do ♪
♪ Something about you ♪
♪ And I can't live without you ♪
♪ Can't live without you ♪♪
- Hey.
- Well, hello.
I want to talk to you
about last night.
Oh, I'm not even gonna
sit here and argue 'cause...
You don't have
to sit here and argue
but if you wanna be single
then be single,
but let me know.
Um, you pretty much
made me single when you...
- No, I didn't.
- Aye?
You call it
relationship vacation.
Anyone else on planet Earth
calls that breaking up.
- No, they don't.
- Yes.
Who takes a vacation
from a relationship?
I mean, we were just
fighting so much.
- We were...we fought twice.
- I wanted space.
- I wanted...
- Well, you got your space.
Yeah, but I didn't want you,
like, hooking up with other...
I didn't hook up,
I didn't hook up with anybody!
I was there with
my friends and you
embarrassed me
in front of everybody...
- I embarrassed you?
- Yes!
- For standing at a bar?
- Okay, you know what?
Next time I stand at a bar
and there happens
to be some guys there
and I'm flirting
with them taking shots
let's see how you feel.
Bottom line is, you're
delusional if you think
I was flirting
with those girls.
How long is
relationship vacation?
Like, am I supposed
to not go to bars
and not talk to people
for how many months?
I just don't think I can
just keep waiting around
all year long, to wait
for when Heidi decides
she wants to get off
relationship vacation.
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ I have nothing left to say ♪
♪ I'm at a loss ♪
♪ You keep listening ♪♪
- Hi.
- Hi!
OMG.
Oh, my god.
First of all,
you go up the ladder
to, like,
bitch in training.
Oh, God, my mom
would be so proud.
Okay, Lauren, you've gone
from, like slow-mo
to, like, fashion glow.
An unbelievable
two-year increase!
And, um, we would love
to offer you a position
to come and work with us.
We're happy to have you come on,
because we wanna start
making some changes
in our LA office.
Hi, you're going
to the party, right?
Can you make sure everybody
out there has wristbands?
- I'm going, we have two, so...
- But, she's talking about...
No, but I'm talking
about this party
before we go to the other party.
- Oh, I didn't even know there...
- Yeah.
There's one in that
green room for Mercedes.
And then can you get
an assistant to get a taxi
for my nanny and my daughter
to get back?
Yeah, okay, we'll
just figure out
the wristbands and then, okay...
So, thank you so much
for showing up
'and helping us out,
and we're happy'
to have you come on,
you know...
...it's an amazing opportunity
to make the best
of yourself.
♪ Believe believe ♪
♪ You say that no one
will understand ♪
♪ I say that you need
to open up ♪
♪ And believe believe ♪
♪ Believe believe ♪
♪ Believe and you will find ♪
♪ Just a little piece of mind ♪
♪ Mind ♪♪
[theme music]