- Hey.
How's it goin'?
Good. How are you?
I'm a little crazy
but in a good way.
That's good.
The reason I'm here is,
I know that you guys
have been expanding everywhere,
in, you know, every part
'of the country,
and I want to be a part'
of this company
as much as I can.
So I would love to get my hands
in there and make myself
as available to you
as much as I can.
Great
'Especially if that means
traveling or relocating.'
'Great, I mean, it's gonna take'
'a big commitment.'
Over the last
three or four months
we've gotten so much crazier
and there's so many
other projects happening.
And what Sam and I want to do
is expand The Hyde brand
so that we can take Hyde
into other markets.
So what that means is we're
working much more integrally
with the team of people here
and we're all working
at a daunting pace and that you
are gonna have
to be more actively involved
in the things that
I'm working on.
Say one of your jobs could be
the casino in Las Vegas.
Sounds brilliant. I mean, I'm...
I'm so excited and I'm up
for the challenge.
♪ Oh-h-o ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ My life is great ♪
♪ I can't complain ♪
♪ It's never the same ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey ♪♪
Ah, it's such a nice day.
I know.
Where's Audrina?
Um, I believe she's
in her room/chateau.
- Cool.
- I'd invite her to lay out.
But I don't wanna wake her
if she's sleeping.
Yeah, let her come out
on her own time.
Hmm.
(Lo)
'Let's do something fun today.'
- 'I'm down, let's go shopping.'
- 'Okay.'
- 'Audrina?'
- Hi.
Hi, how are you?
What are you doin'?
I'm going to work with
Alkaline Trio today.
- This band.
- Oh, really?
Yeah, and they're in the studio
recording their new album.
So Chiara and I get to go
down there and hang out.
(Lauren) 'Are you working
or are you just hangin'?'
We're just going to see, like,
everything's taken care of
and, like, you know,
it's going smoothly.
So I'm gonna go meet her
and then head over
but I was gonna see
if you guys wanna stop by.
(Lauren) 'The studio?'
You could come and check it out
and maybe you'll like this song.
We could be groupies
for the day.
'Text me the address,
and we'll go stop by later.'
Well, if you guys
are gonna stop by
I'm gonna go finish
getting ready.
Well, we can all do
dinner afterwards
'cause we haven't really
celebrated roommate-ness.
- I know.
- Ha ha ha.
- Okay, well...
- Okay.
I'll text you the address.
I'mma finish getting ready.
(Lo) 'Bye.'
That could be fun.
Oh.
All I want to do is shop.
Hmm. What else is new?
[instrumental music]
- Hey.
I just got out
of Brent's office.
So I think he wants me to be
project manager,
you know, like...
- Really?
- Helping.
Like, open up all
the Hydes and stuff.
And, like, working on more,
like, the hotels and...
- Yeah.
- I'll be going to Vegas.
Coming up, there's, like, this
whole trip
he was talking about.
So when is all that happening?
In a couple days.
- So, I'm excited though, like...
- Cool. Yeah.
'Yeah, I'm excited for you.'
Just get out of here and,
you know, clear my head.
- What's Spencer gonna say?
- I don't care.
[instrumental music]
♪ So you got me ♪
♪ Where you want me ♪
♪ Not until you prove it ♪
♪ To me baby that you feel it ♪
♪ That you believe it ♪
♪ Show it to me ♪♪
- 'Will you try this again?'
- 'You're ready?'
[instrumental music]
♪ You paste it on
my face here again ♪
♪ And aga-a-a-in ♪
♪ Whoa-oh whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ And I don't want
to be the one... ♪
- I'm in love with that voice.
- Yeah.
He's got a great voice.
♪ In vain ♪
[instrumental music]
♪ I don't wanna take ♪
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- 'Hey, Lo and I just got here.'
- 'Um, can we just walk in?'
- 'Yeah, come on in.'
♪ I don't wanna
take this place ♪
♪ Do you recognize this shape ♪
♪ It's the back
of your hand... ♪
- This is cool.
- 'It is.'
I'm glad you guys could make it.
♪ You paste it on my face... ♪
What do you guys think?
Sounds good, huh?
Yeah, you don't mind if I,
like, flip a few switches?
[laughing]
♪ And I don't wanna be the one ♪
♪ Who takes this place ♪
So you guys like him?
- Yeah.
- It's good.
[guitar strumming]
I'm hungry.
(Lauren) 'Do you want to go get
something to eat?'
Yeah.
♪ Saved my name... ♪
'Okay.'
I think we're gonna go to Sushi.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah, can you come with us?
(Audrina) 'I need to stay
until they're done.'
Oh, okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Thanks for letting us stop by.
You guys are great, bye.
♪ And I don't wanna be
the one who takes this place ♪
♪ Don't want to be the one... ♪
That's weird that
they left, like
they were here for five seconds.
♪ Don't wanna be the one
who takes this place ♪♪
I wish she would come with us.
We haven't had, like,
a roommate dinner yet, you know.
We'll just bring her
some food home.
[instrumental music]
♪ I'm crying I'm dying
on the inside ♪
♪ I'm falling I'm drowning
♪ I'm lying denying ♪
♪ On the inside ♪
♪ On the inside ♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
(Lo) 'Come on, sushi.'
(Lauren) 'I don't know what
it all is, though.'
I don't know
but this is really fun.
Wait, this one
for sure looks good.
'I think Audrina wanted us
to stay, the entire time.'
I'm just not cool enough
to, like...hang with bands.
I just feel bad.
We should get Audrina a present
for her little backhouse.
We should get her
a Chateau Audrina.
'Like a little sign.'
Yeah.
I hope she doesn't, like,
just stay back there.
I feel like it might
be a little bit different
now that you live in there
because sometimes it's like
pulling teeth trying to get
her to, like, talk about stuff.
Whereas you are, like, one of
the first people I call, so...
It's a different dynamic
because we've been best friends
since we were little.
- Yeah.
- Oh, well.
This is yummy soup.
[instrumental music]
♪ I'm afraid of time
and changing ♪
♪ Afraid of this life
in making sense ♪
♪ 'Cause someone
makes some sense ♪
♪ You know I'd stop
this changing... ♪♪
- Hello.
- 'Come in.'
- Thank you.
- How are you?
- I'm, Oh, my God!
Is this the same apartment?
Yes, I'm just cleaning
a little bit.
It's such a mess.
- Not as messy as my place.
- Yeah?
- How is it?
- 'A nightmare.'
He's gotta move out somewhere.
I guess he's gonna be homeless.
[laughing]
Um, I got, um, a really
big job opportunity
and I'm gonna
be traveling a lot.
- You're lying.
- No.
So I'm gonna be traveling with
like, Brent and with Sam
to, like, Hydes and...
Who's Sam? Is he hot?
He owns SBE.
- Like, the name...
- And you're working with them?
Yeah, as, like,
the project manager.
And they bought a hotel in
Vegas so I'm gonna go there
'you know, just be
in Vegas for a while.'
And it's good,
because I just need to kind of
like, clear my head, you know...
In Vegas? In Sin City?
That's where you're
gonna clear your head?
There's nothing really
holding me back.
I cannot believe you're
saying this right now.
If he's gonna move on,
I've gotta move on.
But do you guys
really want this?
Like, I would never...
I just didn't imagine it
going like this.
I know deep down, he doesn't
wanna date anyone else.
You guys are perfect
for each other.
I don't know.
I cannot believe this.
You're leaving town.
If you leave, I'll never
get rid of Spencer.
You can't tell him.
You can't tell him at all.
This isn't his business.
This is something that
I'm doing for myself.
♪ While you're out
sowin' your seeds ♪
♪ I'm tearin' at the scenes ♪
♪ I got no answer
I can cling to ♪
♪ Am I strong enough
for what is out ahead ♪♪
[toy squeaking]
(Lauren)
'I can't believe we got a puppy.
She's so cute!'
[toy squeaking]
Her reactions
are the best, yeah.
'I love that she has
blue eyes like us.'
[chuckling]
- Chloe.
That's such a cute name.
- Hey.
- You guys done unpacking?
Whoa.
[giggling]
Look at what we did!
- Yay!
- 'Oh, my God!'
[laughing]
So cute!
We adopted her.
- We got her from the shelter.
- Hey.
We saved her!
- She has the prettiest eyes.
- I know.
[laughing]
We're so excited to have a dog.
You're so perfect.
You're perfect.
[toys squeaking]
'Oh!'
[barking]
So you guys went to Petco
and got her everything?
Yeah, like this lovely bed
that Lauren's sitting in.
- Yup.
- Wait.
Where are you gonna keep her?
I think one of us is just
gonna sleep with her.
'In puppy daycare,
she's gonna be like'
"I have two mommies."
'Calm down, pretty girl.
No, no, no.'
[Chloe snarling] Ow, ow, ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Let me see her. Let me try.
- Oh, my god, you, you take her.
- Come here, baby.
'Out, Chloe.'
Wait, you were really cute like
five minutes ago. Calm down.
♪ Don't look away don't... ♪
(Lo) 'Chloe!'
'Chloe. Baby girl.'
♪ It's only life ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Spencer, this is how
bread goes stale.
Sorry.
And why is this out?
You don't even drink coffee.
- I didn't take that out.
- Ugh. Then who did?
Spence, you can't
just take out stuff
and not put it away, look...
Obviously, since
I don't drink coffee
I did not take it
out of the fridge.
Spencer, stop with the phone.
I'm serious. I'm sick of this.
I'm sick of you.
What's your point?
I don't want you
controlling my life anymore.
What? I don't even
tell you anything.
I don't care what you do
with your life.
Oh, really, like,
every day, I come home
from school with Lauren and when
I wanna go to her parties?
I don't need * * *
from you anymore.
This is my life
and you're invading my space.
And I want you to leave today.
I cannot wait to leave
and get out of your life
'cause the fact that
you even talk to L.C.
makes me have,
wanna have nothing to do
with your life,
'cause it just makes me think
how pathetic you really are.
So what's up?
I'll move out. Shoo.
You're calling me
pathetic, Spencer?
- Please, leave.
- You're living on my couch.
Heidi doesn't want anything
to do with you.
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪♪
Go away.
I will be gone
by the end of the day.
Get out of my face.
Alright.
[instrumental music]
♪ How could you just
let it go? ♪
♪ You never let me know ♪
♪ And when I get home ♪
♪ Will you be alone? ♪
I wonder if anyone's here.
Hello?
♪ Will you be alone ♪♪
- You could come in.
- Thanks.
- Ha ha.
- Alright.
I don't think I've ever
cooked in here.
- Now, do you want to cook?
- No.
- You could cook.
- I'm just not a big cook.
I always go out to eat.
Well, I'll be
your first client so...
- My first client?
- Yeah, I want some...
I'll have some
toast with butter.
Um...that's good.
I wonder if we have any bread.
You don't know
where anything is?
No. I never cook in here.
So do you even, ever come
in this house or what?
I mean, I'll come in
the kitchen sometimes...
But you don't even,
like, come to see
your roommates and stuff?
I don't know, Lauren and Lo
they, they're always upstairs
and then I'm always
in the back so...
Right. How do you like it?
Do you, I mean,
are you likin' it or...
I don't know, it just seems like
it's been really awkward lately.
- 'Really?'
- Yeah.
Well, that's not,
that's not good.
It shouldn't be like that.
It just feels, like,
there's weird vibes.
So why even be here, huh?
I chose the guesthouse
in the back
just 'cause I'm more
of a private person
whereas, like, Lauren and Lo
constantly
they share everything.
They share their clothes,
their, like, makeup everything.
And I don't really,
I'm not like that, I'm never...
- Not even with my sister.
- Right.
Yeah, I just feel like we're
just distant. It's weird.
You don't wanna have that.
You don't have to come home...
(Audrina) 'I don't want it
to feel awkward.'
Exactly.
You guys are all roommates.
You guys are all friends,
you know what I mean?
It shouldn't, there shouldn't
be that heat at all, you know?
Then, it's like, in, uh, right,
I do try to make an effort
'and talk to them as a friend.'
She rolls her eyes
or she turns her head
or, like, texts on her phone.
I'm like, I'm not gonna talk
to someone who does that to me.
Put it this way,
you got to think of what...
...how you act to people,
it's like...
(Audrina) 'And I, I treat people
how I wanna be treated.'
Exactly, if you don't feel like
'you're getting
that same respect'
I don't know, maybe see
some other places, you know.
Maybe even just check something
out for you, you know?
Maybe I will look at places.
[instrumental music]
Maybe the best thing for you
to do is take the first step.
Check some places out.
[instrumental music]
♪ So you're hangin'
on to your life now ♪
♪ And you swear to God
you won't die out ♪
♪ And we hope that
you wouldn't lie down ♪
♪ You will ♪
♪ She's out back
and you're against the wall ♪
♪ Just wishing
for somewhere to go ♪
♪ Well she's out back
and you're against the wall ♪♪
[instrumental music]
(Sam) 'So, now you can
travel more, I hear.'
- Yeah.
- 'What was the holdup before?'
Because we haven't really talked
but, I mean, like
you can travel more,
you have more time?
I just had a lot going on,
and I just think...
- 'What does that mean?'
- 'Heidi's being shy.'
- Ha ha ha.
- 'She had a boyfriend.'
(Heidi) 'He's a little bit out
of the picture right now so...'
- You guys broke up?
- 'Yeah. Pretty much broke up.'
(Sam)
'So is he gonna lose his mind'
'when he finds out
that you're in Vegas? '
- I don't think so.
- How old is he?
- 'Twenty-four.'
- Just twenty-four?
He's gonna lose his mind.
[laughing]
♪ If this should be
the easy part ♪
♪ Then why's it always
seem so hard? ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't really change ♪
♪ How you feel for me honey ♪
♪ I just need
some peace tonight ♪
[instrumental music]
Heidi?
[music continues]
Yo, Steph, it's Spencer.
Where is Heidi?
When you get this message,
hit me back, okay.
♪ You're all I have ♪
♪ I'll risk it all ♪
♪ Just to feel alive again ♪
[instrumental music]
♪ Just to feel alive again ♪♪
[theme music]