- Hi, Whitney, how are you?
- Good, how are you?
Great, you know Kimball from New
York.
- 'He just arrived.'
- Welcome.
With very exciting news for you.
- Really?
- Yes.
We're going
to send you to Paris.
- Par... Again to Paris?
- Yes.
You are the lucky chosen one
to go to Paris with Kimball
to go to the Crillon Ball.
(Kim) 'It's-it's kind
of the most surreal'
mix of celebrities' children
and authentic, like,
aristocrats and royalty.
Yeah, you might
come back a princess.
That wouldn't be bad.
You'll have so much fun,
but you'll work really hard.
- As always.
- Alright.
- Okay.
- See you soon.
Oh, and what about Lauren?
Is she coming?
I think Lauren had her chance
to go to Paris.
[instrumental music]
- Hey.
What's going on?
[sighs]
I got in another
huge fight with Spencer.
What were you fighting about?
We've been fighting
about all this stupid
wedding stuff,
and I told his sister
like, "Look, I think
'this is all getting
way out of hand."'
And so then I guess she told him
I was getting cold feet,
and he took it
'like I didn't wanna marry him.'
I just think we need
to work on our relationship
and not this wedding.
Like, let's just get back to us.
Right.
I feel like you guys
keep fighting
and then it's okay.
And then you guys
are fighting again, like
you're not really
getting to the root of, like...
- Why you guys are...
- Right.
...getting so upset
with each other, you know?
I feel like
I'm in a relationship
with a five-year-old.
I just don't know what to do.
Like, I gave up
everything for him, you know?
Yeah.
I just need some breathing
room for a minute.
[instrumental music]
- Morning.
- Hi.
What are you doing here early?
I thought
I was gonna beat you here.
(Whitney)
'Lisa wanted to see me.'
And I actually just found out
I'm going to Paris.
- Again?
- 'Yeah.'
For what?
For this Crillon Ball.
'Lisa and Kimball'
asked if I would go
and help out.
Are they sending anybody else?
- Uh, I don't think so.
- Oh.
Obviously, if I had my choice
I would want you there with me.
No, I know.
(Whitney) 'Are you upset?'
I just shouldn't have passed
the first time.
The first time was all
situational, though, you know?
You can't take
back those things.
I just, like,
I tried to work really hard
to show her, but...it's fine.
You're just disappointed
that you...
I'm just...
I mean, when am I
gonna have a chance
to go again, you know?
I know.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales sharply]
Stupid Jason.
[instrumental music]
(Stephanie) Hey.
What's wrong?
I walked out
on another fight with Heidi.
What?
- Where did you go?
- Just home.
- To mom and dad's?
- Yeah.
What did mom and dad say?
I'm an idiot.
Have you talked to her?
Oh, my God.
I'd kill you.
This is bad.
I don't know what to do.
You've got to send her
an e-mail or something.
I mean, you can just say adios
to the relationship
if you don't try.
[instrumental music]
- Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm just doing magazine cuts.
'Oh.'
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Uh, Whitney found out she's
going to Paris again today.
They're sending her,
there's like a Crillon Ball
and they need help dressing
'so they're sending her again.'
She actually gets to go
to the ball, too.
It seems like this year
Lisa would have invited you
'or, like, let you go 'cause...'
But, like,
why would, why would she
invite me, like, when I said no?
You know what I mean, like,
they offered me an opportunity
that, like, I probably
didn't even deserve at the time.
And I said no to it
and for a careless reason.
So, they have no reason
to offer it to me again.
That sucks you can't go.
'I'm sorry.'
[music continues]
[instrumental music]
- Hello.
- Hey, how are you?
Good, just here to see Heidi.
Hi, Spencer's here.
Okay, thanks.
- Okay, just a minute.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
[footsteps approaching]
Hey.
She left.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- For the day, night?
- I don't know.
She said
she was leaving early, so.
[sighs]
If I were you, I would call her.
Okay, well,
if you speak with her
tell her I came by.
- I will.
- Take it easy.
You, too.
[instrumental music]
- Good morning.
- Hey.
(Whitney) 'What are you doing?'
- Inventory.
- Oh, putting away those bags?
Yeah, they've been sitting
there for so long.
- 'How are you?'
- I'm good. What's up?
Have you started shopping yet?
No, I just wanted
to start making a list
actually, of what
I think I needed.
Coats, lots of coats.
Lots of coats, right.
Gloves, ear muffs.
Like, it's freezing there.
Have you ever been t-there
in this time of year before?
- Where?
- 'Paris.'
'Or have you never
been there before?'
I've never been.
Oh.
Coats, gloves, hats.
If you... You need
a couple of nice dresses.
You'll probably
have to go to events.
I know. I only have, like,
a couple days to do this.
- I'm going on Thursday.
- Are you excited?
Yeah. I don't know
how I couldn't be.
I know it's gonna be
a lot of work
but it just sounds so fun.
'I really need
to practice my French.'
I love guys with French accents.
It sounds like
they're singing everything.
I don't know why accents
are just so attractive.
- 'Cause they're different.
- Yeah.
[telephone rings]
Hello. Teen Vogue.
'Okay, bye.'
Um, Lisa wants to see you.
- Did she say why?
- No.
She just said, "Send Lauren in."
[chuckles] Throw out that gum.
[laughing]
[sighs]
[Lisa speaking French]
Hi, Lauren, how are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Good.
I just got off
the phone with Ophelie.
She's the director
of the fabulous ball
'that Whitney is going to.'
And Kimball is overwhelmed, so
'they need to send
additional help.'
- So, you are going to Paris.
- I'm gonna go to Paris?
(Lisa) 'You'll go
with Kimball and Whitney'
and help Ophelie backstage.
It is a bit of a fashion show
because all the girls
have to be presented
so they'll need your help.
Thank you so much.
Who's gonna take you
to the airport?
- I've always dropped my...
- 'You'll go with Whitney.'
She'll make sure
you get on the plane.
Do you think I wouldn't
get on the plane this time?
Oh, I don't know,
last time you didn't go so...
- Have you learned your lesson?
- Yes.
Because it's my favorite city
in the world.
(Lauren) 'I know.'
I ran away from home
when I was 15 to go to Paris.
- Fifteen?
- It changed my life.
And hopefully
it'll change your life, too.
'And it's just magical.'
It's just an incredible
sophistication
that you've never seen before.
I think it'll be an incredibly
inspiring trip for you.
[instrumental music]
I'm going to Paris with you.
Oh, my God!
I am so excited.
We're gonna have so much fun!
We're gonna get to fly
out there together.
That just made my day.
Uh, made my life. Try.
[instrumental music]
I would pull out your chair,
but it looks like...
- It's stationary.
- It's pretty fixated in there.
Whoo!
I had a good day at work today.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
Remember how I told you
Whitney's going to Paris?
Yeah.
I get to go, too, now.
Wow.
When is this all going down?
Uh, I leave Thursday.
This Thursday?
It's really nice to know that
you're not gonna miss me at all.
I didn't say
I wasn't gonna miss you.
I'm just, I'm so excited
to go, I mean...
I'm a little sad
that you're leaving
but I'm happy for you to go.
Why are you sad your single
friend is leaving?
What?
There's a lot
of single people in LA.
There's a lot of single
people in Paris, too.
Stinky people
with hairy armpits.
[gasps]
Those are just the girls,
I think.
Um, the guys...stinky.
Well, I'll find
a Parisian that showers.
So, what, you really want
to find a boyfriend?
Is that what it is?
Where did that come from?
I don't know.
What are you saying?
I don't know, I just haven't
had the best, like, honestly...
I have not had the best
relationships in the past.
So, therefore I'm scared
to get into a relationship.
Nobody's had the best
relationships in the past.
That's why they end.
If you really want
to be with someone
it should be someone
you really like.
Someone you're really,
someone you're really proud
to be with,
and you should want to call them
your boyfriend or girlfriend.
[instrumental music]
[door opens]
Well, hello, stranger.
I thought you changed
the locks on me.
What are you packing for?
I think I'm just gonna
go home for a little bit.
To Colorado?
Yep.
So...
Where were you?
Giving you space.
Well...
- I'm gonna give you some space.
- I don't need space.
I didn't need space
either, but now I do.
So, you can think
about what you want.
I'll think about what I want.
I know what I want.
[sighs] I just don't know
what else to do.
When are you coming back?
You can stay here. You can
have the place to yourself.
I need to go home.
So, I assume the wedding
isn't going to happen
anytime soon?
It's not working.
I need some space.
Okey-dokey.
(Audrina) 'I hope we get
a day off to actually'
'like, go sightsee
or, like, shop.'
'So, do you know your French?'
Obviously.
Have you been practicing?
-Bonjour.
-C'est la vie.
Bon...
Bonsoir.
Oui.
Je m'appelle.
- I don't know.
- You'll do fine.
Time to pile in the shoes.
- Want me to help you?
- Sure.
- Just your boots...
- Stack them in here.
You have a lot of black.
Black goes with everything.
Don't forget your passport.
- Oh, my God!
- I know.
Oh, thank you for reminding me.
I stuck it right there.
Oh, my God!
I would have gone to the airport
without my passport.
Dude, I hope I packed enough.
I feel like I didn't.
- I'm really scared.
- I'm sure whatever you don't...
[gasps]
Whitney's an over-packer.
- She'd have been upset.
- Yeah.
- 'You got it all?'
- Yeah, I'm good.
Okay.
- Well, bye!
- Okay.
I love you, and I will call you
when I get to...
- Be safe.
- I will.
- Alright, there.
- Are you sure you got it?
I got it.
- There.
- Okay, bye.
Bye.
[instrumental music]
I'm about to stop this,
you can't be going
to the airport
looking this cute.
- Stop.
- I'm serious.
Are you sure
you want me to put this in?
Put it in the trunk, Brody.
Come on!
[grunts] What?
[chuckles]
Oh, I think the trunk's broken.
- Close it.
- It's not closing.
Oh, God!
- Whoa.
- Did I really get your finger?
No, no, no, you're good.
[instrumental music]
Are you leaving me?
Yeah, I am.
I won't be gone that long.
- What?
- I won't be gone that long.
I'll miss you.
I'll be back really quick.
Okay.
Be safe.
I will.
Okay?
- Bye.
- Have a safe flight.
(Lauren) 'Thank you.'
Bye!
[instrumental music]
I can't believe
we're going together.
(Lauren) 'I'm just so glad
I'm finally going.'
It could be life-changing.
- It's gonna be so fun.
- I know.
[music continues]
[theme music]