- Hey!
Look at you with your own desk.
I know, so official.
Oh, my God, they moved
everything around in here.
- I know.
- It looks good though.
And all the clothes are more
organized and everything, too.
Like, all the sweaters
and the shoes back there.
I'm so proud of you
and your new job.
- Thank you.
- Are you gonna be my boss man?
Supposedly.
How are you doing?
I didn't tell you what happened?
No.
Started having, like, my friends
coming up to me
and just telling me, like
really, like,
rude, horrible rumors.
Like, the next thing I know,
all the exact same things
they were telling me, like
ended up, like, on the Internet.
Horrible.
And it got back to Laguna
and my parents.
What were the rumors?
They basically were
saying that, like
me and Jason made, like,
inappropriate videotapes.
Ay.
'Who does that?'
I just could never understand
hating someone so much
that you want to do something
like that to them.
Have you heard
from Heidi, lately?
[upbeat music]
- Delivery!
- Hey! You got the TVs?
- What is that?
- 'A jelly aquarium.'
[laughs]
A what?
I didn't even know you were
looking for a fish tank.
Are you working on invites?
- Yeah, I was.
- Look at you.
I need the guest list
of who's coming
for the housewarming party.
The guests? I don't think
we have a guest list.
'Cause I invite friends
and tell friends
to invite friends,
so I don't know what...
So, how many people are coming?
(Spencer)
'I invited Brody, Frankie'
I invited your boy.
I invited Gino, Panaro.
What about you?
Who are you gonna invite?
I'll invite Lauren and Audrina
and then, um, Whitney.
I already invited.
That's pretty much it.
We'll see if we can
get them on the list.
[chuckles]
[instrumental music]
- Hey!
- Hi. How are you?
Good. Haven't seen you
in so long.
- How's work going?
- Good.
Yeah? You just sit
here by yourself?
Um, Spencer and I are having
a little housewarming party.
I wanted to see if you
and Lauren wanted to come.
One for both of you.
If you want to come,
I talked to Whitney
and I think
she should be coming.
- Whitney is gonna go?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'll deliver it to Lauren.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
so, if you guys can come.
- 'Yeah!'
- If not but...
Um, but it was good seeing you.
I have to go take these
to the mailroom.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
[instrumental music]
Oh, my God.
- Chiara.
- Hi.
Oh, my God.
Heidi just came in here right
now.
Is she still here?
No, she just left.
What was she doing here?
She came her to give us
housewarming invitations.
Argh, I didn't even tell you
the story, but, like
she hasn't called Lauren once
since she's moved out.
We've heard from friends
that her and Spencer
were talking so much crap
on Lauren
saying really mean,
mean things.
'Saying that Lauren was no one
without Heidi'
and she could never get in
any club without her.
That's so pathetic.
You know what's the bad thing?
Lauren's mom called her.
She was like, "Lauren...
"...there's these rumors
on, on these websites
saying that you and Jason
have a sex-tape out."
And Lauren's like, "What?"
I cannot even imagine.
Even if these rumors
are going around
she could have called her
and been, like
you know, like, "I'm sorry."
Like, "Are you okay?"
Even if they had
nothing to do
with the rumors
in the first place.
We don't have any real proof
but they were best friends
and for Heidi just to stand back
and not do anything
and then for her to come in here
and give us invitations
and expect us to go
to her housewarming party?
- It's not gonna happen.
- No. That's really weird. Ugh.
I mean, I have Lauren's back,
regardless.
[instrumental music]
(Lauren)
'Oh, my God,
I have to tell you something.'
Audrina was at work today,
and Heidi walked into her work.
Really?
She came to give us invitations
'to her housewarming
party tonight.'
That's strange. Does she really
think you're gonna go?
No. She can't think
I'm gonna go.
I feel bad not going,
but at the same time
I just think I would feel really
uncomfortable being there.
- She's in a different world.
- Yeah.
Oh, well, hope she has fun.
So, what are we doing tonight?
'We're going to Les Deux.
You should come.'
Almost every time I go there,
I meet a cute guy.
Really? That sounds fun.
[both laugh]
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chatter]
[trance music]
[instrumental music]
(Brody)
'Oh, yeah.'
[indistinct chatter]
'Unbelievable.'
Wait till you taste
these things.
[knock on door]
- Jenny!
- Hi!
[Jen squealing]
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, I love you.
[both laugh]
Spencer better pay me for this.
Hi, nice to meet you.
You guys, margarita's in here.
Your apartment is so cute.
Okay.
Whitney, come here, pretty.
[Brody whistles]
'Refill, playboy.'
I shouldn't even be drinking.
It's Friday night.
You're 23 years old.
Brody is such a good influence.
Who wants one?
Oh, what a nice party.
I'm so glad that you came.
- I know.
- I'm so, so glad...
- I'm so glad to see you.
- I missed you so much.
I'm totally focused on, like,
my real friendships right now.
'Like, you're a very important
person to me.'
I know.
'I'm just really glad that'
you know, I'm here
and we're talking.
I'm just glad that
you're part of my fresh start.
You know, I'm glad
that you're here
to really be a part of all this
because, you know,
you mean so much to me.
- 'Did you invite Lauren?'
- I did.
I wish, you know, she were here
to see how much fun this is.
[upbeat music]
Lauren?
[clears throat]
How are you feeling?
'I think the girls' pre-party'
before going out
isn't always a good idea.
No. No more.
We can't start so early. Oh.
- I have the worst headache.
- Oh, yeah.
'What time did you get home?'
6:00 in the morning.
The club closes at 2:00.
What did you do for four hours?
We went back
to Justin's apartment.
- So you hooked up with him?
- We made out.
[chuckling]
You made out with that guy
from London.
Oh, God.
- You guys kissed a lot.
- No, we didn't.
- It wasn't just once.
- Really?
Yes.
[laughing]
No.
[instrumental music]
[machine whirring]
I liked all your friends
last night.
You know, they loved you
actually.
They seem very nice,
all of them.
Oh, Frankie invited us
to his birthday party
at Les Deux tonight.
Oh, yeah?
Is, um, Lauren going?
'Um, she actually
just called me.'
I just missed her call, and I'll
call her back and ask her.
I wish that Audrina and Lauren
would have come last night.
I mean, I totally accept
that she doesn't like me
but she shouldn't take
that out on you.
I know, our friendship
shouldn't suffer from it.
[upbeat music]
(Audrina)
'So, what time do
we have to be at Frankie's?'
(Lauren)
'Let's go around 10:00.'
So, I told you
I saw Brody, right?
He came up to me
and was really nice at first
and then he started
saying how we didn't go
to the housewarming party
and how we missed out.
- That's just rude though.
- It is really rude.
When you've disrespected
someone so much
they're not gonna be
there for you.
They're not, no, not at all.
And at this point,
I have no intention
of being there for her.
Oh, well.
What can you do?
All I know is, "Thank you
for getting out of my life."
Because now I have a better
roommate and a better apartment
'and I'm just
in a better situation.'
- Yeah.
- Cheers. Frankie's birthday.
Let's go have fun. Who cares?
It's done and over with.
It's gonna be a long night.
[Spencer whistles]
That looks good.
And those are the shoes?
I think so.
[whistles]
I'm dying to see if Lauren,
Audrina, and Whitney
show up to Frankie's birthday.
Somebody they've known
for three months
and they didn't show up
to their best friend's
housewarming apartment party.
So I wrote Lauren
a letter about
'not coming to
the housewarming party.'
Let me read these.
'Well, how about you don't read
them? They're personal.'
Oh!
Okay. So, should we go?
Oh, look at this.
You come in handy
so often these days.
[instrumental music]
[indistinct chatter]
Frankie's here!
The birthday boy!
(Frankie)
'Oh!'
Oh!
[clamoring]
'Frankie! Happy birthday!'
'Oh, yeah!'
[indistinct chatter]
- Happy birthday!
- Out of my mind.
I just wanted my... Yo, listen.
[indistinct chatter]
Not really.
- 'Lauren?'
- 'I don't want to talk to you.'
- 'What is your problem?'
- 'I don't understand.'
Heidi,
you're a different person.
You're not my friend anymore.
I don't...
I really,
I don't care about you.
I don't ever, ever
wanna talk to you again.
I think
that's really sad, Lauren.
- I think you're really sad.
- I feel bad for you.
'I always feel bad for you,
Lauren, always.'
- No, you're a bad person.
- What did I do? What did I do?
I was there for you
through everything
and now you're mad at me, it's
like, oh, come on, seriously.
- You know why I'm mad at you?
- Why, Lauren?
- You know why I'm mad at you.
- Why?
- You know what you did.
- Why? What did I do?
- You know what you did!
- What did I do? What?
'Heidi, you're brainwashed.
You're a different person now.'
- You guys are crazy.
- Yes, you're crazy.
What did I do? What did I do?
- 'You guys are sick people.'
- What did we do?
- You say... What did you do?
- Yeah.
What did you do?
You started a sick
little rumor about me.
- I didn't start any rumor.
- 'Oh, really, nothing?'
[instrumental music]
(Audrina)
'Lauren!'
Ugh!
She is playing Miss Innocent.
She knows exactly what she did.
I'm so...mad right now.
You don't know
what just went on.
[upbeat music]
(Elodie)
'Oh, I'm so hungry.'
(Heidi)
'Oh, my God, I totally forgot
to tell you what happened.'
- What?
- I went to Les Deux.
For, uh, Frankie's birthday,
right?
So, I walked in
with Frankie and everyone.
Lauren was at the table, right?
And she got up
from the table and left.
- So I was like, "Okay." Yeah!
- What?
And it's like I didn't
even think we had a problem.
So I go downstairs
to see what's wrong
and she starts looking at me
so crazy, and she's like
"You know what you did,"
and starts screaming at me.
"You're pathetic!
You're brainwashed!
Spencer brainwashed you!"
And I'm just like,
"What are you talking about?"
(Elodie)
'What are you guys
gonna do now?'
I don't know. I guess
we're not really friends or...
I don't know.
- I mean, do you even care?
- 'I mean, I do, but...'
- 'Like, do you miss her?'
- I mean, only to an extent.
It's like, you know,
she hates my boyfriend...
I just feel like
it's more drama than anything.
Yeah, it's like
I'm not a child...
And then for Audrina
just to take her side...
I'm not a catty girl,
and I'm not...
You know, I don't have time
for this.
Forget it.
[upbeat music]
- Hello.
- How are you?
'I'm pretty good. How are you?'
- Good.
- You look pretty.
Thank you. I like your jacket.
Thank you.
Did you go out last night?
No, actually.
I took the night off. Did you?
- It was Frankie's birthday.
- 'Oh, yeah?'
You have a good time?
It was alright. I got
in a fight with Heidi, though.
'Heidi was there?'
Was there a confrontation?
She was like,
"I don't understand
why you're mad at me."
W-T-F.
And she just won't take
any responsibility for it.
I mean, it's sad that
I lost her as a friend.
It's sad the things
she did to me.
Mm-hmm, but maybe
you haven't lost her forever.
I don't want a friend that I
know I will never trust again.
Right, I know.
I feel like, lately
or at least since I've known you
it's been really difficult
with friends.
It's like, you've had
a lot of problems with friends.
I'm lucky that I have Lo
that moved back.
And I have you at work and
I have Audrina in my apartment.
But, I literally feel like
one of my friends died.
You know what I mean?
Like, that friend is gone.
It's so sad.
She's just not a part
of my life anymore.
Maybe that's a good thing.
Yeah, and maybe you'll be
better off, you know.
I am so far.
[upbeat music]