So you know how Stephanie
was at my birthday party?
Yeah, I saw her.
I guess Spencer freaked out
at her, like made her cry.
Are you serious?
People just waste so much time
being angry at people.
I mean, she's not involved
in the situation at all
so she has no reason
not to be nice to you.
- And he called her Brody.
- Oh, God.
I mean, if he, oh,
that's ridiculous.
Can I hear about your new job?
I'm like...
So I get to New York,
and I walk in
and it's, like,
such a different atmosphere.
I mean, like, she wanted me
to see how the New York offices
work because she basically
wants to model the LA office
after the New York office.
So the day that I was there
we were working
on the Sass & Bide show.
- So fun!
- 'So fun. And the stuff...'
Wait, did you get
to work backstage?
Yes. My job during the show
was to, um, call the models.
Like, Kelly would be like,
okay, next model, out
and I'd be like, go, go, go.
- That's, like, my ideal job.
- I know.
I mean, while I was
doing it I was like
Lauren would be loving this
right now.
Yeah.
♪ Stop cold ♪
♪ I sold my soul ♪
♪ So you could be
my millionaire ♪
♪ Sit back and enjoy the show ♪
(Kelly)
'Okay, let's gather around
like the family that we are.'
Emily, Whitney, move down.
Emily, can you sit
over here with us?
'Alright. Next week
is LA Fashion Week.'
'I just wanna be really clear'
about what's goin' on
here this week.
'Rules for Fashion Week.'
What's expected of you
is complete devotion.
So any kind of concepts
of, like, 9:00 to 5:00
'LA, not happening here.'
I would plan to be here every
night to at least 11 o'clock.
You're gonna wear all black.
I don't wanna see your boobs.
I don't wanna see any piercings,
if you have tattoos
I don't really care,
I don't wanna see them.
'Do not roll your eyes at me,
do not question'
'what it is
that we're asking you to do.'
I'm not here to be your friend.
Emily, you're not here
to be their friend.
'We really care
about ourselves more.'
We already know this job,
but we will do our best
'to help teach you
as much as we can.'
'One of the things
that we need to talk about'
is celebrity outreach.
I don't think
any of it's happened yet.
- Working on that.
- Okay, it's a little late.
- I know, but we were...
- No.
- We, we, we nothing.
- Okay.
That was supposed to be
your responsibility, Jessica.
No, and I have been
working on that.
Do you have any press scheduled
for any of the clients?
- To come to the shows?
- No.
Any kind of preview
opportunities?
What other sort
of preview opportunities?
Well, for the Robin Antin one,
aren't there so many celeb
uh, woman celebrities
that have performed with her
that we can reach out to?
Yes. Good thinking.
'There you go! There you go!'
That's right, support is key.
Support and delegation is key.
'Alright, let's get to work.'
♪ I'd do it all over again ♪
♪ Aah ♪
♪ Aah ♪♪
[sighs]
[phone rings]
- 'Hey, Whitney.'
- Hi, Laur, how are you?
- Hey, what're you doin'?
- 'Fashion Week is next week.'
And there's just a lot of
things, like, riding on my back
so I wish you were here
to help me.
Mmm. I wish I was there, too,
but I'm not.
I'm in the closet.
There's no one in here.
- And I'm in here all day.
- 'I think we're starting.'
- 'I got to go.'
- Uh, okay. I love you. Bye.
Okay. Love you. Bye.
♪ Burned in your mind ♪
♪ I said freeze
we'll ride it again ♪
♪ They thought they
heard a shot ♪
♪ Run and face the wind ♪
♪ You can understand... ♪
So girls' night,
Spencer's totally not invited.
I at least need to do this like
once a week or once every...
- 'Oh, really?'
- Yeah.
Alright, now you're
steppin' up the game.
It's so weird, like,
going back into that scene...
- And like...
- Even going into Hollywood?
Yeah, like to a club and stuff,
like, that used to be my life.
We'll check out a different
couple clubs tonight.
- Okay.
- It'll be good.
♪ Tell you were telling me ♪
♪ I'm allowing here ♪
♪ But I don't need
nobody for me ♪
♪ I'm gonna allow ♪
♪ And tell you were telling me ♪
♪ I'm allowing here ♪
♪ But I don't need
nobody for me ♪
♪ I'm gonna allow ♪
I've never been here,
but I like the name.
- I've never been here either.
- Sounds tricky.
Hi.
♪ Wanna say hey hey hey hey ♪
♪ I say hey hey hey hey ♪
♪ Hey hey hey hey ♪♪
I would go out
it was like, Monday, is it
Tuesday is it,
Wednesday is it.
You gotta come back out.
Cheers to many more nights.
- To girls' night out.
- Yes.
- Feels good being out again.
- I know.
Ah! There you are!
Can I have
one more Red Bull vodka?
- Okay.
- Cabernet.
Cabernet?
(Stephanie)
You should.
Hey.
It's just, I try to stay out of
what's not my business anymore
because I don't
wanna get involved.
- Bye, Chiara.
- Bye. It was good to see you.
Bye, Audrina.
[instrumental music]
♪ When you hold
your head up high ♪
♪ In the middle of a fight ♪
♪ Rearrange ♪
(Heidi)
'Oh, I'm so excited to,
like, redo my apartment'
'cause I feel like,
you know, with Spencer gone
my taste is kind of evolving
and I get to do what I wanna
do to my apartment finally.
- Instead of graffiti?
- Right.
A little bit more of
a grown-up, mature apartment.
This is cute.
- I love this mirror.
- It's flattering.
- It's very tall.
- Yeah.
I actually have a mirror
and, like, some other things
that I need to get
that I left at Lauren
and Audrina's house.
And I don't know,
Audrina seemed pretty cool
when we saw her last night,
so maybe...
Maybe I can, like, talk to her
and try to get it or something.
- You didn't take your stuff?
- I left some stuff on accident.
I moved out so quickly
that I hardly
had time to get everything,
you know?
What if, like, Lauren got mad
and, like, burned it all
or poured, like, red wine on it?
I bet they threw it away.
- I wouldn't keep it.
- Unh-unh.
No, but I would love to,
like, see Audrina.
There's no reason why Audrina
and I should have a problem
when we were friends first,
you know?
I think she's just,
like, under Lauren's wing
and, like, not
trying to piss off Lauren.
I don't know.
[rock music]
♪ I never got much
out of this life ♪
♪ Never saw myself
with someone's eyes ♪
♪ Until this day ♪
I need to hold this
for ten seconds.
Good job.
(Lauren)
What are you guys doing right
now at People's Revolution?
Just getting ready
for Fashion Week?
Basically, yeah.
It's just getting
all the press to the shows
and making sure
that it's being covered
and then getting
all the clothes together
and just the production.
So, basically,
it's kind of what we've done
before but just more intense.
Exactly. It's what
we've done before
but it's six at a times
instead of, like,
one at a time, you know?
That's crazy.
You weren't there the first time
I met Kelly Cutrone, were you?
No, but I got a crying
phone call of you in panic.
Remember? It was the first
young Hollywood party
and you, I was prepping for it
and you were going
to get tickets, right?
Yeah, I needed them
for Lauren Howell.
And she was a little bit of a...
Oh, my god!
Everyone says, like "Watch out."
She's a little scary
and I never saw that scary side.
'But there's this girl Jessica
who's, like'
'basically the boss
in the LA office that'
I don't know, maybe didn't do
what she was supposed to do.
I didn't know
'cause I wasn't there.
But she brought out her fangs.
- Scary side?
- Scary. Yeah, so...
- I wanna see the office.
- It's really cool.
- Is it?
'I usually have a lunch break,
so maybe you can come by.'
Oh, that's good.
Maybe I'll come tomorrow.
Do you have, like,
friends there, like...?
It's not like us
working together, you know?
There's no one
that I necessarily
click with, that I could...
Nice to know
I haven't been replaced.
Yeah, you...
Never, never.
♪ And everybody knows
it's a great big lie ♪
♪ So d-d-don't say
it's all alright ♪
♪ And everybody goes
when you say goodbye ♪
♪ You d-d-don't look back ♪♪
- Hey.
I missed last week.
You did the homework
that was due today?
No, I did the homework
that was due last week.
Oh, yeah.
I went over it with her,
and she was like...
"This is wrong, this is wrong
and this is wrong."
And did the raisings.
- It's so annoying.
- Oops.
So Heidi and I
went to Vice last night
and we saw Audrina and Chiara.
- You what?
- 'Yeah.'
'Heidi and Audrina
talked for a long time'
and it kind of seems like
they're cool now
but it was interesting.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
It was a crazy night.
♪ Tell me lies tell me lies
tell me sweet little lies ♪
♪ I'm okay I'm alright
I got nothing to hide ♪
♪ Hello drama hello drama
hello drama hello ♪
♪ I don't want it but I get it
any more than I want ♪♪
- 'Hey.'
- Hi.
'What you doin'?'
I'm writing down
a shopping list.
Oh.
[sighs]
So, what's up?
- Um, just curious.
- What?
'Were you talking to Heidi
at Vice last night?'
Yeah.
I mean, like, you can be friends
with her, no matter what.
I would just be careful
if you considered
being good friends with her,
because it wouldn't surprise me
if she wanted to be
friends with you...
I have no intentions of being...
I know, but I'm just
telling you to be careful.
I will.
'Cause she is someone
who's gonna stab you
in the back two seconds later.
Lauren, I have no intentions
of being friends with her.
Like, I have my good friends.
I have you.
You know, what I mean?
Like, I don't need
someone else
in my life to stir up drama.
I think that
you're a really nice person
and that sometimes
people take advantage of that.
- Seriously?
- I would just be careful.
Okay.
'You've been
such a good friend to me'
and I'm not gonna,
like, go behind your back
and, like, hang out with someone
that's done bad things to you.
[rock music]
- Hi!
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- You look so cool.
Yeah, we're just doing, uh...
'styling for a photo shoot
right now.'
So can you just switch
these to plastic hangers?
Okay.
What makes it easier
for riding up the poles
also, is if you're try
and separate it by designer.
- Mm-hmm.
- Everything that is poled...
- Yes.
- You can just wheel it over.
'And we enter everything
on our computer system.'
What's been shot, who wore it,
when it's coming out?
All that sort of thing,
so then we track it.
(Whitney)
Okay, cool. Thanks.
- 'You wanna help me?'
- Oh, wow!
- Lauren, you're comin' with me.
- Sorry, I'm comin'.
- You okay, there, Whitney?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- I'm just moving.
- I think the one in the...
(Whitney)
We might not have time
for lunch.
That's okay.
'So we're just gonna
record it over here.'
Here, I'll just
ring stuff to you.
Okay. Um, so this is
Morphine Generation.
We're starting with, not
that shirt, the one after it.
- So, it's a gray tee.
- Yeah.
Gray tee. And then
the next one is a pink tee.
I'm so jealous
you went to New York...
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
I'm playing assistant
right now.
- Oh, you're helping?
- Yeah? Yeah, she's a big help.
Uh, we worked together
at "Teen Vogue."
Awesome. Well, we've got
a huge schedule
coming up for the Fashion Week.
We're doing about eight shows.
So, you know, we always bring
on people for extra help, so...
Oh, yeah, if you need any help.
We'll see. Yeah,
maybe that would work out.
- We'll put her to work.
- Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
- That'd be cool.
- It would be awesome.
♪ Come on come on come on ♪
♪ Come on you better take me ♪
♪ 'Cause I know I know I know ♪
♪ You know nothing
will take my place ♪
♪ Nothing will take my place ♪
[doorbell rings]
- Hi, what're you doing?
- Hello. How are you?
- Hi.
- You look cute.
A little messy.
But it looks different, huh?
So different.
Oh, there's my mirror.
Yeah, this is yours,
and then this is yours, right?
- Right, that's mine.
- "Cause it has like...'
Yeah, that was, like, a painting
from my mom's friend.
It's really cute. And this
is yours, too, I think.
- I don't know.
- Yeah.
That's okay. We don't
have to open that box.
Memories of Lauren and I
and ex-boyfriends.
- Mm-hmm.
- Fun.
I think that was it.
I don't know.
Yeah? It's so awkward
being in here.
So how about Lauren
and Stephanie being friends?
I was just like,
"This is too crazy."
- Right now, like...
- That's really random.
You don't like me
'cause of my boyfriend
but you like his sister.
It's weird how the world works.
I know.
Well, I think
I'm gonna get out of here
'cause I don't really know
when Lauren's coming back.
'But if you ever wanna hang out,
give me a call.'
♪ We're stuck on a stage
of parading lust ♪
♪ It seems it's always
only one thing more ♪
♪ It's always
Hi.
- So how was your day?
- Fine. I'm just tired.
Me too.
- I'm cleaning up.
- Thanks.
- A little bit.
- Was it messy?
'No, there were just, like,
magazines everywhere.'
- I have something to tell you.
- Oh, tell me.
Well, when you were gone today,
Heidi came over.
Did she just, like, show up
or did you talk to her?
She called me,
and she's like, "Is it okay
if I come and get my stuff
'cause I'm redoing..."
What stuff?
She had that box that you put
in a pile with the mirror.
Did she, like,
come in here and chill?
She sat down
for a few minutes, yeah.
She was saying, like,
how weird it was being in here.
Why the hell was she in here?
I don't know.
She came to get her stuff.
Grab her stuff and leave then.
Why is she, like, coming in here
and like,
makin' herself at home?
It's not her home anymore.
I know,
I honestly don't even know
what to say
about the whole thing.
It's just weird.
[rock music]
♪ And everything comes ♪
♪ With a price ♪
♪ But how much
can you sacrifice ♪
♪ You feel when you win
you still lose ♪
♪ And no one else
is in your shoes ♪♪
[theme music]