- Hi.
- I'm home. I'm home. I'm home.
Oh, my God.
- Arghh!
- How are you?
- Hello.
- Ohh.
I'm jet-lagged.
I want to hear about it.
How was it?
It was a lot, a lot,
a lot of work.
Like, and my body never really
fully switched times.
So now that it's getting darker,
it's like morning for me, right?
Yeah, did you get
any time to play
or was it all working
the whole time?
We had a little bit of
playtime, but not really.
We saw the Eiffel tower
at night with the band guys.
- They went took us...
- Oh, the French band.
- Eiffel Tower, yeah.
- How was that?
It was really nice to,
like, get away
from LA for a little while,
you know what I mean?
Just kind of, like, remove
myself and get away from Brody
'and realize there's other guys
out there...but I think'
I've kind of gotten to the point
where I'm just over it.
I know exactly how you feel.
Did Whitney have fun, too?
I think Whitney
doesn't want to work
for Teen Vogue anymore.
♪ Let's start this over ♪
♪ Yeay-yeay ♪
♪ Don't you see? ♪
♪ We can't give up ♪
♪ We can't give up ♪♪
- 'Hi.'
- 'Hi, Whit.'
(Whitney)
'Do you have a second to talk?'
Come in, please.
So, I wanted to talk to you
about my future.
I think that I've had
a great two years
and I feel so honored
to have worked here.
But, I feel like,
since working here
I've learned I kind of
want to be in styling.
And I don't know that I'll have
that opportunity here.
I've kind of been behind
the scenes and always assisting.
(Whitney)
'And so, I actually'
'got a call
for a job opportunity'
with Kelly Cutrone
here in Los Angeles.
So, I wanted to get
your blessing first
before I decided
to make a huge decision
and I didn't ever
want to burn any bridges
and I wanted to get
your feedback.
Well, two years
is a natural progression
to wondering where
you're gonna go next.
And it's time for you,
at this point, to start looking
at the opportunities
that are available to you.
That sounds like a great one.
'And styling is what
you want to do.'
I don't have that position
open for you.
If I did,
I would love to keep you.
- 'Right.'
- But, of course.
You have our blessing
and recommendations
will be made in your favor.
Well, thank you very much.
- 'Okay.'
- Okay. Thank you.
♪ You're on top of the world ♪
♪ And I'm just waiting
making up your excuse ♪
♪ You say that love's tough
are you sure? ♪
♪ Ain't it just a piece of cake
to make me look like a fool? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ You're on top of the world ♪
♪ If you're thinking
I've been blinking ♪
♪ While you're breaking
the rules ♪
♪ Don't that make you
the fool? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh-o-o-oh yeah ♪
Wow!
This place looks amazing.
Yeah.
It's different, right?
- Geez. Uh, here's the files.
- 'Cool.'
So, how's everything going
with you? You're busy, busy.
(Heidi)
'You know, I'm getting back
from Colorado.'
Just trying to figure
everything out with Spencer.
I haven't really, like,
talked to him or anything
since I've been back.
So, is he gonna move out or...
Yeah, I think he needs to,
like come over.
- And get his stuff and...
- Okay.
You know, I thought
it would be out
by the time I got back,
but I guess not.
It's like the dividing
of the things.
Right...it's gonna be such,
like, a heart-wrenching thing.
Even though I want him
to move out, like...
...it's not gonna
be easy watching him
like pack up his stuff,
you know.
Are you gonna be cool with him
if he starts to wanna see
other people...
I mean, no.
No, like, I thought we wouldn't
see other people.
- That was kind of like...
- 'Okay.'
I don't even
wanna really break up.
- I just need my space.
- 'Okay.'
I need my friends back.
Like, I gave up so much
for Spencer, you know?
Like, I literally gave up
everything for him.
I would just be careful, though
'cause it sounds like
you're going through exactly
what I went through with Danny.
And I was kind of
the same way where
you know, "We don't have
to be together."
'And he would kind of
use it against me.'
He'd be like, "Oh, well,
you're not my girlfriend, so..."
You know what I mean?
Ugh, I don't even want to get
into that territory.
[instrumental music]
- Really, like, you went
to Colorado, and she got mad?
Like, what could be
worse than that?
Nothing, thanks.
That-that's a great game plan.
Go get it as worse as possible,
and then it can only get better.
Well, let's find
the bright side.
'There is no bright side.'
I'm beyond annoyed
that I have to move out.
I would have rather
never moving in
knowing I was eventually
gonna have to move out.
Like...I just don't even know.
Well, if you're gonna be
living here
and if Heidi comes back
and she wants to hang out
with me, I mean...
Go hang out with her.
Uh, just don't bring her here.
'Cause she'll be like
"Oh, Spencer, space
and now you're in your sister's
condo trying to hang out."
Oh, my God.
Seriously.
I'm dead serious.
Just keep her away from me.
'Cause I don't want her to think
that I'm not giving her space.
And it's like, I hate dating.
I don't want to start
dating again.
It's like...
You're even considering that?
Yeah.
[rock song]
(Lauren)
'How did it go?'
(Whitney)
'Lisa was surprisingly
supportive.'
Really?
She just said, basically
you know, "I give you
my blessing
if you need a recommendation."
- That's good.
- 'I know.'
'And it kind of, like, gave me'
the little boost
to feel confident
in my interview
with Kelly Cutrone tomorrow.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah, I'm really excited.
I don't really see
how I can pass up
an opportunity like this.
- That's so weird.
- It is weird.
- 'I mean, it's great for you.'
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, 'cause it's just weird
'cause we got hired together.
I know. It's weird.
I haven't known this job
without you.
And I can't even imagine
not walking in here every day
and seeing you.
[instrumental music]
♪ Oh-o-oh ♪
♪ He-y-y-y ♪
♪ Oh-o-oh ♪♪
[phone ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
(Jessica)
'Thank you so much.
I appreciate it.'
Okay, have a great day.
Bye.
- Hi. I'm Whitney.
- Hi, I'm Jessica.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'm here to see Kelly.
- 'Okay.'
'You can just have a seat
right over there.'
Okay, cool.
[telephone ringing]
(Whitney)
'What-what line?
Okay.'
(Kelly)
'Hey, it's Cutrone.
We have a serious problem.'
'They hung the clothes outside'
'on Nikki's gate and I think
someone stole them.'
'So, what you need to do now is
you need to figure out'
'who the idiot is
that would hang clothes'
'on the outside
of a gate, okay?'
'Alright, I gotta go, I don't
wanna talk about this anymore.'
'Thank you, bye.'
(female employee)
'We had Crystal Mirrors
with "Daily Candy."
Excuse me.
- Hi, I'm Kelly Cutrone.
- Hi.
- I'm Whitney.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- I'm well.
Nice to meet you.
Listen, uh, I don't
have a lot of time
so I just wanted to say
thank you for coming.
I don't know what you know
about People's Revolution
but we have three offices,
we have one in New York
one in Los Angeles,
and one in Paris.
We produce more shows
in New York than anyone.
We're a full-service
branding company.
'By the way, if we do decide
to do this together'
we would want you
to come to New York
and work with us
during fashion week.
Our office here is really
about styling.
We do 65... Mike, don't you
think, like
eighty five percent of
our pulls come from...
'It's from stylists
coming into the showroom.'
So 85 percent of what
this office generates
is an influx of traffic
from stylists
'that are usually working
with the celebrities.'
I mean, why do you want
to work on this side of it?
I think that the more
opportunities I have
and the more opportunities
I put myself out there for
'I should take advantage.'
'I just think
working at Vogue'
'was an unbelievable
experience.'
I just wanted a job that,
uh, I could do more.
What are your strengths, like
why should I let you
come work here?
I could probably be
very helpful, in terms of...
...whether it's, you know,
stylists that come in here
and pulling for photo shoots
or styling for lookbooks
or styling for runway shows.
Lisa said a lot of
great things about you
and she's not an easy person
to please all the time.
'I mean, we have the same
kind of work aesthetic.'
So, let's just go out on a limb.
We'll just do it,
and we'll see how it goes
'and we'll reevaluate
everything.'
But I think it's really
important to let you know this.
Like, you're basically
making a deal with the devil.
Why do you say that?
'Cause you have to
give up your life.
The good news is,
you get a whole new one.
♪ This is the love song
you'll never hear ♪
♪ Just a warm breeze
between my mouth and your ear ♪
♪ Hey this is the... ♪
Oh, my God.
They have Eggs Benedict?
This is, like,
my new favorite restaurant.
'I'll never forget the time
when Spencer said'
"I'm gonna get
the mu-mussel breakfast."
And I was like, "Why?
'cause you have no muscles?"
And he was like, "Shut up."
He was, like, so mad.
Oh, my God, So, I think
Spencer's moving in with me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Huh.
So, this is what you want?
You don't care
if he dates other girls?
No, he's not dating other girls.
We're not dating other people.
Why, did he say something
like that to you?
When I talked to him last, like,
we were just gonna start over.
You know, we weren't gonna
see other people.
We weren't gonna
try to do that.
Like, we were just
being together
and living in separate places.
I don't know, people do crazy
things when they're mad.
I mean, I hope
he doesn't pull anything
because I really do,
I really do love him, and...
'Hmm.'
I don't know.
♪ One mistake ♪
♪ Can lead you to another ♪
♪ Heartbreak ♪
♪ And you're going through ♪
♪ Life ♪♪
I feel like I need to go out
in L.A., it's been so long.
- I know.
- I've missed it so.
I haven't really been out,
I went out
that one night
when you were in Paris
when I saw Brody
and Frankie and them.
Have you talked to him at all?
He might be with the new "Girl."
Aren't you kind of, like,
relieved that Brody's, like
kind of done with now?
Yeah, I mean, I just really wish
they weren't coming tonight.
[groaning]
Who cares...let's just not
worry about the guys.
We're gonna go out and have fun.
'We're both, like,
full-on single.'
- Yay!
- I know.
I'm actually
really happy about it.
So am I.
You ready to go get in trouble?
Mm-hmm.
♪ Yeah
Come on come on ♪
♪ Give me a bump bump bump ♪
♪ Everybody in the club
get a bump bump bump ♪
♪ We're gonna keep it high
Ya we gonna get it done ♪
♪ Come on come on
give me a bump bump bump ♪
♪ Give me ♪
♪ Come on come on ♪
♪ Give me a bump bump bump ♪
Hi, where have you been
all my life?
♪ We're gonna keep it high
Ya we gonna get it done ♪
♪ Come on come on
give me a bump bump bump ♪
♪ You need
a grown man like me ♪♪
- 'Hey!'
- Oh!
[indistinct chatter]
- 'Well, well.'
- Lauren, welcome back.
Welcome.
She's giving him a hug.
You give me a hug.
She's mad at you.
- You never...
- Oh, she's mad at me?
- Oh, you're mad at me?
- You never called from Paris.
- You better not be mad at me.
- Never called from Paris.
You're not...whoa!
I don't get a hug or anything?
'You're really not
gonna give me a hug?'
You're not gonna
give me a hug right now?
Where's your girlfriend?
My girlfriend?
Who's my girlfriend?
Where's your boyfriend
from Paris?
- I don't have a boyfriend.
- Oh, really, you don't?
That's too funny,
'cause I have friends in Paris.
'And don't you dare
try to turn this on me.'
- 'Oh, no, that's...'
- What is wrong with her?
Why does, why is she doing this?
Treat me as a friend.
- Like we always were.
- I am treating you...
I haven't seen you
in a long time.
I'm excited to see you.
All you, the first thing
you say to me is
"Oh, Brody,
where's your girlfriend?"
'That is...that's ridiculous.
Alright, fine.'
- 'Stop.'
- Yeah, alright, whatever.
Well, then I'm stopping.
I'm out of here.
Brody, stop.
Hey, Hey!
'Stop, bro.'
Dude, what the...?
Just stop,
I didn't do anything.
What did I do? Oh, my God!
I didn't give him a hug.
You're not being mean,
but you're not being nice.
And he really came here,
he was excited to see you.
Do I really have to be nice
right now?
- 'Yes.'
- Why?
Why not?
Well, I know what you're talking
about and why you're mad
But he loves you,
and you love him.
That's just, that's real.
♪ I'm coming to terms ♪
♪ I'm starting to learn ♪
♪ This ain't all
it's cracked up to be ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪♪
[instrumental music]
(Lauren)
'So, Whitney got the job
with Kelly Cutrone'
and she's leaving
Teen Vogue today.
That's really cool.
That might be amazing
for her something like
celebrity
styling over there.
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Excuse me.'
Thank you very much.
You seem a little like, ugh...
What?
I don't know, are you
just tired from your trip?
Just weird being back.
I don't-it's something...
I mean, it was just really
awkward seeing Brody last night.
'What do you mean?'
Did he have
the girlfriend there?
No.
'It's hard because
we're all friends'
and we all go out,
and they're there all the time.
I know.
I don't know
what the answer is.
And this, Brody has a way
of making me feel like
I'm never good enough,
and I hate that feeling.
And I feel like I need
to prove it to myself
and, like, that's
the only reason
- But that's not a good reason...
- Sweety.
- What?
- Of course!
You're good enough for Brody.
He should be the one
that has to work to get you.
Aw, you have to say that
'cause you're my friend.
- I think it's true, though.
- Thank you.
I just don't know how
you're gonna stop concerning
yourself with Brody when
he's such a part of your life.
'You know what I mean?'
- I'm not saying it to be mean...
- I know.
I feel like we have
this conversation a lot
about "You need to find
a nice boy" and...
Yeah.
I just wish that
it wasn't like that.
You know what I mean?
♪ And yet I stay
till I'm not confused ♪
♪ It wasn't wrong ♪
♪ Till I got drowned
in my tears ♪
♪ And now I know ♪
♪ We are all dreamers ♪
♪ We're all just searching for ♪
Ah, so, what would I do
without my Xbox?
♪ We're gonna win again ♪
What else are you taking?
I'm letting you have the TV.
"Letting?" I bought the TV.
You bought the 42-inch.
I bought the 50-inch.
- They were the same price.
- No, they weren't.
- We just split them.
- Whatever, we're not arguing.
Is "Empires Of The Sand"
your book?
'Yeah, that's mine.'
It's not like we're broken up.
Uh, in what sense?
In the sense that...
I mean, you're not planning
on seeing other people, right?
I'm giving you
your space, remember?
Lots of it.
Um...ahh.
All this stuff's good.
[box scraping]
♪ I wonder why ♪
Enjoy your space.
♪ You thought that it was time ♪
♪ To say goodbye ♪
♪ I thought that
you will never ♪
♪ Say goodbye ♪
♪ I wonder why ♪
[instrumental music]
It's so weird.
It's so surreal.
You're happy, right?
I'm really happy.
I'm just...
'I have a bunch
of different feelings.'
I'm nervous,
I'm excited, I'm sad.
'I don't know how
I'm gonna walk into my office'
and not see your
face there every day.
Oh, we're having, like, a
long-distance relationship now.
Ah-ha-ha I know,
is that gonna work?
We'll make it work, Whitney.
I hear long distances
don't really work that well.
I hear that, too.
But we'll make it work.
[laughing]
'Man, have we been through'
'so much together or what?'
From almost getting fired,
well, not fired
but the first night we worked
at the young Hollywood party
when Heidi and her friends
crashed the party.
- Should have known it then.
- I was just about to say.
- We should have known then...
- That she was bad news.
[chuckling]
[sighing]
- 'That's so funny.'
- So funny.
- I think I'm good.
- 'Ohh...'
I'm trying to decide what else.
You wore the same bag
as you wore on the first day.
That is weird.
I find that very strange.
- Isn't that funny?
- It's so weird, I love this...
The first day I met you,
you wore that bag.
What are we gonna do
without each other?
[exhaling]
I think I got everything.
♪ Following your heart ♪
Well, I'll miss you.
- I love you.
- Call me later, okay?
- I will.
I'll help you pick out
what you're gonna
wear for your first day.
Oh, my gosh.
And you have to curl my hair.
- Okay.
- I love you.
- Bye.
♪ And these dreams ♪
♪ Everything is boring
but change ♪
♪ Everything will change ♪
♪ Why don't you say
what you want to me? ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ Go ahead ♪
♪ I am not listening ♪
♪ Say what you want to me ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ Go ahead ♪
♪ I am not ♪
♪ Say say say ♪♪
[instrumental music]
[theme music]