So we're supposed to fold
this stuff up in tissue
and then ship it back
to New York.
- So cool.
- 'So how's Audrina?'
I haven't heard from her
in a long time.
Me neither.
- You haven't either?
- 'Uh-huh, she's good.'
- She's been busy.
- 'She is?'
- She's been okay?
- Yeah.
She keeps running
into Heidi places.
What do you mean
running into Heidi places?
I mean, like, every time she
goes out, she's been seeing her.
Do they get
in confrontations or...
No, it's...
No, no, she's friendly.
- 'Oh, she's friendly?'
- T-They're friends.
Oh.
It puts us all in a little bit
of an awkward position
because it's like,
it's both of our homes
and so she should be able to do
whatever she wants there.
- Why, because she came over?
- She's been over, yeah.
And I can't tell her
what to do in her home.
But at the same time,
it's my home as well
and I don't want people in there
that I don't get along with.
Yeah, I completely
understand that.
'This is so fun.
I have someone to talk to.'
I never thought
we'd be together again.
♪ Popular I don't wanna see
your face again ♪
♪ And I don't care
who you were ♪
♪ 'Cause you're never
gonna be popular again ♪♪
(Lo)
'So how was your first day
with Whitney?'
It was really good. You're going
out to Goa with us, right?
- Yeah, come to Goa.
- I need a night out.
- I'm so like...
- What are you wearing tonight?
I feel like I've worn
everything already.
Oh, by the way,
your green Phillip Lim dress
they made it in white and I
almost died when I saw it.
I'm not gonna wear
the same dress as you.
(Audrina)
'Let's see.'
- There's one option.
- Is it cotton?
(Lauren)
'When did you go and, like,
quadruple your closet, woman?'
Okay, so I have three options.
I got an A plus
on my assignment today.
- Say good job, Lauren.
- Good job, Lauren.
- Good job.
- What class is it in?
I'm so scholarly.
In my computer class.
Is that the computer class
you're in with Stephanie?
- Stephanie Pratt.
- Yeah.
She might actually come tonight.
Well, that's good.
(Lo)
'Maybe she'll bring Heidi.'
Hey, I'm gonna hop
in the shower.
I'm gonna look
for an outfit to wear.
(Lauren)
'Get dressed, woman.'
♪ Really love
to see you tonight ♪
(Heidi)
'I don't know
what to wear tonight!'
I was thinking maybe like this.
Oh, this one wants
to come out too.
That's cute.
And like, or maybe even,
like, with these white shoes.
You are excited about tonight,
I can tell.
I'm so excited
because it's finally, like...
Ooh. Maybe these shoes.
It's finally,
like you know, after S Bar
and seeing how Spencer
was behaving
like, I finally just
wanna have a girls' night
and have a good night
and, you know
like, I don't need
the extra stress, you know?
Well, it is Thursday
and Goa's the best on Thursdays
so Roxy and Alex
are gonna meet us and then...
Audrina said she might be going.
Literally, everyone
goes on Thursdays.
You don't think, um
like, Lauren would go
with her, do you?
She told me she is.
Don't freak out.
Well, I don't care.
If she's there, like, maybe
maybe this will be, like,
the first time it's okay.
Because I feel like
she always had a problem
with me because of Spencer
'and now that I'm not
really with him...'
I mean, it was so long ago
and it had to do more
with, like, I don't know.
'I mean, I don't have
a problem with her.'
Like, I'll be nice to her.
You know? I...
It's old water under the bridge,
you know?
♪ Hey bounce it
bounce it techno ♪
♪ Spin like a DJ ♪
♪ What you're tapping
bounce it bounce it techno ♪
♪ The dance floor
is calling out my name ♪
♪ When the DJ plays
I'm gonna yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Lights are flashing
in my face ♪
I totally like, bumped
into a guy over there
and I-I thought I knew him,
and I was like hey
and, like, made awkward,
awkward eye contact
and then he was like, hey,
and I was like
Oh, my God! I don't know you!
Hey, I'm gonna step out
for just a minute.
I'll be right back.
Can I get a glass
of champagne, please?
Hi!
- Hi!
- Hi! How you doing?
What's going on?
You look so cute!
I love it!
No problem.
- Hi.
- Hi, Justin.
How are you?
I think I'm gonna go.
- How's it going?
- How are you?
(Justin)
'I'm okay, a little tired.'
But how's that?
Is everything cool now?
Oh, my God, I have to leave
this table immediately.
But you guys,
have an awesome time.
- Have fun!
- Yay!
[hip hop song]
♪ On the way to your house ♪
♪ And I drive all night alone ♪♪
Oh, my God,
I can't believe we're up.
How much fun was last night?
It was fun,
but it wasn't really
like, what I expected, you know?
I thought it was really,
like, good progress
that we were all sitting
at the same table.
- 'I really did.'
- Yeah.
But like, for a minute, I was
like oh, we can all be friends.
I thought, especially, like,
not really being with Spencer
that maybe she would be
a little bit warmer, you know?
- 'Like, a little bit.'
- Yeah.
It's just, it's so weird
between her and I, you know?
But, I mean,
you and Audrina are fine.
I mean, it was good
to, like, see Audrina.
But I don't know.
♪ You run until now
run run away ♪
♪ Oh yeah you run run away ♪
- Hello?
- Hey.
- Hi. How are you?
- I'm good. How are you?
- I'm tired.
- Oh.
Will you, will you
grab me a water bottle?
- Yeah.
- 'Thanks.'
How was work?
Worked so hard.
How was your day?
- 'Good. I like my new job.'
- Cool.
What are you spraying
on yourself?
- My... Aah!
- Oops, nails.
- My, like, Insta-Dri.
- Oh, cool.
'Was there a lot of traffic
getting over here?'
Yes.
I hate that you're far away.
I know! It is bad.
- 'Getting here takes a while.'
- I know.
Did you stay here two
or three days over the weekend?
I think I was here
two nights in a row.
Wouldn't that be fun
if we all got a house together
like, all the girls
and then we could just
like, come home and not have
to all go our separate ways?
- That'd be so fun.
- 'Wouldn't it be?'
I'm just kind of sick
of this apartment.
Like, it's,
I just feel so, like...
- When's your lease up?
- Soon.
'There's something to be
said about moving.'
You know what I mean,
like you get to go
through all your stuff
and clean everything out
and kind of have a fresh start.
- A house would be so fun.
- 'Right?'
And you can live
with more people
and it just, like, works.
Who do we want to live with us?
- Audrina.
- Audrina too?
Do you think she'd wanna,
like, go from, like
living by herself to living
with one to living with two?
- I'll ask her.
- Is she here?
- Dinner.
- 'Who'd she go to dinner with?'
- 'Justin Bobby.'
- That's not true.
Yes, it is true and it actually
kind of freaks me out.
Wait, that's so weird.
Maybe she'll bring Heidi
'and Justin Bobby
to the new house.'
That's not allowed.
♪ It feels like this rain
won't stop ♪
♪ And I can't get out ♪
♪ It feel's like
this place is all gone ♪
♪ And I don't want to know ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Can you help me to stand up? ♪
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
- Oh, you're in to eat dinner.
- Where did you come from?
- How are you?
- Good. How you doing?
Good. You smell good.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I haven't showered in weeks.
[chuckles]
I like your leathers.
It looks like you miss
the bike, huh?
Come on. A little bit?
- A little bit.
- 'Little bit?'
Yeah.
I don't think
anybody's, I don't I...
I don't think anybody's
been on it since.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I got a solo seat
and I haven't had anybody on it.
Wow. What have you been up to?
Hanging out. Doing the move.
So your new place
is by the beach?
- Mm-hmm.
- That's so nice.
I'm excited. It's good.
Change is good.
People are different.
I needed to get
my priorities straight.
Yeah.
'Remember the first, our first
little date we went to?'
How long ago was that?
'Long.'
Do you think about all the BS
that's been on between
that time and right now?
I know. A lot.
It's, like, I'm just
over all that stuff.
- Yeah.
- You know?
I have my own stuff going on.
I don't want any more drama.
Like Lauren still won't
talk or look at Heidi.
But I see Heidi out now
and, like, we're okay.
No, she seems really nice.
Yeah. We used to be
really good friends.
Okay.
Like we talked about you
when she came over
the other week.
- Yeah.
- Whatever.
It-It might cause
a little drama.
Oh? A little?
[laughing]
It's not nice
when you fall away from people
but when you, when you kind of
regroup again, it's kind of...
- Good company.
- Absolutely.
Yeah.
- You know, I missed you.
- I missed you too.
What are you gonna do
later tonight?
I don't know.
Uh-oh.
♪ I'm in too deep ♪
♪ Can barely breathe ♪
♪ I've had enough
but I can't give up ♪
♪ 'Cause you're beautiful ♪
- 'Hey.'
- Good morning.
- She lives.
- 'I live.'
Can I have the other half?
- Yeah. I saved it for you.
- Okay. Cool.
So what happened to you
last night? I tried calling you.
- You did?
- Yeah.
I didn't see your call.
'Justin and I went out
pretty late last night.'
- How's he doing?
- 'He's doing really good.'
- That's good.
- He's cleaned up.
Did he burp in your face?
No, he didn't burp at all.
- He didn't burp once.
- Wow.
He's doing good.
I'm happy for him.
So you guys are good
just being friends?
There's always
gonna be something.
I think you still love him.
I don't know. It's like you
and Jason or Stephen, you know?
No, it's not, because I
stopped going back to Jason.
We didn't go on a date
like a date date
like a we-wanna-get-back
together date.
We just went out and talked.
Tomato, to-mah-to...
Call it what you want.
He kept asking me a bunch
of questions about Heidi.
It seems like you and Heidi
are becoming friends again.
I don't know, it's like
whenever you stop talking
to someone who's,
you were really close to
it's like, a good friend,
like, I feel like
I have one of my friends back,
you know?
'I need a spoon.'
Alright, I'm gonna go get
dressed and get ready.
Okay.
[knock on door]
Comin'.
Look who it is.
Steph's not here.
Steph's not here?
She is not.
- Oh.
- Can I help you?
Yeah, I just wanted to come
and see how you are.
I thought you were here
to see Steph.
Okay.
So you came here
to hang out with Stephanie
and now you're pretending
like you wanna talk to me.
- Well, now that I'm here.
- Oh. What's going on?
I went to, uh, to Goa
the other night
with your sister.
Cool. Did you have fun?
No. Actually, I didn't.
Because, uh, your sister
was, you know
like hanging out with Lauren
and I felt really uncomfortable.
And she was, like,
pretty icy to me.
I can't believe you would go to
a club where she was even there.
No, it was awful.
It was a really bad night.
Um, I know you probably
want to vent about this
but I really have
no sympathy for you
'cause who do you expect
to find at Goa?
Oh, I was just trying to be,
like, the bigger person and be...
Why even try? You think you guys
are gonna move back in together?
All of a sudden, everything's
gonna be hunky-dory?
No offense,
I really don't wanna talk
about you out at clubs, so...
Maybe you should wait
for my sister to come back.
You know what, I got to go.
'Will you tell Steph I said hi?'
It was great seeing you.
Enjoy your space.
Yeah, it was great
seeing you too.
You look great.
♪ The past is in the past ♪
♪ Hanging onto a memory
is not gonna bring it back ♪
♪ The people that surround you ♪
♪ They couldn't care
less about you ♪♪
Okay, so I was thinking
more about the house.
I haven't really
talked to Audrina.
About moving in?
Do you wanna live with her?
'I love livin'
with Audrina.'
Remember, like the night that
Audrina had a date with Justin
the first meeting
of Justin Bobby
when we named him Justin Bobby?
That's what it would be like
every night living together.
Fun!
[laughs]
Audrina brings dirty boys home
and I'm like, "Hey, friend,
wanna hang out?"
Want me to torment you forever?
To be fair,
they're not all dirty.
Justin Bobby was just
exceptionally dirty.
That's funny.
Hey! How are you, sweetie?
Good. Tired.
You have the same pants on?
Yes, we have the same pants on.
That's amazing.
We were gonna order food for you
but didn't know what you'd want.
Um, I'll just get whatever
they got and then soup.
- Okay.
- It's good.
Um, you went out to dinner
with Justin last night, right?
Um, no, we just went out
and we caught up
and like, he said he stopped
drinking for now, anyways.
Really?
Um, Lo and I were talking about
how the lease is running up.
Yeah.
Um, so we have to kind of start
figuring out
what our plan is afterwards.
Do you know
what you're gonna do yet?
I mean, I haven't
really thought about it.
Well, we were thinking about
possibly getting a house.
It's totally up to you,
whatever you want.
Have you guys already
been looking?
- A little bit, but not like...
- Kind of.
Oh.
(Lo)
'So this is what
we were thinking about'
and we didn't know,
like, if you
like had a plan yet
or were thinking about it, so...
Well, yeah.
I mean, I'm definitely open.
Yeah, it's, it's gonna be,
like, a weird change.
But at the same time,
like, Lauren and I
have known each other
for so long
and, you know, like,
the social aspect
of it is gonna be different
but still just as fun, you know?
Well, I mean, if you guys want
me to move in with you, I will.
- For sure.
- Yay! I'm so excited!
♪ 'Cause I'm a fool ♪
♪ Think I don't have a clue ♪
♪ I know what you're doing ♪
♪ Who do you think
you're fooling? ♪
♪ I can see it through ♪
♪ Everything you do ♪
♪ You can't you won't
hurt me anymore ♪♪
[theme music]