1
00:01:53,053 --> 00:01:55,317
Wake up.

2
00:01:56,589 --> 00:01:59,456
Wake up, sleepyhead.

3
00:02:16,000 --> 00:02:19,101


4
00:02:19,428 --> 00:02:22,966


5
00:02:24,000 --> 00:02:26,077


6
00:02:30,256 --> 00:02:32,087
Be quiet, woman.

7
00:03:36,990 --> 00:03:39,049
Posca.

8
00:03:41,494 --> 00:03:43,325
Lucius Vorenus.

9
00:03:44,864 --> 00:03:48,527
Your monthly debauch is finished already?

10
00:03:48,568 --> 00:03:50,331
I see yours isn't.

11
00:03:50,370 --> 00:03:53,567
This? This is nothing.

12
00:03:53,740 --> 00:03:56,760
This is for my nerves.

13
00:03:56,810 --> 00:03:59,404
- Where is he?
- Where is he?

14
00:04:00,246 --> 00:04:03,010
A deep question.

15
00:04:03,049 --> 00:04:05,449
His mortal flesh is in the throne room

16
00:04:05,485 --> 00:04:07,953
meeting the delegation from the Senate.

17
00:04:07,987 --> 00:04:10,512
- They're here already?
- Yes.

18
00:04:10,557 --> 00:04:16,291
Senator Bibulus and several other
distinguished men whose names I forget

19
00:04:16,329 --> 00:04:17,591
arrived this morning.

20
00:04:17,630 --> 00:04:19,757
And why are you not in there?

21
00:04:19,799 --> 00:04:22,267
I value my life, such as it is.

22
00:04:23,603 --> 00:04:27,903
When the queen growls at me, I retreat.

23
00:04:33,780 --> 00:04:36,112
It's not cowardice.

24
00:04:37,684 --> 00:04:40,175
Who would look after my wife?

25
00:04:44,924 --> 00:04:49,725
You lead the animal on slightly. You see?

26
00:04:49,762 --> 00:04:52,196
Depending on how fast he's going.

27
00:04:53,199 --> 00:04:55,633
Drink the water.

28
00:04:58,304 --> 00:05:04,140
Now here's the moment.
The animal thinks only of his thirst.

29
00:05:04,177 --> 00:05:06,145
He knows there is danger.

30
00:05:06,179 --> 00:05:09,307
But he cannot resist the water.

31
00:05:22,962 --> 00:05:25,021
Easy, you see.

32
00:05:25,064 --> 00:05:27,157
My turn.

33
00:05:28,101 --> 00:05:31,332
Antony, if we might discuss
the matter at hand?

34
00:05:34,440 --> 00:05:37,273
You'll scare off the deer.

35
00:05:45,151 --> 00:05:49,611
- He moved. The beast moved!
- Again.

36
00:05:49,656 --> 00:05:52,420
Regarding the grain supply...

37
00:05:52,592 --> 00:05:55,857
I have been authorized to offer you
double the previous price,

38
00:05:56,829 --> 00:05:59,696
if you can guarantee delivery
before the end of the month.

39
00:05:59,732 --> 00:06:01,529
Double, you say?

40
00:06:03,069 --> 00:06:04,263
That's not bad.

41
00:06:09,776 --> 00:06:12,404
- Triple.
- Agreed.

42
00:06:13,513 --> 00:06:15,879
We will pay triple the correct price.

43
00:06:17,116 --> 00:06:19,311
And Carthage.

44
00:06:19,352 --> 00:06:22,219
Carthage will be annexed to Antony's control.

45
00:06:24,991 --> 00:06:26,686
That may be possible.

46
00:06:26,726 --> 00:06:28,785
Poor Octavian.

47
00:06:28,828 --> 00:06:31,228
He must be really desperate.

48
00:06:31,264 --> 00:06:34,529
People are starving, dying.

49
00:06:36,102 --> 00:06:39,629
Octavian will do what he must
to prevent further suffering.

50
00:06:39,672 --> 00:06:42,232
Because he loves the people so.

51
00:06:42,275 --> 00:06:45,676
- He does.
- He loves nobody and nobody loves him.

52
00:06:45,712 --> 00:06:50,775
He could feed the people larks
and oysters till they burst,

53
00:06:51,584 --> 00:06:53,745
and they would still love me more.

54
00:06:53,786 --> 00:06:55,720
Isn't that right, Vorenus?

55
00:06:55,755 --> 00:06:57,950
Yes, sir.

56
00:06:57,991 --> 00:07:00,551
There we are. The voice of the people.

57
00:07:00,593 --> 00:07:03,426
They love me.

58
00:07:03,463 --> 00:07:08,457
I have no doubt you are right,
but we do have an agreement, yes?

59
00:07:08,501 --> 00:07:10,162
Yes.

60
00:07:12,205 --> 00:07:13,638
Triple rates...

61
00:07:14,540 --> 00:07:16,201
and Carthage.

62
00:07:16,743 --> 00:07:18,643
- And Spain.
- Spain?

63
00:07:22,048 --> 00:07:23,276
You can't have Spain.

64
00:07:24,817 --> 00:07:28,014
That's a shame. No deal, then.

65
00:07:28,054 --> 00:07:31,683
- Really, this is absolutely...
- No deal.

66
00:07:34,227 --> 00:07:36,821
Brava, my love!

67
00:07:36,863 --> 00:07:38,228
Venison for dinner, then?

68
00:07:43,870 --> 00:07:46,168
Pleasant voyage home, boys.

69
00:07:59,752 --> 00:08:02,050
Get him out of here.

70
00:08:02,088 --> 00:08:04,113
I'll show you to your quarters.

71
00:08:04,157 --> 00:08:06,819
- Is he always like that?
- Like what?

72
00:08:11,297 --> 00:08:15,358
Well, if that doesn't make
the little shit declare war,

73
00:08:15,401 --> 00:08:17,392
I don't know what will.

74
00:08:19,005 --> 00:08:21,303
He's a cautious beast.

75
00:08:30,850 --> 00:08:34,286
Perhaps you should simply cut the cord

76
00:08:34,320 --> 00:08:37,118
and declare war yourself.

77
00:08:37,156 --> 00:08:38,987
Declare war...

78
00:08:40,426 --> 00:08:42,257
on Octavian?

79
00:08:43,129 --> 00:08:47,031
On my most trusted and beloved colleague?

80
00:08:47,066 --> 00:08:50,399
On Rome? On my own people? No, no, no.

81
00:08:51,571 --> 00:08:53,562
No, that wouldn't do.

82
00:08:55,074 --> 00:08:58,134
When I return home,

83
00:08:58,177 --> 00:09:01,578
it will be as a savior,
not as a conqueror.

84
00:09:04,217 --> 00:09:06,583
I'm very tired.

85
00:09:15,628 --> 00:09:17,459
Oh, Helios.

86
00:09:17,497 --> 00:09:21,194
Selene, off with you. Off with you.

87
00:09:21,234 --> 00:09:23,862
Can't you see your father needs to sleep?

88
00:10:11,684 --> 00:10:14,209
Where are you going? Stay.

89
00:10:14,253 --> 00:10:16,244
You can hear them.

90
00:10:19,325 --> 00:10:21,953
What are you gonna do?
Bake 'em a cake?

91
00:10:21,994 --> 00:10:23,791
Oh, Dis.

92
00:10:23,830 --> 00:10:27,163
I forget sometimes
what a cold-hearted bitch you really are.

93
00:10:29,135 --> 00:10:31,228
Would you have me any other way?

94
00:10:32,805 --> 00:10:34,432
Are you joking?

95
00:10:34,473 --> 00:10:37,067
Anyone offers me a good horse
with the leathers thrown in...

96
00:10:38,144 --> 00:10:40,135
...you're gone.

97
00:11:01,767 --> 00:11:03,667
Back! Back!

98
00:11:03,703 --> 00:11:06,035
Keep out of the way!
Get out of the way!

99
00:11:15,715 --> 00:11:17,615
Let me through.

100
00:11:18,618 --> 00:11:20,745
Get out the way!

101
00:11:21,821 --> 00:11:23,516
Clear the way.

102
00:11:27,793 --> 00:11:30,455
Grain! Grain! Grain! Grain!

103
00:11:33,666 --> 00:11:36,601
- Please!
- My father is starving.

104
00:11:37,737 --> 00:11:39,762
Please! My father...

105
00:11:56,122 --> 00:11:58,283
Silence.

106
00:11:58,858 --> 00:12:00,416
Silence!

107
00:12:01,727 --> 00:12:03,786
The day's ration has been given.

108
00:12:05,932 --> 00:12:09,993
There'll be no more until tomorrow
at the appointed time.

109
00:12:10,036 --> 00:12:12,402
No!

110
00:12:16,375 --> 00:12:19,742
I know you're hungry.

111
00:12:19,779 --> 00:12:21,679
But you're alive.

112
00:12:21,714 --> 00:12:25,343
If I do as you ask and open the granaries,

113
00:12:25,384 --> 00:12:28,820
you'll be well fed today and starving tomorrow.

114
00:12:35,795 --> 00:12:37,854
Go home.

115
00:12:37,897 --> 00:12:41,924
Go home and suffer what
the Earth Mother has sent us.

116
00:12:41,968 --> 00:12:44,027
And come back tomorrow.

117
00:12:51,978 --> 00:12:53,741
Right.

118
00:13:03,990 --> 00:13:07,391
Still in one piece, then?
Thought they might have ate you.

119
00:13:07,426 --> 00:13:09,155
Too much gristle on the bone.

120
00:13:09,195 --> 00:13:11,823
Lucius, girls, I thought I told you to wait inside.

121
00:13:11,864 --> 00:13:15,425
I'll not cower when there's blood to be spilled.
Where's the honor in that?

122
00:13:15,468 --> 00:13:17,698
When you have hair on your chin
you can talk of blood.

123
00:13:17,737 --> 00:13:20,160
Vorena, I expected better.
Next time do as you're told.

124
00:13:20,239 --> 00:13:22,469
They're just hungry people.
They'd not hurt us.

125
00:13:22,508 --> 00:13:24,772
Hungry people do strange things.

126
00:13:24,810 --> 00:13:26,903
Then blessed Orbona will protect us.

127
00:13:26,946 --> 00:13:29,005
Well, run along and ask her
to send a grain ship.

128
00:13:29,048 --> 00:13:31,039
Me and Mascius have to talk.

129
00:13:32,218 --> 00:13:33,845
You too, Lucius.

130
00:13:33,886 --> 00:13:36,047
Go learn to read or something.

131
00:13:44,630 --> 00:13:48,396
- What's the tally?
- Ten days left, a quarter ration, give or take.

132
00:13:48,434 --> 00:13:50,595
- Gods below.
- It's hardly worth giving out.

133
00:13:50,636 --> 00:13:52,536
Just prolonging the misery.

134
00:13:53,739 --> 00:13:55,331
Morning.

135
00:13:55,374 --> 00:13:58,172
The bakers' guild man was round earlier.

136
00:13:58,210 --> 00:14:00,474
I told you not to speak to them.

137
00:14:00,513 --> 00:14:02,105
Nor did I.

138
00:14:02,148 --> 00:14:05,049
He spoke, I said nothing.

139
00:14:05,084 --> 00:14:07,052
They're offering 600 a sack.

140
00:14:07,086 --> 00:14:08,747
600?

141
00:14:08,788 --> 00:14:10,983
Yeah, 600 and a few dead children

142
00:14:11,023 --> 00:14:14,186
for every sack that doesn't get
to the people that need them.

143
00:14:15,928 --> 00:14:17,589
We're not in this for profit.

144
00:14:17,630 --> 00:14:19,461
Still, it's 600.

145
00:14:19,498 --> 00:14:21,625
I piss on the bakers' guild.

146
00:14:22,468 --> 00:14:24,902
- Your call.
- Yes, it is.

147
00:14:28,541 --> 00:14:30,907
Why are you wasting
valuable food on him still?

148
00:14:30,943 --> 00:14:33,036
Let the poor bastard die.

149
00:14:33,079 --> 00:14:34,478
Memmio?

150
00:14:36,248 --> 00:14:39,342
No. He reminds the other men to stay honest.

151
00:14:39,385 --> 00:14:41,285
What's to be done, then?

152
00:14:43,322 --> 00:14:46,883
Fetch my best clothes.
I'll see if his honor has any ideas.

153
00:14:51,330 --> 00:14:53,059
Hey!

154
00:14:53,666 --> 00:14:55,725
Quiet, you.

155
00:14:59,538 --> 00:15:00,766
You fucking hairy bastard.

156
00:15:04,543 --> 00:15:08,070
So far it's just the old
and the sick that are dying.

157
00:15:08,114 --> 00:15:10,412
But by next moon, our granaries will be empty.

158
00:15:10,449 --> 00:15:13,850
I understand that dogs make good eating.

159
00:15:13,886 --> 00:15:15,513
They do.

160
00:15:15,554 --> 00:15:19,149
Taste like pork if you cook 'em right.
All gone.

161
00:15:19,892 --> 00:15:23,123
I wondered why the nights were so peaceful.

162
00:15:23,162 --> 00:15:25,995
- No barking.
- This is no moment for wit.

163
00:15:26,999 --> 00:15:28,626
I wish there were something I could do.

164
00:15:28,667 --> 00:15:31,033
But the state granaries
are near as empty as yours.

165
00:15:31,070 --> 00:15:34,403
I can only give to you
by taking from someone else.

166
00:15:34,440 --> 00:15:37,432
- The military silos are untapped.
- And the army needs to eat.

167
00:15:38,010 --> 00:15:40,205
Well, then, send three legions to Africa.

168
00:15:40,246 --> 00:15:42,043
Let Lepidus feed them.

169
00:15:42,081 --> 00:15:45,676
That would supply the city
with enough grain for a month.

170
00:15:46,819 --> 00:15:48,980
Have it done.

171
00:15:49,021 --> 00:15:52,286
It's only a temporary solution,
but it's the best we can offer.

172
00:15:52,458 --> 00:15:55,359
- I'll send you what we can spare.
- Thank you.

173
00:15:56,762 --> 00:15:58,730
Pullo.

174
00:16:01,167 --> 00:16:03,567
Tell me what the people are saying.

175
00:16:03,602 --> 00:16:06,093
Tell me who they blame for this famine.

176
00:16:10,743 --> 00:16:12,677
You, they say.

177
00:16:12,711 --> 00:16:15,202
- You're the man in charge.
- Not Antony?

178
00:16:15,614 --> 00:16:17,411
They hear the newsreaders saying

179
00:16:17,449 --> 00:16:21,180
that he's holding back
the shipments and all that, but...

180
00:16:21,220 --> 00:16:23,211
well, it's Antony, innit?

181
00:16:24,023 --> 00:16:26,423
Why would he starve them?

182
00:16:26,458 --> 00:16:29,723
They've always loved him
and he's always loved to be loved.

183
00:16:29,762 --> 00:16:31,753
Whereas you...

184
00:16:32,898 --> 00:16:35,662
Well, you're you, aren't you?

185
00:16:35,701 --> 00:16:37,225
Cold and heartless?

186
00:16:38,737 --> 00:16:40,728
I'll not say that.

187
00:16:42,408 --> 00:16:45,809
But you've never been
the affectionate type now, have you?

188
00:16:47,947 --> 00:16:49,915
Thank you, Pullo.

189
00:16:51,116 --> 00:16:55,052
- I'll be hearing about the grain, then, will I?
- Agrippa will see to it.

190
00:17:01,760 --> 00:17:04,058
- Perhaps Bibulus will succeed?
- No, he won't.

191
00:17:04,096 --> 00:17:07,554
Antony's not entirely irrational.
Given enough money, why should he refuse?

192
00:17:07,600 --> 00:17:09,363
Antony's not motivated by money.

193
00:17:09,401 --> 00:17:12,063
He hopes the people will rise up
in anger and depose me.

194
00:17:13,005 --> 00:17:16,805
Either that, or he simply wishes
to provoke me into declaring war on him.

195
00:17:16,842 --> 00:17:18,366
Has he really become so foolish?

196
00:17:18,410 --> 00:17:20,935
Who knows what he's become
after all these years out there?

197
00:17:20,980 --> 00:17:23,710
Who knows what Cleopatra whispers to him?

198
00:17:23,749 --> 00:17:25,717
He was always a fool for his women.

199
00:17:25,751 --> 00:17:28,618
If he wants a war, why not give it to him?

200
00:17:28,654 --> 00:17:30,246
You heard Pullo.

201
00:17:30,289 --> 00:17:32,951
You might as well declare war
on wine and song.

202
00:17:35,094 --> 00:17:36,118
No, no, no, no.

203
00:17:36,161 --> 00:17:40,530
War on Antony is doomed
unless the people are with us.

204
00:17:40,566 --> 00:17:43,000
Send for my mother and sister.

205
00:17:43,035 --> 00:17:45,299
I shall have dinner with them this evening.

206
00:17:50,776 --> 00:17:52,744
Grandma?

207
00:17:53,612 --> 00:17:55,603
You shouldn't be here.

208
00:17:56,915 --> 00:17:59,406
It's dangerous.

209
00:17:59,451 --> 00:18:01,942
Antonia, where are you?

210
00:18:01,987 --> 00:18:04,319
She's up here with me. I'll bring her down.

211
00:18:04,356 --> 00:18:06,620
You naughty girl.

212
00:18:06,659 --> 00:18:09,992
What have I told you about going on the roof?

213
00:18:12,531 --> 00:18:15,659
I swear on Diana,
I shall have someone beat her.

214
00:18:15,701 --> 00:18:18,067
She doesn't listen to a word I say.

215
00:18:18,103 --> 00:18:21,038
She's a good girl, really.
Just like you were at that age.

216
00:18:21,073 --> 00:18:23,007
And I turned out so well?

217
00:18:23,042 --> 00:18:26,068
Your brother, on the other hand,
was as biddable as a shepherd's dog.

218
00:18:26,111 --> 00:18:27,874
No trouble at all.

219
00:18:27,913 --> 00:18:30,313
Castor, are there any letters for me today?

220
00:18:30,349 --> 00:18:32,010
No, Domina.

221
00:18:33,018 --> 00:18:34,440
Strange.

222
00:18:34,520 --> 00:18:38,388
I had the strongest feeling
that today was the day.

223
00:18:38,424 --> 00:18:41,291
Mother? There will be no letter.

224
00:18:41,327 --> 00:18:42,885
You're wrong.

225
00:18:44,196 --> 00:18:46,960
Sorry to be blunt, but...

226
00:18:47,366 --> 00:18:49,857
Well, don't you think it's time to face facts?

227
00:18:49,902 --> 00:18:51,767
Antony promised to send for me and he will.

228
00:18:51,937 --> 00:18:54,280
Even if he did, do you think
Octavian would let you go?

229
00:18:54,340 --> 00:18:56,171
I don't give a fig.

230
00:18:57,076 --> 00:19:00,568
Truly, is he worth torturing yourself like this?

231
00:19:01,947 --> 00:19:06,179
Domina? Octavian Caesar summons you both
for dinner this evening.

232
00:19:07,619 --> 00:19:09,951
What does he want now, I wonder?

233
00:19:09,988 --> 00:19:12,013
Nothing to our benefit.

234
00:19:18,397 --> 00:19:20,365
Family and friends.

235
00:19:21,300 --> 00:19:23,461
Nothing better.

236
00:19:29,475 --> 00:19:31,909
Octavia, I have a favor to ask of you.

237
00:19:34,546 --> 00:19:37,777
You are aware of the grain shortage,
I suppose?

238
00:19:37,816 --> 00:19:40,910
You know that the people are dying
in the streets for want of bread?

239
00:19:42,554 --> 00:19:44,249
And you want me to feed them?

240
00:19:45,023 --> 00:19:47,218
In a manner of speaking.

241
00:19:47,259 --> 00:19:49,523
Your husband has plenty of grain in Egypt.

242
00:19:49,561 --> 00:19:52,553
But he is playing politics with it, holding it back.

243
00:19:52,598 --> 00:19:56,193
If you were to go and talk to him...

244
00:19:57,703 --> 00:20:01,036
I? Go to Egypt?

245
00:20:01,073 --> 00:20:04,065
The soft voice of a loving wife

246
00:20:04,109 --> 00:20:06,634
may succeed where all else has failed.

247
00:20:06,678 --> 00:20:07,906
You are joking?

248
00:20:07,946 --> 00:20:11,245
I cannot remember the last time I made a joke.

249
00:20:11,283 --> 00:20:13,012
Last market day.

250
00:20:13,051 --> 00:20:16,077
You said something about fishes
which made me laugh quite distinctly.

251
00:20:16,121 --> 00:20:18,282
I was speaking figuratively.

252
00:20:21,693 --> 00:20:27,325
If you are serious, it is not I should go,
but Mother. She's his real wife.

253
00:20:30,235 --> 00:20:32,567
I thought you might go together.

254
00:20:32,604 --> 00:20:35,630
Present Antony with both
reality and appearance.

255
00:20:37,943 --> 00:20:40,776
That's all very well, but...

256
00:20:40,813 --> 00:20:44,340
I have no desire to take a long sea voyage.

257
00:20:44,383 --> 00:20:47,079
- Do you?
- No.

258
00:20:47,119 --> 00:20:48,814
Besides, we're not hungry.

259
00:20:48,854 --> 00:20:50,845
And we need no grain.

260
00:20:52,090 --> 00:20:54,820
So what's in it for us?

261
00:20:54,860 --> 00:20:59,229
How will you pay us for our trouble?

262
00:20:59,264 --> 00:21:01,528
What do you want?

263
00:21:05,771 --> 00:21:08,433
Pompeii's become vulgar.

264
00:21:08,474 --> 00:21:11,238
I'd like a villa in Capri.

265
00:21:11,276 --> 00:21:13,073
That's fine.

266
00:21:13,111 --> 00:21:15,978
What about you, Octavia?
Do you want a villa?

267
00:21:18,484 --> 00:21:20,247
I don't know.

268
00:21:20,285 --> 00:21:21,980
A villa would be nice.

269
00:21:22,688 --> 00:21:24,883
Some gladiators would be fun as well.

270
00:21:24,923 --> 00:21:27,949
Why not take cash and decide later?

271
00:21:27,993 --> 00:21:31,394
- Good idea. Cash.
- As you wish.

272
00:21:31,964 --> 00:21:35,730
Maecenas, have the newsreader announce
they are leaving as soon as possible.

273
00:22:48,907 --> 00:22:50,397
I like birds.

274
00:22:54,746 --> 00:22:57,909
I don't like eggs.
There is something quite sordid about eggs.

275
00:22:58,650 --> 00:23:02,450
We shan't serve them anymore.
Unless you object, of course.

276
00:23:09,528 --> 00:23:11,894
Why are you sending
Atia and Octavia to Egypt?

277
00:23:13,899 --> 00:23:17,760
- You heard why.
- Well, yes, but that can't be the real reason.

278
00:23:17,836 --> 00:23:20,361
You know Antony will refuse what they ask.

279
00:23:20,405 --> 00:23:21,929
It's very likely.

280
00:23:26,011 --> 00:23:27,478
What?

281
00:23:27,512 --> 00:23:31,710
You calculate... that if Antony
turns Octavia away,

282
00:23:31,750 --> 00:23:35,743
the people will feel that he has
publicly humiliated his darling wife,

283
00:23:35,787 --> 00:23:38,415
that Queen Cleopatra has bewitched him,

284
00:23:38,457 --> 00:23:40,186
and they will all turn against him.

285
00:23:41,226 --> 00:23:43,126
Something like that.

286
00:23:44,162 --> 00:23:46,357
But on the other hand,

287
00:23:46,398 --> 00:23:49,765
if Antony still loves Atia
and yields to her pleading,

288
00:23:49,801 --> 00:23:53,100
then... so much the better.

289
00:23:53,271 --> 00:23:55,262
You'll have your grain.

290
00:23:56,708 --> 00:23:58,573
Clever boy.

291
00:23:58,610 --> 00:24:00,908
Good night, my dear.

292
00:24:26,705 --> 00:24:28,570
I wish you'd stop that.

293
00:24:28,607 --> 00:24:31,075
We'll get there no faster.

294
00:24:32,644 --> 00:24:36,307
Have I changed at all, do you think,
since he last saw me?

295
00:24:38,050 --> 00:24:40,814
No. You're just exactly as you were.

296
00:24:41,653 --> 00:24:44,645
He'll fall into your arms in a delirium of love.

297
00:24:44,690 --> 00:24:46,658
Do you mean that?

298
00:24:46,692 --> 00:24:47,886
No.

299
00:24:49,394 --> 00:24:53,558
You've become very mean, you know.
Mean and bitter.

300
00:24:53,732 --> 00:24:56,292
You've become girlish and sentimental.

301
00:24:57,636 --> 00:24:59,627
It's disgusting, frankly.

302
00:25:18,990 --> 00:25:22,289
No points. No points.

303
00:25:22,327 --> 00:25:24,557
I wasn't ready.

304
00:25:28,300 --> 00:25:29,699
Ten points to me.

305
00:25:29,735 --> 00:25:31,794
Well done, Majesty. Well done.

306
00:25:31,837 --> 00:25:33,361
- Ready?
- No, wait!

307
00:25:33,405 --> 00:25:35,839
I beg thee! Wait!

308
00:25:37,509 --> 00:25:40,273
Useless old woman. Go away.

309
00:25:51,590 --> 00:25:55,026
Vorenus, play with me.

310
00:25:59,097 --> 00:26:01,964
Throw it properly.

311
00:26:06,838 --> 00:26:08,465
Come on, then.

312
00:26:17,182 --> 00:26:18,911
Good catch.

313
00:26:18,950 --> 00:26:21,248
Tell me more about my father.

314
00:26:21,286 --> 00:26:23,083
I told you all that I know.

315
00:26:23,121 --> 00:26:26,989
You've told me only what every fool knows.

316
00:26:27,025 --> 00:26:31,485
He was a great soldier,
the people loved him, blah blah blah.

317
00:26:32,264 --> 00:26:35,324
Tell me what he was like as a man.

318
00:26:36,768 --> 00:26:39,168
Well, he was...

319
00:26:39,204 --> 00:26:41,399
he was a good man.

320
00:26:41,439 --> 00:26:44,203
He was a good man to have as a friend.

321
00:26:44,242 --> 00:26:46,176
You wouldn't want him as an enemy.

322
00:26:46,211 --> 00:26:49,203
He had a nasty temper when he was roused.

323
00:26:49,247 --> 00:26:51,772
When the battle was going hard
and men were faltering,

324
00:26:51,950 --> 00:26:55,442
that's when you'd want to see
your father at your side.

325
00:26:56,354 --> 00:26:58,345
Bravest man I've ever known.

326
00:27:01,293 --> 00:27:03,727
More.

327
00:27:03,762 --> 00:27:05,354
Fine horseman.

328
00:27:05,397 --> 00:27:08,662
Bad gambler, though he'd never admit it.

329
00:27:08,700 --> 00:27:10,565
He liked the women.

330
00:27:10,602 --> 00:27:12,570
He liked to eat.

331
00:27:12,604 --> 00:27:15,664
He'd eat the whole table if you'd let him.

332
00:27:15,707 --> 00:27:17,106
Really?

333
00:27:17,142 --> 00:27:21,010
I've always heard he was very...
abstemious in his diet.

334
00:27:21,046 --> 00:27:24,311
Yeah, well, that would be right.

335
00:27:24,349 --> 00:27:27,318
There's others knew him far better than I did.

336
00:27:31,523 --> 00:27:34,583
- Where are they?
- What's wrong?

337
00:27:40,298 --> 00:27:42,232
What do you mean, here?

338
00:27:42,267 --> 00:27:44,497
Their ship docked an hour ago.

339
00:27:44,536 --> 00:27:46,800
They're on their way to the palace now.

340
00:27:46,838 --> 00:27:48,999
And they request an immediate
audience with you!

341
00:27:49,040 --> 00:27:50,473
How delicious.

342
00:27:50,508 --> 00:27:52,942
Wife and lover come together to see you.

343
00:27:53,111 --> 00:27:55,511
Hush, woman.

344
00:27:56,748 --> 00:27:59,308
- What do they want?
- I don't know.

345
00:28:00,585 --> 00:28:02,746
What shall I tell them? They will be here.

346
00:28:02,787 --> 00:28:05,415
Just, give... give...

347
00:28:05,457 --> 00:28:07,288
give me time to think.

348
00:28:08,326 --> 00:28:10,055
No.

349
00:28:11,263 --> 00:28:14,721
They would not have come of their own accord.

350
00:28:15,967 --> 00:28:18,435
Octavian must have sent them here.

351
00:28:18,470 --> 00:28:20,097
Sent them to do what?

352
00:28:20,138 --> 00:28:23,164
Why else send my wife

353
00:28:23,208 --> 00:28:26,575
except to effect some kind of...

354
00:28:26,611 --> 00:28:28,000
reconciliation.

355
00:28:28,079 --> 00:28:31,048
- Well, you must refuse her.
- Obviously, yes.

356
00:28:32,017 --> 00:28:34,451
But that...

357
00:28:34,486 --> 00:28:38,752
that is exactly what he wants.

358
00:28:38,790 --> 00:28:41,224
He is forcing me to choose publicly

359
00:28:41,259 --> 00:28:45,120
between her and... and you.

360
00:28:45,196 --> 00:28:47,664
And when I turn her away, which I will,

361
00:28:49,100 --> 00:28:51,159
he will have his premise for war.

362
00:28:51,336 --> 00:28:53,361
Then why so glum?

363
00:28:54,606 --> 00:28:57,473
You have what you wanted.
A war that he will start,

364
00:28:57,509 --> 00:28:59,409
a war that you did not seek.

365
00:28:59,444 --> 00:29:02,106
And still...

366
00:29:02,147 --> 00:29:04,479
I do not like it.

367
00:29:04,516 --> 00:29:06,381
He is...

368
00:29:06,418 --> 00:29:09,080
he is striking

369
00:29:09,120 --> 00:29:11,452
at my support amongst the people.

370
00:29:11,489 --> 00:29:15,016
He... he will think he has outmaneuvered me.

371
00:29:15,060 --> 00:29:18,461
What matter?
As long as you win the war.

372
00:29:19,965 --> 00:29:21,990
Yes.

373
00:29:22,033 --> 00:29:24,593
- I suppose so.
- In any case...

374
00:29:26,004 --> 00:29:29,371
we must be gracious hosts, ne?

375
00:29:29,407 --> 00:29:31,637
We shall throw a lovely party for them.

376
00:29:31,676 --> 00:29:35,510
Charmian, send for the kitchen chamberlain.

377
00:29:35,547 --> 00:29:37,208
No, no, no. No!

378
00:29:37,248 --> 00:29:40,479
No? We must be hospitable.

379
00:29:45,123 --> 00:29:47,455
You'd love that, wouldn't you?

380
00:29:50,929 --> 00:29:53,830
Humiliating Atia.

381
00:29:55,166 --> 00:29:59,728
Watching her squirm as you play the queen.

382
00:30:01,039 --> 00:30:03,166
Play the queen?

383
00:30:03,208 --> 00:30:04,800
I am a queen.

384
00:30:05,610 --> 00:30:10,479
- You know what I mean.
- No. No, I don't.

385
00:30:11,182 --> 00:30:16,245
You... you just want
to flaunt our love in front of her.

386
00:30:16,287 --> 00:30:20,155
Why not? We love each other, don't we?

387
00:30:22,060 --> 00:30:23,891
And you no longer love her.

388
00:30:23,928 --> 00:30:26,226
Why should she not know it?

389
00:30:32,937 --> 00:30:35,098
It's an act of kindness.

390
00:30:35,140 --> 00:30:37,131
Stop her pining for you.

391
00:30:39,944 --> 00:30:44,040
I'm not wrong, am I?
You do no longer love her.

392
00:30:44,082 --> 00:30:46,277
Of course I no longer love her.

393
00:30:48,553 --> 00:30:51,784
And you know I no longer love her.

394
00:30:53,758 --> 00:30:57,250
But neither do I think
she deserves public humiliation.

395
00:30:58,563 --> 00:31:01,760
That is the whole point.

396
00:31:01,800 --> 00:31:05,236
That is why they're here, to be humiliated.

397
00:31:07,539 --> 00:31:10,599
No, I don't think she knows that.

398
00:31:10,642 --> 00:31:12,633
Else she would not be here.

399
00:31:14,179 --> 00:31:18,343
I think her fucking son

400
00:31:18,383 --> 00:31:20,874
has manipulated her into it.

401
00:31:24,322 --> 00:31:26,552
Let's kill them, then.

402
00:31:30,962 --> 00:31:33,123
What? What did you say?

403
00:31:34,632 --> 00:31:37,430
Atia will not be humiliated...

404
00:31:37,469 --> 00:31:39,528
because Atia will be dead.

405
00:31:44,175 --> 00:31:48,737
Octavian will know that you're not a man
to be outmaneuvered.

406
00:31:48,780 --> 00:31:50,771
It's perfect.

407
00:31:55,787 --> 00:31:59,314
No. My people will despise me as a wife-killer.

408
00:32:00,692 --> 00:32:02,922
Well, their ship sank on the way home.

409
00:32:02,961 --> 00:32:04,656
- No.
- It happens all the time.

410
00:32:04,696 --> 00:32:06,857
No. I mean it. No!

411
00:32:06,898 --> 00:32:10,857
I see. Well, either you are a coward...

412
00:32:12,804 --> 00:32:14,931
or you still have feelings for her.

413
00:32:15,874 --> 00:32:17,171
Which is it?

414
00:32:18,977 --> 00:32:21,207
Which is it?

415
00:32:21,246 --> 00:32:23,544
Why don't you shut your fucking mouth?

416
00:32:34,459 --> 00:32:35,619
Oh, you...

417
00:33:12,197 --> 00:33:14,495
Gods, what a ghastly place.

418
00:33:15,733 --> 00:33:17,826
Big, though.

419
00:33:17,869 --> 00:33:20,064
It's a sure sign of vulgarity.

420
00:33:21,739 --> 00:33:24,173
Ptolemies were originally goatherds,
you know?

421
00:33:32,016 --> 00:33:33,779
Why are the doors not open?

422
00:33:45,263 --> 00:33:46,423
Enough!

423
00:33:46,931 --> 00:33:48,421
No!

424
00:33:55,740 --> 00:33:59,141
This is outrageous.

425
00:33:59,177 --> 00:34:01,270
The rudeness.

426
00:34:01,312 --> 00:34:03,712
It just goes to show... vulgar.

427
00:34:03,748 --> 00:34:05,545
Royalty, indeed.

428
00:34:05,583 --> 00:34:07,551
This heat's unbearable.

429
00:34:07,585 --> 00:34:10,179
I think I'm going to faint.

430
00:34:10,221 --> 00:34:12,416
You would think they would bring us water.

431
00:34:12,457 --> 00:34:14,652
- Can't we go back to the ship?
- Absolutely not.

432
00:34:14,692 --> 00:34:17,120
We're staying here
until these wretched people...

433
00:34:17,195 --> 00:34:20,062
Oh, and about bloody time.

434
00:34:21,566 --> 00:34:22,624
Hello.

435
00:34:22,667 --> 00:34:25,363
Jocasta. Is it you?

436
00:34:25,403 --> 00:34:27,166
Of course it's me. Who else would I be?

437
00:34:27,205 --> 00:34:28,433
What's happened to you?

438
00:34:28,473 --> 00:34:32,307
This? Her Majesty doesn't like
the Roman style on her women.

439
00:34:32,343 --> 00:34:35,904
Quite irrational about the subject if you ask me.

440
00:34:35,947 --> 00:34:39,439
But anything for a quiet life.
I rather like it now.

441
00:34:39,484 --> 00:34:41,840
What are you doing here?
Have you come for Crocodile Day?

442
00:34:41,919 --> 00:34:45,184
That's what I call it, anyway.
I can't get my mouth round their lingo.

443
00:34:45,223 --> 00:34:47,157
She will shriek.

444
00:34:47,191 --> 00:34:50,422
But I just pretend I'm a little mad,
and she leaves off.

445
00:34:50,461 --> 00:34:53,157
Why is the door kept shut?
Why is there no one here to greet us?

446
00:34:53,331 --> 00:34:56,160
Oh, I'm sure there'll be
someone along in a while.

447
00:34:56,200 --> 00:35:00,796
Things move... ever so slow around here.
It's the heat.

448
00:35:00,838 --> 00:35:04,638
Listen, why don't you go inside
and tell Antony that we're waiting to see him?

449
00:35:04,676 --> 00:35:06,940
Obviously, he's not been
informed that we're here.

450
00:35:06,978 --> 00:35:08,809
I couldn't do that.

451
00:35:08,846 --> 00:35:11,906
No one's allowed to speak
to Antony without she says so.

452
00:35:11,949 --> 00:35:13,541
Except my dear little Posca.

453
00:35:13,584 --> 00:35:15,848
And Lucius Vorenus, of course.

454
00:35:15,887 --> 00:35:17,650
I love your hair like that.

455
00:35:17,689 --> 00:35:19,987
Is that how people are wearing it now?

456
00:35:20,024 --> 00:35:22,458
Thank Juno. Posca.

457
00:35:22,493 --> 00:35:25,587
- What in heaven's name is...
- Jocasta, what are you doing?

458
00:35:25,630 --> 00:35:27,520
- I was only...
- Quiet, woman!

459
00:35:27,598 --> 00:35:28,997
Posca, where's Antony?

460
00:35:29,033 --> 00:35:32,196
Yes, yes! A great pleasure.

461
00:35:32,236 --> 00:35:34,033
Indeed, yes. Come along.

462
00:35:36,708 --> 00:35:39,643
Posca? Posca?

463
00:35:41,145 --> 00:35:42,806
Thank you.

464
00:35:46,117 --> 00:35:49,484
They've all gone insane, obviously.

465
00:36:37,335 --> 00:36:39,326
So hot.

466
00:36:52,917 --> 00:36:54,908
It's for the best, you know.

467
00:36:56,087 --> 00:36:59,215
This palace life is no good for you.

468
00:37:00,224 --> 00:37:02,317
You need action.

469
00:37:02,360 --> 00:37:04,624
Yeah.

470
00:37:04,662 --> 00:37:07,597
You'll be much more happy
when the war begins.

471
00:37:10,868 --> 00:37:13,268
- Vorenus.
- Sir?

472
00:37:16,107 --> 00:37:18,769
I have a delicate mission for you.

473
00:37:30,955 --> 00:37:34,447
I'm glad to see you
haven't gone native, at least.

474
00:37:34,492 --> 00:37:36,824
Perhaps you can talk some sense.

475
00:37:36,861 --> 00:37:38,590
What is the matter with these people?

476
00:37:38,629 --> 00:37:41,189
Why hasn't Antony been told of our arrival?

477
00:37:42,767 --> 00:37:46,168
I've been ordered by Triumvir Mark Antony
to escort you both back to your ship,

478
00:37:46,204 --> 00:37:50,140
and to make sure that you leave Alexandria
as soon as the wind allows.

479
00:37:58,182 --> 00:37:59,979
Without seeing him?

480
00:38:01,853 --> 00:38:04,822
He turns away the mother of his child?

481
00:38:06,190 --> 00:38:08,317
That's correct.

482
00:38:08,359 --> 00:38:12,455
It was she who ordered you to do this,
wasn't it?

483
00:38:12,497 --> 00:38:14,226
Antony wouldn't act so low.

484
00:38:14,265 --> 00:38:16,790
I take orders only from Mark Antony, madam.

485
00:38:24,108 --> 00:38:25,973
No, we're not going.

486
00:38:26,010 --> 00:38:27,773
- Mother, I...
- Madam...

487
00:38:27,812 --> 00:38:30,280
We are not going.

488
00:38:30,314 --> 00:38:32,475
I am not moving from this spot

489
00:38:32,517 --> 00:38:35,640
unless Antony comes down
himself and tells me to go.

490
00:38:35,720 --> 00:38:38,188
If you will not go willingly,
I have been given orders

491
00:38:38,222 --> 00:38:40,986
to use whatever force
necessary to remove you.

492
00:38:41,025 --> 00:38:42,993
You would manhandle the women of the Julii?

493
00:38:43,027 --> 00:38:45,757
No, but these men here...

494
00:38:46,964 --> 00:38:48,261
they have no such scruples.

495
00:38:57,642 --> 00:38:58,836
- Antony!
- Madam.

496
00:38:58,876 --> 00:39:00,173
Come down, you bastard!

497
00:39:00,211 --> 00:39:01,906
Madam, please!

498
00:39:28,806 --> 00:39:32,765
You tell my husband that he's cowardly scum.

499
00:39:33,911 --> 00:39:35,572
Tell him that.

500
00:39:58,803 --> 00:40:01,670
You realize, of course,
we'll have to leave all our money behind.

501
00:40:01,706 --> 00:40:03,537
- I don't care!
- We're penniless.

502
00:40:03,574 --> 00:40:07,806
I'm scared. I want to go home. Please, hurry.

503
00:40:09,547 --> 00:40:11,674
- Going somewhere?
- No.

504
00:40:11,716 --> 00:40:13,081
No. What makes you think that?

505
00:40:15,886 --> 00:40:17,717
Please, Vorenus.

506
00:40:17,755 --> 00:40:20,155
Don't tell. Please don't tell.

507
00:40:20,191 --> 00:40:21,818
Have mercy on us.

508
00:40:21,859 --> 00:40:24,953
They'll kill us.
They'll throw us to the crocodiles.

509
00:40:24,996 --> 00:40:27,260
My wife is overwrought.

510
00:40:27,298 --> 00:40:30,597
We were merely going to take
a stroll along the harbor

511
00:40:30,635 --> 00:40:32,466
to look at the ships.

512
00:40:34,372 --> 00:40:37,671
Then you must hurry.

513
00:40:37,708 --> 00:40:40,541
The wind is changing.
The ships look best when the sails are set.

514
00:40:41,846 --> 00:40:43,905
Come with us.

515
00:40:46,384 --> 00:40:48,944
- No.
- War is sure to come now.

516
00:40:48,986 --> 00:40:51,580
This is no place for decent Romans.

517
00:40:51,756 --> 00:40:54,020
True, but I have responsibilities here.

518
00:40:54,058 --> 00:40:55,787
Now is the time.

519
00:41:00,464 --> 00:41:03,956
If you happen to see Titus Pullo,

520
00:41:04,001 --> 00:41:06,026
ask him to kiss my children for me.

521
00:41:07,004 --> 00:41:08,164
I will do that.

522
00:41:15,746 --> 00:41:17,714
Thank you.

523
00:41:51,649 --> 00:41:53,310
Hello again.

524
00:41:55,786 --> 00:41:57,344
Sorry to trouble you.

525
00:41:57,388 --> 00:42:00,414
Would you mind awfully if we hide here

526
00:42:00,458 --> 00:42:03,086
until this boat is at sea?

527
00:42:08,733 --> 00:42:11,133
I've told you everything I remember.

528
00:42:11,168 --> 00:42:12,897
There must be more than that.

529
00:42:12,937 --> 00:42:15,064
Look to yourself.

530
00:42:15,106 --> 00:42:17,040
You are what remains of him.

531
00:42:18,542 --> 00:42:20,601
Vorenus.

532
00:42:23,514 --> 00:42:25,141
Well?

533
00:42:26,751 --> 00:42:29,049
They're gone.

534
00:42:29,086 --> 00:42:30,610
Good.

535
00:42:31,789 --> 00:42:33,723
Good.

536
00:42:35,092 --> 00:42:37,890
And how was... Atia?

537
00:42:37,928 --> 00:42:41,091
I suppose she took it with her usual poise?

538
00:42:42,032 --> 00:42:44,626
- No.
- No?

539
00:42:46,837 --> 00:42:49,897
Well. Had to be done.

540
00:42:52,510 --> 00:42:56,139
Where's Posca?
I sent for him but he did not come.

541
00:42:56,180 --> 00:42:58,444
I don't know, sir.
Do you wish me to go and look for him?

542
00:42:58,482 --> 00:43:00,177
Oh, no, no.

543
00:43:00,217 --> 00:43:02,947
It's all right.

544
00:43:02,987 --> 00:43:04,955
I'm sure he'll turn up.

545
00:43:06,957 --> 00:43:09,687
Sir, your wife instructed me
to tell you something.

546
00:43:11,996 --> 00:43:15,989
She instructed me to tell you
that you are cowardly scum.

547
00:43:17,668 --> 00:43:20,762
She did, did she?

548
00:43:22,373 --> 00:43:25,865
And... and what's your opinion of that?

549
00:43:25,910 --> 00:43:28,344
It's not my place to have an opinion, sir.

550
00:43:28,379 --> 00:43:30,472
Nah. Tell me anyway.

551
00:43:30,514 --> 00:43:32,982
Is that an order?

552
00:43:33,017 --> 00:43:35,042
Yes. That's an order.

553
00:43:38,989 --> 00:43:41,355
You're no coward.

554
00:43:42,993 --> 00:43:45,689
But you do have a strong disease in your soul.

555
00:43:47,631 --> 00:43:51,397
A disease that will eat away at you...

556
00:43:51,569 --> 00:43:53,560
until you die.

557
00:43:56,473 --> 00:43:58,464
Really?

558
00:44:02,646 --> 00:44:04,307
And what is this disease?

559
00:44:05,683 --> 00:44:08,208
I don't know. I'm not a doctor.

560
00:44:08,252 --> 00:44:09,913
No.

561
00:44:09,954 --> 00:44:12,514
No, you're not.

562
00:44:12,556 --> 00:44:16,993
So how can you be so sure
of your diagnosis, then?

563
00:44:18,229 --> 00:44:20,629
I recognize your symptoms.

564
00:44:22,733 --> 00:44:25,463
I have the same sickness.

565
00:44:46,523 --> 00:44:48,684
Long one.

566
00:45:10,014 --> 00:45:12,107
Hello, Mother.

567
00:45:12,149 --> 00:45:15,243
And Posca. What a pleasant surprise.

568
00:45:15,886 --> 00:45:18,548
I gather Antony was not amenable
to persuasion.

569
00:45:20,658 --> 00:45:22,956
No, he was not.

570
00:45:22,993 --> 00:45:26,326
But you knew that, didn't you?

571
00:45:28,999 --> 00:45:31,399
You wanted a villa in Capri.

572
00:45:31,435 --> 00:45:33,835
Now you may have one.

573
00:45:36,073 --> 00:45:37,904
Is Octavia well?

574
00:45:41,612 --> 00:45:44,240
Posca has something here

575
00:45:44,281 --> 00:45:46,340
that will help you destroy Antony.

576
00:45:48,018 --> 00:45:51,351
- Mother, I am hoping...
- Crush Antony and his queen.

577
00:45:54,325 --> 00:45:56,691
And you can keep your damn villa.

578
00:46:03,400 --> 00:46:05,698
You have something for me, Posca?

579
00:46:05,736 --> 00:46:09,695
It is the last will and testament

580
00:46:09,740 --> 00:46:11,935
of Antony and Cleopatra.

581
00:46:13,510 --> 00:46:16,536
To be opened and read only
on the occasion of their death.

582
00:46:16,580 --> 00:46:18,673
It is a despicable document.

583
00:46:18,716 --> 00:46:21,844
Taken together with
his repudiation of your sister,

584
00:46:21,885 --> 00:46:26,015
the Roman people would think
a war against Antony not only inevitable,

585
00:46:26,056 --> 00:46:29,116
but eminently desirable.

586
00:46:29,159 --> 00:46:31,889
- Is it genuine?
- It is genuine.

587
00:46:34,398 --> 00:46:36,025
You are a good and loyal friend, Posca.

588
00:46:50,781 --> 00:46:53,341
This one's cooked himself for dinner.

589
00:46:53,384 --> 00:46:55,409
He asks to be buried in Alexandria.

590
00:46:55,452 --> 00:46:58,478
He declares Cleopatra his wife
and that they are living gods.

591
00:46:58,522 --> 00:47:01,047
She is Isis and he, Osiris.

592
00:47:01,091 --> 00:47:04,322
- It's perfect.
- Wait, wait. It's better.

593
00:47:04,361 --> 00:47:07,853
He leaves to his children by Cleopatra
all the eastern provinces.

594
00:47:07,898 --> 00:47:11,197
And her son by Caesar
is to be given Rome and the west.

595
00:47:13,203 --> 00:47:17,196
Having rejected his loving wife Octavia,

596
00:47:17,241 --> 00:47:19,675
Mark Antony has coupled himself

597
00:47:19,710 --> 00:47:22,838
to the sorceress Cleopatra,

598
00:47:22,880 --> 00:47:25,576
promising her dominion of all Rome!

599
00:47:27,017 --> 00:47:30,350
He worships dogs and reptiles.

600
00:47:30,387 --> 00:47:32,787
He blackens his eyes with soot

601
00:47:32,823 --> 00:47:34,680
like a prostitute.

602
00:47:34,758 --> 00:47:37,852
He dances and plays the cymbals

603
00:47:37,895 --> 00:47:40,295
in vile Nilotic rites.

604
00:47:41,899 --> 00:47:45,733
I know how unhappy you are
and I cannot blame you.

605
00:47:45,769 --> 00:47:47,498
For who would not weep when he hears

606
00:47:47,538 --> 00:47:52,168
that the great Mark Antony
pays homage to foreign gods?

607
00:47:52,342 --> 00:47:55,160
That he has abandoned his wife,

608
00:47:55,212 --> 00:47:58,079
his child and his country?

609
00:47:58,115 --> 00:48:02,017
I am asked if he is gone mad,
if he is bewitched.

610
00:48:02,052 --> 00:48:04,384
I have no explanation.

611
00:48:04,421 --> 00:48:08,221
We may weep for him,
but then we must do our duty,

612
00:48:08,258 --> 00:48:12,319
for he is no longer a Roman, but an Egyptian.

613
00:48:12,362 --> 00:48:15,229
And what is left for us to do but fight him?

614
00:48:15,265 --> 00:48:18,029
Fight him and destroy him!

615
00:48:30,414 --> 00:48:33,008
Pullo. My old friend, it's good to see you.

616
00:48:33,050 --> 00:48:36,178
- Sir.
- Come, sit down.

617
00:48:46,296 --> 00:48:50,494
Posca tells me our friend Vorenus
stands by Antony even now.

618
00:48:51,335 --> 00:48:52,700
Loyal man, Vorenus.

619
00:48:52,736 --> 00:48:55,296
He sends you his best regards,

620
00:48:55,339 --> 00:48:58,103
asked that you kiss his children for him.

621
00:48:58,876 --> 00:49:03,472
- He's all right, is he?
- You know him. Iron as ever.

622
00:49:04,715 --> 00:49:07,513
- You and he are still friends, then?
- Yes.

623
00:49:08,886 --> 00:49:13,050
Very soon I will have to go east
to end this thing with Antony.

624
00:49:13,090 --> 00:49:14,489
I want you to come with me.

625
00:49:14,525 --> 00:49:16,280
- Why?
- You are close to Vorenus.

626
00:49:16,360 --> 00:49:20,023
He is close to Antony.
It may be you can act as a mediator.

627
00:49:20,063 --> 00:49:23,294
Maybe we can save unnecessary bloodshed.

628
00:49:23,333 --> 00:49:27,064
Not to argue with you,
but it doesn't seem likely.

629
00:49:27,871 --> 00:49:31,068
There are some will have to die, of course.
Antony cannot be saved.

630
00:49:31,108 --> 00:49:34,202
- The boy Caesarion will have to go, obviously.
- Caesarion?

631
00:49:34,244 --> 00:49:37,941
They have named him putative king of Rome,
Pullo.

632
00:49:37,981 --> 00:49:40,006
He will have to die but...

633
00:49:40,050 --> 00:49:42,780
perhaps Cleopatra and her children
by Antony may be saved.

634
00:49:42,819 --> 00:49:45,413
- Preserve some stability.
- Yes.

635
00:49:45,455 --> 00:49:47,548
I see.

636
00:49:47,591 --> 00:49:50,890
I do not want to order you to come, Pullo,
but I will if I have to.

637
00:49:50,928 --> 00:49:54,125
No. No problem.

638
00:49:54,865 --> 00:49:56,924
- I'll come.
- Good.

639
00:50:03,874 --> 00:50:05,865
It will be like old times.

640
00:50:08,011 --> 00:50:09,444
An adventure together.

641
00:50:14,117 --> 00:50:17,450
So, Antony more or less
forced Octavian into war.

642
00:50:17,487 --> 00:50:20,718
Else the east would be lost to the gyppos.
We wouldn't want that, now would we?

643
00:50:20,757 --> 00:50:24,090
Worshipping a bunch of dogs
and cats and what have you.

644
00:50:25,028 --> 00:50:29,397
Any road, the thing is,
Octavian's ordered me to go along with him.

645
00:50:29,433 --> 00:50:32,800
So that's what I'll be doing.
Going along with him.

646
00:50:32,836 --> 00:50:36,067
- Can I come with you?
- No. Sorry.

647
00:50:36,106 --> 00:50:38,904
You stay here with me. We'll be fine.

648
00:50:38,942 --> 00:50:40,466
You'll hardly notice I'm gone.

649
00:50:40,510 --> 00:50:42,978
And the good news is,

650
00:50:43,013 --> 00:50:45,573
I'm more than likely to see your father.

651
00:50:49,686 --> 00:50:53,452
He sent word that
I should give you all a kiss from him.

652
00:51:02,266 --> 00:51:04,666
If I see him, can I give him a kiss
from you in return?

653
00:51:04,701 --> 00:51:07,727
No. He killed our mother.

654
00:51:09,606 --> 00:51:11,369
It's true, isn't it?

655
00:51:16,346 --> 00:51:18,337
You're a hard one, you.

656
00:51:18,382 --> 00:51:19,815
My father made me so.

657
00:51:21,652 --> 00:51:23,017
I hear you.

658
00:51:42,472 --> 00:51:45,873
While I'm away,
there'll be no trouble between you.

659
00:51:45,909 --> 00:51:49,436
No skimming from the grain ration,
no stealing of women,

660
00:51:49,479 --> 00:51:53,313
nor any extortion, robbery, or arson...

661
00:51:53,483 --> 00:51:56,640
unless under direct license by Mascius.

662
00:51:56,720 --> 00:51:58,415
Anybody steps out of line,

663
00:51:58,455 --> 00:52:00,923
they'll be sharing their dinner with Memmio.

664
00:52:13,003 --> 00:52:15,471
Don't forget your vinegar flask.

665
00:52:15,505 --> 00:52:17,336
Right.

666
00:52:18,709 --> 00:52:21,974
Give us a smile.
Won't be gone forever.

667
00:52:23,613 --> 00:52:26,912
If you really loved me,
you'd take me with you.

668
00:52:28,318 --> 00:52:31,219
It's a war, not a shopping trip.

669
00:52:32,122 --> 00:52:35,023
- I can take care of myself.
- I know you can.

670
00:52:35,058 --> 00:52:37,686
Which is why I'm not worried
about leaving you here.

671
00:52:37,728 --> 00:52:40,891
- Where are you going now?
- Vinegar.

672
00:53:19,503 --> 00:53:21,368
Memmio?

673
00:54:38,915 --> 00:54:42,578
This is not happening. This isn't happening.

674
00:54:44,221 --> 00:54:46,519
What have I done?

675
00:54:46,556 --> 00:54:48,683
Why are you punishing me like this?

676
00:54:48,725 --> 00:54:52,684
Oh, you selfish bastard. It's me who's dying.

677
00:54:52,863 --> 00:54:56,856
It's not you who's being punished, it's me.

678
00:54:57,534 --> 00:54:59,525
I'm gonna die.

679
00:55:00,604 --> 00:55:03,232
It is as... as it should be.

680
00:55:03,273 --> 00:55:07,607
What have you ever done?
You're a good woman.

681
00:55:08,912 --> 00:55:11,437
Don't get sentimental on me now.

682
00:55:11,481 --> 00:55:13,312
One thing I'm not is a good woman.

683
00:55:13,350 --> 00:55:15,409
You've been good to me.

684
00:55:15,452 --> 00:55:18,683
No, I haven't.

685
00:55:18,722 --> 00:55:20,587
Eirene.

686
00:55:21,858 --> 00:55:26,022
Eirene was a good woman.
Not a she-wolf like me.

687
00:55:27,564 --> 00:55:30,362
- She had her moments.
- She was gonna give you a child.

688
00:55:35,005 --> 00:55:37,269
Fate had a different plan.

689
00:55:39,309 --> 00:55:41,709
We're happy enough, you and me.

690
00:55:43,413 --> 00:55:45,711
I'm sorry.

691
00:55:50,353 --> 00:55:53,584
I can't go to the afterlife with lies in my heart.

692
00:55:53,757 --> 00:55:56,225
Nemesis won't let me rest.

693
00:55:59,229 --> 00:56:01,220
What lies?

694
00:56:02,432 --> 00:56:04,366
What's Nemesis want with you?

695
00:56:05,368 --> 00:56:07,302
Send these people away.

696
00:56:08,438 --> 00:56:10,133
Get out.

697
00:56:15,445 --> 00:56:19,211
Remember when I'm gone,

698
00:56:19,249 --> 00:56:21,513
what I did,

699
00:56:22,452 --> 00:56:24,215
I did out of love for you.

700
00:56:26,222 --> 00:56:28,156
Did what?

701
00:56:31,661 --> 00:56:33,891
It was me

702
00:56:33,930 --> 00:56:35,830
who killed Eirene

703
00:56:35,865 --> 00:56:37,924
and your child.

704
00:56:39,536 --> 00:56:41,731
I wanted you for myself.

705
00:56:41,771 --> 00:56:43,466
So I poisoned her.

706
00:57:00,557 --> 00:57:02,115
Goodbye, love.

