1
00:01:45,145 --> 00:01:47,477
The boy is blameless.

2
00:02:20,613 --> 00:02:22,945
That's my girl.

3
00:02:42,769 --> 00:02:44,202
Cack!

4
00:03:09,796 --> 00:03:12,458
You all right? You're looking pointy.

5
00:03:12,499 --> 00:03:14,194
What's the news from Ostia?

6
00:03:14,234 --> 00:03:17,294
Three grain ships from Alex in.
Mussa's people.

7
00:03:17,337 --> 00:03:19,168
Have a cup of wine. Set you up.

8
00:03:19,205 --> 00:03:21,196
Take 25, no less.

9
00:03:21,241 --> 00:03:23,300
Give the lading to Ajax.

10
00:03:24,878 --> 00:03:26,175
Well, Mussa will complain.

11
00:03:26,212 --> 00:03:28,510
If he does, cut out his tongue.

12
00:03:32,352 --> 00:03:34,081
You think I'm joking?

13
00:03:35,388 --> 00:03:37,049
I'll see to it now.

14
00:03:42,862 --> 00:03:44,420
Vorenus...

15
00:03:49,168 --> 00:03:50,328
Nothing.

16
00:03:51,638 --> 00:03:53,765
Memmio of the Caelian is here.

17
00:03:53,806 --> 00:03:56,366
He asked to see you.

18
00:04:11,491 --> 00:04:13,083
Salve, Memmio.

19
00:04:14,127 --> 00:04:15,890
Please sit down.

20
00:04:19,198 --> 00:04:21,530
Weather's turning.
I like a bit of heat.

21
00:04:21,568 --> 00:04:24,366
What brings you
to the Aventine, Memmio?

22
00:04:25,204 --> 00:04:29,140
No chitchat. Straight to cases. I like that.

23
00:04:29,175 --> 00:04:32,406
A young nephew
of my colleague Carbo here

24
00:04:32,445 --> 00:04:35,505
was defiled by an Aventine man.

25
00:04:35,548 --> 00:04:37,982
Name of Quintus Bubo.
You know him?

26
00:04:39,852 --> 00:04:41,717
I know him.

27
00:04:41,754 --> 00:04:44,985
With your permission, Carbo wishes
to avenge his family's honor

28
00:04:45,024 --> 00:04:48,084
- and kill this Quintus.
- The boy's only 12.

29
00:04:48,127 --> 00:04:50,595
He was sucking his cock for pennies.

30
00:04:50,630 --> 00:04:52,325
He was paid, then?

31
00:04:52,498 --> 00:04:55,660
Yes, but he didn't ask me first.

32
00:04:55,702 --> 00:04:57,897
The boy was paid.

33
00:04:57,937 --> 00:05:00,804
Nobody in my family
sucks cock without I say so.

34
00:05:02,108 --> 00:05:04,440
Carbo is from respectable people.

35
00:05:06,813 --> 00:05:08,007
The boy took money.

36
00:05:09,282 --> 00:05:11,842
He was working as a prostitute.

37
00:05:11,884 --> 00:05:14,478
Quintus Bubo's committed no offense.
You won't touch him.

38
00:05:14,520 --> 00:05:16,750
Brother Vorenus,
perhaps you misunderstand.

39
00:05:16,789 --> 00:05:20,418
I misunderstand nothing, brother.

40
00:05:20,460 --> 00:05:24,157
I've been given strict mandate
by Mark Antony to maintain the peace.

41
00:05:24,197 --> 00:05:27,394
Quintus Bubo is a man
of property and respect.

42
00:05:27,433 --> 00:05:30,197
You will not touch him.

43
00:05:30,236 --> 00:05:32,932
Money or not though,
he took advantage of the boy.

44
00:05:32,972 --> 00:05:35,873
Perhaps some moderate
form of punishment...

45
00:05:37,210 --> 00:05:41,010
We come to you out of politeness.
A mere formality.

46
00:05:41,047 --> 00:05:42,639
I've given you my answer.

47
00:05:42,682 --> 00:05:44,547
Wrong fucking answer.

48
00:05:44,584 --> 00:05:47,883
This maggot pisses on my name,
on my family honor.

49
00:05:47,920 --> 00:05:50,650
Control your man, Memmio.

50
00:05:50,690 --> 00:05:52,555
Vorenus, the man has a fair point.

51
00:05:52,792 --> 00:05:54,555
Silence, Pullo!

52
00:05:55,328 --> 00:05:57,125
Brother Vorenus, in all candor,

53
00:05:57,163 --> 00:05:58,630
even your own man knows...

54
00:05:58,665 --> 00:06:01,725
My man doesn't know
when to keep his mouth shut.

55
00:06:13,112 --> 00:06:15,546
I've given you my decision.

56
00:06:16,649 --> 00:06:18,708
And we graciously accept your judgment.

57
00:06:18,751 --> 00:06:21,083
I thank you for your time

58
00:06:21,120 --> 00:06:23,680
and I apologize for the disruption.

59
00:06:31,698 --> 00:06:33,165
You didn't have to insult me in front of...

60
00:06:33,199 --> 00:06:35,326
Do not question my authority
in front of others.

61
00:06:35,368 --> 00:06:37,859
Do not question my authority
under any circumstances.

62
00:06:37,904 --> 00:06:39,872
Authority?

63
00:06:49,482 --> 00:06:51,450
Hard being the boss?

64
00:07:08,434 --> 00:07:09,628
Good stuff.

65
00:07:09,669 --> 00:07:12,035
Is it? How does one tell?

66
00:07:12,805 --> 00:07:14,170
Try.

67
00:07:23,082 --> 00:07:24,777
Hold your breath.

68
00:07:30,189 --> 00:07:31,213
It's horrid.

69
00:07:32,225 --> 00:07:34,489
In a minute, you'll feel delicious.

70
00:07:38,564 --> 00:07:40,156
You know Jocasta.

71
00:07:41,267 --> 00:07:42,256
Do I?

72
00:07:42,301 --> 00:07:45,896
- We met at the theater last year. I was with...
- What are you doing?

73
00:07:46,873 --> 00:07:48,101
We're inhaling hemp.

74
00:07:48,141 --> 00:07:50,234
I can see that.

75
00:07:50,276 --> 00:07:52,506
You're making the whole house stink.

76
00:07:52,745 --> 00:07:56,442
- In future, do it outside if you must.
- Yes, Mother.

77
00:07:58,417 --> 00:08:01,011
- Is it any good?
- Excellent.

78
00:08:02,188 --> 00:08:04,019
Give it here.

79
00:08:07,426 --> 00:08:09,826
I brought back two sacks from Macedonia.

80
00:08:09,862 --> 00:08:11,762
So much better than the Italian kind.

81
00:08:14,133 --> 00:08:15,828
Macedonia?

82
00:08:15,868 --> 00:08:18,098
Papa has quarries there.

83
00:08:18,137 --> 00:08:21,060
We're going there when Antony
takes up his governorship.

84
00:08:21,140 --> 00:08:23,165
My dear, it's ghastly.

85
00:08:24,877 --> 00:08:27,937
Filthy climate, vile food, beastly people.

86
00:08:27,980 --> 00:08:32,713
- Perhaps you didn't mix in the best society.
- Oh, no, Papa is hideously rich,

87
00:08:32,752 --> 00:08:35,186
but there's no society to be found.

88
00:08:35,221 --> 00:08:37,655
The men are overly fond
of fucking their sheep.

89
00:08:37,690 --> 00:08:40,625
And when you meet the women,
you can hardly blame them.

90
00:08:40,660 --> 00:08:42,958
It truly is the end of the world.

91
00:08:49,268 --> 00:08:50,792
I'm no snob, Octavia,

92
00:08:51,037 --> 00:08:54,302
and I don't mind that you bring home
a tradesman's daughter...

93
00:08:56,242 --> 00:08:59,040
but let's just stop there, shall we?

94
00:08:59,078 --> 00:09:02,775
No actors, no gladiators,
or that sort of thing, ne?

95
00:09:08,754 --> 00:09:10,415
Don't mind her.

96
00:09:10,456 --> 00:09:13,857
She's been an infernal grump
since Octavian left.

97
00:09:16,829 --> 00:09:19,730
Send to ask Antony
when he's coming home. No, don't.

98
00:09:19,765 --> 00:09:21,130
A fig for him.

99
00:09:21,167 --> 00:09:23,158
Yes, domina. Timon is waiting,

100
00:09:23,202 --> 00:09:26,535
asking if it pleases you to see him.

101
00:09:44,423 --> 00:09:46,152
Domina.

102
00:09:48,361 --> 00:09:50,556
- Domina...
- Go away.

103
00:09:50,596 --> 00:09:53,326
- But Merula said...
- Changed my mind.

104
00:10:28,334 --> 00:10:30,165
Hello, Duro.

105
00:10:43,416 --> 00:10:45,213
Yes, it's good.

106
00:10:46,285 --> 00:10:48,014
It's good.

107
00:11:03,602 --> 00:11:05,365
Very good!

108
00:11:08,274 --> 00:11:10,799
Hello, Abba. We're learning Hebrew.

109
00:11:10,843 --> 00:11:13,903
- I can see that.
- They'll be reading Torah in no time.

110
00:11:13,946 --> 00:11:16,039
I can't wait.

111
00:12:11,070 --> 00:12:13,766
You came in very late last night.

112
00:12:14,540 --> 00:12:16,667
Business.

113
00:12:16,709 --> 00:12:19,940
Business involving wine, vomit and sex.

114
00:12:20,980 --> 00:12:22,914
I'm sorry, did I disturb you?

115
00:12:22,948 --> 00:12:25,075
No, not at all.

116
00:12:25,117 --> 00:12:27,483
But do please wake me
before you come at me so.

117
00:12:27,520 --> 00:12:30,011
It would be a little less...

118
00:12:30,056 --> 00:12:31,853
alarming.

119
00:12:36,362 --> 00:12:39,092
I was thinking about Macedonia.

120
00:12:39,131 --> 00:12:40,530
Were you?

121
00:12:40,566 --> 00:12:44,195
Do we have to go?
Can't we just... stay here?

122
00:12:44,236 --> 00:12:45,999
No.

123
00:12:46,038 --> 00:12:49,201
Once my consulship is over, we're gone.

124
00:12:49,241 --> 00:12:51,607
But it's so far from Rome.

125
00:12:51,844 --> 00:12:54,369
They have dressmakers

126
00:12:54,413 --> 00:12:58,440
and jewel merchants
in Odessa just like here.

127
00:12:58,484 --> 00:13:00,645
Once you're gone from Italy

128
00:13:00,686 --> 00:13:02,677
your enemies will no longer fear you

129
00:13:02,721 --> 00:13:05,212
and you will be powerless
to strike at them.

130
00:13:05,257 --> 00:13:07,555
I don't want to strike at them.

131
00:13:07,593 --> 00:13:10,118
There's no juice in it anymore.

132
00:13:10,162 --> 00:13:12,130
I want peace and quiet

133
00:13:12,164 --> 00:13:14,962
and a nice rich province to squeeze.

134
00:13:15,000 --> 00:13:17,491
Peace and quiet?

135
00:13:17,536 --> 00:13:21,597
While you're swilling wine in Macedonia,
will Brutus and Cassius be idle?

136
00:13:21,640 --> 00:13:23,904
Those abject creatures?

137
00:13:23,943 --> 00:13:27,379
Abject only while you have power.

138
00:13:27,413 --> 00:13:29,745
Your enemies will not rest
until you are dead.

139
00:13:29,782 --> 00:13:32,808
You have a wolf by the ears.
You cannot let go of him now.

140
00:13:42,761 --> 00:13:44,786
Pass the oil, would you?

141
00:13:59,678 --> 00:14:00,975
Make way!

142
00:14:23,335 --> 00:14:25,394
Well, thank you. Thank you very much.

143
00:14:25,437 --> 00:14:27,598
We'll see you next week? Yeah.

144
00:14:29,141 --> 00:14:30,870
- Brother!
- Who was that man?

145
00:14:31,744 --> 00:14:34,838
- Who?
- The man you were speaking with.

146
00:14:34,880 --> 00:14:37,007
You mean Barak.
He's a saffron trader.

147
00:14:37,049 --> 00:14:39,040
Doesn't look like a saffron trader.

148
00:14:39,752 --> 00:14:41,652
Not everybody looks like what they are.

149
00:14:59,405 --> 00:15:00,660
Justice, Captain!

150
00:15:00,739 --> 00:15:02,604
- I beg for justice!
- Who's this?

151
00:15:02,641 --> 00:15:04,632
Quintus Bubo and his wife.

152
00:15:04,677 --> 00:15:06,235
Gelded by Memmio's boys.

153
00:15:09,848 --> 00:15:12,009
Please, Captain, justice!

154
00:15:17,289 --> 00:15:19,086
Come on. Calm down, brother.

155
00:15:19,124 --> 00:15:21,388
He shouldn't have been goating around.

156
00:15:21,427 --> 00:15:24,726
- Memmio disobeyed me.
- He didn't kill the old fool at least.

157
00:15:24,763 --> 00:15:27,698
- He disobeyed me!
- Let me go talk to Memmio.

158
00:15:27,733 --> 00:15:30,429
- I'll sort out a compromise.
- No.

159
00:15:30,469 --> 00:15:33,438
If you punish Carbo over this trivia,

160
00:15:33,472 --> 00:15:35,906
Memmio is going
to take it as disrespect.

161
00:15:35,941 --> 00:15:38,102
He'll retaliate. You'll start a gang war.

162
00:15:38,143 --> 00:15:40,008
Very likely, but I've got no choice.

163
00:15:40,045 --> 00:15:44,744
- And it's your fault.
- What? How is it my fault?

164
00:15:44,783 --> 00:15:46,717
You questioned my authority.

165
00:15:46,752 --> 00:15:50,381
- That gave him license to disobey me.
- Oh, bollocks.

166
00:15:50,422 --> 00:15:52,151
Now, you go and find Carbo.

167
00:15:52,324 --> 00:15:55,780
You show him the same disrespect
that he has shown me.

168
00:15:55,828 --> 00:15:59,059
- Everyone is in the wrong here.
- I gave you an order.

169
00:15:59,098 --> 00:16:02,590
This isn't the mumpin' Legion.
I take orders from no man.

170
00:16:02,635 --> 00:16:05,195
Then you're no use to me. You, go and do it.

171
00:16:05,237 --> 00:16:07,831
Will do, Captain.

172
00:16:09,875 --> 00:16:11,604
You are thinking all backwards.

173
00:16:11,644 --> 00:16:15,171
I warned you about questioning my authority.
You learn your place.

174
00:16:15,214 --> 00:16:18,140
My place? Well, fuck you,
you miserable bastard,

175
00:16:18,217 --> 00:16:20,140
I'm the one trying to keep you alive.

176
00:16:20,219 --> 00:16:22,312
You'd love to start a gang war.

177
00:16:22,354 --> 00:16:24,948
Get yourself killed.
Put an end to all your misery.

178
00:16:24,990 --> 00:16:26,753
Take half the city with you.

179
00:16:26,792 --> 00:16:29,590
Well, I tell you what.
You can die a thousand times.

180
00:16:29,628 --> 00:16:33,758
And it won't bring back Niobe
or the children or Caesar!

181
00:16:33,799 --> 00:16:35,994
Listen, I'm your friend. I'm trying to help.

182
00:16:36,035 --> 00:16:39,129
- You've never helped me.
- Have I not?

183
00:16:39,171 --> 00:16:40,832
Well, who saved your life a dozen times?

184
00:16:40,873 --> 00:16:42,636
Who took care of that snake Evander?

185
00:16:42,675 --> 00:16:45,838
Who carried you home when...
when you were drunk?

186
00:16:52,618 --> 00:16:54,643
What do you mean?

187
00:16:54,687 --> 00:16:56,580
"Took care of Evander."

188
00:16:56,655 --> 00:16:58,953
Nothing... I didn't mean anything.

189
00:17:00,626 --> 00:17:02,594
What do you mean?

190
00:17:05,564 --> 00:17:07,293
Speak.

191
00:17:11,103 --> 00:17:13,230
I killed him.

192
00:17:13,272 --> 00:17:15,934
I found out what he'd done and killed him.

193
00:17:15,974 --> 00:17:17,908
Listen, she loved you.

194
00:17:17,943 --> 00:17:21,902
You were happy together.
If I'd told you, you would have killed her.

195
00:17:21,947 --> 00:17:23,380
Get out!

196
00:17:24,616 --> 00:17:26,049
What was I supposed to do?

197
00:17:26,085 --> 00:17:28,053
Get out.

198
00:17:44,002 --> 00:17:46,334
Atia thrives, I trust?

199
00:17:46,372 --> 00:17:48,363
She does. She does.

200
00:17:49,174 --> 00:17:51,608
And the rest of the family?

201
00:17:51,844 --> 00:17:53,505
Good enough.

202
00:17:53,545 --> 00:17:55,740
Yes, a surprising boy, isn't he?

203
00:17:56,582 --> 00:17:59,949
Octavian. Such vim and vigor
for one so young.

204
00:17:59,985 --> 00:18:03,011
They say it's a considerable army he's raised.

205
00:18:03,055 --> 00:18:06,547
Buying up all the fools
and cripples in Campania

206
00:18:06,592 --> 00:18:08,890
is hardly raising an army.

207
00:18:08,927 --> 00:18:12,021
You are right, no doubt.

208
00:18:12,064 --> 00:18:14,624
But many are veterans also.

209
00:18:14,666 --> 00:18:18,466
Eighth Legion men. Seventh Legion.

210
00:18:18,504 --> 00:18:21,632
Sat on their backsides taking his money

211
00:18:21,673 --> 00:18:24,836
to cheer him as he goes by.

212
00:18:24,877 --> 00:18:28,040
Caesar my arse.

213
00:18:28,080 --> 00:18:31,379
But I didn't bring you here to talk of children.

214
00:18:32,050 --> 00:18:34,575
Indeed, I await your pleasure.

215
00:18:50,636 --> 00:18:53,366
When my term as consul is over...

216
00:18:53,539 --> 00:18:56,900
I no longer wish to take the governorship
of Macedonia.

217
00:18:56,975 --> 00:18:58,670
I wish to take Gaul.

218
00:18:59,411 --> 00:19:01,777
But Decimus is Governor of Gaul.

219
00:19:01,814 --> 00:19:04,715
Well, he can have Macedonia if he likes.

220
00:19:04,750 --> 00:19:08,481
I want Gaul. The weather's better.

221
00:19:08,520 --> 00:19:12,456
I'm afraid that will be a bit difficult.

222
00:19:18,163 --> 00:19:21,223
The Senate may suppose
you plan to emulate Caesar,

223
00:19:21,266 --> 00:19:23,393
camping your legions on our border.

224
00:19:23,435 --> 00:19:26,871
Close enough to Rome

225
00:19:26,905 --> 00:19:29,066
to scare us into doing anything you wish.

226
00:19:30,876 --> 00:19:34,368
Steady on. Hadn't even crossed my mind.

227
00:19:34,980 --> 00:19:37,107
I just prefer Gaul.

228
00:19:37,149 --> 00:19:40,050
But you understand why the Senate

229
00:19:40,085 --> 00:19:42,315
would not pass such a measure?

230
00:19:42,354 --> 00:19:45,812
You are the Senate, Cicero.

231
00:19:48,594 --> 00:19:51,020
The next time we meet,

232
00:19:51,096 --> 00:19:54,759
perhaps you will propose
my governorship of Gaul.

233
00:19:54,800 --> 00:20:00,238
No one can make any trouble
if the noble Cicero is backing me.

234
00:20:00,272 --> 00:20:03,070
I don't think that's a good idea.

235
00:20:05,811 --> 00:20:09,110
Not that I do not wish to help you...

236
00:20:09,147 --> 00:20:10,910
as a friend.

237
00:20:10,949 --> 00:20:14,544
But the Senate would know I was backing you

238
00:20:14,586 --> 00:20:18,181
only through... through fear of death.

239
00:20:20,626 --> 00:20:22,651
I understand.

240
00:20:22,694 --> 00:20:25,993
You do not want to seem cowardly.

241
00:20:27,633 --> 00:20:30,568
Well, tell them I bribed you.

242
00:20:31,270 --> 00:20:32,999
Would you accept a bribe?

243
00:20:33,038 --> 00:20:35,097
I would not.

244
00:20:36,308 --> 00:20:38,401
Rich enough?

245
00:20:38,443 --> 00:20:40,240
Well, it's always worth a try.

246
00:20:44,650 --> 00:20:47,744
Well, you leave me only one option, then.

247
00:20:47,786 --> 00:20:51,381
It always comes to this.

248
00:20:52,090 --> 00:20:53,421
I know.

249
00:20:54,459 --> 00:20:56,359
I'm sorry.

250
00:20:57,696 --> 00:20:59,721
Such times we live in.

251
00:21:00,999 --> 00:21:02,796
Please, go on.

252
00:21:02,834 --> 00:21:05,064
Make your threats.

253
00:21:05,971 --> 00:21:09,031
I don't like to submit to mere implication.

254
00:21:18,250 --> 00:21:21,879
There is a question
I've always wanted to ask you.

255
00:21:23,622 --> 00:21:25,783
Your old friend Crassus,

256
00:21:25,824 --> 00:21:29,089
when he was captured by the Parthians,

257
00:21:29,127 --> 00:21:33,154
is it true that they poured
molten gold down his throat?

258
00:21:33,198 --> 00:21:37,100
Because that would really sting.

259
00:21:41,139 --> 00:21:43,437
Thank you.

260
00:21:46,511 --> 00:21:48,706
It is correct, what you say.

261
00:21:50,349 --> 00:21:54,149
The weather in Macedonia is...

262
00:21:54,386 --> 00:21:56,115
dreadful.

263
00:22:19,344 --> 00:22:22,040
I thought maybe you'd want to know a bit more

264
00:22:22,080 --> 00:22:24,844
- than what I said.
- I don't.

265
00:22:27,653 --> 00:22:29,814
You should know Niobe wasn't...

266
00:22:29,855 --> 00:22:31,550
Don't speak of her.

267
00:22:32,591 --> 00:22:34,821
It's in the past. It is done.

268
00:22:36,528 --> 00:22:40,157
Brother, I'm sorry I kept it from you.

269
00:22:40,198 --> 00:22:42,462
I thought it was for the best. I'm sorry.

270
00:22:43,268 --> 00:22:45,259
I forgive you, brother.

271
00:22:47,039 --> 00:22:50,600
I understand why you didn't tell me.
I understand.

272
00:22:52,344 --> 00:22:55,074
- I hear you say that, but...
- I mean it.

273
00:22:57,282 --> 00:22:58,715
I forgive you.

274
00:23:01,153 --> 00:23:04,179
How could I not forgive you, Pullo?

275
00:23:04,222 --> 00:23:06,417
You're all I've got left in life.

276
00:23:18,303 --> 00:23:20,737
Keeping me alive?

277
00:23:22,641 --> 00:23:24,506
This business with the Caelians...

278
00:23:24,543 --> 00:23:28,604
- What of it?
- We can still stop it turning into a war.

279
00:23:28,647 --> 00:23:30,444
Let Carbo pay a fine.

280
00:23:30,482 --> 00:23:32,143
If I go and talk quietly to Memmio

281
00:23:32,184 --> 00:23:35,620
we can sort it out
so that no one loses face.

282
00:23:35,654 --> 00:23:37,884
You suggested that before.

283
00:23:37,923 --> 00:23:40,790
Worth a go. Better than a war.

284
00:23:40,826 --> 00:23:42,418
You may be right. You may be.

285
00:23:42,461 --> 00:23:45,123
But it's too late now.

286
00:23:46,698 --> 00:23:48,427
Move.

287
00:24:04,716 --> 00:24:06,775
Salve, Carbo.

288
00:24:11,790 --> 00:24:12,916
Get him up.

289
00:24:23,301 --> 00:24:25,633
No!

290
00:24:36,515 --> 00:24:39,450
Tell your mistress
I have a message from her son.

291
00:25:07,145 --> 00:25:09,010
Piss and blood!

292
00:25:14,019 --> 00:25:17,147
Forgive the intrusion. I was entranced.

293
00:25:18,857 --> 00:25:20,324
Who are you?

294
00:25:20,358 --> 00:25:23,327
I am Marcus Vipsanius Agrippa,

295
00:25:23,361 --> 00:25:25,056
a friend of Caesar...

296
00:25:25,096 --> 00:25:28,088
of Octavian as was.

297
00:25:28,133 --> 00:25:30,601
Have I the honor of speaking
to his sister Octavia?

298
00:25:30,635 --> 00:25:32,762
Yes. Is my brother here?

299
00:25:32,804 --> 00:25:35,830
There's nothing wrong, is there?
He's all right?

300
00:25:35,874 --> 00:25:37,842
No... Yes.

301
00:25:37,876 --> 00:25:40,709
I mean, no, he's not here.
But yes, he's well.

302
00:25:40,745 --> 00:25:42,804
I left him five days ago, thriving.

303
00:25:42,848 --> 00:25:44,281
Happy.

304
00:25:44,316 --> 00:25:47,149
- I am to convey his best wishes to you.
- No letter?

305
00:25:47,185 --> 00:25:50,018
I told him he ought to write,
but you know how he is.

306
00:25:50,055 --> 00:25:51,579
Please.

307
00:25:54,526 --> 00:25:58,326
In place of writing, I am charged to tell you
that he loves you as ever

308
00:25:58,363 --> 00:26:00,695
and to answer any questions you may have,

309
00:26:00,732 --> 00:26:03,098
consonant with political security.

310
00:26:03,134 --> 00:26:06,160
He's grown no less pompous, then?

311
00:26:06,204 --> 00:26:08,263
It suits him better now than at school.

312
00:26:09,074 --> 00:26:10,234
He's a powerful man.

313
00:26:10,275 --> 00:26:13,301
So everyone says. I cannot believe it.

314
00:26:13,345 --> 00:26:14,700
My little brother.

315
00:26:14,779 --> 00:26:17,509
Your little brother has an army 10,000 strong.

316
00:26:17,549 --> 00:26:21,542
I have written him a hundred times
asking him to stop this madness.

317
00:26:21,586 --> 00:26:25,522
- But he does not listen to me.
- On the contrary.

318
00:26:26,524 --> 00:26:30,051
I think you are the only person in the world
he does listen to.

319
00:26:32,364 --> 00:26:33,695
Is this the messenger?

320
00:26:35,033 --> 00:26:38,161
This is Agrippa, a friend of Octavian.

321
00:26:38,203 --> 00:26:39,932
Deeply honored.

322
00:26:42,107 --> 00:26:43,267
And so?

323
00:26:43,308 --> 00:26:45,276
He asked that I make certain you're well,

324
00:26:45,310 --> 00:26:47,904
and to assure you of his respect and fidelity.

325
00:26:48,847 --> 00:26:50,542
We're very well.

326
00:26:51,850 --> 00:26:54,683
And as for his respect and fidelity...

327
00:26:54,719 --> 00:26:56,516
He begs that in the name of family

328
00:26:56,554 --> 00:26:59,717
you keep an open mind
as to your future prospects.

329
00:27:01,226 --> 00:27:04,684
You came all the way
from Campania to say that?

330
00:27:04,729 --> 00:27:07,562
- I have other business.
- With whom?

331
00:27:07,599 --> 00:27:09,430
I am not at liberty to say.

332
00:27:11,036 --> 00:27:12,860
Intrigue, is it?

333
00:27:12,938 --> 00:27:15,168
I imagine you're a master.

334
00:27:15,206 --> 00:27:18,300
Does Mark Antony know
that you're in the city?

335
00:27:18,343 --> 00:27:22,109
I expect there are many citizens
whose location is unknown to the Consul.

336
00:27:22,147 --> 00:27:24,940
True, but he does like to know

337
00:27:25,016 --> 00:27:27,007
- where the traitors are.
- Mother!

338
00:27:27,052 --> 00:27:29,612
Well, they are traitors, aren't they?

339
00:27:29,654 --> 00:27:31,519
Antony is consul in Rome,

340
00:27:31,556 --> 00:27:33,990
and Octavian is deliberately
challenging him.

341
00:27:35,460 --> 00:27:38,623
If this is not a traitor, I don't know what is.

342
00:27:39,297 --> 00:27:41,390
I have said what I must.

343
00:27:41,433 --> 00:27:43,094
I will take your leave to go.

344
00:27:43,134 --> 00:27:45,125
Tell my son I...

345
00:27:48,673 --> 00:27:51,642
No, tell him nothing.

346
00:28:02,787 --> 00:28:05,654
Send to tell Antony that Marcus Agrippa
is in the city.

347
00:28:05,690 --> 00:28:07,317
Mother, no!

348
00:28:07,359 --> 00:28:09,156
Who knows what Antony will do to him?

349
00:28:09,194 --> 00:28:10,855
Nothing pleasant, I would think.

350
00:28:10,895 --> 00:28:13,022
He is your son's friend.

351
00:28:13,765 --> 00:28:15,733
I have no son.

352
00:28:34,519 --> 00:28:37,647
Althea, my honey. How goes it?

353
00:28:37,689 --> 00:28:41,250
- You know you're not allowed in the kitchen.
- But I'm hungry.

354
00:28:41,292 --> 00:28:43,522
You won't tell on me, will you?

355
00:28:48,900 --> 00:28:50,868
You should try some.

356
00:29:13,425 --> 00:29:15,586
We've been waiting for you.

357
00:29:16,694 --> 00:29:18,594
Keep waiting. Where's your mistress?

358
00:29:18,630 --> 00:29:21,656
- Never mind about my mistress.
- I want to speak to her.

359
00:29:21,699 --> 00:29:23,758
She doesn't speak to the like of you.

360
00:29:23,802 --> 00:29:26,464
And I don't speak to the like of you.

361
00:29:26,504 --> 00:29:28,404
She wants the job done, she'll see me.

362
00:29:28,440 --> 00:29:30,374
You speak to me.

363
00:29:31,509 --> 00:29:32,976
Maybe some other time.

364
00:29:33,778 --> 00:29:35,541
Wait.

365
00:29:42,020 --> 00:29:44,784
So you're Servilia, then, are you?

366
00:29:46,091 --> 00:29:48,457
Choice. Very choice.

367
00:29:48,493 --> 00:29:50,723
Address me by my name again

368
00:29:50,762 --> 00:29:53,595
and I'll have your tongue
nailed to a wagon wheel.

369
00:29:53,631 --> 00:29:56,998
Forgive me. I've not spoken
to nobility before.

370
00:29:59,671 --> 00:30:02,105
- What's his name?
- Duro.

371
00:30:06,377 --> 00:30:08,208
Eleni was right.

372
00:30:08,246 --> 00:30:10,646
You're a pretty little man, aren't you?

373
00:30:15,753 --> 00:30:18,745
You've been in the house of the Julii
for some time now.

374
00:30:18,790 --> 00:30:20,587
Why is Atia still alive?

375
00:30:20,625 --> 00:30:22,820
Trouble's finding the right time.

376
00:30:22,861 --> 00:30:25,386
They always eat together,
her and the daughter.

377
00:30:25,430 --> 00:30:28,126
If I can kill the young cunny
I can do it tomorrow.

378
00:30:28,166 --> 00:30:30,657
No. No harm to the girl.

379
00:30:30,702 --> 00:30:35,639
Well, then, if I could only put the poison
on Antony's cock, we'd be sweet.

380
00:30:36,274 --> 00:30:39,107
The domina dines on that regular.

381
00:30:39,144 --> 00:30:41,339
Failing that, you'll have to be patient.

382
00:30:41,379 --> 00:30:43,870
You have only foul jokes to tell me.

383
00:30:43,915 --> 00:30:46,475
- Why are you come here?
- Shekels, queen.

384
00:30:46,518 --> 00:30:49,612
- Shekels.
- He wants money.

385
00:30:49,654 --> 00:30:52,054
Has he not already been paid?

386
00:30:52,223 --> 00:30:54,700
The job's taking longer than we thought.

387
00:30:54,759 --> 00:30:56,420
Let's be fair.

388
00:30:58,229 --> 00:30:59,560
Give him what he asks.

389
00:30:59,597 --> 00:31:01,724
Make it 300.

390
00:31:11,009 --> 00:31:12,601
Wait!

391
00:31:13,711 --> 00:31:16,236
Give me a kiss before I go.

392
00:31:16,281 --> 00:31:19,876
- Excuse me?
- Kiss me.

393
00:31:22,320 --> 00:31:24,083
I don't think so.

394
00:31:24,122 --> 00:31:27,148
You want this woman dead? Kiss me.

395
00:32:04,395 --> 00:32:06,795
That's very good.

396
00:32:06,831 --> 00:32:12,235
So if we could return to the subject of money...
please bear in mind, Your Excellency,

397
00:32:12,270 --> 00:32:15,706
that those that help us now
will have good friends in Rome

398
00:32:15,740 --> 00:32:19,699
when Mark Antony, the traitor, is deposed.
Very good friends.

399
00:32:19,744 --> 00:32:22,804
It's only a matter of time.
With or without your help,

400
00:32:22,847 --> 00:32:25,247
we shall raise an army.

401
00:32:25,283 --> 00:32:26,443
We shall.

402
00:32:26,484 --> 00:32:29,385
Antony's head will rot on a spike.

403
00:32:31,256 --> 00:32:35,158
There are Roman women
who are fucked by baboons.

404
00:32:35,193 --> 00:32:36,785
Excuse me?

405
00:32:36,828 --> 00:32:40,662
I've heard there are shows
where such things can be seen.

406
00:32:42,867 --> 00:32:46,325
They're not so much shows, really.
They're more a punishment.

407
00:32:47,138 --> 00:32:49,436
I should like to see that.

408
00:32:49,474 --> 00:32:51,237
We do not have such in Bithynia.

409
00:32:52,010 --> 00:32:56,344
I should imagine it's simply a matter
of training the baboons.

410
00:32:56,381 --> 00:32:58,246
We have no baboons here.

411
00:32:58,283 --> 00:33:00,342
No apes of any kind.

412
00:33:00,385 --> 00:33:02,683
I wasn't aware of that.

413
00:33:02,720 --> 00:33:05,689
So as I say, those who help us now...

414
00:33:05,723 --> 00:33:09,955
Yes, you want my money
to raise an army.

415
00:33:09,994 --> 00:33:13,953
I want to see a Roman woman
fucked by baboons.

416
00:33:16,467 --> 00:33:18,196
Perhaps arrangements can be made.

417
00:33:20,538 --> 00:33:24,201
I killed him. I did.

418
00:33:24,242 --> 00:33:25,971
I had to.

419
00:33:26,010 --> 00:33:27,500
You know, it's in my blood.

420
00:33:27,545 --> 00:33:30,810
My ancestor dethroned
the tyrant Tarquin.

421
00:33:30,848 --> 00:33:34,545
I understand there were a great many
who stabbed your Caesar.

422
00:33:35,787 --> 00:33:37,721
I delivered the final blow.

423
00:33:37,755 --> 00:33:40,280
Seems a bit cowardly, no?

424
00:33:41,225 --> 00:33:42,283
You say what?

425
00:33:42,327 --> 00:33:45,421
He was wounded already -
dying, defenseless, alone.

426
00:33:45,463 --> 00:33:47,693
And you stabbed him yet again.

427
00:33:48,166 --> 00:33:50,361
He was a tyrant.

428
00:33:50,401 --> 00:33:52,460
Our killing him was a necessity.

429
00:33:52,704 --> 00:33:54,228
A necessary and noble act.

430
00:33:54,272 --> 00:33:57,366
Perhaps I shall find a fresh corpse to stab

431
00:33:57,408 --> 00:34:01,037
- and become great myself.
- What, you dare to insult me?

432
00:34:02,180 --> 00:34:04,648
- Excuse me.
- A senator of Rome?

433
00:34:04,682 --> 00:34:06,172
Stand up.

434
00:34:07,618 --> 00:34:10,018
- Stand up!
- Perhaps we should get some air?

435
00:34:10,054 --> 00:34:12,818
No, this man... this dog insults me.

436
00:34:12,857 --> 00:34:15,189
Dog, he says? I'm a dog?

437
00:34:15,226 --> 00:34:16,989
Excuse us. It's the wine, the heat.

438
00:34:17,028 --> 00:34:18,962
We are guests here! Looking for favor.

439
00:34:18,996 --> 00:34:22,796
Favor? I ask no favor of such animals.

440
00:34:25,236 --> 00:34:27,727
Control yourself, you fool.

441
00:34:27,772 --> 00:34:30,240
They called me a coward.

442
00:34:31,976 --> 00:34:34,501
Come with me. Come on.

443
00:34:36,547 --> 00:34:38,344
I am a senator.

444
00:34:42,687 --> 00:34:46,521
- My friend, you have lost your way.
- Leave me alone.

445
00:34:46,557 --> 00:34:49,048
- Brutus...
- Leave me alone!

446
00:35:07,745 --> 00:35:09,406
I'm sorry.

447
00:35:12,450 --> 00:35:14,441
I'm sorry.

448
00:35:44,715 --> 00:35:47,616
Wine in the bath? Bad sign.

449
00:35:47,652 --> 00:35:49,340
You're late again.

450
00:35:49,420 --> 00:35:51,479
Revise your expectations, my dear,

451
00:35:51,722 --> 00:35:54,850
- and I will always be early.
- Did you get my message?

452
00:35:55,593 --> 00:35:57,424
About?

453
00:35:57,462 --> 00:35:59,828
Octavian's man Marcus Agrippa.

454
00:35:59,864 --> 00:36:01,798
Oh, yes, yes. I know all about him.

455
00:36:01,833 --> 00:36:04,666
- Well, did you catch him?
- There's no need.

456
00:36:04,702 --> 00:36:06,761
But he's up to no good.

457
00:36:06,804 --> 00:36:09,568
I know exactly what he's up to.

458
00:36:09,607 --> 00:36:11,871
Octavian sent him to meet with Cicero,

459
00:36:11,909 --> 00:36:15,310
- hoping to form an alliance against me.
- Well, then?

460
00:36:15,346 --> 00:36:17,906
Cicero will refuse.

461
00:36:17,949 --> 00:36:20,315
I have my foot on his throat.

462
00:36:22,386 --> 00:36:25,617
And I'm happy for your son to know it.

463
00:36:25,656 --> 00:36:29,319
Agrippa can come and go as he pleases.

464
00:36:32,230 --> 00:36:34,221
What will become of Octavian?

465
00:36:36,000 --> 00:36:38,491
Don't worry yourself.

466
00:36:38,536 --> 00:36:40,060
I'll not harm him.

467
00:36:42,740 --> 00:36:44,435
Swear it.

468
00:36:45,276 --> 00:36:48,541
On Jupiter's stone. He's family.

469
00:36:59,891 --> 00:37:02,257
If they catch us, they'll crucify us.

470
00:37:03,461 --> 00:37:05,258
Watch for the guard.

471
00:37:28,686 --> 00:37:32,315
When I get through, you pass Lucius to me.

472
00:37:38,696 --> 00:37:40,596
Hey, come here.

473
00:37:40,631 --> 00:37:42,622
Lyde! Lyde!

474
00:37:42,667 --> 00:37:44,328
Lyde, no!

475
00:37:58,082 --> 00:38:01,347
Oh, Gaia, give me a hand here.

476
00:38:01,385 --> 00:38:03,250
Carry your own piss.

477
00:38:05,890 --> 00:38:08,723
Bitch pig whore.
See how you like a whipping.

478
00:38:16,834 --> 00:38:20,133
Are we sure that it's Memmio's work?

479
00:38:20,171 --> 00:38:21,832
Caelian coin in his mouth.

480
00:38:23,474 --> 00:38:25,442
Call armed assembly.

481
00:38:29,847 --> 00:38:32,338
Here we go.

482
00:38:32,383 --> 00:38:34,749
You think we should ignore this, I suppose?

483
00:38:34,785 --> 00:38:37,583
No, you wanted a war, you got it.
We have to fight now.

484
00:38:37,622 --> 00:38:40,989
You don't think you should go and talk
to Memmio? Find a compromise?

485
00:38:41,025 --> 00:38:42,458
It's too late for that.

486
00:38:42,493 --> 00:38:44,586
Surely he'd listen to you, wouldn't he?

487
00:38:46,330 --> 00:38:48,321
Are you saying I'm with Memmio?

488
00:38:48,366 --> 00:38:50,664
I didn't say it, you did. Quick as Mercury.

489
00:38:50,835 --> 00:38:52,462
Brother...

490
00:38:52,503 --> 00:38:54,835
Brother, can't you see
what's happening to you?

491
00:38:54,872 --> 00:38:57,432
I can't see it, brother.
What is happening to me?

492
00:38:57,475 --> 00:39:00,603
What is it that you can see
so clear that I can't?

493
00:39:00,645 --> 00:39:03,307
A demon. A demon has possessed you
or I don't know what.

494
00:39:03,347 --> 00:39:06,544
You see a demon, is it?
What does it look like?

495
00:39:06,584 --> 00:39:08,882
Listen to yourself, man. Me and Memmio?

496
00:39:08,919 --> 00:39:11,547
How could you think that? I'm your friend.

497
00:39:11,589 --> 00:39:13,454
I love you. I would never betray you.

498
00:39:13,491 --> 00:39:15,982
Lying to me, going behind my back.

499
00:39:16,027 --> 00:39:19,121
- It was never like that.
- It wasn't like that?

500
00:39:19,163 --> 00:39:21,893
You tell me, did you enjoy fucking my wife?

501
00:39:21,932 --> 00:39:24,230
- What?
- Is that why you didn't tell me,

502
00:39:24,268 --> 00:39:25,895
because you were fucking her?

503
00:39:25,936 --> 00:39:27,403
You have stepped over the line.

504
00:39:27,438 --> 00:39:30,771
Did you fuck my wife?
I am asking you a question.

505
00:39:30,808 --> 00:39:32,700
- Get out of my way.
- I am asking you a question!

506
00:39:32,777 --> 00:39:34,711
What can I say? You won't believe me.

507
00:39:34,745 --> 00:39:38,613
- If you tell the truth then I will believe you.
- On the bones of my mother,

508
00:39:38,649 --> 00:39:43,143
there was nothing between me and Niobe.
Nothing, never.

509
00:39:43,187 --> 00:39:45,178
I don't believe you. Tell me the truth.

510
00:39:45,222 --> 00:39:46,883
All right, I fucked her! All right?

511
00:39:46,924 --> 00:39:49,017
I fucked her!
Me and half the men on the hill.

512
00:39:49,060 --> 00:39:50,823
Any time you were away, bang!

513
00:39:50,861 --> 00:39:52,590
Legs open, line at the door.

514
00:40:36,107 --> 00:40:37,540
Come on.

515
00:40:42,813 --> 00:40:44,804
Are you all right?

516
00:41:12,877 --> 00:41:15,971
Don't touch me. Don't touch me.

517
00:41:55,920 --> 00:41:58,582
Where are we going now?

518
00:41:58,622 --> 00:42:01,716
I don't know. Anywhere.

519
00:42:01,759 --> 00:42:03,954
Away from this damn place.

520
00:43:30,314 --> 00:43:32,805
Divine Janus,

521
00:43:32,850 --> 00:43:36,251
as this day follows the night,

522
00:43:36,287 --> 00:43:39,313
let me start my life anew.

523
00:43:39,356 --> 00:43:42,917
As the shore is scoured by the tide,

524
00:43:42,960 --> 00:43:45,690
let me be cleansed.

525
00:43:45,729 --> 00:43:49,426
As the seed becomes the flower,

526
00:43:49,466 --> 00:43:51,593
let me be born again.

527
00:44:28,072 --> 00:44:30,040
I'm so sorry. Am I late?

528
00:44:30,074 --> 00:44:32,872
We have completed taking roll.
A quorum exists.

529
00:44:32,910 --> 00:44:34,300
Excellent.

530
00:44:34,378 --> 00:44:37,176
Then let us begin.

531
00:44:39,950 --> 00:44:41,941
No, actually, not quite yet.

532
00:44:41,986 --> 00:44:45,854
I see that Cicero outdoes me
in his tardiness.

533
00:44:45,889 --> 00:44:47,857
Cicero is regrettably ill

534
00:44:47,891 --> 00:44:50,291
and unable to attend this session.

535
00:44:50,327 --> 00:44:53,091
But he has an important matter to propose

536
00:44:53,263 --> 00:44:55,260
regarding my governorship of Gaul.

537
00:44:55,332 --> 00:44:57,527
Should I send my litter bearers for him?

538
00:44:57,568 --> 00:45:00,935
He did, however, provide me with a speech

539
00:45:00,971 --> 00:45:04,737
that he most urgently insisted
be read into the rolls.

540
00:45:06,443 --> 00:45:12,040
Well, then, by all means,
let us hear the words of mighty Cicero.

541
00:45:13,684 --> 00:45:18,678
These being the words
of Marcus Tullius Cicero -

542
00:45:22,993 --> 00:45:27,123
"When I was a young man,
I defended our state.

543
00:45:27,164 --> 00:45:30,930
"As an old man, I shall not abandon it.

544
00:45:30,968 --> 00:45:33,732
"I give sincere thanks to Mark Antony,

545
00:45:33,771 --> 00:45:36,035
"who has generously presented me

546
00:45:36,073 --> 00:45:38,837
"with the most promising
theme imaginable.

547
00:45:40,744 --> 00:45:43,338
"I address you directly, Antony.

548
00:45:43,914 --> 00:45:46,405
"Please listen as if you...

549
00:45:48,352 --> 00:45:50,411
"as if you..."

550
00:45:51,455 --> 00:45:53,150
Go on.

551
00:45:54,458 --> 00:45:56,449
"Please listen...

552
00:45:56,493 --> 00:45:59,428
"as if you were sober and intelligent

553
00:45:59,463 --> 00:46:03,923
"and not a drink-sodden, sex-addled wreck."

554
00:46:06,904 --> 00:46:09,737
"You are certainly not
without accomplishments.

555
00:46:11,141 --> 00:46:14,668
"It is a rare man who can boast
of becoming a bankrupt

556
00:46:14,711 --> 00:46:17,839
"before even coming of age.

557
00:46:20,918 --> 00:46:23,751
"You have brought upon us war,

558
00:46:23,787 --> 00:46:27,580
"pestilence and destruction.

559
00:46:27,658 --> 00:46:30,126
"You are Rome's Helen of Troy.

560
00:46:32,529 --> 00:46:34,394
"But then...

561
00:46:35,432 --> 00:46:37,923
"But then..."

562
00:46:37,968 --> 00:46:39,629
Go on.

563
00:46:41,605 --> 00:46:43,937
Go on!

564
00:46:45,609 --> 00:46:48,772
"...a woman's role has always suited you best."

565
00:47:14,972 --> 00:47:16,462
Write a note.

566
00:47:17,674 --> 00:47:21,337
To Octavian... Caesar, rather.

567
00:47:22,346 --> 00:47:24,576
Tell him I have exposed Antony

568
00:47:24,615 --> 00:47:27,982
for the debauched rat he is.

569
00:47:29,186 --> 00:47:33,486
At this time, the Republic would be
most grateful to accept

570
00:47:33,524 --> 00:47:36,857
Caesar's offer of assistance.

571
00:47:36,894 --> 00:47:39,988
We shall need his army at once.

572
00:47:47,571 --> 00:47:49,163
In Gaul,

573
00:47:49,206 --> 00:47:52,733
the renegade Mark Antony has laid siege

574
00:47:52,910 --> 00:47:54,660
to the city of Mutina.

575
00:47:54,711 --> 00:47:58,306
But salvation is at hand!

576
00:47:58,348 --> 00:48:00,839
The Senate sends an army

577
00:48:00,884 --> 00:48:05,082
led by the generals
Hirtius and Pansa.

578
00:48:05,122 --> 00:48:09,354
The noble patriot, young Caesar Octavian,

579
00:48:09,393 --> 00:48:13,090
joins our generals with his own legions

580
00:48:13,130 --> 00:48:16,258
to crush the rebels.

581
00:48:25,142 --> 00:48:28,111
So much traveling. All the way to Massilia,

582
00:48:28,145 --> 00:48:30,773
now come all the way back. Crazy.

583
00:48:30,814 --> 00:48:33,374
Sorry, love. Had to do it.

584
00:48:33,417 --> 00:48:35,942
The gods have me vexed over Vorenus.

585
00:48:35,986 --> 00:48:38,113
I can't go on until I sort things out with him.

586
00:48:38,155 --> 00:48:40,487
That's all.

587
00:48:40,524 --> 00:48:42,515
Then we'll be on our way again.

588
00:48:47,464 --> 00:48:49,455
What's happened?

589
00:49:02,579 --> 00:49:04,479
Anyone home?

590
00:49:10,087 --> 00:49:12,612
- Pullo!
- Mascius.

591
00:49:13,624 --> 00:49:15,251
What's all this?

592
00:49:15,292 --> 00:49:18,750
Expecting visitors.
I never thought I'd see you again.

593
00:49:18,795 --> 00:49:20,558
Nor I you.

594
00:49:20,597 --> 00:49:23,930
Anyroad, it's good to have you home.
We need every man we can get.

595
00:49:23,967 --> 00:49:27,869
We're not stopping.
I just came to talk to Vorenus. Where is he?

596
00:49:27,904 --> 00:49:29,166
Well, he's not here.

597
00:49:29,206 --> 00:49:30,798
When is he back?

598
00:49:31,642 --> 00:49:34,475
I don't know. He's gone.
Went north with Mark Antony.

599
00:49:35,412 --> 00:49:37,607
- Went north?
- Months ago.

600
00:49:37,648 --> 00:49:40,540
Antony gathered his troops
and set off to take Gaul.

601
00:49:40,617 --> 00:49:44,280
Vorenus went with him.
Asked for special by Antony himself.

602
00:49:44,321 --> 00:49:46,846
He's left me in charge
of a right old mess.

603
00:49:46,890 --> 00:49:49,415
Ever since we gave Carbo
one up the arse,

604
00:49:49,459 --> 00:49:53,020
Caelian boys and their friends have been
going at us like Belgians.

605
00:49:53,063 --> 00:49:54,530
We lost ten men this month.

606
00:49:54,564 --> 00:49:57,260
- Come on, are you sure you're not stopping?
- What?

607
00:49:58,101 --> 00:50:00,433
No. I just came to talk to Vorenus.

608
00:50:12,849 --> 00:50:15,147
What now?

609
00:50:15,185 --> 00:50:16,846
I don't know.

610
00:50:17,821 --> 00:50:19,812
I don't understand it.

611
00:50:20,991 --> 00:50:23,380
The gods are playing tricks.

612
00:50:23,460 --> 00:50:26,361
"Go back to Rome," they say.
"Talk to Vorenus."

613
00:50:26,396 --> 00:50:28,296
Then they hide him from me.

614
00:50:32,035 --> 00:50:33,559
I did as I was told.

615
00:50:33,603 --> 00:50:35,860
If he's not here, he's not here.

616
00:50:35,939 --> 00:50:37,839
I can leave him a letter.

617
00:50:37,874 --> 00:50:40,809
"Dear Vorenus, I don't fuck your wife."

618
00:50:41,945 --> 00:50:43,412
Something like that.

619
00:50:48,585 --> 00:50:50,052
Let's be going.

620
00:50:52,289 --> 00:50:54,416
Best get out of Italy.

621
00:50:54,458 --> 00:50:56,585
A civil war is coming again, looks like.

622
00:50:57,127 --> 00:50:58,856
You people.

623
00:51:00,130 --> 00:51:02,189
Is this the way to Aventine...

624
00:51:04,534 --> 00:51:06,195
Pullo!

625
00:51:08,138 --> 00:51:10,003
Don't you know me?

626
00:51:10,040 --> 00:51:12,201
Lyde?

627
00:51:12,242 --> 00:51:13,539
Yes.

628
00:51:15,612 --> 00:51:18,410
I'm Lyde. I'm Lyde.

629
00:51:18,448 --> 00:51:20,973
But you're all right. You're all right.

630
00:51:21,017 --> 00:51:23,212
- Thank you.
- Where have you been?

631
00:51:23,253 --> 00:51:27,019
The children! The children are alive!

632
00:51:53,617 --> 00:51:55,448
Where's Octavia?

633
00:51:55,485 --> 00:51:57,510
Out with Jocasta.

634
00:51:59,823 --> 00:52:01,347
Excellent.

635
00:52:01,391 --> 00:52:04,588
I shall finally be able
to enjoy my dinner in peace.

636
00:52:42,999 --> 00:52:45,968
- What is this?
- Sea urchins, domina.

637
00:52:46,002 --> 00:52:48,129
I don't care for it. What else is there?

638
00:52:48,171 --> 00:52:51,197
A savory stew of goose
and root vegetables.

639
00:52:51,942 --> 00:52:53,933
Bring me that.

640
00:53:00,083 --> 00:53:01,641
Still here?

641
00:53:02,385 --> 00:53:04,216
Can't get enough of you, my love.

642
00:53:05,455 --> 00:53:07,082
Come here.

643
00:53:37,053 --> 00:53:38,543
Go on.

