1
00:01:37,703 --> 00:01:40,640
In the dawn of our history,

2
00:01:40,706 --> 00:01:44,540
we men of Rome were strong and fierce

3
00:01:44,576 --> 00:01:48,808
but also uncouth and solitary creatures.

4
00:01:48,847 --> 00:01:51,975
It was only when we acquired wives

5
00:01:52,084 --> 00:01:55,110
that our rise to greatness truly began.

6
00:01:55,988 --> 00:01:57,615
It is the women of Rome

7
00:01:57,656 --> 00:02:02,025
with their steely virtue and chaste morals

8
00:02:02,060 --> 00:02:04,688
who have conquered the world.

9
00:02:08,267 --> 00:02:10,531
It is by their virtuous light

10
00:02:10,569 --> 00:02:14,164
that we men have trod
the perilous paths of glory.

11
00:02:18,310 --> 00:02:20,870
It is the women of Rome

12
00:02:20,913 --> 00:02:22,840
who guarded hearth and home

13
00:02:22,915 --> 00:02:26,112
while we men burnt Carthage.

14
00:02:26,151 --> 00:02:27,743
It is the women of Rome,

15
00:02:27,786 --> 00:02:31,882
like the she-wolf that suckled
Romulus and Remus,

16
00:02:31,924 --> 00:02:35,724
who have raised a nation of wise statesmen

17
00:02:35,761 --> 00:02:39,219
and invincible warriors.

18
00:02:39,264 --> 00:02:42,062
And on behalf of we men,

19
00:02:42,100 --> 00:02:45,069
I take this moment to thank you all.

20
00:02:49,308 --> 00:02:51,276
When the time is right,

21
00:02:51,310 --> 00:02:53,039
I shall make sure that you women

22
00:02:53,145 --> 00:02:55,136
are rewarded for your virtue.

23
00:02:56,648 --> 00:02:59,617
In the future, I shall enact laws

24
00:02:59,651 --> 00:03:03,610
that reward fertility and sanctity in marriage.

25
00:03:04,156 --> 00:03:05,817
I shall enact laws

26
00:03:05,857 --> 00:03:07,916
that severely punish adultery,

27
00:03:07,960 --> 00:03:10,588
promiscuity

28
00:03:10,629 --> 00:03:13,996
and vice of all kinds.

29
00:03:18,737 --> 00:03:21,467
That's very good.
I shall remember that one.

30
00:03:21,506 --> 00:03:23,497
If you'll excuse me.

31
00:03:24,076 --> 00:03:25,304
What did you think?

32
00:03:25,344 --> 00:03:27,812
Your speech? Oh, strong stuff.

33
00:03:27,846 --> 00:03:30,007
Very amusing. They bought it wholesale.

34
00:03:30,048 --> 00:03:32,016
I mean every word.

35
00:03:32,050 --> 00:03:34,018
Yes, I really think you do.

36
00:03:34,052 --> 00:03:36,020
Myself, I suspect the women of old Rome

37
00:03:36,054 --> 00:03:38,386
were a parcel of whores and termagants.

38
00:03:38,423 --> 00:03:40,584
We shall agree to differ.

39
00:03:41,560 --> 00:03:44,393
There's the young piece
I was telling you about.

40
00:03:49,434 --> 00:03:51,360
She's very presentable.

41
00:03:51,436 --> 00:03:53,233
As ordered.
Impeccable family,

42
00:03:53,338 --> 00:03:56,160
young, healthy, proven fertility.

43
00:03:56,208 --> 00:03:58,699
- How many children?
- Just the one.

44
00:03:58,744 --> 00:04:01,212
A son, Tiberius.

45
00:04:03,015 --> 00:04:04,710
Introduce me.

46
00:04:12,090 --> 00:04:14,081
Caesar, may I present

47
00:04:14,126 --> 00:04:17,323
Alfidia and her daughter Livia?

48
00:04:17,362 --> 00:04:19,330
Honored.

49
00:04:21,066 --> 00:04:24,058
Tell me, how would you like
to be married to me?

50
00:04:30,776 --> 00:04:33,540
I would like that...

51
00:04:34,613 --> 00:04:36,638
if my husband does not object.

52
00:04:36,682 --> 00:04:39,651
- What is his name?
- Claudius Nero.

53
00:04:39,685 --> 00:04:42,711
I know the family.
They're good, patriotic people.

54
00:04:42,754 --> 00:04:46,212
- They will not say no to a divorce.
- I'm sure not, sir.

55
00:04:46,258 --> 00:04:48,226
Excellent.

56
00:04:48,260 --> 00:04:50,228
See to the details.

57
00:04:54,199 --> 00:04:56,167
She'll do nicely.

58
00:04:56,201 --> 00:04:59,932
Now that other business before
I dive back into this female swamp.

59
00:04:59,971 --> 00:05:02,997
Herod's gold is offshore at Ostia
waiting on the high tide.

60
00:05:03,041 --> 00:05:06,807
I've been liaising with Antony's man, Posca,
on the details of delivery.

61
00:05:06,845 --> 00:05:09,973
We wanted to use the Aventine collegium
for transportation,

62
00:05:10,015 --> 00:05:11,607
if you are agreeable.

63
00:05:11,650 --> 00:05:13,049
It's a good idea.

64
00:05:13,085 --> 00:05:17,385
They have men allied both to myself
and to Mark Antony. That's good.

65
00:05:17,422 --> 00:05:21,654
Make sure the entire business is invisible.
I want complete deniability.

66
00:05:21,693 --> 00:05:23,490
If the bribe comes to light,

67
00:05:23,528 --> 00:05:25,689
it must be Antony's fault alone.

68
00:05:29,401 --> 00:05:31,760
Papa, when we get to Jerusalem,

69
00:05:31,837 --> 00:05:33,760
will Uncle Levi be there?

70
00:05:33,839 --> 00:05:36,774
Maybe. Maybe not.

71
00:05:36,808 --> 00:05:39,208
Remember when we first met?

72
00:05:39,244 --> 00:05:41,940
- Your cousin's house.
- Yes.

73
00:05:41,980 --> 00:05:43,607
I saw you and I thought,

74
00:05:43,648 --> 00:05:47,243
"There. There is a good man for me.

75
00:05:47,285 --> 00:05:51,654
"Maybe not such a nice dresser
as I would like, but a good man."

76
00:05:51,690 --> 00:05:54,250
It's been many years now,

77
00:05:54,359 --> 00:05:56,680
and you have never proved me wrong.

78
00:05:56,728 --> 00:05:58,719
Papa, are we there yet?

79
00:06:00,732 --> 00:06:04,498
It's gorgeous. I can have it?

80
00:06:04,536 --> 00:06:06,527
Anything you like, my love.

81
00:06:06,571 --> 00:06:09,438
My little caramel.

82
00:06:09,474 --> 00:06:11,806
Why don't you...

83
00:06:11,843 --> 00:06:14,971
go inside and see...

84
00:06:15,013 --> 00:06:18,312
if there's anything else you like?

85
00:06:18,350 --> 00:06:20,875
How good you are to me.

86
00:06:22,320 --> 00:06:24,481
Off you go.

87
00:06:26,424 --> 00:06:28,415
Take your time.

88
00:06:37,169 --> 00:06:41,071
You might have chosen
a less conspicuous conveyance.

89
00:06:41,106 --> 00:06:44,769
This is my third-best litter.
You are nondescript enough for both of us.

90
00:06:48,079 --> 00:06:51,515
Has the... has the Judean shipment
arrived yet?

91
00:06:52,784 --> 00:06:56,311
You needn't worry about them.
They don't understand a word we say.

92
00:06:56,354 --> 00:06:57,685
Do you, my darlings?

93
00:06:57,722 --> 00:07:01,021
The lower orders understand
more than you think.

94
00:07:15,841 --> 00:07:17,775
Really, you are too absurd.

95
00:07:17,809 --> 00:07:20,200
We are stealing from our own chiefs.

96
00:07:20,278 --> 00:07:23,270
No precaution we take is too absurd.

97
00:07:23,315 --> 00:07:26,978
I wouldn't call it stealing.
It is a commission for services rendered.

98
00:07:27,018 --> 00:07:30,954
- They won't even notice the shortfall.
- Don't fool yourself!

99
00:07:30,989 --> 00:07:32,456
We are thieves.

100
00:07:32,490 --> 00:07:34,481
If Antony or Octavian discover it,

101
00:07:34,526 --> 00:07:36,221
we shall both die!

102
00:07:36,261 --> 00:07:38,252
They won't discover it.

103
00:07:41,366 --> 00:07:43,561
Where and when shall we extract our share?

104
00:07:44,502 --> 00:07:48,598
The Aventine men will make delivery
to the Temple of Saturn by night.

105
00:07:48,640 --> 00:07:51,438
You and I will be alone with the gold until day.

106
00:07:51,476 --> 00:07:54,206
Bring slaves you trust.

107
00:07:56,314 --> 00:07:59,340
- Oh, hello, Maecenas.
- Jocasta.

108
00:07:59,384 --> 00:08:02,478
Why on earth do you travel
in such a garish litter?

109
00:08:02,520 --> 00:08:05,751
I thought sure
my husband was intriguing with an actress

110
00:08:05,790 --> 00:08:07,883
or some such trollop.

111
00:08:09,494 --> 00:08:10,756
How amusing.

112
00:08:10,795 --> 00:08:12,990
So where are we going?

113
00:08:13,031 --> 00:08:16,467
The gold will be in Ostia tomorrow,
Argosy docks.

114
00:08:16,501 --> 00:08:20,062
The ship's name, Triton's Crown.

115
00:08:20,105 --> 00:08:21,902
We take it from there.

116
00:08:21,940 --> 00:08:23,874
By river or road?

117
00:08:23,909 --> 00:08:27,003
I'm told Octavian and Antony's men
will take it by river.

118
00:08:27,045 --> 00:08:29,809
So we'll take it by road,

119
00:08:29,848 --> 00:08:31,713
avoid any leaks their end.

120
00:08:31,750 --> 00:08:33,718
Clever.

121
00:08:33,752 --> 00:08:35,549
No one,

122
00:08:35,587 --> 00:08:37,919
no one must know what the shipment contains.

123
00:08:37,956 --> 00:08:40,015
Secrecy is essential.

124
00:08:40,058 --> 00:08:42,583
I'll use Rasca and his boys. They're reliable.

125
00:08:42,627 --> 00:08:45,323
- They don't ask questions.
- Good.

126
00:08:45,363 --> 00:08:49,424
But Pullo's gonna handle this, not you.

127
00:08:49,467 --> 00:08:51,196
I always handle Ostian business.

128
00:08:51,236 --> 00:08:53,204
This is different.

129
00:08:53,305 --> 00:08:54,966
You don't trust me, is it?

130
00:08:56,241 --> 00:08:59,768
I trust you.
Octavian and Antony, they both know Pullo.

131
00:08:59,811 --> 00:09:02,473
They trust him.

132
00:09:02,514 --> 00:09:05,711
Anything should go wrong,
it won't come back at us.

133
00:09:05,750 --> 00:09:09,015
It's all right. I understand.

134
00:09:09,054 --> 00:09:11,045
Third fucking man.

135
00:09:32,444 --> 00:09:34,435
Your tea, Domina.

136
00:10:05,410 --> 00:10:08,208
Help! Help!

137
00:10:08,246 --> 00:10:10,840
Help! Help, somebody!

138
00:10:10,882 --> 00:10:12,713
Help!

139
00:10:12,751 --> 00:10:16,278
Get a doctor! Get a doctor! It's Eirene!

140
00:10:16,321 --> 00:10:19,654
There's blood. There's blood!

141
00:10:44,549 --> 00:10:47,382
She'll put you right.
No trouble.

142
00:10:48,219 --> 00:10:49,880
I don't think.

143
00:10:49,921 --> 00:10:51,650
She will.

144
00:10:51,689 --> 00:10:54,180
Please, no burning.

145
00:10:54,292 --> 00:10:56,760
In my country we are buried.

146
00:10:57,962 --> 00:10:59,793
Don't talk like that.

147
00:10:59,831 --> 00:11:01,458
No burning.

148
00:11:01,499 --> 00:11:04,434
Put me in a black shroud...

149
00:11:06,204 --> 00:11:10,300
and bury me in an open field.

150
00:11:10,341 --> 00:11:13,435
No trees. No trees.

151
00:11:13,478 --> 00:11:15,810
You are not dying.

152
00:11:15,847 --> 00:11:19,305
- Promise me.
- I'll not promise anything. You are not dying.

153
00:11:19,350 --> 00:11:22,547
Promise me.

154
00:11:22,587 --> 00:11:25,784
When you're old and gray,

155
00:11:25,824 --> 00:11:29,316
I promise I'll bury you.

156
00:11:29,360 --> 00:11:32,921
If I'm still around.
You'll be onto your second husband by then.

157
00:11:32,964 --> 00:11:35,728
The baby...

158
00:11:35,767 --> 00:11:38,395
Was it a boy or a girl?

159
00:11:39,604 --> 00:11:41,595
A boy.

160
00:11:45,210 --> 00:11:47,405
Bury him with me.

161
00:11:51,182 --> 00:11:53,707
Don't be sad.

162
00:11:53,818 --> 00:11:56,878
You make me cry.

163
00:12:33,725 --> 00:12:35,693
You gods that might know this woman

164
00:12:35,727 --> 00:12:37,820
as one of your own,

165
00:12:37,862 --> 00:12:39,659
please listen to me.

166
00:12:40,965 --> 00:12:43,433
We here call her Eirene,

167
00:12:43,468 --> 00:12:46,335
but she was called Adela
where she came from,

168
00:12:46,371 --> 00:12:48,862
somewhere beyond the Rhine,

169
00:12:48,907 --> 00:12:51,307
not sure exactly where.

170
00:12:51,342 --> 00:12:54,277
Anyway, you'll know her.

171
00:12:54,379 --> 00:12:56,760
She was a good woman.

172
00:12:56,814 --> 00:13:00,079
She always spoke very highly of you.

173
00:13:00,118 --> 00:13:04,578
So please look after her

174
00:13:04,622 --> 00:13:06,283
and our boy.

175
00:13:11,563 --> 00:13:13,758
My name is Titus Pullo,

176
00:13:13,798 --> 00:13:15,993
ex-13th Legion,

177
00:13:17,168 --> 00:13:19,068
her husband.

178
00:13:19,103 --> 00:13:22,129
Wasn't always as good to her
as I should have been.

179
00:13:22,173 --> 00:13:26,371
I give my life to you to use as you like,

180
00:13:26,411 --> 00:13:29,312
if you'll see that she's happy now.

181
00:14:12,624 --> 00:14:14,990
It's Mascius, sir. There's trouble.

182
00:14:15,026 --> 00:14:16,323
Go on.

183
00:14:23,101 --> 00:14:24,762
Be still, Mascius. Be still.

184
00:14:24,802 --> 00:14:27,794
Careful, you bastard. I'm not poultry.

185
00:14:27,839 --> 00:14:30,103
- What happened?
- Ambush...

186
00:14:32,477 --> 00:14:34,274
Just before we got to the Ostian Gate.

187
00:14:51,829 --> 00:14:53,720
All but me and him are dead.

188
00:14:53,798 --> 00:14:56,198
- The gold.
- It's gone.

189
00:15:04,375 --> 00:15:06,800
Do you have any idea
who it was attacked you?

190
00:15:06,878 --> 00:15:09,642
No. They were good, though.

191
00:15:09,681 --> 00:15:11,672
They didn't give us a chance.

192
00:15:12,684 --> 00:15:14,440
And brother,

193
00:15:14,519 --> 00:15:17,044
they were waiting for us.

194
00:15:18,656 --> 00:15:20,886
All right.

195
00:15:24,862 --> 00:15:27,524
Call on every man.
Tell them to cover the city.

196
00:15:27,565 --> 00:15:30,830
Pay coin, give torture, kill if necessary.

197
00:15:30,868 --> 00:15:33,098
Find out who did this.

198
00:15:33,137 --> 00:15:37,096
You, sit with Pullo.
Make sure he has everything he needs.

199
00:15:38,776 --> 00:15:41,540
I've men out all over the city looking into it.

200
00:15:41,579 --> 00:15:46,175
We'll find out who's responsible soon.
You can't keep a thing like this quiet.

201
00:15:46,217 --> 00:15:49,653
For a man who has lost his masters a fortune,
you show little shame.

202
00:15:49,687 --> 00:15:53,020
I took all proper precaution.
I used my best men.

203
00:15:53,124 --> 00:15:54,955
You used Titus Pullo?

204
00:15:56,294 --> 00:15:58,228
No.

205
00:15:58,262 --> 00:16:00,560
Why? He is your best man.

206
00:16:01,332 --> 00:16:05,166
His wife died in childbirth yesterday,
so I used another man.

207
00:16:05,203 --> 00:16:08,104
I see. I see.

208
00:16:09,374 --> 00:16:10,705
Well...

209
00:16:11,275 --> 00:16:13,300
Very convenient.

210
00:16:14,045 --> 00:16:17,708
- I do not take your meaning.
- The one man we know Octavian can trust

211
00:16:17,749 --> 00:16:21,185
is replaced at the last minute
by who knows who?

212
00:16:21,219 --> 00:16:22,709
That's very convenient.

213
00:16:22,754 --> 00:16:26,087
Are you accusing me of being involved in this?

214
00:16:26,124 --> 00:16:28,217
I could just as easily accuse you.

215
00:16:30,528 --> 00:16:32,587
- Or Lepidus.
- That's ridiculous.

216
00:16:32,630 --> 00:16:34,689
No one is accusing anyone.

217
00:16:34,732 --> 00:16:37,257
Could it be that one of
your own men betrayed you?

218
00:16:37,301 --> 00:16:40,031
Anything is possible, but I doubt it.

219
00:16:40,071 --> 00:16:41,595
Why?

220
00:16:41,639 --> 00:16:43,698
They are scared of me.

221
00:16:43,741 --> 00:16:46,039
- Then who?
- Good question.

222
00:16:46,077 --> 00:16:48,602
If not one of my men, then who?

223
00:16:48,646 --> 00:16:51,410
Do not lay the blame elsewhere.

224
00:16:51,449 --> 00:16:53,713
You had custody of our property.

225
00:16:53,818 --> 00:16:55,480
Its loss is your responsibility.

226
00:16:55,520 --> 00:16:58,489
I understand.
I will find your property and bring it back.

227
00:16:58,523 --> 00:17:00,491
Be sure that you do.

228
00:17:02,026 --> 00:17:04,551
You know the consequences of failure.

229
00:17:09,000 --> 00:17:11,468
I'll tell you who it was.

230
00:17:13,404 --> 00:17:14,894
Gauls.

231
00:17:17,008 --> 00:17:19,203
I'll wager any amount of money it was Gauls.

232
00:17:19,744 --> 00:17:21,735
They breed like rabbits, you know.

233
00:17:21,779 --> 00:17:24,577
No notion of working for a living.

234
00:17:24,615 --> 00:17:27,209
Thieves, the lot of them.

235
00:17:40,932 --> 00:17:43,059
I know it was you.

236
00:17:43,100 --> 00:17:45,091
I know.

237
00:17:45,136 --> 00:17:47,070
You and Antony double-crossed me.

238
00:17:47,104 --> 00:17:49,504
- I assure you...
- No, no, no.

239
00:17:49,540 --> 00:17:51,508
I assure you,

240
00:17:51,542 --> 00:17:53,305
you'll both pay.

241
00:18:18,302 --> 00:18:21,635
Brother Vorenus. Welcome, sit.

242
00:18:21,672 --> 00:18:25,369
Have some wine.
Make a way for the captain, boys.

243
00:18:26,544 --> 00:18:28,478
Come alone?

244
00:18:29,113 --> 00:18:32,207
You celebrating something?

245
00:18:32,250 --> 00:18:35,481
No, we're just happy sort of people.

246
00:18:36,120 --> 00:18:39,453
Property in my charge was stolen
on the Ostia Way last night.

247
00:18:39,490 --> 00:18:42,550
- Oh, dear. What sort of property?
- Belonging to the state.

248
00:18:42,593 --> 00:18:46,586
That's not good.
Peeved, I'll bet, the quality.

249
00:18:46,631 --> 00:18:49,361
- They are.
- Wasn't us, was it?

250
00:18:49,400 --> 00:18:51,425
With state property? Us?

251
00:18:51,469 --> 00:18:53,733
No, we wouldn't dare.

252
00:18:53,838 --> 00:18:56,080
No, wasn't us.

253
00:18:56,140 --> 00:18:58,802
I didn't say it was.

254
00:18:58,843 --> 00:19:00,834
Just a social visit, then?

255
00:19:01,913 --> 00:19:05,349
If you happen to hear
who it was did this,

256
00:19:05,383 --> 00:19:07,578
- I'm sure you'll tell me.
- Certainly.

257
00:19:07,618 --> 00:19:12,681
Can't have people robbing a fellow captain.
It's humiliating. It makes us all look bad.

258
00:19:12,723 --> 00:19:15,080
What was it exactly, this state property?

259
00:19:15,159 --> 00:19:17,218
That doesn't matter.

260
00:19:17,261 --> 00:19:19,889
Can't help if we don't know
what we're looking for.

261
00:19:22,233 --> 00:19:23,530
You're right.

262
00:19:23,568 --> 00:19:26,537
Never mind. You've helped more
than enough already.

263
00:19:26,571 --> 00:19:29,870
Thank you, Memmio.
I will see you again soon.

264
00:19:29,907 --> 00:19:31,738
Always a pleasure.

265
00:19:34,078 --> 00:19:37,514
My advice - look to your own people.

266
00:19:37,548 --> 00:19:41,211
This kind of affair
is nearly always someone close.

267
00:19:51,596 --> 00:19:55,657
Go tell Cotta, Acerbo, and the other captains
I need to see them today.

268
00:19:55,700 --> 00:19:58,328
- Acerbo?
- You heard me.

269
00:20:05,376 --> 00:20:08,573
- I wish you took this seriously.
- These things happen.

270
00:20:08,613 --> 00:20:11,514
- It's a great deal of money.
- More money will come.

271
00:20:11,549 --> 00:20:14,143
A thousand rich dukes and satraps
want to be kings.

272
00:20:14,185 --> 00:20:17,348
But you were robbed
as if you were some petty grocer.

273
00:20:17,388 --> 00:20:20,289
Tell me, why do you
take such personal offense at this?

274
00:20:20,324 --> 00:20:22,986
It is a gross personal insult to you.

275
00:20:23,027 --> 00:20:25,860
Someone is always insulting me.
It's the price of fame.

276
00:20:25,896 --> 00:20:29,127
Mark Antony
is your colleague and brother-in-law.

277
00:20:29,166 --> 00:20:33,227
If you have proof that Mark Antony
is responsible, tell me.

278
00:20:33,270 --> 00:20:35,431
Who else knew of the shipment?

279
00:20:35,473 --> 00:20:38,670
- Lepidus?
- Very possibly. It's likely it was an accident.

280
00:20:38,709 --> 00:20:40,973
There are no accidents. It was Antony.

281
00:20:41,012 --> 00:20:43,572
Since we reconciled,
he has been just and honest.

282
00:20:43,614 --> 00:20:46,549
I won't jeopardize our alliance
because you dislike him.

283
00:20:46,584 --> 00:20:49,678
I know for a fact he's been
neither just nor honest with you.

284
00:20:49,720 --> 00:20:51,688
He's been making a fool of you.

285
00:20:53,457 --> 00:20:55,220
What do you mean?

286
00:20:55,259 --> 00:20:59,389
Forgive me, I thought it best not to tell you.
Your alliance, the wellbeing of the republic...

287
00:20:59,430 --> 00:21:01,193
Speak!

288
00:21:03,300 --> 00:21:05,632
Antony's marriage to your sister is a sham.

289
00:21:05,670 --> 00:21:08,138
He's been bedding your mother as before.

290
00:21:08,172 --> 00:21:12,506
That's impossible. Antony would not dare
disrespect me like that, and Octavia...

291
00:21:12,543 --> 00:21:14,841
Octavia would have told me.

292
00:21:16,514 --> 00:21:19,005
She has her own reasons for keeping silent.

293
00:21:24,989 --> 00:21:28,220
Domina, your son summons you

294
00:21:28,259 --> 00:21:29,954
to dinner this evening.

295
00:21:29,994 --> 00:21:31,894
Tell him no. I am going to the theater.

296
00:21:31,929 --> 00:21:35,092
He says it's important.
Attendance is compulsory.

297
00:21:35,132 --> 00:21:37,600
He's getting more and more officious.

298
00:21:41,172 --> 00:21:42,662
Who else is coming?

299
00:21:42,707 --> 00:21:44,698
Just family.

300
00:21:49,980 --> 00:21:52,141
Thank you all for coming so promptly.

301
00:21:52,249 --> 00:21:54,240
I have urgent business to discuss.

302
00:21:54,285 --> 00:21:57,118
- With these?
- Patience, Cotta.

303
00:21:57,154 --> 00:22:00,555
- You'll like what I have to say.
- Giving half price on olive oil?

304
00:22:00,591 --> 00:22:05,358
No. Rather, I was thinking
of getting deeper into the grain trade.

305
00:22:08,766 --> 00:22:11,564
Things with brother Vorenus
are coming to a head.

306
00:22:11,602 --> 00:22:15,561
I'm thinking it's time
to put an end to his arrogance.

307
00:22:15,606 --> 00:22:17,972
So it was you.

308
00:22:19,744 --> 00:22:21,974
- You took his gold.
- What gold is that?

309
00:22:22,012 --> 00:22:25,504
The gold every beggar in the city
is talking about. It was you.

310
00:22:25,549 --> 00:22:28,677
Might have been. I don't say that it was
but it might have been.

311
00:22:28,719 --> 00:22:31,381
- And you kept it from me?
- Kept what from you?

312
00:22:31,422 --> 00:22:33,549
- Don't joke with me.
- You took his gold?

313
00:22:33,591 --> 00:22:35,286
Vorenus thinks I did.

314
00:22:38,996 --> 00:22:41,794
So he's after your head
on a stick and you're scared.

315
00:22:41,832 --> 00:22:45,529
- What's that to us?
- No one can handle the Aventine on their own.

316
00:22:45,569 --> 00:22:49,505
But if all of us were to cooperate,
like the brothers we are, different story.

317
00:22:49,540 --> 00:22:50,871
- Story!
- We'll crush them.

318
00:22:50,908 --> 00:22:54,435
The Aventine will be ours.
The grain trade will be ours.

319
00:22:54,545 --> 00:22:56,843
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.

320
00:23:01,485 --> 00:23:04,921
I don't expect you to help me
out of brotherly love.

321
00:23:20,671 --> 00:23:22,605
That's it, boys.

322
00:23:22,640 --> 00:23:25,000
That's what you want, isn't it?

323
00:23:25,075 --> 00:23:28,306
Yes! Pick it up!

324
00:23:28,345 --> 00:23:30,472
Missed a bit there. Look.

325
00:23:30,514 --> 00:23:33,005
That's what you want, a bit more!

326
00:23:33,050 --> 00:23:36,645
Here it comes. More! More!

327
00:23:36,687 --> 00:23:40,589
That's right! Now, pick it up.

328
00:23:55,372 --> 00:23:59,536
Forgive me.
I unnerve you with my silence.

329
00:24:00,611 --> 00:24:02,374
No, sir.

330
00:24:06,483 --> 00:24:08,474
What small hands you have.

331
00:24:10,054 --> 00:24:12,522
- So dry.
- Thank you.

332
00:24:16,393 --> 00:24:18,827
Tell me, does your husband ever beat you?

333
00:24:18,863 --> 00:24:20,626
No, sir.

334
00:24:20,664 --> 00:24:23,656
I hope I have never given him reason to do so.

335
00:24:25,102 --> 00:24:28,503
- Your father, perhaps?
- No, sir.

336
00:24:28,539 --> 00:24:31,872
A virtuous woman.
Good. That is good.

337
00:24:35,913 --> 00:24:40,873
You should know that when we are married,
I shall, on occasion, beat you,

338
00:24:40,918 --> 00:24:44,877
with my hand or a light whip.

339
00:24:44,922 --> 00:24:47,186
When I do, do not think you have offended me.

340
00:24:47,224 --> 00:24:49,624
I do it because it gives me sexual pleasure.

341
00:24:52,062 --> 00:24:54,826
You must remember that and not be upset.

342
00:24:54,865 --> 00:24:56,799
Yes, sir.

343
00:25:04,375 --> 00:25:06,605
I think we shall get along very well.

344
00:25:07,811 --> 00:25:10,109
They're all here.

345
00:25:22,593 --> 00:25:24,618
About time.

346
00:25:24,662 --> 00:25:27,153
Any news from Lucius Vorenus?

347
00:25:27,197 --> 00:25:30,530
- No.
- Strange.

348
00:25:30,567 --> 00:25:34,298
We must be patient. Vorenus always does
what he says he'll do.

349
00:25:34,805 --> 00:25:37,672
- I am glad you think so.
- And who is this sweet creature?

350
00:25:37,708 --> 00:25:41,109
This is Livia, daughter of Livius
Drusus Claudianus.

351
00:25:41,145 --> 00:25:46,947
- I'm going to marry her.
- How nice. Welcome to the family.

352
00:25:46,984 --> 00:25:50,215
Thank you. I am glad to make
your acquaintance.

353
00:25:50,254 --> 00:25:53,155
And this must be my sister Octavia.

354
00:25:53,257 --> 00:25:55,316
Such a lovely complexion she has.

355
00:25:55,359 --> 00:25:57,259
What a furtive person you are.

356
00:25:57,294 --> 00:25:59,592
I had no inkling you were looking to marry.

357
00:25:59,630 --> 00:26:00,756
I wanted her to be here

358
00:26:00,798 --> 00:26:04,598
so she would properly understand
what it means to be a part of this family.

359
00:26:04,635 --> 00:26:06,762
It's a species of benign slavery.

360
00:26:06,804 --> 00:26:08,601
Slavery, is it?

361
00:26:10,140 --> 00:26:13,303
Well, you fancy yourself
a Spartacus then, do you?

362
00:26:13,344 --> 00:26:15,600
- I don't follow.
- I am master of this family,

363
00:26:15,679 --> 00:26:17,476
and you have rebelled against me.

364
00:26:17,514 --> 00:26:22,110
- I wish I had such courage.
- You are courageous enough. I was surprised.

365
00:26:22,152 --> 00:26:25,178
I knew Mother had the stomach
for any kind of depravity,

366
00:26:25,222 --> 00:26:27,520
but you, I was surprised.

367
00:26:27,558 --> 00:26:30,959
I have shown you nothing but love
and you repay me with treachery.

368
00:26:30,995 --> 00:26:33,589
Remember, colleague,

369
00:26:33,630 --> 00:26:37,361
- you are talking to my wife.
- Your wife in name only.

370
00:26:37,401 --> 00:26:40,666
It is still Mother that performs the wifely
function, is it not?

371
00:26:40,704 --> 00:26:44,504
While Octavia does the same
for my good friend Agrippa.

372
00:26:44,541 --> 00:26:46,873
That's very convenient for all involved.

373
00:26:46,910 --> 00:26:49,378
- What are you getting at?
- Do you deny it?

374
00:26:49,413 --> 00:26:52,905
- I'll not be interrogated by you!
- Do you deny it?

375
00:26:53,017 --> 00:26:55,720
Fuck your little girl
and leave my business to me!

376
00:26:55,786 --> 00:26:58,050
- Do you deny it?
- It's true.

377
00:27:01,725 --> 00:27:04,353
I'll not deny it.

378
00:27:05,062 --> 00:27:07,053
I love your sister.

379
00:27:07,998 --> 00:27:10,592
We have been meeting
in secret for some time now.

380
00:27:14,004 --> 00:27:15,760
But I cannot answer for Antony.

381
00:27:15,839 --> 00:27:18,364
Thank you.
Thank you for being honest with me.

382
00:27:19,276 --> 00:27:23,440
So what? What if it is true?
What are you gonna do about it?

383
00:27:23,480 --> 00:27:25,840
There is nothing you can do about it.

384
00:27:25,916 --> 00:27:28,384
I shall send my women to their house,

385
00:27:28,419 --> 00:27:31,013
where they shall remain
in seclusion under guard

386
00:27:31,055 --> 00:27:33,046
- until I say so.
- I'll do no such thing!

387
00:27:33,090 --> 00:27:35,354
Silence.

388
00:27:35,392 --> 00:27:37,724
You, you shall leave this city.

389
00:27:37,761 --> 00:27:40,958
- Leave this city?
- You shall go east to your provinces

390
00:27:40,998 --> 00:27:44,490
- and you shall not come back.
- Or else what, boy?

391
00:27:44,535 --> 00:27:47,368
Leave this city,
or I declare our alliance is broken.

392
00:27:47,404 --> 00:27:49,770
I shall have this sad story told in the Forum.

393
00:27:49,807 --> 00:27:52,708
I will have it posted in every city in Italy.

394
00:27:52,810 --> 00:27:56,720
And you know, the people
are not so liberal with their wives as you are.

395
00:27:56,780 --> 00:27:58,805
They will say you wear cuckold's horns.

396
00:27:58,849 --> 00:28:02,808
They will say your wife betrayed you
with a lowborn pleb on my staff.

397
00:28:02,853 --> 00:28:06,084
You will be a figure of fun.

398
00:28:06,123 --> 00:28:08,614
The proles will laugh at you in the street.

399
00:28:08,659 --> 00:28:12,254
Your soldiers will mock you behind your back.

400
00:28:24,475 --> 00:28:27,603
Go on. Strike me.

401
00:28:27,644 --> 00:28:29,475
See what happens.

402
00:28:54,938 --> 00:28:56,838
Oh, and Antony,

403
00:28:56,874 --> 00:28:59,843
if you find that gold,
you'll be sure to tell me, won't you?

404
00:29:04,148 --> 00:29:08,983
- You would disgrace your own sister?
- She has disgraced herself.

405
00:29:10,787 --> 00:29:13,119
It was nice to meet you.

406
00:29:13,157 --> 00:29:15,148
Take care.

407
00:29:15,192 --> 00:29:16,853
You're marrying a monster.

408
00:29:31,575 --> 00:29:33,805
Take them home. Take guards with you.

409
00:29:33,844 --> 00:29:37,075
Make sure they get home... safely.

410
00:29:41,518 --> 00:29:43,247
It was you who told him, wasn't it?

411
00:29:43,287 --> 00:29:45,346
I always knew you were a weasel.

412
00:29:45,389 --> 00:29:48,586
I wish I could apologize,
madam, but it was my duty.

413
00:29:48,625 --> 00:29:53,187
You've done your master a terrible disservice.
Now he has no family at all.

414
00:29:57,935 --> 00:29:59,835
Maecenas.

415
00:30:02,206 --> 00:30:04,834
Do not blame him.
He did what he thought was right.

416
00:30:04,875 --> 00:30:07,800
- I do not think you can say the same.
- For which I apologize.

417
00:30:07,878 --> 00:30:10,346
But do not let Octavia suffer for my sins.

418
00:30:11,882 --> 00:30:14,240
The fault is mine.

419
00:30:14,318 --> 00:30:16,878
It was I seduced her.

420
00:30:16,920 --> 00:30:19,980
You have many talents, Agrippa.

421
00:30:20,023 --> 00:30:22,548
Seduction is not one of them.

422
00:30:22,593 --> 00:30:24,925
She does not deserve your cruelty.

423
00:30:24,962 --> 00:30:27,954
- She's not...
- I've stated my intentions.

424
00:30:27,998 --> 00:30:29,693
You will not be banished. I need you.

425
00:30:29,733 --> 00:30:34,193
Besides, your sudden disappearance
would suggest some sort of scandal.

426
00:30:36,473 --> 00:30:38,134
I thank you.

427
00:30:38,175 --> 00:30:39,699
You can go.

428
00:30:48,185 --> 00:30:50,050
Try one of the stuffed songbirds.

429
00:30:50,087 --> 00:30:52,555
My cook does them particularly well.

430
00:31:14,511 --> 00:31:16,240
Has he eaten?

431
00:31:17,347 --> 00:31:18,712
Water?

432
00:31:23,587 --> 00:31:26,021
Pullo.

433
00:31:26,056 --> 00:31:29,880
Pullo, you've had no water in two days.
You need to drink something.

434
00:31:29,960 --> 00:31:32,827
Mascius looked in. Cut up nasty.

435
00:31:32,863 --> 00:31:34,091
Drink.

436
00:31:36,433 --> 00:31:38,526
Gold got stolen, did it?

437
00:31:40,037 --> 00:31:43,336
All but Mascius and Zeno are dead.

438
00:31:43,373 --> 00:31:46,501
Don't you worry about it.

439
00:31:46,543 --> 00:31:49,569
I'll... I'll get it back.

440
00:31:49,613 --> 00:31:50,944
Memmio?

441
00:31:52,082 --> 00:31:54,414
Looks like. I went to see him.

442
00:31:54,451 --> 00:31:58,888
He had guilt written on his face very plain.

443
00:31:58,922 --> 00:32:00,355
Who told him?

444
00:32:00,390 --> 00:32:03,223
He as good as said
it was one of my own people.

445
00:32:05,095 --> 00:32:06,687
Mascius.

446
00:32:07,798 --> 00:32:09,698
- He's not been happy.
- And he lived.

447
00:32:09,733 --> 00:32:12,258
Still, he's always been loyal.

448
00:32:12,302 --> 00:32:14,930
Never had to doubt him before.

449
00:32:18,942 --> 00:32:21,934
No one's a traitor until they are.

450
00:32:21,978 --> 00:32:23,969
Pullo, where are you going?

451
00:32:42,833 --> 00:32:44,266
Mascius.

452
00:32:48,372 --> 00:32:50,533
All right, Pullo.

453
00:32:50,574 --> 00:32:52,474
Boss.

454
00:32:53,577 --> 00:32:55,568
How are you feeling?

455
00:32:56,480 --> 00:32:59,278
Not so bad. I was lucky.

456
00:32:59,950 --> 00:33:01,679
Very lucky.

457
00:33:03,019 --> 00:33:04,043
No word yet?

458
00:33:04,721 --> 00:33:06,245
Give it back!

459
00:33:06,289 --> 00:33:10,020
- Give it!
- Children, quiet.

460
00:33:13,563 --> 00:33:17,124
The only thing I can think of is maybe...

461
00:33:17,167 --> 00:33:20,398
Maybe one of Octavian
or Antony's men set it all up.

462
00:33:20,437 --> 00:33:24,373
Couldn't be. They thought we'd go by river.
Didn't know we'd use the road.

463
00:33:24,408 --> 00:33:26,103
True.

464
00:33:26,143 --> 00:33:29,078
Memmio said that we should
look to one of our own.

465
00:33:31,148 --> 00:33:32,740
Listen...

466
00:33:34,384 --> 00:33:35,942
brother,

467
00:33:35,986 --> 00:33:37,851
our lives are on the line.

468
00:33:37,888 --> 00:33:40,220
You wanted the responsibility.

469
00:33:40,257 --> 00:33:42,817
- We just want some answers.
- It had to be you.

470
00:33:42,859 --> 00:33:45,487
You're joking. You think I did this myself?

471
00:33:45,529 --> 00:33:49,659
Mascius, the only people who knew
what the plan was was we three here.

472
00:33:49,699 --> 00:33:51,599
Third fucking man.

473
00:33:51,635 --> 00:33:55,071
- It wasn't me.
- Give it back!

474
00:33:55,172 --> 00:33:57,470
Give me that. Get out of here.

475
00:33:58,975 --> 00:34:01,000
Don't come back in here.

476
00:34:03,380 --> 00:34:04,972
Just tell the truth.

477
00:34:16,393 --> 00:34:17,826
I'm sorry, brother.

478
00:34:17,861 --> 00:34:21,627
Near on 20 years marching together,
you boys and me.

479
00:34:22,866 --> 00:34:26,358
- Tell the truth.
- The truth?

480
00:34:26,403 --> 00:34:29,702
The truth is I have known you as a brother.

481
00:34:29,739 --> 00:34:32,333
The truth is I saved your life at Gergovia.

482
00:34:32,375 --> 00:34:34,775
Took an arrow for it.

483
00:34:34,811 --> 00:34:37,177
Arrow's still in there.

484
00:34:37,214 --> 00:34:40,945
The truth is I'd do it again, brother.

485
00:34:40,984 --> 00:34:45,978
The truth is I've been nothing but
a good soldier and a good fucking friend.

486
00:34:46,022 --> 00:34:47,853
You do what you have to do, brother.

487
00:34:52,162 --> 00:34:54,153
See you in Hades.

488
00:34:56,333 --> 00:34:59,496
- Where's the gold?
- Pullo! Lucius!

489
00:34:59,536 --> 00:35:00,662
- What?
- Lucius!

490
00:35:03,173 --> 00:35:05,641
Where did you get this?

491
00:35:13,783 --> 00:35:15,751
Father.

492
00:35:17,220 --> 00:35:18,983
Father, stop it.

493
00:35:19,022 --> 00:35:20,717
Stop it!

494
00:35:20,757 --> 00:35:23,089
Stop it! What are you doing? Stop it!

495
00:35:23,126 --> 00:35:25,060
Father! Stop it!

496
00:35:36,940 --> 00:35:39,431
- Where'd you get these?
- I bought them.

497
00:35:39,476 --> 00:35:41,410
Don't you lie to me.

498
00:35:41,444 --> 00:35:42,706
I did.

499
00:35:42,746 --> 00:35:44,640
One of Memmio's men gave them to you.

500
00:35:44,714 --> 00:35:46,511
- Didn't he?
- No, I don't know...

501
00:35:46,550 --> 00:35:48,415
- Don't you lie to me.
- I'm not lying.

502
00:35:52,789 --> 00:35:55,781
You get back here.
Get back here!

503
00:35:59,229 --> 00:36:02,062
It was you, wasn't it? It was you.
You went to Memmio.

504
00:36:02,098 --> 00:36:05,090
It was you who betrayed me.

505
00:36:05,135 --> 00:36:08,468
You've been whoring yourself
to one of Memmio's men.

506
00:36:08,505 --> 00:36:11,531
You've been whoring yourself
to the whole damn Caelian.

507
00:36:11,575 --> 00:36:14,066
That's not true. He loves me.

508
00:36:14,110 --> 00:36:15,634
He loves me and I love him.

509
00:36:15,679 --> 00:36:18,409
How could you be so stupid?

510
00:36:18,448 --> 00:36:20,006
He was using you to get to me.

511
00:36:20,050 --> 00:36:22,314
You know nothing about it.

512
00:36:22,352 --> 00:36:24,149
He loves me.

513
00:36:24,854 --> 00:36:27,084
And for love of this scum

514
00:36:27,123 --> 00:36:28,988
you would betray your own father?

515
00:36:29,025 --> 00:36:31,687
Oh, yes! I betrayed you!

516
00:36:31,728 --> 00:36:34,720
And I was glad to do it.

517
00:36:40,837 --> 00:36:42,498
Why?

518
00:36:43,707 --> 00:36:46,574
Why? Why? Why would you do that?

519
00:36:46,610 --> 00:36:49,579
You killed my mother.

520
00:36:51,247 --> 00:36:54,011
You cursed us to Hades.

521
00:36:54,117 --> 00:36:57,160
You made me a fucking whore.

522
00:36:57,220 --> 00:36:59,814
And you ask why?

523
00:36:59,856 --> 00:37:01,619
Because I hate you.

524
00:37:01,658 --> 00:37:05,025
I hate you! We all hate you.

525
00:37:05,061 --> 00:37:07,825
I wish you were dead.

526
00:37:16,973 --> 00:37:18,804
Go ahead.

527
00:37:18,842 --> 00:37:22,300
Try and kill me like you killed Mother.

528
00:37:22,345 --> 00:37:23,869
I'll not go so easy.

529
00:37:23,913 --> 00:37:25,710
- I didn't kill her.
- Liar.

530
00:37:25,749 --> 00:37:28,616
- I didn't.
- She didn't love you. You killed her for it.

531
00:37:28,652 --> 00:37:30,440
Shut your mouth. Shut your mouth.

532
00:37:30,520 --> 00:37:33,114
- She never loved you.
- You shut your mouth.

533
00:37:33,156 --> 00:37:35,488
- She never loved you.
- You shut... shut...

534
00:37:35,525 --> 00:37:37,891
Keep your mouth shut!

535
00:37:42,932 --> 00:37:44,593
Vorenus.

536
00:37:46,936 --> 00:37:48,699
Vorenus.

537
00:38:35,819 --> 00:38:39,550
Our noble triumvirate
announces the immediate departure

538
00:38:39,589 --> 00:38:43,389
from the city of his honor Mark Antony.

539
00:38:43,426 --> 00:38:46,452
He will take up his seat in Alexandria

540
00:38:46,496 --> 00:38:49,329
as supreme governor of Egypt

541
00:38:49,365 --> 00:38:51,492
and the eastern provinces.

542
00:38:54,304 --> 00:38:57,364
Tomorrow, at the house of Rufus,

543
00:38:57,407 --> 00:39:01,036
an auction of excellent slaves,

544
00:39:01,077 --> 00:39:04,774
from pliant virgins to learned Greeks,

545
00:39:04,814 --> 00:39:08,750
Rufus has slaves for every budget.

546
00:39:22,332 --> 00:39:25,961
Make way for the Triumvir Mark Antony.

547
00:39:26,002 --> 00:39:29,460
Orders of his honor Triumvir Octavian Caesar,

548
00:39:29,506 --> 00:39:32,475
none shall enter this house.

549
00:39:32,509 --> 00:39:34,807
Shall we use force?

550
00:39:37,847 --> 00:39:39,974
No.

551
00:39:50,693 --> 00:39:52,786
Atia!

552
00:39:58,835 --> 00:40:01,065
Atia!

553
00:40:07,811 --> 00:40:10,109
Out of my way, you little insects.

554
00:40:10,146 --> 00:40:12,239
You cannot leave without permission.

555
00:40:12,282 --> 00:40:15,149
Atia, calm.

556
00:40:15,185 --> 00:40:17,210
Leave it be.

557
00:40:25,228 --> 00:40:27,253
I just want to talk.

558
00:40:33,136 --> 00:40:36,572
Don't push me to violence, centurion.

559
00:40:41,144 --> 00:40:43,009
Just talk.

560
00:40:52,589 --> 00:40:54,921
I'm leaving tomorrow.

561
00:41:03,233 --> 00:41:05,463
Very well.

562
00:41:06,236 --> 00:41:08,101
Goodbye, then.

563
00:41:13,376 --> 00:41:15,367
When the time comes,

564
00:41:16,646 --> 00:41:17,670
I'll send for you.

565
00:41:17,714 --> 00:41:19,875
When will that be?

566
00:41:19,916 --> 00:41:22,180
Who can say?

567
00:41:23,052 --> 00:41:24,713
We must be patient.

568
00:41:24,754 --> 00:41:27,951
Promise me. Promise me you'll send for me.

569
00:41:28,758 --> 00:41:32,455
On my life, I promise.

570
00:42:07,330 --> 00:42:08,820
Burn it.

571
00:42:08,865 --> 00:42:10,992
- And this?
- I don't know.

572
00:42:11,034 --> 00:42:14,561
Burn it. Wipe your arse with it.
I really don't care.

573
00:42:29,819 --> 00:42:31,912
Well, well.

574
00:42:31,955 --> 00:42:34,280
Lucius Vorenus.

575
00:42:34,357 --> 00:42:36,154
You found my gold yet?

576
00:42:36,192 --> 00:42:39,423
- I know where it is.
- And?

577
00:42:39,462 --> 00:42:42,056
Titus Pullo will retrieve it.

578
00:42:44,600 --> 00:42:48,127
I have resigned from the collegium.

579
00:42:48,171 --> 00:42:51,504
- Resigned?
- It's a personal matter.

580
00:42:52,642 --> 00:42:57,238
I have no doubt Pullo will not let you down.

581
00:42:57,280 --> 00:43:00,477
I had no doubt that
you would not let me down, but here we are.

582
00:43:00,516 --> 00:43:03,485
For that, I apologize.

583
00:43:07,690 --> 00:43:11,148
I am come to offer you my services

584
00:43:11,194 --> 00:43:14,129
in Egypt, if you will take me.

585
00:43:14,163 --> 00:43:17,655
Your services? In Egypt?

586
00:43:22,505 --> 00:43:25,440
I cannot stay in Rome, sir.

587
00:43:30,947 --> 00:43:34,940
Let me go to Egypt with you.

588
00:43:34,984 --> 00:43:36,815
Please.

589
00:43:42,158 --> 00:43:44,058
All right.

590
00:43:46,596 --> 00:43:48,587
Come with me.

591
00:43:48,631 --> 00:43:50,599
I need good men.

592
00:43:52,568 --> 00:43:54,798
You'll not turn to drink, will you?

593
00:43:55,872 --> 00:43:57,533
No, sir.

594
00:43:57,573 --> 00:44:01,009
Well, you stoic types often do

595
00:44:01,044 --> 00:44:03,069
when disappointed in life.

596
00:44:10,486 --> 00:44:12,249
Welcome aboard.

597
00:44:13,723 --> 00:44:16,283
Thank you, sir.

598
00:44:21,364 --> 00:44:24,299
- What did he say?
- We sail tomorrow.

599
00:44:25,301 --> 00:44:28,270
You're not gonna come back
and say goodbye?

600
00:44:30,106 --> 00:44:31,596
No.

601
00:44:33,943 --> 00:44:35,800
Vorena's got your blood in her.

602
00:44:35,878 --> 00:44:38,142
Doesn't forgive easy.
And she's young.

603
00:44:38,181 --> 00:44:41,548
- Girls...
- Pullo, it's best this way.

604
00:44:45,822 --> 00:44:47,414
You'll take good care of them?

605
00:44:52,628 --> 00:44:54,858
Tell them...

606
00:44:58,000 --> 00:44:59,991
Tell them I tried.

607
00:45:04,574 --> 00:45:06,508
Gods protect you, brother.

608
00:45:08,444 --> 00:45:10,002
And you, brother.

609
00:46:13,676 --> 00:46:16,338
- Don't do that.
- Why not?

610
00:46:16,379 --> 00:46:19,314
I paid good money for those flowers.

611
00:46:19,348 --> 00:46:22,010
You'll leave the place a desert if you carry on.

612
00:46:23,286 --> 00:46:25,379
I've nothing better to do.

613
00:46:26,689 --> 00:46:29,419
In the kitchen you might find something
to amuse you.

614
00:46:29,458 --> 00:46:32,621
What? Help the cook peel onions?

615
00:46:32,662 --> 00:46:34,061
Better than that.

616
00:46:34,096 --> 00:46:36,155
Well, not much better, in my opinion.

617
00:46:36,199 --> 00:46:38,861
You always did have lamentable taste in men.

618
00:46:40,436 --> 00:46:41,926
Go on.

619
00:46:43,206 --> 00:46:45,902
And don't let the guards see you smile.

620
00:46:45,942 --> 00:46:48,740
They'll know something's amiss. Go on.

621
00:47:07,396 --> 00:47:09,591
How on earth did you get in?

622
00:47:09,632 --> 00:47:12,601
Octavian's men don't let a mouse get by them.

623
00:47:13,936 --> 00:47:16,029
Your mother could outfox Ulysses.

624
00:47:16,072 --> 00:47:19,200
Well, if she can get you inside,
perhaps she can get me out.

625
00:47:19,242 --> 00:47:21,540
We could run away together.

626
00:47:21,577 --> 00:47:23,568
It's a nice thought but...

627
00:47:24,513 --> 00:47:26,811
...it's not possible.
- We could try, at least.

628
00:47:26,849 --> 00:47:29,909
- No.
- Why not? I have a little money.

629
00:47:29,952 --> 00:47:32,978
We could go to the east.
He couldn't reach us there.

630
00:47:34,423 --> 00:47:36,618
I would go with you to Hades,

631
00:47:36,659 --> 00:47:40,060
to Britain, even,
if I thought we had the right.

632
00:47:40,096 --> 00:47:41,927
But we don't.

633
00:47:41,964 --> 00:47:43,989
Right?

634
00:47:45,134 --> 00:47:48,501
What right has he to keep me captive?

635
00:47:49,338 --> 00:47:51,306
- What right has he to...
- Please.

636
00:47:51,340 --> 00:47:53,205
Don't be angry.

637
00:47:53,309 --> 00:47:56,801
He has every legal and moral right
to do with us as he wishes.

638
00:47:58,781 --> 00:48:00,640
He has forgiven me.

639
00:48:00,716 --> 00:48:03,014
And he remains my friend.

640
00:48:04,687 --> 00:48:08,020
I cannot repay his forgiveness
by betraying him a second time.

641
00:48:11,761 --> 00:48:14,821
Well, why are you here, then?

642
00:48:18,901 --> 00:48:20,766
I'm here to say goodbye.

643
00:48:22,138 --> 00:48:24,163
Where are you going?

644
00:48:24,206 --> 00:48:27,607
I mean, we shall see each other again,

645
00:48:27,643 --> 00:48:29,941
quite often, I expect.

646
00:48:31,881 --> 00:48:35,977
But our relations will be formal and correct
as they should be.

647
00:48:40,189 --> 00:48:42,453
Coward.

648
00:48:42,491 --> 00:48:44,322
You're a miserable coward.

649
00:48:44,360 --> 00:48:47,659
- Octavia...
- No. I understand.

650
00:48:47,697 --> 00:48:50,097
You love my brother
and the power he gives you.

651
00:48:50,132 --> 00:48:52,498
Why throw that all away for a woman?

652
00:48:52,601 --> 00:48:54,762
It'd be very foolish.

653
00:48:57,640 --> 00:48:59,301
Goodbye.

654
00:49:01,844 --> 00:49:04,540
Oh, by the way,

655
00:49:04,580 --> 00:49:06,741
I'm having a baby.

656
00:49:09,218 --> 00:49:11,618
Who is the father?

657
00:49:11,654 --> 00:49:13,645
Who knows?

658
00:49:14,757 --> 00:49:19,421
Neither man is worth a brass obol,
so what matter?

659
00:50:30,366 --> 00:50:32,163
Go, go, go!

660
00:50:39,275 --> 00:50:41,266
Quickly, shut the door.

661
00:50:56,792 --> 00:50:59,056
Come on!

662
00:51:26,522 --> 00:51:28,649
Titus Pullo.

663
00:51:33,295 --> 00:51:35,160
A parley.

664
00:51:40,469 --> 00:51:43,700
Brother Pullo, I have no quarrel with you.

665
00:51:43,739 --> 00:51:45,969
You're a reasonable man like I am.

666
00:51:46,008 --> 00:51:49,842
It's that madman Vorenus took us to this pass.

667
00:51:51,647 --> 00:51:54,480
No reason you and me can't do business.

668
00:52:58,814 --> 00:53:00,645
13!

669
00:53:35,584 --> 00:53:38,382
Stand firm! Don't run, you cowards!

670
00:54:34,710 --> 00:54:37,042
Antony.

671
00:55:00,235 --> 00:55:02,066
Cleopatra.

