1
00:01:45,612 --> 00:01:47,944
Brutus.

2
00:01:54,821 --> 00:01:56,948
Brutus.

3
00:02:09,035 --> 00:02:12,198
Domina. Domina, please don't do that.

4
00:02:17,277 --> 00:02:19,268
I'm so sorry.

5
00:02:23,082 --> 00:02:25,846
Why don't you lie down? You're very tired.

6
00:02:26,986 --> 00:02:28,248
Yes...

7
00:02:28,288 --> 00:02:30,256
I'm...

8
00:02:30,290 --> 00:02:32,724
very tired.

9
00:02:32,759 --> 00:02:35,626
Would you like some willow water?

10
00:02:37,130 --> 00:02:39,155
Would I?

11
00:02:39,199 --> 00:02:40,496
It will help you sleep.

12
00:02:41,568 --> 00:02:46,904
No. No more sleep.

13
00:03:03,790 --> 00:03:06,088
Oh, come along, cheer up.

14
00:03:06,125 --> 00:03:08,559
You can't cry at your own wedding.

15
00:03:12,432 --> 00:03:14,593
Show her how lovely she looks.

16
00:03:18,204 --> 00:03:21,640
- I look horrid.
- No, you're beautiful.

17
00:03:23,543 --> 00:03:26,671
Gods, still weeping.

18
00:03:26,713 --> 00:03:29,341
I went to a lot of trouble
to arrange this marriage.

19
00:03:29,382 --> 00:03:32,044
Please don't ruin it.

20
00:03:32,085 --> 00:03:35,452
There's not many men
willing to marry a penniless orphan.

21
00:03:35,488 --> 00:03:38,548
I'm sorry. I am very grateful.

22
00:03:39,726 --> 00:03:44,686
It's just... I'm sure he's a very nice man.

23
00:03:44,731 --> 00:03:46,961
It's just, I had always imagined

24
00:03:47,000 --> 00:03:50,094
I'd wed someone...

25
00:03:50,136 --> 00:03:51,797
Someone different.

26
00:03:51,905 --> 00:03:55,068
You won't wed anyone at all
if you come out all red and puffy.

27
00:04:02,882 --> 00:04:05,350
I know men.

28
00:04:05,385 --> 00:04:10,220
And this one will make a lovely husband.

29
00:04:22,969 --> 00:04:25,995
When and where you are Gaia,

30
00:04:26,039 --> 00:04:29,475
there and then I am Gaius.

31
00:04:32,579 --> 00:04:33,978
Yes, sorry.

32
00:04:34,013 --> 00:04:37,278
When and where you are Gaius,

33
00:04:37,317 --> 00:04:40,445
then and there, I am Gaia.

34
00:04:53,766 --> 00:04:56,326
Makes you think, doesn't it?

35
00:04:56,369 --> 00:04:59,497
- About what?
- About marriage.

36
00:05:01,441 --> 00:05:05,104
- Does it?
- The two of us.

37
00:05:06,846 --> 00:05:09,280
With the augur here,
we might as well do it now.

38
00:05:09,315 --> 00:05:10,942
Quick and simple.

39
00:05:12,085 --> 00:05:15,851
When we get married,
it'll have to be the best wedding ever seen.

40
00:05:15,888 --> 00:05:18,288
You deserve nothing less.

41
00:05:20,093 --> 00:05:22,152
Just a thought.

42
00:05:25,131 --> 00:05:28,430
This augur moves like a snail.

43
00:05:28,468 --> 00:05:30,493
Atia of the Julii,

44
00:05:30,536 --> 00:05:33,164
I call for justice!

45
00:05:33,206 --> 00:05:35,606
Atia of the Julii,

46
00:05:35,642 --> 00:05:37,872
I call for justice.

47
00:05:37,910 --> 00:05:40,572
Atia of the Julii,

48
00:05:40,613 --> 00:05:43,377
I call for justice.

49
00:05:43,416 --> 00:05:45,714
Excuse me for a moment.

50
00:05:45,752 --> 00:05:48,448
Atia of the Julii,

51
00:05:48,488 --> 00:05:51,321
I call for justice.

52
00:05:51,424 --> 00:05:53,824
Atia of the Julii,

53
00:05:53,860 --> 00:05:56,727
I call for justice.

54
00:05:56,763 --> 00:05:59,357
Atia of the Julii,

55
00:05:59,399 --> 00:06:02,129
I call for justice.

56
00:06:02,168 --> 00:06:04,636
Atia of the Julii,

57
00:06:04,671 --> 00:06:07,970
I call for justice.

58
00:06:08,007 --> 00:06:10,532
Atia of the Julii,

59
00:06:10,576 --> 00:06:13,010
I call for justice.

60
00:06:13,046 --> 00:06:16,940
- Atia of the Julii, I call for justice.
- Ludicrous old bat.

61
00:06:17,016 --> 00:06:22,079
- What shall we do?
- Atia of the Julii, I call for justice.

62
00:06:22,121 --> 00:06:24,783
Nothing. Nothing at all.

63
00:06:24,824 --> 00:06:27,725
She'll go away soon enough
if we just ignore her.

64
00:06:34,300 --> 00:06:36,598
Hey, wife.

65
00:06:38,638 --> 00:06:41,038
Sun's been up for hours.

66
00:06:41,074 --> 00:06:43,702
It's time to get up.

67
00:06:43,743 --> 00:06:45,233
Soon.

68
00:06:47,480 --> 00:06:50,643
While we're here...

69
00:06:50,750 --> 00:06:52,411
No.

70
00:06:52,452 --> 00:06:54,977
You don't know what I was gonna ask.

71
00:06:55,021 --> 00:06:57,353
You want to make love.

72
00:06:58,191 --> 00:06:59,783
That's an idea.

73
00:06:59,826 --> 00:07:01,851
No good for baby.

74
00:07:01,894 --> 00:07:03,885
He won't mind.

75
00:07:03,930 --> 00:07:05,921
Maybe she.

76
00:07:05,965 --> 00:07:09,298
She won't mind, neither.

77
00:07:09,335 --> 00:07:13,294
No good for baby. Priest says so.

78
00:07:13,339 --> 00:07:16,035
Priest? Priest?

79
00:07:16,075 --> 00:07:18,407
What priest?

80
00:07:18,444 --> 00:07:20,435
Priest in my country.

81
00:07:22,482 --> 00:07:25,645
Well, we're not in your country, are we?

82
00:07:25,685 --> 00:07:29,052
When baby start to move, no love.

83
00:07:29,088 --> 00:07:30,851
Is rules.

84
00:07:31,891 --> 00:07:33,586
The baby's moving?

85
00:07:33,626 --> 00:07:36,595
Yes, feel.

86
00:07:50,676 --> 00:07:54,112
So we have no choice
but to use the deeper berths in Ostia.

87
00:07:54,213 --> 00:07:57,876
We now have grain ships
in excess of 10,000 amphorae.

88
00:07:59,185 --> 00:08:03,588
Tricky. Those berths have been
reserved for our oil ships

89
00:08:03,623 --> 00:08:05,980
since fuck knows when, way back.

90
00:08:06,058 --> 00:08:08,083
Well, that's no reason to keep it so.

91
00:08:09,462 --> 00:08:12,431
- Times change.
- So you keep saying.

92
00:08:13,966 --> 00:08:16,366
I'll allow you to use our berths,

93
00:08:16,402 --> 00:08:18,097
but we'll take 5% of the grain

94
00:08:18,137 --> 00:08:21,004
and the ships will be unloaded by my own men.

95
00:08:21,040 --> 00:08:24,532
Bollocks. That's a license for thievery.

96
00:08:24,577 --> 00:08:26,704
If we were thieves.

97
00:08:28,414 --> 00:08:31,315
I'll give you the 5%, but Mascius
will go down to Ostia

98
00:08:31,350 --> 00:08:33,944
and he will supervise the dock work.

99
00:08:33,986 --> 00:08:36,614
I'll leave today.

100
00:08:36,656 --> 00:08:38,817
As you wish.

101
00:09:13,926 --> 00:09:15,723
Atia of the Julii,

102
00:09:15,761 --> 00:09:17,388
I call for justice.

103
00:09:17,430 --> 00:09:18,988
Atia of the Julii,

104
00:09:19,031 --> 00:09:20,555
I call for justice.

105
00:09:20,600 --> 00:09:22,659
Atia of the Julii,

106
00:09:22,702 --> 00:09:24,670
I call for justice.

107
00:09:24,704 --> 00:09:26,695
Atia of the Julii,

108
00:09:26,739 --> 00:09:28,206
I call for justice.

109
00:09:28,241 --> 00:09:30,209
Atia of the Julii,

110
00:09:30,243 --> 00:09:31,733
I call for justice.

111
00:09:31,777 --> 00:09:33,768
Atia of the Julii,

112
00:09:33,813 --> 00:09:35,212
I call for justice.

113
00:09:35,648 --> 00:09:37,340
Good morning, all.

114
00:09:37,416 --> 00:09:39,441
You're late.

115
00:09:41,954 --> 00:09:43,945
Posca's wedding yesterday.

116
00:09:45,858 --> 00:09:48,918
I'm afraid I drank rather too much.

117
00:09:48,961 --> 00:09:52,795
I could not get out of bed,
no matter how hard I tried.

118
00:09:53,833 --> 00:09:57,735
I have the most shocking headache.

119
00:09:57,770 --> 00:10:00,762
So you must both speak very quietly

120
00:10:00,806 --> 00:10:04,207
or I shall shatter into a thousand little pieces.

121
00:10:13,286 --> 00:10:17,313
I've been approached by a number
of eminent friends among the Senate.

122
00:10:18,758 --> 00:10:20,988
They are troubled.

123
00:10:21,027 --> 00:10:24,554
I do not say that they have grounds for anxiety,

124
00:10:24,597 --> 00:10:27,589
but I feel I would be remiss
if I did not communicate...

125
00:10:27,633 --> 00:10:30,568
- Do get on with it, man.
- Yes, yes.

126
00:10:31,971 --> 00:10:35,065
They're worried that perhaps we three intend

127
00:10:36,175 --> 00:10:38,336
to establish some form of...

128
00:10:38,377 --> 00:10:39,935
tyranny.

129
00:10:39,979 --> 00:10:43,278
And who are these worriers?

130
00:10:43,316 --> 00:10:45,614
- Give me names.
- That's awkward.

131
00:10:45,651 --> 00:10:48,347
They spoke to me in confidence.

132
00:10:48,387 --> 00:10:50,685
I'll bet they did.

133
00:10:50,723 --> 00:10:55,592
You tell your eminent friends
to shut their mouths.

134
00:10:55,628 --> 00:10:59,325
Tell them to go look
on Cicero's hands in the Forum

135
00:10:59,365 --> 00:11:01,526
and remember what happens

136
00:11:01,567 --> 00:11:05,003
to those that prattle of tyranny.

137
00:11:05,037 --> 00:11:08,131
I only mention it.
I would be remiss if I did not.

138
00:11:08,174 --> 00:11:10,165
You're quite right, Lepidus.

139
00:11:10,209 --> 00:11:12,234
Quite right.

140
00:11:12,278 --> 00:11:14,371
Now, shall we get down to business?

141
00:11:14,413 --> 00:11:16,847
Yes, by all means.

142
00:11:16,882 --> 00:11:19,646
Clearly, we three cannot
all rule together at once.

143
00:11:19,685 --> 00:11:21,949
We shall confuse and contradict each other.

144
00:11:21,988 --> 00:11:24,889
- True enough.
- We must divide responsibilities.

145
00:11:26,125 --> 00:11:28,525
What are you proposing?

146
00:11:28,561 --> 00:11:31,359
I suggest we divide
the territory of Rome into three.

147
00:11:31,397 --> 00:11:34,025
Each one of us shall assume
command of one region.

148
00:11:39,472 --> 00:11:41,838
Sounds reasonable.

149
00:11:43,275 --> 00:11:45,766
Who gets what?

150
00:11:45,811 --> 00:11:47,802
I haven't considered that yet.

151
00:11:47,847 --> 00:11:49,838
But Rome is a very complex machine.

152
00:11:49,882 --> 00:11:53,147
One can't simply chop it up like cabbage.

153
00:12:05,798 --> 00:12:09,859
You should have Rome and the west.

154
00:12:10,936 --> 00:12:17,671
And I will make do with
Egypt and the eastern provinces.

155
00:12:21,047 --> 00:12:24,710
- Objections?
- Rome and the west has what?

156
00:12:24,750 --> 00:12:28,811
Rowdy Gauls, Germans, a fractious Senate,

157
00:12:28,854 --> 00:12:31,982
all the trouble of keeping
the Roman mob happy.

158
00:12:33,759 --> 00:12:35,590
The east is where the money is,

159
00:12:35,628 --> 00:12:38,825
the grain supply, most of the tax revenue.

160
00:12:38,864 --> 00:12:42,698
Well, all the revenues
would be divided equally, of course.

161
00:12:42,735 --> 00:12:45,260
It would be a purely administrative division.

162
00:12:45,304 --> 00:12:49,434
All monies would be held in a single treasury.

163
00:12:50,176 --> 00:12:53,771
- That would work.
- And I?

164
00:12:55,581 --> 00:12:57,242
What would I get?

165
00:12:59,819 --> 00:13:01,810
Yes.

166
00:13:09,662 --> 00:13:11,493
Africa.

167
00:13:15,801 --> 00:13:18,065
Atia of the Julii,

168
00:13:18,104 --> 00:13:20,698
I call for justice.

169
00:13:20,739 --> 00:13:23,003
Atia of the Julii,

170
00:13:23,042 --> 00:13:25,806
I call for justice.

171
00:13:25,845 --> 00:13:28,370
Atia of the Julii,

172
00:13:28,414 --> 00:13:30,740
I call for justice.

173
00:13:30,816 --> 00:13:33,307
Atia of the Julii...

174
00:13:33,352 --> 00:13:36,048
What is this? Is she putting down roots?

175
00:13:36,088 --> 00:13:38,113
Atia of the Julii,

176
00:13:38,157 --> 00:13:41,092
I call for justice.

177
00:13:41,127 --> 00:13:43,823
Atia of the Julii,

178
00:13:43,863 --> 00:13:46,093
I call for justice.

179
00:13:46,132 --> 00:13:47,793
Atia of the Julii...

180
00:13:47,833 --> 00:13:50,131
So...

181
00:13:50,169 --> 00:13:53,036
How goes your day?

182
00:13:53,139 --> 00:13:54,980
Mine went extremely well.

183
00:13:55,040 --> 00:13:57,900
She's driving me mad.
It's completely unfair.

184
00:13:57,977 --> 00:14:00,036
It wasn't me who killed her precious son.

185
00:14:00,079 --> 00:14:04,914
- She should be wailing outside your house.
- She just wants a little attention.

186
00:14:04,950 --> 00:14:08,647
Go out. Let her rant at you a while.

187
00:14:08,687 --> 00:14:11,019
She'll soon leave.

188
00:14:11,357 --> 00:14:14,224
And have her curse at me
in front of a mob of ogling plebs?

189
00:14:14,260 --> 00:14:17,252
Never. I wouldn't give her that pleasure.

190
00:14:17,296 --> 00:14:18,820
It's up to you.

191
00:14:18,864 --> 00:14:22,698
But I guarantee
she won't leave until she's seen you.

192
00:14:22,735 --> 00:14:25,863
Atia of the Julii...

193
00:14:28,240 --> 00:14:30,231
Stop pushing!

194
00:14:31,443 --> 00:14:33,843
Wait your turn, woman!

195
00:14:33,879 --> 00:14:35,642
My family is begging for food!

196
00:14:40,119 --> 00:14:41,882
Seen you on line before.

197
00:14:41,921 --> 00:14:43,912
Me? No.

198
00:14:45,191 --> 00:14:47,716
This looks like a fake to me.

199
00:14:47,760 --> 00:14:49,853
I bet you don't even live on the Aventine.

200
00:14:49,895 --> 00:14:52,420
No fake. I swear
to you by the sacred black stone.

201
00:14:52,531 --> 00:14:55,557
Get out and don't let me
catch you around here again.

202
00:14:56,936 --> 00:14:58,927
Get off!

203
00:15:13,686 --> 00:15:15,677
Did you bring in wood?

204
00:15:16,522 --> 00:15:20,083
- Not yet.
- Go do.

205
00:15:20,125 --> 00:15:23,026
- No hurry.
- Get wood now.

206
00:15:23,062 --> 00:15:26,589
Get it yourself. I'm busy.

207
00:15:27,399 --> 00:15:29,629
I give you an order.

208
00:15:29,668 --> 00:15:31,431
Kiss my ass.

209
00:15:35,241 --> 00:15:38,005
Go ahead. Try.

210
00:15:38,043 --> 00:15:39,900
I'll shove it down your throat.

211
00:15:39,979 --> 00:15:41,446
You'll be sorry.

212
00:15:43,649 --> 00:15:46,311
My husband will beat you in pulp.

213
00:15:49,655 --> 00:15:51,646
Go on, on your way.

214
00:15:54,326 --> 00:15:56,556
Fake.

215
00:15:56,595 --> 00:16:00,258
Half the people in the line had them.

216
00:16:00,299 --> 00:16:02,130
Well made.

217
00:16:02,167 --> 00:16:05,193
Maybe one of the other collegia
trying to fuck things up.

218
00:16:05,237 --> 00:16:07,865
- Memmio, I expect.
- Very likely.

219
00:16:07,906 --> 00:16:11,342
- What do we do?
- Nothing.

220
00:16:13,012 --> 00:16:15,446
Lost me there.

221
00:16:15,481 --> 00:16:17,472
Memmio is dishonest and greedy.

222
00:16:17,516 --> 00:16:19,484
Nothing we can do can change that.

223
00:16:19,518 --> 00:16:22,544
If he thinks he's deceiving us, then he's happy.

224
00:16:22,588 --> 00:16:24,453
And I want everyone to be happy.

225
00:16:24,490 --> 00:16:26,788
That's how we keep the peace. We do nothing.

226
00:16:26,825 --> 00:16:28,486
But he's stealing from us.

227
00:16:28,527 --> 00:16:30,893
People who need food are getting fed.

228
00:16:30,929 --> 00:16:33,659
What matter where they live exactly?

229
00:16:35,968 --> 00:16:37,629
You must go to beat her dead!

230
00:16:37,670 --> 00:16:40,662
- Calm down. Beat who?
- That whore, that Gaia.

231
00:16:40,706 --> 00:16:43,504
- You beat her dead!
- What's she done now?

232
00:16:43,542 --> 00:16:48,036
She wouldn't bring in wood like I tell her.
Then she say she'll choke me with a stick.

233
00:16:48,080 --> 00:16:51,982
- What?
- She say she's gonna choke me with a stick.

234
00:16:52,084 --> 00:16:55,260
I don't understand. Why would she do that?
What did you do to her?

235
00:16:55,321 --> 00:16:57,255
Perfect. Now it's my fault?

236
00:16:57,289 --> 00:17:00,156
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
- Eirene.

237
00:17:01,226 --> 00:17:03,558
Oh, cack.

238
00:17:03,595 --> 00:17:05,620
What do I do?

239
00:17:05,664 --> 00:17:08,428
- Don't look at me.
- Very funny.

240
00:17:08,467 --> 00:17:12,130
If I go and beat Gaia like she deserves,
what do you think Mascius will do?

241
00:17:12,171 --> 00:17:15,402
- She's his girl.
- It's a puzzle, all right.

242
00:17:15,441 --> 00:17:19,309
Where's Mascius? Maybe if I go and talk
to him man to man, he can chastise her.

243
00:17:19,345 --> 00:17:21,609
He's in Ostia. The new grain-ship business.

244
00:17:21,647 --> 00:17:23,012
Oh, cack.

245
00:17:24,717 --> 00:17:27,652
Maybe if you were to give her the beating...

246
00:17:28,954 --> 00:17:30,819
I will if you want.

247
00:17:32,825 --> 00:17:37,194
No. It's my wife she insulted,
my responsibility.

248
00:17:38,864 --> 00:17:41,924
Marriage, it's complicated.

249
00:17:43,068 --> 00:17:47,004
With her pregnant now...
I think it drives them a little mad.

250
00:17:48,774 --> 00:17:50,571
Here's to a boy.

251
00:17:50,609 --> 00:17:52,634
A boy.

252
00:18:02,221 --> 00:18:04,052
Chief.

253
00:18:07,860 --> 00:18:09,350
What's that for?

254
00:18:09,928 --> 00:18:12,260
Don't make a fuss now.

255
00:18:13,799 --> 00:18:16,660
What? You're gonna whip me?

256
00:18:16,735 --> 00:18:18,032
I am.

257
00:18:19,204 --> 00:18:21,229
Why would you want to do that?

258
00:18:21,273 --> 00:18:23,298
You know damn well why.

259
00:18:24,943 --> 00:18:29,209
- Tell me.
- You disrespected my wife.

260
00:18:30,449 --> 00:18:32,781
Oh, that. She tried to hit me.

261
00:18:33,552 --> 00:18:36,919
She's lady of this house. You're a slave!
She's allowed to hit you.

262
00:18:36,955 --> 00:18:38,081
Now let's get it done.

263
00:18:38,123 --> 00:18:41,092
It's hard to remember
she's married to the boss.

264
00:18:41,126 --> 00:18:44,584
I mean, nothing against her.
It's just not natural.

265
00:18:44,630 --> 00:18:46,962
She's such a mouse of a woman.

266
00:18:46,999 --> 00:18:48,990
You're such a lion of a man.

267
00:18:49,034 --> 00:18:52,470
Gerrae. You know nothing of us.

268
00:18:52,571 --> 00:18:54,232
Mouse.

269
00:18:55,441 --> 00:18:58,501
Lion. Anyone can see.

270
00:19:02,748 --> 00:19:04,807
What sort of animal does that make you?

271
00:19:04,850 --> 00:19:07,614
What kind of animal do you want me to be?

272
00:19:08,720 --> 00:19:12,679
The kind that will bend over
and take her whipping without complaint.

273
00:19:13,692 --> 00:19:15,683
I could do that for you.

274
00:19:18,697 --> 00:19:21,495
But you've got to treat me nice first.

275
00:19:21,533 --> 00:19:24,764
Just shut it, all right?
Just shut it and come here.

276
00:19:24,803 --> 00:19:26,896
What will Mascius do if you beat me?

277
00:19:26,939 --> 00:19:30,033
I don't give a fuck.
Mascius will do what I tell him.

278
00:19:30,075 --> 00:19:33,135
No, Mascius does what I tell him.

279
00:19:33,178 --> 00:19:34,372
Oh, yeah?

280
00:19:35,848 --> 00:19:37,145
More fool him, then.

281
00:19:38,150 --> 00:19:40,209
Fuck you!

282
00:19:48,494 --> 00:19:50,485
What are you gonna do now?

283
00:20:55,260 --> 00:20:57,285
Is that all you got?

284
00:21:27,259 --> 00:21:29,250
This was a mistake.

285
00:21:30,963 --> 00:21:33,056
This never happens again.

286
00:21:34,499 --> 00:21:37,059
Shame.

287
00:21:37,102 --> 00:21:40,003
You and me go nicely together,
don't you think?

288
00:21:40,038 --> 00:21:43,474
You and me are nothing.

289
00:21:43,508 --> 00:21:46,477
But what if I misbehave again?

290
00:21:46,511 --> 00:21:49,173
You gotta keep me disciplined, haven't you?

291
00:21:51,283 --> 00:21:53,308
Don't test me, girl.

292
00:21:53,352 --> 00:21:55,582
I'm warning you.

293
00:21:55,621 --> 00:21:58,419
You'll be sorry.

294
00:21:58,457 --> 00:22:00,220
Relax.

295
00:22:01,660 --> 00:22:06,427
Where's it say a man can't have his slaves
if he wants?

296
00:22:09,835 --> 00:22:12,429
I can kill them too,

297
00:22:12,471 --> 00:22:14,564
if I want.

298
00:22:16,642 --> 00:22:18,906
You can.

299
00:22:18,944 --> 00:22:21,708
You can do anything you like.

300
00:22:39,598 --> 00:22:42,226
Atia of the Julii,

301
00:22:42,267 --> 00:22:44,735
I call for justice.

302
00:22:44,770 --> 00:22:47,330
Atia of the Julii,

303
00:22:47,372 --> 00:22:49,897
I call for justice.

304
00:22:49,941 --> 00:22:52,705
Atia of the Julii,

305
00:22:52,811 --> 00:22:56,100
I call for justice...

306
00:22:56,148 --> 00:22:59,743
I give up. I give up! I give up!

307
00:22:59,785 --> 00:23:01,980
Atia of the Julii,

308
00:23:02,020 --> 00:23:04,454
I call for justice.

309
00:23:04,489 --> 00:23:06,252
Atia of the Julii,

310
00:23:06,291 --> 00:23:08,953
I call for justice.

311
00:23:08,994 --> 00:23:11,258
Atia of the Julii

312
00:23:11,296 --> 00:23:13,025
- I call for justice.
- Here, then!

313
00:23:17,636 --> 00:23:19,900
Here I am, you crazy bitch!

314
00:23:19,938 --> 00:23:23,704
Speak your piece and then be gone.
Here I am!

315
00:23:33,752 --> 00:23:35,913
Gods below...

316
00:23:39,424 --> 00:23:42,882
I am Servilia

317
00:23:42,928 --> 00:23:45,123
of the most ancient

318
00:23:45,163 --> 00:23:47,529
and sacred Junii,

319
00:23:47,566 --> 00:23:53,505
of whose bones the seven hills
of Rome are built.

320
00:23:54,639 --> 00:23:57,540
I summon you to listen.

321
00:24:01,513 --> 00:24:04,141
Curse this woman.

322
00:24:05,317 --> 00:24:08,514
Send her bitterness and despair

323
00:24:08,553 --> 00:24:11,420
for all of her life.

324
00:24:11,456 --> 00:24:13,981
Let her taste nothing

325
00:24:14,025 --> 00:24:17,324
but ashes and iron.

326
00:24:18,530 --> 00:24:21,795
Gods of the Underworld,

327
00:24:21,833 --> 00:24:24,358
all that I have left

328
00:24:24,402 --> 00:24:27,496
I give to you in sacrifice

329
00:24:27,539 --> 00:24:30,064
if you will make it so.

330
00:24:36,181 --> 00:24:38,046
My God.

331
00:25:10,515 --> 00:25:13,507
Now that is an exit.

332
00:25:22,761 --> 00:25:25,525
Come. Come back inside.

333
00:25:33,972 --> 00:25:35,667
She's dead.

334
00:25:53,725 --> 00:25:56,216
All citizens be aware

335
00:25:56,261 --> 00:25:58,729
that the vassal Prince Herod,

336
00:25:58,763 --> 00:26:00,560
Tetrarch of Galilee,

337
00:26:00,599 --> 00:26:02,396
has come to the city.

338
00:26:02,434 --> 00:26:04,629
By order of the Triumvirate,

339
00:26:04,669 --> 00:26:06,603
during his residence here,

340
00:26:06,638 --> 00:26:11,337
all mockery of Jews and their one God

341
00:26:11,376 --> 00:26:15,335
shall be kept to an appropriate minimum.

342
00:26:19,484 --> 00:26:24,888
I am told
Roman gentlemen do not solicit bribes.

343
00:26:25,490 --> 00:26:30,052
One must offer the bribe as a gift.
Is that so?

344
00:26:30,095 --> 00:26:32,154
Yes.

345
00:26:32,197 --> 00:26:34,188
Yes, that is so.

346
00:26:36,134 --> 00:26:40,093
We are the most dreadful
hypocrites, I'm afraid.

347
00:26:41,907 --> 00:26:44,774
I offer you a gift, then.

348
00:26:44,809 --> 00:26:47,100
Help me take the throne of Judea,

349
00:26:47,178 --> 00:26:51,911
make my enemies your enemies,
and I offer you a substantial gift.

350
00:26:55,620 --> 00:26:58,589
How substantial would this gift be?

351
00:26:58,623 --> 00:27:00,921
How substantial does it need to be?

352
00:27:00,959 --> 00:27:02,756
20,000 pounds of gold.

353
00:27:02,794 --> 00:27:04,819
Done.

354
00:27:06,364 --> 00:27:08,332
I said we should have asked for more.

355
00:27:09,434 --> 00:27:11,595
You must guarantee, of course,

356
00:27:11,636 --> 00:27:14,002
to keep your Jews in line.

357
00:27:15,106 --> 00:27:19,475
They will do as I say,
or they will suffer the consequences.

358
00:27:21,046 --> 00:27:22,638
Congratulations then, Herod.

359
00:27:22,681 --> 00:27:24,911
You have the full backing of Rome.

360
00:27:25,850 --> 00:27:27,010
One question.

361
00:27:27,052 --> 00:27:30,647
- Yes.
- Our friends, Octavian and Lepidus.

362
00:27:30,689 --> 00:27:32,156
You speak for them too?

363
00:27:33,224 --> 00:27:36,489
I do. We speak with one voice.

364
00:27:37,329 --> 00:27:41,095
So they will not come to me later
expecting gifts of their own?

365
00:27:41,132 --> 00:27:46,399
- No, your gift is for all of us.
- Good.

366
00:27:47,205 --> 00:27:51,869
Wonderful to have such trust
between friends.

367
00:28:02,554 --> 00:28:05,387
That is what I call a good morning's work.

368
00:28:06,558 --> 00:28:09,425
Indeed. A good morning's work.

369
00:28:09,461 --> 00:28:13,591
May I inquire what my share will be?

370
00:28:13,631 --> 00:28:15,861
Share? Share of what?

371
00:28:16,634 --> 00:28:18,499
Of Herod's gift.

372
00:28:18,536 --> 00:28:21,972
- What gift?
- I see.

373
00:28:22,007 --> 00:28:24,373
Do you?

374
00:28:24,409 --> 00:28:26,900
Let me be clear.

375
00:28:26,945 --> 00:28:29,004
There was no gift.

376
00:28:29,047 --> 00:28:33,484
Herod came here today
to discuss administrative issues

377
00:28:33,518 --> 00:28:35,952
of taxes on olive groves,

378
00:28:35,987 --> 00:28:39,650
of border defenses against the Parthians.

379
00:28:39,691 --> 00:28:42,558
- There was no gift.
- I understand.

380
00:28:43,962 --> 00:28:46,157
Really, Posca,

381
00:28:46,197 --> 00:28:48,961
ever since you got your freedom,

382
00:28:49,000 --> 00:28:51,867
you have become insufferably greedy.

383
00:28:52,437 --> 00:28:55,406
Go home, have a good lunch,

384
00:28:55,440 --> 00:28:58,739
make love to your pretty young wife,

385
00:28:58,777 --> 00:29:02,838
but do stop grubbing about
after other people's money.

386
00:29:03,548 --> 00:29:07,541
Trust me, you'll be far more content.

387
00:29:20,198 --> 00:29:22,530
Scum.

388
00:29:23,068 --> 00:29:25,059
Bastard scum!

389
00:29:25,103 --> 00:29:27,697
What good is shouting at him on the street?

390
00:29:27,739 --> 00:29:30,230
It's childish. You'll only get into trouble.

391
00:29:30,275 --> 00:29:32,436
He's worse than his father.

392
00:29:32,477 --> 00:29:35,446
He'll make our people slaves and idolaters.

393
00:29:35,480 --> 00:29:37,607
He should die. The bastard should die!

394
00:29:38,249 --> 00:29:40,979
Well, it would be a mitzvah, no doubt.

395
00:29:41,019 --> 00:29:43,249
I'm serious.

396
00:29:43,288 --> 00:29:45,950
Come on. Us?

397
00:29:45,990 --> 00:29:48,982
If not us, then who?

398
00:29:49,027 --> 00:29:52,053
Herod is here. We are here.

399
00:29:52,097 --> 00:29:55,760
The future of our people is in our hands.

400
00:30:22,360 --> 00:30:24,726
Salve, Maecenas.

401
00:30:24,762 --> 00:30:26,753
Hello, Posca.

402
00:30:31,669 --> 00:30:34,263
Might I have a word?

403
00:30:36,007 --> 00:30:39,238
I suppose, if you must.

404
00:30:40,678 --> 00:30:43,977
It strikes me you're the sort of man

405
00:30:44,015 --> 00:30:47,212
that knows how to keep a confidence.

406
00:30:47,252 --> 00:30:49,277
Yes.

407
00:30:50,989 --> 00:30:56,086
If a man were to tell you something
in confidence,

408
00:30:56,127 --> 00:31:00,826
you might tell others,
but you would not reveal your source.

409
00:31:03,268 --> 00:31:05,259
No.

410
00:31:12,677 --> 00:31:17,671
And perhaps you're the sort of man
that knows how to properly...

411
00:31:18,750 --> 00:31:20,877
reward...

412
00:31:20,919 --> 00:31:23,786
those who confide in him.

413
00:31:23,821 --> 00:31:26,153
You have me exactly.

414
00:31:26,191 --> 00:31:28,421
You're a fine judge of character.

415
00:31:29,794 --> 00:31:32,592
Those lions you bought me were useless.

416
00:31:32,630 --> 00:31:36,896
Wouldn't pull my chariot for shit
and bit the arm off a perfectly good groom.

417
00:31:36,935 --> 00:31:39,403
They are temperamental animals.

418
00:31:39,437 --> 00:31:42,338
I am very fortunate to have a giraffe,

419
00:31:42,373 --> 00:31:44,068
should you be interested.

420
00:31:44,108 --> 00:31:47,600
What would I do with a giraffe?

421
00:31:47,645 --> 00:31:49,977
Camels, perhaps?

422
00:31:50,014 --> 00:31:53,506
Camels? Do I look
like a fucking date merchant?

423
00:31:53,618 --> 00:31:56,416
Lions that run!

424
00:31:57,255 --> 00:31:59,246
Get out.

425
00:32:00,792 --> 00:32:04,853
Now, what news, young Caesar?

426
00:32:04,896 --> 00:32:07,922
What is one-third of 20,000?

427
00:32:08,967 --> 00:32:12,630
6,666 or thereabouts.

428
00:32:12,670 --> 00:32:14,763
Do you take me for a fool?

429
00:32:14,806 --> 00:32:17,866
Question after question.

430
00:32:17,909 --> 00:32:20,673
Makes for very poor conversation.

431
00:32:20,712 --> 00:32:23,704
If you have a grievance, just say what it is.

432
00:32:23,748 --> 00:32:25,739
We had an agreement.

433
00:32:25,783 --> 00:32:29,378
- We would share all revenue.
- Yes.

434
00:32:29,420 --> 00:32:34,187
Herod has agreed to give you
20,000 pounds of gold.

435
00:32:34,225 --> 00:32:36,216
I want my share.

436
00:32:36,961 --> 00:32:39,020
Who told you this?

437
00:32:39,063 --> 00:32:41,054
You deny?

438
00:32:43,468 --> 00:32:46,494
- Who told him?
- I've bought one of Herod's people.

439
00:32:48,273 --> 00:32:50,264
Do you deny it?

440
00:32:50,308 --> 00:32:53,835
If Herod is kind enough to give me a gift,

441
00:32:53,945 --> 00:32:55,820
what business is it of yours?

442
00:32:55,880 --> 00:32:57,848
A gift is not revenue.

443
00:32:57,882 --> 00:33:01,841
It is not a gift. It is a bribe
for political and military favors,

444
00:33:01,886 --> 00:33:05,083
the cost of which favors
shall be borne by the state.

445
00:33:05,123 --> 00:33:08,354
- Pedantry.
- Let us be realistic.

446
00:33:08,393 --> 00:33:11,089
This arrangement of ours cannot work

447
00:33:11,129 --> 00:33:13,097
if you seek every opportunity

448
00:33:13,131 --> 00:33:15,759
to aggrandize yourself at my expense.

449
00:33:19,237 --> 00:33:21,205
Aggrandize myself?

450
00:33:23,241 --> 00:33:26,972
This from the boy who...
whose so-called father

451
00:33:27,011 --> 00:33:29,309
has been declared a god.

452
00:33:30,481 --> 00:33:32,472
An honor he well deserves.

453
00:33:32,517 --> 00:33:37,318
You only did it so that you might be known
as the son of a god.

454
00:33:37,355 --> 00:33:39,414
You have no accomplishments of your own,

455
00:33:39,457 --> 00:33:43,689
so you seek to borrow the glory of others.

456
00:33:43,728 --> 00:33:48,358
It's true. It was no accomplishment
to defeat you at Mutina.

457
00:33:48,399 --> 00:33:50,890
You defeated me?

458
00:33:53,137 --> 00:33:56,004
You cowardly little shit!

459
00:33:56,040 --> 00:33:58,372
He'd never even left his tent.

460
00:33:58,409 --> 00:34:02,812
You have never defeated me in anything.

461
00:34:02,847 --> 00:34:06,044
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
let's not get overheated.

462
00:34:06,084 --> 00:34:09,178
I'm sure we can come to some
kind of reasonable agreement.

463
00:34:09,220 --> 00:34:13,179
I had hoped you might have learned
some humility and discipline.

464
00:34:13,224 --> 00:34:19,322
I see now that you are still
the same crude, arrogant lech

465
00:34:19,364 --> 00:34:21,355
you always were.

466
00:34:21,399 --> 00:34:24,260
That's right, just the same.

467
00:34:24,335 --> 00:34:27,498
And still fucking your mother!

468
00:34:38,983 --> 00:34:40,951
Are you all right?

469
00:34:40,985 --> 00:34:42,953
Yes, nothing.

470
00:34:42,987 --> 00:34:45,547
- Do you want to go lie down?
- No, it's fine.

471
00:34:48,893 --> 00:34:50,861
Anything else, Mistress?

472
00:34:50,962 --> 00:34:52,953
Water.

473
00:35:01,205 --> 00:35:03,537
Master?

474
00:35:03,574 --> 00:35:05,565
No. Nothing.

475
00:35:13,551 --> 00:35:14,950
See? Good slave now,

476
00:35:14,986 --> 00:35:17,750
ever since you gave her a good beating.

477
00:35:19,490 --> 00:35:21,151
There you go.

478
00:35:23,594 --> 00:35:26,461
You should beat her
the same way every month.

479
00:35:39,243 --> 00:35:44,112
If she wakes before I'm back,
tell her I've gone to Lyde's temple.

480
00:36:00,898 --> 00:36:05,358
Tell me again about the farm.
What kind of animals will we have?

481
00:36:05,403 --> 00:36:08,260
Sheep,

482
00:36:08,339 --> 00:36:10,534
goats,

483
00:36:10,575 --> 00:36:12,500
- pigs.
- And chickens?

484
00:36:12,577 --> 00:36:16,206
Yes, horses as well. Elephants, if you like.

485
00:36:16,247 --> 00:36:18,875
- Sons of Dis, will you...
- What's the matter?

486
00:36:18,916 --> 00:36:22,147
I'm sorry. It's not you, it's...

487
00:36:22,186 --> 00:36:24,848
It's business matters...

488
00:36:24,889 --> 00:36:26,857
Forget it.

489
00:36:26,891 --> 00:36:29,155
Give me a kiss.

490
00:36:29,193 --> 00:36:31,161
Do you still love me?

491
00:36:31,195 --> 00:36:34,164
Of course.

492
00:36:34,198 --> 00:36:36,189
Very much.

493
00:36:46,377 --> 00:36:48,300
Omnipor, I've been looking...

494
00:36:48,379 --> 00:36:51,576
Oh, excuse me.

495
00:36:55,119 --> 00:36:57,087
- Is that...
- It's nobody.

496
00:36:57,121 --> 00:36:59,180
It's just a girl. I'll see you outside.

497
00:37:00,591 --> 00:37:04,049
- That's the daughter of Lucius Vorenus.
- No, it's not.

498
00:37:04,095 --> 00:37:07,189
Don't fuck me about.
I've got eyes, haven't I?

499
00:37:07,231 --> 00:37:09,563
How long's this been going on?

500
00:37:09,600 --> 00:37:10,931
A few months.

501
00:37:12,537 --> 00:37:15,870
Are you insane? You know
what disrespect this shows your father?

502
00:37:15,907 --> 00:37:20,207
- I don't care. I hate him.
- But think what will happen if he finds out.

503
00:37:20,244 --> 00:37:24,408
If I smile at him and serve his damn soup
like a good daughter, he thinks it's fine.

504
00:37:24,448 --> 00:37:26,916
- He won't find out.
- Will he not?

505
00:37:26,951 --> 00:37:31,615
Him and me are friends by oath. It is my duty
to be honest with him. I'll have to tell him.

506
00:37:31,656 --> 00:37:35,114
- You can't. You can't tell him!
- Sorry, love, but if I don't tell him

507
00:37:35,159 --> 00:37:37,184
I'm just as guilty as you two, aren't I?

508
00:37:37,228 --> 00:37:40,356
And what if he finds out?
He'll never believe I didn't know.

509
00:37:40,398 --> 00:37:43,196
His precious daughter and one of my men.

510
00:37:43,234 --> 00:37:45,464
He'll have my guts!

511
00:37:45,503 --> 00:37:47,596
This is a right fucking mess.

512
00:37:47,638 --> 00:37:50,232
Please, sir, don't tell him.

513
00:37:50,274 --> 00:37:52,242
He'll kill her.

514
00:37:52,343 --> 00:37:54,460
No, he won't go that far, I shouldn't think.

515
00:37:54,512 --> 00:37:56,275
Yes, he will. You know him.

516
00:37:56,314 --> 00:37:59,078
He's an animal.
He killed my mother. He'll kill me.

517
00:37:59,116 --> 00:38:03,883
But what am I to do?
You've put me in an impossible position here.

518
00:38:03,921 --> 00:38:06,981
I'll do anything you say.
Just please don't tell him.

519
00:38:10,962 --> 00:38:13,430
I don't know.

520
00:38:13,464 --> 00:38:16,092
Maybe.

521
00:38:17,501 --> 00:38:19,162
Maybe I can help you out.

522
00:38:20,171 --> 00:38:22,298
Thank you.

523
00:38:24,141 --> 00:38:26,905
Would you do something for me in return?

524
00:38:28,279 --> 00:38:30,577
Anything.

525
00:38:31,215 --> 00:38:34,446
Me and him do a lot of business together.

526
00:38:34,485 --> 00:38:38,114
If you kept your ears and eyes open,

527
00:38:38,155 --> 00:38:40,123
told me what was going on,

528
00:38:40,157 --> 00:38:42,250
that would be very helpful to me.

529
00:38:42,293 --> 00:38:44,227
I can do that.

530
00:38:44,261 --> 00:38:46,252
Good girl.

531
00:38:47,765 --> 00:38:49,420
It's settled, then.

532
00:38:49,467 --> 00:38:54,837
- Herod's gift will be shared three ways.
- Minus a finder's commission.

533
00:38:54,872 --> 00:38:59,138
Each of you will consult the other
before naming any officials above aedile rank.

534
00:38:59,176 --> 00:39:04,375
The same goes for the appointment of
foreign chieftains, princes, kings and so forth.

535
00:39:04,415 --> 00:39:06,508
Now, all monies received,

536
00:39:06,550 --> 00:39:09,348
including taxes,
customs revenue, military spoils

537
00:39:09,387 --> 00:39:11,947
and informal gifts and bribes,

538
00:39:11,989 --> 00:39:14,219
will be placed in the treasury

539
00:39:14,258 --> 00:39:16,920
under the supervision of a Saturnine priest.

540
00:39:16,961 --> 00:39:19,293
Fine.

541
00:39:19,330 --> 00:39:22,026
And now you must shake hands.

542
00:39:26,704 --> 00:39:28,638
Lovely. Friends again.

543
00:39:28,673 --> 00:39:30,100
That wasn't so hard, was it?

544
00:39:30,174 --> 00:39:32,506
No. If we're all done, I have work to do.

545
00:39:32,543 --> 00:39:36,070
You do realize your two bickering
has put the whole city in a panic?

546
00:39:36,113 --> 00:39:38,775
I'll have the newsreader say something,

547
00:39:38,816 --> 00:39:41,216
"Renewed vows of amity" and so forth.

548
00:39:41,252 --> 00:39:43,686
No one believes what the newsreader says.

549
00:39:44,989 --> 00:39:47,355
You have some notion you wish to suggest?

550
00:39:48,225 --> 00:39:49,886
I do.

551
00:39:51,629 --> 00:39:55,588
If a marriage was to happen
between our two houses,

552
00:39:55,633 --> 00:39:57,863
no one could doubt all was well.

553
00:39:57,902 --> 00:40:01,167
Well, I don't care if all Italy burns,

554
00:40:01,205 --> 00:40:03,605
I'll not marry him.

555
00:40:05,376 --> 00:40:07,276
It's not a bad idea.

556
00:40:08,446 --> 00:40:10,846
It would be a strong expression of unity.

557
00:40:10,881 --> 00:40:14,044
And the plebs love a good wedding.

558
00:40:18,222 --> 00:40:20,850
I have no objection.

559
00:40:20,891 --> 00:40:23,860
Thank you. I should think not.

560
00:40:24,562 --> 00:40:27,827
We should discuss it, at least.

561
00:40:27,865 --> 00:40:30,800
We could do it after Lupercalia.
It's very auspicious.

562
00:40:39,243 --> 00:40:41,211
What?

563
00:40:41,245 --> 00:40:46,740
If we are to discuss a marriage contract,
it's inappropriate for a woman to be present.

564
00:40:46,784 --> 00:40:50,515
Yes, sorry. Carry on.

565
00:40:50,554 --> 00:40:55,321
Be sure to leave enough time for
my dressmaker to make me something nice.

566
00:40:55,359 --> 00:40:57,327
Yes, Mother.

567
00:40:58,996 --> 00:41:00,964
I'm getting married.

568
00:41:00,998 --> 00:41:02,966
Antony and I are getting married.

569
00:41:03,000 --> 00:41:04,297
Where's Octavia?

570
00:41:28,826 --> 00:41:31,556
This wedding of Antony's tomorrow...

571
00:41:31,595 --> 00:41:33,859
I've just heard the dog Herod will be there.

572
00:41:33,898 --> 00:41:38,835
Him and a thousand other aristos.
There'll be lictors all over, soldiers as well.

573
00:41:38,869 --> 00:41:42,828
Watching the bride and groom,
nobody will be paying any mind to Herod.

574
00:41:42,873 --> 00:41:45,467
There'll be a big crowd, lots of noise.

575
00:41:45,509 --> 00:41:48,342
Chaos. It's the perfect time.

576
00:41:49,413 --> 00:41:51,040
I don't know.

577
00:41:52,316 --> 00:41:55,149
You're not losing your nerve, are you?

578
00:41:55,186 --> 00:41:58,053
- No.
- We made an oath on the Torah.

579
00:41:58,088 --> 00:42:00,613
And I'll not break it. I'm just saying,

580
00:42:00,658 --> 00:42:03,218
we've got to be sure,
we only get the one chance.

581
00:42:03,260 --> 00:42:05,251
This is it!

582
00:42:08,098 --> 00:42:09,588
Who knows?

583
00:42:09,633 --> 00:42:13,330
If we're lucky and the crowd's thick,
we might even make it out alive.

584
00:42:13,370 --> 00:42:16,362
No. There's no chance of that.

585
00:42:16,407 --> 00:42:19,171
We'll be hacked to pieces quick as Pan.

586
00:42:20,177 --> 00:42:22,839
His will be done.

587
00:42:22,880 --> 00:42:24,814
Tomorrow, then.

588
00:42:29,854 --> 00:42:31,822
Come, children.

589
00:42:37,728 --> 00:42:39,719
Yesh.

590
00:43:05,890 --> 00:43:08,757
- What are you doing?
- You scared me.

591
00:43:08,792 --> 00:43:11,283
I was looking for you, but you weren't here.

592
00:43:12,796 --> 00:43:14,787
Here I am.

593
00:43:17,768 --> 00:43:20,498
Are you all right? You look feverish.

594
00:43:20,537 --> 00:43:22,437
No, no, I'm good.

595
00:43:23,908 --> 00:43:25,432
Now, what do you need?

596
00:43:26,443 --> 00:43:27,637
Nothing.

597
00:43:28,812 --> 00:43:31,076
Sister needs a new dress.

598
00:43:33,450 --> 00:43:38,046
She grows like mustard.

599
00:43:38,088 --> 00:43:39,555
Thank you, Father.

600
00:43:39,590 --> 00:43:41,615
Nothing for me?

601
00:44:12,556 --> 00:44:14,547
I love you.

602
00:44:18,595 --> 00:44:21,428
We need to talk.

603
00:44:21,465 --> 00:44:23,433
Yes, we do.

604
00:44:23,467 --> 00:44:26,300
I was thinking we should take a little break.

605
00:44:27,805 --> 00:44:29,773
- A break?
- From sex.

606
00:44:29,807 --> 00:44:32,002
Just until our wedding night.

607
00:44:32,042 --> 00:44:37,378
I want our wedding night
to be something special.

608
00:44:37,414 --> 00:44:40,474
Don't you agree?

609
00:44:40,517 --> 00:44:43,577
And we have so many practical
things we need to discuss...

610
00:44:43,620 --> 00:44:47,056
Where we're going to live.
I'm happy moving into your villa,

611
00:44:47,091 --> 00:44:50,857
but it will need to be
redecorated from top to bottom.

612
00:44:50,961 --> 00:44:52,758
And I insist you sell your slaves,

613
00:44:52,796 --> 00:44:55,321
male or female,
whom you've previously fucked.

614
00:44:55,366 --> 00:44:57,163
- Atia, I...
- I insist.

615
00:44:57,201 --> 00:45:00,466
And another thing,
you still haven't bought me my wedding gift.

616
00:45:00,504 --> 00:45:03,166
I need to talk.

617
00:45:04,341 --> 00:45:06,673
Well, I'm not stopping you.

618
00:45:10,247 --> 00:45:14,047
When and where you are Gaia,

619
00:45:14,084 --> 00:45:17,645
I, then and there, am Gaius.

620
00:45:19,590 --> 00:45:23,617
When and where you are Gaius,

621
00:45:23,660 --> 00:45:26,788
I, then and there, am Gaia.

622
00:46:59,356 --> 00:47:02,018
Why so gloomy?

623
00:47:03,627 --> 00:47:06,721
No reason. A bit of a headache.

624
00:47:06,763 --> 00:47:11,291
Poor Atia.
I feel for her.

625
00:47:11,335 --> 00:47:16,637
I always thought her attachment to Antony
was purely practical, but look at her.

626
00:47:20,711 --> 00:47:24,169
I think the old girl's genuinely in love with him.

627
00:47:27,084 --> 00:47:29,075
Why did Octavian do this?

628
00:47:29,119 --> 00:47:31,519
Simple.

629
00:47:31,555 --> 00:47:34,581
Octavia is more likely to provide children.

630
00:47:34,625 --> 00:47:39,790
And what is marriage, if not a machine
for the production of babies?

631
00:47:39,830 --> 00:47:41,991
It's wrong.

632
00:47:42,032 --> 00:47:44,091
It's just wrong.

633
00:47:45,669 --> 00:47:48,194
Careful, friend. Anyone who didn't know better

634
00:47:48,238 --> 00:47:50,900
might think you were in love with Octavia.

635
00:48:00,417 --> 00:48:02,510
Blessings upon you.

636
00:48:18,168 --> 00:48:20,159
I'd rather eat shit.

637
00:48:36,720 --> 00:48:40,383
Please try to see beyond your own desires.

638
00:48:40,424 --> 00:48:42,688
I couldn't very well let you marry Antony.

639
00:48:42,726 --> 00:48:45,126
Everybody knows you were lovers.

640
00:48:45,162 --> 00:48:51,897
The public would assume it was a marriage
of mere sentiment, of lust.

641
00:48:52,002 --> 00:48:55,699
Whereas this match is clearly
a political statement of unity.

642
00:49:13,790 --> 00:49:16,088
- Atia.
- Go away.

643
00:49:16,126 --> 00:49:19,618
You cannot stay in here.
Our guests will wonder where you are.

644
00:49:19,663 --> 00:49:23,429
Well, our guests can go and fuck themselves.

645
00:49:30,507 --> 00:49:32,498
There was no choice.

646
00:49:32,542 --> 00:49:34,737
Your son would have it no other way.

647
00:49:34,778 --> 00:49:36,100
And he is your master?

648
00:49:36,179 --> 00:49:39,410
He is my political partner. Policy dictates that...

649
00:49:39,449 --> 00:49:42,009
Policy be damned. Speak plain.

650
00:49:42,052 --> 00:49:43,917
You love power more than you love me.

651
00:49:43,954 --> 00:49:47,788
They are two completely different things.

652
00:49:48,659 --> 00:49:51,150
This marriage has nothing to do with us.

653
00:49:52,763 --> 00:49:54,731
It changes nothing.

654
00:49:54,765 --> 00:49:58,565
Love, and you and I...

655
00:49:58,602 --> 00:50:00,160
It changes nothing.

656
00:50:00,203 --> 00:50:05,334
I see. First you betray me
and now you propose to betray my daughter.

657
00:50:07,911 --> 00:50:10,379
Forgive me.

658
00:51:23,653 --> 00:51:25,450
Are you ready?

659
00:51:37,768 --> 00:51:38,962
Let's go.

660
00:51:39,002 --> 00:51:40,902
- Wait.
- They're coming!

661
00:51:42,139 --> 00:51:43,697
I'm sorry, I can't do it.

662
00:51:43,740 --> 00:51:45,708
What?

663
00:51:45,742 --> 00:51:50,736
No more killing. Herod is just a man.
His death is useless. It's just more blood.

664
00:51:50,847 --> 00:51:53,111
If we kill him, another will take his place.

665
00:51:53,150 --> 00:51:55,948
- We'll kill him too.
- Not by my hand.

666
00:51:59,089 --> 00:52:01,250
Listen, you made an oath.

667
00:52:01,291 --> 00:52:03,623
I break it, then.

668
00:52:03,660 --> 00:52:05,628
Brother...

669
00:52:07,230 --> 00:52:09,425
I have a wife. I have children.

670
00:52:09,466 --> 00:52:12,264
You're a coward, a sniveling coward.

671
00:52:12,302 --> 00:52:14,270
You always were.

672
00:52:14,304 --> 00:52:16,272
I'll do it alone, then.

673
00:52:16,306 --> 00:52:18,274
No. No!

674
00:52:32,422 --> 00:52:34,686
Brother!

675
00:52:35,859 --> 00:52:37,827
You...

676
00:52:37,861 --> 00:52:40,455
are not

677
00:52:40,497 --> 00:52:43,057
my brother.

678
00:53:02,052 --> 00:53:04,646
This is strange, isn't it?

679
00:53:09,826 --> 00:53:11,885
Look, I...

680
00:53:11,928 --> 00:53:16,388
I know you're not exactly
happy about all this, but...

681
00:53:17,634 --> 00:53:20,296
it is our wedding night.

682
00:53:22,706 --> 00:53:25,038
Do as you like.

683
00:53:30,847 --> 00:53:33,441
Well, if you wouldn't mind just...

684
00:54:03,146 --> 00:54:06,138
Send her bitterness and despair

685
00:54:06,182 --> 00:54:09,345
for all of her life.

686
00:54:09,386 --> 00:54:11,354
Let her taste nothing

687
00:54:11,388 --> 00:54:15,586
but ashes and iron.

688
00:54:24,034 --> 00:54:26,696
I need silphium and hellebore.

689
00:54:28,271 --> 00:54:30,262
You caught it early.

690
00:54:32,576 --> 00:54:34,339
Yeah.

691
00:54:37,080 --> 00:54:39,071
Drink this...

692
00:54:41,952 --> 00:54:43,886
before bed...

693
00:54:46,957 --> 00:54:49,391
and when you wake

694
00:54:49,426 --> 00:54:51,394
in the morning,

695
00:54:51,494 --> 00:54:52,893
problem is over.

696
00:54:52,929 --> 00:54:54,760
How's it taste?

697
00:54:57,434 --> 00:54:58,765
I hate strong flavors.

698
00:54:58,802 --> 00:55:02,932
If you put it in willow tea,
you won't taste it at all.

699
00:55:02,973 --> 00:55:06,670
I'll give you some horsetail
in case there's much bleeding.

700
00:55:06,710 --> 00:55:08,837
No, that's all right.

701
00:55:08,878 --> 00:55:10,277
I don't need that.

