<
ROME202
Man:
COME ON!
- THIS WAY!
COME ON, QUICKLY!
MOVE!
YA-HA!
OUT OF THE WAY!
MOVE!
EVIL INSIDE.
EVIL--
VIE!
- GIVE US A KISS THEN.
- YOU SHAVE, I KISS.
YOU TALK TO HIM.
I SAID I WOULD,
AND I WILL.
WE CANNOT STAY
HERE FOREVER.
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
THIS PLACE IS
A HOUSE OF DEATH.
I KNOW.
WHAT IF WE MAKE
A BABY HERE?
GODS FORBID,
IT WOULD BE A MONSTER.
I SAID I'D
TALK TO HIM.
HEY, BROTHER.
GOOD DAY OUT.
GOOD DAY FOR A WALK
IN THE COUNTRY MAYBE.
NO.
SPRING'S HERE,
BLOSSOM ON THE TREES,
- LAMBS IN THE MEADOWS.
BROTHER, THE FULL MOON
HAS COME AND GONE.
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO CUT OFF
THESE MOURNING BEARDS, EH?
LIFE MUST CONTINUE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
- YOU SHOULD GO.
- AND LEAVE YOU
HERE LIKE THIS?
- GOOD FRIEND I'D BE.
- I'M PAST NEED OF FRIENDS.
NOW WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
YOU CAN'T JUST SIT HERE
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
I'VE CAUSED THE DEATH
OF MY WIFE.
OF MY CHILDREN.
I HAVE CAUSED THE DEATH
OF CAESAR.
WHAT WOULD YOU
HAVE ME DO NOW, HUH?
WHAT?
RUN A BUTCHER SHOP?
FINE, FINE.
SORRY I SPOKE.
EAT YOUR DAMN PORRIDGE.
WHAT SORT OF WOMAN IS SHE?
- WHO?
- THE EGYPTIAN GIRL.
OH, HER.
I BARELY MET HER.
SKINNY THING.
TALKS TOO MUCH.
WELL, SHE MUST
HAVE SOMETHING
TO LURE A COLD
FISH LIKE CAESAR.
SHE'S A QUEEN.
CAESAR WOULD'VE FUCKED
MEDUSA IF SHE'D WORN A CROWN.
YOU JEALOUS, FLOWER?
OF COURSE.
I DON'T MIND YOUR WHORES,
BUT I DON'T WANT YOU
MAKING LOVE TO HER SORT.
MEANING YOUNGER WOMEN
OF HIGHER RANK THAN...
THAT'S A GOOD GENERAL RULE.
I SHALL REMEMBER IT.
I LOVE YOU.
ANTONY?
A WORD, IF I MAY.
WHAT IS IT, DEAR BOY?
ABOUT MY MONEY--
CAESAR'S MONEY.
YOU ASSURED ME
I'D HAVE IT BY NOW.
I'M SO SORRY.
IT SLIPPED MY MIND.
I WILL SEE TO IT.
GOOD, ONLY THAT IS WHAT
YOU SAID SEVERAL TIMES NOW.
WELL, THESE THINGS
TAKE TIME.
WE ARE TALKING
VAST SUMS OF MONEY.
IT'S A GREAT DEAL
OF PAPERWORK AND LAWYERING
TO BE DONE AND--
SO WHEN CAN I EXPECT
TRANSFER TO MY CONTROL?
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
SOME WICKED WOMAN GIVING
YOU THE SQUEEZE, EH?
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL SEE TO IT.
TOLERABLE VOYAGE?
- IT WAS.
- MYSELF...
I CANNOT ABIDE
SHIPS AND BOATS.
TOO MUCH LIKE CAGES, NEH?
WITH THE ADDED
RISK OF DROWNING.
YOU'VE CHANGED
SINCE WE LAST MET.
HAVE I SEEN YOU BEFORE?
YES.
IN ALEXANDRIA,
WITH CAESAR.
IT'S THOSE UNIFORMS YOU WEAR.
YOU ALL LOOK ALIKE.
WHEN I SAW YOU THEN,
YOU SEEMED...
HAPPIER.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
A STRANGE QUESTION.
CAESAR IS DEAD.
HE WAS AS A HUSBAND TO ME.
- I WAS AS A WIFE TO HIM.
- I AMUSE YOU.
- FORGIVE ME.
IT'S AN ODD THOUGHT.
A ROMAN CONSUL WITH
A 'GYPTIAN WIFE.
- WOULDN'T DO, YOU KNOW?
- I FAIL TO SEE WHY.
I BELIEVE WE MAY
BEGIN NEGOTIATIONS.
HERE IS THE TEXT
OF OUR PROPOSAL.
WE WOULD READ IT
INTO THE SENATE RECORD.
"I MARK ANTONY,
CONSUL OF ROME,
GUARANTEE THAT OUR ARMIES
WILL CONTINUE
TO PROTECT AND PRESERVE
THE THRONE OF CLEOPATRA,
CHILD OF PTOLEMY,
QUEEN OF EGYPT,
MISTRESS OF SEDGE AND BEE,
ET CETERA, ET CETERA."
- WHAT IS YOUR PRICE?
- HER MAJESTY WILL GUARANTEE
10 GRAIN SHIPMENTS A MONTH
AT THE STANDARD RATE,
FROM WHICH REVENUES
THE CONSUL WILL ACCEPT--
AS A PERSONAL GIFT--
48,000 DENARII A MONTH.
- 35.
- 45.
42.
42, DELIVERED
ON THE KALENDS.
ARE WE DONE THEN?
ONE MORE THING.
MY SON BY CAESAR
IS NEAR FOUR YEARS OLD.
HE HAS BEGUN TO ASK
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS FATHER.
HOW TOUCHING.
HE'S TOO YOUNG
TO UNDERSTAND NOW,
BUT SOON I MUST TELL HIM
THAT HIS FATHER'S PEOPLE
DO NOT ACCEPT HIM.
NOT AS A TRUE LEGAL SON.
IT WILL NEVER HAPPEN.
THE PEOPLE WOULDN'T LIKE IT.
WE HAVE NO POLITICAL DESIGN,
MERELY THE HAPPINESS
OF MY BOY.
A SIMPLE PUBLIC DECLARATION
OF PATERNITY WOULD SUFFICE.
AND WHAT WOULD
I PROFIT BY THAT?
YOU WOULD HAVE
MY ETERNAL GRATITUDE.
THAT'S POSSIBLE.
DECLARE MY BOY
A LAWFUL SON OF CAESAR
AND WE SHALL BE FRIENDS.
- YOU DON'T TRUST ME?
- NOT SO MUCH.
YOU HAVE A CHANGEABLE
LOOK ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
STEADY AS A PRIEST
OF SATURN, ME.
COME NOW.
IT IS NOT PERMITTED
TO TOUCH.
NICE MANNERS...
FOR A WHORE.
IF I MUST PROSTITUTE MYSELF
FOR THE GOOD OF MY COUNTRY
AND MY FAMILY,
I WILL.
BUT THE CUSTOMER PAYS FIRST,
DOES HE NOT?
YOUR SON WILL
EAT SHIT AND DIE
BEFORE I MAKE HIM LEGAL.
YOU SEE?
VERY CHANGEABLE.
SORRY WE COULDN'T AGREE.
PERHAPS YOU'LL
CHANGE YOUR MIND.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT DINNER
TOMORROW, I BELIEVE.
HE WASN'T APOLLO,
BY NO MEANS,
BUT WHEN ERASTES FULMEN
WAS ALIVE THERE WAS PEACE
ON THE AVENTINE.
NOW EVERY GANG
IN THE CITY
IS FIGHTING FOR
CONTROL OF THE HILL.
EVERY DAY
THERE'S VIOLENCE.
THERE'S... HOO-HA.
- IT'S KILLING COMMERCE.
- I WILL SEE TO IT.
AND IS NOT COMMERCE
THE ROOT OF CIVIC VIRTUE?
CAN ROME LONG SURVIVE
IF COMMERCE IS--
YOU MAY GO.
SOMETHING-- SOMETHING MUST
BE DONE ON THE AVENTINE.
YES, YES, I KNOW.
I HEAR OF NOTHING ELSE.
THE GANGS WILL NOT STOP
FIGHTING OF THEIR OWN ACCORD.
IT IS TOO RICH A PRIZE.
WHOEVER CONTROLS THE AVENTINE
CONTROLS THE DOCKS
AND THE GRAIN SUPPLY--
- I AM AWARE!
- THE VIOLENCE WILL SPREAD.
IF IT IS NOT STOPPED,
THE WHOLE CITY WILL
SWIFT DESCEND
INTO CHAOS AND
FAMINE AND YOU WILL
BE BLAMED, I'M AFRAID.
THOUGH IT'D BE NONE OF YOUR
FAULT, OF COURSE.  STILL...
I WILL HANDLE IT.
NOW...
WHAT CAN
I DO FOR YOU?
- YOU SENT FOR ME.
- OH YES, THAT.
SHOW HIM.
IT APPEARS TO BE A LIST
OF EVERY DISHONEST RASCAL
IN THE CITY.
VERY DROLL.
IT IS A LIST OF CANDIDATES
FOR NEXT YEAR'S ELECTIONS
DRAWN UP BY OUR BELOVED
CAESAR JUST BEFORE HE
WAS TAKEN FROM US.
POSCA FOUND IT
AMONGST HIS PAPERS.
OH, ANOTHER LUCKY FIND?
YOU ARE PRODIGIOUS, POSCA.
I WANT YOUR ENDORSEMENT
OF THE NAMES.
FOR THE SAKE OF UNITY
AND AMITY, ET CETERA,
ET CETERA.
ISN'T THAT BEING JUST
A LITTLE TOO BRAZEN?
WHO WOULD BELIEVE THAT CAESAR
CHOSE SUCH WRETCHES?
SURELY YOU DON'T THINK
THOSE MEN PAID ME TO PUT
THEIR NAMES ON THE LIST?
NOT AT ALL.
I EXPECT THEY
HAVE PAID POSCA.
SO, WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
MY ENDORSEMENT WILL
BE WORTHLESS.
PEOPLE WILL MERELY ASSUME
I'VE BEEN INTIMIDATED BY YOU.
- ARE YOU NOT INTIMIDATED?
- NOT ESPECIALLY.
AT PRESENT,
YOU CANNOT AFFORD TO KILL ME.
YOU NEED ME
TO RUN THE SENATE.
TODAY, I NEED YOU.
- TOMORROW...
- THEN TOMORROW
I WILL WORRY.
TODAY, I SUGGEST YOU
LET ME STRIKE THE WORST
SCOUNDRELS OFF THIS LIST.
THEN I WILL ENDORSE IT.
FINE, FINE.
DO AS YOU LIKE.
A PLEASURE AS ALWAYS.
NEXT THERE IS A DELEGATION--
NO, ENOUGH.
ENOUGH OF THIS.
CALL MY GUARD.
IMMEDIATELY.
BEFORE YOU GO,
IF I MIGHT RAISE THE
MATTER OF MY RECOMPENSE
AND COMMISSION?
NO! NO, YOU MIGHT NOT,
YOU WRETCHED GREEK THIEF!
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY.
I'M SURROUNDED
BY MONEYGRUBBERS.
MARK ANTONY, SIR!
IT'S ME SIR!
TITUS PULLO OF THE 13TH!
LEGIONARY PULLO?
HOLD IT.
LET HIM THROUGH.
SIR!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
REQUIRING ADVICE AND COUNSEL
REGARDING LUCIUS VORENUS, SIR.
GO ON.
HE HAS GONE AWRY, SIR.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S TO
BE DONE WITH HIM.
Pullo:
VORENUS!
OFFICERS AFOOT!
CENTURION VORENUS.
AS WAS.
SIR?
LOOK AT THE FUCKING
STATE OF YOU.
- IT'S MOURNING DRESS, SIR--
- MOURNING?
YOU MAY WELL MOURN.
CAESAR IS DEAD,
AND IT WAS YOU AS
GOOD AS HELD THE KNIFE.
STAND AT FUCKING ATTENTION
WHEN I'M TALKING TO YOU!
YOU KNOW THAT YOUR NAME
IS DISGRED FOREVER?
I DO, SIR.
"I DO, SIR."
WHY THEN ARE YOU
STILL ALIVE?
WHY HAVE YOU NOT DONE
YOUR DAMN DUTY
AND OPENED YOUR STOMACH?
I WOULD LIKE THAT
ABOVE ALL THINGS, SIR.
BUT DIS  MY MASTER,
AND HE WILL TAKE ME
WHEN HE CHOOSES.
AT PRESENT,
HE WISHES ME TO SUFFER
HERE ON THIS EARTH.
YOU ARE WRONG,
CENTURION.
DIS IS NOT
YOUR MASTER.
I AM YOUR MASTER
BY SACRED OATH
UNDER THE STANDARDS
OF THE 13TH.
SIR.
AND THIS, I TAKE IT,
WAS ERASTES FULMEN.
I TOLD HIM TO GET RID,
BUT IT CALMS HIM
TO LOOK AT THE THING.
NOT CONTENT TO LET
OUR GREAT FATHER DIE,
YOU START A DAMN WAR
ON THE AVENTINE
THAT THREATENS TO ENGULF
THE WHOLE FUCKING CITY.
NOW...
WOULD YOU LIKE
A CHANCE TO REDEEM
YOURSELF, CENTURION?
THERE'S NO REDEMPTION.
NO MAN IS BEYOND
REDEMPTION, LUCIUS.
NOT EVEN YOU.
AND SO?
THE EGYPTIAN GIRL.
TELL ALL.
WELL, E WAS NAKED
BEFORE THE PRIESTS
HAD LE THE ROOM.
I HAD TO CALL MY PEOPLE
TO PULL HER OFF ME.
SERIOUSLY.
SHE WAS IN MOURNING.
SHE WAS VERY GRAY
AND FORMAL.
SHE WAS QUITE
THE LITTLE MOUSE.
ON JUPITER'S STONE?
ON JUNO'S CUNT.
HMM, NO.
NOTHING AT ALL
INTERESTING HAPPENED.
OH, SHE DID ASK ME
TO FORMALLY RECOGNIZE
HER BASTARD
AS CAESAR'S SON.
BLESSED IMPUDENCE!
YOU REFUSED, OF COURSE.
OCTAVIAN IS THE ONLY--
YES, YES,
OF COURSE I REFUSED.
WHICH SET OFF A GREAT FLOOD
OF ROYAL WHINING.
NO.
NO, IT'S BEEN A PIG
OF A DAY, ALL AROUND.
RUNNING THIS DAMN CITY
ISN'T NEARLY AS AMUSING
AS I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
- MMM, MY POOR LAMB.
OH, GOD.
MORE TEDIUM
TO FOLLOW THIS DAMN
DINNER TOMORROW, NO DOUBT.
IS SERVILIA COMING,
BY ANY CHANCE?
YES.
GOOD.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN BITTEN
BY A MORAY EEL?
I SHOULD THINK NOT.
WHERE'S YOUR MOTHER?
- SOMETHING WRONG?
- POSSIBLY.
- AH.
- JUNO'S MERCY.
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
I SUPPOSE ANTONY
WANTS A SHOW OF UNITY
FOR THE EGYPTIANS.
SERVILIA MY LOVE,
IT'S GOOD OF YOU TO COME.
I AM HERE UNDER PROTEST.
MARK ANTONY'S INSISTENCE.
HE'S A TERRIBLE
BULLY, ISN'T HE?
YOU MUST BE VERY SCARED.
NOT IN THE SLIGHTEST.
WELL, YOU NEED
HAVE NO FEAR OF ME.
I WISH YOU NO HARM,
TRULY.
IT'S ENOUGH FOR ME TO KNOW
THAT I HAVE WON AND YOU'VE
BEEN HUMBLED.
WE'VE BOTH SUFFERED ENOUGH.
YOU ARE MOCKING ME,
I BELIEVE.
NOT AT ALL.
I'M OFFERING YOU FRIENDSHIP,
AND RECONCILIATION
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
TWO FRIENDS TOGETHER?
I CANNOT
HONORABLY REFUSE.
I'M SO HAPPY.
KISS ME, MY DEAR.
ENJOY THE PARTY.
DID YOU SEE THE LOOK
ON HER FACE? PRICELESS.
I SAW TIMON AND SOME
OF HIS MEN IN THE YARD.
KNIFE-AND-HATCHET MEN.
- SO?
- I WAS WONDERING WHAT
THEY'RE DOING HERE.
SECURITY, WHAT ELSE?
THE OBVIOUS PURPOSE
WOULD BE THE ABDUCTION
AND KILLING OF SERVILIA
- AS SHE LEAVES THIS EVENING.
- THAT'S ABSURD.
THERE'S A TRUCE
RATIFIED BY PRIESTS.
- YOU CAN'T HARM HER.
- A TRUCE? PRIESTS?
YOU THINK THAT
BITCH CARES?
MOTHER, THERE IS MORE
AT STAKE HERE THAN YOUR
DESIRE FOR VENGEANCE.
THE POLITICAL SITUATION
IS EXTREMELY DELICATE.
HER DEATH WOULD THROW
THE REPUBLIC INTO UPROAR.
- I DON'T CARE.
- YOU'RE BEING CHILDISH.
DOES ANTONY KNOW OF THIS?
OF COURSE HE DOES.
ALL RIGHT, HE DOESN'T,
OBVIOUSLY.
AND DON'T YOU
DARE TELL HIM.
I'M SORRY, MOTHER.
YOU LITTLE BASTARD.
I WON'T BE NEEDING YOU.
YOU CAN GO NOW.
WHERE IS YOUR
DAMMED EGYPTIAN?
IT'S TIME TO SERVE DINNER.
I HAVE A GOOD MIND TO CANCEL
THE WHOLE DAMN THING.
OH, DON'T SULK.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE IN THE WRONG.
JUST AS YOU
DESCRIBED HER--
QUITE THE LITTLE MOUSE.
CLEOPATRA PHILOPATOR,
MISTRESS OF SEDGE AND BEE,
QUEEN OF BOTH UPPER
AND LOWER KINGDOMS.
PLEASE...
WE SHALL BE INFORMAL.
WE SHALL ACT AS IF
WE WERE ALL EQUALS.
IT'S MUCH MORE FUN
THAT WAY, DON'T YOU THINK?
NOW, WHO ARE ALL THESE
LOVELY PEOPLE?
UH... OUR HOSTESS,
ATIA OF THE JULII.
ATIA.
YOUR HIGHNESS.
NICE--
JUST AS YOU SAID.
COME HERE, BOY.
THIS IS MY DARLING
CAESARION.
DOES HE NOT LOOK
EXACTLY LIKE HIS
NOBLE FATHER?
UNCANNY.
LOOKS NOTHING LIKE HIM.
SHALL WE EAT?
YOU'RE BACK.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE LATE.
- HERE I AM.
- YOU'LL NEVER GUESS--
- TEVYE!
- LEVI?
RELEASE ME NOW, CHILDREN.
LET ME HUG YOUR FATHER.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
SO HAPPY TO SEE
YOUR BROTHER.
YOU GAVE ME A START,
THAT'S ALL.
I'M VERY HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
YOU COULD'VE WRITTEN.
OH, FORGIVE ME.
I CAUGHT A SHIP
ON THE TIDE'S TURN.
HERE I AM.
LOOK AT YOU?
HOW LONG'S IT BEEN?
EIGHT YEARS?
NINE.
WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE?
OH, MY PARTNERS AND I ARE
SETTING UP A NEW BUSINESS.
I'M TO RUN THE OFFICE HERE.
- YOU'LL BE STAYING
A WHILE THEN?
- IF YOU'LL HAVE ME.
OF COURSE.  OUR HOUSE
IS YOUR HOUSE.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU
MADE HIM DINNER?
NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
WE'RE NOT KOSHER.
ALREADY WE'RE NOT
GOOD ENOUGH, EH?
WELL, HAVE SOME
WINE AT LEAST.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
SO, YOU'RE STILL IN SPICES?
SPICES, CLOTH, OIL.
THANK YOU.
GOES WELL, I HOPE?
OH, UP, DOWN, UP, DOWN.
IT GOES.
MMM, AND YOU?
DEBORAH, TELLS ME
YOU'RE DOING VERY WELL.
OH, UP, DOWN.
HORSES?
HORSES.
CONSUL, FAREWELL.
YOUR VASSAL QUEEN
SHALL WEEP
UNTIL SHE SEES YOU AGAIN.
I SHALL SEE YOU SOON
THEN, I HOPE.
ATIA,
I HAVE MADE A FRIEND
FOR LIFE.
I FEEL IT.
INDEED.
KISS ME.
DIE SCREAMING,
YOU PIG-SPAWN TROLLOP.
SAFE JOURNEY,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
WHEW, I'M GLAD THAT'S-
PARTY'S OVER!
EVERYBODY CAN
GO HOME NOW!
SO TELL ME THE TRUTH NOW.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
I TOLD YOU, I'M JUST
SETTING UP A NEW BUSINESS.
YOU HATE ROME.
YOU HATE ROMANS.
HOW MANY TIMES
DID YOU TELL ME
WHAT SCUM THEY ARE?
VILE OPPRESSORS,
BABYLONIAN WHORES.
AND HOW YOU'VE COME
TO LIVE AMONGST THEM.
I DON'T THINK SO.
BUSINESS IS BUSINESS.
THIS IS WHERE THE MONEY IS.
THINGS WERE GETTING A LITTLE
HOT FOR ME IN JERUSALEM.
BETTER I LEAVE FOR A WHILE.
- THINGS?  WHAT THINGS?
- POLITICS.
- OH.
- NOTHING SERIOUS.
MAYBE I SPOKE A LITTLE
TOO FREELY.
- OH, BROTHER.
- HOW IS A MAN
TO STAY SILENT?
OUR SO-CALLED LEADERS
LICK THE BOOTS OF
ROMAN SOLDIERS.
- THE PHARISEES ARE--
- LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'RE IN ROME NOW.
YOU'RE IN MY HOUSE.
I'VE GOT A WIFE
AND CHILDREN TO THINK OF.
YOU KEEP THAT CACK TO YOURSELF.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
I HEAR YOU.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
HOLD HIM DOWN.
TAKE HIM OUT.
HE'S DEAD.
WOULD YOU DO ME
A SMALL FAVOR?
GO BACK AND TELL
MY FRIEND
THAT I HAVE GIVEN UP
TRYING TO REASON WITH HIM.
EVERYTHING ON THE AVENTINE
ABOVE PERSEPHONE'S OAK
IS MY TERRITORY NOW.
IF HE TOUCHES ANY MAN
OF MINE AGAIN,
THERE'S A GRAVE DANGER
THAT I WILL BECOME IRATE.
AND IF I DO--
CAPTAINS AND MEN
OF THE COLLEGIA:
UNDER THE AUSPICES
OF MOTHER CONCORD,
A SANCTIFIED TRUTH
IS DECLARED.
VIOLENCE SHALL CEASE
UNTIL THE WAXING
OF THE MOON.
AT THE SIXTH HOUR
ALL CAPTAINS ARE SUMMONED
TO ATTEND A PARLEY
AT THE AVENTINE COLLEGIUM.
THE FUCK'S
ALL THIS THEN?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WHO CALLED A PARLEY?
- NOBODY KNOWS.
- THE PRIEST MUST KNOW.
YOU CAN'T TALK
TO A PRIEST OF CONCORD.
- WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE YOU CAN'T,
YOU FUCKING SAVAGE.
FOREIGNERS.
MY NAME IS LUCIUS VORENUS.
I SPEAK TO YOU UNDER
THE AUTHORIZATION
OF MARK ANTONY,
CONSUL OF ROME.
CAPTAINS, FOLLOW ME.
YOU'LL HEAR SOMETHING
TO YOUR BENEFIT.
CONSUL MARK ANTONY
DECLARES YOUR CONTEST
FOR CONTROL OF THE AVENTINE
IS FINISHED.
- ALL VIOLENCE WILL CEASE.
- HE CAN DECLARE
WHAT HE LIKES.
IT DOESN'T MAKE IT SO.
AS KILLER
OF ERASTES FULMEN,
I CLAIM HIS CAPTAINCY
OF THE AVENTINE COLLEGIUM
AS MY RIGHTFUL SPOILS.
THE AVENTINE IS NOW MINE.
- YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
- YET, HERE I AM.
YOU CAN HAVE THIS OLD
RAT'S NEST IF YOU LIKE,
BUT YOU'VE GOT NO MEN.
THEY'RE ALL DEAD
OR RUN AWAY.
I'LL FIND MEN.
ROME HAS NO SHORTAGE
OF CRIMINAL SCUM.
MAYBE I'LL TAKE
SOME OF YOURS.
BROTHERS,
REMEMBER THE LADY.
WE ALL KNOW OF YOU,
LUCIUS VORENUS.
WE KNOW YOU'RE
A MAN OF GRAVITY
AND WE'RE DULY
RESPECTFUL.
YOU WOULD DO WELL
TO RETURN THAT RESPECT.
I CAN'T DO THAT, BUT I CAN
GIVE YOU COIN INSTEAD.
ONCE ORDER IS RESTORED,
ALL COLLEGIA WILL
RECEIVE A MONTHLY STIPEND
OF 5,000 DENARII
DIRECTLY FROM
CONSUL MARK ANTONY
UNDER MY SUPERVISION.
IN RETURN, HE EXPECTS YOU
WILL LIMIT TO YOURSELF
TO YOUR TRADITIONAL
LIBERTIES AND MALPRACTICES--
NOTHING THAT WILL
DISRUPT TRADE OR POLITICS.
ANYTHING ELSE?
NATURALLY, SHOULD THERE
BE CIVIL VIOLENCE,
YOU AND YOUR PEOPLE WILL
BE CALLED UPON
TO DEFEND THE RIGHTS
OF THE CONSUL.
I REQUIRE
YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT
AND ACCEPTANCE
OF THESE TERMS.
5,000 DENARII--
THAT'S NOT BAD.
IN CASH OR GRAIN?
- AS YOU LIKE.
- ARE YOU WOMEN?
ONE BARK FROM THIS RED DOG
AND YOU BEND YOUR NECK.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
GAIUS IGNUS ACERBO,
CAPTAIN OF THE OPPIAN
COLLEGES.
TELL US, WHY WOULD SANE
AND RESPECTABLE MEN
LIKE OURSELVES, DO BUSINESS
WITH A POOR, CURSED,
HOUNDED BEAST
LIKE YOU?
GAIUS IGNUS ACERBO,
YOU ASK A FAIR QUESTION.
THOSE OF YOU WHO WILL
NOT DO BUSINESS WITH ME
ARE MY ENEMY.
AND SO THEY WILL DIE
MUCH SOONER
THAN THEY EXPECT.
STEADY ON.
REMEMBER BLESSED CONCORD.
NO MENACES.
CONCORD.
I AM A SON OF HADES!
I FUCK CONCORD IN HER ASS!
- THE TRUCE IS RAISED!
- BROTHER!
ACERBO, WILL YOU
DO BUSINESS WITH ME?
YES, IT'S FUNNY,
ISN'T IT?
I WARN YOU, WOMAN.
ANOTHER WORD ABOUT
THAT DAMN GIRL AND I WILL--
YOU WILL WHAT?
WHAT WILL YOU DO?
FIGHTING AGAIN?
HOW TIRESOME.
I NEVER TOUCHED
THAT WOMAN!
SO YOU KEEP SAYING.
- GOOD MORNING.
ALL RIGHT.
ANTONY, ABOUT MY MONEY--
OH, GODS BENEATH US.
I JU--
- NOT NOW, OCTAVIAN.
- HAS THE MATTER MOVED
FORWARD AT ALL?
TELL ME, BOY,
IF I DID GIVE
YOU THE MONEY,
WHAT ON GAIA'S GREAT ASS
WOULD YOU DO WITH IT?
THAT'S A COMPLEX QUESTION,
BUT I'D CERTAINLY START
BY GIVING THE PLEBS
THE MONEY THAT
CAESAR PROMISED THEM.
THEN YOU'RE A FOOL.
BASIC POLITICS, LAD.
ONCE THEY HAVE THE MONEY
AND SPEND IT,
THEN THEY WILL
WANT MORE MONEY.
AND WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO THEN?
I WAS AFRAID
YOU'D TAKE THIS ATTITUDE,
SO I'VE ENGAGED A LAWYER.
A LAWYER.
HMMM.
HE CAN HELP POSCA EXPEDITE
THE DELAY IN TRANSFERRING
THE MONEY TO ME.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
ANTONY'S FAMILY.
HE'S NOT, ACTUALLY.
ALL RIGHT, BOY,
YOU CAN TELL YOUR LAWYER
TO SHOVE A TAPER UP HIS ASS
AND SET HIMSELF ALIGHT.
YOU'LL NOT GET ONE BRASS
OBOL OF THAT MONEY.
NOTHING.
COME ON, MY LOVE.
BROTHER, WILL YOU PASS
THE FRUIT SALAD?
SEE WHAT YOU'VE DONE?
I'M SORRY IF I'VE
DISTURBED YOUR LOVE AFFAIR.
- I MERELY--
- OH, SHUT UP, YOU FOOL.
LOVE AFFAIR BE DAMNED.
YOU WILL APOLOGIZE
AND PROMISE TO STOP
ALL THIS TALK ABOUT MONEY.
TELL HIM THAT YOU'RE
PERFECTLY HAPPY
FOR HIM TO ADMINISTER
CAESAR'S ESTATE.
- BUT I'M NOT HAPPY.
- DO YOU THINK I AM?
WHAT CHOICE DO WE HAVE?
DON'T YOU SEE WE'RE
DEPENDENT ON ANTONY NOW?
WHO WILL PROTECT
US IF YOU DRIVE HIM
AWAY FROM ME? WHO?
- I'M PERFECTLY CAPABLE.
- OH, PLEASE DON'T.
MARK ANTONY BUGGERS
BOYS LIKE YOU FOR
A MORNING SNACK.
YOU WILL APOLOGIZE,
AND THERE'S AN END ON IT.
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH
FIGS IN THIS SALAD.
HEY.
HEY!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
VAI.
VAI!
OFF WITH YOU!
THANK YOU, SIR.
PLEASE, SIR, I NEED WORK.
I'LL DO ANYTHING.
I'LL SUCK YOUR COCK.
WHY ARE YOU MAKING ALL
THIS FUSS OVER THE MONEY?
IT WAS OBVIOUS HE WOULD
NEVER GIVE IT TO YOU.
ALL YOU'RE DOING
IS MAKING MOTHER ANXIOUS.
SISTER,
YOU MUST PROMISE ME
NEVER TO SPEAK OF WHAT
I TELL YOU NOW.
OH, GODS.
I PROMISE.
THE REPUBLIC IS ON
THE BRINK OF AN ABYSS.
ANTONY-- ANTONY'S
A DESTRUCTIVE BRUTE.
THE SENATE IS WEAK
AND COWARDLY,
AND THE PLEBS ARE ROILING
IN WANT AND ANGER.
ROME IS IN NEED
OF NEW LEADERSHIP.
I CAN PROVIDE
THAT LEADERSHIP.
NOW, I ALREADY HAVE
SEVERAL INITIATIVES ON--
Pullo:
IT'LL COME TO NO GOOD,
THIS HADES BUSINESS.
WORKED THOUGH, DIDN'T IT?
THE BASTARDS FELL INTO LINE.
OH, YOU SCARED THE FUCK
OUT OF THEM RIGHT ENOUGH,
BUT THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
YOU'RE NO SON OF HADES.
YOU'RE A MORTAL MAN.
THE GODS DON'T LIKE
THIS SORT OF SHIT
FROM MORTAL MEN.
I'M FOLLOWING THE ORDERS
OF A CONSUL OF ROME,
MY MASTER BY OATH,
FOR THE SAKE OF PEACE
AND PUBLIC ORDER,
FOR THE GOOD
OF THE REPUBLIC.
ARE YOU WITH ME OR NOT?
I'M WITH YOU.
BY GRACE OF JUPITER,
GAIUS OCTAVIAN CAESAR,
LAWFUL SON OF GAIUS
JULIUS CAESAR,
MAKES THIS HIS PLEDGE:
THAT HE PERSONALLY
WILL FULFILL THE TERMS
OF HIS BELOVED FATHER'S
BEQUEST TO THE PEOPLE.
IN THE FIELDS OF MARS
NEXT NINE DAYS,
ALL ELIGIBLE CITIZENS
AND SOLDIERS
WILL RECEIVE 300 SESTERTIA
FROM THE HANDS
OF OCTAVIAN CAESAR HIMSELF!
- LET IT BE KNOWN
THAT CAESAR'S SON
HAS SOLD AWAY
ALL HIS OWN PROPERTY
TO HONOR
HIS FATHER'S WISHES.
MAY SUCH PIETY
BRING BLESSINGS UPON HIM.
- WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
- WAKE UP!
WAKE UP AT ONCE!
WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS?
WHAT?
THE MONEY!  YOU'RE GIVING
THE PLEBS THEIR MONEY!
IS IT SO LATE ALREADY?
I'VE OVERSLEPT.
I DON'T CARE.
WHAT ABOUT THE MONEY?
I'VE PROMISED IT.
I'M SORRY I DIDN'T
TELL YOU BEFORE NOW.
I KNEW YOU'D OBJECT.
I'VE DECIDED TO ENTER
PUBLIC LIFE.
THIS SEEMED THE BEST WAY
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF
TO THE PEOPLE.
Antony:
THAT WILL BE SEEN
AS A DIRECT CHALLENGE
TO ME.
YES, BUT THAT ISN'T
MY INTENTION AT ALL.
I SUGGEST WE MAKE
A PUBLIC DISPLAY OF UNITY
TO QUASH SUCH NOTIONS.
A PUBLIC DISPLAY OF UNITY!
WHA--
IT MAKES SENSE.
OUR INTERESTS ARE CONJOINED.
WHILE YOU ARE CONSUL,
MY NAME WILL LEND
WEIGHT TO YOURS.
AND WHEN YOUR
CONSULSHIP IS OVER,
AND YOU RETIRE FROM POLITICS
AS YOU HAVE PROMISED,
I WILL STEP IN AS LEADER
OF THE CAESARIAN PARTY.
I SEE.
YOU WILL NEED PROTECTION
FROM YOUR ENEMIES
IN THE SENATE,
AND I CAN PROVIDE THAT.
JUST WHO THE FUCK
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
- I'M CAESAR'S RIGHTFUL HEIR.
- NO, JUST STAY CALM.
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE MONEY,
SO HE CAN'T GIVE IT AWAY,
CAN HE?
THIS IS ALL JUST
CHILDISH TALK.
THE MONEY IS LEGALLY MINE.
I WAS ABLE TO BORROW
AGAINST IT.
- BORROW?
HOW MUCH DID YOU BORROW?
IT'S NOT SO MUCH
IN THE GREAT SCHEME
OF THINGS.
HOW MUCH?
THREE MILLION SESTERTII.
OH, JUNO'S CUNT!
YOU STUPID--
YOU STUPID BOY!
YOU--
YOU STUPID LITTLE SHIT!
FUCKING WHORE!
- APOLOGIZE.
- THAT'S IT.
NOW JUST LEAVE IT NOW.
- APOLOGIZE!
- NO!
NO, ENOUGH.
( snarls )
LITTLE FUCK.
Atia: ANTONY!
STOP IT!
ANTONY, LEAVE HIM!
( both grunting )
LEAVE HIM.  LEAVE HIM.
LEAVE HIM.  LOOK AT ME!
LOOK AT ME!
STOP IT!
STOP IT.
Octavia:
JUNO'S MERCY!
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU'RE BREATHING!
- DO YOU HEAR ME, BOY?
- COME ON.
- YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU'RE BREATHING!
- ANIMAL!
YOU'RE NOT FIT
TO LEAD ROME!
WHO ARE YOU THEN?
SLAVE OF THE COLLEGE BROTHEL
SORRY, LOVE,
WE'VE ENTY OF WHORES.
NO, I'M NO WHORE.
YOU GONNA MAKE ME GUESS?
SUPERVISOR.
I HANDLE THE GIRLS,
KEEP THE CUSTOMERS IN LINE.
NAME?
ROMANS CALL ME GAIA.
WHAT DO YOUR OWN
PEOPLE CALL YOU?
NOT YOUR BUSINESS.
FAIR ENOUGH.
I GET MY OWN ROOM,
I EAT WHAT I WANT.
EVERY 500 COINS THAT COMES
THROUGH THE BROTHEL, I GET ONE.
SAVING UP TO BUY
YOUR FREEDOM, ARE YOU?
NO, A FUR COAT.
SIGN HER UP.
THANKS, BOSS.
BROTHER MASCIUS.
PULLO, YOU BLACK DOG.
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE?
YOU'VE COME
TO JOIN UP, THEN?
I HEARD YOU WERE HIRING.
OH, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
WELL SET-- FARM AND ALL.
OH, CROOKED DICE
DONE FOR THAT.
- SHAME.
- WHAT CAN YOU DO?
DIDN'T LIKE FARMING
MUCH ANYWAY.
BE SURE ABOUT THIS, BROTHER.
IT'S A DARK ROAD WE'RE ON.
NO ONE KNOWS WHERE
IT WILL LEAD.
ALL ROADS LEAD TO THE SAME
PLACE, DON'T THEY?
THAT THEY DO.
GLAD TO HAVE YOU WITH US.
COME THROUGH THE BACK
AND SAY HELLO TO VORENUS,
- CHEER UP THE OLD BASTARD.
- IS IT TRUE WHAT
THEY SAY THEN?
- ABOUT THE WIFE AND CHILDREN?
- TRUE ENOUGH.
NOT A FUCKING WORD.
- BROTHER VORENUS.
- MASCIUS, HOW ARE YOU?
I'M FAIR.  FAIR.
COME TO JOIN
OUR MERRY BAND.
YOU TRIED TO WARN
HIM OFF, DID YOU?
I DID.
THIS ISN'T THE ARMY,
BROTHER.
WE'RE HERE WITH THE PIMPS,
KNIFEMEN, THIEVES.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'VE SUNK SO LOW?
I WALKED HERE FROM CAPUA.
I SLEPT IN DITCHES.
WHEN I GET HERE,
I HEAR PEOPLE TALKING.
THEY SAY A BLACK-HEARTED
VILLAIN HAS TAKEN OVER
THE AVENTINE COLLEGE.
HE'S IN LEAGUE WITH THE GODS
BELOW, THEY SAY.
AND HIS NAME
IS LUCIUS VORENUS.
I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
"MASCIUS, OLD BOY,
YOUR LUCK HAS CHANGED."
SEE, PULLO, I TOLD YOU
I KNOW WHAT I'M ABOUT.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
THE GODS DON'T LIKE IT.
YEAH.
WHAT MORE CAN THE GODS
DO TO ME?
HOW CAN THEY PUNISH ME NOW?
DON'T KNOW.
DON'T WANNA FIND OUT.
Servilia:
HAVE YOU HEARD
THE GOOD NEWS?
I HAVE.
THIS IS THE BEGINNING
OF THE END FOR THEM.
FROM YOUR LIPS
TO THE EARS OF THE GODS.
A FOOL LIKE ANTONY
WAS SURE TO BLUNDER.
THEY'LL FIGHT AMONG
THEMSELVES AND THEY'LL
DESTROY EACH OTHER.
I DOUBT THE BOY
WILL BE MORE THAN
A NUISANCE TO ANTONY.
HE CANNOHOPE
TO RIVAL HIM.
CAESAR DID NOT
CHOOSE THE BOY ON A WHIM.
- HE'LL SURPRISE
YOU, I THINK.
- WE CAN HOPE.
THE SENATE SHOULD ASK
MY SON TO RETURN.
THE TIME IS RIGHT.
BRUTUS RETURN?
NO.
NOT YET.
- NOT QUITE YET, I THINK.
- WHEN?
WE MUST WAIT AND SEE
HOW THINGS DEVELOP.
WAIT AND SEE?
A NOBLE STRATEGY.
NOT NOBLE, PERHAPS,
BUT SENSIBLE.
IN ANY CASE,
TELL YOUR SON THAT I--
NO, NOT I--
HIS FRIENDS IN ROME
LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING
HIM AGAIN
AT SOME POINT
IN THE NEAR FUTURE.
HMM.
I WILL TELL HIM.
Octavian:
"MY DEAR MOTHER,
I WRITE TO BID YOU FAREWELL.
I'M VERY SORRY YOU CHOSE
TO ACT AS YOU DID.
I HOPE IN TIME YOU WILL
UNDERSTAND THE GRAVITY
OF YOUR MISTAKE.
BE ASSURED,
I'M AS DETERMINED AS EVER
TO PURSUE
A POLITICAL CAREER.
DO NOT BE CONCERNED
FOR MY SAFETY.
I'M ON THE ROAD SOUTH
TO CAMPAGNA
WHERE I'LL STAY
WITH MY FRIEND AGRIPPA
WHO IS WELL
ESTABLISHED THERE.
I REMAIN YOUR RESPECTFUL SON,
OCTAVIAN."