RONDA: You know, you
look really good today.
Can I take a picture? (Chuckles)
- CAITLYN: Let's see it.
- RONDA: Stop.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- RONDA: Oh. Oh, I video'd you
by accident... you want to see?
(over phone): Hold on.
- I'm not really good with this phone.
- COURTNEY: Do your favorite pose.
RONDA: I hate my voice.
COURTNEY: Oh, I hate mine. I just hate it.
- RONDA: I want to show you how pretty you are.
- CAITLYN: I don't look good in pictures.
- RONDA: Yes, you do.
- CAITLYN: Unless it's Annie Leibovitz.
The only thing that bothers me about that,
I really haven't heard my voice, you know?
And any trans person,
the voice is always, like...
- RONDA: What do you mean?
- CAITLYN: ... you know, scary.
- What do you mean you haven't heard your voice?
- Well, you... you obviously don't have
the feminine voice, and
that kind of bothers you.
COURTNEY: There's a voice coach app.
CAITLYN: Oh, okay.
COURTNEY: And it tests your
pitch and you can practice.
So you're gonna say the
word "he" over and over.
- CAITLYN: What is it?
- COURTNEY: "He."
- H-E.
- CAITLYN: Oh, "he." Eh...
- Just normally? Sorry. Just...
- COURTNEY: Yeah.
- just say it normally?
- Yeah, however you want to say it.
- RONDA: You need a lesson.
- Okay.
CAITLYN (cracking): He.
- (laughing)
- RONDA: Cracking the voice.
CAITLYN: I got to do
it again. Wait a second.
(high-pitched): He, he, he, he.
One thing that's always a
challenge for anybody is your voice.
That can out you every time.
You know? You look great,
you look fabulous, and...
(deeply): then you open
up your voice, you know?
And everybody goes... (gasps) "Oh, my God."
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
COURTNEY: 70%.
CAITLYN: My voice has
never been terribly bad,
but it's... it's certainly not quite right.
- He...
- ALL: He...
(laughing)
♪
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
- (birds chirping)
- (doorbell rings)
(door opens)
- KIM: Look at you.
- CAITLYN: My Kimmy's here.
KIM: Look at you. Are
we wearing the same tank?
Hmm.
CAITLYN: I think so. Hello, baby,
- I haven't seen little Malika in a while.
- MALIKA: A while.
- CAITLYN: How are you doing?
- MALIKA: Good. How are you?
- I love your eyes.
- CAITLYN: Have a seat.
Um, talking about looks, honestly,
this girl thing is a lot of work.
- MALIKA: Yeah, it is.
- CAITLYN: Yes, it is.
Do you have any feminine tips?
Here we have two very feminine women.
MALIKA: Men and women eat very different.
As a woman, you have to
be very mindful. Like,
I'm not saying you can never
touch a rib again, but, like,
- the way you eat...
- CAITLYN: Touch the rib
in the privacy of your...
- your own room or anything, yeah.
- MALIKA: Just some things, you know?
- Exactly.
- CAITLYN: But, actually,
- that's a good tip.
- MALIKA: How are you clearing the... You...
Okay, you don't have on heels.
I was gonna say, if you're
gonna clear this doorway,
- you know...
- CAITLYN: Oh, just because you're...
you're so short
and you got to wear massive heels...
MALIKA: No, but it's just like you can't
- bend all the way to the side.
- CAITLYN: Oh, please, look,
plenty of clearance, girl.
- Look at this. Look at this.
- MALIKA: I was just telling her, she can't do that. Like, it's not...
- That's fi... But when you have heels on...
- CAITLYN: Not even close.
- Not even close.
- MALIKA: When she wears heels
and they're, like,
- four or five inches...
- CAITLYN: Don't be jealous of my height
- and start to put me down.
- MALIKA: I'm completely jealous of your height.
CAITLYN: Yes.
Being feminine,
you got to kind of learn everything.
Jenny Boylan did a book
on her transition,
and she had a statement in
there and I... just I loved it.
And she says,
"I never felt feminine,
but I always felt female."
And I'm, "Ah."
That kind of hits the
nail on the head for me.
KIM: Like, you never felt feminine
'cause you're a tomboy.
CAITLYN: Yeah, but I always felt female.
KIM: Mm-hmm.
CAITLYN: But for so many years,
um, you depress all of that.
All I want to do is just
kind of slip into society.
One thing that
I really need to work
on is kind of that voice.
KIM: Well, at least your
voice isn't that deep,
so it's not like you're...
(deeply): "Hello."
CAITLYN: No, it's not that
deep, and I... it's okay.
- KIM: What about vocal lessons?
- CAITLYN: Yeah,
you may be able to, I
think, with some training,
'cause a lot of people go
through training. In fact, um,
I want to show you.
Here we go.
WOMAN (deeply): When the sunlight
strikes raindrops in the air,
they act as a prism...
CAITLYN: That's before.
WOMAN: The rainbow is a division of
white light into many beautiful colors.
(high-pitched): Rainbow passage.
When the sunlight strikes
raindrops in the air,
they act as a prism and form a rainbow.
- KIM: Wow.
- WOMAN: The rainbow is a division of
white light into many beautiful colors.
MALIKA: That's a big difference.
CAITLYN: That is a huge difference.
KIM: Just, like, try out some
voices, like, that are just
a little lighter. Have you ever tried, or
is it gonna be too much
work if you're like...
- (high-pitched): "Hi."
- CAITLYN: I used to,
for years,
like, if you called down
for room service, okay,
okay, I'd be sitting there in my
room, all by my little lonesome,
and I'd think, "Okay, now, I'm
gonna try to get my best feminine
voice and call down so
they say, 'Yes, ma'am.'"
I could never do it.
- KIM: Like, go... Okay, try. Let's hear.
- CAITLYN: What?
KIM: Let's hear... Yeah. I'll
tell you if you get a "yes, ma'am."
CAITLYN: Well... (chuckles)
KIM: Front desk.
Hey, this is room service.
How can I help you?
CAITLYN: Okay.
Um...
- KIM: Order bacon and eggs.
- CAITLYN: Yes.
- KIM: And an orange juice. And toast.
- CAITLYN: Okay.
Um... Yes, actually, you can help me.
- Um...
- KIM: You sound no different!
- CAITLYN: I didn't think so.
- KIM: No. Sir, sir, what would you like, sir?
CAITLYN: Sir, yeah, what
would you like? Yeah.
See, that's the problem.
Women cannot relate to
the whole voice thing.
They don't see it as being that important
when it is that important,
not only for you just to speak and order
and do all that kind of stuff but
very important for your soul that
you're feeling good about that.
There are things that you
can do to change your pitch.
KIM: Really? Like what?
CAITLYN: Surgery.
- MALIKA: Why surgery?
- CAITLYN: Well, I was thinking
- about starting there...
- KIM: Surgery would scare the
- (bleep) out of me.
- MALIKA: What if you had no voice at all?
KIM: What if they made a mistake
and you, like, came out with no voice?
(gulls crying)
PRODUCER: What's different
about tonight's girls' night?
'Cause you've been doing girls' nights
- for a while, right?
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
You know, for a long time, I've been
doing... having all the girls over.
But tonight
- we have all trans girls.
- JENNY: Hello.
- COURTNEY: Hi.
- JENNY: I'm looking for the lady of the house.
- RONDA: Jennifer's here.
- CAITLYN: Right here.
- COURTNEY: There she is.
- JENNY: Hi, darling.
CAITLYN: Hey, baby. Are you ready for this?
JENNY: I am so ready. I'm
Jennifer Finney Boylan.
Caitlyn and I met when she was
doing the Diane Sawyer special.
I'm an author and I'm a professor
at Barnard College in New York City.
I'm also the co-chair of GLAAD,
the LGBT advocacy organization.
I'm a transgender woman,
and I've been married
to my wife for 27 years,
12 as
husband and wife and 15 as wife and wife.
CAITLYN: We're gonna do a little glam.
COURTNEY: What are you thinking?
Like, what's your favorite way
to wear your hair that you love?
JENNY: Kind of like... kind of like this.
As befits the dignity of my station.
Do you have any idea
what I'm talking about?
CAITLYN: I would be scared
to death to take your class.
- JENNY: Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- CAITLYN: I would be.
JENNY: We couldn't come
from more different worlds,
you know? I am this New England academic,
and, you know, she lives here in Malibu.
It's kind of freaky
that we got to be friends
at all, but here we are.
CAITLYN: Jenny, this is looking so good.
JENNY: I can feel my IQ plummeting.
- (laughter)
- CAITLYN: Oh, no!
- COURTNEY: No!
- CAITLYN: You didn't just say that!
JENNY: It's just a joke.
- Everyone relax.
- CAITLYN: What size are you?
I have something in the
closet I want you to wear.
It's just a wraparound.
- JENNY: Oh, I think it's too formal.
- CAITLYN: Try it on.
We'll leave you in here. Try it on.
JENNY: Wait, what was that look?
My paws and whiskers. Did
you just give me a look?
You just gave me a freaking look.
CAITLYN: If you want to
go with a great skirt...
JENNY: (sighs) Well, I could try it on.
For Caitlyn, being pretty, being
beautiful, caring about clothes
and makeup is really important.
But there are more important
things than what you look like.
- CAITLYN: Oh, you even got the purse!
- JENNY: I got your purse.
CAITLYN: Look how cute
and adorable you look.
JENNY: She has the problem of not knowing
the community really well.
She's a stranger in some
ways to the community.
Now, let me ask you this.
Nervous?
CAITLYN: Off the charts. But
pressure's good, something
that's very positive to me.
Pressure makes me think.
JENNY: I invited a diverse group of
transgender women for Cait to meet
and get a sense of our community.
However, Caitlyn is a person of
tremendous privilege and power.
I'm a little afraid about
what's going to happen
when she meets a lot of transgender people
who... who don't have the privilege
- that... that she has had.
- (Doorbell rings)
CAITLYN: And here they come.
CAITLYN: We're gonna do this.
- JENNY: All right, let's go get 'em.
- CAITLYN: We're gonna do this.
Hello.
- The first to arrive, baby, how are you doing?
- CANDIS: Hello.
- You look incredible.
- CAITLYN: And so do you!
- CANDIS: Yay.
- CAITLYN: How are you doing, babe?
CANDIS: I'm doing great.
My name is Candis Cayne,
and I'm an actress, showgirl, performer,
high-kicker, high-stepper.
JENNY: I've never been with
so many tall women in my life.
CAITLYN: Isn't it great?
You're the shortest one in the room.
- JENNY: I know! One second...
- CANDIS: When I started my transition
in '95,
there was no manual,
there was no way of, like,
figuring out how to do it. It
was all kind of black market.
Get your shots from the corner
store that had a, you know,
a secret knock to get your hormones,
you know, that kind of thing.
- RONDA: I'm Ronda.
- CHANDI: Hi, Ronda, I'm Chandi.
- RONDA: Nice to meet you.
- CAITLYN: Hello.
DRIAN: Hi, oh, my God, I
didn't recognize you...
- you look incredible.
- CAITLYN: Well, I know.
I know.
- Come on, let's go in the living room, we'll sit down.
- CHANDI: All righty.
CAITLYN: This is so much fun.
COURTNEY: They have a lot to talk about.
- CAITLYN: It's pronounced "Shardee"? Or...
- CHANDI: Chandi.
- CAITLYN: Chandi, okay, with an "N."
- CHANDI: Like "Candy."
CAITLYN: Okay... I got
to get 'em all right.
CHANDI: The transition period for me...
it was rough.
Uh, totally a different journey
than what Caitlyn experienced.
It was hard enough for my family
to accept me being gay,
but to want to be considered a woman...
that was, like, taking
it to the next level.
- CAITLYN: You made it!
- JEN: Yes, I did, hi, how are you?
CAITLYN: Good, good to see you,
thank you for coming. Thanks for coming.
JEN: My pleasure. My name is Jen Richards.
I came out and transitioned about
three and a half years ago.
At the time, I was the managing director of
a contemporary classical chamber ensemble.
About that time, I also
started engaging in activism.
I launched a Web site
called We Happy Trans,
which was designed to highlight
positive trans experiences.
I was kind of tired of only
hearing about trans people
all in their death.
I really wanted a chance
to shine a spotlight
on the people who are alive
and doing great work today.
- ZACKARY: You look incredible.
- CAITLYN: Thank you.
- DRIAN: I didn't recognize her.
- ZACKARY: You look really, truly incredible.
CAITLYN: I appreciate that.
CANDIS: It's difficult
for somebody that has
been so sheltered to understand
the life of-of some trans women,
but I think by asking us all
to share our experiences,
Cait's doing the right thing:
she's learning from people
who've lived the life.
CAITLYN: I am so excited
about this evening.
Um,
I got a lot to learn, you know?
- I've been out for two weeks.
- CANDIS: Yay, welcome!
CAITLYN: I'm a baby, okay, yay! Okay.
Yeah, I'm talking all of
your fantasies in life
coming true when Vanity
Fair was here, shooting.
- Annie Leibovitz started crying.
- JEN: Wow, amazing.
COURTNEY: She's loving this.
- She's never had a girls' night like this.
- RONDA: I know.
I feel kind of jealous.
DRIAN: This is really just
a monumental event, you know?
I remember growing up with
no trans people anywhere.
- CHANDI: Right.
- DRIAN: And so, to see somebody
on the cover of Vanity Fair,
on the Diane Sawyer
interview... that is changing
- for the children, especially.
- JEN: So inspirational.
DRIAN: I love being a trans
person. It's a true gift.
And I always think about
the youth who are suffering
and who are in states
where they can't transition,
they can't live free lives.
You know, for them to see that
you may be struggling right
now, but that's not forever.
And there's definitely a
light at the end of the tunnel,
and you just have to be true
to yourself and love yourself.
CHANDI: I love having
conversations with people
who try to tell me that
I'm going to hell for
being secure in who I
am, when God knew who...
who I was before I did.
We bleed the same, so why not use love?
- Just love.
- JEN: Right.
CHANDI: It's not that hard.
It's not that hard for us
to be able to embrace things
that we may not understand.
COURTNEY: In the community,
do you think people are going to embrace
Caitlyn and what she's done?
Or do you think they're going to
be envious?
JENNY: What you should expect people to say
is, "Caitlyn is a sweet, smart, good soul
who wants to do good in the world, but has
every advantage, every
privilege in the world."
And that the world is full of people
that no one wants to take their picture.
JEN: We can support an individual
trans person and celebrate
their authenticity and
their... their place for dignity
and what they do with their privilege
while still calling into question a system
that makes this particular story
the one that we finally listen to
while we've been ignoring
the stories of black and Latina
trans women, poor trans women.
Cait's experience of
coming out is singular.
I... I don't think in
history anyone has ever
been so publicly welcomed.
For most of us, coming out is
a really kind of terrifying,
horrifying experience.
And it's a little discomforting that
everything Cait says is gonna
receive far more attention
than anything anyone else
in the community will say,
and she has relatively little
experience in the community.
So I think everyone is
a little bit cautious.
CANDIS: You know, the trans
community was invisible ten years ago.
- CHANDI: Yes.
- CANDIS: So the fact...
JEN: Except for Jerry Springer.
CANDIS: Except for Jerry Springer.
JEN: Maury Povich and Donahue and...
CANDIS: Exactly, and so to actually...
to... to be, as an actress, to be doing
roles and, like, going to auditions...
- that's, like, a huge thing.
- JEN: Right.
CANDIS: But, like, then you
have other stuff, like life and
trying to pay rent and
trying to get medical care.
I mean, you know, just last year
I was trying to find a doctor
to get hormones from. You know what I mean?
And I tried to go into
the... to the LBG center,
and they were like, "We're booked up."
My girlfriend was like,
"Come to my doctor."
And I went in and the doctor said to her,
"Oh, you're not bringing any
more of those people in, are you?"
CAITLYN: Really?
- JENNY: "Those people."
- CHANDI: "Those people."
CANDIS: And I was like,
- "Wow," like, it's still happening, you know?
- CHANDI: Still, today.
CAITLYN: Really, that happened to you?
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- CHANDI: Yes, Cait,
that happens all the time... a
day in the life of being trans.
CAITLYN: Wow.
Hearing Candis' story is shocking to me.
Um, I can't believe
some people would act that way.
Honestly,
this is really scaring me.
I have been catapulted into the spotlight,
becoming a spokesperson for
the transgender community,
but, oh, my God,
what if people turn on me like that?
RONDA: Dinner is served!
CAITLYN: Okay, let's go, come
on, let's go get something to eat.
DRIAN: Let's do it.
JENNY: I... I will tell you that my...
that my last name is Boylan... Jenny Boylan.
There are... my students
have not... have called me "J. Bo."
CAITLYN: Really?
JENNY: Which I think is very funny.
CHANDI: Well, I came
from the world of drag.
And I needed to come up
with a name really quick,
so I became Miss Chandelier, and
then, as I decided to
transition and become full-time,
I felt like Chandelier was
too dramatic for the daytime.
So I chopped it off to
Chandi and it has stuck.
- So that's kind of, like, how I got my name.
- JENNY: Wow, that's a great story.
JEN: I don't think any
of us can top that...
we should have gone with
you last. That's too good.
JENNY: I cannot top that.
The first night you were ever in a
room with with... with more than one
transgender woman was...
CAITLYN: Oh, about an hour
ago, couple hours ago, yeah.
CANDIS: Oh, my God, that's amazing.
- CAITLYN: Yeah. I... I couldn't.
- CANDIS: That's amazing.
CAITLYN: I was isolated from
the world, I couldn't do that.
'Cause I moved in here and then
kind of had one little, uh,
procedure after another, here.
- CANDIS: Well, it's worked, honey.
- CAITLYN: I know.
(Laughs) CANDIS: Whatever
they did, it worked.
- CAITLYN: Oh, yeah, yeah.
- CANDIS: You look... you look amazing.
CAITLYN: But, um,
actually, one of the things
I've wondered about...
everybody seems to have
pretty good vocal cords.
That's always been a concern
for me, from the beginning.
JEN: Ah, interesting.
CAITLYN: What have you guys done?
CHANDI: I haven't done one thing.
CAITLYN: Thank God,
girl, I like that, okay?
CHANDI: When people say, "Oh,
you need to talk like this."
Child, cheese, I don't have time
to be trying to maintain that.
I feel like if you're gonna accept me,
you're gonna accept me, so...
- JEN: I worked really hard on changing my voice.
- DRIAN: Really?
JEN: Oh, God, yeah. My
voice was lower than yours,
much lower than yours.
Um, I did see a vocal therapist in
Chicago... God, I've never talked about this.
Um, but, yeah, I did see
a vocal therapist and just
learned some basic techniques to
raise the pitch a... a little bit.
I just hated being
called "sir" on the phone.
I hated being outed by my voice.
CANDIS: I was walking in a New York
subway and I was feeling grand prize
and I was in my skirt
and I was flipping my hair
and this, like,
woman walks by me, she's, like,
limping... she has, like, a cane.
So I hear a clunk, clunk. "That's a man."
- JENNY: Yeah.
- CANDIS: And I hear it louder.
- "That's a man."
- CAITLYN: And just...
CANDIS: And then starting
going, "That's a man!"
- (laughter)
- And I...
ZACKARY: And once you've survived that,
you realize that it's okay.
- (laughter, overlapping chatter)
- CANDIS: Yeah, you can survive anything.
- ZACKARY: Confidence is contagious.
- DRIAN: Yes. Yes.
- CAITLYN: Totally. Yeah.
- CHANDI: Right.
JEN: Guys, what we need is one straight
male celebrity to stand
up in public and say,
"Yeah, my girlfriend's
trans. She's a woman."
CHANDI: Right.
CAITLYN: Does anybody...
does anybody know one?
- JEN: No. Never.
- CHANDI: No.
JENNY: And the narrative is,
it's so much more shameful
than some other woman, you know?
JEN: Yup. Exactly.
DRIAN: Oh, yeah.
I was an immigrant, so I came to this
country not speaking the language, not,
- you know, being familiar with anything.
- CAITLYN: Where did you come from?
DRIAN: Mexico,
and so, acclimating to culture
and being gender variant,
um, you know, it was always
really tough. And, um,
I had gone to college, I
had a degree, I was working,
and my insurance didn't cover any
of my transitional-related care.
And at that point, I was doing sex work.
That was the only way I could transition.
If I couldn't transition,
I didn't want to live anymore.
I just didn't want to live a lie.
I wanted to be myself.
And I was asking the universe.
I was saying, "Change
the way I see the world
- so I can see my way out of doing sex work."
- CAITLYN: Hmm.
DRIAN: So I felt really
horrible about that,
- that I really...
- CAITLYN: Have you ever
- talked to Janet Mock about it?
- DRIAN: No.
CAITLYN: You should read her book.
- DRIAN: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: That's how she paid for it.
CHANDI: Cait thinks that because
she read a couple of pages in a book
that she's in the know,
but she doesn't get it.
She doesn't realize how
common sex work stories are.
She could never understand how it
would feel to walk in those shoes.
If she's going to become
our representative,
Cait needs to learn the
struggle we all face.
CAITLYN: I say we go to San Francisco.
- We could rent a bus. Like Priscilla.
- Seriously?
- JENNY: How do we sneak you out of here?
- CAITLYN: In a trunk.
Uh, could this be the paparazzi right here?
- Are we moving?
- RONDA: All right. Yes.
- RONDA: Jump in behind...
- CAITLYN: Hello, girls!
I still haven't been able to access
what you've been able to access so quickly.
Let's just be real, it had something
to do with your socio-economical status.
CHANDI: It's not your problem,
but it would be great if you
would just step up and let
the people who are doing wrong
- know that they're wrong.
- ALISON: Uh-huh.
I have a bunch of friends in San Francisco,
that I would love to introduce
you to and hear some stories.
- CAITLYN: Oh.
- JEN: Oh, well, there's also an HRC office there,
so I could introduce you to
some of those people, too,
- and we can start talking about...
- CAITLYN: Explain HRC.
JEN: Oh, HRC is the Human Rights Campaign,
which is one of the world's
biggest LGBT advocacy organizations.
What you should really do
is hear some of their stories
about what they've been through.
CAITLYN: Oh, we should go there.
- JEN: Really?
- CAITLYN: Why not?
I say we go to San Francisco.
- (Jen laughs and claps)
- JENNY: All right.
- JEN: Well, are you serious?
- CAITLYN: Why not? What's holding us back?
We could rent a bus.
A big camper.
- JEN: Are you serious?
- JENNY: Yeah,
- a bus.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, like Priscilla.
- JENNY: Seriously?
- JEN: Like Priscilla?
JENNY: Right, that's...
CAITLYN: All we got to do
is sneak me out of here.
JENNY: How do we sneak you out of here?
CAITLYN: In a trunk.
JENNY: This could be fun.
CAITLYN: Road trip!
- JENNY: Road trip!
- JEN: Road trip! Yes!
JENNY: Yeah.
CAITLYN: San Francisco,
here we come! (Laughter)
- CAITLYN: Hey, babe.
- MADDIE: We brought Starbucks.
CAITLYN: Oh, my God.
- RONDA: What are you wearing, you little... ?
- MADDIE: A romper.
- SPENCER: You're wearing a romper.
- RONDA: I'm wearing a romper.
- MADDIE: It's promper, proper romper.
- RONDA: Thank you, honey bunny.
We need to start packing.
Five days. So you need four night outfits,
- bathing suits...
- CAITLYN: Okay, wait.
- SPENCER: Yeah, bathing suits.
- MADDIE: Bathing suits.
CAITLYN: Are we actually
doing bathing suits?
RONDA: Yes. There's a swimming pool.
- Which drawer is your... bathing suits in?
- CAITLYN: That's like...
- MADDIE: Are they in here?
- CAITLYN: ... the scariest thing I've ever heard.
RONDA: You want to bet? I've
seen you in your bathing suits.
CAITLYN: Having the opportunity
to go out with these girls,
go on the road,
pack all of Caitlyn's
stuff is to me so freeing.
I've never gone on the road with
just Caitlyn clothes. I mean,
it's just never happened, couldn't happen.
- RONDA: Well, this is cute just for fun.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, that's... that's fun.
RONDA: But you need a sexy one for Candis.
MADDIE AND SPENCER: Who is Candis?
CAITLYN: We're not going there.
- RONDA: Who's Candis?
- CAITLYN: A girl that's going on the trip with us.
SPENCER: That's it?
Do you find her attractive?
CAITLYN: No, no. No, no, no.
Well, she's a very attractive lady, yeah.
SPENCER: Which one's Candis?
SPENCER AND MADDIE: Oh!
RONDA: And look how close
she is next... Look.
- Oh, yeah.
- SPENCER: Oh!
RONDA: Oh! Hot mama.
CAITLYN: These girls won't
give up, and I get it.
Candis is a beautiful woman,
but as far as dating in the future...
I have absolutely no idea.
SPENCER: Mom, are you
going on the road trip?
CAITLYN: You should go.
SPENCER: Mom, you really
need to have some fun.
MADDIE: Yeah.
CAITLYN: That's exactly right.
You got all this work ahead
of you, you got to move.
- SPENCER: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: You get a few days.
I'll keep her out of you guys' hair
- for a couple of days, yeah.
- MADDIE: Yeah. Thank God.
- RONDA: No. Wait. Wait, wait. Wait.
- MADDIE: Get out of here.
CAITLYN: Yeah, not to work.
You're coming for fun.
RONDA: Okay. I've known Bruce
for about 15 years.
Throughout those years, we've been friends.
We became quite close
probably about three years ago
when I first found out she was Caitlyn.
I started working for her,
and she didn't have anyone
really that she confided in.
It was for two years pretty
much just the two of us,
because it's been hidden and private.
I look forward to just
having fun and relaxing.
RONDA: Well, now that I'm
going, I have to pack, too.
- CAITLYN: Oh.
- SPENCER: Yeah, you need to pack.
CAITLYN: Look at all these bags.
My first trip.
All those bags, and I still
don't know if I have everything.
- RONDA: Why am I carrying all the bags?
- CAITLYN: They're out here. They'll know.
- RONDA: Whatever.
- COURTNEY: Peanut?
- Oh!
- Peanut?
RONDA: So where are we
going now? What's the plan?
CAITLYN: Oh, we're gonna
rendezvous with the other girls.
- COURTNEY: Uh-huh.
- CAITLYN: And we're going to get the bus.
I mean, this is like a big camper,
- you know, really cool.
- RONDA: Oh.
Is that weird for the other girls that we
-  are not trans?
- RONDA: That's true.
CAITLYN: You're the only
cis girls on the trip.
- RONDA: What does "cis" mean?
- COURTNEY: What does "cis" mean?
RONDA: Like sissy?
CAITLYN (laughing): What does "cis... "?
- It means, um...
- COURTNEY: Sissy?
CAITLYN: ... men or women
who are not transgender.
- You know those types.
- COURTNEY: Okay.
CAITLYN: Yeah.
- Uh, could this be the paparazzi right here?
- RONDA: Is this paparazzi?
COURTNEY: Everybody, look the other way.
CAITLYN: Everybody's gonna split up.
- RONDA: Oh, my goodness.
- CAITLYN: Ever since the Vanity Fair article came out,
the paparazzi have been
following me everywhere.
Some of my kids haven't even met Caitlyn.
So I really want to stay
away from the paparazzi.
I don't want the crazy tabloid
media to write stupid stories.
- RONDA: Okay.
- COURTNEY: The neighbors are gonna come out.
CAITLYN: Let's go, guys. Let's just do it.
If I can just get out of town,
I'll have so much more freedom,
'cause they'll never figure out
where I am and what I'm doing.
- Are we moving?
- RONDA: All right. Yes.
- JOE: All right. Finally.
- RONDA: Jump in behind...
Well, there is people. Hurry, hurry, hurry!
CAITLYN: Okay, are we ready?
Is everything moved around?
RONDA: Get in there.
- Are we moving?
- JOE: All right. Finally.
RONDA: Jump in behind...
Well, there is people. Hurry, hurry, hurry!
CAITLYN: Okay, are we ready?
Is everything moved around?
- RONDA: Get in there!
- CAITLYN: Hello, girls!
- CANDIS: You're so kind.
- CAITLYN: Hello, babe.
How you doing? I'm excited.
- We'll have a good time.
- CHANDI: I'm excited, too.
- Okay.
- CAITLYN: Candis, are you ready to go?
- CANDIS: I am so ready to go.
- CAITLYN: Okay, good.
I apologize for the slow start.
- JEN: It's all exciting.
- JENNY: It's not your fault.
CAITLYN: It's not...
Well, it is. (Muttering)
JENNY: Well, okay. Maybe it's your fault.
JEN: What are you
talking about? Completely.
- CAITLYN: You're wrong.
- JENNY: It's because you're so gorgeous, that's it.
CAITLYN: Yeah, that's ex...
- Is that what it is? Okay.
- JENNY: Yeah.
CAITLYN: There it is.
JENNY: Oh, my freaking God.
CAITLYN: Oh, yay! We have our camper!
JEN: That's like... That's like a tour bus.
CAITLYN: The fun part about a road trip
is that everybody's kind of forced
to all be together, you know?
Nobody's going anywhere. And all the girls,
I've noticed, are so
excited about the trip,
'cause they've all
transitioned a long time ago.
They're very rarely ever
in a group with nothing but,
you know, trans women.
- Are we ready?!
- JENNY: We're ready!
RONDA: We're about to start moving.
CAITLYN: Fire this big... (cheering)
- COURTNEY: Viva la road trip.
- CAITLYN: We're officially in a paparazzi-free zone.
CHANDI: Yeah.
CAITLYN: Nobody's following us.
JENNY: ♪ 100 transgender women on the wall ♪
♪ 100 transgender women on the wall ♪
- ♪ Take one down... ♪
- (laughter, Ronda whoops)
RONDA: This is fun.
JEN: Had you ever met any
trans women before Caitlyn?
RONDA: Nope, and
it was so great when I found out.
One time, you called me and said,
"Hey, well, what are you
doing?" I'm like, "Nothing."
And you're like, "Well,
do you want to come over
for a glass of wine? "
And I was like, " Yeah, of
course." And I'm thinking, oh, no.
- He's not gonna... hit on me?
- (Laughing)
Literally changed my life.
Caitlyn told me her story that night,
after a couple glasses of wine.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- RONDA: Because we all have our
issues and our problems. And I'm like,
"No, no, you don't even want to hear mine.
Like, mine are... No. Mine are just, like,
way too much for anyone to listen to."
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- RONDA: And...
she kind of trumped
mine. I'm like, "Really?"
CAITLYN: And the reason
I came out to Ronda, um...
- good shopper.
- (Laughter)
- (Courtney speaks indistinctly)
- CAITLYN: I needed help.
- I couldn't... I can't shop.
- RONDA: Who wants vino?
- Raise your hand.
- (Whoops)
- CAITLYN: Oh, there you go.
- RONDA: Okay, I'll get you a glass.
CHANDI: Thanks, Ronda.
RONDA: I'm a party starter. Cheers.
- Here's to the road trip.
- CHANDI: Road trip.
CAITLYN: Hey! ♪
COURTNEY: Look at all her
color variations in her hair.
Unbelievable.
- JEN: Is that all natural?
- CANDIS: It's all natural, yeah.
JEN: You want to keep it,
lock your door at night.
- Lock your door at night.
- COURTNEY: I will come in and just...
I will buzz off the bottom chunk.
CAITLYN: Oh...
CANDIS: Let's show... I'll show my butt.
RONDA: Why don't you
put 'em out the window?
- I'm just gonna spank your ass.
- CANDIS: I'm gonna do it. Ready?
Ow!
- (glass shattering)
- (screams)
- CANDIS: Oh, my God.
- RONDA: No.
CANDIS: Oh, you spanked
the window out of the car.
CAITLYN: What the hell have you done?
CANDIS: I don't know! The
emergency exit fell out.
We have fresh air now, Cait.
That's why we did it.
- CAITLYN: Oh, you did it for my benefit?
- CANDIS: Yeah.
(whooping)
RONDA: Are we a third of the way?
CAITLYN: Nah... maybe about
a third of the way, yeah.
Jenny, where the hell are you going?
(Ronda laughs) RONDA:
This is like a '70s ad.
CAITLYN: Look at you. Look what you found.
CANDIS: Poppy.
- JENNY: A California poppy.
- CAITLYN: This is a poppy?
RONDA: I didn't get a rose.
JENNY: Yeah, that's right. Oh,
it's just for us trans girls.
- You get that one.
- RONDA (laughing): Oh...
CANDIS: You get the cis rose.
- RONDA: What, 'cause I'm a cis?
- CANDIS: I know.
RONDA: So here you go. Here, take
advantage of it while you can.
- CANDIS: Trying to yuk it up while we can.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
All right, everybody
just pile back on the bus.
Let's get this
- show on the road.
- JEN: Let's get this party started.
CAITLYN: I'm sure you've
heard a lot of stories.
- CHANDI: I've heard plenty of stories.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
CHANDI: Plenty of stories.
Working with young people has
really given me a lot of drive,
- because their lives are just...
- CAITLYN: Now, is this just trans youth or gay...
CHANDI: This is trans and
gender nonconforming youth.
CAITLYN: Gotcha.
What's the big issue?
CHANDI: They're homeless
and they're unemployed,
so it's just gonna take a lot more.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- JEN: I think if I was to focus on one area,
it would be, like, entry-level jobs.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- JEN: Just have... so that these girls have
some alternative if they want it.
- CHANDI: Right.
- CAITLYN: Don't... a lot of times,
they can make more not working...
with social programs
than they actually can
with an entry-level job.
JENNY: I'd say the great majority
of people who are getting help
are getting help 'cause they need help.
CAITLYN: But you don't want people to get
totally dependent on it.
That's when they get in
trouble. "Why should I work?
You know, I got a few bucks. I got my...
my room paid for."
JENNY: Now I'm worried.
Caitlyn has every right to be just
as conservative as she chooses.
But many transgender men and women
need social programs to survive,
and that's nothing to be ashamed of.
Living in the bubble is an impediment
to understanding other people.
If Cait's gonna be a
spokesperson for our community,
this is something she's
gonna have to understand.
_
RONDA: No, but she gave her
a big hug when they came.
When I talked to her about it, she...
it's not like she blushes, but
she's like, "Oh, stop! Stop!
- Let's stop talking about it."
- COURTNEY: I know, but she's probably nervous.
RONDA: Does she even know
that we're on the same...
COURTNEY: No, she has no idea we're here.
'Cause Candis is there and
she's, like, doesn't know...
You know, like, when you like someone
and you have that electricity?
RONDA: I'm trying to make eye contact
with her and she's not looking.
- CANDIS: But they didn't say...
- CAITLYN: Oh, come on.
- (Ronda laughs)
- Both of you, turn around.
(laughter)
- Our cis girls, just leave 'em up there.
- RONDA: See?
COURTNEY: Oh, see? She's
like, "Leave 'em up there."
(birds singing)
CAITLYN: We made it! It's the first stop.
- CHANDI: Yay.
- CAITLYN: Everybody out.
- CANDIS: No. (Laughs)
- CAITLYN: Go ahead, baby.
- JENNY: Oh, wow, it's beautiful.
- CAITLYN: Go ahead.
COURTNEY: Look at how there's,
like, a little house in the woods.
Isn't that crazy?
CAITLYN: All right!
- Look at this.
- JENNY: Wow, it's gorgeous.
JEN: Oh, my goodness.
- JENNY: It's beautiful.
- (Jen gasps)
- (Jen shrieks, laughs)
- CAITLYN: I brought the moose in for you.
COURTNEY: Oh, my God.
- Come on.
- JEN: It's screaming.
- COURTNEY: Touch it.
- JENNY: Screaming at you when you walk in the...
Touch it?
- RONDA: Ew, that's just creepy. I can't look, just...
- CAITLYN: Don't touch it,
- it could bite.
- JEN: What did it feel like?
- JENNY: It's like a...
- CANDIS: Wow, it's so gorgeous.
CAITLYN: Now, Ronda, are you cooking?
(Laughter)
RONDA: Uh... not tonight.
- CAITLYN: Okay.
- RONDA: I'm sorry.
'Cause this is my vacation, remember?
CAITLYN: Oh, yeah, right.
(Ronda laughs) RONDA: Well,
don't say "Oh, right."
JENNY: Let's sit out here.
CHANDI: Oh...
JENNY: So this is California.
- Beautiful view.
- CAITLYN: It's kind of cold, yeah.
CANDIS: Thank you.
- CAITLYN: Now we're talking.
- CHANDI: Thanks, Ronda.
CAITLYN: The Santa Cruz mountains.
CANDIS: That's beautiful, right?
- I love the smell.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, it smells really nice.
RONDA: Caitlyn's finally out.
CAITLYN: I'm out! Yeah, this is the
furthest I've been away from home.
Yay!
- (women whooping)
- JENNY: Bravo.
- COURTNEY: Cheers.
- CANDIS: Cheers.
Wow.
CAITLYN: To be with all these girls who are
so accepting of me and who I am
is probably the most freeing
thing I've ever done in my life.
Just to be out there...
it makes me really look
forward to the future.
CHANDI: So how does it feel?
- CAITLYN: It feels free, baby.
- CHANDI: Right, right.
CAITLYN: Free. To be here with all of you
- is nothing but good.
- (Chandi chuckles)
- JEN: Feeling good.
- CHANDI: All good, all good.
CAITLYN: Nice.
(insects trilling)
Looks like somebody already
parked down here. Was that you?
CANDIS: Yeah, it's the...
COURTNEY AND CAITLYN: ...
it's the smallest room.
- CANDIS: Nobody wants to be here.
- CAITLYN: Actually, it is. It's very nice.
JEN: This is the room I would've
chosen, just for the record.
RONDA: We'll get the honeymoon suite.
COURTNEY: This is my bed.
Get off my bed!
RONDA: Oh. Oh, you fancy...
CAITLYN: What are you guys doing?
I guess you girls have taken this room?
COURTNEY: Well, no, no, no, no, no.
CAITLYN: There's only one bed.
- RONDA: There's zero...
- CAITLYN: We had two separate
beds downstairs for you, if you wanted 'em.
COURTNEY: That does not sound good.
CAITLYN: Follow me.
- COURTNEY: Down there?
- CAITLYN: Hello!
Ronda.
- The guesthouse.
- JENNY: Oh, my God.
- COURTNEY: Wait, no.
- RONDA: Is that really?
CAITLYN: Here's the deal:
we're one short down there.
- I think you should stay up here.
- RONDA: What, me?
CAITLYN: Yeah. Okay,
everybody's got a room now.
RONDA: Can I just say something?
Caitlyn.
You told me this was a vacation.
- CAITLYN: You're doing fine. Everything's gonna be fine.
- RONDA: Oh, great.
I'm gonna hobble down here
to the bathroom in the middle of the night?
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- (Ronda sighs)
CANDIS: I'll see you in the hot tub.
JENNY: Okay. Bathing suit or naked?
JEN: I'm gonna wear my bathing suit.
JENNY: You're gonna wear your bathing suit?
JEN: You can do whatever you want.
JENNY: Well, it'll be kind
of awkward if I'm... if I'm...
- JEN: Not at all.
- JENNY: ... if I'm not wearing
any... I'm gonna wear a bathing suit.
If you're gonna wear a bathing
suit, I'll wear a bathing suit.
JENNY: I won't be the only trans girl...
naked in the...
So I'll put on a thing.
JEN: Okay.
COURTNEY: It's a little hot,
so I'm gonna let myself
in a little bit slow,
'cause it's, like, lobsters cooking.
- CANDIS: Oh.
- RONDA: How hot is it?
- COURTNEY: Hottish.
- RONDA: It's 103.
- JENNY: Cait, have you been swimming?
- CAITLYN: What's that?
JENNY: Have you been swimming
in your own bathing suit yet?
CAITLYN: No.
Well, I've been in the
bathing suit, but I haven't
- gone swimming yet.
- JENNY: You haven't been in the, in the pool?
CAITLYN: No, I haven't even been in
the pool. It's too damn cold right now.
JENNY: It's a really...
For me, anyway, it was an
incredible moment when I was like...
CAITLYN: To actually go swimming?
To be honest with you,
that'll happen at some point.
- I'm in no rush.
- JENNY: It will.
CAITLYN: Yeah. I'm in no rush.
Yeah.
- JENNY: I hear you.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
This process of coming out
doesn't happen overnight.
There are so many hurdles to overcome.
Every day, it seems like,
you know,
what about a "beijing-thuit"?
- (spits)
- PRODUCER: Bathing suit.
CAITLYN: Bathing suit.
See, I can't even say it.
It's hard for it to just, to come out.
Saying, "A bathing suit."
But, you know, that's where I got
to get, and that's gonna take time.
CHANDI: Can I say how amazing
everybody looks in their swimsuits?
(Candis whoops)
- Okay?
- (Indistinct chatter)
RONDA: We're overflowing.
JENNY: It's all these boobs.
JEN: (laughs) It's all the boobs.
(laughter)
CAITLYN: All right.
Little red light's on, camera's working.
Jenny: "Come on, let's get in the hot tub."
I don't think I'm ready for that.
You have to realize,
these girls transitioned
years and years and years ago. Um...
I just don't know if I'm ready
to expose myself like that.
Maybe down the line, I'll feel
more comfortable with myself,
but right now...
I just can't see myself doing it.
Bedtime.
All right.
(Golf ball pings)
Wow.
It's just absolutely
gorgeous. I love a great view.
To me, a view is like freedom.
So, uh, Caitlyn being out for
the first time is wonderful.
Well, the big question now is:
does it make a difference...
swinging a golf club... with boobs or not?
Will I still be free enough to
be able to swing the golf club?
But I think in the putting department,
I think it's gonna be very
good, 'cause you can just kind of
latch onto those little babies
under your arm, right here,
and get a nice putting stroke going.
So I'm optimistic about the future,
'cause I needed help on my putting.
(Caitlyn whoops)
JENNY: So are you enjoying the ride?
JEN: Yeah, of course, of course, it's...
I don't know, I kind of
almost take it for granted. I
spend so much time with
trans women already,
but Caitlyn's joy is kind of contagious.
Like that feeling when you're first out
- and everything is new.
- JENNY: Yeah, yeah. Yeah, no.
CAITLYN: Oh, that was great, actually.
JENNY: So we're going to HRC today.
- JEN: Mm-hmm.
- JENNY: Right?
To see these trans women,
many of whom have done
sex work and who are gonna talk in a very
vulnerable and personal way about that, and
Cait needs to learn
what the risks are to the community.
JEN: Yeah.
JENNY: You know, if Cait emerges
from this whole thing thinking that,
you know, that it's...
that womanhood is a party,
or that being... that being trans...
I mean, and we, you know,
she's so happy, and it's so...
it's so moving to see
her so elated, you know?
Um, but it's also, I'm
afraid people will think that,
you know, it's... it's just, you know,
that... it's all about makeup and hair.
And yet there are all
these trans women out there
who are in real danger.
Transgender people often go through
a kind of second adolescence.
And when you first come out,
you can really find yourself acting,
you know, like a giddy teenager.
The sad fact is that our community
is in trouble.
Caitlyn, she wants to be our savior,
but most people don't have
what she has, and she may be oblivious.
- JEN: I mean, that's why we're here.
- JENNY: She's... she's
eager to learn, but,
you know what, there are some
times I'm not sure what...
- what gets through to her.
- JEN: Yeah.
CAITLYN: Beautiful! Caitlyn is out.
I really haven't done anything
to alter my voice. We
talked about it last time.
CAITLYN: This is not what I looked
like, okay? That's somewhat scary.
But what I sound like...
CAITLYN: I've seen some trans people,
they look great, and then
they open up their mouth,
- and you go, "Oh, my God."
- JEN: Yeah.
CAITLYN: I felt... I felt sorry
for them, 'cause they were,
you know, they had a
real deep voice, you know?
JEN: Yeah, I know girls like that.
CAITLYN: And I went,
"God, I don't want that
for me." Because I do so much speaking.
CAITLYN: You know, 'cause there's
all sorts of options on that.
CAITLYN: It's little things
that get into your head.
RONDA: We got to go.
- CAITLYN: Well, let's go.
- RONDA: Otherwise, we... we're gonna be late
- for the, um, meeting.
- CAITLYN: Let's do it.
JENNY: Do we need to bring our bags?
CAITLYN: Yeah, actually, you
know what the other good thing is?
We get guys to carry our bags for us.
(Laughter)
I want to kind of keep it low-key.
I don't want to make, like, a big
spectacle or anything like that.
Keep it low-key.
We're going in to the HRC place. Now,
you work with them.
- JEN: Yeah, I do, so...
- CAITLYN: What would you like to accomplish?
JEN: Primarily, just to
hear these girls' stories.
They're survivors of... of
violence because they're trans.
We don't want to reduce them
to these traumas, you know?
JEN: They're so much more than... than
these things that they've suffered.
But we also need to
acknowledge what's happened...
- CAITLYN: Yeah, right.
- JEN: ... in order to
lift the visibility of their stories.
- CAITLYN: I am so amped.
- JEN: Good. Good, I'm glad.
JEN: Hi.
MAN: We're ready to
welcome you with open arms.
- JEN: Hi, I'm Jen.
- MAN: Welcome to the Human Rights Campaign...
- just really carefully watch your step.
- JEN: All right, okay. Thanks.
CAITLYN: Caitlyn. Nice to see you.
- Thank you for having us.
- MAN: Good to meet you.
(Jen laughs giddily)
- CAITLYN: Is this your friend?
- ANGELICA: Yes. Hello,
gorgeous, how are you? Can I get a hug?
- CAITLYN: Absolutely. How are you?
- ANGELICA: I'm awesome.
- CAITLYN: So nice to meet you.
- JAY: It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Thank you.
- ALISON: Hi, Alison Gill.
- It's nice to meet you.
- JENNY: I'll say it again, I'm so glad to be here
- at HRC. It's a pleasure.
- LAYA: Laya Monarez.
CAITLYN: Nice to meet you.
- BLOSSOM: I'm Blossom.
- JENNY: How are you, Blossom?
- That's a pretty...
- BLOSSOM: Nice to meet you.
- JENNY: Pleasure to meet you.
- JEN: Okay.
CAITLYN: Oh, my gosh, where do we start?
JAY: We're really happy to be
here today, talking with you
and talking about sort of the
issues that the community faces.
I mean, we're really honored to have some
incredible advocates here, uh, today
to talk about their personal stories.
ALISON: You know, most
people think that trans people
are protected from
discrimination across the country,
and that's really not the
case. And it can really lead to
- all sorts of problems.
- (Others affirming)
ANGELICA: I've been
transitioning since I was 19.
I still haven't been able to access
what you've been able to access so quickly.
When I first came out, I was fired
from, like, four jobs in a row...
once they found out I was trans, so
I felt like I would never in my life
choose to do sex work...
but after being fired after so many jobs,
- what other choice did I have?
- WOMAN: Yeah, mm-hmm.
JENNY: This type of
discrimination is all too common
in the workplace for trans women.
We have to struggle to be employed,
which is one reason why sex work
is so prevalent in our community.
For some transgender women,
it's the only work that we can get.
BLOSSOM: Whenever someone
sees a transgender person,
uh, the first thing they're gonna
think is, "Oh, they're a prostitute."
You know, I mean, it's
sex work or whatever.
- But what people don't understand is...
- CAITLYN: Is that what they're gonna think of me?
- (laughter)
- ANGELICA: Not you, girl.
- BLOSSOM: Yeah, not you.
- CAITLYN: My God, all of a sudden... shock.
Wait a second.
BLOSSOM: Yeah, but, see, what
people don't understand is,
the reason why some of
us do turn to sex work
- is because people will not hire us.
- ALISON: Mmm, that's right.
BLOSSOM: I'm gonna be honest. Caitlyn,
when you came out, it was
so mixed or whatever, because
it seems like you have these
transgender women of color
who are going out here, and... and
we're basically saying the
same thing you were doing,
- and, like, nobody wanted to hear it.
- CAITLYN: No, okay, first of all...
BLOSSOM: Nobody wanted to hear
it. And, you know what I mean?
And... you were... it was...
it had something... (sighs)
Let's just be real,
it had something to do with
your socio-economical status.
(others affirming)
CHANDI: It's not your problem,
but it would be great
if you would just step up
and let the people who are doing wrong
- know that they're wrong.
- ALISON: Uh-huh.
BLOSSOM: I definitely agree
with that. You're up there.
Come down and... and
understand with everybody else.
CAITLYN: Months and months ago...
I thought, "How could I make a difference?"
And I'm thinking about my
family, and I struggled...
Damn it.
We're gonna go roller-skating.
- (woman whoops)
- CHANDI: Put a ring on it.
CAITLYN: Ooh, wait a second,
we got to get our legs.
COURTNEY: Who's more attracted to men?
- JENNY: Is that a hand?
- CAITLYN: I don't know.
You would feel so much more
feminine if you were with a guy,
- you know?
- JEN: Wait, what?!
CAITLYN: I can appreciate the male form.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -