CAITLYN: Okay. It's,
like, 4:32 in the morning.
And I can't sleep.
God, I look in the
monitor, I look like crap.
I, anyway... I... I feel bad that
these... especially young people...
are going through such a
difficult time in their life.
We don't want people dying over this.
We don't want people
murdered over this stuff.
What a responsibility I have...
towards this community. Am I
going to do everything right?
Am I gonna say the right things?
Do I project the right image?
My mind's just spinning with thoughts.
I just hope I get it right.
I hope I get it right.
Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Vanity Fair is out!
- (People cheering, applauding)
Look at that cover, baby!
REPORTER: We begin with the world's
introduction to Caitlyn Jenner.
- COURTNEY: Yeah! (Whoops)
- CAITLYN: Shh, shh!
REPORTER: Former Olympian Bruce Jenner
confirmed her transition to a woman
on the cover of Vanity Fair.
Jenner first talked about her transition
in an interview with Diane Sawyer,
saying we can meet her soon.
CAITLYN: I don't think I have
ever been more excited about life
than I am right now.
Living my true identity.
Um, and hopefully, going to
make a difference in the world.
That's my mission.
REPORTER: Khloe Kardashian
tweeted this morning:
"We were given this life because
you were strong enough to live it.
I couldn't be prouder.
Caitlyn, you are beautiful."
ROB: Your cover looks amazing.
- CAITLYN: Isn't that rockin'?
- ROB: So good, yeah, you look
- amazing and everything.
- CAITLYN: It's so good to hear from you.
Kim?
KIM: You didn't tell
me you were on Twitter.
CAITLYN: I've been on Twitter for an hour.
KIM: Well, the head of Twitter just said,
"We think Caitlyn could
break President Obama's gained
follower record one million
within the first five hours."
CAITLYN: Well, let's go.
Okay! Let's go for the record!
I love records!
At this point, what's the total amount?
- KIM: 720,000.
- CAITLYN: No!
RONDA: In two hours.
CAITLYN: In two hours.
We're going for the record.
KIM: Just wanted you to
know I'm on the bandwagon.
CAITLYN: Yay! Thank
you for all the support.
- KIM: Of course, of course.
- CAITLYN: All right.
KIM: All eyes on you now.
You cannot disappoint.
CAITLYN: I know. No, it's got to be good.
The tremendous amount of
support that I've gotten
has been overwhelming.
But you also have to realize that,
uh, it's not this way for everybody.
There are so many people
that have struggled with family;
who struggle with friends;
who struggle with ridicule;
who are not having financial resources.
The suicide rate nine times higher
in the trans community
than in the general public.
Murder rate's higher.
This is a really important issue.
People are dying over this issue.
I feel a tremendous responsibility here.
Because I have a voice and there's so
many trans people out there
who do not have a voice.
I can't speak for them, because
everybody has their own experience,
but I am an expert
on my story.
- WOMAN: Cheers to Caitlyn.
- CAITLYN: Out two weeks, yeah!
There's so much to learn,
so many people to meet.
WOMAN: Your transformation has
helped me to understand my father.
CAITLYN: I've lived a great life.
And I realize, in this transition,
- that I have that privileged status.
- (Crowd clamoring)
But I hope that I'm in a
position to turn around...
Yay! ... And help this community.
Hi, everybody. I want to
spotlight those organizations
that are out there doing
some really good things.
BOY: Being around friends is
really nice when you haven't
- been around friends for most of your life.
- CAITLYN: Well, you got friends here.
But also I have to
figure out my own journey.
Now I know why girls need a sports bra.
There's a lot of firsts out there for me.
My entire family have not met Caitlyn.
- KIM: Hi.
- CAITLYN: Hi, babe.
I want to be able to make
friends in the trans community.
- WOMAN: Everybody on Jenner.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, yeah.
And I have to figure out how I'm
going to live the rest of my life.
KYLIE: I love you.
CAITLYN (crying): I want them
to be proud of their daddy.
ANNOUNCER: Bruce Jenner has a
commanding lead in the home stretch.
Bruce Jenner has the world
record in the decathlon.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
CAITLYN: My mother's coming today.
Um...
I don't know what it is.
I was able to tell
everybody in my family first,
before I ever got to my mom.
It's so important, during this transition,
that you surround yourself
with positive people.
How you doing in there, Ronda?
RONDA: I'm good, I got
three outfits for you.
- CAITLYN: All right.
- RONDA: That you can pick from.
CAITLYN: Years ago, I confided in Ronda.
And she really has been a
friend that has supported me.
Combined with Courtney,
I've really got a great support group.
It... it, from that standpoint, it's...
I'm... I'm blessed.
RONDA: They just landed. So...
do you want me to start
looking in the clotet
- for things that you can wear?
- CAITLYN: Uh, I don't know.
I don't think I can be too...
you know,
in "la femme" mode.
- It's got to be kind of, yeah, right.
- RONDA: No dressy dress.
CAITLYN: No, I... I already told them:
you're coming down to meet Caitlyn.
COURTNEY: I've never
seen you actually nervous.
CAITLYN: Well, it's my mother... God.
PAM: Mom hasn't had her children together
- since her birthday party, four years ago.
- ESTHER: That's right.
PAM: So this is, this is very special.
- ESTHER: And I think... (Esther laughs)
- PAM: In many ways.
CAITLYN: Sleeves up or down?
- Let's me see.
- RONDA: Slightly up.
- CAITLYN: What about a necklace?
- COURTNEY: Do you...
I mean, should we button it one more up
- just 'cause it's Mom?
- RONDA: Yeah, it's Mom.
LISA: When everything first broke,
it was difficult because I had known
my brother as, you know, Bruce,
this amazing athlete, for,
you know, all of my life...
and, I guess the whole family
has to change along with... with her.
ESTHER: When you're in the
grocery store, to see these
tabloid magazines and all the things
that they come out with, with...
you know...
PRODUCER: So, what was your
reaction when you found out?
ESTHER: I think I was silent.
PAM: He confided in me over 30 years ago.
ESTHER: You thought maybe he
was... uh, getting over it?
PAM: Because the subject
never came up again.
- ESTHER: Yeah.
- PAM: I thought
it was something that maybe
counseling would help him with.
Then, about two years ago,
he started talking to me about
wanting to live an authentic life.
CAITLYN: Now, here's the question.
- RONDA: What?
- CAITLYN: I'm signing the birthday card for Mother...
RONDA: I bought you two!
- CAITLYN: How do I sign it?
- COURTNEY: In case you mess up.
RONDA: You got two. (Laughs)
COURTNEY: You're Caitlyn.
This is the life you're living.
CAITLYN (sing-songy): Scary.
PAM: He... he felt like
he needed to follow through
on his desires and to go, actually, public,
um, and discuss the issue.
I initially discouraged him.
I... I didn't understand
how that could work.
(Esther sighs)
CAITLYN: It's kind of tough to
tell your mother all these secrets.
You always have doubts in your mind
of how that first impression
is going to work out.
You want it to be so good.
She's never met Caitlyn.
And I'm just hoping for the best.
Oh, God, here we go.
♪
PRODUCER: So come on in.
- ESTHER: Okay.
- PRODUCER: Welcome.
ESTHER: There you are.
CAITLYN: Now, everybody. It's okay, it's...
- Hello, Mom.
- ESTHER: I knew it would be.
CAITLYN: Yeah, I know.
It's okay, it's okay.
- Sister Lisa, hold on.
- LISA: Hello.
CAITLYN: I know, I'm taller than you.
LISA: Yes, you are, and you've always been.
CAITLYN: It's sister Pam. Hey...
Hey... We're all here.
- PAM: You're gorgeous. Gorgeous!
- CAITLYN: Well, thank you. Thank you.
PAM: I was quite apprehensive.
I knew she would be d... different looking.
Uh, and I was hoping that she
would have the same personality,
uh, as Bruce. And she does.
And she's so relaxed and so happy.
That makes me very happy.
- I thought you were gonna look more like me.
- (Everyone laughs)
CAITLYN: Little sister,
after, what has it been,
- 35 years we've talked about this?
- PAM: Yes, about that long.
- CAITLYN: Yeah. Yeah, I know.
- PAM: About that long.
CAITLYN: Back that long. I know.
ESTHER: And you never talked to me.
CAITLYN: I know. I know. Well, we
could sit down and talk about that.
ESTHER: I never knew.
- I never guessed you were having a problem.
- CAITLYN: I know.
ESTHER: You hid it very well.
CAITLYN: I did. I was a
professional at hiding it.
- PAM: I guess so.
- ESTHER: It is
overwhelming. I guess
I've been preparing myself.
Uh...
I knew he was going to be...
dressed...
as a woman.
Uh...
I think he's a very good-looking woman.
Uh... he's still Bruce.
- (crying): Oh, I don't want to do that.
- PRODUCER: No, no, no, it's okay, it's okay.
ESTHER: I... I love him so much.
I always have, I always will.
- PRODUCER: And... yes.
- ESTHER: And yes.
It's... it's...
- a lot to get used to.
- PRODUCER: Mm-hmm. Of course.
- It's a surprise.
- ESTHER: But I will.
- PRODUCER: Yes.
- ESTHER: I will.
PAM: I was asking Bruce how did
he come up with the name Caitlyn.
CAITLYN: I kind of narrowed it down
to a few of them,
Caitlyn being one of them.
And I actually was with Ronda.
When I was talking to her
about this whole thing about two years ago,
she goes, "Well, you know, I always
liked the name Caitlyn." And I went...
at some point, you just have
to kind of bite the bullet...
and say, "Okay, boom. It's done."
But talking to other trans
people, they said a good way
to get your female name...
is to...
ask your mother.
I'm sure
when you didn't know
- there was a boy or a girl...
- ESTHER: Mm-hmm.
CAITLYN: ... you had names for
a boy name, and you had a girl name.
- I don't know if you remember.
- PAM: Do you remember?
- ESTHER: I don't remember.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
ESTHER: And I'm sure I did
have two different names picked.
- (Cell phone rings)
- PAM: Did you have a boy's name
picked out for me?
- CAITLYN: Hi, baby.
- KYLIE: Hey, Daddy.
CAITLYN: Am I on FaceTime with you?
Kylie has not met Caitlyn
yet. And she FaceTimes me.
And there I am. I didn't
know it was coming on.
Um, don't want to scare you.
You just woke up? Where are you?
KYLIE: The dentist.
CAITLYN: Oh, you just
woke up at the dentist.
Are you feeling okay?
KYLIE: I'm a little loopy.
CAITLYN: A little loopy? I've
never...
had my first experience
with somebody on FaceTime.
To be honest with you,
I didn't know what to do.
Like, do I turn it away? Or, you know...
I... I... uh... I don't know... I
was kind of shocked, when I thought...
"Oh well." ♪ Ta-da. ♪
- (everyone laughs)
- KYLIE: You look pretty.
CAITLYN: I don't want to scare you.
- Okay.
- KYLIE: You're not scaring me. You look pretty.
CAITLYN: Okay, good.
- I love you.
- KYLIE: Bye, Daddy.
CAITLYN: Mwah! Yeah.
There's an expert in
town named Susan Landon.
She's coming up...
uh... to answer any
questions that you might have.
- Uh, she's great.
- ESTHER: I need to learn more.
CAITLYN: Yeah, okay, we'll
have a great conversation.
ESTHER: Good.
- CAITLYN: Susan, baby, how you doing? Hello.
- SUSAN: Hi, darling, how are you?
- CAITLYN: I am great.
- SUSAN: Good.
- CAITLYN: So good to see you.
- SUSAN: You too.
- CAITLYN: Thanks for coming out.
- SUSAN: Thank you for asking me.
CAITLYN: I know. Susan works with families.
Uh, Mom has said, on numerous
occasions, "I need to know more."
SUSAN: Well, you can
ask me whatever you want.
CAITLYN: Let's take... Let's go in here
and sit down, so we can relax and...
SUSAN and ESTHER: Okay.
SUSAN: There's nothing more
important than acceptance, support.
This takes time in some families.
But the other thing to remember
is that it's a process over time.
ESTHER: I hate to brag, but I
have some beautiful children.
- Where's Pam? There she is.
- CAITLYN: Some getting prettier.
ESTHER: Yes, I... I know.
CAITLYN: Yeah, I know. I know.
Yeah, some getting... a little prettier.
All right, just stay on point.
Since we have Susan here,
the big question is: have
you ever seen anybody...
like, get over it and get cured of this?
SUSAN: Uh, me personally, no, I have not.
CAITLYN: Yeah, I know. It's
just kind of the way you're born.
- ESTHER: You know how little boys outgrow their clothes?
- SUSAN: Yes.
ESTHER: I took you to a store, and
- you did not want those clothes on you.
- (Caitlyn laughs)
You were trying to pull them off of you.
And I was trying to get them on you.
And you didn't want them. And I thought,
"He just doesn't want new clothes."
Would that have been in his person,
then, that he would
rather have had a dress?
SUSAN: Oh, absolutely.
Let's say for a minute that
that's what he would
have preferred to wear...
- sorry. She.
- CAITLYN: It's quite all right.
SUSAN: I meant "he" then.
- CAITLYN: You got it.
- SUSAN: ... she would have preferred to wear.
'Cause pronouns are really
important, everybody.
So if that, at that point,
is what she had wanted to have,
she probably wasn't able to pick it,
okay? And then, when children get older,
they notice the reactions of other people.
- ESTHER: But they, the...
- SUSAN: They start taking in information...
like, "This probably isn't gonna be okay",
- "so I better fit in."
- ESTHER: Yeah.
SUSAN: And if anybody tried
to fit in more than you,
- I don't know who it was.
- CAITLYN: I did a good job, yeah.
(Laughter)
ESTHER: But the child
has no idea why
their reaction is that way.
For instance, the clothes.
SUSAN: But by the time they're about five,
they start figuring it out.
ESTHER: Now, I'm sure you've
read the passage in the Bible
about if you dress...
if you're a man and you dress
like a woman, you know...
SUSAN: Yeah.
ESTHER: Do you have any,
uh, interpretation of that?
SUSAN: Um... I'm not a biblical
scholar, so I don't know exactly
what that verse represented
to people at the time,
obviously, but for me, personally,
Caitlyn is a woman,
and really always has been.
- PAM: Be gentle, please.
- CAITLYN: What?
- PAM: I said, be gentle.
- CAITLYN: Oh, my God, I'm gonna be gentle.
You know I've always been gentle with you.
This one's a little...
higher strike. You don't care.
(Pam laughs)
- Let's do it.
- PAM: Okay.
CAITLYN: What do you do with the balls?
- Guys, we got pockets.
- (Pam laughs)
Ready?
- Bad start.
- PAM: One point.
CAITLYN: Take it easy on me, Sis.
Here it comes.
PAM: Ooh!
- (Pam laughs)
- CAITLYN: God, come on.
It's great... to be able
to base with your family
a relationship
on honesty. I mean, I am... so happy,
uh, the way this whole process has begun.
PAM: I know we talked about
you and your straight guy friends...
you haven't really met yet.
CAITLYN: Honestly, I've come out
to all the girls, you're right.
- PAM: And everybody's...
- CAITLYN: I think it's just harder
for... I don't know. My guy
friends... what do you think?
PAM: I think they're gonna be
much more supportive than you think.
They're gonna meet Caitlyn
and they're gonna say,
"Same personality."
CAITLYN: But I don't know if they
get it, I don't know if guys get that.
PAM: Hold on, I'm getting warm.
CAITLYN: I don't know, girls
just seem to be easier, you know?
- PAM: Yes, we are.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
Oh, we are... don't start bragging on me.
Let's go, get over there, I'll show you.
PAM: See how I hit 'em
right to you, to be nice?
- Oops.
- CAITLYN: Hup, I got it!
PAM: Oh, it's legal, it's legal.
Uh-oh. I... aah!
(Pam laughs)
I love it.
CAITLYN: Now I know why
girls need a sports bra.
- (Pam laughs)
- When you start running,
- it gets a little tougher, doesn't it?
- PAM: Yeah.
Get in.
- CAITLYN: The hair got in my eyes again.
- (Pam laughing)
Bruce was a lot better
tennis player than Caitlyn is.
- PAM: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Okay?
- PAM: It was fun.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, it was fun.
It was fun.
(indistinct chatter)
(footsteps approaching)
- KYLIE: Hello?!
- PAM: Oh, my goodness.
- I haven't seen you in so long.
- KYLIE: Hey, Aunt Lisa.
- LISA: How are you?
- KYLIE: Good.
- LISA: You look so pretty.
- KYLIE: Oh, thank you.
MADDIE: Aah! I've missed you.
KYLIE: I missed you. Where's my dad?
MADDIE: He's in there.
KYLIE: I do want to meet her.
It'll be a little
uncomfortable in the beginning.
But I think we're both ready.
- Hey, pretty.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, I know, I know... Hey, baby!
I didn't know you were here.
- KYLIE: You look so pretty.
- CAITLYN: Where did you just sneak in?
KYLIE: Hey, Grandma.
- CAITLYN: Little Kylie made it.
- ESTHER: Oh, my... (kisses)
- CAITLYN: Mom's in the chair.
- KYLIE: How are you?
- Are you getting pretty?
- ESTHER: I'm having fun.
- KYLIE: Oh, yay.
- ESTHER: I have a little present for you.
KYLIE: I'm excited.
CAITLYN: Oh, yeah, yeah.
Okay, you want to do it?
- ESTHER: Okay.
- CAITLYN: Okay, come on.
(Esther chuckles) CAITLYN: Okay...
ESTHER: I thought... I
thought you should have this.
It's me when I was 17.
- KYLIE: Oh, my God.
- CAITLYN: When she was your age.
KYLIE: Wait, we kind of look alike.
- ESTHER: We do kind of look alike, don't we?
- CAITLYN: I know, you do.
KYLIE: I definitely take the Jenner side,
- 'cause...
- CAITLYN: And here's the kicker:
she was 17 years old in this picture...
- ESTHER: Married to...
- CAITLYN: ... and she was married.
- ESTHER: And...
- KYLIE: Kind of like... kind of like me.
CAITLYN: Uh, uh, but, you...
I better not hear that from you.
Yes, yes, yes. My big concern,
obviously, from the beginning...
besides all the rest of the kids...
is Kendall and Kylie. Isn't that cool?
KYLIE: I love it. So pretty.
CAITLYN: Once it was
out there, they saw the
support that I was getting,
especially in the celebrity world.
From the Lady Gagas of the world
to Miley Cyrus to Elton John.
To see their support, I think
it really made my kids feel...
especially Kylie...
that it's gonna be okay.
SPENCER: How's Kenny?
- KYLIE: She's good, I don't know, she's so busy.
- CAITLYN: She's in Cannes right now.
- KYLIE: Let me see your hair.
- CAITLYN: Mm-hmm.
- KYLIE: You should get extensions.
- CAITLYN: Oh, we would never use extensions, would we?
KYLIE: No.
CAITLYN: No, not in a
million years, would we?
KYLIE: Where are the ones that I gave you?
CAITLYN: Uh, in the other room.
- KYLIE: I want to put them in.
- CAITLYN: Okay.
I got no problem with Kylie.
After the first five minutes,
it's like, "All right... "
it's Caitlyn... big deal."
KYLIE: I was, like, looking
at Google pictures of you
when I was trying to pick the hair
color, and then you dyed it on me.
(All laugh)
- ESTHER: Does it match your eyes?
- COURTNEY: Don't look, don't look!
- CAITLYN: Sorry.
- (All laugh)
- I almost peeked, I'm sorry.
- COURTNEY: Don't ruin it.
CAITLYN: Isn't this more fun than
sitting around talking about sports?
- KYLIE: Mm-hmm.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, that's what I thought.
- SPENCER: Or watching golf.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, or watching golf.
Yeah, thank you, thank you.
- KYLIE: Or playing golf?
- CAITLYN: Or playing golf.
Well, I don't know if
I can go quite that far.
- COURTNEY: Look at yourself, look.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, wait, wait...
Kylie.
- SPENCER: I know, right?
- Look how long it is.
- KYLIE: Lean back.
- ESTHER: Wow.
- KYLIE: Look.
- CAITLYN: Could be Caitlyn's first post.
And they would never know who it is.
- SPENCER: They'd be, like, "Oh!"
- KYLIE: What do you want to say?
CAITLYN: A good friend
modeling my new extensions,
or something like that.
KYLIE: I don't want to say "a good friend."
- CAITLYN: Okay, uh...
- RONDA: My dad?
- CAITLYN: My dad?
- (Everyone laughs)
CAITLYN: Having that opportunity to
just be honest with your family...
it's like somebody taking
a thousand pounds off my shoulders.
Besides, most people, once they
meet Caitlyn, they go, "Oh, my God,
she's more fun than Bruce " ever was."
- KYLIE: I love you.
- CAITLYN: Okay, I love you, too.
And everything's gonna be good.
- KYLIE: I'll see you tomorrow.
- CAITLYN: I appreciate you coming out and being understanding.
- KYLIE: Of course, I love you.
- CAITLYN: Good.
- Bye, buddy.
- KYLIE: Bye!
CAITLYN: All these pants
I'll never use again.
PAM: Yeah, where'd you
put the other hangers?
- Are they underneath?
- CAITLYN: I don't know.
Here's the question...
I hate to say it, but...
- what the hell was Bruce thinking?
- PAM: (laughs)
You prob... it was probably
a Christmas present.
CAITLYN: That is one ugly shirt.
Considering I've had all these
clothes down here for six months,
I guess I really don't need
anything that's here, right?
- PAM: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Yeah. Anyway,
how's Mom doing?
PAM: She hasn't said a
word to me, privately.
- CAITLYN: Really?
- PAM: Yeah, no, I think she's... she's...
- CAITLYN: I just, you know, sit here and...
- PAM: Wonder.
CAITLYN: Yeah, I wonder.
Everybody's very positive
and everybody feels really
good about all this stuff,
but, you know, I'm kind of waiting.
PAM: And you're waiting for?
CAITLYN: Well, I'm waiting
for, you know, Mom to go...
in a quiet time... "Oh,
my God, what's happening?"
Even Kylie coming over
today... you never know,
you know, when they get away from
here and they go home, they go,
"Oh, my God, that was so
strange." I mean, she has not
- met Caitlyn. She was kind of shocked.
- PAM: Kylie hadn't?
CAITLYN: No, no. She would never come over.
- PAM: I didn't know that.
- CAITLYN: I would invite her over
and this and that, she would never come.
Khloe hasn't been here.
Kourtney hasn't been here,
hasn't met Caitlyn. Um...
- Rob.
- PAM: No?
CAITLYN: You know? Maybe...
them not being around is, you know,
kind of their way of saying, "I don't know
if I really agree with this" or what or...
You know, they keep
saying to me, openly, that,
"Everybody's great, it's great,
we want you to live your life."
And then they never show up.
So you know something else
is going on in their head.
You know, for most people,
dealing with something like this,
there's a lot of families that just are...
- PAM: Torn apart, I'm sure.
- CAITLYN: Torn apart by it, you know?
Um, I don't want to tear my family apart.
Now that Pam and Lisa have
gone, we can actually talk.
ESTHER: I know.
CAITLYN: I know, that's kind of nice.
ESTHER: I really didn't
want to go to the beach.
CAITLYN: This beach down here... it's a...
a lo... tough walk to get down to the beach,
'cause you got to walk down that... Yeah.
ESTHER: As you are right
now, as I look at you...
CAITLYN: Right.
ESTHER: You look so much like someone
in my family, and I was
trying to figure it out.
CAITLYN: Um,
I think I look like myself, Mom.
ESTHER: Huh.
CAITLYN: Because the most
important thing in life
is that you're true to
yourself, and I'm doing
better now than I've ever
done before in my life,
you know?
ESTHER: It's going to
be so difficult for me...
to c... to think of you as "she"
and to say "Caitlyn"
when I want to speak with you
or call your attention or... you know...
"Hey, Caitlyn" instead of "Hey, Bruce."
I don't think... It's not easy.
- It's not easy.
- CAITLYN: No, it's not easy.
What aspect is it not easy?
Losing a son?
ESTHER: I don't think... it's not easy.
- It's not easy.
- CAITLYN: No, it's not easy.
What aspect is it not easy?
Losing a son?
ESTHER: The problem before with you and I,
I... I'm guessing this...
you felt uncomfortable with me.
We would see each other, and it
was like you wanted to get away.
CAITLYN: At that point in my life,
I was very much an isolationist.
I would isolate myself from the world
on many, many, many, many occasions.
'Cause I never felt like I fit in anywhere.
I didn't fit in with the male side,
I didn't fit in with the female side.
You're kind of stuck in the middle.
I feel like Caitlyn fits in
a lot better into society,
uh, than Bruce ever did, 'cause Bruce,
uh, had to lie about
all that sort of stuff,
where Caitlyn's kind of got a place.
ESTHER: But Bruce will always be in there.
Your values are always gonna be the same.
CAITLYN: Oh, same.
- I'm still the same person.
- ESTHER: That's not changing.
That's your soul.
CAITLYN: Yeah, that's your
soul... that's exactly right.
ESTHER: You... you have the
same soul you were born with.
CAITLYN: Yeah.
ESTHER: I love Bruce.
It'll never change.
That'll never change.
It's going to take some getting used to.
But I want... I want to do what he wants.
CAITLYN: And the response has been very
good, so that even makes it better, you know?
If the response was,
"Oh, my God, what a weirdo,"
uh, it would be a lot more difficult. But
people have really been behind my honesty,
and I really appreciate that.
I'm very optimistic about the future,
and I'm dragging you along with me.
ESTHER: (chuckles) Okay.
- CAITLYN: Okay, good, good.
- ESTHER: Okay.
CAITLYN: Here's my attitude,
when you go through what I'm going through,
it affects a lot of people.
My entire family kind of
has to go through this...
called "transition."
And all those things will
be worked out in time.
All right.
Maybe I should get this
wild color hair out.
Right now, what I want to
do is just be able to create
understanding so the next person
doesn't have to be like me.
We have to be able to reach out,
one soul at a time,
and figure this problem out.
REPORTER: Kyler Prescott,
a local transgender teen,
- has taken his own life...
- CAITLYN: Another suicide.
REPORTER: ... making this the third
suicide of a transgender youth this year.
His mother spoke out in
an emotional interview.
KATHARINE: I think the world was kind of
too hard a place for such a gentle soul.
He didn't understand cruelty.
He didn't understand
people that didn't understand him.
(Sighs) It's tough.
He would fill the house
with his piano music,
and the house has just been silent,
um, since he left. The music stopped.
LISA: Wow.
CAITLYN: That's the problem.
That's... that's the
problem that we have here
is it happens all the time.
Suicide is a permanent solution
for a very temporary problem,
and most of the ones that are at
risk are these young kids, okay?
- ESTHER: They're... they're still children.
- CAITLYN: Got their whole life ahead of 'em.
It just doesn't need to
happen. That kind of hit home.
I know how these kids can feel.
I've had some very dark moments in my life.
I have been in my house...
with a gun and said...
Let's just end it right here.
"Um, no more pain, no more suffering."
That struggle...
it's real.
And I've been there.
- Hello!
- Hey.
- Look who's here!
- KIM: You look beautiful.
CAITLYN: Well, thank you very much...
- not as good as you. Good to see you.
- KANYE: What up?
CAITLYN: Good to see
you. Thanks. Come on in.
- Welcome to my home.
- KIM: Hi.
- PAM: Long time no see.
- CAITLYN: Sister Pam.
- PAM: We know each other.
- CAITLYN: My older sister.
- PAM: We haven't met. Nice to meet you.
- KANYE: Hey, how are you?
CAITLYN: Kanye and I have
never really been very close,
but, um, I love his open-mindedness,
and I love how he's helped Kim
come to grips with what's going on. K
IM: You look beautiful.
You know, the one thing
I'm really shocked about
is how skinny...
you are. You literally look like Kendall.
- Like Kendall's mom.
- (Laughter)
KANYE: I mean, I think
this is one of the strongest
things that have happened in our,
you know, existence as human beings
that are so controlled by perception.
'Cause you couldn't have
been up against more.
Like, your daughter's a supermodel.
You're a celebrity. You
have every type of thing,
and it was still like, "(bleep) everybody.
his is who I am."
- CAITLYN: This is all good.
- KIM: This is just the beginning.
- KIM: Just the beginning.
ESTHER: Are you gonna take your coat off?
I want to see what you're wearing.
KIM: Oh, nothing hardly fits anymore,
so it's, like, a half-zipped-up skirt.
- ESTHER: I read that you're expecting.
- PAM: That's right.
- KIM: Yes. Yes, yes.
- PAM: Congratulations.
KIM: Thank you. We've
wanted this for a long time.
PAM: That's wonderful.
- KIM: Yeah.
- PAM: So, tell me about the untied shoelaces.
KANYE: These are sock shoes,
so they, like...
PAM: Oh, yeah.
Oh, look at how light they are.
- KANYE: Yeah. But the laces are sort of after the fact.
- PAM: Yeah.
- Not necessary to keep 'em on your feet.
- KANYE: Yeah.
PAM: Yeah. Okay. I just
wanted to be cool, so...
(laughter)
- KIM: All right, can I see these new things in your closet?
- CAITLYN: Okay.
They gave me a ton of
stuff. Tom Ford stuff.
Diane von Furstenberg sent me this...
- three, three outfits.
- KIM: Ooh. I like that. That's so nice.
I like the plain black.
CAITLYN: Yeah... this is all kind of
a little bit more casual stuff here.
This is all vanity... KIM:
These color tones are so
much better than
what you had before.
- Like, I was secretly dying in your last closet.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, secretly dying?
Yeah, this is all just kind
of very casual, good stuff.
- KIM: But this has got to go. Like...
- CAITLYN: Yeah. Oh, I agree.
- this... ?
- And that's the one they caught me in.
- KIM: I know.
- CAITLYN: I said, "Oh, my God,
- Kim's gonna shoot me."
- KIM: Oh, it looks black and white...
no, this has got to go.
I said that last time I saw it.
CAITLYN: I love
- this Tom Ford dress.
- KIM: Mom has that.
- CAITLYN: What's that?
- KIM: So it'll be like a "Who Wore It Better?"
- CAITLYN: Actually, no, no,
- "Who Wore It Best?"
- KIM: She has it in chocolate brown.
CAITLYN: We got to do
that. Isn't that...
- Wouldn't that be the funniest thing ever?
- KIM: Yes...
No, you should just come over,
- like, at a time where, you know, I know she's there.
- CAITLYN: Right.
KIM: And I'll just pick out
an outfit for her to wear,
and "I'll say, " Oh, my God,
I'm gonna take you to dinner.
- You should wear this."
- CAITLYN: Yes.
KIM: And then you should stop by...
CAITLYN: And we'll both
have the same outfit.
- That is...
- KIM: Yes... (laughs)
CAITLYN: That is funny.
I better wear it before she does.
KIM: Very cool.
CAITLYN: Yeah.
- PAM: Oh, there they are.
- CAITLYN: They're leaving.
And so are you guys.
ESTHER: Good to see you again.
KIM: Of course. Bye, everyone.
CAITLYN: Bye, babe!
- I know. All right, good-bye, Mom. You're out of here, too.
- PAM: We'll see you soon.
- ESTHER: Bye, Bruce.
- CAITLYN: All right, have a good trip back.
- ESTHER: I love you.
- CAITLYN: Love you, too.
ESTHER: I always did
and I always will.
CAITLYN: I know, I know.
It's 'cause I got this
adorable personality.
That's what it is. It's
the adorable personality.
ESTHER: I like it better.
CAITLYN: Oh, good, good. Okay, good.
ESTHER: I was so proud of Bruce
when he stood on that podium,
receiving that gold
medal in Montreal.
And I had tears and the American
flag was going up in the middle,
and I thought I could
never be more proud of him.
And, you know, I was wrong.
Because I am more proud of him
for the courage that he has shown.
I loved him with all my heart,
and I certainly love
her with all my heart.
(crickets chirping)
(water running)
CAITLYN: For me, the most
important thing is to learn
about other people.
So far, down in San Diego,
there has been three suicides
of trans teens.
It's devastating. Kyler Prescott,
14 years old,
had his whole life ahead of him.
14... years... old.
I reached out to
Katharine, his mother, and
I want to spend a little bit of time
with her and find out what we can do
to make a difference. Under
the cover of darkness.
So, heading for San Diego.
I'd say we go up the hill.
They'll never see us.
DRIVER: Uh, they're
waiting up there, too.
CAITLYN: The key to this trip is
a clean break from the paparazzi.
Actually, we've only got
one guy following us.
DRIVER: They're posted all
through the hill, so...
CAITLYN: Oh, yeah.
We just, uh...
changed cars. Now I'm in this...
- luxury van.
- DRIVER: There's a silver Lexus up here parked.
There he is.
CAITLYN: I heard the price
tag just for a picture of me
is $250,000.
They are extraordinarily aggressive.
I don't want to bring that kind of
tabloid attention to Kyler's family.
Damn.
Now, we're going to get a third car.
It seems like we've lost the paparazzi.
Every journey is different,
and to learn those stories,
it just kind of educates me.
I can't even imagine what
Kyler's family's going through.
Uh, I don't know what
I can do, at this point,
but just be a friend.
Hello. How are you?
- KATHARINE: Hi. I'm Katharine.
- CAITLYN: Thank you for inviting me down.
- KATHARINE: Thank you.
- CAITLYN: How are you doing?
- KATHARINE: Hanging in there.
- CAITLYN: Hello.
- KATHARINE: This is Chloe.
- CAITLYN: Nice to meet you.
- CARL: I'm Carl.
- CAITLYN: Hi. Nice to meet you, Carl.
Thanks for inviting me down.
- What a cute kid.
- KATHARINE: I know.
- He is, huh?
- CAITLYN: Look at that. Love the hair.
KATHARINE: Yeah. He was a
beautiful kid with a beautiful soul.
Kyler was truly an
amazing... an amazing kid.
I was proud of him for working
so hard to be his authentic self.
CAITLYN: From a parent's perspective,
when... you know, this
kind of probably came out
- of left field...
- KATHARINE: Absolutely.
Um, I knew nothing
about it when we started.
I just luckily had an open mind
and an open heart from the beginning.
From the very first day, I
said, "Sweetheart, I love you.
No matter what, I love you."
And, unfortunately, not all
transgender teens get that.
- Um...
- CAITLYN: That's for sure.
KATHARINE: Yeah, I guess
that's an understatement.
That's something else I want
people to understand is that
even with this full support of your family,
it's still a hard journey.
People always assume when
they talk to me that Kyler was
bullied by other kids or
something like that, and
that's actually not really the case.
Really where he had the
most problems was with
adults not understanding,
people out in society that really
didn't understand that he needed
them to use a male pronoun.
And he had a legal name and gender change.
- CAITLYN: Oh, he did?
- KATHARINE: He did. And
the new birth certificate
arrived, unfortunately,
- just a few days after he passed away.
- CAITLYN: No way.
KATHARINE: Yeah. And that was heartbreaking
because he would have loved to have seen
- the new birth certificate.
- CAITLYN: Loved it.
KATHARINE: But I don't think any suicide is
a sim... has a simple
cause. It's always a complex
set of things that are
challenging that kid.
CAITLYN: We need more tolerance
and empathy towards other people.
It's so hard for young people
because they just don't... th
ey... they can't see the future.
And because of that, they
become extraordinarily desperate,
and suicide becomes an option.
We have to do something about that.
- He was gonna get there, and he was gonna be...
- He just needed to turn that corner.
- KATHARINE: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
KATHARINE: He was young, you
know? He was still just 14,
and at that age, they just don't realize
they're gonna get through
it, they can get through it,
they can get to these wonderful
things on the other side.
CAITLYN: Yeah.
KATHARINE: Today some students are going to
be doing a balloon release in Kyler's honor,
which is so sweet. So I would love it
- if you want to come and see.
- CAITLYN: That is nice.
CAITLYN: I would be honored.
I would love to meet everybody.
KATHARINE: It will be a beautiful moment.
- CAITLYN: It will be.
- KATHARINE: This is a song that was written
by a friend of ours.
It's a beautiful song,
and it was written...
for Kyler.
But it will speak to kids everywhere.
SINGERS: ♪ You wake in the morning ♪
♪ but you can't seem to get out of your bed ♪
And the weight of the covers
♪ Is the weight of the world ♪
Of the people who care
♪ if you're a boy or a girl ♪
But there's just one thing you need to know
♪ Love you no matter what... ♪
CAITLYN: Young people, they have to realize
there is so much help out there.
Thank you for telling your story.
And sometimes it's not always
the parents... it's outside help.
It's a friend, it's a therapist,
organizations that are willing to help.
It's somebody in your life
that you can open up with and
tell 'em your feelings and
what's happening in your head.
- MACY: Hi, I'm Macy.
- CAITLYN: Hello. Caitlyn.
- Nice to meet you.
- MACY: Nice to meet you.
- Thank you so much for coming.
- CAITLYN: Oh, thanks for having me.
MACY: I'm gonna cry.
Like, um... like, he was, like, the
first friend that I made this year, and...
I don't know, I've attempted
I've been... suicide before,
and it got better for me.
I just... (sighs) It's not fair that he
didn't get to see that it gets better.
SINGERS: ♪ Why does
it have to be so hard? ♪
♪ I love you for being
true to who you are ♪
CAITLYN: Seek help.
You just have to get through that day.
- BOY: All right!
- (Cheering)
SINGER: ♪ So be who you truly are... ♪
CAITLYN: Group hug! Group hug!
- (laughter)
- CAITLYN: Just the gals.
GIRL: Thank you.
CAITLYN: Little Caitlyn's
out into the world.
- CANDIS: Yay! Welcome!
- CAITLYN: Yay!
Right now, every day's a new adventure.
- Road trip?!
- WOMAN: How do we sneak you out of here?
CAITLYN: In a trunk.
- (laughing)
- CAITLYN: What happens at a slumber party?
WOMAN 2: You pillow fight,
- you tell ghost stories...
- CAITLYN: Pillow fight?!?
WOMAN 2: You compare your boob sizes...
- (Caitlyn laughs)
- WOMAN 3: Bathing suits.
- You need a sexy one for Candis.
- CAITLYN: We're not going there.
CANDIS: Would you like to go out on a date?
(Caitlyn chuckles)
CAITLYN: But because of my
status, everybody is looking at me
as the spokesperson for
the transgender community.
- WOMAN 4: Nervous?
- CAITLYN: Off the charts.
WOMAN 4: I'm afraid people will
think it's all about makeup and hair.
And yet there are all
these trans women out there
who are in real danger.
WOMAN 5: I was doing sex work.
MAN: I was so suicidal
for so much of my life.
- WOMAN 6: I got stabbed here in the chest.
- WOMAN 7: Oh, my God.
CAITLYN: I'm thinking about my family, and
I'm thinking about all this kind of stuff,
and I'm struggling with it.
Khloe's upset.
She didn't like the Vanity Fair article...
RONDA: Well, you better put
your armor on, and your helmets,
- and get ready.
- KIM: You look amazing;
it's your time; but you don't
have to bash us on your way up.
CAITLYN: I don't want to hurt my kids.
The guys are tougher. They want me
to be the old Bruce.
SCOTT: It's gonna take some getting
used to, I think, for everybody.
WOMAN 8: I thought of it as
my great curse to be trans.
Now I think of it as my great gift.
CAITLYN: What I'm hoping for
is that the world is gonna
follow along with me and
we can learn together.
WOMAN 7: Stop looking on the outside
and start looking on the inside.
We want to be just normal people.
MAN 2: If you have a transgender
kid, you are living with a unicorn,
- an amazing human being.
- CAITLYN: We're all beautiful!
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -