♪ Ano hi jinrui wa omoidashita ♪
♪ Humanity remembered
on that day ♪
♪ Usuyami no naka susumu kage wa
Dare mo kokoro motonaku ♪
♪ The shadows advancing in the dim light
are all restless ♪
♪ Futashika na mirai wa itsu da tte
Hakuhyou no ue ni saku ♪
♪ The uncertain future always blooms on
top of thin ice ♪
♪ Yoru wa otozureru tabi ni hito wo ♪
♪ Every time night fell ♪
♪ Tsumetai te de ore tachi no kubisuji o
yasashiku nadeta ♪
♪ Betraying the dusk, we clung to the
back of burning hope ♪
♪ Tasogare wo uragitte tomoru kibou no
se ni sugari ♪
♪ Betraying the dusk, we clung to the
back of burning hope ♪ii
♪ Oikaketa jigoku e to mukatte iru to
shitte mo ♪
♪ We chased it, despite already knowing
that we were headed for hell ♪
♪ Yume no tsuzuki ga mitainara omae wa
nani o sashidaseru ♪
♪ If you want to see the continuation of
your dreams ♪
♪ Akuma wa amaku sasayaita ♪
♪ What can you proffer? ♪
♪ Shikabane de michi o tsukure ♪
♪ The devil whispered sweetly:
Make a road from fallen corpses ♪
♪ Kono kabe no muko ni nani ga aru ♪
♪ What lies on
the other side of this wall? ♪
♪ Osanaki hibi ni akogareta ♪
♪ Haunting us
since our childhood days ♪
♪ Shinjitsu ga sugu soko ni aru ♪
♪ The truth is right there, ♪
♪ Shikabane no michi no saki ni ♪
♪ waiting for us
at the end of the road ♪
♪ Yumiya ga kakenuketa kiseki tsubasa o
chirashite ♪
♪ In the trail where bows and arrows
fly through, spread your wings ♪
♪ Shinzo o tabanete mo ♪
♪ Even if you have to hide away
your burdened heart ♪
♪ Requiem ni wa haya sugiru ♪
♪ It's too early for the dawn of
requiem to arise ♪
♪ Taiyo wa mada shizunde
inai no da kara ♪
♪ As the sun has yet to set ♪
♪ Susumitsuzukeru ♪
♪ Keep going beyond ♪
♪ Nami no kanata e ♪
♪ The endless moving waves ♪
*ATTACK ON TITAN*
(Shingeki no Kyojin)
Season 03  Episode 19
(S3-56)
"The Basement"
Episode Title: "The Basement"
Armin! Get down!
It hurts...
It hurts so bad...
Bertholdt...
It hurts...
It hurts so bad...
Sasha?
Sasha!
You're in terrible shape...
What happened...?
Armin!
Eren?
I'm glad... you're back!
Huh?
You're up?
Captain!
What in the world happened here?
I remember...
Bertholdt becoming a Titan...
What about the others?!
Are they okay?!
That's as far back as you remember?
Huh?
Eren, tell him everything.
Well? Up to speed, Armin?
Are you telling me... the Scout Regiment...
...is the nine of us here... and that's it?
For the time being.
The fighting ended four hours ago.
We've been looking for survivors,
but... none yet...
S-So, we managed to seal
the walls of Shiganshina...
But Reiner, the Beast Titan,
and one other escaped...
Bertholdt was captured...
Then... there was a dispute...
...about using the injection on
Commander Erwin or me...
And I...
...turned into a Titan
and ate B-Bertholdt...
Here.
Why... did you pick me?
No matter how you look at it,
wasn't Commander Erwin
the right one to bring back?
Captain!
Why did you give me the injection?!
Tsk!
I told you to tell him everything.
The thing is, it seems your two
friends here didn't think that way.
They stood up to me...
prepared to draw blood.
Huh?
We'll take whatever punishment comes.
You'll be disciplined for
insubordination, but...
Does taking the punishment
allow you to do anything?
No...
However...
The final decision to choose you was mine.
No...
I chose this to be the
place where Erwin dies.
I don't understand...
There's no way it's okay
to let Erwin die...
If the commander is gone,
how... how will we go on?
I agree. I thought it should've
been used on Erwin...
...if we're being brutally honest.
No... It's a shame we were
put in that position...
Anyways, Erwin entrusted Levi
with the decision to use it.
And Levi ended up choosing you.
There's nothing more to say.
Erwin's life and a Titan's power
rest on your shoulders.
No matter what anyone says,
that's part of who you are now, Armin.
Does that mean... I need to be...
Erwin's replacement?
No way... I can't...
Don't get me wrong.
You'll never be Erwin's replacement.
But...
...I know you have a strength
that nobody else has but you.
I won't regret my decision.
However, don't make these guys regret it.
Nor anyone else.
And don't regret it yourself, either.
That is your mission.
Shut up!
We're no match for Sasha.
Well, being the successor of Erwin
as commander of the Scouts,
we're kinda in the same boat.
From here on out,
we'll have to grin and bear it.
Right...
Now then...
If it's not a problem for Armin,
we should get going.
Levi, Eren, Mikasa, and
I will go investigate.
You other four keep watch
from atop Shiganshina's wall.
Roger.
Eren. Do you still have the key?
Yeah.
Right here.
Eren...
When I get back,
I'll show you the basement that
I've kept secret all this time.
Hey, Eren!
How many times must I say
you can't go in the basement?!
Why aren't I allowed to?!
Because your father keeps
his work tools there.
Medicine, too.
It's dangerous for children.
Tsk...
Your intentions are the key.
The key to saving humankind
from this despair.
We have reason to believe that the
basement of his home in Shiganshina...
...houses a secret of the Titans
that not even he is aware of.
If we can just reach this basement,
we may be able to obtain information
that will help us break free from
the Titans' century-long tyranny.
Hey, where's your house?
R-Right...
Is this it?
Hey, Dad!
When will you show me
what's in the basement?
Who knows?
Perhaps when you realize
the most important thing of all.
"Information Available for Public Disclosure"
"Basement Key"
"Grisha Jaeger, having come from outside the walls and thus knowing many secrets, entrusted the basement key to his son. The basement will likely reveal the mysteries of the world which Grisha couldn't mention to anyone."
Luckily, the fires didn't make it this far.
Right here.
Under this are the stairs to the basement.
Good.
That's a relief. It's not flooded with water.
Let's go.
Eren.
Right.
What's wrong?
Eren?
Hurry it up.
This... This key...
It doesn't go to this door...
What?
You're kidding... I'm certain that's
the key Dr. Jaeger had.
Step aside.
I'll open it.
Huh? Wait...
Hold up...
It almost feels like
a laboratory down here.
My dad was a doctor, so... he was always
cooped up down here mixing medicine.
That makes sense.
In fact,
if this medicine is all labeled correctly,
it's stuff that's widely available.
And since all the books
here relate to medicine,
at first glance,
it's just a doctor's study.
"There's nothing suspicious here."
It's like that's what he
wants people to think.
Yeah...
If you're hiding stuff from the Interior Police,
you wouldn't want it out in the open.
Hey. Quit standing around, brats.
Erwin's hunches are rarely wrong.
Right.
Thanks, Mikasa.
It's another all-nighter.
Eren...
There's a keyhole right here.
Eren.
It opened.
It's empty?!
Look closer.
It's a false bottom.
It smells like peppermint oil and charcoal.
Were these treated to keep
moisture and bugs away?
We were looking for something...
and these must be it.
I wonder what it was
my dad wanted to show me.
That's when Erwin asked this question...
"How do we know there's not
more humans outside the walls?"
He insisted that as long as we haven't
been able to freely explore the outside,
we can't know for sure if humanity
was completely wiped out by Titans.
And yet, history books declare
the rest were wiped out.
Hmm?
If you consider that history books
should maintain an objective viewpoint,
it should read, "It is believed
the rest of humanity was wiped out."
You're just trying to find fault
in anything and everything.
I'm not! There's intent behind it!
For example...
To make us believe that humanity
doesn't exist outside the walls.
That is, by the royal government
that issues the books.
You're overthinking it.
This is what they call splitting hairs.
I was teasing him back then,
but look at us now...
You'll just have to apologize
to the man himself.
In not too long, it'll be dawn.
If our heroes were to return,
it's about that time...
The Scouts returned just a moment ago!
They successfully took back Wall Maria!
This is... a portrait?
Let me see that.
No... It's far too detailed for this
to be drawn by a person.
That's Dr. Jaeger's writing.
"This is no illustration.
Instead, this uses light
reflected off a subject...
...and burns the image on special paper.
It's called a photograph.
I come from a place outside"...
..the walls where humanity
lives in elegance.
Humanity has not perished.
I pray the person who finds
this book is a fellow patriot.
♪ Sayonara sekai ♪
♪ Goodbye world ♪
♪ narabu kage
nobite majiwaranai ♪
♪ Shadows that line
up do not intersect ♪
♪ negai hikari ♪
♪ Light of hope ♪
♪ mada shiranai keshiki
sagashiteitan da ♪
♪ I was looking for a
scene I could not know ♪
♪ tada hitotsu
yakusoku kawasou ♪
♪ Only one promise
will be exchanged ♪
♪ bokura dake no
namae wo yobiatte ♪
♪ We call our own name ♪
♪ bokura dake no
yorokobi wakachiatta ♪
♪ We only share our happiness ♪
♪ bokura dake no
kotoba de tashikamete ♪
♪ Make sure only
in our own words ♪
♪ bokura dake no itami wo dakishimeta ♪
♪ We embrace our only pain ♪
♪ kono sekai no dokoka
mirai de aeru nara ♪
♪ If you can meet the future
somewhere in this world ♪
♪ wasurenaideite
boku no koto hontou no koto ♪
♪  Don't forget
to tell the truth about me ♪>
Hurry, Fay!
We'll lose it unless we're fast!
Wait up, Grisha!
You two stop right there.
I told you not to forget
your armbands when you go outside.
Grisha, you absolutely
must not leave the walls.
Hey, wait!
I got it, Mom!
We'll be back!
Come on!
When I first thought as to how
I should start my story...
..I immediately thought of that day.
Hey!
- Whoa!
- Sorry!
Grisha, be careful!
Watch where you're going!
Oh... It's leaving...
Must be nice...
Someday when I'm rich, will I be able
to ride on an airship, too?
What are you talking about?
There's no way either of us will get rich.
Yeah...
But it must be nice...
I wonder what we could see from up there.
There it goes...
Let's go, Fay!
Huh?!
My teacher said the airships take off
and land at a place near here!
Let's go see!
What?! But Mom said we're
not allowed to leave the walls!
It'll be fine!
Just for a bit!
We'll be right back!
Hey! Get back here!
That naive day of my youth...
..when I...
..had to face the truth of this world.
His story began with pulling his sister's hand
while gazing upwards at the sky.
The hatred and hope reflected in
his eyes show Eren a cruel world.
Next episode: "That Day."
"That Day"