Life is at its most intense
during the struggles
between predator and prey.
Each side, to survive,
must outwit
and outmanoeuvre the other.
The prize, for the hunter...
a meal.
For the prey,
the chance to live another day.
Three male cheetahs.
These brothers are very special.
They hunt prey few other cheetahs
would dare to tackle.
To succeed,
they must first select a victim.
And then work together
to overpower it.
It's dangerous work.
An adult zebra is
potentially lethal.
The outcome is by no means certain.
The first cheetah is driven off.
And his brothers have already
made a critical mistake.
They aren't close enough
to take over the attack.
Each is chasing a different target,
making it easy for
the zebra to defend their young.
A quarter-tonne stallion
finally puts paid to their chances.
Chasing different zebra
was bound to lead to failure.
Perhaps their enthusiasm
got the better of them.
They must try again.
In the shadow of Mount Kenya,
the brothers regroup.
Their mistake with the zebra was
to hunt as ordinary cheetahs do -
as individuals.
To catch such prey, they must
hunt like no other cheetahs.
That means acting together,
as one.
They start again.
An ostrich outweighs and outguns
a single cheetah.
This time there's only one target.
And all three cheetahs are onto it.
The third brother starts to
throttle the ostrich.
Even off its feet,
it's still dangerous.
The brothers have found a unique way
of catching their prey.
The ability to invent such
novel hunting tactics
is one thing
that really sets mammals apart.
But mammals themselves can also
be targets for predators,
and the hunted
also need to devise special tactics.
The desert shores of the Dead Sea.
Living here is difficult indeed.
It's March, and high
on these cathedral cliffs,
ibex have given birth.
For the first few days
the kids were kept safe,
isolated on the cliff tops.
But now the ibex have a problem.
The only food and water is far
below at the bottom of the gorge.
And that is where predators lurk.
If they're to feed,
it's a risk they will have to take.
The adults lead the way.
They know the safest routes.
Though safe, here,
is a relative term.
The kids
have no choice but to keep up.
One slip could be the last.
Their only assets are cloven hooves
that spread under load,
astonishing balance...
..and the most uncanny agility.
Barely a week old,
they are utterly fearless.
Learning to negotiate these cliffs
is central to their survival.
But now the family must be
on guard against predators.
All grab a chance to browse.
Trailing behind,
the last youngster is almost down.
And runs right into trouble.
A fox.
It's been waiting for the straggler.
The kid has never seen a fox before,
but knows it's in real peril.
It appears to be running
into more trouble,
as it heads back up the cliff.
The fox tries to
gain the higher ground.
But the kid has found safety
on a face so steep
that only an ibex could stand there.
The lessons learnt
on this morning's descent
have saved its life.
Finally, the fox
gives it up as a bad job...
..perhaps suddenly aware
it's standing on a precipice.
Despite its tender age,
the ibex has outwitted
one of the canniest of predators.
The fox's failure
epitomises a predator's plight.
Most hunts fail,
so hunters are continually
devising new tactics.
The rainforests of Belize
in Central America.
And as evening falls
and the shower comes to an end,
a predator begins to hunt.
The greater bulldog bat.
A flying mammal...
..and a fisherman.
A fish swimming just below the
surface creates tell-tale ripples
and that is all the bat needs
to detect them.
With little more than a fin
to aim for,
and whilst flying at
40 miles an hour,
the bat takes the fish
completely unawares.
If the shoal scatters...
..the bat trawls the surface.
Raking the water,
trying to snag a fish.
He won't have the best
fishing spot to himself for long,
and soon, other bats arrive.
Oncoming traffic would make
grabbing a fish almost impossible,
so the bats avoid collisions
by honking -
dropping their calls an octave
to say, "Look out, here I come!"
Soon the shoal has either
been captured or has fled,
and the bats move on.
Skills like this take practice,
and for some mammals that
practice begins in infancy.
A young stoat.
And it's not alone.
STOATS CHIRP
These wild games
are too much to resist.
Stalking, chasing and ambushing,
all practised in play.
Soon the young stoats must
hunt for themselves,
and then these athletic skills
will be crucial.
It's September
in the English countryside.
This stoat is about to take on
an adversary ten times its size.
It's too dangerous
to rush straight in.
Instead, the stoat's aim
is to wear the rabbit down.
The rabbit is flagging,
and the stoat's stamina is
starting to make a difference.
But stamina alone is not enough -
the rabbit must still
be overpowered.
A bite to the back of the neck
and a kill.
The incredible agility of the stoat,
practised since it was a kit,
was just enough
to swing the balance.
There are times when
mere physical powers
are not enough to give
the hunter an edge.
Then mammals must deploy their most
sophisticated weapon - their brains.
Strange patterns are visible
in the mud of Florida Bay,
a faint hint
of a unique hunting tactic.
The perpetrators...
..bottlenose dolphins.
And they're on a mission -
a mission to catch fish.
The fish here
are very difficult to catch
and in such shallow water
they ought to be safe.
Yet the dolphins have a plan.
They have learnt to corral the fish
by working as a team.
The lead dolphin beats its tail
on the sea bed,
stirring up a ring of mud.
Trapped inside, the fish
take their only way out,
but they're leaping out of
the frying pan and into the fire.
Once the mud ring loses its shape,
the fish scatter.
The dolphins move on
and repeat the process.
Brain power
combined with team work -
it's a winning formula.
This behaviour is unique to
the dolphins of Florida Bay.
Successive generations have
learnt it from their parents
and in turn they will teach it
to their own young.
The ability to pass on
such complex behaviours
is one of the mammals'
greatest talents.
It enables them to survive
where others would perish.
As winter approaches in Alaska, food
gets progressively harder to find.
To live here is to walk a tightrope.
Yet every year, this coast attracts
North America's
most impressive hunter.
A brown bear.
Here they grow larger
than anywhere in the world.
Other bears have also gathered
at the edge of the surf.
They've come here
to fatten up for the winter.
They're waiting for an event
that happens just once a year.
The salmon run.
Others will tackle the fish
upriver, but here in the sea,
these bears have the first chance.
Each bear's survival depends
on this run of fish staying strong.
There are years when their gamble
fails and the fish hardly show.
Then the bears face starvation.
This year promises to
be a bumper one
and the bears will be able to
pile on the pounds ahead of winter.
Mammals are supreme
in their ability
to exploit
such fleeting opportunities.
Chances come and go
with the passing of the seasons.
But for some predators, conditions
are tough whatever the time of year.
At first glance, these mountains
seem barren and empty of life.
Like islands thrust up into the sky,
they tower above
the surrounding plains.
Yet, far from being deserted,
they are a refuge.
Isolated here,
on the roof of Africa,
is one of the rarest hunters
in the world.
The Ethiopian wolf.
The only wolf in
the whole of Africa.
Despite being close to the equator,
these peaks are so cold at night
that the wolves face
a frost-covered dawn.
Each pack is centred around
a single dominant female.
Normally it is only she who breeds.
This year she has produced six pups.
But if she is to raise them all
in this barren land,
she will need the help
of the entire pack.
Every morning,
the pack sets off to hunt,
leaving her back among the rocks
with the pups.
The pack's hunting ground is about
five square miles of mountain top.
They guard it zealously,
patrolling its frontiers every day.
Wolves elsewhere co-operate
and use their united power
to pull down big prey.
But there are no caribou or moose
to be found up here.
The pack splits up.
Each member is going to hunt alone.
One of them spots something.
It's a rat.
But catching rats is not easy, no
matter how carefully you stalk them.
Another hunter has
a more pro-active technique.
And that works.
It's a lot of work for
relatively small rewards,
and demands its own
particular style of hunting.
A hunter returns.
Mother demands food and
the successful hunter delivers it.
So rearing a single litter here
takes the combined labour
of a dozen or so adults
and the Ethiopian wolves
have adjusted their behaviour
accordingly.
That adaptability is
the mammals' great strength,
enabling them to survive in
some very unlikely habitats.
A star-nosed mole,
possessor of perhaps the most
extraordinary nose on the planet.
Its nostrils are surrounded
by twenty-two fingers.
Fingers that allow the mole to sense
the world around it by touch alone.
It enables it to detect food
with astonishing speed.
It can also swim...
..and once underwater, its nose
helps it in a most extraordinary way.
It blows out a bubble
and breathes it back in,
detecting in a millisecond
if there's prey close by.
This bubble-blowing allows it to
sniff out its food underwater,
but, unfortunately, that means
it soon runs out of breath.
So it's just as well
that it can hunt as fast down here
as on the surface.
Few creatures can hunt
equally successfully
underground and underwater.
Bandhavgarh, India,
at the height of the dry season.
A chital deer.
They must live their lives with
all their senses at a high pitch.
The faintest smell,
the slightest sound,
the briefest glimpse
could give warning of an attack.
The chital must detect their enemy
before it takes them by surprise.
And they have allies.
Langur monkeys.
Keen eyesight
and a perch high in the trees
means they can scan the forest.
The jungle is full of distraction.
Senses are strained,
trying to detect approaching danger.
Yet the chital still need to feed.
And the hunter must get
within striking distance.
There's a hint of danger
carried on the wind.
The herd shares a nervousness.
You should never run from
what you can't see,
you might just run
straight into danger.
The tiger is nearly close enough
to launch her attack.
She must wait.
The chital need to come
just a little closer.
If she moves now,
the langurs will see her.
The deer had a moment's head start,
and escape.
The langurs' vigilance
saved the chital.
And the tiger goes hungry.
For some mammals,
attack is the best form of defence.
This squirrel is arming herself.
It's a California ground squirrel,
and she's found a snake skin.
She's chewing it into a paste
which she then rubs into her fur,
especially her tail.
She now stinks of snake.
She lives in a colony that extends
across a wide expanse of prairie.
There is one downside
to this neighbourhood -
it's in the middle of
rattlesnake country.
Not good when you have
young to raise.
Her neighbour has sensed something.
A rattlesnake,
hidden right next to their burrow.
They both investigate
but what can they do?
Kicking stones only
provokes the snake.
Rattlesnakes sense prey
by the heat they give off
and the squirrel is able
to take advantage of this.
She heats up her
tail with warm blood.
Waving it at the snake is a threat.
It makes her look much larger
than she is.
SNAKE RATTLES
And the scent of rattler on her
fluffed tail intimidates the snake.
It decides to retreat.
The mother decides this part of
the neighbourhood is too dangerous,
and moves her young
to new quarters.
With luck, this may be
a safer place to raise a family.
Both predator and prey must
endlessly refine their strategies.
Just occasionally, an individual
makes a unique breakthrough
and learns to do something
completely new.
It's December, and a storm rages
around the Falkland Islands.
Gentoo penguins face blizzards
of blown sand.
Young elephant seals
risk being dragged off the rocks
by the surging waves
and swept out into open water.
Orca - the largest and most
predatory of the dolphin family.
Killer whales.
This pod of nine can only
survive here by being opportunists.
Normally, young elephant seals
are not on the menu.
They stay close to the shore,
safe in the shallows of
their nursery pool.
The pool is almost entirely
cut off from the sea.
A narrow, shallow channel is
the only access to the open water.
But this pod of killer whales
contains a very special female.
She's easily identified by her calf,
which is always close by.
Every year she comes to the pool
at the same time,
when the seals
first swim in the shallows.
She knows how to get them.
Negotiating the channel
is her first challenge.
The water near the mouth of the pool
is slightly deeper.
Here she sets her ambush,
waiting for a seal
to stray out of the shallows.
For mother and calf,
this is an extremely risky ploy.
She must continuously assess how big
the waves are, how deep the water is
and what the tide is doing.
One bad decision would see
both mother and calf stranded.
The seals lie in the shallows,
just out of reach
and unaware of her presence.
But she is more than aware
of the dropping tide.
A floundering seal
catches her attention...
..and with her calf,
she slowly moves towards it.
The seal is lying
right on the edge of a rocky ledge,
oblivious to the danger.
The projecting ledge
keeps the seal just out of reach.
Yet she has a plan.
Rocking back and forth,
she's making a wave,
trying to wash the seal
off the ledge.
But it is securely
surrounded by kelp.
SPLASHING
A splash alerts her
to a better opportunity.
Another seal has started to swim
into the pool. This is her chance.
Edging further into the shallows
than ever before,
she's risking everything.
Half beached and with
a struggling seal in her mouth,
it takes all her strength
to drag it out of the pool.
She is the only killer whale
on the planet
that knows how to hunt
these seals in this way
and, crucially, she's now passing
on that skill to her own calf.
Extraordinary strategies like these
lie at the heart of the struggle
between predator and prey.
They're born of a conflict
that is relentless and unforgiving.
A conflict that eternally binds
the hunter and the hunted.
It's looking very promising.
The Life team had set themselves
a tough challenge
in trying to film
exceptional hunting sequences,
but our teams were lucky enough
to observe some of the world's
most charismatic predators.
It was the killer whales
of the Falklands, though,
that brought the team
closest to the action.
Every year, off Sea Lion Island,
killer whales snatch young elephant
seals from their nursery pool.
Filming most hunting sequences
involves a great deal of waiting
and a slice of luck, but here
things were a little different.
Cameraman Mike Pitts and
producer Adam Chapman travelled
to the Falklands
having heard that, for two weeks
each year, killer whales focus
on one particular spot.
The killer whales have learnt
to target elephant seal pups
as they first venture into the water
and this gives the team
their best chance of filming a hunt.
The first task facing the team
is to familiarise themselves
not only with a new location
but also with the animals
they will be working around.
And the team soon realise
that they and their equipment
are a great novelty
to the seal pups.
I daren't look into the camera
because I'm more worried about
the tripod being knocked over.
We've got a little friend here
so I'm gonna report him for
interfering with the film crew.
The pups' fascination with the team
is rather unexpected.
You've got a great way
with wildlife, Michael!
At one with nature!
It's quite difficult out here.
There's so many of them.
The large number of youngsters
bodes well for the killer whales,
but the longer
the team spend with the pups,
the more they warm to them.
When you look at these little pups
you can't fail
to be captivated by them,
especially when you gaze
into those eyes,
it really pulls on
your heartstrings,
but for an orca, of course,
it's 120 kilos of pure protein,
so that's why they're hunted.
As the days go by, the team continue
to get a feel for the location,
when suddenly
the killer whales arrive.
The pod of nine is clearly
interested in the pool,
and one female is
particularly confident.
She's coming in.
The female and her calf start
to come into the pool regularly,
but there never seems to be
a pup within reach.
The team have come to the Falklands
prepared to film underwater.
Now the time has come to see
if this is a realistic ambition.
With lookouts posted and the whales
far away, Mike is able to get in.
Even so,
who can blame him for being jumpy?
Ah!
Whoo!
The pups' playfulness is becoming an
issue - the last thing the team want
is to have any influence
on the events they're here to film.
There's also the question of
how the killer whales might react
to a person in the water.
It's quite intimidating in there.
It shelves up, so I'm in the centre
of the channel and it goes down to,
I don't know, maybe eight feet
I think, a couple of metres.
But the visibility's
really stirred up.
How they find their way in
that channel I just don't know.
And what I'm worried about
is if I do get in the water
with the orca...
Which I'm slightly concerned about,
I have to say...
She's in a hunting mode,
she's not here just for her
to pass the time of day.
She's out there to kill something,
and, you know, I just don't want
to be that person, or seal...
Whatever she thinks I am.
She'll probably realise once she's
bitten me that she's made a mistake
and, I don't know,
is it worth the gamble? No. No.
With a week already gone,
the killer whales have not
yet made a full-blown attack,
and then the weather changes.
Well, hopefully it'll blow
itself out but I think...
The pool, it's going to be a couple
of days before that calms down.
The storm rages for two more days,
but on the eleventh day
the good weather returns.
Mike knows that time is running out.
Well, the orcas are out there,
they're still quite a way off.
The team decides a camera
on the end of a pole
might be the way to reveal
the underwater action.
After that storm,
it's been so stirred up.
And just... Just bring it slightly
out of the water, Adam,
so draw it back towards you and stop.
And it's dark, dark, green,
basically, very dark green.
There's still a lot of...
Suspension, yeah.
The storm had stirred up the pool
making it hard to see anything,
but the team remain in good spirits.
Does my bum look big in this?
Massive!
As the seal pups are nearly
ready to go to sea,
the whales' opportunity
to hunt this year will soon pass
and the team know
this could be their last chance.
Look at the size of that fin!
OK, Mike, she's coming in.
She's coming in, Mike.
She's coming in?
Just here.
Mike?
One second, mate.
I can talk to you gently here now
and I can also see
where you're pointing.
She's in.
I'm recording.
Hold it steady, hold it steady.
I got it.
She's gone past, Mike,
she's in the pool.
OK, get in there.
She's got one, definitely,
you can't mistake it.
Bringing it out now.
Taking it straight out.
She's pulling it out.
Out to sea...
Taking it under.
God, he just got hammered.
Part of me's elated that I've got it,
but part of me's sad, really,
cos I've watched these
little characters, these pups
grow in the last few weeks
and the orcas too,
they've got to survive
and they've made a successful hunt
and they're now continuing
their journey, so what can you say?
Witnessing such events often results
in such a conflict of emotions.
The two-week window is over
and the killer whales move on.
It'll be a whole year before
this exceptional female
returns here to hunt again.