♪♪ (music playing)
Lucy...
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Hello, darling!
The Lord is my Shepperd,
and I shall not fear.
In green pastures He leads me,
beside still waters...
♪♪ (music playing)
FIVE LITTLE PIGS
Based on Agatha Christie's novel
Merci.
- Santé.
Alors,
Mademoiselle Lemarchant...
- For starters, Monsieur Poirot,
that is not my name.
Pardon, but I understood it was
with Mademoiselle Lemarchant
that I was to meet.
- That was the name I was given as a child.
My real name is Crale,
Lucy Crale.
- Crale! Now, I seem to remember...
- My father was Amyas Crale,
the artist, and my mother was...
- Caroline.
- Caroline... Crale.
- That's right.
- Yes, yes...
A story most tragic.
- But it was a long time ago, yes?
- Fourteen years.
14 years?
You know, I saw a picture
that your father painted...
... in the Tate.
- "Girl In The Shadow" .
- That was the one.
- It is a composition most tracking.
- Yes, he was a great painter.
- His reputation is, yes, considerable.
- I'm not here to discuss his art, Mr Poirot.
I'm here because I want you
to investigate his murder.
I was 7 at the time. Too young,
really, to know anything about it.
We lived in Devon,
in a house called Alderbury.
My parents were very much
in love and, in many ways,
it was an idyllic childhood.
But then, one day,
I was suddenly taken from my home
and sent to relatives, in Canada.
Then finally, when I turned 21,
they were obliged to tell me the truth.
For one thing,
I came into my own money.
And then, you see, there's the letter...
- The letter?
- That my mother wrote me
just before she died.
That was the first I knew that my mother
was hanged for killing my father.
That is what I want you to prove.
- But why Hercule Poirot, Mademoiselle?
- I've heard about you, the things you've done,
the way you work. The psicology
is your "forte", n'est-ce pas?
Oui, c'est vrai. My success
it is found in psicology, or...
... the " why" of human behavior.
It is this that I use.
Tout de même, Mademoiselle,
it is so long since it happened.
Secrets and lies, Monsieur.
The past keeps pulling me back,
it won't let me be.
And until these ghosts
are laid to rest,
I can't move on.
Bon,
I am honored
by your faith in me.
But...
I can not, you understand, accept the
insurance about the innocence of your mother?
- And if she was guillty, what then?
- I have to know the truth, Monsieur.
And if the truth is not
what you wish to hear?
I have to know.
... taken for a place of execution,
where you'll be hanged by the neck,
until death.
Not one of my greatest successes,
I have to say.
- The defence was suicide, yes?
- Didn't get on too well, I'm affraid.
Amyas Crale simply wasn't
that kind of chap.
Wine, women, beer...
the lusts of the flesh.
The idea of his
killing himself out of conscience...
Well, frankly,
I don't think he had one.
So, in your opinion, Sir Montague,
Caroline Crale, she was guilty?
I rather thought
that we were taking that for granted.
- Did she ever admit as much?
- Monsieur Poirot, she didn't need to.
I knew we had lost
as soon as she stepped into this box.
She certainly had a motive.
Amyas Crale was always
mixed up with some woman around him,
but this was rather different.
A girl.: Elsa Greer.
Just turned 18.
Quite a looker, I might say.
She knew what she wanted,
and that was Amyas Crale.
She got him to paint her
he ended up falling for her.
Caroline Crale was overheard
to say this...
... if he didn't give her up,
she'd kill him.
What was the evidence against her?
She stole some poison to the neighbor
who dabbled in herbs and alike,
and hid it in a scent bottle,
and when the police found it
in her room, she claimed
she intended to kill herself.
What she couldn't explain
was why the bottle was empty
and only her fingerprints
were on it.
We contempted, of course, that
Amyas Crale had used it to kill himself,
but, if he had, his fingerprints
would be on it as well.
And how did she give it to him,
this poison?
She used a pipet to spike
his beer.
Pardon, Monsieur. "Spike"?
Uh- tempered. She took him a bottle
while he was painting.
The police found the pipet
crashed near the scene of the crime.
The prosecution had a filled day.
So,
she put the conium into the bottle
before taking it to him?
No, there was no conium in the bottle
at all, only in the glass.
I see!
- Was that you beeing inscrutable, Mr Poirot?
- Non, non. Pardon.
But were there, I'd believe,
other people present, at the time?
Oh, yes, there were. Let me think.
Five, if memory serves.
Philip Blake, a stock broker,
one of Crale's best friends;
Meredith, his older brother.
He lives across the estuary, from the
house where the murder took place ;
Elsa Greer, of course,
currently Lady Dittisham,
though now
she spends most of her time
in the gossip columns
in the divorce Courts;
and the governess, Miss... Wilson?
Williams! That's it!
Very capable, but not exactly
a bottle of laughs.
Then, of course, there was
Angela, Caroline's half-sister.
Oh, she'd been off back to school,
by the time of the trial. Poor thing.
- She had perhaps a problem?
- There was a rather unfortunate incident,
when she was a toddler.
Caroline Crale, as a young girl,
threw a bit of a tantrum.
I did argue that she was not in
her sain mind, but...
Fascinanting creature!
I'll never forget her, you know?
She had a quality
one couldn't help but admire.
Somehow, she was,
above it all.
What people would do,
in the name of love!
It makes fools of us all,
n'est-ce pas?
Eh bien, I thank you, Sir Montague.
You have been most helpful.
Pleasure meeting you, Poirot.
Tell to me, if you please...
If, as her daughter hopes,
Caroline Crale did not kill her husband...
- But she did, old boy. Take my word for it.
... but then it makes the logic that
one of these 5 people must have done it.
There's no reason
why any of them should.
No, but all the same, I think I shall
pay each of them a visit.
And hear five different versions
of the same event?
- Thank you, Hollinghurst.
- A pleasure, mr. Blake.
A fairly good aid, old Hollinghurst,
even though he does bat for the other side.
Telly-o!
Telly-o...
Well, who'd have thought it? Raising a glass
with the famous Hercule Porrow.
Poirot, Monsieur. Hercule Poirot.
Poirot, Porrow... Could never
get my tongue around French.
Let's keep
the old  entente cordiale, eh?
But I am Belgium, Monsieur,
not French.
So, what can I do for you?
It is the Crale case, Monsieur.
It is that which I wish to discuss with you.
What the hell for?
Because I have accepted the commission
Monsieur to review the case.
- From whom?
- Lucy Crale.
- Lucy Crale?
- Oui, Monsieur.
Nothing to discuss.
Five minutes of your time, Mr Blake,
it is all that I ask.
What the hell is she
poking her nose in, now?
- Because she wishes to know  the truth.
- Everyone knows the truth!
But all she wishes is to access
for herself the facts.
- It's over! Dead, buried.
- As are her parents, Monsieur.
Amyas Crale was the best friend
a chap could have.
We knew each other since we're children.
We all: myself, my brother, Caroline.
Neighbors, you see.
By the seaside, in Devon.
Amyas was a great play.
And all that talent, that...
... lust for life,
wiped out because of her.
You did not like her?
Rotten... through and through.
Amyas could never see it.
But he was also something of a
rotten, was he not?
That's what she'd have you believe.
Oh, she liked playing the injured part,
and did it very well,
but.... underneath it all,
she was cold and calculating.
Had a devil of a temper!
Tried to kill her baby sister,
for God's sake!
- Is it true?
- Damn right.
Chucked a paperweight at her
and blinded the little blight in one eye.
Disfigured for life.
Do you know the reason
for this fit of temper?
Sibling's jealousy,
simple as that.
And were jealously that
made her kill Amyas.
I tell you, that woman
was trouble.
Even as a girl... the way
she played us boys along.
Gave us all the one say,
but finally settled on Amyas.
Not surprisingly.
He was in line to inherit Alderbury
and showing talent as an artist.
A rich genius,
what could be better?
It is surprising, is it not, how soon
in life the dice is cast?
Yes, I suppose it is.
Anyway, after the marriage,
I kept my distance,
for a while, at least.
But I soon succumbed to temptation.
Temptation, Monsieur?
Alderbury.
A place I couldn't resist.
I spent some of the happiest
times of my life in that house.
That September,
like the Summers of childhood,
I was hoping for a peaceful
few weeks.
- Uncle Phil!
- But I should've known better.
- Good morning, mr. Blake.
- Good morning, mrs. Spriggs.
- It's good to see you again.
- Good to see you.
- Amyas, please!
- They've been at it for hours.
- Hello, uncle Phil.
- Hello!
My, you grown!
Angela's looking after you, is she?
- No? No?
- Com'on, Lucy!
- Catch me if you can!
- Give her a chance.
Wait for me, Angela.
- Why won't you listen to me, Amyas?
- Caroline, for God's sake!
- That's right, run away like ya always do.
- There goes the jardinere.
There was something
up in the atmosphere...
But this time,
you could cut it with a knife.
And I soon saw why.
Amyas, old chap! How the hell are ya?
Lovely, isn't she?
Sometimes I wish
I'd never met her.
Thank God you turned up.
Living in a house full of women is enough
to send any men out to his chump.
- Philip, how lovely to see you!
- Hello, Caroline.
Just in time for lunch.
Will Elsie be joining us?
- Elsa.
- Amyas is doing her portrait.
Skittish little thing. She should watch
all that sun, you know?
Can be very ageing.
- Things are a bit rocky at the moment.
- Is it serious, Elsa and you?
- It'll be a damn good painting.
- That's not what I asked.
You know me, Phil.
I can't help myself.
Then things got worse.
Amyas and Caroline's
half sister, Angela,
had been beckoning all morning.
Would you stop that please, Angela?
- What?
- Slurping.
- I'm not slurping.
- Yes, you are.
Amyas...
I thought I might try that other
kimono, the canary yellow.
It could be rather stunning
against that water, don't you think?
Canary! How lovely.
Of course on some people it might
look a little... how shall I put it?
Don't worry, Caroline. I'm
young enough to carry it on.
We're not changing anything.
For God--! Did you hear that?
Looks like the feeding hour
in the monkey house!
Why don't you just
leave me alone?!
- I hadn't seen this before.
- It's by Wolgemut Dahl,
a young Norwegian. Extraordinary, don't
you think? Everyone's talking about him.
Got a sense of humor,
I'll give him that.
Don't you agree, Miss Williams?
- Beech wood, isn't it?
- Thank you, mrs. Spriggs.
This room would be so lovely
if it weren't so clutched.
When I'm living here,
I'll throw out all the rubbish,
which is, let's face it,
is pratically everything.
And I've always thought copper coloured
curtains would be simply divine.
Don't you think they look
rather lovely in the setting sun?
- Are you thinking of buying any, Elsa?
- That won't be necessary.
- You seem to have lost me, my dear.
- All this pretense,
it's so dishonest.
Amyas and I love each other
and we're going to be married,
so I shall be moving in.
- As I suspected, my dear,
you're completely insane.
That bloody bisque
gave me a frightful indigestion.
Ask mrs. Spriggs, she'll give you
bicarbonate of soda.
Good thinking.
By the way, Elsa says
you want to marry her.
Is this true?
- Is it true?
- It's only fair that she should know.
Amyas, is it true?
Then, it is.
If you'll excuse me, I'll just...
You know, looking back,
I wouldn't be surprised if she had
made up her mind to kill him then.
Amyas, do tide yourself up. We're going
up to Meredith for tea, remember?
- Ahn, yes, I'd forgotten.
- Philip,
you should do some fishing while you're here.
The sea's probably sworming with mackerel.
So, we all trooped off to Merri's.
Weren't very merry that afternoon...
Amyas can't do this!
Looks like he's going to.
He can't just leave his wife and child
for some slip of a girl.
She's too young to know
what she's doing.
She knows all right.
Poor old Merri, all that sensitivity
no use at all.
Hard to believe we come
from the same stable.
After tea, he took us to his lab.
Conium. I've never heard of this.
It's distilled from the flowers
of the spotted hemlock.
Highly poisonous, but can be
efficacious in the treatment...
Sorry.
Then he had the treat
to read us
some classical about the whole death
of Plato or Socrates,
or someting whatnot.
"The man who administered the poison
pinched his foot,
"and asked if he felt.
Socrates said no.
"Then he did the same to his legs,
"and gradually, moving up
and led us this way, and let us see
"that he was cold and numb.
"He said that, when it reached
the heart,
Sócrates would be gone."
Back at HQ, that evening,
Amyas and Angela had a God-allMighty
row about someting,
but nothing out of the ordinary.
I even think she might have
thrown something at thim.
- Can you remember what?
- Good Lord, no.
- It was 14 years ago!
- But yes, of course.
You are being most helpful,
Monsieur Blake.
The next morning,
when I came downstairs,
I heard Amyas
and Caroline in the library.
I don't know where they
the energy from.
...I swear to God!
You and your women!
Someday I'll kill you, Amyas.
- Don't be idiot.
- I swear to God I will!
Good morning.
- Lovely day!
- I want to get on.
- I'll go change.
- Don't be long. Bloody women!
And off he went, back to his painting
while I went back inside.
- Good morning.
- It's too cruel, too cruel.
She hardly noticed me.
Now, of course, I know why.
Hello?
What the hell's the matter?
I heard these noises
from the laboratory...
... so, I went to have a look
and the conium bottle
was not only out of place,
but was practically empty.
And I swear to you, Phil,
that yesterday it was full.
- Are you sure?
- Of course I'm sure!
I'm very careful about these things.
And I knew at once it must
have been Caroline.
I should've gone straight to Amyas
and warned him.
That's absurd. Caroline
wouldn't dream of such a thing.
- Then, what's your explanation ?
- ..being too harsh with her.
- For God's sake!
- We'll discuss after lunch.
I'll see to her packing...
- What are you two up to ?
- We were just...
- What a surprise!
- Yes...
We're just having a little chat
about Angela and school.
I'm not sure at all
it is the right thing.
Sorry about that.
- Hello everybody!
- I'd kill for a cold beer.
I'll send some down.
I think we all could do with one.
And that's when it happened.
- Why don't I take it?
- Oh, no! Enjoy the sun.
At the time, I reasoned
that it might be jealousy,
That she couldn't stand the thought
of the two of them being alone together.
I should've realized, but, instead
I sat and watched.
I had the chance to save him,
and I did nothing.
You reproach yourself unduly,
Monsieur Blake.
Amyas didn't join us for lunch,
and Caroline took him cofee.
so calm and collected,
and yet,
she must have known by then
he'd be dead.
Miss Williams went with her,
and then Meredith...
... wandered off, but it wasn't long
before we saw him again.
Get a doctor! Quick!
What's wrong?
- It's Amyas...
- What?
I'm affraid he's dead.
Amyas!
Phone a doctor.
I'll take care of her.
She was like an Avenging Fury.
I had mever seen anything  like it.
You killed him! You killed you !
My Amyas!
- You've killed my dearest friend!
- No!
- He did it to himself.
- Tell that to the police.
They didn't believe her either.
Eh bien, Monsieur Blake,
The truth, it has the habit of revealing itself.
Monsieur Poirot...
- Lady Dittisham...
- Let's get on with it, shall we?
I said all I had to say about
the Crale Case many years ago.
But I found your letter
rather intriguing.
How lucky you are curiosity
took the better of me.
Indeed I am, milady.
It must be very painful
for you to recall.
Painful? No.
My father was a manhandled who
worked his way up and made a Mint.
You can't do that with thin skin
in eye, I'm my father's daughter.
I am not as sensitive
as you might think.
Then that makes my task a little easier.
One so often jumps to
the wrong conclusion.
At the trial, for example,
people thought what a terrible
ordeal it must have been for me:
the brutish questions,
the ghastly jornalists,
the mindless screaming crowd.
But the english are a people
very moral, n'est-ce pas?
That's one way of looking at it.
Alors, if you did not find
the trial an ordeal,
how do you find it?
- I enjoyed it.
You see, I got exactly
what I wanted.
And what was that?
Caroline Crale
at the end of a rope.
Coffee?
Thank you, Tipping.
You said in your letter
that Mademoiselle...
- Lemarchant.
- That's right.
Had commissioned you.
I don't believe I know her.
She is the daughter of
Amyas and Caroline Crale.
Oh, yes! Of course.
There was a child.
Oh, dear!
Does she think it was my fault?
It is a possible interpretation, oui.
- How very stupid. Cream?
- Non, non. Merci.
So, you take no responsability?
Why should I? I loved him,
and I would've made him happy.
And that woman killed him
to stop that from happening.
You have to understand, Amyas Crale
did not seduce an innocent young girl.
It wasn't like that at all.
Elsa Greer.
As soon as I laid eyes on him,
I knew I had to have him.
- I want you to paint me.
- I don't do portraits.
I'm rather rich, you know?
I can afford to pay.
And what makes you think
I'd want to paint you?
But you do, don't you?
And I always get what I want.
So, when do we start?
If I paint you, you realise
I'll make love to you?
I'd have thought
that went without saying.
So, he invited me down to their house,
quite bold of him, really.
But Caroline
didn't seem to mind.
She didn't like me, but then,
why should she?
And  we never said anything
that she couldn't have overheard.
But we were more than aware
of what was going on.
What is it?
I think you ought to go
back to London.
But the picture... we've hardly started.
I can't paint you, Elsa.
- Why?
- You know why.
So, I left.
I didn't write, or telephone.
And after 10 days...
He couldn't keep away.
We were together for two weeks
and soon we realised that
we had to be together.
- Always.
- I want you to come back to Alderbury.
I've decided to finish the painting.
- What about Caroline?
- What about her?
- Shouldn't you tell her?
- What on earth for?
She's bound to find out,
sooner or later.
We'll get the picture finished first.
But you will tell her, won't you?
- Yes.
- Promise?
Promise.
Do you she'll make
a terrible fuss?
She always makes a fuss.
She loves me.
Then she should put
your happiness first.
He painted in a kind of frenzy.
I'd never seen like that before.
- Keep still, for God's sake!
- I was convinced we should tell her,
but Amyas wouldn't hear of it. Then,
one day, I... lost my patience.
Amyas and I love each other
and we are going to be married.
So I shall be moving in.
Amyas was furious
but he had to admit
what I said was true.
And I still think I was right. Honesty is,
after all the best policy, don't you agree Mr Poirot?
Desirable, certainly,
but not always advisable.
We believe in plain speaking,
where I come from.
I'm very pleased to hear it, Madame.
But Caroline had a devious way
about her.
When we went to Meredith
for tea, that afternoon,
she behaved as if
nothing had happened.
I even began to think
she was taking it rather well.
How wrong I was!
If you please to tell me,
Lady Dittisham,
in plain speaking,
if, when you were all assembled
in the laboratory of Monsieur Blake,
you observed Caroline Crale take the conium.
- No, I did not.
I seem to remember chatting
with Meredith in the doorway,
so I wouldn't have been able to see a thing.
- Caroline...
Sorry, Merri.
It's such a fascinanting collection...
But of course she did take it,
and we all know why.
Perhaps not everyone is
as sure as you.
I actually heard her threatening him.
You and your women!
Someday I'll kill you, Amyas.
- Don't be an idiot.
- I swear to God I'll kill you.
You can threaten all you like,
but get this,
I'm going to marry Elsa
and nothing is going to stop me.
- I'll kill you rather than let you go.
- Morning.
For God's sake!
- Lovely day!
- I want to get on.
- I'll go change.
- Don't be long.
Which I did. Then, I went to
join him and I poured him a beer.
She's making a terrible
song and dance.
Told you she would.
- To my Mona Lisa.
- My darling Amyas.
- God, it's warm!
- I can get you a cold one.
On that seat. Sit down, now!
He painted as if his life
depended on it.
Dear Amyas...
I loved him so much...
It happened shortly after that. I
popped up to the house to fetch a shawl,
and, when I came back, she was there.
Sorry about that.
Hello everybody!
- I'd kill for a cold beer.
- I'll send some down.
She must have known then
what she meant to do.
She brought it back
about 10 minutos later.
Tastes foul!
Everything tastes foul, today.
Too much bile, my dear.
It'll choke you, one of these days.
I didn't suspect a thing.
About 40 minutes later,
he complained about stiffness and pains.
- Bloody rheumatism!
Then, the bell sounded for lunch
and Meredith came to fetch me.
Amyas decided to skip lunch,
as he often did.
Old grumpy doesn't want any lunch.
So we left him...
... to die alone.
Amyas! Amyas!
And I just knew it was Caroline.
How could she do that?
How could she?
It is a story most...
... tragique, n'est-ce pas?
Hanging was too good for her.
Monsieur Blake...
Little Lucy...
... a grown woman.
One can hardly believe it.
- Time passes swiftly, does it not?
- Poor child.
Such a terrible shock. How much
better to let it all be.
The whole point, you see, is that
Amyas Crale was an artist,
and his art was his passion.
When he painted,
he was like a man-- possessed.
He meant to finish that portrait,
whatever the cost.
Elsa was terrifically enthusiastic
about the painting, and Caroline...
- Yes?
- I had always been...
... very fond of her.
Come on, Merri, come on!
There was a time
when I'd hoped to marry her,
but that was soon nipped in the bud.
Still I remained,
if I may say so,
devoted to her service.
Dear God!
When I think of what they did to her!
Strung up like an animal!
Such a gentle creature...
I remember a conversation we had
shortly after it all began.
Do you think he really cares for her?
Well, he's very committed to
the painting.
- He's in love with her, isn't he?
- A little, perhaps.
A great deal, I think.
There's only one person
he reallly cares for, I think that's you.
These infatuations, they come
and they go.
That's what I used to think.
But this time I've a feeling it's serious.
- She's just a girl.
- That's the trouble.
The way she looks at him!
So intense!
I'm affraid, Meredith.
It's nothing.
I hope you're right.
But I can't help feeling
I'd like to take a hatchet to her.
- A hatchet?
- It's a small ax.
I know what a hatchet is. I was
commenting rather on her remark.
- It was merely to make her point.
- She made her point a little more forcibly,
forcibly, did she not? With her
baby sister Angela,
- The paperweight.
- Oui.
It was a moment of sibling's jealousy
for which she never forgave herself.
And disfigured a girl for life.
That was the problem.
It was a constant reminder,
and she tried desperatly
to make amends,
which, in turn,
made Amyas very jealous.
You knew him for many years,
n'est-ce pas?
Since boyhood.
But he was always more
Philip's friend than mine.
You did not like him?
I think his conduct was
frankly disgraceful.
Don't you understand?
This painting is the best thing I've done
and I'm determined to see it through.
No. I think it's a disgrace...
... the way you treat Caroline.
The way you've always treated her.
What about Lucy, for Heaven's sake?
You can't just throw it all away.
You're a good man, Merri,
but such a old softy.
Wait til the picture is finished
then you'll see I was right.
That grin he gave me...
I'll never forget Caroline,
that afternoon.
She made such an effort,
and yet, behind it all...
Is there anything the matter, my dear?
Everything. It's gone.
Finished.
When she said, at the trial,
that she took the poison to kill herself,
I swear she was speaking the truth.
But why did you take your guests
into the laboratory?
- Someone must have sugested it.
- Caroline Crale, perhaps?
Well, I often took guests into
my laboratory. It wasn't unusual.
- This is valerian.
- The one that cats like.
Yes, they can't get enough of it.
It can be used as a sleeping draft.
Elsa, You should have a sniff.
I've amount pleasure
from my brews,
getting the plants at night,
macerating and all the rest of it..
It's astonishing how a simple
decoction can make wonders.
Conium. I've never heard of this.
It's distilled from the flowers
of the spotted hemlock.
- Isn't that what Socrates took?
- That's right.
You know, there's the most moving
description of his death on Plato's "Fédon".
I can read it to you if you'd like.
Sorry. Sorry,
it must be the heat.
"The man who administered the poison
pinched his foot,
"and asked if he felt anything.
Socrates said no.
"Then, he did the same to his legs,
"gradually moving upwards,
showing us this way and letting us
"see that he was getting cold and numb.
"He said that when it reached
the heart,
Socrates would be gone."
And that is how Amyas
met his fate...
... the very next day.
When did Madame Crale
take the conium from the bottle?
Just before she came
into the study area...
I think Philip e a Angela
left first,
followed by Amyas. I was
in the doorway, waiting to lock up,
having a word with Elsa. I supose
that's when she took it.
- Caroline.
- Oh sorry, Merri.
Such a fascinating collection...
Phil? It's Meredith.
Something terrible's happened.
He immediately suspected Caroline.
Quite unfairly, in my opinion.
Who else could have done it?
It must have been Caroline.
As we approached the water garden,
we overheard Amyas and Caroline
having a rather heated discussion,
I think about Angela
being packed off to school.
It's such a shameful behaviour!
I was in such a state
I didn't pay it much atention.
It's settled.
I'll see to her packing.
Philip blamed himself
for not acting sooner,
but how on earth could
anyone have assumed,
at that point, that someone
had murder in mind?
I needed time to think.
So, just before lunch, I sat
above the water garden
where Amyas was painting Elsa.
... and I can sit like like a
Roman Emperess in the Coliseum.
So radiant,
full of life,
more alive than any person
I have ever known.
- Keep still!
- The blind confidence of youth.
- Bloody rheumatism!
- Poor thing!
Old grumpy doesn't want any lunch.
The problem was, he often looked
like that when he was working,
so I didn't think anything of it.
- Elsa...
- I could eat a horse.
You know, I do so wish...
What?
Well, that you and Amyas would stop it.
Just stop it.
He has a wife and child.
His place is with them.
Oh, Meredith... (laughs)
After lunch,
they had coffee on the terrace.
Caroline took a cup down to Amyas,
and Miss Williams accompanied her.
I followed shortly afterwards,
I think to...
... walk off my lunch.
- Mr. Blake!
- What's wrong?
- A terrible thing!
- What on earth is it?
Mr. Crale... He's dead.
Would you be so kind as
to call a doctor?
My God!
(sound of running and panting)
Get a doctor! Quick!
- What?
- It's Amyas.
- I'm affraid he's dead.
Amyas!
Poor child.
She just just couldn't believe that
life could play so cruel a trick.
Caroline stood there, quite calmly,
and said he must've done it to himself.
So, you are perfectly convinced, Monsieur,
that she was guilty?
She was provoked, in the extreme.
- But you do not believe it was suicide?
- Caroline did it, I'm sure of it.
And anyway,
what if she didn't...
Hercule Poirot, Mademoiselle.
Lucy Crale...
She must have been very young
When you last saw her.
Seven and a half.
Charming.
A little too quiet.
Lived in a world of her own.
If you tell to me, please,
Mademoiselle,
her parents,
they were most devoted, yes?
One does occasionally find,
Monsieur Poirot,
a husband and wife
so wrapped up in each other
that the child
hardly seems to impinge.
So, more like lovers
than husband and wife?
If that's how you wish to put it.
- Did you like Madame Crale?
- Yes, I was very fond of her.
And your pupil?
Angela was a most interesting
if difficult girl.
I cherish the belief that I've played a
modest part in her success.
Have you read her book
of the tombs in the Fayum?
- Sadly, non.
- It's compelling stuff. Read it.
I guess. Yes, I  shall...
You must have been upset
when she was sent away to school.
No, no, not at all.
To her, home life was hardly
what would turn "ideal" .
Caroline indulged her,
Amyas got jealous,
he and Angela would fight, and she'd
end up playing some spiteful trick.
And though, of course,
far greater actions prevailed.
You mean Elsa Greer?
Exactly.
What was your opinion of her?
She was totally unprincipaled.
And also very much in love. His death
must have been for her a shock most terrible.
- And it was entirely her fault.
- Mademoiselle Greer?
The way she carried on.
She even had the insolence
to suggest they were going to marry.
- It's only fair that she should know.
- Amyas, is it true?
Then, it is.
The look she gave him!
Magnificent!
And then she walked out,
head held high,
her grace
and dignity unsolid.
- Was she aware of how much you admired her?
- I believe...
I hope that... I adequately
expressed my...
... my support for her.
- Mrs. Crale...
- Not now, Miss Williams.
- I just meant to tell...
- Another time, please.
Yes, of course. I'm sorry.
- I think you're wonderful.
- Oh, but you don't know...
And then, Mademoiselle?
And then, they all went to tea
at Meredith Blake's.
And that evening, after dinner,
the usual arguments began
about Angela and school.
Now, you listen! The fees are payed
the uniform's bought,
case closed!
- I'm not going!
It's a lovely school, darling.
It's right in the middle of the Downs.
I'm sure that you'll
make lots of nice friends.
I don't want any friends.
- You won't get any, if you carry on like this.
- Why do you want to get rid of me?
Nobody wants to get rid of you.
You know we all love you.
He doesn't! He won't care
if he doesn't see me again.
Right! All this screaming
like a fishwife...
- You know all about them!
- Now, look here, girlie...
- I wish you were dead!
- Angela!
I followed Angela to her room
e reprehended her sharply.
The next morning was so beautiful
that I fondly thought it might
restore some peace to our lives.
Little did I know it was
the harbinger of murder.
Angela!
Angela had yet again disappeared,
I thought for a swim,
but there were no signs of her.
So, I returned to the house.
Mrs  Crale was about to serve some beer
before lunch, so I offered to help her.
We went to the cellar, which was used
to cold storage.
As we arrived, we found Angela,
behaving in a most suspicious manner.
- What on earth are you doing with that?
- I was just...
I hope you weren't thinking
of drinking it.
I'll take, if you don't mind.
Would you mind serving the others?
I'll pop this down to Amyas.
And all this time Mlle. Greer
was sitting for Monsieur Crale?
Yes.
- Oh, he got what he deserved.
- He acted very badly, oui, c'est vrai.
But he was...
- A great artiste, n'est-ce pas?
- Great? Couldn't even draw.
His perspective was terrible,
The anathomy was all over the place...
I know what I'm talking about.
I studied art, as a girl, in Florence.
Tell me, Mademoiselle,
you were with Madame Crale
when she discovered the body, yes?
No, not exactly.
We went down from the house together,
after lunch.
She was taking Mr. Crale some coffee,
and I was going to the beach
to look for Angela's jersey.
Amyas? Amyas!
Mrs. Crale?
It's Amyas.
He's dead.
- Mr. Blake! Mr. Blake!
- What's wrong?
I bumped into Meredith Blake,
told him the terrible news,
and asked him
to telephone the doctor.
I was most concerned
about Mrs. Crale,
I didn't want her to be left alone.
Did you get an impression about what
Madame Crale was thinking at the time?
It was impossible to tell.
She was stunned.
What view did she adopt
oficially as to his death?
Suicide.
- Even in private, to you?
- She had no doubt whatsoever.
And what did you say to her?
- Is that chair uncomfortable, Mlle.?
- It's perfectly comfortable, thank you.
- Tou were about to tell me...
- I-I- I think I said,
"Cnly, Mrs. Crale,
it must have been suicide" .
- Did you believe that?
- No, I did not.
But understand this:
I was entirely on her side.
- So you'd have liked to see her acquited?
- But of course I would.
I woman of honor, of dignity,
hanged like a carcace in a butchershop!
Poor Lucy! Having to be confronted
by all of this!
Still, it is always better to face the truth.
But there's more to it than that. She wants
to prove her mother to be innocent.
Then, her wish will not
be granted.
Before she was hanged, Caroline Crale
wrote to her daughter a letter
in which she solemny swears
her inocence.
It would perhaps have been better...
... to tell her daughter not to judge.
- You seem very sure of her guilt.
- It's hard to believe otherwise.
- And yet you profess to have loved her.
- I did love her.
I did.
If that is all...
Yes, yes, of course.
Thank you very much for your time,
Mademoiselle. You have been most helpful.
I know that she was guilty,
Monsieur.
- Without a shadow of doubt.
- May I ask how?
After bumping into
Meredith Blake
and informing him of Mr. Crale's
death, I returned to the water garden.
Mrs. Crale was not in command of
herself , as I implied.
It was the fear in her face
that told me the truth.
That's when I knew
she had poisoned her husband.
And I, for one, do not blame her.
She never knew what I'd seen,
and I never told her.
In fact, I never told anybody.
During the trial,
I was never asked a question
to which I returned an untrue answer,
but I was guilty
of witholding certain facts.
And I do not repent of that,
Monsieur Poirot.
I would do so again.
... was in fact such a corrupt and venal
as the sociedade of today.
Since then, there have been
other other key  excavations,
but none as remarkable
as Chagar Bazar. Thank you.
Thank you so much for coming.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hercule Poirot, Mademoiselle.
The Chagar Bazar digging
was quite simply extraordinary.
Did my account of it
in the "National Geographic"?
- Sadly no. I have not yet...
- Fairly definitive,
if I may say so myself.
Little Lucy...
I'd so like to see her.
- You have not kept in contact?
- No, not nearly as much as I should've.
I think it's admirable that she wants
to clean her mother's name.
- Then, you approve it?
- Of course.
Caroline didn't do it.
I've always known that.
You surprise me, Mademoiselle.
- Everyone else with whom I have spoken...
- I know, I know.
The circunstancial evidence
were overwhelming,
that's frankly why I never
tempted anything myself.
I knew my sister extremely well
She quite simply
couldn't have killed anyone.
The human nature has the infinite
capacity to surprise .
- Not in this instance.
- How can you be so certain?
Because I am.
But I'm affraid, Mademoiselle,
that would not stand up in court.
That's why I was never called
to give word in evidence.
- And if you had been...?
- This is why I know.
But for many,
that would prove the exact opposite.
As they claimed at the trial,
but this was a moment's rage
haunted her for the rest of her life.
She never forgave herself,
as a result, she was
constantly on her garde.
I don't say she was meek
or timid, quite the opposite,
but murder? Never! Never!
It was an idillic summer
in so many ways...
... what I can remember of it.
Oh, come on, Lucy, do shoot me!
That's all the point.
If only that woman didn't
come into our lives...
All this pretense,
it's do dishonest.
Amyas and I love each other
and we're going to be married,
so I should be moving in.
Then, when Amyas came out...
Why did Elsa say
she's going to marry you?
- And how did you hear that?
- The window's open.
It's damned rude eavesdropping.
- But why did she say it?
- It was a joke.
- It's not very funny to me.
- Enough, all right?!
Come on. Come on.
And then, on our way to tea
at Meredith's, I confronted Caroline.
- Is it true?
- What, darling?
Is Elsa going to marry Amyas?
Only after I'm dead.
The rest of the day is blur.
Kinda remember Meredith reading
rather beautiful about Socrates...
" ... he said when it reached the
heart, Socrates would be gone."
... and then Amyas and I having
a real humdinger after dinner.
Now look here, girlie!
I think I threw something
at him.
And the next day,
the day it happened,
again it's all very vague, up until the
point Merry came panting down the path.
I kept saying to myself,
"Amyas is dead" .
But it didn't seem real.
Then the doctor came, the police
came, they brought him to the house.
I want you to go to grandma's,
with Lucy.
No, no. I don't want to go.
- I want to stay with you.
- I know, my darling,
but it's best that you do. It'll
easier that way, believe me.
No, please,
I don't want to leave you.
For me, my darling, do it for me.
And you must try not to think about it.
There's nothing to worry about,
I promise.
And that was
the last time I ever saw her.
The end of Summer...
... was the end of childhood.
A few days later she was arrested.
I was sent to school,
in Germany,
Lucy was sent to relatives,
in Canada.
Just before she was hanged, she wrote me
a letter. I've never shown it to anyone.
I think you should read it.
Merci, Mademoiselle.
"My darling Angela,
"I want you to know that
it is all alright.
"I've never lied to you, and I don't now
when I say that I'm happy,
that I feel a peace
that I've never known before."
It's remarkable.
She was a remarkable person,
and innocent.
- But the letter does not say it explicitly.
- Because it didn't to say it.
Then, how do you think
Amyas Crale died?
Suicide.
- But is that not out of character?
- As you said before,
human nature has an infinite
capacity to surprise.
Then, you can see no other explanation?
- You mean, someone else might have killed him?
- Oui.
I think it unlikely.
But if, for one second,
we consider the possibility, what then...
I would say Philip Blake
might be your man.
Now, that interests me very much,
mademoiselle. May I ask why?
I cannot see what possible motive
he could have.
He was the best friend
of Amyas Crale, n'est-ce pas?
Or were the two men rivals, perhaps, over Elsa?
- Not Elsa.
One night, that Summer,
I got up, to get to the bathroom.
And, as I opened the door,
I saw Caroline coming out
from Philip's bedroom.
She had a look on her face
at the time I didn't really understand.
- But, looking back...
- I got the impression,
from Monsieur Blake,
that always he disliked your sister.
I have, I confess, precious little experience
on the affairs of the heart,
but what other explanation
could there possibly be?
- This could be a disaster.
- You can trust me, Mademoiselle.
♫ (gramophone music- flashback)
It warms my heart
to see you all together again.
Is Lucy joining us?
- This is very good of you, mrs. Spriggs.
- My pleasure, sir.
It is, really.
I'm very proud of you,
my dear.
I wish someone would tell us
the point of all this.
If you will excuse me...
Lady Dittisham, I am delighted
that you could make it.
I hope it's worth it.
God, this place
is falling apart!
- Before we join the others...
- I'd kill for a Martini.
... we might have a little word?
- You don't let up, do you?
- To come straight to the point...
I'm pleased to hear it.
After the trial, did Meredith
Blake show any interest in you at all?
Animals! Stupid
unthinking animals!
What a terrible ordeal
for you, my dear!
What a brave girl you are! Elsa,
I've had special feelings for you
ever since we met, you know?
And now you're all alone in the world...
Do shut up!
- Weren't you surprised?
- Just vaguely nauseated.
- Can I have my Martini now?
- But of course.
Well... what a hoot!
Can't one have a moment's peace?
You were not entirely
honest with me
when we had that little chat
in London.
- Is that so?
- Yes indeed, Monsieur Blake.
On at least one night, during that Summer,
Madame Crale was seen
coming out of your room
at an hour somewhat compromising.
Who told you that?
- It's none of your damn business.
- I am affraid that it is, Monsieur,
if this matter is to be laid to rest.
She thought she might
try it on.
He's going to leave me, I know he is.
I can't bare the thought of being without him.
Philip, Philip...
Sometimes I get so lonely
I feel I'm going mad.
She always thought she could get
what she wanted,
but that didn't wash with me.
I think you better
go back to bed.
So, you see, when I said I didn't
like her, I wasn't telling fibs.
Non.
Merci, Monsieur.
Actually...
It's not quite true.
- Monsieur Blake, are you all-right?
- Everything was such a mess!
Always has been,
ever since we were children.
She was always ready with
some sny remark.
Amyas and I...
... we...
... we were true friends.
She couldn't stand him.
He meant everything to me.
Everything!
Meredith knew, I think.
Caroline suspected.
But nothing she could say
changed anything.
It's Amyas, isn't it? Still Amyas.
You just can't get him out of your head.
Do you have any idea how pathetic you are?
It just made me hate her all the more.
I...
... I trust you keep this to yourself.
Of course.
Not that I care much, anyway.
How kind of you to come.
Do you think you can get on
with the business in hand?
Indeed, Monsieur,
I was about to suggest the very same.
Et alors, where to begin, hmm?
As you know,
it was my purpose to dicover the truth
about the murder of Amyas Crale.
- We all know the truth!
- Yes, indeed, Monsieur Blake,
but sometimes,
what we accept as the truth
may not be the full story,
n'est-ce pas?
And, sometimes,
it may not be true at all.
D'accord. This is what I learned:
that, at no time did Caroline
Crale protest her innocence,
except in a letter to her daughter;
that, in the Dock,
she showed no fear;
that, in a letter to her sister,
she expressed acquiescence to her fate;
and that, in the opinion of everyone...
Pardon, with one exception, most notable,
Caroline Crale was guilty.
- Of course she was!
But it was not for me to accept
the verdict of others.
Non, it was necessary
for me to examine the facts,
and to ensure that
the psycology of this case
accorded itself with them.
There's no doubt whatever that
she had ample motive
and much of the evidence,
it tells against her:
the scent bottle
discovered in her room;
the poison she admitted to steal;
the row with her husband,
where she threatened to kill him.
None of this seems incorrect,
psychologically.
But, then, we come to something
that does not quite ring true.
After Meredith Blake discovers
the poison is missing,
he rows over here to discuss it
with his brother.
On their way up to the house, they overhear
a discussion between Caroline and her husband
on the vexed subject of Angela
being sent away to school.
It's shameful behavior, Amyas!
- You're being so hard on her.
- We'll discuss this after lunch.
- I'll see to her packing.
- That does strike me as odd.
They just had a row most horrific
in which she has threatened to kill him,
and then, a short time later, they are
having an argument relatively trivial
in which Monsieur Crale says
he will see to Angela's packing.
Now, does that not strike you as strange?
Why should he do her packing?
When there is her sister, or the
governess, or the housekeeper?
I did not know Monsieur Crale,
But you know, somehow I can not picture him
folding neatly
the skirts, the blouses, or the underwear.
Another thing that striked as odd:
having just threatened to kill him,
Caroline Crale offers to bring to
her husband a cold beer.
- Dissimulation.
- You think so?
But if she intends to poison him,
wouldn't it be more inteligent to...
What is the word?
"Spike" the supply of beer
that he has on the water garden,
when no-one was about, hmm?
Alors, Caroline Crale brings
to him a beer from the house,
he drinks it, he says,
"Everything tastes foul today", and
after lunch she finds him dead.
- We know all this.
- Oui, oui, bien sûr.
But now, I offer some information
which is new.
After asking Meredith Blake
to call for a doctor,
Mademoiselle Williams
returns to the water garden.
- You actually saw her do that?
- Well, that settles it.
Not necessarilly.
- That is what I saw.
- And only your word for it.
I'm not accustomed
to having my word doubted.
And I do not doubt it,
Mademoiselle Williams.
I believe that what you saw took place
exactly as you say that it did,
and, because of what you saw,
I know that Caroline Crale
was not guilty.
- Well, how the hell did you work that out?
- Do calm down.
I will tell to you. Mademoiselle
Williams saw Caroline Crale
wipe off the fingerprints
from the beer bottle
and impose the prints of her husband
onto it... Onto the bottle, mark.
But the conium was in the glass,
not the bottle.
The police found no traces of it in the bottle.
No conium had ever been in the bottle.
And Caroline Crale, she did not know that .
She, who has poisoned her husband,
did not know how he had been poisoned?
- So, why make it look like suicide?
- Because she knew who was the culprit
and she would do anythining rather
rather then let that person be suspected.
So, who could it be?
There was only one person
whom she would be willing to protect
at all costs.
Mademoiselle Warren, I would like
to read the letter your sister wrote you.
No!
- But, Mademoiselle...
- I realize what you are suggesting
and I deny it utterly. That letter
was meant for my eyes only.
- Aunt Angela, please...
- No!
For my mother's sake.
Please.
Merci, Mademoiselle.
"My darling Angela,
"I want you to know that it is al alright.
"I have never lied to you, and I don't now
when I say that I am happy,
that I feel a peace that I've never
known before." (Caroline's voice)
Don't look back,
and don't grieve for me.
Live your life and succed.
It's all alright, my darling,
it's all alright.
I'm going to Amyas and I'm happy,
and you must be too.
One has to pay one's debts.
"Your loving sister, Caroline."
It is a beautiful letter, non?
And also quite remakable, for it contains
one omission that is most tracking.
There is no protestation of innocence.
- Because it was unnecessary.
- Oui, bien sûr.
Because she thought her sister
knew that she was innocent
for the best of possible reasons!
And her only concern
was to comfort, to reassure, and to advert
of you having to confess.
"It's all alright, my darling,
it's all alright."
She wanted me to be happy,
it's as simple as that.
Yes indeed, and so that the burden
of your guilt may not be too great,
she tells to you,
"One must pay one's debts" .
And now, she has, at last, the chance
to repay you the debt she has to you
for the injury she caused you
all those years before.
And now the trial, the sentence, pff!
Nothing can touch her,
because, finally,
she felt redeemed.
She felt at peace with herself.
And in the light of this,
everything falls into place.
- Now look here, girlie...
- I wish you were dead.
When Angela threw
the paperweight at Amyas Crale,
the memory that haunts her
is brought to life most vividly.
Then, in the next morning, she sees
Angela tempering with the beer...
I'll take it, if you don't mind.
... which she then brings to Amyas.
- Tastes foul.
- Everything's foul today.
- And after lunch,
she finds him dead.
Alors, she is convinced
he has been poisoned,
but who could have done it?
And then, suddenly,
it its her.
The resentment of Angela over the school,
the desaproval of Elsa,
her rage on the night before,
her tempering with the beer.
And she remembers also well
her own violent emotions at that age.
So yes, Angela.
It has to be!
And the one thought
that springs into her mind...
... is how to protect her.
So, she wipes the fingerprints
from the bottle,
puts her husband's there
to make it look like suicíde,
sends Angela out of the country
as soon as possible,
hoping, against hope,
that she does not confess.
But if I'd have done it,
of course I'd have confessed.
I'd never let Caroline
suffer for what I'd done.
- But you did temper with the beer, did you not?
- I can't remember that!
Monsieur Blake, you said that
you heard a noise in the laboratory
in the morning of the murder.
- Yes, just probably a cat.
Or probably not. I would suggest rather,
it was someone who got in through
the sash window
and took something from the shelf.
The valerian!
To put in Amyas' drink!
I remember taking it.
Angela!
- Was it really that day?
- Oui, Mademoiselle.
- This is valerian.
- The one that cats like?
They can't get enough of it.
And it was the description given by Monsieur
Blake which gave to you the idea.
Yes, I remeber getting out some
beer and Caroline...
... catching me before I could put
the stuff in it.
I never connected it
with that particular day.
She thought it was me!
Oh! I didn't kill him.
- I didn't kill him.
- Of course not, my dear.
Can't you see she's telling the truth?
I see it quite clearly,
because I know very well who killed him.
Don't you think
you're milking it a bit, old man?
It is the older story in the world:
two women and one man.
What we have taken for granted
is that the man would leave his wife
for the other woman.
But I would like to suggest here now
is that he had no intention of doing
anything of that kind.
After all, the women he had
fallen in love with in the past
never expected too much from him,
but this time it was different.
She was just a girl,
who saw the world in black and white.
She had the passion for him,
and so assumed he had for her.
She assumed, without question,
it was for life,
so, naturally, he would leave his wife.
- He said he would.
- Well, a little white lie, perhaps.
All he really wanted
was to finish the painting,
and nothing could be allowed to stand
in the way. And when Elsa Greer
let the cat from the bag,
he was furious,
but he was not concerned unduly.
After all, Caroline had only
to put up with things for a few days longer,
then he would tell her the truth, and
she would believe him, as so often before.
And Elsa Greer? She would get over it
soon enough.
But by that last evening, I believe that
he was getting worried
that Caroline Crale was taking things
more seriously than usual.
And, by the following morning,
I think he had decided to come clean.
You're the only woman in my life, Carol.
You always were, you always will be,.
You know that.
She is nothing to me. Nothing.
She was, yes. She knocked me for six
to start with, but now is gone.
It's over. I swear to God.
She's just a kid.
A passing fancy, that's all.
You and your women!
Someday I'll kill you, Amyas.
- Don't be an idiot.
- I swear to God I will!
What he did not know
was that Elsa Greer
had overheard every word.
And the account that she gave to me
of the conversation was not the true one.
You're very sure of yourself,
aren't you, Monsieur Poirot?
Of this, Lady Dittisham, yes, I am.
When Amyas Crale came down
and said he wanted to get on,
you said you had to go and change.
Which you did... eventually.
I wonder you'd realized how angry
was Madame Crale with her husband
for his treatment of you?
- How very touching.
When Philip Blake encountered her
coming out of the library...
- Good morning.
- It's too cruel, too cruel.
... it was of you she was thinking.
I wonder what she would have thought
had she known that,
at that very moment,
you were in her room
preparing to murder her husband
and put the blame on her?
You see, something else
that I am sure of, Lady Dittisham,
is that in the laboratory,
in the previous afternoon,
you would have seen Caroline Crale
steel the poison.
Monsieur Blake had his back
to the room when he was talking to you,
so, it was perfectly possible
for you to see her,
the only person who could do so.
Sorry, Merri. It's such a fascinating
colection...
And once you had the poison,
you went to join Amyas in the garden,
poured him some beer...
To my Mona Lisa.
... and he tossed it back,
in his usual manner.
My darling Amyas.
As he painted, you watched
and watched,
waiting for the poison to take its efect.
A short time later,
you went to fetch a shawl and Caroline Crale
again took the opportunity...
... to confront her husband
on your behalf.
It's shameful, your behavior, Amyas!
You're being too hard on her.
For God's sake! It's all settled.
I'll send her packing.
And it was this that the Blake brothers
misheard, on their way up from the jetty.
An error that is understandable,
n'est-ce pas?
You, then,
returned with a shawl,
and then Caroline Crale,
she plates straight into your hands,
for she brought to her husband
a bottle of cold beer.
It tastes foul!
Everything tastes foul today.
"Everything tastes foul today" ,
which suggests that he had tasted
something else unpleasant
before the beer that Caroline Crale
had brought to him.
And so, you sat, and posed,
and chatted, and waved
to Meredith Blake.
You played your part
beautifully!
Bloody rheumatism!
... while Amyas Crale painted on, and on,
until his limbs failed,
and his speech thickened,
and he layed sprawled on the bench,
helpless, with his mind still clear!
And when Meredith Blake appeared
from the shadowy path onto the sunny garden,
he could not see clearly.
Only his friend
turning slowly around,
unable to covey the fact that he was
in the grip of a paralysis that was fatal.
En route to the house,
you crushed the pipet on the foot,
the traces of which
the police were to find.
And then went to lunch,
leaving Amyas Crale
to his fate.
Thank you, Monsieur Poirot.
Mademoiselle.
Amyas dead,
Caroline hanged...
After all these years...
After all these years!
You're very clever, aren't you?
I hope you don't expect me to confess.
So, what are you going to do?
I shall do what I can to induce
the appropriate authorities
to grant to Caroline Crale
a postumous free pardon.
And me?
What're you going to do about me?
I shall lay my conclusions
before the necessary people.
If they decide there is
a case against you, they may act.
But, it is my opinion...
... that the evidence
is not suficient.
Inferences only, not facts.
Moreover, I believe they won't be
anxious to proceed against a...
... person in your position.
When I saw Caroline take the conium,
I thought she meant to kill herself.
But in the next morning, when I
overheard them talking about me, I...
I loved him...
... and he was just stringing me along.
And she felt sorry for me.
I watched him die, Monsieur Poirot.
And I never felt more alive,
but what I didn't understand
was that I was killing myself.
It was as if they hadn't died at all,
but I had.
I died, Monsieur Poirot.
Elsa!
Come on then, Lucy.
Shoot me. You know you want to.
Do not listen to her, Mademoiselle.
That's right.
Just pull the trigger.
If you do, she will have won.
Come on, do it.
- You're not affraid, are you?
- If you kill her, you kill yourself.
Just one little squeeze,
that's all it takes.
Spare her, Mademoiselle,
and justice may still be done.
Lucy, shoot me!