"Gentlemen of the jury,
"we have presented
copious, clear evidence
"that Elinor Carlisle,
who stands before you,
"is a vicious, multiple murderess
"and one who shows not
the slightest feeling of remorse.
No remorse.
That's right.
I feel nothing.
Why should I?
When you have wanted someone dead,
longed for it,
planned it
and watched
'til you see
the last flicker of life in the eyes...
We ask you now to contemplate
the full horror
of the second cold-blooded
murder,
wickedly
planned and executed
on a hot afternoon
at Hunterbury.
The deadly salmon paste
so thickly spread...
He is trying to see just exactly
why I did it,
what I felt...
All of it seems
so inevitable now,
as if it began
years and years ago.
And yet,
it was only last summer.
The beginning.
The beginning seemed happy.
- Are the roses alright?
- They're lovely.
Good. I try to be
a respectable fiancé.
And you are!
Soon, even theses extended
lunch hours will be respectable.
So, if I go to France
for two weeks,
you can meet me in "Le Tourquet".
Ma maman will be back than.
It'll be all very respectible
and we'll be back for
Astor's Autumn Ball.
How about it?
Elinor?
Oh, it sounds perfect.
But there's something else
on your mind, isn't there?
Oh Roddy, you know me so well.
Yes. Something arrived this morning.
It's stupid, but I can't take it
out of my mind.
I'm intrigued...
Is it a bill?
After all, it's the height of Summer
when the fairies dance
"To warn you: Someone's sucking up
to your aunt in Hunterbury
"so you and your fiancé
get cut out of the will.
"The person may seem as white
as snow,
"but wants to cheat you both and the old lady
will die with another stroke any day."
God...
It can't be true. It's just someone
out to cause trouble.
Yes, you're probably right.
It was quite a shock, though.
We haven't been down there this month.
- Yes, we should go.
- Because of this?
No, not just this...
You care for her. So do I.
But the house matters.
Think of the summers
we spent there as children.
She always said she wanted
one of us to have it.
Which means both of us,
now that we're engaged.
So, what in Heaven's name is wrong
with us making sure?
- Oh, Roddy! I'd love to go there.
- Then it's settled .
I decided to bring the letter, after all.
I want to show it to Dr. Lord.
You sure that's wise?
Yes. If anyone knows
who sent it, he would.
But, darling, it's so poisonous.
Oh well, if you must.
I still say you should burn it.
Do you know what I'd like?
Sometime when we're married
and living here together,
we send all the servants away
and we'll exactly what we want.
Oh, yes? And what about your meals?
We'll eat with our fingers
by the fire.
We won't have anybody
to disturb us.
Just you and me
and the wind in the trees.
Where is Ms. Bishop?
Somewhere. The hall
was always so dark.
Good Lord...
I never did get used to this lift.
It's a shame she doesn't use it now.
She doesn't even come out
of her room anymore.
Miss Carlisle, Mr. Winter...
I'm so sorry.
The nurses are coping well, though
her last stroke did take your aunt
so badly.
And look, here's another great help.
She's just back from her
studies in Germany.
You must both remember Mary,
the gardener's daughter.
Hello, Elinor, Roddy...
Hello, Mary. Well, it's been a while...
Hello, Miss Carlisle, Mr. Winter...
How good to see you.
Well, she's not so bad today.
But she may be asleep, now.
- Would you like to go in?
- Yes, I think so.
Would you excuse us, please.
Thank you, nurse Hopkins.
- Would you like some tea?
- Oh, no thank you. I don't drink tea.
- Mr. Winter?
- Yes, please.
Elinor!
Aunt Laura!
I thought you were sleeping.
No, lying here like a captive,
as usual.
"Come away, death, and in
the sad cypress let me be laid."
Morbid as ever.
It gets me through.
Roddy! How lovely!
I am so pleased you are engaged.
Aan I know your parents
would have been too.
About time, I thought.
It's wonderful to see you, aunt Laura.
- You look fine.
- No, I don't.
Roddy, I'm quite sure you need
some refreshment.
And I want to have a little talk
with your bride-to-be.
Fine. I'll look in on you later.
But don't go pulling her of me
or I'll make a point of moving in here
wailing from your battlements.
Did you see Mary?
Yes. I was astonished.
When did she get back?
A few weeks ago.
I'm sure I told you.
Isn't she beautiful?
I am so glad she has
come back from Germany.
She has been very good to me.
And I am so pleased
that you and Roddy are together.
You do care for him?
Of course I do.
- Enough and not too much?
- What?
It's just something we used to say.
You should never care
too much for a man.
Aunt Laura, tell me
something, honestly.
Do you think love is ever
a happy thing?
Oh, Elinor! Perhaps it always brings
more sorrow than joy.
But who could do without it?
Anyone who has never really loved,
hasn't lived.
And now Miss Carlisle's here
with her fiancé.
Miss Carlisle is still in there
with her now.
- Miss Carlisle, the niece?
- Exactly.
Never was that sure about her.
No?
Tries too hard.
And they call them
"kissing cousins" in "The Tatler".
But she's lucky to have caught him
and she knows it.
Behind the eyes,
she's nervous as a kitten.
I remember I was dripping in sweat.
I could hardly hold on.
But you did. You got
right to the top, didn't you?
I think you must've
got to your grip.
I couldn't help it. My hands
were slipping with the perspiration.
And then you fell at my feet laughing.
Oh! Hello, Elinor. We were just
remembering the old times.
Of course. We'll have
lots to talk about.
There's tea in the dining toom.
Now, look here, doctor, I've
said this before.
In any civilized country,
I'd just say I wanted to end it,
and you would finish me off
with some nice painless drug.
Well, I am not sure
if I wish to be hanged just yet.
Not now, you're doing so well.
Leave me all your money
and I might reconsider, if you like.
Boo humbug...
And who were you looking at?
Hum... your niece.
Elinor?
That reminds me,
she wants to see you before you go.
So, what do tou think of her, hey?
She is, uh... she's very impressive.
Yes... Very impressive...
Yes, she is.
You know, you ought to
get married, doctor.
I'm sorry. I just couldn't think
of anyone else to take on confidence.
No, no... I'm flattered.
But you're right, this is a horrible thing.
I supose it must be
someone in the village.
But who could the letter be referring to?
Who has access to our aunt
other than the nurses?
Well, Ted Horlick, the gardiner,
he helps to carry the oxygen.
Ms. Bishop goes in, the vicar, myself...
Mary Gerrard is there a lot, of course.
Nurse O'Brien lives in
and nurse Hopkins
comes everyday.
I suppose Mary is the newest here.
Can somebody be jealous of her?
Does she have a suiter?
I don't think so,
though Ted Horlick always
did have a soft spot for her.
It's probably nothing to do with her!
I'm sorry, somehow a thing like this
just plays on your nerves.
Just the idea of having someone
spying and trying to cause bad feelings...
Yes, it's probably best forgotten.
You have been kind,
but it's idiotic from me
asking you to play detective.
Shall we just burn it?
No, no. Nobody need to play detective.
I know a real one,
his name is Poirot.
He's staying here a few days
preparing evidence
for a trial in Manbury.
He's horribly bored. And I'm sure
he'd leap at the chance of some diversion.
He has some peculiarities,
like his many herbal teas.
He's charming and very,
very discreet.
Mon ami...
A doctor who bares a message
is always a sight most worrying.
I hope it isn't from none
of my physicians.
Of course not, Poirot.
How are you?
You settled in alright?
Are you any more comfortable?
Well, for some maybe.
As for me, well, I have my work.
What pleasure is there for me in the
evidence of a case I solved one year since?
None. I am, as you say,
bored to the tears.
Well, perhaps I can help. You see,
a lady, whom I admire a good deal
has come to me with a problem:
an anonimous letter.
You mean I'll maybe
a little exercise at last?
Well, don't get too excited,
I'm sure it's trivial.
There goes Ted Horlick
with Mary Gerrard.
She is in great favour
to Hunterbury House.
This letter is about that household.
It's a grand film. It's with
Garbo and it's set in Paris.
I'm sorry, Ted, I've already said no.
- You've set your eyes in someone else?
- No. Of course not. I'm sorry.
- Bon, enter if you please.
- Thank you.
The writer of this
has been very careful.
That interests you?
Oh, oui! Regard the pressure
on the page.
Now regard the words.
There is malice here, or, just as
concearning, the pretense of malice.
And I don't believe for one moment
that the writer of this letter
wishes to protect the interests
of Elinor Carlisle.
Unless, of course, Elinor Carlisle
wrote this herself.
That's a strange suggestion, Poirot.
I could see how upset she was.
Strange for you, maybe.
But once I found your strategy
of pawns most strange
and you almost put me in check.
- That was a long time ago.
To say the truth,
when you came here,
I thought this letter
would be a thing just trivial.
And yet, the care of its construction,
the words, even the design,
tell to me it is not the case.
Of course it may lead to nothing.
So, why? Why do I sense
that the outlook may be dark?
- Miss Carlisle.
- Mrs. Bishop.
Have you seen Mr. Winter?
No, but I don't think he's upstairs.
The garden, maybe?
Oh, yes, of course. Thank you.
Aye, it's nice enough, Mary dear,
but I'm sure you can do better.
Yes, with your education
especially.
Now, let us see
what your aunt sent.
Oh, I'm so sorry,
I was looking for Mr. Winter.
- I haven't seen him. Have you, Mary?
- No, I've just come back from the post-office.
This is from my aunt Mary,
New Zealand, my mother's sister.
I was named after her, so she
always sends me things.
That is kind.
Yes. She emigrated before I was born.
And now she's the only family I have left.
What a lovely thing.
Yes, it is. I am sorry
to interrupt you.
You show it to Mrs. Welman.
You know, she's been so kind to me.
Only today she was saying
she might help me in the future.
Just like she did with my schooling.
Well, I guess I'll se on aunt Laura
before I go to bed.
Of course. I'll wait in here and then
I can always come and tuck you in.
Perhaps not tonight. Ms. Bishop may be
doing her rounds. There's time enough.
All right. I'll let you rest tonight.
So... How did you like
meeting Mary again?
What? Oh yes! She's...
she's a sweet girl.
Nighty night.
What were you doing?
Elinor... I was just
making her more comfortable.
Yes, of course. Good night.
Good night.
Elinor Carlisle,
this is Hercule Poirot.
- Monsieur Poirot.
- Mademoiselle Carlisle.
This is my fiancé, Mr. Winter.
- Monsieur Winter...
- How do you do?
- We are so grateful for you to come.
- Oh please, not at all.
It is most kind of you to invite me.
We are honoured. The Cartwright trial
has been most exciting.
Indeed, for me hélas!, it is like eating
the same meal three times a day.
Monsieur Poirot,
this is Mary Gerrard.
Whose late father looked after the garden
here. She has just returned from Europe.
Mademoiselle Gerrard.
I'm very glad to meet you,
Monsieur Poirot.
Oh, I'll take a salmon, thank you.
Mademoiselle Gerrard, may I
ask you where in Europe?
Germany. I was staying with a family
near Freiburg.
Ah, the Black Forrest...
It's a beautiful country.
Do you know, I think the nacional-socialists
are doing a good job over there.
I sometimes wish we had
politicians like that here.
I think, monsieur, that
you are most fortunate you do not.
Do you?
It's much to pleasant an occasion
for european politics.
- May I have a word, Roddy?
- Excuse me.
So, Monsieur Poirot,
do you think my letter is important?
I can not yet
give to you an answer.
But to me, everything is important
until it proves otherwise,
even the strategies of chess
of my friend Dr. Lord.
- Does he ever win?
- Non, but one time he came quite close.
Non non, he has a mind
truly wonderful for the game.
That is my aunt, Monsieur Poirot.
She's too ill
to join us, I'm affraid.
I realize its much too soon to say
who may have written the letter.
But I know Dr. Lord
has told you about our household.
So, do you have any suspicions
about whom it refers to?
The intruder?
There's no need for me to suspect.
The writer has made it quite obvious.
How?
Alors  the phrase " white as snow"
is most odd, yes?
But certainly it is used deliberately.
So, tell to me. mademoiselle, who was it
who was it that had a little lamb
whose fleece was white as snow?
Mary.
Oui.
Mrs. Welman, are you all right?
Oh dear, you're not yourself.
Stay calm. You've had another turn.
I'll call the doctor.
Please, Lewis...
I need to see
the photograph of Lewis.
Not this again...
Please, I can't open your private things.
I must get the doctor.
Mrs. Welman, you're ill.
I must send for the doctor now, I must!
It's all right, it's all right, get calm.
Don't excite yourself.
You want somebody to come?
Your lawyer? You want
your lawyer to come?
Provision? You want to change
something in your will?
Related to Mary?
Mary Gerrard?
I'll call the lawyers.
Seddon shall be here directly.
- Please don't worry about it.
- Rest now, It will be done.
May I go in?
Yes, of course.
The doctor's in there.
I see... Yes...
Well, thank you. I'll meet him
here tomorrow. Goodbye.
Seddon can't be here until tomorrow.
Is that all right?
Yes, yes I think so. She's had another stroke,
But I'm sure she has a little time yet.
I've seen some improvements
since last night.
Have you lost something, dear?
It's that sarcoma in the village
Eliza Rykin.
I was sure I had
put her tube of morphine here
for tomorrow.
But somehow it's gone.
The only place where I've put my bag
down was out there, in the corredor.
Oh, why don't you look again, dear?
Nobody here would take it.
No, it's gone.
Now that your work is done,
I thought you'd be singing, Poirot.
I am content to return to London,
mon ami,
but I do not like
the unfinished business.
- The letter!
- Oui
Well, perhaps you wanted it
to be more than it was.
I promise you, they have
other things to think about now.
- Yes?
- Ordinary things.
Ah! Even so, I return this letter
with reluctance
and only because it is not
my property.
Ask them to keep it safe,
if you please.
- And keep me informed of any developments.
- Oh, I'm sure there'll be none.
- Of course.
- Bon.
There's no sense in hanging on to it.
Even your detective didn't get anywhere.
But, Roddy he asked us to keep it safe.
Well, no doubt to cover his own failure.
He's gone now and we have
more important things to think about.
Thank God the doctor said
she would make out of this.
Shouldn't be too bloomy,
she wouldn't want that.
No. It's just seeing her like this...
I'm so tired, Roddy.
I think I'll go to bed early.
What're you going to do?
I'll let you sleep.
You look worn-in.
I'll just play some billiard
or sometin' before I go up.
Elinor, nurse Hopkins
is happy to stay tonight
and take for nurse O'Brien.
But she woud like a word.
Oh, thank you, Mary.
Are you off home now, or...
- I'd really like to stay.
- Of course, if you want to stay close by
you could use the room at the end.
- My aunt would like that.
- Thank you.
Good night.
But I don't... I don't know...
Miss Carlisle!
Miss Carlisle,
Mrs. Welman's been taken very bad.
The doctor was called.
You must come at once.
I'm coming.
I'm very sorry.
Would it have been painful?
No, no absolutely not.
Sometimes you have a sudden relapse
like that. It's very quick.
And in it's way is a mercy.
You must tak any consolation
any consolation you can from that.
I'm so sorry, Elinor.
But thank God for it, I say,
I couldn't have borne seeing her
lingering in the state she was tonight.
You... saw her tonight?
What? Oh, yes...
I left the cards and looked in briefly
while the nurse was getting tea.
She was lying there, breathing so hard.
I hated seeing her like that.
It's probably why
I've felt so strange all evening.
I know I wasn't really myself.
No?
You should go to bed. I won't
come in and disturb you. Not tonight.
Good night, Roddy.
- I'll have the "Times", if you please.
- Certainly, sir.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you, sir.
The British Library,
if you please.
"Laura Welman died suddenly
at her hone in Hunterbury House
" on September 16th 1937.
Funeral Hunterbury church
" September 21. 'The nobel strain
a noble day doth make'."
... dust to dust.
In the sure and certain hope of
the ressurrection to eternal life. Amen.
You came back just because of this?
It was quite sudden. I was wrongly
optimistic in my diagnose.
Sometimes they change
quickly.
She had another stroke
that affected her very badly.
So - you see,
the letter, it was correct.
It said that she would die
after another stroke.
Yes, that's true, but given the severity
of the first stroke, it wasn't remarkable.
Poirot, I think you may be
overreacting.
There was no murder.
Please be honest with me. In your profession
as a doctor, this is your true opinion?
Yes, it is. And I have to ask you
to honour it as a friend.
So you give to me no choice?
- I don't want to see people upset.
- Bon.
- When will you go back?
- I'm not going back.
I intend to stay a little.
And perhaps we can play some chess...
Well, now! We're nearly all down here.
What a terrible shame they didn't offer
the village a cup of tea.
It's not the same without it.
Maybe, but Miss Carlisle
didn't look no good at all.
I doubt that she had the strenght.
Strenght enough
to hear the will, though.
The lawyer is down there with her, now.
And Mrs. Welman would've made sure
there was refreshment after
a funeral. Hear my words.
Oh, I meant to ask you, dear.
Did you find that tube
of morfine when you went home?
No, I did not. I don't understand it.
But there were some papers and things
I threw out, it may have been there.
That must have been it. I wouldn't worry
about it anymore if I were you, dear.
Well, time to say goodbye.
Again, I'm very sorry for what happened,
Miss Carlisle, Mr. Winter.
I can't degree the pity she didn't
summon me earlier.
Mr. Seddon, it's perfectly obvious
she wanted to alter her will.
It's clear to everyone. She mentioned
Mary and she wanted to change it.
Miss Carlisle, I can assure you of one thing.
You're wrong in that assumption.
There could be no change as such,
you see, your aunt made no will.
- What?
- But that's extraordinary!
Not as extraordinary as
you might think, Mr. Winter.
People are often supersticious.
They think if they make
a will, they die.
So they put it off.
Didn't you reason with her?
Frequently. But she
said all the usual things,
that she didn't intend to die just yet.
It's just human nature, I'm affraid.
People go on avoiding a thing
in her personal life which is distasteful.
So, the upshot is very simple.
Since your aunt died
with no bequests,
no will, no settlements or trusts,
everything, including this house,
goes to her next of kin,
which, of course, is you,
her niece, Elinor Carlisle.
Everything?
Well, apart from her death duties,
the state will still be substantial.
No, Elinor, you should have it all.
I don't want you to think otherwise.
It's your right.
But Roddy, we said it didn't matter
who was left the money,
since we were to be married.
Remember?
Yes.
But... are we?
I thought that was the idea,
of course if you have other plans, now...
Roddy, can't you be honest?
Sorry, I don't know
what's happened to me.
I do. It's Mary, isn't it?
I saw you.
God, I...
Something happened
when I arrived here,
when we were at the garden,
I don't know what.
Isn't id obvious? Every time you
look at her, I see it in your face.
I didn't want to feel like this.
I was quite happy.
This upset all decent,
reasonable things.
Love isn't reasonable.
You better take this back, Roddy.
Will she marry you?
I don't know.
Well, give it time.
Take the fortnight in France.
Clear your head. If you still
feel the same after you're back,
then that's the time to pursue it.
I didn't deserve you.
Even as a friend.
Sometimes, it's all like a dream.
As if I may wake up
and see that she isn't there.
But she is there!
Damn you, Mary!
Ah! Mary... Sit down, please.
Thank you.
So, what are your plans now?
Do you intend to go away?
Not directly. I still have
to clear out my parents' things
from the lodge house.
That'll take me a few days.
I've been putting it off
ever since I got back.
As you know, Mary, my aunt
always took a great interest in you.
Yes, she was very kind.
You'd be aware that she made no will.
I have thought about that a good deal
and it seemed to me that, if she had lived,
she would have wanted to make
several legacies.
Of course I've made provision
to the servants.
But you don't quite come
into that class.
I am sure she would have wanted
to make some contribution for your future,
therefore, I'm arranging, as soon as
the probation is granted,
to advance you 7000 pounds,
that sum to be yours, to do
absolutely as you please.
Thank you.
It was quite a surprise
that she left no will.
But then, many people don't...
Yes, I only made one myself this year.
A will?
Nurse O'Brien thinks
everyone should.
I have my aunt in New Zealand.
So I named her.
You've been so kind.
It was my aunt's wish.
Or that's what I think.
Thank you.
- Bonjour, Mademoiselle Gerrard.
- Hello.
You're in a hurry?
I just had some good news,
now, I'm on my way to meet someone.
I'm very pleased for you, Mlle.
Mademoiselle, is it your intention
to remain in the village?
I'm staying here for now.
Yes, yes of course.
Pardon. I will not detain you further.
Mademoiselle, please be careful,
as you go.
Of course.
That's a great piece of luck for you, Mary.
It was good of Miss Carlisle to do the right thing.
She didn't... Well, she didn't look
very pleased about it.
Hardly surprising, after what happened
between you and Mr. Winter, is it, dear?
That's hardly our business.
Sorry dear, but all
village must be talking about it.
I didn't lead him on.
But has you made you an offer?
The truth is... he's indicated.
There you are, now.
Isn't that romantic?
Excuse me.
I do hope it's alright.
You wonder if he won't hurt her in the end?
I know. And that family in the house
hasn't always been lucky in love.
Mademoiselle Carlisle,
do you permit that I join you?
Yes, of course.
I wish to speak to you
of your anonymous letter.
I do not yet know who wrote it.
- Oh! The letter...
- Oui.
So much has happened
I'd quite forgotten.
I'm affraid, Mr. Poirot,
the letter is destroyed.
It doesn't matter who sent it now.
We'll never know anyway.
Mlle. Carlisle, it is no matter if the letter
is destroyed. It is in here.
And I said I did not yet know.
I did not say never.
Please, extend me the cortesy of
having some confidence in my skills.
I'm sorry, Monsieur Poirot.
The truth is I'm a little distracted.
I'm sure you've heard that
my engagement has ended.
I'm sure all village is talking about it.
Yes, I was very sorry to hear it.
If you permit, mademoiselle,
I extend to you my utmost simpathy.
I can understand the ache of the heart.
It is a place very lonely.
Thank you.
It is certainly hard when
the accident of another person's return,
another person's beauty,
suddenly destroys your life.
D'accord. But then a man
who is swayed by such things
is not likely to be constant,
is that not so?
No, that is not so. It's only her.
Nobody else could've changed him, nobody!
Mary has destroyed everything,
and I can't help it, but I just wish...
I wish so much...
... that she was dead.
Come on, Poirot. Drink it.
You see, it troubles you also, my dear
doctor. That the glass that is poured
it is perfect in every way
and yet I choose not to drink it.
I wait. And this troubles you.
What are you thinking?
About action that is uncompleted.
Action that is suspended,
like this:
pouring without drinking.
And yet, surely, once it is poured,
it will be drunk. But non...
And it is the same here.
For crime it can be like this, also.
You questioned me for
staying here.
But sometimes, as in
the case of your letter, I see a pattern.
I see a color.
I sense in my heart
the inevitability
and yet, what can I, Poirot, do?
Nothing.
For the glass, it's
on the table, waiting.
Waiting for someone to drink.
Me?
The cook and the maids
have taken a week, as you asked them,
but I don't require time off.
And you shouldn't be alone
in the house. It's not right.
Mrs. Bishop, I just want to go quietly
through my aunt's things.
I don't need anyone, you see.
I'm almost certainly going to sell.
The other servants wondered
if that would be the case.
- Naturally, we had hoped...
- Yes...
I had hoped, too.
Miss Carlisle, what can I do for you?
I wanted some sandwich paste, Mr. Turner.
Of course. Now, what would you like?
Salmon, crab and shrimp,
ham and tongue?
You know, in spite of the names,
I always think their taste is rather alike.
Hmm, in a way... But, of course,
they're tasty. Very tasty.
I want the salmon,
and crab and shrimp.
People used to be rather affraid
of eating fish paste, didn't they?
Well, there have been cases
of ptomaine poisoning.
I can assure you, Miss Carlisle,
this is an excellent brand.
I've never had a single complaint.
Of course, I didn't mean
anything. Thank you.
We best hurry, Mary.
Miss Carlisle is expecting us
for lunch.
All right.
That's last of the living room here.
What a tangle...
Have you come across
any old gardiner gloves?
Hold on.
Hello?
Sorry. Did I give you a fright?
I was just getting my other appron.
Of course.
I'm making sandwiches.
I saw Mr. Winter in the village.
Is he back again so soon?
What? No, Roddy is not here.
He's still abroad.
Well, it certainly looked like him.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Yes...
I'm sorry' there seems to be
rather a lot of flies around.
The salmon is for you, Mary.
It's the nearest.
Thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry. The others
are crab and shrimp.
Thank you.
I meant to get some coffe,
but I quite forgot in the end.
Well, if there's tea, I can make some.
Oh, yes. Not for me, but... please.
♪ Polly put the kettle on ♪
Remember we used to sing that
when we were children?
Yes, I do.
It is a pitty, isn't it?
We can never go back.
Here we are.
It's nice and strong.
- Here we are, Mary.
- Thank you.
This was very thoughtful
of you, Miss Carlisle.
It's a nuisance having to break off
and go into the village for lunch.
Are you all right, Mary?
Just the sandwich was rather bitter.
I hope the paste was all right.
Mine is all right.
Will you have some more tea?
Are you sure you won't have
a cup, Miss Carlisle?
No, thank you.
Then I'll just go and
turn off the kettle.
I left in on, in case we wanted
to fill the pot up again.
Mary?
Yes?
Nothing.
I thought I saw a man, outside.
Is there someone here?
No. Only Ted.
It wasn't him.
It's quite hot in here.
Yes, the place heads south.
I tidied up the other plates.
Let me finish these.
Thank you. Did you hurt yourself?
No, it was the rose treaders.
It's quite a jungle there.
I might ask Ted
to help us.
Are you all right, Miss Carlisle?
You're not looking quite the thing.
Well, I-- I just want
all this clearing done.
I'll be up, when I'm finished
down here.
So, it's Nellie and Ms. Markinson
for these.
And that poor creature at Ivy Cottage
could have some of the night things.
This will be a godsend to them.
I think I'll take them there myself,
while Mary gets on with the lodge.
She's gone back there, has she?
Mary? No, I left her in the library.
But that was ages ago.
What's she been doing?
Mary?
She's fallen asleep.
Come on, my girl.Wake up.
Mary?
I'll have to call
Dr. Lord this moment.
- What's the matter?
- The matter?
This girl is near death.
I think she's been poisoned.
You have heard?
That Elinor Carlisle
has been charged with murder? Yes.
- There's something I need to tell you.
- This way.
Ah, Poirot! Have a look at this.
We found it yesterday, just here,
where the sandwiches were made.
We can't find any more, but it's been
identified as part
of a label for morfine.
They shared the tea,
so it must be
the sandwiches.
Are you aware that a file of morphine
disappeared from this house?
What?
Oui.Dr. Lord here just told me
of it. It was in the bag of the nurse.
I'm sure the nurses
will confirm it.
So Miss Carlisle had the ample
oportunity to take it and use it.
And her motive is clear. She was destroyed,
her fiancé had abandoned her for the deceased.
Of course, there are
some difficulties.
Like the fact they all ate
the sandwiches.
It is scarcely a difficulty
if you read the statements.
Yes, they all ate the sandwiches. But
the poison, it only needed to be in one.
And the favorite of Mary Gerrard,
as Elinor Carlisle herself testifies,
it was the salmon.
- That's how it was done.
Then there's your anonymous letter,
that doesn't really fit.
Why not? Let us supose
that Elinor Carlisle was most anxious
about the return of Mary Gerrard,
for there is much talk of her beauty
and she knows that her fiancé and Mary
were close in the past.
And that they were bound
to meet together here.
So, Elinor Carlisle herself
writes the anonymous letter
hoping to turn him
against Mary.
She wishes him to think that
she's a girl... (what--?) out for
what she can get.
But that does not work, she loses him.
And so she is driven
to a crime far more desperate.
But how could she hope
to get away wih it?
My dear doctor, I am describing
a crime of passion!
Poirot, Poirot, how could you do that?
How could you build a case
against Elinor Carlisle?
She's not a murderer!
- How can you be so certain?
- You saw her qualities.
- And I also saw her pain.
- She's not capable of it.
On the contrary.
She's more than capable.
That man in there
has no idea of the woman.
My dear doctor,
do you suppose I was advancing the case
just to help him?
Given the facts that I see here,
any prosecuting counsel
any idiot of a magistrate would come
to the conclusions I have, just like that!
And I think that it is fair
to say that you are partial.
I don't deny it, but she didn't do this.
Please, I'm beging you,
help me find the truth.
My dear doctor,
you asked for my help,
but I do not not think
you have been completely honest with me.
I still have my suspicions
about the death of Laura Welman.
And I'm going to ask the Police
to exhume her body.
And so, I ask you again,
to tell me truthfully:
What will they find?
I don't know.
But possibly morphine...
Mon Dieu!
I do not understand you.
You told to me otherwise. You made me
hold back. As a friend, you said.
Poirot, please... I never dreamt
of such a thing.
I thought it was probably natural,
but there was another possibility.
I was aware that she might have
taken the drug herself.
- You see, she often talked of it.
- So you were playing the merciful doctor, uh?
As I said, she talked of it.
Under such circunstances,
I didn't wish to cause a scandal
by insisting on an autopsy.
However, I must insist that
you are now completely honest with me.
You did not giver her the drug
at her request?
I swear to you I didn't.
I told her myself I had no wish
to be hanged, I wouldn't do it.
Very well.
All the same, I wish you had told to me
you had those suspicions.
Because if you are right,
it can be worse now to Elinor Carlisle
than even I could have thought.
So, you do not wish to talk?
I made a statement.
I have nothing else to say.
Mademoiselle Carlisle,
you are aware of how your silence,
it will be constued?
It is no matter.
It's such a shock, I can tell you.
- Now, we'll have some tea.
- Merci.
Like I told the Police,
Monsieur Poirot,
Miss Carlisle was so strange,
very strange in her manner.
I'd thought it for days, but
that afternoon she was downright odd.
Talking as if didn't know
what she was saying
her eyes so bright and queer.
And you said that she looked guilty?
Oh, yes!She was trembling, before and afterwards.
It was as if she'd been caught out.
And those sandwiches that she made,
did they look the same?
They were not on different bread?
No. Definitely not, white bread,
looked very much the same.
But Mary had the salmon
and we had the crab.
When I think of how poor
Mary was when we found her...
She was one of the most
beautiful girls I ever saw, Mr. Poirot.
And not stuck-up,
as she could have been.
The old lady had taken
a tremendous fancy to her.
Suprising, perhaps?
Oh, that depends. Might be
quite natural in one way.
And surely does an elderly person
good to have a young face about.
I see.
And there's nothing else?
Nothing else at all, that
you can tell to me about Mary Gerrard?
I don't know of anything.
No, Mary was not poisoned
before she came here.
How could she have walked
from the lodge?
Non... Without doubt
she was poisoned in this room.
But she and nurse Hopkins
shared the tea, so...
It must have been in the sandwiches.
But Poirot, somebody could easily have
entered in here and tempered with them.
There was a figure in the garden, out there.
Perhaps somebody from Mary's past.
Or, what is more likely,
someone we know.
I made a statemen to the Policemen, Mr. Poirot.
I wasn't around this side of the house
at all, that day.
I was up, near the road.
- Did you see a figure?
- No...
But I d-- I did see a car. Hum, parked
on the road, early in the afternoon.
And did you recognise the car?
N-- no, I don't think so.
I think it was green.
I just can't  believe anyone
would do such a thing.
And certainly not Miss Carlisle.
Tell me, Monsieur Horlick,
you were fond of Mary, were you not?
Everyone knows that.
Wasn't the same,
when she came back from abroad.
But did she have any enemies?
Not that I know.
She was always a bit different,
but-- people liked her.
Then, after she came back,
nobody knew her so well.
Why is that?
She was just changed.
Not stuck-up exactly, just...
not one of us anymore.
This is for Mary.
"But she is in her grave.
And ! the difference to me."
Wordsworth. I read him much.
This poem expresses perhaps
what you feel?
Yes, expresses widely now
what I feel. If you'd to bring it up.
Pardon. Please do forgive me,
Monsieur Winter.
There are certain things
one should not say,
but, nevetheless,
a detective is forced to say.
Or to ask about
the feelings of people.
Well, if it helps Elinor, Poirot,
ask what you want.
Merci.
You returned home early
from France, I believe?
You were seen here
on the day of the murder.
Yes, all right, I did come back,
but I didn't want Elinor to know.
You see, I decided
to ask Mary to marry me.
- And you saw her?
- No, I didn't.
You see, she wasn't expecting me,
so I decided to wait.
Certainly wasn't goin' to
barge into Hunterbury.
I waited here,
close to Mary's lodgings.
And, of course, Mary
she never came.
I saw an ambulance,
Police cars.
People were talking
and I've heard what they said.
Couldn't face anyone,
so I took a train back into town
and waited for news.
Then I learned she was dead.
I felt like--
And you do not think Elinor did this?
No, of course not. The fact
they dragged Elinor into this
makes it even more tragic.
So, if she escapes the gaolers,
you will reconsider your engagement?
What do you think I am?
Of course not!
It is ended.
But I want her to be alright.
She's a very decent person.
- Better than...
- ... than you?
Is that what you you were going to say?
No doubt at all, Poirot.
Several ounces of morphine
were found in her body.
It was administered
on the day she died.
You're very kind, Mr. Poirot.
I am happy to answer your questions.
Of course I heard about
Mrs. Welman. What a terrible thing, too.
And you had no suspicions at that time?
Not the least in the world.
So, tell to me, if you please.
Did anyone else enter the room
of Madame Welman that night,
other than Mademoiselle Carlisle?
I never left her side. Except
when Miss Carlisle came in.
Well, she was so bold and clever,
that one.
So why would she have wanted
to do it?
For the money, that's why!
She knew quite well if she didn't do it,
every penny would go to Mary Gerrard.
And that's the truth.
So Mary Gerrard was a girl
who was scheming and clever?
No! Oh, that's a terrible thing to say.
Mrs. Welman adored her.
She was a very sweet girl.
But not one of us.
Pardon...
She was an only child?
Is it possible pehaps that
she had been adopted?
What?
No, certainly not.
I must say, this is a lovely cake.
She made a will, is that correct?
Awful, awful to think of it now.
Nurse Hopkins and I
advised her it was a good thing to do.
We thought she should,
since she had expectations.
But I wish we'd never
mentioned it now, I do.
So the 7000 pounds goes to her aunt.
She has no family here?
Just her mother's sister
nursing at New Zeland.
I've written to the old lady.
What a terrible shock it will be, too.
So will Miss Carlisle be hanged?
If she is found guilty.
"Mrs. Welman, whose money
went to Elinor Carlisle,
"was murdered by morphine.
Mary Gerrard,
who came between
Elinor Carlisle and her fiancé,
was murdered by morphine.
And nobody in the world had the
slightest motive to commit these murders,
other than the acused.
No one had the slightest opportunity,
other than the accused.
And this vengeful woman.
who openly whished her victim
dead to more than one witness,
never expressed
the slightest remorse...
Gentlemen of the jury,
what is your verdict?
Guilty.
Elinor Carlisle,
you're sentenced to be taken hence
to the prison in which you were last confined
and from there to a place of execution
where you'll be hanged
from the neck until dead.
And may the Lord have mercy
upon your soul.
Monsieur Poirot...
Mademoiselle,
please be careful as you go.
Of course...
"Appeal Denied
Hanging in five Days"
I will admit that I've not
been sleeping very well,
but last night
finally I sleep.
And I dream...
I dream... I dream of the victim,
as she was at first.
On the street, outside of my hotel.
A girl so lovely,
the favorite of Madame Welman.
A girl who is liked by everyone,
and yet she's still a mystery.
And then-- then I wake up
and I recalled something.
What?
Uh... it is detail, in fact it is half a detail,
one twentieth of a detail,
but yes, my friend,
it worries me.
Something nurse Hopkins
said concerning Mary.
What about her?
Yes. What about her?
What is behind her?
- You are not making sense.
- Then suddenly I see there's something
that the good nurse Hopkins
she does not wish me to know.
Something she thinks
has no baring on the crime,
but I believe that it may.
But surely she would realize that.
Non. My dear doctor, nurse Hopkins
is a woman of high inteligence,
within her limitations.
But her intelect is hardly equal
with that of mine.
She might not see it,
but Hercule Poirot, he would.
And suddenly, that raises in my mind
so many questions.
No, I was right before.
Something here is crooked.
But, doctor, time is short. There is
something I need from you, it is a book,
how does it call itself, a book which describes
the various medicines you prescribe?
- A formulary?
- Oui, c'est ça!I must borrow it.
Merci.
When I visited you before,
I said it was surprising
how Madame Welman
favored  Mary Gerrard
you said
it was only natural.
And I thought that you merely talking
about the friendship, that it was natural.
And then, I think again of  Mary
and I hear that word again " natural"
and I see that
you used it deliberatly.
Oh, I know it.
And now you must tell to me why.
Nurse O'Brien and I
had both heard crying out
about something in her past.
There was a man called Lewis.
But we both knew
there was much more to it than that.
And then I found this in the lodge,
after Mary had died.
It is Madame Welman?
And the baby?
It's Mary Gerrard.
So Mary was the illegitimate daughter
of Madame Welman...
It's a sad story,
as you'll see from the letter.
The man couldn't marry her,
he had his own family.
Sometime later,
he was killed in the western front.
The Gerrards had no children.
Mrs. Welman went to Scotland
and took Mrs. Gerrard with her,
where the baby was born.
Naturally she payed
for Mary schooling
and told them she would
provide for her.
But she couldn't admit the truth.
She had to avoid the scandal.
But, at last, Mary becomes clearer.
But what sadness.
"So, dear Mary, for all theses years
I had to keep this secret
"from the girl I brought up,
and such a hardship that has been."
Of course, we had suspected this much.
Nurse intimated she knew, but...
What's the point of it coming out now?
I was going to destroy this.
As I said before, Mr. Poirot,
let the dead rest in peace.
Non. Not when one
has to consider the living.
Mademoiselle Carlisle,
you would say nothing before.
But now I know a little more.
I want to help you
and I believe I can.
But you must answer some questions
about that day, I beg of you.
- Why? Is there any p--
- --purpose? Yes, of course there's a purpose.
Please.
Now, just tell it to me,
from the very beginning.
Firstly, why did you give
time off to the servants?
I was upset.
I wanted to be alone.
And, when you made the sandwiches,
did you see anyone outside?
No.
Right. Then you went to sort through
some things of your aunt.
Did you discover anything
that afected you.
Any private matters
concearning your aunt?
What? No.
Well, then, you took Mary
and nurse Hopkins into the library
where you gave them the sandwiches.
What was Mary doing
when you left her?
She was on the sofa.
She seemed normal.
Now, each detail,
if you please.
I went down to the pantry.
Nurse was there doing the washing up.
She said she'd seen a man
in the garden, I didn't see anything.
What then did you you talk of?
I don't know.
Oh yes, the rose treaders
by the lodge.
She had a mark in her arm,
where the thorn had scratched her.
And then it all came back to me.
When we were children,
Roddy and I, we kept having this quarrel
about the War of the Roses.
He liked the white roses
I said they weren't real,
because they didn't even smell.
I preferred red, because
they were big and dark
and smelled... like Summer.
Then I realized something,
yes, I did...
There was no reason to kill Mary, because
Roddy would never have stayed with me.
When I went...
When you went back,
Mary was dying.
You might as well ask me then:
did I intend to kill Mary Gerrard.
Non, non, Mademoiselle.
Now, please do forgive me.
I have very little time.
You told me all that I need.
And there are some things
I still do not wish to know.
Monsieur Horlick,
enter if you please.
Mr. Poirot, I'm sorry. There's
something I need to say in private.
Sr. Horlick, you see before you a miserable
animal, who has been a triple imbecil.
- I am 36 times an idiot.
- Sir?
Forgive me, I have discovered something
in a way that is most painful.
Hideously painful,
but very important.
Pardon. Ca suffit.
No matter. Please, do seat.
Tell to me what you wish to say.
It concearns Dr. Lord, sir.
If you do not agree,
I will go higher.
I wish you to take this matter
with the utmost seriousness.
- I'll do what I can, sir.
- It will have to be tomorrow.
Very well.
Poirot, you realize we have
less than a day and a night?
Why did you ask me here?
Because I wanted to show you this.
- The Zéphrine Rose.
- So?
Isn't that Mr. Winter?
What's going on?
What did Elinor say?
I will tell it to you. She told me
of a quarrel a long time ago.
And how she and Monsieur Winter
were in different sides.
And it made it very clear to me how she fell in love
a long time ago
with a man
who could not return her feeling.
And so, doctor, I began  to see through
all the lies that have been told to me.
Who has lied to you?
Everyone.
Particularly you.
But, at last, the matter
it is almost concluded,
for I've made a trap.
Shall we go back to the house?
I had a message from the Inspector, Poirot.
Can you tell me what's this all about?
It strikes as very unpleasant.
I never wanted to see this room again.
- I am not surprised.
- What does that mean?
Gentlemen, please.
I have concluded that nothing
in this matter is what it seems.
Firstly, we have heard
that, on the day on the murder
it was seen in the garden, a man very tall
and resembled to you, Monsieur Winter.
I told you I never came here.
So, would you be surprised to learn
of the will of Mademoiselle Carlisle.
I established last night
that it is everything to you.
I swear I had no idea.
So, perhaps you stood outside
and observed her making the sandwiches
and thought that they were for her.
Alors, had she died,
you'd be a man very rich.
This is outrageous!
I told I never came into the grounds.
However, if she was hanged,
you would be equally rich.
So, let us assume,
as did the trial,
that the murder, it was successful.
It is easy to imagine, you or another,
being aware
that Elinor Carlisle intended
to invite Mary Gerrard here
and also to know that the preference of Mary
was for the salmon paste.
Both these things,
they were well known.
- Oh, you're including me?
- I include everyone.
Now this person
has the file of morphine.
And the chance it comes...
And this is what he finds.
The sandwiches.
One of salmon paste,
the other two of shrimp and crab.
Alors, our murderer
approaches the sandwiches.
And, at once, he observes that
the colour and the texture are identical.
So, which one is the salmon paste?
No, there's no way on earth
he could distinguish by smell.
So, what can this person do?
I am affraid that there's only
one thing that he can do.
He tastes.
It was bad enough
the first time...
But then, suddenly, I realized
how stupid I had been!
I, Hercule Poirot,
had followed my reasoning, yes,
but I had failed to take into account
the madness of the English palate.
For, gentlemen, what do we find?
What we find is that we are
entering into the realms of lunacy.
I do not care if our murderer had
the palate of a master-chef.
He could never distiguish
between theses two slurries.
No,it is a fact. These sandwiches
are all but indistinguishable.
Then I came to the conclusion.
I, Hercule Poirot, do not care
what was said at the trial.
This could never, ever, be
the pratical method of murder.
So Elinor Carlisle did not
poison the sandwich?
- No, she did not.
- Who did?
Nobody.
- So it was an accident?
- Non, non...
She was murdered, but not
by these disgusting sandwiches.
I said just now that
everyone had lied to me, uh?
For example, the man that
nurse Hopkins saw outside here.
- She was lying?
- Non, non, non. Indeed, she was not.
And you know that, Dr. Lord,
because you are aware of who it was.
It was you. Monsieur Horlick
recognised your car,
but did not want to say so
in front of you.
So, last night,
he came to the hotel to tell it to me.
So, here is yet another lie, uh?
But why?
Was it because you feared
for Elinor Carlisle?
Was it your heart I could forgive?
Or something much more sinister?
All right, all right. I would have done
anything to protect her.
I was just a fool to think
I could deceive you.
Oui. Either a fool
or something worse.
Please, to remain.
I will return.
Do you believe in ghosts?
No, of course not.
I had a message to come here.
Oui. As you know, someone
entered this room
on the last night that
Madame Welman was alive
and gave to her the morphine.
You told to the court that
you never left the side of your patient
during that evening, except when
Mademoiselle Carlisle was present.
She was the accused,
so no person could challenge you.
But it is a fact that Mr. Winter
entered this room
when you were making the tea,
and perhaps others.
Maybe I was out a few times.
That's no crime.
That is not your only lie.
When I asked you if
Mary Gerrard was adopted, you denied it.
Why did you not tell to me the truth?
What? That?
But it has no baring.
No baring?
You suppose the fact that Mary Gerrard
being illegitimate daughter of
Madame Welman has no baring on this?
Elinor Carlisle only inherited the money
because she was the nearest next of kin.
Now it emerges that she was not.
At that point, Mary Gerrard stood
to inherit 200 thousand pounds.
Ah, so that's it! It was another motive
for Miss Carlisle to do away with her.
On the contrary.
It was no motive at all.
Such an action,
it would have been pointless,
since Mary Gerrard
had already made a will.
Was it you who told her
to do that?
We talked about it.
What are you saying, Mr. Poirot?
That someone other than Elinor
Carlisle beneficts from her death.
This came to me yesterday
and then I began to think again
about the anonimous letter
designed to breed the distress between
Mary Gerrard and Elinor Carlisle.
And suddenly the light, it began to dawm
about, amongst other things,
New Zealand.
Excuse me.
Well, Mr Poirot, so long as you wanted me
here, I thought I'd make us a cup of tea.
Oh! Thank you. You're most kind.
And now, perhaps you'd tell me
what this is about.
The truth is, nurse Hopkins,
I brought you here
to talk about this rose.
It is the rose of the treader
from the lodge.
You were pricked, I believe,
by its thorn.
Yes.
But, as you can quite well regard...
... the Zephirine Rose
it has no thorn.
Well, then it was a nail
from the treaders.
I thought it was a thorn.
It was sharp enough too.
- Your tea.
- Merci.
Quite so...
A mistake...
Tell me, you have lived
in New Zealand?
How would you discover that?
Mind you. It is known.
Is it?
The truth is, I have tried to discover it
myself, but without any success.
It little matters.
But I did have a little more success
in discovering your real name.
Your first name is Mary,
the same as Mary Gerrard.
And your surname is Riley,
the same as her adoptive mother.
Poor Mary, she did never guess
who you really were, did she?
And that letter you showed me,
you never discovered it here at the lodge.
Non, that was a letter you received.
You know, at the time I thought
the writing was rather strange.
"And so, dear Mary,
"I have had to keep this secret
from the girl I brought up."
So why would the writer address
her daughter directly as Mary
and then proceed to talk
about her in the third person?
Because it was not
a mother writing to her daughter at all.
Non. It was a mother
writing to her sister,
confessing the secret ot the true
parentage of her adopted daughter.
Yes, it was your letter, sent to you,
her aunt in New Zealand.
And this planted a temptation
which grew.
What temptation?
The temptation of a big inheritance.
And it was for that reason
that you came here.
You tried to store her feelings
against Mary
with your poisonous pen,
the anonimous letter.
You killed Madame Welman,
knowing that she had made no will
and even tricked poor Mary
into making a will
in favour of her kind aunt
in New Zealand,
encouraged by the postcards
and presents which you arranged.
Oh yes, she was named after you
and yet you killed her.
Later, you would release
that sad letter,
ensuring that the
settlement would change.
And, from a safe distance,
clame your money.
This is a strange sort of fiction,
Mr. Poirot.
But, so long as you finish
your tea, I'll wash up.
But I still worried about the scrap
of label that they discovered here.
Oh, certainly it said morphine,
but there was one bit
that did not quite fit, uh?
The small "m".
Why not the capital?
And eventually I realized
that it was only
part of the name of
the drug that they discovered.
It was incomplete
and not for morphine at all.
And I searched, and searched
and, at last, I discovered
a drug of great interest.
Apomorphine! An emetic.
Yes, an emetic, Mr. Poirot.
Apomorphine makes you vomit.
If you are poisoned
and than inject that,
you vomit quite enough
to expell the poison.
And so it was the tea.
You poisoned it,
you drank it with Mary.
A little while later,
Elinor Carlisle find you with
a prick from the needdle in your arm,
standing over basin
where you'd been so sick.
And now, I have to do it again.
The poison's safely washed up,
though luckily I had much less than you.
Not morphine this time,
something nastier.
But nobody will quite know
how it entered your system.
And there's no trace of it.
Oh, but my dear lady, there is.
You see...
... I hate, and always have hated, tea.
And here... is your emetic.
I removed it from your bag.
Give me that!
Come on, lads!
You filthy foreigner!
There was no way they could've found out!
Poirot, come now.
We have a car waiting.
We need to hurry.
There's no time to waste.
And Dr. Lord also, if you please.
I think you will be needed.
Monsieur Winter.
This is for you.
It is from the lodge
and it saved your life.
You have been acquitted.
You are free to go.
But--
There is someone outside
who will explain to you everything.
Amongst other things,
who it was that wrote to you your letter.
And it is to him that you
should give the thanks.
Monsieur Poirot,
you know what I told you. I--
Mademoiselle Carlisle, wanting a
death is no crime.
Bon? Now go...
May I take you home?
Yes.
Translation & resync by titta
to Addic7ed.com