[theme music]
[upbeat music]
-[man] Are you guys excited for ice cream?
-[gasps]
-Awesome.
-Are you excited?
The Ice Cream Museum is just super cool.
It's like something different
to do in town.
Yeah. Who wouldn't want to swim
in a bed of sprinkles? Like, come on.
Kim, turn around and stand on the phone.
[upbeat music]
[Jonathan] So exciting.
[Kim] Oh, walk on the stars.
Oh, Scoop Dogg?
Kim Carbstashian?
You guys, I finally got a star.
-[Kourtney] Ah, you guys are so cute.
-Wait, it's even better.
Here you go, Bo. Cheers.
Remember, guys,
try not to dive or jump into the pool.
A pool of sprinkles? Holy Food God!
Oh, there's a diving board.
[Kim] How fun, guys! Whoo!
[Kim chuckling]
[overlapping chatter]
-Ah!
-Hey!
[coughs]
-[Jonathan] This is good.
-Food God dies by choking on sprinkles!
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Look, a whole store
of sewing machines.
Mason loves to sew. He loves it.
He'll go, "Mom, I want to sew."
What the hell does he sew?
They make stuffed animals
and they sell them on a website,
and it goes to, like, a charity.
Remember when we used to come down here
to do all the buying for DASH?
I swear, we, like, parked
in one of these parking lots.
I used to have an apartment
on 7th & Flower. The good old days.
[Kim] You're allowed to just put a tent
on the side of the road?
There's so many, like...
[Khloé] If you look up all these streets,
there's tons of tents.
Like, up all...
Every street here, I'm seeing tents.
[Kourtney] I should have driven my kids
by here when they were down here.
Dad used to drive us down here.
Yeah, but we were just
at that Ice Cream Museum.
Like, we should have driven by...
with them.
My dad used to drive us to Skid Row
when we were little
to just show us that the rest of the world
doesn't really live
like how we live in Beverly Hills
and that always stuck with me.
[somber music]
And then when I had kids, like,
everything kind of opens up,
and you want our world to be
the most perfect place for them,
and your awareness
just becomes so heightened.
Just so much has changed of things
I was just oblivious to before.
[Kim] But it's not enough to witness it.
I really want to do something about it.
[Khloé] It's so sad.
[upbeat music]
-[Khloé] Matthew, is my mom in her office?
-[Matthew] Yes.
[Khloé] Thank you.
-Hello, darling. Bonjour.
-Bonjour.
You snuck this one on
just so ever so quickly.
[Kris] I always have your covers here,
and all the new covers
get to be on the presidential desk.
-Oh, my goodness.
-[Kris] Isn't it exciting?
I'm so excited for our barbecue.
-What barbecue?
-[Khloé] Mom, you're joking.
-Mom...
-[Kris] When's the barbecue?
-Mom!
-[Kris] Is it today?
Are you okay? Like, do you...
Like, are you losing it?
-Maybe.
-We had a whole conversation.
We're having a barbecue
and you are making a dish.
[Khloé] You're bringing it over
and everyone's coming to the house.
150 percent,
you've never mentioned a barbecue.
-All right.
-[Kris] Okay?
So nothing's ever slipped your mind
in the past, right?
[Khloé] Hold Post-its in your hand
and start sticking things places.
-Okay.
-[Khloé] Like, "brush my teeth."
"Wipe my ass." Like, that should be
in the bathroom, like, when the door,
-when you shut it.
-I've got those little details covered.
-Oh, so those things you remember.
-[Kris] Yeah.
You just forget family barbecues
and the dishes to make.
I am constantly multi-tasking
and trying to take care
of a gazillion things at the same time.
And I'm always working
on my organizational skills
and trying to figure out how to become
more organized and more productive.
[Khloé] Well, you've just been holding
this pen for how long?
No, I was gonna write it for the...
[Khloé] Do you keep forgetting
what you have to write?
-It's like, where is my note cards?
-Do you want me to tell you?
-"Barbecue."
-Here it is. Here it is.
-Barbecue.
-[Khloé] "Bring a dish of your choice."
[Kris] Barbecue. See?
It helps when I write it down.
[Khloé] Kris Kardashian?
Did you forget what your last name is too?
[laughter]
Did you?
[Kim] Oh, my gosh.
Look what Kylie is tempting me with...
So I would have to go to Cleveland,
and then go there.
-[Kris] Where are you going?
-[Khloé] Maybe Anguilla. I'm not sure.
[Kris]
Oh, so you can't bring back the doughnuts?
I could bring you doughnuts, Mom.
-[Kris] Hey.
-[Khloé] Penelope.
I just hired a scriber.
-[Tristan] You did?
-Yeah. Do you know what a scriber is?
-Yeah, they write down everything.
-Yeah. Everything I say.
Everything you say, so yeah,
keep it all for, like, memories.
That's right 'cause I, I'm getting older
and I feel like I can't remember anything.
So I need to write it down
because five minutes later...
I called Kendall today. Two minutes later,
I didn't know why I called her.
I'm at the doctor and I realize that
there's someone standing right next to him
writing down on a little table
every single thing he says.
[Kris] And I ask him, what is she doing?
And he said, "That's my scribe.
She keeps track
of every single thing I say and do,
because I can refer to it later."
And a huge light bulb goes off.
This is genius.
That I can have somebody follow me around
every single day
and then repeat back to me
what I said or did. This is everything.
-All right, babe. I'll talk to you later.
-Okay.
-Love you.
-I love you, too.
[Kourtney]
It's crazy that you're getting a scribe.
I want everything I say documented
from now on.
[Kris] There's so much I miss.
Do you know how much stuff
is rolling around up here in this head?
Like, just this side alone,
I walk around like this
'cause there's so much stuff over here
and then some days,
-I'll walk around like that over there.
-Isn't Lovely so silly?
-How silly is she?
-So I need somebody to write it all down.
And then, when I can't remember
what I was supposed to do,
or what I meant to say,
or take it to a meeting,
I have somebody right there that...
Chop-chop, we have a scriber.
It's a scribe. Scribe.
Whatever. A scribe for my tribe.
[laughs]
[laughing]
Yeah, oh, yeah.
[upbeat music]
-[Khloé] How's your diet been going?
-[Kim] Good.
You know, I had
a few gluten-free pretzels today,
which threw me off,
'cause that's carbs, but it's fine.
Gluten-free, it's like you're eating air.
Not really.
I feel like that's gonna be the...
like, the trick, 'cause people think that.
[Khloé] Mm.
After we went downtown,
didn't you feel, like, so bad?
Like, there were so many people.
[Khloé] It's definitely different
than when, like, Dad used to take us.
I think people are blind, and people
kind of like to live in their bubble...
-Yeah.
-...and ignore what's really going on.
[Kim] I just want to work
with, like, some organization.
I don't know what...
which one, or where to go,
but I just feel like there's something
that we can do to help.
For sure, I think you would definitely...
I mean, it's easy to find an organization
that would love to have your, uh,
like, help and to bring awareness to it.
I am just at a point in my life
where I don't want to be naive anymore,
and I just want to use my platform
to get other people involved.
And I really do want to learn
and figure out what we can all do
to fix this problem.
[upbeat music]
-[Khloé] I'm working out tonight.
-[Kim] Why?
Just because I'm as fat
as [bleep] fat can be.
[Kim] Mm.
-[Kourtney] Hey, Mom.
-[Kris] Hi.
-[Khloé] Hi.
-How are you guys?
-[Khloé] Oh, wow. You look beautiful.
-[Kris] Thank you. This is Madhvi.
-Nice to meet you.
-She is my scribe.
[quirky music]
-Are you being serious?
-Yeah.
Oh.
Wait, when you're having a conversation,
does Madhvi also record what I'm saying,
or just what you're saying?
-[Kris] What everybody's saying.
-Okay. Just curious.
Right?
-[Madhvi] Mm-hmm.
-[Kris] Mm-hmm.
[keyboard keys clacking]
I mean, it's kind of amazing.
I can look back and tell you
exactly what I said.
There's no doubt.
Meeting the scribe for the first time
is just strange.
Do you really want
everything documented? Everything?
All right,
I'm gonna make a urination sample.
Mom, do you have to pee
or are you good with your diaper?
[keyboard keys clacking]
[quirky music]
I just feel like, let's just make
Kris Jenner so uncomfortable, it's fun.
[Khloé] What? She queefed in our workroom
the other day.
-I did not.
-[Khloé] Yes, you did.
She was queefing. She did. Queef.
[laughs]
I did not.
[Kris] You are funny.
You're funny to have around.
[Khloé] Me? Oh, thanks.
But I will say, as a child,
the way you used to talk to me
when I thought my name was [bleep]head.
And all you do is get drunk. It's wild.
Please call Child Services.
You have no idea what I go through
on a nightly basis.
Don't punish me
because somebody's writing
everything down.
It's not funny anymore.
[upbeat music]
I was trying to get in touch with my mom,
but she isn't calling me back.
I just know something's up with her,
so why not ask Kim, her favorite child?
-So, question.
-Yeah.
When we were at dinner with Mom,
do you think Mom had a nice time?
[Khloé] Or do you think she was angry?
I think she was, like, laughing a lot,
nervously laughing.
-Did you think she...
-[Kim] You hurt her feelings?
-[Khloé] Yeah.
-Yeah, just because I know her.
From the moment you started,
I knew she was, like, gonna...
Then why would she say, "You're so funny"?
Because I think she was nervous
at the moment in front of the girl.
Then, why have the scribe?
Like, it's stupid.
Don't just be, "What?"
Like, obviously, you didn't chain me
to a wall, and it's my first time leaving.
Obviously, I didn't think my name
was [bleep]head until I was ten.
-[Khloé] Obviously, like, come on.
-Yeah. I mean, I get it.
-Just, like... This family, I can't handle.
-[Kim] 'Cause I...
[Khloé] You look cute.
-[Kendall] Do I?
-Your belly button is so vertical.
[Khloé] I'm envious.
I literally will get Botox
around my belly button
just so it looks like that.
-What? Who does this for you?
-Well, I don't.
I'm going to, is what I'm saying.
-I'll do anything to tighten the skin.
-No one's offered me that.
[upbeat music]
-Hi, ladies. I'm Andy.
-[Khloé] Hi. How are you?
-Hi. Khloé. Nice to meet you.
-Great to see you, Khloé.
-[Khloé] This is Kim.
-Hi, Kim. Great to meet you.
-Hi, I'm Alexandra.
-Hi. Khloé.
[Andy] I wanted to take you
on a little tour if you have time.
-[Khloé] Yeah, we would love that.
-[Kim] Yeah, for sure.
[Kim] As I've been doing my research,
I just feel like
I have to start somewhere,
and this is the perfect place for me
to get some more information,
and to figure out all of the questions
that I really have
as to what we can do to help.
[Kim] I just hope that I can shine a light
on this issue, and that, hopefully,
more people will come together,
and we can figure out a solution for this.
Oh, wow.
[Andy] This is our beautiful rooftop
with one of the best views of downtown LA.
[Kim] So, like, all these people
that are just roaming the streets,
do they not want to come and stay here?
[Andy] There just aren't enough
shelter beds in LA,
so 47,000 people are on the streets,
and there's only 12,000 shelter beds
to go to.
This is the worst man-made disaster
in the United States.
Over 2,000 people living on our sidewalks.
And, you know, people say
they want people to get off the streets.
There's nowhere to go.
[Andy] I can tell you, recently,
what's causing it to skyrocket
is the cost of rent.
Rents have gone up 30 percent.
Salaries have gone down 3 percent.
It's like a perfect storm of homelessness,
especially in LA.
This year, we have 55 percent more people
under our roof.
-And do you guys have the space for that?
-[Andy] We've made space.
We never turn away a woman,
because there's 800 registered
sex offenders on the streets,
so our hearts won't let us.
The homeless issue is a full epidemic,
and I don't know what the answer is
to get people off the streets,
but you know, I'm so willing to help
in any way that I can.
You cannot survive on the streets
without being brutalized
and devastated by the experience.
I just want to bring awareness
to this issue.
Unfortunately, people do live in bubbles,
and people probably think,
like, LA is this glamorous place.
[Kim] And it makes me feel really sad
that people are just living like this,
and the problem's just getting worse.
[light music]
[Andy] This is the floor
that our families with children stay on.
[Alexandra] You can see everybody's
bags of clothing and everything.
We want to make sure our women feel safe,
so we have separate floors for everybody.
Hi. This is Khloé. This is Kim.
This is Alex Cornejo.
-Hi. Kim.
-Hi. Khloé. Nice to see you.
Alex is somebody that came through
our men's program,
and has been working here
a little bit longer than me.
[Khloé] Do you guys want to sit down,
or get comfortable?
Recently, we drove by,
and we noticed how much it's escalated,
the homelessness here, and...
-from when we were younger.
-How many tents there are.
And just... we were, like, shocked
by what it looked like.
And so for us,
we really wanted to educate ourselves
as to kind of why I think
it's, like, multiplied,
and just kind of hear stories,
and maybe, like, what we can do.
So Laquita, uh, I wanted you to share,
because I think Laquita's a great example
of somebody who didn't suffer
from any of those issues
that you usually, typically ask.
[Alexandra] Like, is this person addicted?
Is there mental illness?
She was just a mom who needed a hand up.
Um, I just didn't have a job that paid
well enough for me to get my own place,
-you know, and to support us.
-Yeah.
We all don't come
from abusive points of view,
or running away
from our husbands or boyfriends,
or we have drug or alcohol...
Sometimes you just need a place
to... take a breath and to move on.
-Thank you for sharing.
-[Laquita] Yeah.
The reason I'm here
is because I don't think
I can afford to pay housing on my own
for my one-bedroom apartment.
I go to my brother's house
and he likes to smoke drugs.
[Khloé] Mm-hmm.
And I can't stand that.
I don't even want to be around.
I don't want to see it. I drove down here,
and I didn't know this program here
at the Union was like it was.
It's a good program
if people do what they came here to do.
But if they don't...
[chuckles]
...that's why they end up out there.
[Latanya]
The things that I've seen down here...
nasty things.
[chuckles]
[Khloé] Right.
There are so many circumstances
that can lead to, you know,
this situation for so many people.
[Kim] And I think just having a place
where they take in mothers
and their children,
that is so important,
because they are so vulnerable,
when they're on the streets, to rapists
and pedophiles and drug trafficking.
This can happen to anyone.
It's just really sad
to hear that, you know,
so many people are just one paycheck away
from being homeless.
[Patrice] My name is Patrice.
I became homeless probably in 2014
due to financial hardship.
I'd been doing it on my own,
hit financial hardship,
lost my income and became homeless,
then went to stay with friends.
And, you know,
staying with friends don't work out a lot,
so end up back on the street.
-[Kim] It's okay.
-But that's where I'm at now.
[Patrice] But they gave me a voucher.
I'm looking for a place now.
And I've been here since Saturday.
-[Khloé] Since Saturday?
-Mm-hmm.
For most of society,
it seems like there's this net or web
that kind of catches you when you fall.
I think for some, that net or web...
there was never the father,
there was never the mother, there was
never aunts and uncles to help facilitate.
And so they just kind of
fell through the cracks,
and all of a sudden, now they end up here,
that it's just completely inundated.
Thank you guys so much
for sharing your stories with us.
Thank you for coming.
-[Khloé] Thank you.
-Thank you.
-And thank you.
-Bye.
[pensive music]
[Khloé] Thank you, I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
So crazy.
I mean, just these people
are such good people.
[Khloé] You know, I do think,
like, I don't know.
Dad always made us do things,
so like, I have never been scared
of stuff like this.
[Kim] I mean, obviously,
to have awareness.
[Khloé] Totally.
I think it is important
to teach your kids that stuff.
[Kim] Totally. I think it's so important.
From this experience, I've learned
that it's just not that simple.
The city needs to figure out housing,
and it's not gonna be just one person.
It has to be a bunch of people
coming together to figure this out.
[pensive music]
Just seeing how many people
don't really have an option
really was so sad.
So sad.
[tranquil music]
[birds chirping]
Oh, my God.
I've never sat in this little chair.
You haven't?
-[Khloé] No.
-It's cozy.
[Kim] Um...
That was pretty intense.
-[Khloé] Yeah.
-Wait. I want to look up some stuff.
-That was really sad.
-So I just want to google,
like, other things on Skid Row,
because I feel like...
[sniffles]
...there's just so many more,
like, untold stories.
I wonder how many shelters are downtown.
'Cause when we were driving by that time,
we were naming shelters.
[Kim] Do you want to watch this?
[Nury]
I have real concerns about this. Um...
When we talk about all of us sharing
the burden of how... and how we deal
with the homeless issue,
we have paid the price
of poor land use decisions
for people who live
in these sensitive areas.
And now we're saying it's okay
to have people live in their vehicles,
in these very areas
that we're trying to protect people from.
It's going to become a problem
in the Northeast San Fernando Valley,
particularly City 7 and City 6.
I brought my father home
from the hospital...
There's a lot that I think can be done
in our community,
and it starts
with just getting the information.
Councilwoman Nury Martinez,
I just feel like
she would give me some major insight
on what I can do to help.
I mean, it seems like she really cares
and really wants to change the situation.
And I feel like that's what,
you know, is most important.
-What do you want to do?
-[Kim] I don't know.
[Khloé] If I'm in town, I'll go with you.
[Kim] But, like, it's crazy that there's
so much, like, in our neighborhood.
So close to us, there's so much going on.
[Khloé] It's so sad.
Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Oh, look how cute they are!
-Look at my sheepy.
-[Khloé] That's cute.
There's an artist who made these things.
[Khloé] Oh, my God. This is crazy.
[Kris] It took me two years to find her,
but I haven't named her yet.
I don't really take
this scribe thing too seriously.
I think having a person follow you around
and type on a computer all day long
is a little excessive.
So... a little birdie told me that
you're upset about dinner the other night?
-[Kris] You have no filter.
-Everyone said that dinner was so fun.
Like, Kourtney and Kim were like,
"Thank God you were there." It was fun.
[Kris] You're always fun, but sometimes,
you take it to another level.
-And you have no filter.
-[keyboard keys clacking]
I wonder where I get the other level from?
[Khloé] You have a [bleep] scribe
dictating everything you do.
-I could replay it for you...
-[Kris] Oh, I can ask her
-and she can tell me exactly what we said.
-It's a visual, because...
it caught me off guard that you show up
with a scribe somewhere.
So what am I gonna do?
I'm gonna make a joke out of it
and make it uncomfortable,
because it's uncomfortable
to have someone going...
[keyboard keys clacking]
-Khloé, but that's what her job is.
-That's her job.
But it's also my job to show you
how ridiculous some things are.
-I wasn't trying to hurt your feelings.
-Okay.
I was trying to have fun
and be playful with you.
In the moment, you're laughing,
crying so much you're laughing.
I think I was really crying.
But then say, I would never want
to hurt your feelings, ever.
It's obviously all bull[bleep].
But that was the joke of it all.
You have
some ridiculous situation going on
with some person
dictating your every word.
No offense.
But you're a normal human being.
[Khloé]
We're not in the court of law here.
Okay, are we done with this conversation?
Yeah, I think we're done in general.
[upbeat music]
It's been really amazing
having the scribe around,
but I kind of get Khloé's point.
So I'm gonna lighten up
and do the same thing to her.
I think you're just as insane as she is.
And you wonder where she gets it from.
"Do unto others."
Good for you.
And that's not what it means,
"Do unto others."
"As you would have them do unto you."
Oh, yeah. You're right.
-I was saying...
-[Kourtney] Hey, you guys.
-You guys are matching.
-Khloé inspired me.
I said, what are you wearing,
so I can throw something on.
-[Khloé] I like your Good American skirt.
-I said, "I gotta represent."
It looks so good and it feels so good.
[Kourtney] Do you want to be
the head of the table?
-[Larsa] Is Kylie coming?
-[Khloé] Yeah, right.
-Kylie's the new Rob.
-[Kourtney] The big boss.
-[Kim] Hey, Mom. Hey, Corey.
-Hi!
-[Kris] How are you?
-[Kendall] What is going on?
Oh, this is my scribe. This is Kendall.
[Kris] She writes down everything I say.
[Khloé] This person follows her
around everywhere.
Oh, my God.
-[Kris] Mm-hmm. Thank you.
-[Kourtney] Anybody? Brussels sprouts?
[Kim] Mm-hmm.
Do I need to leave a name at the gate
for a prescription delivery?
[Larsa] What are you getting?
Can we share?
Medication for Khloé's lice.
[Larsa] You have lice?
Kourt, she's trying to do
what I did at the restaurant.
-[Larsa] Khloé, I've been watching you...
-Could you go get the basket, babe?
-[Khloé] By preparation, each...
-So in case...
-[Kim] I love it.
-You've told me about your dryness problem
-in your vagina.
-My dry vagina. Yeah.
-So I got you K-Y Jelly. Yup.
-Thank you!
So she has this fungus.
-[Larsa] That's why she's been limping.
-[Khloé] For jock itch.
Mom, I actually have a dick.
This is perfect.
For your moustache.
-Kim will say I need this the most.
-[Kim] Yes.
-Here's your yeast infection medicine.
-I need that.
-This is for your colon health.
-[Khloé] Are you okay?
And I got you
high-waisted diapers this time.
Look at her, she's crying.
[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
Going forward,
I think probably best to do the scribe
during meetings and business hours
and not family time maybe.
Okay.
[Kris] Okay. All right, Kourt,
I'll see you later.
[Kris sighs]
Bye, guys.
[chair creaking]
[soft scoff]
[upbeat music]
-Hi. How are you? I'm Kim.
-Hi! I'm Nury.
Nice to meet you. Sit down.
Thank you for expressing interest
on this issue that, you know,
quite frankly, has gotten so much worse
over the last,
I would say, five to ten years.
I had no idea. I mean,
my sisters and I had gone downtown.
It's shocking to see
-families and children.
-It really is shocking.
To me, it's infuriating
that we are, you know,
the most powerful country in the world
and that we allow people to live this way.
Yeah. That's so intense.
[Kim] Councilwoman Nury Martinez
has focused so much of her career
on helping the homeless.
What I want to know most
is what is the city doing to help.
'Cause that is what
will ultimately cure this issue.
So what we're trying to do is
not only address the housing needs,
but also the issue
of these large encampments
where you have, you know,
more than 50, 100 people.
But I want to show you a sort of a...
a glimpse of what my district looks like.
[Nury]
So this is what we call Cabrito Road
and it's literally a tent community.
You have all kinds of elements.
You have people who have, of course,
have serious drug addiction problems
that need treatment.
You have people who need medication
for their mental health issues.
But you also have a criminal element here
that nobody wants to talk about.
Sometimes you have pimps hiding, um,
young kids, as young as 11 year olds,
being trafficked in our country
every single day.
-[Nury] And, um, we do nothing.
-That's crazy.
Yeah, we do nothing to address this issue.
It's an epidemic.
It's hard to deal with it if you have
all the resources in the world.
[Nury] Right. In the city of Los Angeles,
we have to be very careful about
how we clean these encampments up.
Here's an indication of what sort of...
we find when we're there.
It's just the amount of stuff
that they accumulate over there for months
and they've been out there.
I mean, who can live this way?
[Kim] Yeah.
No one should ever live like this
in this country.
[Kim] I think the problem is just
so much bigger than people really realize.
You get, like, a glimpse of it,
but when you drive,
like, 20 minutes further,
you see...
it's, like, just like devastation
of like, people just all over the streets.
Like, people just have to see this.
Like, I want to drive down here.
I want to bring our cameras.
I want to show people what it's like
just right down the street.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
I'll follow you.
[upbeat music]
The homeless issue
is now starting to become
such a prevalent thing
all over, across the city.
I can't imagine
that people are not watching
these small encampments
kind of creep up in their neighborhood.
It's basically spreading everywhere.
I know that this is not something
that I could fix by myself,
but I hope
that everything that I'm learning
will hopefully wake something up
inside of other people,
so that everyone can just come together,
and...
You know, if me speaking about it
even brings awareness to one person,
then that can help make a difference.
[Nury] So this is all San Fernando Road,
along the railroad tracks.
And this is probably one of our...
the most difficult encampment to clean up.
[Nury] And look at the trash
and the amount of debris, and...
So let's say you get out and you want
to talk to people, what would you say?
Oh, I would just ask them if, um,
anybody from the HOPE Team,
or from the city has approached them
about finding a place to live.
[Nury] If we see too many people out...
that doesn't seem like
it's gonna be a safe situation,
we can just stay in the car.
Sometimes they're willing
to talk to you, sometimes they're not.
[Kim] I can handle it.
I feel like we have a lot of people
around us, if something got crazy.
[Nury] Yeah, no, it actually gets
a little bit more dicier than that.
I just don't want to put you
in a situation.
[tense music]
-I'll just follow your lead.
-[Nury] All right. Let's go.
Look at this.
It looks like a third-world country.
[Nury] This used to be a lot worse camp.
This was all lined up with tents.
We've come out here a couple of times,
and as you can tell,
there's still some folks out here.
We're not trying to arrest anybody.
We're just simply trying to figure out,
how did you get here?
Are you willing to accept services?
[Nury] And then we'll bring in
the team to assess it.
[in Spanish] Hello, how are you?
What is your name?
[indistinct chatter]
-[Manuel] Manuel.
-Manuel, how long have you lived here?
-Two years.
-[Nury] Two years?
-This is my friend, Kim.
-Hola.
[Nury] Before you came here,
what was your job?
Before this, I worked with my brother
in a granite shop.
-Oh, where? Here?
-[Manuel] Around the corner over here.
[Nury] Uh-huh.
-Did you have a place to live before?
-Yes.
[Nury] Yes? What happened?
The company went broke
and we didn't have a chance
to look for other work.
Who lives here with you?
My wife lives here,
but she isn't here right now.
[Nury in English] Oh, okay.
So he's here with his wife
and he actually works around the corner
at a granite, um, crushing facility.
He, uh...
Two years ago, his company lost, um...
basically went bankrupt,
and he lost his job.
[in Spanish]
Has anyone come by to offer you services,
or help you find a place to live?
Honestly, no.
-And would you like to find some services?
-Who wouldn't? Because living here is...
-[Nury] It's hard, right?
-A little.
[Nury in English]
He said he's open to receiving services
or help to try to get off the street.
[Nury in Spanish] Thank you, Manuel.
Hello. How long have you lived here?
-Four months.
-[Nury] Four months?
-I'm from the streets.
-[Nury] Oh.
[in English] So the HOPE Team was out here
a couple of... a couple of months ago,
and so they did offer him services,
and he didn't accept it
about four months ago.
So, he doesn't really have a real,
an answer as to why, but this is...
He chose to stay out here.
[somber music]
The whole point is to try to get people
to accept the help.
But if you're not willing to,
it makes it harder.
[Kim] Yeah, for sure.
Walking through the encampment
and seeing the tents,
and just seeing that,
it's like this whole community.
It's just, you know, so unsanitary,
so not safe.
I don't know. It's just so...
It was, like, heartbreaking
to see these living conditions.
[Kim] Thank you so much
for taking the time to show it to me,
so it can, like, be really real.
We're gonna dive into it
and start meeting with people
and see what we can do to help.
-Okay. You're welcome.
-Thank you so much.
-[Kim] So nice to meet you.
-Same here.
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Mason] Mom, can I have an Oreo?
-No.
-[Kourtney] You're very persistent but no.
-[Penelope] What do you want?
Eggies, a hotdog and...
-[Penelope] Pizza?
-Yeah.
So when we went downtown the other day,
there was, like, so many single moms.
-Yeah. It didn't seem like it was couples.
-It was so crazy. Yeah.
This one lady, when I was volunteering
at that homeless shelter,
she got injured at work.
And, like, the workers' comp
only covered so much
that, like, she had to like...
she was in the hospital for so long after,
she had to put
all of her money towards it.
And then when she was out of the hospital,
she just couldn't pay her bills.
'Cause she had no more money
and she couldn't work,
'cause she was disabled.
And then... so she had nowhere to go.
[Stephanie] She went to this,
like, transitional housing.
That's, like, where I told you
I was gonna volunteer for Mother's Day.
And they, like,
just give you a place to stay.
-Where is it?
-[Stephanie] Um...
It's, like, on the Eastside,
like, by my house. It's off of Alexandria.
I've heard of it, actually.
-[Stephanie] It's really cool. Yeah.
-[Kim] Alexandria House.
-The place is really cute.
-We have to go.
-[Stephanie] You guys should come.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-I'm sure they would be, like, so excited.
Oh, thank you.
[imitates sipping]
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Hi. How are you?
This is so cute.
-Hey, Justine. How are you?
-[Justine] Hey, how are you?
-Thank you for doing this.
-Oh, my gosh. Thanks for having me.
It's so cool.
[Kim] Today, I have an amazing party
planned to support the Alexandria House,
a long-term shelter for women
and single moms.
We are partnering with companies
like Priv and Cost Plus World Market
to provide
some great products and services.
And I just want to bring awareness
to this issue
because I feel like there's a lot
that can be done in our community,
and it starts
with just getting the information.
-Hi. How are you?
-Hi. I'm Caroline. How nice to meet you.
-[Kim] Oh, of course. Of course.
-Come on over here.
-[Kim] Hi. How are you?
-She's the director.
-Nice to meet you.
-[Kim] Nice to meet you.
Yeah, so glad that you're here.
Could I get everyone's attention
just for a moment, please?
Um, we just want to thank you, Kim,
for bringing your amazing crew here
for Alexandria House.
Alexandria House has been here
for 21 years.
As you know, LA is the homeless capital
of the United States.
[Caroline] The rising population
is women and children.
Alexandria House,
we're just a drop in the bucket
of what the good that we can do
to eliminate homelessness.
We really appreciate you being here
and casting some attention
on this incredible issue
that's impacting so many.
And what we'd like to offer to you
is a gift of stories.
[Judy] We'd like to start with Madisen.
Most people don't understand,
you know, the homeless.
They think that, oh,
you had to have been a bad kid.
You had to have run away.
You're doing drugs. I was an athlete.
Um, and for whatever reason,
my mom, she just couldn't deal.
She was on drugs,
and she kicked me out the house at 17,
and I found myself homeless
and I've met so many...
In my journey at 17 in the shelter,
I met so many kids who were like me.
So I just kinda wanted
to highlight that part of my story,
'cause most people
here in Alexandria House,
they know about the domestic violence
that I did.
They know that when I came here
at 20 years old with a one-year-old.
You know, they know
about that part of my story.
They don't know
what I went through before.
-[Madisen] So I just want to...
-Oh, wow.
Thank you so much for sharing your story.
[applause]
I'm gonna do my signature piece.
It's called Skid Row Sister.
It's a piece that I wrote
when I found myself on Skid Row.
There's a place in LA
That's been titled obscure
It's a place I've embraced
As my gifts become sure
And in this space
I erase a lifetime of being demure
On the 17th of December
In the year of 2000
At 10:00 a.m.
I checked in to Skid Row Housing
Check all egos at the door
Because here humility comes
My Skid Row family
In spite of their insanity
Shows me undying support
Unlike those lames with my same last names
That said "Your dreams, you should abort"
Not to harp on the past
Because my losses are vast
Before you stands one completely broken
I love you, miss, and I love you, mister
Sincerely yours, a Skid Row sister
[applause]
That was so beautiful.
[Angela] Thank you very much.
It's so important to understand
that not everyone on the street
is a drug addict.
People that I've met
are just having hardships.
Maybe they lost their job.
Maybe they just had a bad circumstance.
There's so many different stories,
and I think that's just...
the most important thing
is to get people off Skid Row.
Alexandria House is really helping me
with my life.
So I'm totally happy, but, you know,
I'm still homeless,
but I'm trying so hard.
And also, when I... Um...
Especially when I had my breast cancer,
I cannot... I cannot know what I'm doing.
-Don't cry.
-Thank you, Ms. Kim.
[Siti sobbing]
Thank you so much.
[Siti sniffles]
We appreciate everything that you did
to make this happen
and also, really count on you to spread
the word on this issue of homelessness.
We appreciate you doing that.
I just want to say
thank you for having me.
And I know this is, like, a lot
to share your stories,
and I think it'll help so many people
just put a different face on homelessness,
'cause I think that so many people
just have such an idea
of what that looks like,
and it's really so different.
And so many people that are
just a paycheck away from being homeless.
So I appreciate you guys
for sharing your stories with us.
And, you know, today,
I just wanted to pamper you guys.
We have people inside that are gonna
talk to you about money management
and things that I wish they taught
in high school and in schools
that they just never really teach you,
and women in there
to help you write résumés for jobs.
It's just a pampering day
because you guys
really all deserve it so much.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
There's so many organizations,
but the epidemic
is just growing so much that...
you know, every organization
just needs more resources.
[woman] So what we're gonna end up doing
is moving work experience to the top.
This is our after-school program
and we have a day care
in this building, also,
on this floor in the bottom floor.
I mean, the problem is just so big
that it's not gonna take, you know,
just one person saying
they want to make a difference.
It's gonna take, like, the whole city
and the country coming together
to fix this huge issue.
[woman] All right, one, two, three.
[Kim] Next on...
-Oh, my God!
-[dog barks]
-[Kim] She sleeps with the dogs.
-Kim, yours really makes a lot of noise.
Kourtney's does not bark.
I want to go swap.
[Kourtney] Give me my dog.
[Kim] Guess who this is.
I literally, once a week, have a stalker.
I want to protect myself.
I'm not comfortable with it.
I wouldn't want my kids around it.
I wouldn't want the kids here,
and I know there's a gun.
I want to feel comfortable around a gun.