[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] Want to look around?
Tell me if you like anything.
[Khloé groans]
-Are these all vintage?
-[Sarah] Yeah.
Hold on.
This isn't really my thing.
-This Bruce Springsteen is cute for you.
-[line ringing]
Look. Journey.
[line ringing]
-[Tristan] What's up, babe?
-[Khloé] I need your assistance, babe.
[Tristan] What you need, girl?
[Khloé] Look.
I don't know any of these things.
[Tristan] You should do Guns N' Roses,
Metallica, Kiss...
[Khloé] Oh, my god,
I don't know who the [bleep].
-Oh, sorry. David Gilmour is...
-[Penelope] You said a bad word.
-She did.
-Okay, I'll give you a dollar.
-You owe me a dollar!
-[Khloé] I'll give you a dollar.
-What about Styx?
-[Tristan] Oh, that's...
-Who's this?
-[Sarah] The Steve Miller Band.
[Khloé] I love Steve Miller.
I have no idea who Steve Miller is.
[Tristan] You have no idea
who Steve Miller is?
You're so passionate about this.
-[Tristan] How much are they?
-[Khloé] I don't know.
How much could a vintage shirt be?
A hundred and forty dollars for a T-shirt?
[Tristan] A hundred and forty,
not bad, yeah.
Take mad pictures for me.
No, can't you... Oh, [bleep].
[Tristan] Let me see
where all the good ones are.
[Khloé] Okay, I love you.
You're not helping me, babe, but...
[Tristan] No, 'cause I wanna see
what else they got...
[Khloé] Okay, babe. Love you.
[Tristan] Have yourselves a good day.
Love you.
I can't wait for your text messages
to come with pictures.
-Okay, me too.
-[Tristan] All right, babe.
[Khloé] Bye, babe.
I can't handle vintage shopping.
It's too stressful.
[theme music]
[birds chirping]
[Kourtney] Hi, guys.
[Khloé] Oh, hey, Kourt.
Oh, my god! You look so cute.
[Kim] You look so tiny.
Yeah, you're so tiny.
[Khloé] Kourt, your arms and everything.
My arms?
I felt like my arms were so large
and in charge.
[Khloé] This big. This big.
Let me see. No, let me see.
-It's basically that big.
-No, but...
Joe's been doing the craziest arms on me.
[Khloé] Like what?
[Kourtney] Just crazy.
[phone chiming]
-[chiming continues]
-"Simon."
[Kourtney] Hi, Simon.
[Simon] Hello.
What's cooking?
[Kourtney] I'm just at Khloé's.
We're hanging out and Kim's here.
-Hey.
-[Simon] Hell to the lo.
[Khloé] Hello!
Are you excited?
I'm so... I haven't even started packing,
but it is literally 100 degrees there
every day.
[Kourtney] No, I think it's, like, 115.
-Wait, you're going on another trip?
-[Kourtney] Yes.
Where?
[Kourtney] To Egypt.
[gasps]
Kim is so jealous.
No, you have no idea,
that's, like, my dream...
That's, like, on my bucket list.
[Khloé] With your kids?
[Kourtney] No. Sadly.
Is, um, is Younes excited?
[Kourtney] Yeah.
I can't wait. I need to text him
and find out what he's bringing.
I was gonna say, are you doing,
like, Indiana Jones vibes?
Or are you gonna do, like...
Oh, I'm going full Cleopatra.
I'm going big.
[Simon laughing]
-Um, all right, I will call you later.
-Okay.
And I'm gonna send you
some outfit inspirations,
so you can see my vibes.
-Okay. Okay, perfect.
-Okay.
-Okay, bye.
-Okay, bye, guys.
So, what's the plan for the kids
while you're gone?
Well, I'm gonna make a thorough plan
so that every day is scheduled,
but lots of activities and I was thinking
maybe Mason could sleep here,
like, two of the nights.
-[Khloé] Yeah. We have fun together.
-'Cause we know he has a great time.
Kim, Penelope said she would like
to stay with you the entire time.
-[Khloé laughs]
-[Kim] Okay. I'm down.
[Khloé] I'm really proud of you.
I'm proud that you're... like,
doing something for yourself,
and you're just, like, YOLO.
I've come a long way.
There was a time when I wouldn't even
-sleep out for one night.
-Think about it. Mm-hmm.
Because it's a new relationship
where I'm not ready to mix the two worlds,
going on a trip and going out of town
is, like, the easiest way
to keep my two worlds separate right now.
[Khloé] Me and Mase will have,
you know, older kid time.
I'm just, like, his age basically.
Tristan will be here.
[Khloé] We'll be fine.
You got a lot of Cs on today.
Can you shut the [bleep] up?
-I didn't even...
-[Kourtney] Champion, Chanel.
[Khloé] I'm at home.
-Okay.
-[Khloé] What's wrong with you?
-You're just a nitpicker. What?
-There's a lot. A lot wrong with me.
[Khloé] You're just a picker.
Well, this has been super exciting.
[upbeat music]
Look, you have purple flowers.
I want purple flowers.
[birds chirping]
[Khloé] This little chair?
These are what you chose to have
next to these big couches?
[Khloé] These little itty-bitty chairs?
Who are they for? North?
They're not that small.
What? All right.
[Kim] Did you see how I just, like,
went off on Rob in our group text?
I couldn't take it.
Listen, there's a plus and a minus.
One of the plus of all this,
there's no way Rob and Chyna
could get back together after this, right?
[Kim] Totally.
-Let's focus on the positive.
-[Kim] Yeah.
The negative is
all of this other [bleep] right now.
The negative is just that, like,
as Rob having sisters,
he should just know better
-and he could've just, like...
-Totally.
...he should've, just, like,
controlled himself.
So, Rob and Chyna
have officially broken up,
but they obviously still have
to communicate
for the custody of Dream.
But, you know what, they're still having
a hard time getting along.
The legal battle that has been going on
between the two of them
has been super frustrating.
[tense music]
I feel like this is escalating to a place
that none of us could have ever imagined.
[Khloé] But it just sucks.
Like, he is made out to this bad guy
when she's taunting him.
[Khloé] Like, love makes you do
[bleep] up things.
Do you think anyone's proud of that? No.
[Khloé] You don't [bleep]
with someone's heart and emotions.
[Kim] Yeah.
[Khloé] Kim!
[laughing]
Wanna come down here with me?
What are you doing?
Going down.
Do you want to go on my kayak? Yes or no?
So not funny.
[Khloé] All right.
[upbeat music]
[phone ringing]
Hi, Kylie.
[Kylie] Something crazy is happening.
What?
-You know the girl that works for me?
-Yeah.
So, I'm sitting in the kitchen
talking to Vic and I look over
and the girl that works for me
is taking photos of me.
What?
[tense music]
[Kris] I really feel bad for Kylie
because there's always somebody that's
trying to exploit a certain situation.
And to have somebody in her own home
trying to snap pictures
they shouldn't be snapping,
is really, really stressful.
[Kris] Do... Should we have her arrested?
Where's your security?
Where... where is she?
[Kris] You want to be able to trust
the people that you're surrounded by,
but you really... I mean, we have
to really be on alert at all times.
And that's extremely upsetting
-when you can't feel like...
-It's so crazy.
...you can be in your own bathroom
or your own bedroom.
I just... This day.
[laughs]
Uh...
[sighs]
Um...
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] I don't think it's good for me
to be out in the sun.
-[Khloé] Why?
-So...
-Do you wanna sit under there?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
I just can't sit out here and melt away.
[Khloé] Do you know what's going on
with Rob with custody?
[Kourtney] I don't know.
[Khloé] Me neither.
I should call and ask him.
Um, I like these little... pots.
-Thank you.
-[line ringing]
-[Rob] Yo.
-[Khloé] Hey, Bob.
I'm with Kourt. What are you doing?
Just at my house, about to shower.
Hey, Bob.
Is Dream coming over today?
[Rob] Hey, Kourt.
Yeah, she's going to Kourtney's house,
and then after,
she's going to stop by your house.
Okay.
Um... What's going on with, like,
your custody with her?
[Rob] Nothing's going on.
[Khloé] Nothing happened from that day?
[Rob] No. After, like,
an eight-hour mediation day
of nothing being resolved.
Well, that's crazy,
and I'm sorry you have to go through that.
[dramatic music]
I know this is super hard for Rob
because he was so in love with that girl,
and this is definitely not the way
he thought his relationship was gonna end.
Unfortunately, this has been really hard
on my mom as well.
You know, she loves her kids
with everything that she has.
So, any stress or burden
that any of us have,
she carries it on times ten.
-I'm sorry, Rob.
-[Rob] It's okay.
[Khloé] Well, as long as Dream's okay.
[Rob] Hold on. Hrush is calling me.
I gotta go to the Armenian deli.
I'll call you back.
-[Kourtney] Okay, bye.
-Bye.
All right, you know what?
What, Kourt?
You with the furry slide?
-[Kourtney] I never could've dreamt it.
-[Khloé laughs]
Listen. You with the [bleep]...
[Kourtney chuckles]
Body outfit on?
[Khloé] Yeah, like, where the [bleep]
are you going?
[upbeat music]
Here, Reign, go under the tunnel.
[Penelope] Reign, go under the tunnel!
[Khloé] Turn it around.
Reign, go. Go in there.
[scoffs]
Show him.
[Khloé] Reign, look!
Like that. Come.
[Khloé] All right.
[Kourtney] I'm having second thoughts
about going now.
-[Khloé] Why?
-Come on down.
[Kourtney] I want to put the kids to bed.
-Reignoosh!
-Yeah, but they're just gonna go to bed.
-Thank you.
-[Khloé] Ah, she went through on her own.
Yeah, but bedtime
is one of my favorite times.
Like...
-doing lullabies.
-[Khloé] Kourt.
-Putting on the night light.
-It's one night.
[Khloé] I think you need
to enjoy yourself.
It's just church.
[Khloé] The kids are with me.
It's not that big of a deal.
I try to go to church once a week,
and that's one of the things
that I do for myself,
but I don't like missing, you know,
bedtime and bath time
and all the special moments.
Like, I try to be there as much as I can.
I just feel like,
because I'm leaving town,
I really just don't know
if I should be going tonight.
[Khloé] Cut the cord, Kourt. Right, Mase?
Tell her to cut the cord.
-Are you gonna be okay?
-[Khloé] He's like, "Duh."
Why, for sure.
[somber music]
[gibberish]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Mom, you look so cute.
Look at you.
Do I look like I have any lipstick on?
Are you wearing, like, a nude lip?
-There's a mirror right behind you.
-[Kris] Oh.
I'm so tired, I can't...
Yeah, I need a little color.
I just don't even know what to do.
-So, what's up, guys?
-Sit down, stay for a while.
[Kris] Mm-hmm.
I've got kids with problems.
I can't stay anywhere
for more than five minutes.
-[Kris] Right, Gabbana?
-[Khloé] What kid has a problem now?
-[Kris] Oh, all of you. It's just wild.
-I don't have a problem.
Swear to God,
I'm gonna lock myself in a funny farm.
[Khloé] I haven't had a problem,
I think, in a minute.
Thank God.
-[Kris] Is that better? Is that... I can't.
-[Khloé] Yeah.
[Kris] This mirror's a little fuzzy.
-It's either that, or my... Oh.
-It's an antique mirror.
Like, I thought it was my eyesight.
[Khloé] No, it's an antique mirror.
Thank God.
"The mirror's fuzzy."
So... you know, there's just a lot going on.
It's Rob and the whole custody thing,
and... just settling,
and it's just wild, wild.
You're just stressed out.
It's stressful
because at the end of the day,
you know, I'm trying
to help him navigate this
because he's never gone through
anything like this before.
I mean, I totally get that
it feels like it's pouring,
and all this [bleep] is happening,
but you can't let it consume you,
and you got to just, like,
smile and still enjoy life.
Like, you can't let these things
just ruin your day
or make you feel this overwhelmed
and stressed out.
Yeah.
[Khloé] Got to laugh a little.
[feigned soft laugh]
[laughs]
Right now, it doesn't feel funny.
It just feels like...
No, you don't have to think some...
You don't think that's funny.
Like, that's serious,
-but, like, we got to... move on.
-[phone ringing]
Hello.
[Khloé hums]
[Kris] What's going on?
[tense music]
Oh, [bleep]. Okay, I'll be right there.
-All right, Khloé, I'm sorry.
-[Khloé] Are you okay?
[Kris] I got to go.
-Are you okay?
-[Kris] No.
I know that my mom
is under so much pressure
and I feel like
there's so much on her plate.
And I could tell that she's slowly
cracking and crumbling.
She just doesn't know how
to filter through all this bull[bleep].
Well, can I help you with anything?
[upbeat music]
My mom has a crazy, wild sense of humor.
She's just hysterical.
She's the life of the party.
[whoops]
Mom.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
[laughing]
[Khloé] I feel like, lately,
she's all about business.
What does she have to do?
She's in, she's out.
Like, everything's super serious
and a little more dark,
and I just want her to get back
to her old awesome self.
-[Kourtney] Honey Bun Buns.
-[Khloé] You're free!
I know you don't watch a lot of TV,
but do you ever watch, like, prank shows?
Prank shows? No.
-Just, like...
-You know I don't watch television at all.
-Well, anyway.
-I don't.
I watched this show. It's a prank show.
It's called Impractical Jokers,
and it's, like, these four guys
who've been, like, best friends forever.
The premise of the show is, they basically
have to, like, humiliate each other.
-So, anyway, one of the punishments was...
-[Kourtney] Honey?
...that this guy had to be handcuffed
to a mime for 24 hours,
and I just thought, what an obnoxious,
fabulous prank is this to do to Mom.
-[Kourtney] Get a mime?
-[mumbles]
The mime.
I want this...
I've never seen a mime...
-You want the same mime from the show?
-...be this legendary. Yes.
I've already reached out to his manager,
and he's so down for this.
He doesn't speak on the phone,
only through management.
Love him even more.
And he's so excited
to have a fun day with my mom.
And hopefully, he could break her
out of her stiff funk.
Don't tell her the plan.
No, you moron,
we're showing up with the mime.
Oh, what... I think you should just, like,
say we're having dinner
and we have a special guest
that we want her to meet.
And then just handcuff them?
But what? Is she gonna...
Why would she agree to have a mime...
She's not gonna agree. We just do it.
When would she agree to any of this?
-She takes herself too seriously.
-So, what, do we say
there's a guest at the door?
We got to figure that part out.
We're just gonna be like,
"Yo, you take yourself so seriously,
and, like, let's have fun."
I think this is just...
I mean, she'll definitely kill us.
Well, whoever's affiliated.
Me, most likely.
[Khloé] It's just, like, fun
to [bleep] with her.
Oh, yeah.
-[Kourtney] My guard dog.
-[barking]
[Khloé] Get it, Honey.
[upbeat music]
[high-pitched]
Love you, Mom.
Love you, too, Kimmy.
I don't know.
[Khloé] Oh, my gosh.
You just wanna be free!
[Khloé] Oh, she's such a cute dog.
[phone chiming]
[Kourtney] Chonch.
-[Cici] Hi! How are you?
-[Kourtney] Hi!
-Hi! What are you doing?
-[Kourtney] I'm sitting here with Khloé.
-How are you?
-[Khloé] I'm good. How are you?
[Kourtney] How are you feeling?
Mm, better, thank you.
[Kourtney] Good.
So, what's new?
[Kourtney] I'm going on a trip.
Okay. Where?
[Kourtney] To Egypt.
Okay. Would the kids go on the trip?
No, I was just gonna go
with Simon and my friends.
-Well, for how long?
-For, like, seven days.
That's a long time.
Yeah. It is.
You don't want them to always think
you're getting up and going.
No. Especially since I didn't
for so long, you know?
Right. But that's probably what,
you know, helps them keep grounded,
is that you are there.
And even though you work
and they know that,
you know, you're there.
But when you're not there, it's a void.
And you don't want them,
at a young age, to feel a void.
Yeah.
You know, our greatest gift
is our stability from our family
is our togetherness and the presence
-that gives us our strength.
-And I think it's frustrating to me
to have my co-parenting partner
who's not, like, you know, fully reliable.
Yeah, no, of course, it is,
'cause your children,
you know, are the most important things
in your life.
Uh, I think you should stay at home.
I already feel like
I'm having separation anxiety
when it comes to leaving my kids,
and Cici is making the situation worse.
All right. Well...
[Cici] Keep me posted.
Okay. I'll call you later.
-Okay. Love you.
-[Kourtney] Love you, bye.
-Bye, Khlo. Love you.
-Bye. Love you.
[upbeat music]
-[Kourtney] Hi!
-[Kendall] Hi!
[Kourtney] Here, let me just show.
Look, for my lip kit.
The package would be this little box.
And it has... one of our colors
is, like, a true, true red,
not orangy red, like, a good fall red.
And it's red kisses all over it,
but they're wet-looking.
-Is that cute?
-Yeah.
It's really the only option
for right now if I want to do it.
-Listen, listen, listen!
-What?
So, I need you to stay here,
and you can't leave the kitchen.
-[Khloé] Stay with Kylie and Kourtney.
-[Kris] Why?
-'Cause I said. You got to do me a favor.
-[Kris] Okay.
[quirky music]
[Khloé gasps]
Pierre, come here.
I'm so excited.
I know you can't talk to me.
Ooh, thank you.
[Khloé laughs]
Being handcuffed to this mime
is exactly what my mom needs to get going.
I think this is a pretty genius idea.
Mommy, this is your friend, Pierre.
[Kris] Oh! Hi...
[laughs]
-What? What?
-[Khloé] Come here, Pierre.
[Kris] Hi, Pierre. How are you?
-This is Pierre.
-Who's Pierre?
What's this?
[Khloé] This is a fun little bracelet
that I got you.
-Do not take it off for now. No, no.
-I don't like how it is starting to feel.
What's going on, Pierre?
Oh, so cute.
Wait, what's up? Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to be chained to anybody.
-Mom, it's just for a second.
-Okay.
-It's just for fun. Enjoy your life.
-[Khloé] It's little Pierre.
-Okay, I'm starting to sweat.
-Live in the moment.
-Okay.
-[Khloé] Ooh!
Don't you feel good, Pierre?
What's going...
So, I met Pierre on a TV show
called Impractical Jokers,
and he was chained to someone
for 24 hours.
Yeah.
So, Pierre doesn't talk or anything.
He's fine.
[Khloé] Look, he's talking to you.
Here, it's... it's his friend.
Hello. I'll call you back later.
-Yeah. Just really busy.
-[line ringing]
Look at our friend, Pierre.
[Kim] Oh, hi!
You're talking to the clown guy!
He's not a clown.
Look how mad he is!
[Kim] Oh, he's mad at me, Northie.
I think he's called a meme.
A mime, not a meme!
Oh, my gosh, Northie!
-It's a mi... a mime?
-[Khloé] A mime.
-We wish you were here.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-Stop it.
-[Khloé] Okay. Love you. Bye.
Let's go make a martini.
Come to the bar.
Mom, come on.
-I don't want any alcohol.
-Yes, you do.
Matthew.
[laughing]
-What is Matthew gonna do to you?
-[Kris] I don't know.
And I have the only key.
Oh, my god.
-You guys, I'm gonna kill you.
-Hey, Mom, make a martini for Pierre.
-No, I don't want to make a martini.
-Yes, I need to see you do things.
-[Kris] Khloé.
-[Khloé] Okay.
What... No, thank you. I'm trying to quit.
Let's open the vodka.
[indistinct chatter]
-[laughing]
-[Kris] Oh, my god, help me.
-[Khloé] Take him to the party tonight.
-[Kourtney] What party are you going to?
Victoria Jackson's birthday party.
-Oh...
-[Khloé] Mom, he's...
Oh, look at him. He's so excited.
All right, Pierre.
You could shake this up.
You shake it. He's not your assistant.
[laughing]
-[Kris] There we go.
-[Khloé] Only one?
[Kris] We're sharing.
Oh, look at us.
Aw!
-[Khloé] You guys are so cute.
-[Kourtney] So, cute.
[Khloé laughing]
-[Kris] I really have to pee.
-[Khloé] Okay.
[Kris] Come on, Pierre.
-I love you.
-[Kris] Mm-hmm.
You have to come with me.
[Khloé] Okay. Wait, you're afraid
to have him alone?
-[Kris] All right.
-[laughs]
Okay. Okay.
Come over here.
-[Kris] Okay.
-[Khloé] You're fine right there.
-[knocking on door]
-[Kris] Okay, no.
He's not coming in.
[laughs]
[Khloé] Mom, are you taking
a deuce in there?
[Kris] I'm just peeing.
I can't even get the toilet paper.
That's not toilet paper.
-[Kris] Oh, man.
-[Khloé] What's happening in there?
[Kris] It's just all over the place.
[Khloé] I don't think my mom knows
what is going on at all.
My mom's frustrated,
but she'll get over it.
You can't help
but fall in love with Pierre.
I mean, I love Pierre.
-[toilet flushes]
-[Khloé] Yay!
[Kris] Okay. All right. Let's go.
I'm so sorry, Pierre.
[Kris laughs]
[Khloé] I'm probably gonna leave
'cause I have a few things to do.
[Kris] Wait, leave? Where's the key?
[Khloé] The key I flushed down the toilet.
-Yeah, Mom.
-[Kris] No.
-[Khloé] I just feel like sometimes...
-No.
...you're so uptight.
Let's just have fun.
Remember, this is all the beauty of life.
[Khloé] Right?
-[laughing]
-What is that?
-Okay.
-[Khloé] Bye, Mom.
-Oh, my god.
-[Khloé] Have fun.
-All right. Where's the key?
-[door closes]
I know Khloé wants me to lighten up
and I get what she's trying to do,
but I don't think she understands
how packed my day is.
You're a good sport.
I would not have done that.
No.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Here we go.
Off to the market.
[music stops]
No.
[laughs]
You're, like, mischievous.
[upbeat music]
[groans]
I don't have time
to play with the mime today.
Yeah, I don't know
where she came up with this idea.
[Kris] We're here. Yay!
Hi, P.
Let's go find some snacks.
[playful music]
[Kris] Nope, nope, no. Don't you dare.
Don't you dare.
Don't you...
[laughs]
[Kourtney] Have you ever talked this much
with someone
-who doesn't talk back?
-[Kris] No, I'm exhausted.
[Kourtney] Do you want to get this?
[Kris] Oh, no, that's good. We're good.
We're good. Did you break that?
No. No. No. Stop that.
Ooh! I almost got my head taken off.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
-[Penelope] Lovey.
-[Kris chuckles]
[laughing]
Kourtney, will you go put this back?
[Kris laughs]
Stop it.
[line ringing]
Khloé, answer the phone.
Oh, my god.
We're gonna get kicked out of the market.
-[Kourtney] Who are you calling?
-[Kris] Khloé. I want my key.
-[Kourtney] She has it?
-[Kris] Yeah, but...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
[Kris] No, no, no.
No, no, that's not for sale.
[Kris] It's called a ladder.
[laughing]
Oh, my god.
[Kourtney]
He's balancing that on his head.
P, help me.
[Kris laughing]
[Kourtney] How does he know
how to do that?
[Kris] That was very good.
[claps]
Very good. No, we don't want to take it.
Please, just behave for 15 minutes
until we can get out of here.
Fifteen. Give me fifteen minutes
of good behavior,
and I will buy you a Popsicle.
Come on.
[upbeat music]
-[Penelope] Lovey!
-Oh. What?
[Penelope] He opened those!
I know. He likes white gloves.
It's his thing.
[Kris] I just had to surrender.
Pierre was never going to give up.
He has more energy
than you can ever imagine,
and he wasn't getting tired anytime soon.
-[Kris] Hi.
-[clerk] Hi, how are you?
[Kris] Good, how are you?
Okay, we... we have that.
We have...
You know, we don't want that.
Okay, you have to get off
the basket for a second.
-[Kris] Take those.
-[Kourtney] Mom, do you need this?
[Kris] Yeah. Do we have one of those,
uh, blue collagen tubs?
-[clerk] Yeah, we do.
-Okay, no, no, no, no.
[Kris] No. No. Get down right now.
This is... You are gonna be
in so much trouble. Get down.
[Kris] Kourtney, tell him to get down.
Okay, come on.
Get off the counter.
Okay, no, no, no, no.
No, get down.
Get down right now. I...
Where's Khloé with my key?
[Kris] Thank you so much.
Here's your gloves.
Put your gloves on. Let's go. Come on.
-Have a good day, guys.
-[Kris] Thank you.
[line ringing]
[Kris] Khloé. I want my key.
I'm exhausted.
Thank you.
[Kris groans]
Wild!
Put your... Stop it.
[Kris] Put your seat belt on.
I literally need to take a shower
after that.
[laughing]
[Kris laughs]
-[Kris] Jenna.
-[Jenna] Yes?
[Kris] Can you bring me some scissors?
[quirky music]
-Can you see if you can cut this?
-There is no way.
Cut this.
[soft chuckle]
How about...
No. He's gonna steal.
You cannot steal the scissors.
What are you doing?
[Jenna] Oh.
[Kris laughing]
[laughing continues]
Now, I feel kind of bad.
It's okay.
[laughing]
[somber music]
It's...
Okay, here's your...
Here's your little thing.
Okay.
I don't... I didn't mean
to hurt your feelings.
It's just that I have to go.
Okay?
[Kris] By the end of the day,
I... I've got to say,
it was really fun.
It was the best remedy for stress?
I've never laughed so hard
in my whole life.
It was nice to meet you.
Okay? I wanna... Oh.
Oh.
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
[upbeat music]
So, I think we're done with the thing.
She's gonna sign whatever
the family law agreement,
so for custody and...
-Good. What's the...
-...payments and stuff like that.
So I'll just be glad
when this is behind him.
Him and I had a really good talk,
I mean, just in general about everything,
and just where he wants to,
like, see his life.
[Khloé] With Rob, when he loves,
he loves hard.
Yeah.
He would kind of do anything for her.
A hundred percent.
A lot of us are impulsive
when we do things,
and especially out of, like,
love and jealousy.
[Khloé] We've all been there.
He knows it was wrong, what he's done.
I think he's learned
a lot of lessons from this.
Even though this has been a rollercoaster,
I'm really proud of Rob for being able
to handle all of this really maturely.
[Khloé] Now that the custody is settled,
Rob can start fresh and move on from this.
Rob is definitely an awesome dad to Dream,
and I hope he just takes
these life experiences
and becomes better and better
as he gets older.
I'm sure this will be a weight lifted off
of his shoulders
once these papers are signed.
Um, just the end to a really bad chapter.
Well, it could only get better
from here, right?
[Kris] That's right. Yay.
-So, Pierre... he's really funny.
-You didn't love him?
Oh, I'm to... I am kind of
have a crush on Pierre.
Is he not amazing?
He's life.
No, seriously,
you'll never forget that day.
-Uh, no, I won't.
-[Khloé] No.
And I'll never, ever find something
that's enough to repay you,
or thank you for that.
I could only imagine.
[laughs]
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] Penelope!
Yeah.
-[Kourtney] There she is.
-[Larsa] Hey.
-[Kourtney] Is there money in here?
-Yeah.
Oh, am I gonna be rich?
It's heavy.
[Kourtney] Ooh, my goodness!
-This is all your money?
-[Penelope] Mm-hmm.
Wow.
[Larsa] Well, P, you've been saving up.
You've been saving.
[Penelope] Mm-hmm.
Um... So, I think I'm gonna flake
on dinner tonight.
You flaked on dinner last night.
-I flaked on you all week, but...
-[Larsa] I know.
[Kourtney]
I just want to hang out with the kids.
Why... Wait, why are you changing your mind?
I'm tired, but I also get,
like, mom guilt.
Like, I was talking to Cici,
and I was telling her,
like, I might leave town.
She was like, "You can't go away again.
Like, when you're a parent, you have to be
a parent, and that's your first priority."
But I feel like your kids are good.
You're with them all day.
And your kids don't go to camp.
Like, you're the camp counselor all day.
[Kourtney] Yeah. But after talking to her,
she was, like, re-instilling,
like, the mom guilt.
[Larsa] I think every mom feels guilt
at some point.
Of course, there are gonna be
some bumps along the road,
like you're feeling now.
It's, like, a lot to balance, like, work,
being a mom, and being social.
[Larsa] It is.
But I feel like you have to, like...
You have to live and be present,
you know what I mean?
[Kourtney] I have realized in life
that I need the balance.
-That's what it is managing your time.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
Spend quality time with them
and be present when you're with them,
and then you won't feel guilty
when you're not.
It is hard to balance being
in a relationship, work, and my children.
I just think that it's really important
for me to be there for them,
and... even though, like, I want to go away
and travel and do things for myself,
it's hard to find the balance
of allowing myself to do that
and not feel guilty.
[Larsa] You can't listen to Cici.
You got to listen to someone like me,
who's got four kids
and everything going on.
[Kourtney] Yeah.
[upbeat music]
Why are you gonna have
your shirt on today?
It's more motivating for me
when you don't.
We could start with the shirt on.
And when we get a little hot, you know...
[Khloé] Take it off.
I like it off.
Be like your personal, like,
workout stripper.
[Khloé] Mm-hmm.
[Rob] What's up, bro?
[Tristan] What up? What's up?
-Yo, you knocked out early.
-[Rob] I know.
[Tristan] You went to sleep early.
[Rob] I left the house at, like, 5:30.
[Tristan] What time was the appointment?
[Rob] Uh, 7:30, I had to be there,
-but... it's fine.
-[Tristan] Yeah.
[Rob] It's just annoying.
[Khloé] What is that appointment for?
[Rob] Uh, just a checkup
to do blood work and stuff.
I'm happy you're doing that.
That's really positive.
[Rob] Yeah. If you don't see the doctor,
you can't get medicine.
Insulin?
[Rob] And then I start to feel [bleep].
But one day, you could stop taking it?
[Rob] Yeah, I just got to be on it,
work out, eat well,
and that [bleep] will go away.
I am so proud of Rob,
and I really hope
he can just take our talk
and put everything into action
and just focus on bettering himself.
[Khloé] And, hopefully,
everything else will just fall into place.
Rob has always been super sensitive
and emotional,
and I know this entire experience
has been really hard on him.
But just, like, seeing him with Dream
and seeing him be such a great dad,
I really just hope he stays
on this path right now.
-[Joe] Oh, you gonna take a chill route?
-[Rob] Yeah.
[Joe] Okay, circuits.
First part the quad report.
Thirty seconds three more times.
-And then 40 seconds...
-And then a minute.
Ready? Two, one.
[upbeat music]
Yeah, hit it, hit it. Two, one, end.
-[Joe] And five seconds.
-Oh, yeah, babe.
Take it off.
[Joe] And go. Reverse hamstring here.
One, ten.
[woman] Khloé, how do you feel?
[shoes squeaking]
[birds chirping]
[classical music]
Oh!
[laughing]
[Khloé] Oh, my god.
[playful music]
Whoa!
[Khloé] You want me to get up?
[Khloé grunts]
Come in, Pepe.
Hi!
Bonjour.
Yay! I love being handcuffed to you.
Okay, don't touch my hair too much.
Who did your makeup? It's so pretty.
Hm? You did?
[Khloé] So, are you gonna entertain me
for hours?
Okay. I don't know what you want to do.
Upstairs?
My mom looks [bleep] awesome as a mime.
[Khloé] I love this.
She should be a mime more often.
[Khloé] If this is my mom
trying to get back at me,
then, honey, you got to try harder.
Handcuff yourself to me all day long
'cause I love me a double dose
of Kris Jenner.
[Khloé] Hold on. Let's show Tristan.
Babe, look at this.
-Oh, my god.
-[Khloé laughing]
[Tristan laughs]
Oh, my gosh.
What?
[knocking on door]
Hold on.
That's your mom?
-Oh.
-[Khloé] This is my mom.
Oh, sh... I... Oh, my god. I thought it was...
-[Tristan] I thought it... I kept looking.
-Who'd you... think this was?
I was like, "Hold on. Looks familiar."
And then you saw her ass
and knew it was her?
I mean, it runs in the family.
[Kris laughs]
You can't laugh.
[laughs]
That was epic.
Oh, my gosh.
[Khloé] Why didn't you get me
long handcuffs, like I got you?
There you go.
Mom, this is really your look.
I think you should do this all the time.
Oh, where are you going?
You have to pee?
[quirky music]
Oh, [bleep].
Are you okay?
[Khloé] It fell.
It broke.
I am so happy to see my mom
as this light, fun Kris Jenner.
This is the Kris Jenner that I know.
So, the next time things get crazy,
pull out that face paint
and your mime costume.
You're good to go.
[Khloé laughs]
Mom, what are you doing?
[Khloé] It looks like you're having sex.
I can't figure it out.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go.
[Khloé] Anyways, this was fun.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Hello.
[Reign] Hi, Lovey.
[Kris] Hi. Oh, it's so dark in here.
Hey! Jeez.
[indistinct chatter]
-[Kris] This is such a great room.
-[Scott] Yeah, it's really cool.
Hi, Reigny. Where's P?
[Scott] Playing with her dolls
in the other room.
Kourtney decided to go to Egypt,
so our entire family is rotating turns
taking care of the kids.
[Kris] Today is Scott's day,
and the kids are with him.
So I'm just gonna check in
and see how they're doing.
[line ringing]
-[Kourtney] Hey, Mom?
-Hi! How are you?
I'm good. How are you?
Good. It must be very late
over there in Egypt.
It's very late.
Oh. I don't even...
I can't even keep up with you.
I just wanted to make sure you were okay
and you're having a good time.
I am having the best time.
Everything,
the pictures look so beautiful.
I can't even imagine what it would be like
to be inside of a pyramid.
So insane.
Right?
I've definitely learned from,
you know, my past relationship,
where I really wouldn't travel
without the kids.
And I think it is important to take time,
especially because my relationship
is important to me,
and just because those worlds
aren't colliding right now,
just making sure
that I make time for both.
And I think going on a trip,
once in a while,
reminds me the importance of being present
and in the moment when I'm home.
And I think it makes me the best mom
that I can be.
[Kourtney] Reigny-Reignoosh.
[gasps]
Yummy.
[Kris] Wait!
P! Here's this one.
Hi, Mom.
[Kourtney] You look so beautiful.
[Penelope] Love you.
I love you guys.
Love you, Kourt.
[Kim] On the next episode...
'Cause I have the biggest earlobes
in the universe.
I have made a decision
to do something about my ears.
[Kris] Oh, my gosh.
Corey was doing anything in his power
to avoid me.
If that energy is out there,
it's not okay with me.
I'm a young dude dating your mom.
Y'all are not my [bleep] kids.
[Tristan] Thank you guys for all coming.
We have an announcement. KoKo?
[overlapping chatter]