[Khloé] Queen of Cleveland!
For the past eight months,
I have been basically bicoastal.
I appreciate how comfortable
he wants me to be.
It's just sad that she's, like,
definitely not coming back anytime soon.
I have such anxiety, just going places.
[Kim] I'm not as, like, open and out there
as I used to be.
[upbeat music]
[Scott] Oh! It is nice out.
-So, my dog's so cute.
-[Scott] Yeah.
-How old is that dog?
-[Khloé] Like, 12.
He's been living the dream.
It's a she.
-[Scott] She has been living the dream.
-Mm-hmm.
-She's had two leg surgeries.
-She's travel a lot.
She's not living,
like, that big of a dream.
Can you... can you not jiggle your butt
when you're talking to me?
[Khloé] First of all, the fact that you
were staring at that...
-I was jiggling my leg.
-I mean, how can I not?
I was trying to get my face out of the sun
and then I glanced over your butt.
[Khloé] That's wild that that's what
you looked at.
I was, literally, out of just like a tic.
It's not a tic. You're literally twerking.
-No. I'm literally shaking my leg.
-[Scott] Are you joking me?
It looks like a vibrator lodged
into your ass right now.
Shut up. That's crazy.
It's not crazy. I'm trying to talk to you.
Your butt's just bouncing around town.
I feel like I'm at a strippy.
-[Scott] I have no cash on me.
-[Khloé] Oh, God.
[theme music]
How beautiful is my country, people!
Oh, this is good.
Oh, yeah.
There she is. The boss is here! The boss.
And I bet you didn't shut the door.
Remember when we had a scorpion
in the house?
-[Kourtney] No.
-I did, a big-ass scorpion.
[Khloé] And my floors are black.
-Remember when I got stung by a scorpion?
-What?
-There's a huge scorpion in the...
-[Kim] I didn't know that.
That's why we got to shut the doors.
[chuckles]
-[Khloé] Well, I have some news.
-[both] What?
-See how I'm building up the suspense?
-[Kim] What? Good news?
-What is it?
-Guess who's coming home, kids?
What? You guys broke up?
-[Khloé] Oh, stop. No!
-Just kidding.
No. Tristan and I will be here
from July to October.
-[Kim] What?
-July to October?
-[Kourtney] Three months.
-That's good,
'cause you live there most of the time,
so he can like then live where you live
-the other time.
-[Khloé] He was like, "I...
-want to, like, be with your family more."
-That's fair.
[Khloé] And like, he like, really wants
to, like, hang out with all of us more.
We're gonna be here,
but we also want a house in the city.
That's cool.
[Khloé] I love that Tristan was like,
"I want to be there this summer."
We're always in Cleveland and he...
not that he...
Like, he literally can't come here
and hang out with you guys.
He's like, "I want to be a part
of your family and do stuff as a group."
-Aren't you guys excited?
-[Kim] Yes!
Tristan and I were thinking about staying
in Cleveland for the summer,
but you know, we talked about it,
and we actually want to come to LA.
It's so nice. I've never had a guy,
like, want our families to blend before.
So Tristan and I
want to find a place in the city,
because Tristan does
two-a-day practices at UCLA.
[Khloé] And trust me,
nobody in LA wants to sit in traffic
for over two hours every single day.
Tristan has always gone out of his way
to make me feel at home,
and in Cleveland,
he's gone above and beyond.
So in LA, I want to do the same for him.
What if I jump from this one to that one?
Why are you sitting with your heels
in my couch, like this is a club?
I was gonna try to jump
from this one to that one.
[Khloé] No, you're not.
-On a stone table?
-[Kourtney] Have you ever poked a hole
-in a club with your heel?
-[Khloé] All the time.
No, you're going to poke a hole.
Oh, my god.
Oh, [bleep], I poked a hole.
I'm just kidding. Ha-ha. Gotcha!
[Kim laughs maniacally]
[Kim] Welcome home.
Okay, guys, I have to do 20 sprints today.
Don't take off my glasses.
Looking at the ocean?
-[Jonathan] Kim, where you at?
-[Kim] I'm here.
-What's up?
-[Kim] Hey.
-What are you doing?
-[Kim] It could be folded in here, though.
[woman] Okay.
[Kim] Um, just going over all this stuff
I have in my closet
that I need to organize and trying to...
[Jonathan] Every time I come here,
you're organizing. Holy crap.
[Kim] You're gonna love
what I've been up to.
You probably think
I've been doing nothing.
No, I don't. What the [bleep]?
-Okay. So, my makeup...
-You're never doing nothing.
-Are you ready to see my makeup?
-Yeah.
So you get a box.
Then this is what my packaging comes in.
-[Jonathan] That's sick!
-[Kim] Gorgeous, right?
-It's like liquid.
-Liquid.
Then, inside is gonna be two sticks.
This color and this is my brush.
Isn't it, like, so pretty? So everything
is just gonna be really pretty nude.
-That's nice.
-Yeah. So that's my whole makeup.
How's Kylie feeling about you being
a makeup mogul as well?
Um, she's really,
like, so supportive of it.
-So cool.
-[Kim] So cool.
I have my makeup line that I'm launching,
KKW Beauty.
And it's so exciting
to do something on my own.
[Kim] I kind of like the darker bag.
-I just think it matches this the best.
-[woman] Mm-hmm.
If you want your single stick, that would
obviously have way more product.
It's only one color.
Basically, for the past almost decade,
my sisters and I have always
had a licensing deal.
[Kim] But going from being a licensee
to an owner is such a big deal,
and it's so much more responsibility.
I feel like this has been
what I've been working for for ten years.
-I love it. Congrats.
-Thanks.
-Exciting.
-Wait, can I post you wearing this jacket?
I don't want to.
You guys, Jonathan stole
my Good American jacket.
This is a guy's jacket. I [bleep] love it.
Well, now it is, but it wasn't.
So, Khlo, your first guys' customer.
-See? I have flowers.
-You love flowers?
[man] You have an awesome face.
[Khloé] Okay, so, basically,
let me tell you.
Malika's dating this guy
who's a football player.
Malika met him with Khadijah.
She has only hung out with him in person
for five days.
-[Khadijah] Yes.
-[Khloé] Okay? And she's tell...
You know how Malika is.
She falls in love like that.
-[Khadijah] Immediately.
-Okay, talk [bleep]
while I'm sitting here.
We're not talking [bleep].
We're just saying the facts.
-That's what you call it.
-[Khloé] And so, whatever.
So he's like, "I don't know if I'm coming
on Friday anymore,
'cause I have a meeting
with my financial advisor."
And I'm, like, thinking you and I,
if we had a meeting with Lester,
-and you see Frenchie...
-We would cancel it.
He just said... He said, "I'm working
on trying to move it to tomorrow."
[Khloé] No, but it's not even working.
My point is, it's so easy to do that.
Whatever. What are you laughing at?
"The quality of your life
is the quality of your relationships."
-It's a Tony Robbins quote.
-Really? I like that.
[Khloé]
I was gonna say, what did you just google?
-You can thank me later.
-[Malika] I got it. I like that.
"The quality of your life
is the quality of your relationships."
Let's chant it together now, shall we?
[all] The quality of your life
is the quality of your relationships.
[all humming]
I've been reading a lot
of Tony Robbins' work lately.
Okay.
And I feel like he's really inspired me
to have a positive outlook on life.
[Khloé] You're not normally like this.
You're usually so negative
and have nothing positive to say.
It's just not cool that you copy me.
Because you're a [bleep] bitch.
I want you guys to know
this is a non-organic banana,
because it is [bleep] hard to open, A.
Ugh! [bleep] A.
[Khloé] For you to be going
from Negative Nancy to Positive Penny
is pretty strange.
I mean, I just prefer to give Malika
some positive encouragement.
It's not what you say.
It's how you say it.
Okay.
[Malika] Do you have any other,
like, positive reinforcement or quotes
you want to share with me?
I'm gonna need it.
Yes. "I have come to believe
that all my past failure and frustration
were actually laying the foundation
for the understandings
that I've created,
the new level of living I now enjoy."
[Malika] Amen.
I feel like all this applies to me
with Scott too, guys.
I'm making a change
and I want you to know.
-Right. All about change.
-Oh, cool.
[Malika] I'm receiving that for you.
[upbeat music]
What the [bleep] is wrong with you?
Take the [bleep] photo.
I can't stop making it rain.
-[Kendall] Can I have some rice and beans?
-[Khloé] Can you have some?
-[Kendall] Mm-hmm.
-[Khloé] Yeah.
[Khloé clears throat]
You're gonna like this.
[gasps]
No, I don't like hot.
-[Khloé] No, it's not gonna be that hot.
-[Kendall] I don't like spicy. At all.
Like, literally, the tiniest bit of spicy
is so uncomfortable.
-You're not your mother's daughter.
-No. I'm not, apparently.
-[Kourtney] Hi!
-[Khloé] Hi!
-[Kendall] Okay, I'm gonna leave.
-[Khloé] No, no.
-[Kourtney] Sit down.
-We never get to see you.
[Kourtney] Never.
[Khloé] You got to sit down with us.
-[Kris] Hi, guys.
-Hey, Mom.
-Hey.
-[Khloé] So, Mom.
I have been trying to find houses
for me and Tristan
to rent this summer, in the city,
and it has been...
'Cause he's gonna come here and yeah,
we have this house, but we want both.
He wants to, you know, hang out.
That's where he works out in the city.
[Kris] There's so many rentals right now.
-It's such a good time to go look.
-[Khloé] No, it's so hard.
That's why I want to help find the rental.
I want to help and just, like,
make things easier for him.
[Kris] I would love to do that.
[Kendall] In the city, there's a lot less
to rent than there is.
[Khloé] And, like,
they charge so much [bleep] money.
-[Kendall] Yeah.
-[Khloé] For anything decent.
I have been looking non-stop
for rental homes,
and time is running out.
I haven't found one thing.
I am so grateful for how Tristan
makes me so comfortable in Cleveland.
I just want the same for Tristan.
What's your price range? Look at this.
-Oh, my goodness.
-Filter.
[Khloé] Oh, my God! That's beautiful!
How'd you find this in two seconds?
-It has a gate. Like, a big gate.
-Ooh.
Kendall, you are, like,
a real estate agent.
[Khloé] I'm throwing
a Fourth of July party, you guys.
-I'm not gonna be in town.
-Yes, I'm not either. Where are you going?
-Where are you guys going?
-France.
-[Kendall] Why are you going?
-Kendall. Obviously, why is she going?
-[Kourtney] Just going to...
-To see her French croissant.
[upbeat music]
-[Kris] Hi, honey.
-[Kim] What are you doing?
[Kris] Oh, just trying to keep up
with all my, um, emails.
[Kim] You're trying to keep up
with the Kardashians?
God, I'm trying. That purse is so good.
Thank you.
It's a Carole Bayer Sager vintage.
-[Kris] Stop.
-She gave me some, yeah.
So, what's going on, honey?
Nothing. I'm just, like, I was in the area
and then I have to go home and pack
for this whole...
New York trip with the Forbes conference,
and everything.
-So exciting. That's a big deal.
-Yeah. It is really exciting.
I am nervous, just because I've been,
like, slowly taking my time to come back.
[Kris] Yeah.
And so this is, like, a serious,
sit-down, major...
interview.
This isn't, you know, I don't know
how something like this could go.
Just if they want to ask me...
crazy questions. I mean, it's, like,
Steve Forbes, you know?
[Kris] Yeah.
[Kim] It's, like, hard for me
to get back out there.
The Forbes Women's Summit
is an amazing gathering
of all business people and entrepreneurs,
and I've been asked to do the main
speaking event with Mr. Steve Forbes.
[Kim] He's the editor-in-chief
of Forbes magazine,
one of the biggest
business magazines in the world.
I think there's a lot of pressure,
especially since everything that you say
can be taken out of context,
or just taken the wrong way,
so I want to be prepared
coming into this talk.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Are you just gonna bring
a suitcase with you now
wherever you go,
and you're not gonna let it go?
No. This was my suitcase from Anguilla.
-And you just got it?
-Oh, yeah, your luggage.
The boys left it in Cleveland,
so I basically went on a deserted island
with one thing, and then just...
You're like Gilligan?
-He had, like, one outfit.
-I think my island was a little better.
[Kourtney] You know, every problem
is the chance to do your best.
Oh, here comes Ms. Sunshine.
Little Miss Sunshine, they call me,
my part of Calabasas.
I'm just saying it was quite annoying
that we're on this trip with everyone,
and only my luggage gets left behind.
Life isn't about waiting
for the storm to pass.
-It's about learning to dance...
-It's about dancing in the rain.
No. Let me finish.
You don't know it. You don't know it.
-Sorry.
-It's about learning to dance in the rain.
[quirky music]
-Let her complain.
-Right.
Won't you, like, get on our bandwagon
here and help her complain?
This is getting it out. It feels good
to complain once in a while.
I feel like all Kourt does is go
from one extreme to another.
Where she used to go to was just
sitting in sorrow and that negativity,
and, yeah, I don't want her to go there,
but being this positive,
that's also a little crazy.
All right, guys. I've had enough
of this negativity for today.
Why would I sit here and just hear
complaint after complaint? So...
So where are you going?
Everyone around you complains.
[Kourtney] No. I'm gonna go surround
myself with positive vibes and love.
-[Khloé] Good for you, Kourt.
-[Kim] Good for you.
-Good for you.
-[Kris] Good on you.
What [bleep] positive pill did she take?
I think we all [bleep] need to take that.
[upbeat music]
I'm so excited to announce, you guys,
that I'm launching KKW Beauty.
[Kim] I really think you guys are gonna
love it. I've worked so hard on this.
So get ready to be contoured.
-Hi.
-Steve Forbes.
-[Kim] So nice to meet you.
-Very nice to meet you.
[Kim] I'm so excited to be doing this.
-Thank you for doing it.
-Yeah, of course.
[Forbes] And, uh, you have
a big announcement today?
Yeah, yeah, you know.
So I was, like, do I do it right before?
Don't I? Do I wait until tomorrow?
But I'm doing a talk show tomorrow,
so I figured, let's give it to Forbes
instead of the talk show.
-KKW Beauty?
-[Kim] Yes. I'm really excited.
I think that this Forbes Summit,
is, like, the perfect place to announce
that I'm launching a makeup line,
so I know it's gonna be so exciting,
and we've been trying to think
of how we're going to do it.
I just feel like I'm here
doing press in New York,
so there's no better time
than now to announce it.
[Forbes] What do you say to those
who downplay, or dismiss your success?
For people to always say crazy,
mean things,
I mean, it definitely does get to me,
but I think that
with the support of my family,
we've always kind of come through
on the other side.
I feel like my whole career has been
leading up to this year of these launches,
to where it's, like,
really authentically me.
So I just really want to focus
on what I'm doing now,
now that I feel like I've found my place,
and just continue to do that.
[Forbes] Thank you for, uh,
sharing your time with us.
-Uh, I think that people have a...
-[Kim] Of course.
...greater appreciation
of, uh, what you've done and are doing.
-Thank you so much.
-Aw, thank you so much.
[indistinct chatter]
[camera shutter clicking]
Um, what would your advice be
to somebody who's just starting out
in their own career?
I would say...
Just push forward and work really hard.
Like, there's...
You cannot deny hard work.
Your mom... Wait a second.
Your mom's not the boss of this now?
-She's not.
-You're the boss.
Don't worry.
She still gets her ten percent.
[laughter]
This year, I'm super excited that just...
I've gone from,
you know, having licensing deals
to being owners of my companies.
-Thank you for coming.
-Thank you for having me, seriously.
It's a pleasure to have you.
Come back any time.
[upbeat music]
See you soon.
-[Khloé] Hey, madre.
-[Kris] Hi, honey.
Ooh.
What are you doing?
[sighs]
Just stressed about the house.
Can you believe that people
show their house with an unmade bed?
This is, like, photographs
of their home with pictures
scotch-taped to the walls.
Honest to God. It's wild.
I made some appointments
to go look at some houses this Sunday.
Can you come with me to help me,
like, narrow this down?
-I can't.
-[Khloé] Why not?
I'm so... I'm swamped. And I have to work.
Yeah, but you told me
to book it on a Sunday.
-You said, "Any Sunday."
-[Kris] I know, but I can't this Sunday.
I could go by myself
and then give you a synopsis
of why I think the winner's the winner.
The winner is the winner.
[chuckles]
Khloé's not very happy with me right now,
because she thinks I'm turning her down
to go house-hunting with her.
But she just doesn't know
that I'm really helping Tristan
plan the surprise party for her.
Wait... you're planning, uh,
like, a surprise birthday, right?
-Yeah. We're gonna do it in LA, just...
-Okay.
Anything you need help with, just tell us.
She's upstairs.
It kills me when my kids are annoyed
or upset with me.
And Khloé's definitely annoyed.
I don't know what to do!
I can't tell her, but at the same time,
I don't want her mad at me.
I'm sorry, Khloé.
Mm-hmm.
How about something that's for sale?
Just call up the people and say,
"Can we live there for three months?"
I don't think when a house is on sale,
I could call and say,
"Hi, can I just stay in your house
for three months?"
Like, I don't think most people do that.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Oh, my gosh.
I'm seeing these photos
from the campaign, the ones that we took,
and people online are saying
that I'm doing blackface.
But I would never in a million years
be disrespectful and do that.
[tense music]
I did a photo shoot for my first launch
of my KKW Beauty Contour Sticks.
And we wanted them really moody.
I was really tan.
[Kim] I wanted to show the contour.
The photos ended up
being a little bit darker than I was.
And there were some people online
saying that I was doing blackface
and the photos were inappropriate.
[Kim] The Internet world is so toxic.
And I feel like people are just waiting
for you to make a mistake,
just to point it out.
What do you do? It's already out.
[tense music]
[Kim] You know what, I'll call Jen.
[line rings]
Hold on, can you hear me?
-Yeah, I can hear you. Hello?
-Hi, hi, sorry, I'm in the car.
So I am seeing online that people
are thinking that I'm doing blackface.
I just think I have to address it,
'cause, like, if I don't,
then it'll turn into,
like, one of those situations
that people think I'm trying to ignore
something serious.
I just don't want it to turn
into this thing instead of the launch
and what we're working so hard to do.
Yeah, I think take the pictures down.
And you want this to be all positive,
all about the product.
And we don't want to get off
on the wrong foot.
Then, we'll just have to explain
that that wasn't your intention.
We'll redo the images.
We'll make sure they're perfect and just
say that it was the lighting of the image
of the photo shoot.
[Kim] Okay. Thank you so much.
Will you call the photographer
and just have them fix it?
-And then get the new images?
-Yeah. I'm gonna call them right now.
-Okay. Thank you so much.
-You're welcome.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
Like, it just sucks,
because it wasn't the intention.
I mean, I get it. I was super tan.
The lighting is really moody,
so I can get why people would say that.
I just don't want to give anyone
a reason to say something negative.
Yeah. For sure.
[dramatic music]
When you're, you know, running [bleep],
you just literally have to own up to it
and you have to change it and fix it
and not, like, hide and not understand.
I fully understood
what people were saying.
But I'm not gonna let this...
ruin all the hard work we put into it
and like, dwell on it.
Let's fix it. Let's move on. I would...
Everyone knows, I think, that I would
never, ever do a photo shoot like that
and I would never disrespect anyone.
I mean, I'm not gonna freak out. I just
want to make sure we, like, handle it.
Let's, like, get it over with. No time
to, like, freak out and make excuses.
-I feel bad, because...
-We just have to move on.
No, we'll have it handled. It'll be fine.
[upbeat music]
[Khadijah] Um, excuse me, missy,
have you worn this yet?
No, someone just sent it.
-[humming]
-[Malika laughs]
[Malika] You look terrible.
[humming continues]
-You're a naughty little thing.
-Aren't you?
[Khadijah] Yay, Tristan.
Um, so now that you're back,
what's the plan when Tristan gets here?
Did he get a place?
Or is he gonna stay here?
Well, of course this is...
Like, his house is, like, my house.
His house is my house there, like...
but we wanted to get a house in the city.
I just have so much going on right now,
like, because the boys are now in town.
Trying to figure this out,
finding a house in the city. It's like...
-okay, I'm just a little...
-Those are your thoughts.
Don't stress yourself out
because this is all things
you are very capable of,
because you've done them 100 times.
[Khloé]
I just want everything to be perfect.
He makes me feel so special
and, like, everything's ours there.
-I want him to feel the same here.
-Khloé, that's what you specialize in.
-[Malika] He's gonna be happy to be here.
-It's just like a lot of anxiety.
[Malika] And it's all gonna pan out.
Because your thoughts go crazy
on things that are yet to come yet.
Just calm your thoughts,
so you can calm yourself.
-Yes, Mama Khadijah.
-Then you can enjoy it too.
No, let's just... I can't do this right now.
I really can't handle this conversation.
No, no, we've really got to stop.
[tense music]
[Kim] Have you seen
what's going on downstairs?
[Laura] No. Is it amazing?
-I want to show you.
-[Laura] Oh, yeah? I can't wait.
-Should we run out real quick. Just see?
-[Laura] Yeah, let's run.
[upbeat music]
[Laura] Oh, my gosh.
So we carpeted the whole downstairs
since it was all stone.
[Laura] Wow, amazing.
So you're gonna be able to stand inside
and it's like this infinity thing,
-where, like, you see a million of you.
-[Laura] I love it.
The concept of my launch party
is I really wanted it in my home,
and I wanted to transform
my whole downstairs
into this, like, KKW Beauty,
like, showroom.
I wanted everyone to feel intimate.
Every room had to be, like,
an Instagrammable moment.
Wow. Well, as a whole,
-but it's, like, it's an experience.
-[Kim] Yeah.
Rachel? Can it just be the same color?
There's so much risk.
There's so much at stake,
and I'm in charge of every last detail.
[Kim] I really want it to be successful.
I really want it to do well.
This has been what I've been working for
for ten years.
[Kim] Even seeing downstairs,
like, I'm so nervous.
They're, like, down to the wire
of, like, finishing it up.
[hairstylist] It'll be done. Don't worry.
But just to even know that,
like, all these people are coming over
just for something that I worked on,
and after ten years
of, like, hustling in the game...
This whole entire launch
is, basically, on my shoulders.
-[hairstylist] It's finally here.
-It's finally here.
[upbeat music]
Mario, is the white dress better
than the brown?
[Mario] Yeah, I think so.
I love seeing everything come together.
I have an amazing launch party
that I have planned for tonight,
and I'm so excited to meet everyone.
[Kim] We are now in the KKW Showroom.
Look at how cool!
-[Stephanie] Can I let people in?
-[Kim] Yeah.
[Kim] Hi, guys! How are you? Of course.
-Thank you, guys, for coming.
-I'm so excited to check it out.
-[Kim] Oh, my god, thank you. Thank you.
-You look beautiful, of course.
Hi! I love the orange.
I'm wearing my Kylie and Kendall dress.
-Stop.
-[laughs]
[Kim] Hi, guys. I just wanted to say hi.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you so much for coming.
-Patrick. Nice to meet you.
-[Kim] Nice to meet you.
-[Kandee] You look so beautiful!
-Oh, my gosh. Thank you.
-This is amazing!
-Thank you!
The packaging is beautiful.
The product is beautiful.
And I feel like people,
when they think of contouring,
-they just think of you, like...
-[Kim] Oh, thank you.
Hey, guys!
We're gonna swatch an exclusive...
It's shimmer.
[Patrick] Oh, that is so good!
My first swatch test that I've done
on someone here at the party.
I'm getting to meet so many
of the beauty bloggers and YouTubers
that I've never met before.
This is, like, a whole new world for me.
So I'm so excited that I'm just
having so much fun doing it
and meeting all of these amazing people.
[camera shutter clicking]
[Kim] How do you decide
what looks you're going to do?
I was looking at the KKW picture.
I was like, okay,
you look bronzy and glowy as [bleep],
so let me try to do something like
a little less obnoxious tonight.
-So cool. Yeah.
-Those pictures are so [bleep] good.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-You just look so good.
It all, like, came together so fast.
I mean, it looks so bomb. I'm definitely...
I'm filming with this tomorrow.
[Kim] Oh, thank you.
-[Charles] Should we do a selfie?
-[Kim] Yeah.
We should do it in the rose room.
Have you seen the rose room? Okay.
It's such an amazing feeling
just seeing it all come to life.
-Me and Mario. How good is this room?
-This is amazing.
You guys, this is, like, the OG crew.
We're here at Kim K's launch for makeup.
It's the best thing I've ever tried.
[laughs]
We worked so hard on this.
It seemed like such a rush,
and I was, like, in such a panic
to make everything perfect.
Kanye saw the plans,
and it was so helpful, his input.
He called our florist,
and we made that whole
flower rose room last-minute.
And that was honestly,
like, the biggest attraction.
What the [bleep] is this?
[man] Oh, my God!
[Malika]
This is magical. A flower ceiling?
Everyone so far is loving it.
There's such amazing press
on this launch party,
and I'm so happy that we made
so many changes so it would be perfect.
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you.
-Babe, I love you. I'm so proud of you.
-Thank you.
Are you excited?
-Are you good with the way it turned out?
-I'm so excited. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, good! It's been a long time coming
for you to do something with makeup.
-I'm excited. It is.
-I'm proud of you, baby. I love you, too.
I'm gonna have another grilled cheese.
-It's a success. She's eating!
-Love you.
-Love you. Talk to you later.
-All right.
[upbeat music]
Tonight's Khloé's surprise party
and I am so excited.
Everyone's here,
all her friends and family,
and I cannot wait to see her face
when she walks in.
[tense music]
-Here they come.
-[Khloé] Is this a bar?
[Tristan] Yeah, we're going to a bar.
-[man] Hey!
-[all] Surprise!
[crowd cheering]
[upbeat music]
Oh, my god!
I don't even know what's happening!
Oh, my God! Babe!
[Tristan] That was good, right?
I had no [bleep] idea.
I've never had a surprise party, ever.
Oh, my God!
We were at dinner and Tristan was so calm.
Like, he was as cool as a cucumber.
He's good at surprise parties,
because I had no clue.
[dance music]
[woman] What's up, girl?
[camera shutter clicking]
[DJ] Can we get everybody
to surround the stage, please?
[crowd cheering]
First thing, of course,
happy birthday. Um...
Another year, another life,
another year on this beautiful Earth.
I'm very honored and glad
to be a part of your journey.
Uh, ever since I met you...
-[crowd exclaiming]
-[Tristan laughs]
Shout out. Shout out, Brandon.
You already know, set up that blind date.
-Thank you, Brandon!
-[Tristan] Yeah, um...
But, uh, baby, it's your day.
It's your month. It's your year.
And I feel good being around you, girl.
[crowd cheering]
I'm having the best time.
Tristan is just incredible.
I've never been this happy.
[Khloé] I am so lucky to be with someone
that is so thoughtful and so sweet.
[dramatic music]
[Khloé] Kourt?
-[Kourtney] Yeah?
-Do you want to help?
-[Kourtney] Not really.
-[Khloé] Okay.
[Khloé] Don't look at my sunglasses!
-[Kourtney] I am.
-[Khloé] No!
-[Kourtney] I'm just peeking, you [bleep].
-Oh, okay. Damn.
[Khloé] This is why we never get
things done, because we get sidetracked.
-[Kourtney] I've never seen your closet.
-[Khloé] Like this?
[Kourtney]
Such a catastrophe. Actually, ever.
[Khloé] 'Cause I got to find a place
for all Tristan's stuff.
-This is a lot.
-Yes, baby?
Do you want me
to hang this stuff up in here
and put them in... like on hangers so we can
transfer them to the other closet,
or do you not know
if you want to keep this stuff?
Yeah, I'm gonna keep it,
but my stuff can stay folded.
-[Khloé] Okay.
-It's been real, guys.
[laughs]
Bye.
After talking with Tristan, we have come
to the conclusion that I'm crazy.
I don't know why
I was stressing myself out,
when we have our beautiful home
in Calabasas.
All Tristan really wants is to be with me,
and just for us to be able to enjoy
our summer together.
That's really all that matters.
-So, Kourt.
-[Kourtney] Yep?
This closet's obviously overwhelmed,
so I'm taking stuff out of that closet
and moving it to that bedroom.
-Where's his stuff gonna be?
-In the main bathroom. Like over there.
But I'm moving some stuff out
and putting it in this guest thing.
How annoying would that be
if he came in here to get ready.
No, but just...
he's a guy and we're all girls in here.
I don't want him walking around with like,
his shlong around everywhere, you know.
Long dick dong.
[laughter]
[Khloé] Long dick dong.
What's happening? Oh, stop.
[laughter]
Long dick dong.
[upbeat music]
-[Kim] Kourt? Hey.
-[Kourtney] Yeah. Hey.
I have these presents for the girls that
I got from the Coakers and Wolfson's.
-[Kourtney] Oh, cute.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Kourtney] Hey.
-[Scott] Hi.
-Did we have four of these at one time?
-[Kourtney] Mm-mm.
Or you got one fixed?
[Kourtney] I get them fixed all the time.
They're so annoying, most expensive
bar stools that need to be repaired.
Is this yours?
-No. That's all you.
-Yours.
I would go insane if I drank this.
[Scott] You went insane a long time ago.
That girl tried to come to Khloé's party,
like, six times she was asking people.
And I was like, it's a firm no, actually.
[chuckles]
[bleep] I didn't even get invited
to her birthday.
-[Kourtney] Exactly.
-[Scott] And I'm family.
That was really sweet.
That made me feel really good.
I didn't... I-I don't do,
like, a family roll call, so...
No, I mean, there's only one person
that would have gotten me not invited,
and that would be Kourtney.
I highly doubt that Khloé was like,
"The last person I'd want
at my surprise party would be Scott."
It's cool. Honestly, I called my sister,
and I hung out with her the whole night.
And then I actually called my mom after,
like, "Hey, Mom, do you want to come over?
'Cause I'm feeling a little down
and lonely
'cause the family that claims I'm still
blood, even though we're not together,
still doesn't invite me
to a surprise party,
but I really felt good about it."
The pity party is why you would think
that you would act differently.
Okay, and acting differently meaning?
There's things that you just should know.
I don't know because you don't discuss
with me or communicate.
I can understand you
not inviting me to your birthday.
But your sister, who I've known forever,
longer than anybody else who was there
outside of the family.
Like, I would have wanted to be there
for her. I don't get it. Be honest.
Hm, I didn't want to have you
coming to the birthday
and be photographed going in,
and just like...
Photographed going in is your concern?
[tense music]
My concern would be there
to be there for your sister,
who I love and care about
for the past 10 to 12 years
and been there for through thick and thin,
and marriages
and all these different things.
I'm a little bit caught off guard,
and I just said that I didn't want
to be photographed,
even though that's really not
what I meant. I just tried to be positive,
and I didn't want to say, like,
"I just didn't want you there."
So if I can't say anything nice,
I just won't say anything at all.
[Scott] That's all [bleep].
It's funny to realize
how fake you really are, though.
[upbeat music]
-[Khloé] Hi, princess. Can I have a huggy?
-[Penelope] Hi, KoKo.
[Khloé groans]
Hi.
-[Khloé] How are you?
-Good.
[Khloé] You're good? I love these pants.
Look at Mommy's body.
Doesn't she look so gorgeous?
Not without makeup, though, right?
-That's what she tells me.
-No.
What? Mommy looks pretty without makeup.
[Kourtney] Am I doing stairs?
-[trainer] Elliptical, first.
-Okay.
[trainer] Five minutes.
So yesterday, Scott came over
and brought up the birthday.
But like, I just didn't have the words,
and I feel like when I talk to him
in person, sometimes I just smile.
[Kourtney] So I was just smiling,
like, couldn't really get the words out.
And I think that makes him more mad.
[Khloé] My question is, did you tell him,
like, what did you say?
Like, do you think he understands that...
there's going to be a transitional period,
that now he can't be invited
to every family event
if it doesn't have to do with the kids?
Yeah. I think so.
-Maybe I need to repeat that.
-[trainer] And break.
Listen, I love being positive,
I love Positive Penny, I do.
[Khloé] But I don't think it's wrong
if you have the conversation with him.
[Kourtney]
Yeah, I know what you're saying.
[Khloé] Sometimes you're so positive,
and we're all
an incredibly forgiving family.
We just sometimes need to be, like,
still I could forgive you
and have you in my life.
We just got to set boundaries.
[Kourtney] Yeah, like, I need to...
Whether I'm, like, positive or upset,
or whatever it is, it's, like,
just get my emotions out, instead of just
being, like, numb to everything.
I held back in my conversation with Scott
because I was trying to keep
my positive ways.
But sometimes it feels good to have,
like, real emotions.
And I think it's just time to be honest.
I feel like you're gonna be
on that TV show Snapped one day.
Because you're bottling up all this stuff
that's, like, the truth.
-[Khloé] You're just like...
-[laughs]
What the [bleep]? Why are you laughing?
I just have a major problem in life.
Laughing 'cause you're uncomfortable?
[Kourtney laughs]
[upbeat music]
Hey, Khlo. Look at these flowers.
-[Scott] This is insane.
-I have some upstairs.
-They're for everywhere. It's beautiful.
-Don't you like to disperse?
-Yes, they are all dispersed.
-And I added these...
[Scott] You have a lot of people
that love you, Khlo.
I do, and I've never...
This is, like, the first year
I've ever had all of this. It's so nice.
Why do you have
all this condensation around?
The air wasn't working, it's now working.
Maybe that's why.
Maybe it was warmer in these things,
and now it's cooling off.
And I like it cold!
And I have flowers that I like
to keep cool, so they last longer.
Should we take it over there?
I don't even...
This has nothing to do with me.
[Kourtney]
Nothing like a good old-fashioned chat.
So I was recapping Khloé this morning
in our workout...
-[Scott] Okay.
-...about what we talked about last night.
And we thought that our lives
are changing,
and, like, there's times
when I want you to come.
Like, and there's times that I don't.
[tense music]
I just sometimes want to be able to go
-do social things.
-[Scott] And you can.
Every single day of your whole
entire life, every day.
[Kourtney]
But those are big events for me.
[Scott] Yeah,
but they're also big events for me.
You act as if, like,
I wasn't there for this family.
[dramatic music]
I just feel like you love
that you are able to hold this over me,
and that's like your control factor.
And I feel like you think you can go out
and do whatever you want,
and purposely try to hurt me
and still get invited to everything.
What does that mean, though,
at the end of the day?
What do you think that really means?
That means I hate you,
or does that mean that I actually love you
and I do things out of spite?
[Kourtney]
That's not a way to show your love.
-[Scott] No!
-When someone's trying to [bleep] with me,
I'm not into having them
at my sister's party.
I don't think that I do the right thing.
I know that.
But for something like this,
this is not exactly...
But when you intentionally are trying
to hurt me and be, like, tit for tat,
that doesn't make me want to be, like,
"Let's invite Scott to the party.
I want to hang out with him."
But again,
it wasn't about you in this instance.
If it was your birthday, I get it.
I am on the longest Ferris wheel
of all time.
Like, we got to get off the ride
at some point and get on a new one.
Like, it's the same old story
over and over and over again.
[Scott] Okay, so, let's be honest.
I mean, obviously, I'm not able to handle
everything that well.
I don't have the best support team.
I'd like to try
to [bleep] be a better person,
but it's not the simplest thing.
You already know the things
that you should be doing in life.
You don't need me to tell you them.
We're not gonna sit here
and go over it again for the 100th time
in ten years or more.
[dramatic music]
I am proud of Kourt
for expressing herself.
But I just need this
to go further than just this room.
I feel like, okay,
this is the good first step.
[Khloé]
And I just really hope she sticks with it.
You really don't know
what you should be doing?
You're gonna tell me that?
You're one of the smartest people
I've met.
Aw, you want to make out?
Seriously, you guys
are so [bleep] dysfunctional,
and I don't know if this is, like,
something you guys do as foreplay,
but this is [bleep] nuts.
When do you think we're gonna get married,
by the way? Like, 40? I mean...
You think that when I turn 40,
I'm gonna go, "Hey,
I've been looking for this drunk guy,
and he has a bunch of dirty [bleep]
stained underwear, whores..."
[laughs]
-You two are so [bleep] nuts, seriously...
-Let's get out of here.
...and the fact that you waste my time
when you guys are now
just gonna go get mani-pedis together.
-[Kourtney] No!
-Look at this.
-I'm not going... We don't hook up.
-I love you guys.
[Khloé] You guys are getting
manicure-pedicures together?
-No. I'm going to get my nails done.
-[Scott] We're gonna hook up.
[Kourtney]
He's going to hang out with the kids.
You guys are [bleep] sick.
[Khloé] On the next episode...
This is Madhvi. She is my scribe.
What the [bleep] can't you remember,
where you need this person
jotting everything down?
If you look up all these streets,
there's tons of tents.
The homeless issue is a full epidemic.
This is the worst manmade disaster
in the United States.
[Kim] It's just, like, heartbreaking.
I just want to figure out
what I can do to help.