[upbeat music]
-[piano keys playing]
-Oh, wow. You're so good.
[Khloé] Good job.
-No.
-Does your...
Does your mom believe
in air conditioning or no?
-Uh-uh. I'm super sweaty on my neck.
-No.
[laughs]
-[Jonathan] What's sweaty on her neck?
-[Penelope] I'm hot.
[Khloé] I'm always hot here.
-[low melody playing on piano]
-[Penelope] A violin.
This is Mom's theme music
-when she comes down the stairs.
-Play this song.
[Kourtney] That was cute though.
Jonathan, you guys, if anyone
ever needs advice, Jonathan's the one.
[Kim] Why do you think I torture him?
Why do you think he's, like,
number one on my speed dial?
[Khloé] You know what I love about you?
I remember when you hated Jonathan.
-I hated Steph and Jonathan.
-[Khloé] Hated Steph and now look at you.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-[Khloé sneezes]
-[Kourtney] Bless you.
-[Kim] Bless you. Gesundheit.
-Who says gesundheit?
-[Jonathan] Bless you.
-[quirky music]
-A lot of people.
-Gesundheit.
-[Jonathan] Gesundheit from Yiddish.
-[Kim] Yiddish?
-[Jonathan] Yeah.
[Kim] What the [bleep] is Yiddish?
Yiddish. Like a different version
-of Hebrew. No...
-It's like British.
[laughter]
-[Jonathan] It is absolutely not.
-[Khloé] Yiddish is British?
Wait, Yiddish is a real thing?
It's not, like, gibberish?
-[Jonathan] No, Yiddish is real.
-[Kim] That's funny.
[Khloé laughs]
[theme music]
[Kourtney]
Today, we're speaking in French.
[Joel] In French? Just in French?
[Kourtney] So I can see
-how my French skills are.
-It's up to you.
[Khloé] But why are you learning French?
Why all of a sudden...
-at the ripe old age of...
-Why did you want to learn Spanish, Khloé?
Well, we've always taken Spanish classes.
I've always taken French too.
I took French in the eighth grade.
[quirky music]
-[Khloé] Why the resurgence of it now?
-Because I have a French trainer.
Or could it be...
that your boyfriend is French?
[Joel] Donc, on va sauter la corde
pendant deux minutes.
-[Khloé] Jump rope for two minutes.
-Yeah. That's it.
Pendant deux minutes. C'est parti.
[gadget beeps]
We start now.
Okay, what can you say in French?
So far, he's speaking,
but what are you doing?
-[Kourtney] So far, I read French.
-[Joel] Okay. Deux, un.
-Here. Vingt squats.
-[gadget beeping]
Un, deux, trois.
-Copy his counting. What's wrong with you?
-[Joel] Cinq, six, sept.
-[Khloé] Say it!
-Shut up.
What's wrong with you though?
You have a trainer, a teacher right here.
-[Joel] Let's go.
-I don't understand.
You wouldn't, Khloé.
[quirky music continues]
-[Khloé] You freak.
-Et c'est la dernière série.
-This is the last set.
-Me arse...
-[Joel] Dernière série.
-[Khloé] Dernière série.
[Joel] Dernière série. Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] So I do like this. I tried it
on today for Patrick. He liked it.
But so when Kylie and I
were speaking the other day,
she was like, "I really think you need
something that's different.
Like, people want to buy."
We're trying to make some metals
that are... that are vamp but not black.
-[Kris] Hi.
-What if we did our red a metal?
[woman] Ooh.
-[Kris] Are you done with this food?
-I'm done.
You're done? You don't want the pasta?
-No, thank you.
-Kourt.
[Kourtney] Oh.
[Kim] Hey.
So, Saint, last night, at, like,
5:00 in the morning, I heard him talking
and I'm like, "What is he saying?"
And he was like, "Dada. Dada.
Shoes. Shoes, Dada."
And I'm like, "What is he dreaming about?
Like, Yeezys?"
[Khloé] Yeezys.
Like, it's his favorite thing, is shoes.
He'll see someone's shoes
-and just be like, "Shoes."
-[Khloé] He's so cute.
All right, guys,
I gotta go sit in with Kylie.
[Khloé] What? You've never been
to one of my...
Literally, I don't think you've been
to one of my Good American meetings ever.
[Kris]
I have been to a Good American meeting.
You never come to my makeup meetings.
-Yes, I do. I get you off and running.
-[Khloé] Off and running?
Kylie's not off and running?
It's been 18 months.
-[Kim] She's just your favorite.
-[Khloé] Yeah, and Kim's not anymore.
-[Kim] It's fine. Kylie makes...
-More money.
-Yeah. She makes more money right now.
-No. You guys.
That's a horrible thing to say.
This is the perfect example
of why Kylie's so much nicer to me
and why I spend more time with her.
-Right.
-You give me such [bleep]
and she's so sweet to me all the time
and does such nice things and cares.
[quirky music]
Kim has been my mom's favorite since...
-A decade strong.
-I would say longer than that.
-Really?
-Like, literally since you were born.
But now she kind of has been, like,
weaning herself off of you a little bit
-and she's been latching onto Kylie now.
-Totally.
I love a good colander
'cause you can get a facial, look. Facial.
-Facial.
-I do the same thing!
-Are we the same person?
-I think we are.
-Look what I brought you.
-You're so cute!
[laughter]
We're stuck together forever.
[Khloé]
Why is it fun to be Mom's favorite?
I don't know what that's like, so...
I don't know.
She just puts in a lot of attention.
She always builds you up,
makes you feel confident.
I don't know any of these things.
[Khloé] I just want to see what it takes
to be the favorite.
[Kim] Good luck.
Kylie's just so nice to me all the time.
She'll buy me little fun things
to let me know she's thinking about me.
[Kim] So we have to buy you
to get you to like us more.
-[Kris] No, but you know what I mean.
-[Kim] Wait a minute,
we threw you your 60th birthday party.
[Khloé] Yes, we did.
I wouldn't say Kendall or Kylie
even had a thought about that party.
We threw your 60th birthday and we busted
our ass to do it, the three older girls.
And we were dealing with other crises
at the same time
and we still managed to do it.
We bought you
-your [bleep] memories.
-[Kim] Your memories.
Yes, we're on the same page. Memories.
It sounds like you two are a little jelly.
That's all I'm saying.
[Kris] All right,
I have to go to my meeting.
It's right over here if you need me
and right now,
you guys are tied for my least favorite.
-How about that?
-"How about that? How about that?"
[Khloé] I really do think Mom likes me
the best though, out of us.
[Kim] Really? I don't think so.
I think that you're in Cleveland
all the time, so...
[Khloé]
So she doesn't like me 'cause of that?
No, it's just like, you know,
I spend more time with her.
I just think
that I'm, like, always with her.
-[Kim] So...
-Well...
[Kim] Go back to Cleveland, honey.
[chuckles]
Don't you worry.
Do I look scary?
[Kim] Does anybody know where North is?
I can't find her.
-[North] Hello!
-[Kim] Oh, wait, the blanket talks?
-Look at my little pretty kitty.
-Meow.
[Reign] Uh-oh!
-Reigny.
-[Reign babbles]
-Who is this cute boy?
-[Kim] Reigny.
[Kourtney cackles]
You're never gonna get in trouble
'cause of that dimple right there.
Do you think you feel like one is left out
because there's an odd number of kids?
This guy.
[Reign babbles]
But him and P
spend a lot of time together.
I think I should have three more kids.
[Kourtney chuckles]
-Three more?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-Like, you would carry them yourself?
-Yeah.
That's wild.
I think I would do just one more.
But I need to decide, like, ASAP
if we're gonna have another one.
[Kim] Or we're gonna lose our surrogate.
-Really?
-[Kim] Mm-hmm.
Kanye and I have always talked
about having more kids,
but I've gone through so much
with really bad deliveries
that the doctors don't feel like it's safe
for me to carry my own baby.
[doctor] You had toxemia.
You had a retained placenta.
Very traumatic.
The doctor is like, "For sure now,
you should not carry another baby."
Kanye and I are just gonna,
like, look into other options
and see what we're comfortable with.
But getting a surrogate
and finding someone that you really trust
really is so much more difficult
of a situation
than you could really imagine.
You have to, like, make sure
that their lifestyle is healthy
and they have to go through
psychological testing.
And it was, like, maybe a year
before we actually
finalized our current situation.
But I think
everything happens for a reason
because the surrogate that I really love
got approved.
And she's such a nice person.
Like, she's so easy to talk to,
and she's the perfect fit for us.
But we have to decide quickly,
are we really gonna go through with this
or are we gonna wait
until we feel more prepared?
So, Reign, you want to take a nap?
I'll take one with you.
Reigny, you want a nap-nap?
You want to go night-night?
-[Reign] Um, no.
-[Kim] I'll go night-night.
Should I go night-night in your bed?
Um, no. I need the bed.
[upbeat music]
I know my mom has been complaining
about this pantry,
and she loves mine, so we're gonna try
to emulate this as much as possible.
She's just a hoarder.
[Jenna] She wants it exactly like yours.
[Khloé] She's so funny.
So what I did, like, I planned out.
Like, I was like, "Okay, I have
this many cookies that I like in here,
this many nuts." And I put
everything together in one shelf.
Then I was like,
"This is a great spice shelf.
-This is a great cookie shelf."
-[Jenna] Okay.
My mom loves organizing, just like I do
and she always comes to my house
and says, "Oh, my God, Khloé,
you're so good at this."
[Khloé] Raw almonds, roasted almonds,
-candy pecans.
-Yeah.
So I decide,
as a very nice, sweet gesture,
let me go into her kitchen,
into her pantry,
reorganize it, KhloCD it up.
It's just the gift that keeps on giving.
This is, like, ridiculous,
how much [bleep] this woman has.
Like, this is crazy.
And I have a lot of [bleep].
What the [bleep] is this?
[Khloé] What is that, a cock ring?
Like, come on.
[Kris] Uh...
[Khloé] Oh, hi!
What's going on?
-What are you doing here?
-[Khloé] Organizing your pantry.
What did I do to deserve this?
-This is my dream come true.
-I know!
-[Kris] No, this is seriously...
-[Khloé] No, wait, look.
This is gonna be a display here,
like how mine is out.
[Kris] Yes.
'Cause this is
where all of your [bleep] is.
-Okay.
-So...
That's your coffee,
and then you make your tea here.
-[Khloé] So we're gonna get dividers.
-[Kim] Hello.
And you're gonna keep
your tea and everything here.
-That is so smart.
-[Kim] Special delivery.
[Kris] What?
-Hansen's.
-[Kris] You brought a Hansen's cake?
Wait, I'm not done showing you.
-[Kim] Oh, yeah.
-Wait a second.
[Kris] Oh, my God, it's the basketweave.
-[Kim] It's your fave. I know you.
-[Kris and Khloé] What does it say?
It says, "I love you, Mom."
-Why?
-Oh, my God. Thank you.
-What do you mean, why?
-You're such a kiss-ass.
-What are you talking about?
-Oh, and it's black and white.
Okay, wait, but let me just show you
over here real quick.
I love that cake.
So instead of putting
all the sugars over there
on that bottom drawer,
we're gonna get you dividers,
-and put all your sugar packets here.
-[Kim] What are you guys doing?
-It's gonna save so much space.
-She redid my entire pantry for me,
which has been, like, my dream come true
for as long as I've lived here.
It's her dream come true.
Who knew that me mentioning
that Kylie was being so nice to me
would result in them being
even nicer to me?
This is seriously the nicest thing
and the cake's the nicest thing.
[whispers]
[bleep]
This is actually working out in my favor.
[Kris] Is this Be Sweet to Mommy Day
or something?
First, Kylie shows up out of the blue
and got me a massage.
-That was nice.
-[Kris] I'm one lucky mom.
-I really am. You guys are the best.
-[Khloé] Kylie knows how to live.
You really are,
and I'm so excited about my pantry.
Love it, love it, love it.
It really means a lot to me.
It really does.
And the fact
that the plastic bags are over there
and that kind of stuff is over there,
that you found
-little nooks and crannies for this stuff...
-I know!
...is genius.
-So genius?
-Is it? It is.
[Kim] All right, have fun organizing
this disgusting mess.
[Kris laughs]
Thanks for leaving your Hansen's box
on the floor. [bleep] cake.
Oh.
[laughter]
This is legit how I feel inside, okay?
I'm trying to pick eight nudes
but I don't know...
But why do you put them on her?
-Where else are we gonna put them?
-Yeah, where else are we...
Amazing.
-[Kim] Do you like them?
-[Stephanie] I do.
[Khloé] What is all this?
Just mini earrings.
[Khloé] They're so little.
Where do these go? In your ear?
-These are little hoops?
-Yeah, I like little, tiny hoops.
Holy cow. Well,
we are completely two different girls,
-with my hoops and your hoops.
-Why did they order all of these?
I'm so confused.
Anyways, Kourtney's... shh...
secretly learning French.
All of a sudden,
at the ripe old age of 38,
she wants to venture out
to a new language.
-She's not learning French, you guys.
-[Khloé] She's learning French.
She made Joel start doing...
[Kim] Joel do the whole workout in French.
-You're lying.
-[Khloé] Obviously, we all know
that this is for her little friend.
Why else would she
all of a sudden think to do this?
-Okay. This is all very new to me.
-So she hasn't said any of this to you?
-She has not told me.
-[Khloé] She's like a vault.
She doesn't say anything about it.
She really doesn't.
-She's so not like that normally.
-And now it's, like, a vacation and, uh...
[Khloé] And another vacation
and another vacation.
And another one.
-She's getting very invested.
-[Stephanie] I know.
I know.
Why, when it's me, when you guys find
paparazzi pictures of me with Tristan,
you guys, literally, like,
stone me until I answer you?
But when it's Kourtney,
we're like, I'm doing it too,
we're like, "Ooh, her friend."
She won't even say his name,
which blows my mind. Like...
"Let's say his name now.
We don't have to be quiet about it."
[Stephanie] I mean, maybe we just want
to keep it, so that it's like,
"Oh, it's just a little thing.
It doesn't matter,
it doesn't matter. Let's not..."
Well, you weren't around
when Scott started.
-[Khloé] She's doing the same thing.
-Right.
Ten and a half years later.
What is wrong with us? We enable her.
-Let's catch Kourtney.
-[Khloé] Huh?
-[Kim] Let's catch Kourt.
-Okay. Buckle up, kids.
[rhythmic music]
Oh, I love the gifts you guys got me.
-Hey.
-Hi!
[Kourtney] Did you see my snaps yesterday?
-No. Come on in, Kim.
-[Kourtney] What? You didn't?
[Khloé] I know you want it, Kim.
You better watch them now
before they go away.
[Khloé] Oh, my God, I didn't know.
-[Kourtney] It's gone.
-[Khloé] 22 hours ago?
You missed it.
-[Kourtney] You missed it all.
-What was it?
I was hanging out in your closet.
I think I'm just going to hang out
in Khloé's closet all day.
Wouldn't this be fun? Closet goals.
You're lucky we're not the same size shoe,
but if you happen to be missing any bags,
it wasn't me.
Kylie's wearing my Dolce & Gabbana
runway boots that have never been worn.
[Khloé] I'm like, this is what happens
when I'm out of town?
-You guys go through my closets?
-She went to your house?
I mean, it's fine.
She gave me a Lip Kit deal.
Like, what am I supposed to do?
I'm, like, indebted.
[Kim] Not really.
So, I, um...
Top secret, but I, uh,
my surrogate passed all of her tests,
so she starts the pill tomorrow.
-[Kourtney] What pill?
-[Kim] Birth control.
When you do fertility, they need you
to be on the pill for one week
and then get off and then you get
your period, implant the embryo.
So are you doing this for sure?
[Kim] Yeah.
-[Kourtney] This is so exciting.
-Oh, my God.
It's so wild.
[Kim] I definitely had a hard time
making this decision.
Should I do it? Shouldn't I do it?
What do we really want?
This particular surrogate,
she was the best fit for our family,
so we just had to go with it
and try one embryo.
Should we start this workout, guys?
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
[thrilling music]
[Kim] Look at them, snapchatting.
We're trying to work out.
-I'm trying to play the music.
-[Kim] No, you're snapchatting.
[barking softly]
Khloé, we have Saks Fifth Avenue
to ourselves!
Well, if you keep screaming,
they're gonna kick you out.
I figure I got to step it up
to be my mom's favorite.
I'm going full throttle.
So yesterday, I got her the best gift,
this hyperbaric chamber.
[salesman] So you got to turn this on,
right down here.
I can do this so far.
[Khloé] You lay in it for a little bit
and you better just have some Zen time.
-[Kris] Hello, hello, hello! Oh.
-[Khloé] No, we can just talk normal.
I can hear you fine.
And today,
I'm taking my mom to Saks Fifth Avenue,
and I cleared the entire place out.
[Khloé] So Saks is shut down
just for my mom and I.
Let's start at sunglasses.
-Those are great on you.
-[Kris] They feel crooked.
-Wait, but do they...
-[salesman] They feel crooked?
-I can get a fresh pair.
-Open.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Oh, my God.
-[Khloé] They open.
-These are my new favorite thing ever.
[salesman laughs]
-[Khloé] How cute are these?
-[Kris] Those are great.
-[Khloé] They're so cute.
-[Kris] We need these.
[Khloé]
I have matching sunglasses with mom?
[Kris] Yeah, it's mother-daughter.
[Khloé] Mom, do you like that Gucci bag?
[Kris] I have red, but I really like
the one with the little...
-[Khloé] Bow?
-...bow.
I really appreciate you, like,
spending time with me and doing this.
This would be so good on you, Khloé,
because of your height.
[Khloé] Oh, it is kind of cute.
You should get that.
[Kris] There's two of them.
[salesman] Hey, guys.
You guys look like twins. Perfect.
We are twins.
-[salesman] Look how beautiful.
-I know.
We look so cute, we could go out
on, like, a mother-daughter date.
-In the same outfit?
-Yes.
-Those are must-haves for both of you.
-[Kris] Yes.
My mom's other kids are dead to her
after this Saks trip.
I mean, this is...
Who could get this? Ever? Only me.
So you're welcome, Mom. I love you.
[Kris] Best day ever.
[Khloé] Yeah, you're lucky 'cause shopping
with Kim would be the worst.
I'm way nicer.
[upbeat music]
[Joel] Step up on the bench and press.
-[exhales deeply]
-[Joel] Switch.
Let's see if this one could do the same.
One. Yeah. One. Drop the weight.
Yeah, let's go. One more.
[Khloé] Hey. Hold on. Can't hug you.
[Kourtney] You're, like,
dripping with sweat.
-[Khloé] We're working out.
-Okay, I'm gonna just rest.
[Khloé] What?
On this bench.
I literally have in my notes section
on my phone...
-[Kourtney] Yeah?
-...a list of questions to ask you.
-Other leg, right?
-Yeah. Opposite one. Right arm.
[Khloé] So...
I see you online going out every night.
You've been out two nights in a row.
[Joel] Keep your weight here. Last leg.
So who were you with?
I know who...
you were with your little boy... friend.
I mean, I'm not saying that.
Like, a boy that's a friend.
Um...
Why is it so hard for you to say?
Do you guys talk about, like,
where you guys stand?
'Cause I feel like you guys go on,
like, these fairy-tale trips together,
and then, do you guys just go back
to your regular
scheduled programs afterwards?
What does that mean?
Oh, my God.
Is he your out-of-the-country boyfriend?
Do you guys speak every single day?
This is too much information
to share with my sister.
Really? We normally tell each other
everything but more so her.
She'll call me and talk to me
all the time about all this stuff.
[Khloé] But with this,
she's just [bleep] weird.
Like, get over yourself.
Like, this is crazy.
-[Khloé] So then...
-Khloé.
[upbeat music]
-[Kim] Hello.
-[Khloé] Hey.
-Hey. What's going on?
-Um... Nothing.
I want to know, have you heard anything
about the surrogate?
-No, not yet.
-[Khloé] What?
We implanted a few days ago
and we have to wait until, like, ten days.
Well, that's crazy.
I know, right?
-[sighs]
-It's, like, the craziest waiting game.
-It's so frustrating.
-It is.
This is the time that's the most annoying.
And you just wait it out,
there's nothing you can do?
Yeah, there's nothing you can do,
you just have to wait
until it's, like, far enough along
where we can see if she's pregnant or not.
I mean, it's really nerve-racking
because, you know, it's only
a 60 percent chance that it'll take.
[pensive music]
-[Khloé] That's crazy.
-One didn't work with me.
I tried it and I lost one of them.
Oh, my God, I forgot about that.
That's so scary.
Yeah, so it's hard, like,
it's just a chance.
[Khloé] So scary.
Before Kimberly got pregnant with Saint,
she had an embryo implanted into her
and that embryo did not take.
So Kim is super nervous and anxious
during this waiting period.
I mean, of course, she wants to know,
is she or is she not having another baby?
Well, okay,
I don't want to stress you out,
but keep me posted
as soon as you find out.
Okay, I'll call you
as soon as the doctor calls me.
Okay, thank you.
-Okay, love you.
-I love you too.
-Bye.
[chill music]
-[Kris] How are things?
-[Kim] Good.
-[Kris] You look cute.
-[Kim] Thanks.
Hello, darling.
[Kris] Oh, my God.
Look, Kylie bought me this toaster.
She is so sweet.
She's so sweet.
-She is the best. She listens to what...
-[Kim] She's the best.
She is. Look at this.
Obviously, the toaster doesn't compare
to me closing down Saks,
so I feel like the one
who's really shaking in her boots is Kim
because I'm doing a damn good job
of winning my mom's affection and love
and Kim isn't.
I'm so excited.
I really wanted this, you guys.
[Kris squeals]
I can't believe how my kids spoil me.
And it's white and it matches the kitchen.
-It's eggshell.
-It goes with your old-school car.
It does. I love when my kids spoil me.
So we have to buy your love?
-No, but this is pretty fun.
-Oh.
Basically.
This is crazy
how much my mom loves this toaster.
Ugh! She is the cutest kid.
I guess I have to step it up.
I'm not gonna surrender.
Out with the old,
in with the new, mamacita.
[Khloé] Doesn't it bother you
that the name is Smeg?
[Kris] I kind of like it.
The only other thing
that would be better is just K-R-I-S.
-[Kris chuckles]
-What?
-What's that supposed...
-Yeah, I could have my own toaster line.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Can I vent about Kourtney?
-Yes.
-So it pisses me off
that she won't even say his name.
-I don't get that whole thing.
-[Kim] Yeah.
[Khloé]
I don't get what kind of thing this is.
It's all like...
It blows my mind that she thinks
we're, like, blind or something.
-Yeah.
-And it's hard for me to watch,
and I'm like, "Dude."
Hard for you to watch,
like, her, just personality.
Yeah, 'cause I'm just, like...
We're all different and that's fine.
We should... Since she won't admit
that that's her boyfriend,
you know what we should do?
We should be like, "Oh, my God,
we have to set you up with this guy,
he's so cool."
We can make up anyone, you know?
[quirky music]
Chris Hemsworth.
Who's that?
Thor.
-[Khloé] You don't know who Thor is?
-I don't know who Thor is.
Oh, my God.
We are totally testing Kourt,
we do not even know this guy,
by the way, he's probably married,
but we're totally just using a hot guy
to, like, bait her.
To see, like... If she won't go with him,
then she definitely has a boyfriend.
-Yeah.
-[line ringing]
-[Kourtney] Hello?
-[Kim] Hey.
[Khloé] Heya, Kourt.
Hello, governors.
[Kim] Oh, my God, we have
the most perfect guy for you.
Who?
Okay, he's tall. He has the best body.
[Kim] Like, the best body.
-He has blonde hair.
-[Khloé] He has two kids.
-He has, like, a 12-pack and big muscles.
-He's ripped. A scruffy beard.
He's, like, a really good actor.
And he's gluten-free.
Where did you find this person?
[Khloé]
Do you know who we're talking about?
Um...
-Thor.
Did you ask Thor
if he wanted to go on a date with me?
[mouthing]
[quirky music]
-Not yet.
I don't go on dates.
-Why don't you go on dates?
I don't want to sit there
and go, "How old are you?"
Well, I'll go on a group thing.
It'll just be, like,
a chill barbecue at, like, my house.
Um, I'm really busy this week,
I have a lot going on.
-But...
-But we noticed
you were out with a certain someone.
[Khloé] So that's your boyfriend?
Um...
[quirky music]
So you just hang out with this guy,
but you won't validate anything to us?
That's weird.
She fully does not go for it.
-[chuckles]
-So she definitely has a boyfriend.
She's so weird.
This is your best angle, Kim.
Look at that chin.
[Khloé] Ew, why the tongue thing though?
[Kim]
Can't really see with this light. My girl.
[camera shutter clicks]
[laughing hysterically]
-[Kylie] Oh, my goodness. Hot tamale.
-[Khloé] Mm-hmm.
It's like 106. I don't get it.
This is, like, not a good outfit.
[Khloé exhales deeply]
You and me both, sister.
[groans]
Hello? Ooh. Air conditioning.
[Kylie] Mm.
-And marble floors.
-[Kylie] Hello?
[Khloé] Keekaleek.
-[Kim] Hi, guys.
-[Kylie] Is this for me?
-Are you hungry?
-[Khloé] Oh, kiss-ass.
-[Kylie] Which one's mine?
-You want the larger one? I don't know...
Do you leave this out to taunt me?
Look at this [bleep].
-It's a blender. She said she wanted it.
-Right, you're a kiss-ass
'cause she said
this is her favorite thing.
You little sneaky snake.
Now you're gonna do a blender.
-You're trying to...
-I just saw it,
and so I was like,
"Fine, I'll just get it."
Oh, when you just see
some diamond earrings,
you should just get them for me too?
Okay. I'll remember that.
[whispers]
Bitch.
-I see what you're doing.
-[Kylie] What is this?
She's buying Mom's affection.
After the toaster you got her,
she's now buying her the matching blender.
What toaster?
[Khloé] The toaster you got her.
That toaster that she's been dying for
and you're like her favorite daughter
'cause you got her that toaster.
[laughs]
I didn't get her a toaster.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you guys are talking about.
She also said that you took her
to get a massage.
-[Kylie] No. I don't even get massages.
-[tense music]
She's a pathological liar.
-[Kim] Why would she care to lie?
-Why would you lie about that?
I think just to get us
to buy her other stuff.
No, there's no way someone would do that.
-[Khloé] That's, like, crooked...
-[Kylie] She's, like, manipulating
you guys, I think.
[Kim] She really is.
She's really a snake.
I feel pissed
that I didn't see this before,
like, Kim and I were so consumed
in one-upping each other
that we didn't even see
that my mom is the one that is, like,
manipulating us the entire time.
We should, like, somehow get her back.
Yeah, how dare she lie to us?
That's [bleep] up.
[upbeat music]
This is so [bleep] good.
[Khloé] Don't try to eat the other one.
Where is Mom?
Mom!
[Kris] Yup?
Put the sticks both in the other one.
-Yeah?
-[Khloé] How are you?
I'm good. Is that cake?
Mm-hmm. Hold on, it's coming.
We wanted
to truly thank you.
For what?
For just being you.
-Aw.
-[Khloé] Yeah.
That's my favorite cake.
I know.
-I love that cake.
-[Kim] Give me a hug.
Okay. What's wrong?
Why do you want to hug me?
Huh? What?
[Kim laughing]
What are you doing? Khloé, what is wrong...
What is wrong with you?
-What the hell are you doing?
-Read this sweet message.
"How does payback taste? Sweet revenge."
What did I do to...
You've been manipulating all of us
and using your daughters
to buy you [bleep]!
-Yes!
-Are you crazy?
Are you crazy?
[Kim] I talked to Kylie
and she did not get you that toaster,
so you fully scammed us.
If that's what it takes for me
to get you guys to be nice to me,
at least I'm smart enough
to figure that out.
[Kim] And you're teaching us
bribing, lying, scamming.
They're life lessons.
-Don't ever forget.
-No, now you can buy a mop.
Buy your [bleep] self a Hansen's cake.
You don't even deserve this one.
What? Khloé! Oh, my God!
This will show her
not to mess with us again.
Or you're gonna get two cakes
to the face, Kris.
This is bad behavior.
We're big and we're bad.
And we're hungry.
[Kim] This is the best part,
if you want a piece.
No. I don't want a piece.
I have [bleep] cake up my nostrils.
You guys are both grounded.
You're a scam artist.
And we...
are satisfied.
-[Kim] This is delish.
-[Khloé] Mm-hmm.
Come give me a hug. Come...
Come give me a hug.
[North] Hi, Snapchat.
Okay, let me call Khloé
and my mom and Kourtney
real quick.
[Kim] Who should be the lucky one
for me to tell them first?
Kourtney doesn't get very excited
about anything.
Okay, so we'll call Khloé.
Khloé, yeah.
[line ringing]
-[Khloé] Hello?
-[Kim] Hey, what are you doing?
Um, about to have Taco Tuesday
with the whole team here.
No way. So fun. So, are you by yourself?
I'm by myself.
[Kim] So guess what?
I'm afraid. What?
[Kim] What happens every time I say,
"Guess what?"
The person's pregnant.
[Kim] We're having a baby.
[Khloé squeals]
-What kind?
-A girl.
Shut up. So you know what it is already?
-Yeah.
-Oh, my goodness.
I mean, it's so exciting either way.
I can't believe
you're gonna have three kids.
Telling my family about this news, I mean,
it is that exciting feeling,
like, you're pregnant.
It's the exact same feeling,
especially right at the beginning.
-Oh, Kim, I'm so happy for you.
-[Kim] Don't cry. Don't cry.
I know, I just...
To be able to do that is really great.
I'm really happy for you.
[Kim] It's so crazy, right?
You know, it's really exciting,
but it's also like,
"Oh, my God, this is happening."
[Kourtney] No way. How exciting.
We're gonna have a baby number seven.
I know, isn't that crazy?
Mom's gonna have, like, 30 grandkids.
-[Stephanie] Oh, my God.
-Are you excited?
[Kim] I'm so excited.
I mean, you know what?
It's kind of weird when it's not you.
Yeah, like, it's just weird.
So I'm like, I don't know whether
to just start eating donuts and celebrate
like I would, like old times,
or just go to the gym.
I think you can do both.
[Kim] Kanye and I were like, "What do
we do? We do nothing for nine months."
-Yeah.
-I'm totally gonna forget, seriously.
And then like a month before,
we're gonna be like,
"Holy [bleep]. We need to get a nursery."
-[Kim] Just kidding.
-[Stephanie laughs]
[chuckles]
Do we look like deers?
[Kourtney] Ooh.
You're so cute, Reigny.
-[Khloé] Hello.
-[Larsa] Hey, guys.
-[Kourtney] Should we sit and eat?
-Are we sharing salads?
-[Kourtney] Yours is in the fridge.
-[phone chimes]
[Khloé] Why are you smiling like that?
-Hello, obviously, you're talking to some...
-[chuckles]
Oh, come on.
[Khloé] What?
Kourt, you're grinning from ear to ear.
Khloé, you don't get to know
all my secrets.
Kourt's actually getting on
my [bleep] nerve.
Just like, the stupid smile, like, smack
the stupid smile off your [bleep] face.
I'm fed up with this whole,
like, silence game.
[Khloé] What were you just doing?
I'm going on a trip.
He's planning everything.
-[Khloé] Okay.
-It's a surprise,
so you're not gonna
get to know the location,
but I have been told what to pack.
Well, that will be fun.
[Kourtney] Mm-hmm.
Yup.
Why are you giving me a look?
[Khloé] How secretive she is?
It's just so frustrating.
Like, we share everything else.
Are you comfortable, like,
talking about him or no?
Not really, like, I don't feel like
sitting and like, airing my business.
[Khloé] I am the queen of secrecy as well,
but you won't even say his name.
Like, that's crazy.
Okay, but I'm not using it on the show.
I'm not.
[Khloé] His name? It's all in the press.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
I don't feel like I need to, like...
expose.
If no one ever knew about something,
that's fine.
But then you're sitting here,
going on these trips,
doing things, it's, like,
people could piece things together.
No one's saying to film your trip,
I'm saying, [bleep], just say the name.
What are we talking about,
this invisible man,
that has, like, some code word?
That's so crazy.
Like, how old are you? Three?
It's so weird
that everyone's tiptoeing around it.
Like, okay, the guy Kourtney's dating.
Cool. Younes, Y, whatever the [bleep]
you want to call him.
I don't need to expose
every aspect of my life.
[Khloé]
No one is saying you need to do that.
I'm not saying
to expose your relationship.
-And I don't need to.
-I don't get it.
Stop talking about these trips then.
If you don't want to say
who you're going on the trip with,
then stop being seen with...
It's like, you're living now
two separate lives.
And you're not [bleep] saying the name,
that's so [bleep] stupid.
Okay, so say the [bleep] name,
but shut the [bleep] up.
You're not [bleep] saying the name,
that's so [bleep] stupid.
Okay, so say the [bleep] name,
but shut the [bleep] up.
[Larsa] I feel like she's doing
what you did in the beginning.
Like, you don't know
where your relationship is,
-so you don't wanna...
-And I get that.
I'm not saying that,
but don't [bleep], it's the name.
-I'm not telling her to tell me...
-You should tell her about the name.
...his dick size, and what the [bleep]
she's doing in the bedroom.
I feel like everybody at this point
knows the dude's name.
Everyone does,
but that's what's so [bleep] weird to me.
Like, get over yourself. It's so strange.
I mean, I don't know, like,
what the balance should be
with, like, showing and not showing
but, like, you can't, like, yell at me
for, like, how I want to handle it
and don't.
[soft music]
Before we started the show
is when,
like, Scott and I
first started being together...
[Khloé] Mm-hmm.
I haven't, like,
been dating somebody since.
Like, I haven't had a boyfriend
since that, you know?
-So I'm not gonna, like...
-Do you have a boyfriend now?
Sure, Khloé.
-[Kourtney] But I'm not gonna...
-You do?
-Yeah.
-So you guys have had, like, the talk?
[Khloé] Like are you guys really official?
Like, you guys... Like, I know that...
-Yes.
-[Larsa] She's definitely
in a relationship.
I cannot believe Kourt actually says
that she has a boyfriend.
Boyfriend. Kourtney has a boyfriend.
I'm just happy she's [bleep]
talking about it.
That's news to me, Kim and Steph.
You've never said this.
[Khloé] And look at you laughing.
Like, you definitely are so awkward
at times.
-[Khloé] I mean...
-No, she's like a teenager right now.
-[Khloé] Yeah.
-It's a teenage phase.
[Larsa laughs]
Oh, my God.
[chill upbeat music]
Wait. The Daily Mail posted,
"Kim Kardashian reminisces
as she visits old house
she shared with Kris Humphries."
[Kim] He literally spent one night.
Can I retweet it and be like,
"Boo, didn't even have
a toothbrush there, honey. Stop reaching"?
-[Khloé laughs]
-[Kourtney] I'll call you back.
[Khloé] So...
how is everything going
with your surrogate?
Like, I feel like
I don't even know what's happening.
I mean, it definitely is,
like, a different process. Like, it is...
I don't even feel like this is real.
[Kim] Same.
The fact that this is just what we can do
these days, I'm, like, really thankful.
Like, I'm seriously so grateful for her
and that someone is just so, like,
selfless and kind to do this.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-And I definitely want to keep it private.
Like, I don't want people
to find my surrogate.
Like, I don't want them to harass her.
Like, she doesn't know
how to handle stuff like that.
This isn't her world.
I don't want people following her
and chasing her.
It can be dangerous.
I know how dangerous it was.
I almost got into the craziest
car accident when I was pregnant
'cause the paparazzi was chasing me,
so it's just, like, a safety thing.
That's a lot on, like, just her.
Like, it's a lot to take on that role,
and just even for you.
Like, do you have peace of mind ever?
-Just, like, it's a lot.
-[Kim] Yeah.
It is frustrating, like...
Like, to not be able to do it on your own.
[Kim] It is a weird dynamic.
Like, I go
to all the doctor's appointments
and I try to be really present,
but when you're not carrying it yourself,
it is such a fine balance of how much
you're gonna be in their lives.
Of course I want to know every last detail
that's going on with my baby
and that's super frustrating.
[Kim] But I really trust my surrogate
and I don't want to be that person
that's trying to control her every move.
It's gonna be a long, hard process,
but I'm gonna take it one day at a time
and hopefully, it just gets easier.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] I drank one gallon of water
just in my workout yesterday.
I peed at least 700 times.
-I had three bottles of water today.
-[Kourtney] How much is a gallon?
[Khloé] A gallon is a gallon.
Um, Kourt and I kind of got into a fight
the other day.
-Like, we were at the kitchen table.
-You guys never get into fights.
I know.
We definitely got into an argument.
-We did.
-We did and Larsa was there.
And Larsa was, like, sitting, like...
I was just like,
"What the [bleep] is up your ass?
Like, you won't even say
your boyfriend's name."
That lunch with Larsa was the first time
you ever said you had a boyfriend.
-Yeah.
-[Khloé] You just downplay it a lot.
Like, you like to...
I think that's, like, your deflecting,
or, like, downplaying.
-[Kourtney] Mm-hmm.
-And then
somehow just gets
into this 10-year relationship.
There are some people
that just really casually,
just, like, have new people
in their lives all the time.
Like, that's just not me.
Yeah. So how serious are you and...
Y?
[whispers]
Wouldn't you like to know?
Y.
How serious?
What kind of question is that even?
-[Kourtney] Is there a level?
-Do you say, "I love you"?
Khloé...
Does he work out with you and Joel?
-He is going to.
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
-[Khloé] Ooh.
That's when you know it's real.
[Khloé and Kourtney chuckle]
[Khloé] On the next episode...
We need to do a fitness tutorial video.
That's hopscotch.
You don't really follow through.
I just want you to take it seriously.
You guys, so I went
to this media training.
I don't want to do media.
Kris, were there signs that Bruce,
at the time, wanted to become a woman?
[Kendall]
It's just [bleep] one thing after another.
I'm literally going home.