Previously on
"The Rookie: Feds"...
Garza: This is our target,
Tobias Kazan.
He runs the largest fentanyl
syndicate in the Southland.
Simone:
That's his wife, Cora.
They've been married
21 years.
That's his daughter, Aliz.
She's a little ratchet.
Out of my way.
She's my daughter.
Your daughter is the prime
suspect in her own kidnapping
and the kidnapping
of Kellen Filmore.
And for the murder
of Tony Eakins.
You came at me
through my kid.
I won't forget that.
If I were you, I'd get her
a really good lawyer.
As far as Tobias goes,
we'll get him one day.
My darling.
Finally, we are together.
And on Valentine's Day.
An ocean couldn't keep us
apart, Loretta.
It's fate.
I don't know
if it's the champagne,
but my head is spinning.
I mean,
just six weeks ago,
you were
a ClipMates profile.
And now I'm sitting across
from the love of my life.
God, she always
lays it on so thick.
You know you men love
your compliments.
Whenever you're ready.
No, no, no. Um...
I'll take it.
Thank you. Oh.
You know
that pains me.
It's just that my enemies
have tied up my fortune
with their
frivolous lawsuits.
But as soon
as I am victorious,
I am taking you
to Firenze, Italia.
Mamma mia!
Until then, I got it.
I know you're good for it.
Garza: You're doing
great, Simone,
but pretending
to be a rich man
and taking gifts
is not a crime.
Remember, to get him
on wire fraud,
he has to ask for money
for his fake corporation,
which you need to send
and he has to accept.
You got him on the hook,
so let's reel him in.
What's the matter, darling?
Is everything okay?
Well, I told you
coming here is dangerous.
That's why I have
to travel covertly.
I-Is there anything
I can do?
A slight injection of funds
right now would help me
stay one step ahead
of my enemies.
Of course.
Well, how much
do you need?
$25,000 should
more than suffice.
Okay.
Where should
I send it, my love?
My company's account
should be easiest.
Ah. Got it.
You, my dear,
are a lifesaver.
And you, my dear,
are under arrest.
FBI, sweet thing.
Come back here!
[ Eyes' "Wine Lips" plays ]
♪ Just trying to make it
through the weekend ♪
♪ So I can close my eyes ♪
♪ So stuck,
I hit another dead end ♪
♪ What a big surprise ♪
Give me your car! Now!
[ Both grunting ]
[ Music stops ]
[ Siren wails in distance ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
FBI. We got this.
No, I do.
Naomi Voss, LAPD.
And this is my collar.
Back off.
♪ Ah ah, ah ah, ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ah ah, ah ah, ah-ah ♪
[ Radio chatter ]
Captain, I had no idea
they were working this case,
but I made the arrest.
Don't let them do this.
Yes, sir.
I bust my ass for months
to get close
to the ClipMates Casanova,
and you bogart my arrest?
Our case takes priority.
I got on to this guy
after he played
a widow's lonely heart
and conned her
out of a hundred grand,
then I found
five other women
he scammed
from here to Dubai.
I've got files,
interviews--
That all sounds great.
Now please send it over
when you get a chance.
You're not interested
in his romance scam.
You're on to him
for something else.
Detective Voss,
I do appreciate
all of the hard work
that you've--
You want to
blow me off, fine.
This man has ruined
women's lives.
Whatever you're up to,
you better do right by them.
Can I?
Yeah.
Hey.
My name is Simone,
and I'm sorry about
what happened back there.
Just tell me you snagged him
for a good reason.
You didn't hear it from me,
but we're after Tobias Kazan.
That's major.
Keep talking.
Well, a few months back,
we crippled his operation.
But word on the street
is he's planning something big.
What's that got to do
with my case?
Tobias tripled
his security,
so it's been damn near
impossible to get to him,
so we've been tracking him
through his wife.
She's a Casanova victim.
But keep it on the low?
Thanks for
the straight answer.
[ Elevator bell dings ]
Man: Ooh, uh,
hold the door, please.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Ooh!
Beautiful flowers.
I can't believe it's, like,
the first time
in, what, 30 years
that I'm not gonna have
somebody to love up on
for Valentine's Day.
Unlike you, B.
No, Antoinette doesn't like
Valentine's Day,
so I'm cool.
I'm not supposed to do anything
for Fortune, right?
I mean, we've only gone out
a few times.
What?
Being married on Valentine's Day
was so much easier.
My wife would lay out
all the rules a week before,
so I always knew
what to do.
Valentine's Day
is so lame.
It's just another day
of insincere overtures.
But all the sheeple
continue to fall for it.
Well, I love it.
And there's no shame
in my nosy game, sir.
Who are those for?
Oh, um, someone
named Laura Stinton?
Stensen?
Aah! Oh, my God!
Oh, what?
Atlas-- so sweet.
[ Elevator bell dings ]
Thank you, kind sir.
I hope you have
a really nice Valentine's Day.
He even remembered marigolds
are my birth month flower.
[ Laughs ]
Happy Valentine's Day.
Hi.
I know you said
you don't care
about Valentine's Day,
but I had to
get you something,
so... here you go.
"I like you
hot or cold."
You know,
like the pizza.
It's good either way.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Uh, I get
all of that now.
Great.
Thanks.
It's... cute.
Yeah, thanks.
Uh, so I'm-- I'm so glad
we're on the same page
about this whole
Valentine's thing.
You know,
just keep it casual.
Just a regular
old Tuesday.
Indeed.
Yeah.
So, you still coming over
tonight?
Do a little ramen,
watch a documentary?
Yes. Uh, 8:00?
Great.
Uh, you got a secret admirer
I should know about?
Oh, Jackie's husband
always sends her
a bunch of gifts
throughout the day.
It's a big old
waste of money
on things you're gonna
throw away
two days later,
you know?
No, thank you.
I'll see you later, alright?
Chase: It's not a crime
to date multiple women.
Rude? True.
But against the law?
I don't think so.
How about fraud, forgery,
theft, for starters.
And all of those
on an international scale.
Laura: You lie about
who you are, what you do,
con women into giving your
fake business money... Duncan.
I--
Don't say a word.
They can't make
any of this stick.
We literally
caught him conning
one of our
undercover agents.
No way. If anything,
Loretta conned me.
He's telling the truth
about that.
I'm good.
And so humble.
[ Cellphone vibrating ]
Carter Hope.
Yes. Hi.
Oh, that's right.
Uh, I'm gonna need
to cancel that.
My wife and I...
What do you mean,
it's non-refundable?
No, I know what
the word means. It--
Never mind.
What's non-refundable?
[ Sighs ]
Last Valentine's Day,
I messed up with Evelyn,
like, really bad,
so I figured I'd plan ahead
for this year,
save future me
from grief,
so I made reservations
at Ravenna for tonight.
The chef's table's so exclusive,
I had to pre-pay--
$500 a head.
Well,
that's perfect.
What?
Well, you got the dinner
reservations in the divorce.
You forgot to give Fortune
a Valentine's Day gift,
so looks like past you
just hooked future you up.
It's too much
too soon, right?
I mean,
we're barely dating.
[ Chuckling ] Are you hearing
yourself, Carter?
This is the thing
that can lock it in.
Look, we can prove that
you conned multiple women,
but right now, we only want
to talk about one of them--
Cora Kazan.
She's married--
to a very dangerous
drug kingpin.
Ah. Look at that.
He wasn't aware of that.
She told me
he was a businessman,
had his own company.
Yeah, manufacturing and
distributing methamphetamines
and killing a bunch of people
in the process.
You got two paths.
One, we pack you off
to an American prison,
where you never step foot
in your homeland ever again.
Or two, you help us get to
Cora's husband, Tobias,
and you go home.
How about three?
We fight this in court.
Sure, but that might
trigger four--
Tobias greenlights a hit on your
client for screwing his wife.
I'll help.
Absolutely not.
It's my life.
I'll do it.
Just tell me
what I have to do.
You are going
to give her this gift.
Really?
A literal Trojan horse?
It's Celtic.
It's a symbol
of good fortune--
something our Casanova here
should have no problem
making up
a really good story about.
And what is it really?
A Wi-Fi hacker.
Give it to her,
tell her to put it in the house.
When she looks at her husband,
she thinks of you,
or-- or whatever.
And meanwhile, we're tapping
into their home network
and intercepting
all communications.
Fine.
Your phone.
Arrange a meeting
with Cora--
today, in person.
But it's Valentine's Day.
She's probably
with her husband.
Then make sure
that she chooses you.
[ Sighs ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
Hi, Amy.
What a surprise.
Darling,
can you get away?
Today's tough.
Could we do Pilates and mimosas
tomorrow morning?
I can't wait.
I need my lips on your neck
in that spot that you love,
just under your ear.
I'll make it work.
Text me
when and where.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
I still think
we should be the ones
surveilling Cora's date
with Chase.
The surveillance team
is top-notch.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
Plus, Cora already
knows what we look like.
Why risk her
making one of us?
Laura: [ Gasps ]
[ Laughs ]
Is that another present
from Atlas?
Yes, but I'm the only one
with a key
to this drawer.
How'd it get in there?
Did one of you help him?
Wasn't me.
Not me.
I am dating a cat burglar.
[ Gasps ]
Oh!
A dreamy,
romantic cat burglar.
Garza:
You gotta be kidding me!
Well, then get him back, now!
Chase just blew
through a red light,
and he lost the two agents
who were escorting him
to his date with Cora.
He is in the wind.
Any idea
where he's going?
Not a clue.
I bet I know someone
who might know--
the one person who's been
on his tail for months.
[ Tires screech ]
♪
Appreciate this, Detective.
Couldn't wait
to get my gloat on.
Boat slip U-1.
There's a yacht
being leased
by one of Mr. Bad Romance's
shell corporations.
LAPD!
FBI!
We're coming on board!
♪
Oh, no.
You should have
listened to me.
If you hadn't stolen my case,
this guy would be in lockup,
and I'd be getting restitution
for his victims.
Okay, someone please tell me
that they got a lead.
No sign of a struggle, which
means he either knew his killer,
or they got
the drop on him.
And they used a weapon
found in the boat,
all pointing to a crime
of opportunity.
Alright, well,
he ditches us,
he tries to get away
on his boat,
and then someone catches him
before he can.
Yeah, but he has screwed over
so many ladies,
we are not short
on suspects.
Where do we start?
How about Cora Kazan?
I just got off the phone
with surveillance.
She didn't show up
to the hotel to meet him.
That's far from proof she came
here and harpooned him.
Agreed. But she has a FastTrak
on her car for tolls.
She got off the 110 freeway
heading to the marina
less than
two hours ago.
Let's get her in here
for questioning. Now.
Since I clearly know more
about the victim/former suspect
than you,
would you like me
to observe?
Actually, I--
Great.
I'll meet you
at your office.
Damn!
[ Chuckles ]
And you complained
about me.
If you think you can get me
to give you dirt on my husband,
you're crazy.
Mm. Crazy is being married
to a psychopath
and cheating on him
with a con man.
Yes. We know about
Chase Harrison.
And we know that he contacted
you earlier for a hookup,
and then two hours later,
he's dead
with a spear-gun arrow
through his heart.
He's dead?
Yeah.
I want a lawyer.
You can go that way,
but then your husband's gonna
find out about the affair,
and we both know he's not
gonna take that too well, so...
Safer bet-- you just
come clean with us.
I didn't kill him.
We know you set up
a rendezvous.
He called me back an hour later
and changed the plan.
Did you know that?
No.
He called me from a new number,
which was odd.
He said
he was in trouble
and needed me to meet him
at the marina.
What else did he say?
Duncan wanted
to sail away with me.
You knew
his real name?
Yes.
Busted him
on our first date.
So you knew exactly
what he was doing
and you still
gave him money.
Why?
Because burning
Tobias's money
was almost as satisfying
as the sex.
But mostly, I did it because
Duncan and I were in love.
Naomi: Unbelievable.
She knew who he was
and still fell for his lies.
How do you know
he's lying?
Even con men
can fall in love.
Because this guy knew more
than anyone that love is a scam.
Wow, Negative Naomi.
Think about it.
If our victim didn't have
real feelings for her,
he would have given her
the Trojan horse gift
and walked away.
But he didn't.
You're wrong.
I'm right.
No, you're wrong.
No, I am right,
and you--
Would you two
cut the bickering?
I'm trying to listen.
I'm right.
Laura: Tell us what happened
when you met up at the marina.
I never met him.
I couldn't find
his yacht.
I tried calling that phone
number, but he didn't pick up.
Cora, do you expect us
to believe that?
I don't care what you believe.
What we had was real.
You were gonna go
with him?
I wanted to,
but no.
My daughter is in prison
and needs me.
So, why did you go
to the marina, then,
if you weren't gonna
sail off with him?
To say goodbye.
[ Door alarm buzzes ]
Cora, don't say
another word.
Unless you're arresting
Mrs. Kazan, we're leaving.
Her husband's waiting for her
in the lobby.
Of course he is.
♪
Garza.
You've already taken
my daughter from me,
now you're coming
for my wife.
How far do you think
you can push a man
before he decides
to push back?
Careful, Tobias.
You're just a few words shy
of threatening a federal agent.
Yeah, but that would be
such an unsatisfying way
for you to end up
in handcuffs.
So unless you're willing
to escalate
to assaulting
a peace officer,
you should go.
Hmm.
When you're looking into
Cora's alibi,
check out Tobias's,
as well.
Because if he knew that she was
cheating on him with Chase,
he has certainly
killed for less.
Mm.
[ Elevator bell dings ]
Seriously?
Atlas again?
Hey, no. It's not for you.
It's for him.
For me?
Yeah.
From who?
Uh, I don't know.
Laura: Mm!
"Just a sweet
chocolate treat
to an even sweeter
chocolate treat."
It's from Fortune.
You're doing
something right, Carter.
Clearly not.
But I'm about to.
[ Cellphone dials, line rings ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
Hey, you.
Hey. I am looking
for a woman.
Maybe you can
help me find her.
She is kind, thoughtful,
and apparently considers me
a chocolate treat.
Mm. I think I know
who you're talking about.
That was really nice.
Look, I know this is
last minute, and I'm so sorry.
Are you free
for dinner?
Tonight?
Well, maybe I can get someone
to cover me,
but good luck getting in
anywhere on Valentine's Day.
I...actually know someone
at Ravenna.
Uh, he can get us in.
Ravenna? For real?
I've always wanted
to go there.
What time?
Pick you up at 8:00?
I'll be cute.
What did you
tell them?
Nothing about you
or your business.
Not everything
is about you.
So it's about
your boyfriend, then.
You knew?
You're not as clever
as you think.
Did you--
[ Cellphone rings, beeps ]
[ Sighs ] Hello?
Operator: This is a call
from Riverside Correctional.
To accept the charges, say yes.
Yes.
[ Beep ]
Aliz:
[ Panting ] Dad?
Sweetie?
Daddy.
Hey, Aliz,
what's wrong?
They know who I am.
Who? What are you
talking about?
The Mala Noche. They found out
I'm your daughter.
They've been
threatening me.
You said you could
protect her.
I have people inside, but
Mala Noche's running the prison.
Tobias:
What do they want?
Your business,
or I'm dead.
[ Groans ]
Got that, Papi?
Listen to me.
If you hurt my daughter,
I will kill every single person
you care about.
Gotta go.
We'll be in touch
after we put a beating
on your little angel.
Wait.
[ Click ]
[ Line beeping ]
[ Gasps ]
Hey. Got anything on who killed
our ClipMates Casanova?
Waiting to see.
ERT didn't find
any prints
on the spear gun
that killed your victim,
but they pulled multiple
latent prints from the yacht. Okay.
AFIS is searching
for a match.
Well, fingers crossed.
Oh, also, fingers crossed we can
find some good food tonight,
'cause the ramen place
I was gonna take you to--
health code
violation, so...
Guess we dodged
a bullet.
Yeah, totally.
Uh, I was thinking maybe
we could do, like,
a drive-thru on the way
to my place?
Oh, yeah. Uh, fast food
sounds great.
Great.
[ Computer beeps ]
We got a hit.
[ Mouse clicks ]
[ Printer whirs ]
Fingerprint match
from German Intelligence.
Alright.
Hans Becker.
German national suspected of
multiple murders for hire
across Europe.
An assassin.
He just landed at LAX
late last night
from Frankfurt.
And just happened to end up
on our victim's yacht.
What are we thinking?
Valentine's Day Massacre?
All of Chase's recent marks
have deep pockets.
A betrayal like that,
I wouldn't put it past them
to want revenge,
hire a hitman.
No, Tobias wouldn't
waste the money,
and Cora didn't have time
to bring him in.
Well, but Chase has been dead
for hours now.
I mean, this guy could be
on his way back to Germany.
I'll get a BOLO
out for him
and have every agency
in the region on high alert.
With any luck, we'll catch him
before he leaves town.
Look, uh,
it's Valentine's Day, right,
for those of you
who celebrate.
So go and have a night
or whatever,
and just stay
by your phones.
If I get a lead,
I'm gonna call.
What, you got big
Valentine's Day plans tonight?
[ Scoffs ]
No Valentine, no plans.
I lateral transferred
from Oakland PD six months ago,
and I gotta say, I'm still not
vibing with the "LA thing."
[ Clicks tongue ]
Just do my job
and go home.
See, you just haven't given
the right people a try.
Trust, once you find your folks
and a good place to hang,
you gonna see LA
through different eyes.
Really? Down here, there's not
even any decent restaurants,
just overpriced
hot spots and sushi.
[ Chuckles ]
Seriously, what is up
with all the sushi joints?
Okay, um, try this taco truck,
Bangin' Tacos, downtown.
If you love that, I'll give you
some other recommendations.
Not big on tacos,
but thanks anyway.
Have a good night.
Good night.
♪ You were
one of the cool kids ♪
♪ Baggy pants, shades on ♪
♪ Chilling with your friends
at the basketball court ♪
♪ Smoking something,
wearing... ♪
You look beautiful tonight.
I mean, not that you don't
look good on other nights.
I get it.
And thank you.
Evelyn: Carter?
Evelyn?
Carter: What are you
doing here?
Oh, no.
"Oh, no" is right.
[ Scoffs ]
The reservation
was in my calendar,
and I thought
it shouldn't go to waste.
I figured you'd long
forgotten about it.
All those missed
Valentine's Days--
Guess you needed
a new lady
to suddenly
find the time.
Uh...
Hi, I'm Fortune.
Hi, I'm--
I'm sorry about this.
I'm Evelyn.
The ex-wife.
Figured.
Hey, guys.
How are you?
I'm Marcus.
Nice to meet you.
Well, now that we all
know each other,
if you don't mind,
Fortune and I
are gonna enjoy
this reservation
that I prepaid for.
As a gift to me.
Remember?
Aren't you supposed to be
at home with our son?
The one you want to take
2,000 miles away from me?
Really, Carter?
You want to do this
here and now?
[ Sighs ]
Brendon: Hey.
All done.
Thanks for waiting. Yeah.
So, I-I was thinking,
greasy drive-thru
sounds terrible.
On Valentine's Day?
Yuck.
I have a cauliflower pizza
in my freezer,
so I thought maybe
I'll just do that for us.
Yeah.
You are the worst actress
in the world.
[ Scoffs ]
You do care about
Valentine's Day, don't you?
Don't you?
Alright. Yes, okay?
I love it. I'm a woman.
I'm French.
I'm a romantic.
It's the one day of the year
designed for lovers.
Then why didn't you
say anything?
I was embarrassed.
Hey.
[ Clears throat ]
I love that you
love Valentine's Day,
'cause guess what?
I love Valentine's Day.
Which is why I planned
something for us.
I rented us
a house in Malibu,
and there's a chef
there right now
cooking us
a five-course dinner,
and then we are gonna
walk on the beach.
We're gonna get massages
while we listen to the ocean,
and then we are
going to...
sit by the fire
until the sun comes up.
What happens after the fire
and before the sun?
I'll leave that
up to you.
♪ You sing the sweetest tune ♪
Naomi:
You can't have al pastor.
That's pork.
Yes, I agree
pork is delicious,
however,
your diabetes--
Look, we'll eat chicken tacos
and binge-watch something, okay?
Bye.
Oh! So much has happened since
the last time I saw you, hmm?
You took my advice
on the tacos
and got you a hot date.
Get it, girl.
Date? Nah.
That was my mom.
She's getting older
and in denial about it.
She's the reason
I moved down here.
Wanna grab a drink
while we wait for our order?
Sure.
Yeah? Come on.
♪
You and your ex
have some unresolved issues.
I'm sorry you got caught
in the middle.
Look, I get it.
We all have baggage.
But you told me you were gonna
be honest with me,
and then you go
and pull this?
Bringing me to a dinner
meant for your ex?
I know.
And I don't know
what's wrong with me.
I like you, Carter.
I'm just not sure you're ready
to date right now.
No, no, no.
Don't say that.
I like you, too.
We can salvage this night.
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere.
Anywhere at all.
I think it's best
if you just take me home.
I had been with my girlfriend
for two years,
but after I transferred
down here, we broke up.
That sucks.
I don't have any excuse
as to why I'm single.
I date men and women,
so you would think that my odds
would be much better.
Ever date anyone
in law enforcement?
Mnh-mnh.
Why you ask?
No one else understands
the demands of the job.
We move different.
Oh, I would much rather
date a civilian.
I don't want to be in that
headspace when I get home.
Well, then, get used to
being alone.
Damn! Harsh.
I'm just being real.
I come from a cop family,
and everybody's still together.
Just saying.
Anyway, Mama's tacos
are getting cold.
I better go.
You're right, though.
Those were bomb. Later.
♪ Hopefully, Airbnb
don't kick us out ♪
[ Sniffs ]
Show me your hands.
I come in peace.
I don't believe you.
I have an offer.
My daughter was beaten in prison
by the Mala Noche.
Now they're threatening
to kill her
if I don't turn over
my operations to them.
So what's your offer?
Transfer her to a
minimum-security federal prison
Far away.
Where my enemy
can't reach her.
And what do I get
in return?
Me.
I do hope one of y'all made up
for my unsexy Valentine's night.
Talk to me.
Well, I FaceTimed with Atlas
all night.
Props. Carter?
B?
Mine just ended
an hour ago.
Whoo-hoo! Winner, winner!
[ Chuckles ]
Garza:
Well, you better get yourself
a double espresso, probie,
because we've got
a busy day ahead of us. Okay.
Last night, I had a surprise
Valentine's date...
with Tobias Kazan.
Are you serious?
Apparently, Mala Noche
has been threatening
his daughter's
life in prison,
and he wants us to transfer her
to a minimum-security facility
for the rest of her sentence
for her safety.
And in exchange,
he'll help us make a case
against Mala Noche,
and he'll give up
his meth-manufacturing lab
here in LA.
Tobias did not seem like
the type to surrender like that.
I was skeptical
at first, too, Carter,
but as a show
of good faith,
he passed along some intel about
his drug suppliers in Greece.
Interpol verified it,
and this morning,
Hellenic Police
arrested 30 people.
So this is real.
Tobias has already set up
an in-person exchange.
He's gonna hand over
all of his supply
to Mala Noche's
leadership.
So we can kill two birds
with one arrest.
W-When's the exchange?
That's the tricky part.
Tobias says that he's only
gonna give up the time
and the location if we grant him
immunity and move Aliz,
so I'm gonna meet with
the AUSA to work out a deal.
In the meantime, Laura, Brendon,
liaise with
the Bureau of Prisons,
and you make sure that Aliz
is under protective custody
until she's transferred.
And do it on the QT.
We do not want Mala Noche
catching on.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
This is, uh, Naomi.
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Hey, Detective.
You're on speaker
with Garza and Carter.
Naomi: Hey. DHS picked up
our hit man,
Hans Becker, at LAX,
about to board a flight
to Frankfurt.
He's en route to my station
right now.
Oh, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is a federal case.
He should be on his w--
And this is
a courtesy call.
More than you gave me,
for the record.
[ Beep ]
She hung up.
[ Sighs ] Okay.
Will you two please
go over there
and see what you can get
out of Hans?
Don't ever complain
about me again.
Okay.
Mnh-mnh.
Don't do it.
How much were you paid,
Hans, to kill Chase?
Which would be
the eighth murder
across three continents
you're suspected of.
But never charged with.
That's the most
important part, yes?
Hans, we didn't pick
your name out of a hat.
Your prints
were at the scene.
Sure. 'Cause I'm a conflict
resolution specialist.
You have
my mobile phone.
So you'll discover I was hired
by a woman, Victoria Wagner,
to find a man who played
a nefarious confidence game
and tricked her
out of over $200,000.
She paid you to find him
and to kill him.
No, resolve conflict.
But when I boarded
the ship,
I found him sitting there,
speared like a fish.
You expect us
to believe that?
Hypothetically,
were I this man
you're accusing me of being,
I would never use a weapon
so crude and unreliable.
[ Chuckles ]
It's a nice story.
I did not
kill that man.
Just found him.
Naomi:
So what do we think?
Hans is clearly a killer,
but is he our killer?
Well, he's telling the truth
about one thing.
He did get money from
Victoria Wagner-- 20,000 euros.
And then she started sending him
all these texts in German.
I'll reach out to the language
analysts to translate.
There's a lot of clearly coded
text about payment.
And then yesterday
at 11:47 a. m.,
he messaged her,
"The job is done."
Wait. You speak German?
And Spanish.
Some Arabic.
Show-off.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
Hans just got a text
from Victoria.
"You lied.
Chase is not dead.
He just contacted me
for more money."
That's impossible.
Unless someone has access
to his account
and is posing as him.
Chase must have
had a partner
who's just become
desperate for cash.
Damn.
You want to do
what now?
Catfish the catfisher.
Our Casanova had a partner,
and they contacted
one of his German victims,
Victoria Wagner,
posing as him,
trying to extort
another payment.
Okay, so we want to draw
the partner out
by pretending
to be Victoria online.
Naomi: Victoria will say
she can't transfer funds
electronically the way
she normally does
because her account's
tapped out.
Yeah, but she can get a physical
check made out to cash
by one of her business
associates in Los Angeles.
And we'll set
that trap up
in an office building
that we control.
You smell
what I'm cooking?
Do it.
♪
We're in position.
Carter: Copy.
Position secured
in the lobby.
When the partner picks up
the check from the receptionist,
we got him. Okay.
So it's obvious that the partner
is the killer, right?
But why turn on Chase?
My bet-- [Snaps fingers]
They were lovers.
No.
No, no, no.
Hold on.
The partner finds out that Chase
is gonna run off with Cora,
has a fit,
kills in a jealous rage.
Boom.
50 bucks says
it was all business.
Why do you hate love
so much?
Again with this? It's like
"The View" with you two.
Oh, hush.
One thing that's
become clear--
If Chase was the face
of the operation,
then his partner
was the brains.
I agree, Whoopi.
I take that
as a compliment.
Now, Chase had a sophisticated
financial operation,
so his partner
had to be someone
who knew how to open
shell corporations,
move cash internationally.
Chase's lawyer.
That's a reach,
don't you think?
Not really.
She's here.
It's Audrey Evans, Carter,
and she's headed your way.
As soon as she picks up
the envelope, we'll move in.
♪
Damn!
She made us.
♪
Audrey, don't.
FBI!
Naomi: LAPD!
♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Handcuffs click ]
Settle a bet. Did you kill Chase
for love or money?
Lawyer.
Damn!
Alistair: This looks
to be in order.
Deal's not gonna
get any better, Tobias.
You work your entire life
to build something,
and then just like that,
with some paper
and a borrowed pen,
it all goes away.
I'm not the audience
for your self-pity.
You are a drug dealer,
and everything
that you've built
has been at the expense
of other people.
That's karma.
Hmm.
[ Sniffs ]
At 8:00 p. m. tonight,
several high-ranking members
of Mala Noche
will meet at my cookhouse
on Soto and Valley.
They're coming to take
all my product and supplies.
Get comfortable
because you're not
going anywhere
until this is done.
[ Door alarm buzzes ]
What's the sit-rep?
We closed
the ClipMates Casanova case.
Well, Naomi did.
We let her
take the collar,
'cause honestly,
she earned it.
Should we fold in
on Tobias?
Yeah.
I need you to get
Aliz's statement
before marshals transfer her
to her new prison, okay?
Simone, you got her
to open up the last time,
so do your thing.
Don't I always?
Yeah.
Laura, Brendon, and I
are going with SWAT
to Tobias's cookhouse.
Carter: Got you.
They said if my dad
doesn't hand over his business
by tomorrow...
...they'll cut
my throat.
[ Beep ]
Thank you, Aliz.
A marshal will be here soon
to transfer you.
I was surprised you were
taking my statement.
You put me away,
and now you're helping me out.
Thank you.
Thank your father.
Wait.
I-I thought you were
just being kind.
My-- My father actually
gave up his drug operation?
Yeah.
He made a deal with Garza.
[ Scoffs ]
Garza?
No, my-- my dad
hates that guy.
Well, maybe he loves you
more than he hates him.
No, he doesn't.
You think my dad
actually cares about me?
No. The only thing
that he loves is his business.
He would never
give that up.
Especially to your boss.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Train horn blares
in distance ]
♪
Garza: Surveillance feed
is up and running.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
Did you get
Aliz's statement?
Carter: Yeah.
But are you sure this deal
is on the up and up?
Why do you ask?
Because based on
what Aliz just said,
Tobias as the dutiful father
is an act.
Meet's supposed to be
at 8:00.
They're already
12 minutes late.
Maybe Mala Noche
got cold feet.
Or Tobias
gave you bad intel
to lure you down
to an environment he controls,
setting up both the FBI
and Mala Noche.
Simone:
Boss, what better way
to get rid of
all your enemies
than to have them there
at the same time?
Matt, this is
a meth lab.
With the amount
of volatile chemicals in there,
it would only take one
well-placed explosive
for this whole block to go boom
and a lot of people die.
Would he sacrifice
his own men like that?
Risk blowing the deal
that he cut?
Tobias Kazan?
One hundred percent.
Let's go check it out.
[ Lock disengages ]
♪
[ Indistinct conversation ]
We have two armed bogeys,
south wall.
Copy that.
Keep eyes on them.
♪
[ Guards speaking Spanish ]
It's getting
a little crowded in here.
We need to step this up.
Almost to the tanks.
♪
[ Steady beeping ]
[ Gasps ]
Matt, we got a problem.
Carter was right.
This is a trap.
Tobias wired C4
onto one of the tanks.
And if it goes off, this whole
block becomes a crater.
Mala Noche just arrived.
We need to disarm that bomb
right away.
[ Door opens ]
[ Indistinct conversation ]
Bogeys on the move.
They're all in the one spot.
♪
[ Conversations in Spanish ]
[ Beeping continues ]
♪
[ Rapid beeping ]
[ Conversations continues ]
♪
[ Beeping stops ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Bomb disarmed.
SWAT team, move in.
Go, go.
[ SWAT team shouting ]
♪
FBI!
Hands up right now!
No, no, no, no, no.
Hands up. Let's go.
Show me your hands.
Hands up, everyone.
[ Indistinct chatter ]
Boss, you okay?
Yeah. You good?
Yeah.
Laura, you good?
You surprised
to see me alive?
Did something go wrong?
Cut the crap, Tobias.
You set us up,
and you set up Mala Noche.
You had that place rigged
to explode.
Why on earth
would I do that?
To send a message to anyone who
might be coming after you again.
Your daughter's prison transfer
was dependent on this deal,
and I'm pulling it.
Threatening
my daughter's safety?
Oh, you must
be desperate, Garza.
But we both know
you're too much of a do-gooder
to send her back
into that lion's den.
Are you willing to risk
your daughter's life for this?
To use her
like some kind of pawn?
Aliz--
she's a big girl.
She made her choices.
Now she's on her own.
And the deal I signed
granted me immunity
from prosecution regarding
the LA meth lab.
So...
...unless you can prove
I have something to do
with that supposed bomb...
...may I go now?
Cora:
Why am I here?
Tobias says he gave up
his entire operation.
But I know that
there's got to be more,
and we believe
that you know all about it.
Turn state's evidence.
We can put him away
for good.
[ Chuckles ]
Forget it.
We can keep you safe.
You can start a new life.
Find new love.
[ Sighs ] Look, my husband
is not a good man.
But my daughter needs
her father in her life.
I'm not going to destroy
what's left of our family.
Well, it's a shame
that your husband
doesn't feel the same way.
Garza:
Are you willing to risk
your daughter's life
for this?
To use her like
some kind of pawn?
Tobias: Aliz--
she's a big girl.
She made her choices.
Now she's on her own.
[ Beep ]
You are the only one
who cares about Aliz.
It would seem
that you're right.
Which is why
the last place I should be
is in witness protection--
unable to look out for her,
to use his resources
to protect her.
So you're gonna stay
with him,
even though he is
a complete monster?
I have to.
For my daughter.
♪
[ Thud ]
Man: Delivery.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Who's it for?
You.
You trying to buy
my forgiveness?
I am so sorry
about last night.
You were right...
about everything,
except one.
I am ready to date.
Sure about that?
Absolutely.
I promise you,
no more lies.
No more dodging, hiding,
no more being afraid
that my truth is too much
for you to handle.
Just radical transparency.
That's a serious commitment.
I'm a serious dude.
I can prove it to you.
Here are
some straight-up truths
that I've never mentioned
to anyone before.
[ Exhales sharply ]
In the fifth grade,
we had "share day."
But I thought the teacher
meant Cher, the singer/actress.
So I dressed up
in a big wig and jumpsuit.
No, you did not.
[ Chuckles ]
Yes, I did.
And I looked fly as hell.
Here's another truth--
"Breakin' 2:
Electric Boogaloo"
is my all-time
favorite movie.
And that's for real.
I tear up during
the final dance number
every time.
Sorry not sorry.
[ Laughs ]
Number three--
Okay, stop now,
or I'll regret
what I'm about to say.
I am willing to give
this radically transparent
truth-teller another chance.
[ Bear Hare's
"Fire In The Sky" plays ]
♪ Let go ♪
[ Laughs ]
♪ Of that warrior mind ♪
Hey, you.
Hi.
How was your day?
It was touch and go
at first.
[ Laughs ]
I haven't pulled
an all-nighter
since... l'université.
Mm.
But it was worth it.
Best Valentine's Day ever.
It was.
And so sweet
and thoughtful.
Now it's my turn.
Oh. [ Pats hand ]
I bought us
the last two tickets
for "Amélie"
at the New Beverly.
I know
it's your favorite film.
Uh, tonight?
Okay.
Uh, it's a late show.
It's midnight.
Yep.
Can we fall asleep
and stream it
at your house instead?
Oh, thank God. Sweeter words
have never been said.
Thank you.
Let's go.
[ Laughing ]
♪ Hold tight ♪
Hey, girl, hey.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Well, I had an update
on the Casanova case
and wanted to share.
What's up?
Garza invoked the power
of the federal government
here and abroad to seize
all of Aubrey Evans's assets.
So the women
that her and Chase conned
will get restitution.
I'm glad to hear it.
Now, if only we could un-break
their hearts, too.
Wait a minute.
Is that a sweet statement
from someone who hates love?
Could you please
speak into the mic?
[ Chuckles ]
Shut up.
Even I've got a heart
buried in here somewhere.
And for the record,
I give you Feds props
for how you handled
the case.
But the jury's still out on this
sun-baked purgatory called LA.
And Negative Naomi
is back.
You've got to admit that
the sunsets here are unmatched.
And you even said
you liked the tacos.
Ah?
True, true.
See you.
Hey, since you're
the LA restaurant expert,
I read about this Jamaican spot
on Washington-- Natraliart?
Ah. They have the best
beef patties in town.
Well,
we should go sometime.
I'd say tonight,
but I'm taking my mom
to this
"silver and sexy" mixer.
You're a good daughter.
Rain check?
Rain check.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- Captions by VITAC--
♪