7-Adam-15,
silent alarm, 801 North Heatherly.
Respond Code 2-High.
We got an I.D. on the homeowner?
Nope. Listed to a holding company.
Police!
Bishop?
Hey! Hi.
Oh, thank God.
I've been stuck up here
for almost an hour.
Control, send LAFD to our location.
We got a guy in a tree.
I have so many questions,
starting with "How?"
and ending with "Why?"
I missed the landing zone.
That's obvious.
Excuse me.
What are you guys doing on my property?
Do you guys have a warrant?
We got a call.
Uh, silent alarm.
And what are you doing in my tree, bro?
He missed the landing zone.
Yeah, that's obvious.
Actually, I was aiming
for Selena Gomez's house.
Uh, Selena Gomez doesn't live here.
She li... I-I can't tell you
- where Selena Gomez lives.
- Wait.
Are you stalking Selena?
Stalking's such an ugly word.
Parachuting into somebody's backyard
is, like, kind of psycho, bro.
You need to check yourself
before you wreck yourself.
Does that mean you don't want
to press charges?
Nah. Just get him
off my property A.S.A.P.
You got it.
Oh, my God, that's will.i.am!
That's so cool.
Phew!
Oh, geez!
That's not creepy at all.
It arrived.
What did?
Oh, the Ferrari?
V-12, single overhead cam,
0 to 60 before you can blink.
Oh, I don't know, man.
I can blink pretty fast.
Come with me to pick it up.
Oh, okay.
Oh. Wait a second.
You just want to use my badge
so you can open it up on the freeway.
No! No!
Sorry, buddy. No dice.
Besides, I got to get into work
early, check on Bishop.
She has her DRP tomorrow
for her PHQ violation.
- The what for the what?
- Oh.
Disciplinary Review Panel
for leaving her foster brother
off of her
Personal History Questionnaire
when she joined the department.
Guy had a criminal record.
Is that a big deal?
Well, she could be fired for
lying on an official document.
Oh, that's rough.
I can see why you're taking your
frustrations out on the bag.
Well, 'cause Bishop says there's
nothing I can do to help her.
- That's your problem, you know.
- Oh, good.
I was hoping we could make this
about my inadequacies.
No, I'm serious.
You have a pathological need
to fix things for people,
even when you know
there's nothing you can do.
No, I don't.
I... Okay, look,
I simply refuse to believe
that there's never not a solution.
That's, like, a triple negative.
So, tell me, Mr. Fixit...
does Bishop even want your help?
- Why wouldn't she?
- Because you're a rookie...
bottom of the food chain.
Nothing you think or say matters
inside the department.
Especially with the Chief of Police...
who personally decides
Talia's punishment.
Sounds a little harsh.
Harsh as it is,
you got to stay focused
on yourself right now.
We got a six-month exam
in the next week,
and we got to ace it
in order to move on
to the next stage of our training.
Where we'll still be
riding with our T.O.s
for, what, another seven months?
Yeah. But we'll get more freedom.
And no more daily evaluations.
Otherwise, it's back
to the starting line,
and you're the rookie
who got held back.
Or worse.
What's with the glasses?
Uh, I realized I need to start
having more fun with the job,
stop taking everything so seriously.
All right, listen up.
Got some bad news for our rookies.
Thanks to Detective Jenkins
being placed on the Brady List,
the department is tightening the rules
regarding the Field Training program.
Bottom line...
every recruit now has to complete
the "training and experience"
checklist as a primary officer
before they'll be allowed
to take the six-month exam.
You got to be kidding.
I don't let my rookies be
primary until the second month.
If our recruits experience an event,
it shouldn't matter
if they were primary.
- It's not fair to them or us.
- I agree.
But this is "cover your ass"
time for the department.
When the city gets sued,
the first thing they look at
is the officer training and experience.
They've decided
that experience can't just be
"I was standing there, too."
We can't start this
with the next round of recruits?
The LAPD is a bureaucracy,
Officer Bishop.
The last thing they care about
is a bunch of rookies.
So, how do we know
how many cases we owe?
Putting your listening ears on,
Officer Chen,
'cause I'm about to tell you.
To complete your checklist,
you still needed to be primary
on an auto theft,
carjacking, ethical dilemma,
meth possession,
a false I.D.,
assault on a peace officer,
and damage to city property.
- That's... like, seven things.
- What about us?
Officer West needs
a high-risk crowd control,
meth possession, and a carjacking.
Piece of cake, boss.
I mean "Sir."
I'm afraid to ask.
So, Officer Nolan,
the number of items you need
on your checklist are...
...zero.
You might want to thank
your training officer
for making you primary
starting day one.
And, since we are
ripping off the Band-Aid,
here's the rest of the bad news.
HR needs proof of completion
by end of shift tomorrow.
Otherwise, the recruits are
extended in the program.
Meaning we fall behind.
Sir, there's no way we can
control what "experiences"
they'll get in the next two days.
Understood.
Look, I know this is a tall order.
But I believe in you.
I've notified dispatch
of the calls that are needed.
They will funnel them
to your shops if...
when... when they come in.
That's it. All right?
Good luck. Be safe out there.
Officer Nolan,
since you're free and clear,
go see Detective Wolfe.
He has a job for you and Bishop.
Yes, sir.
Heard you had a case for us.
Yeah. Come in.
I need your help with a fugitive.
Craig Lawson... skipped town last year
when he learned
he was gonna be arrested
for embezzling a couple million
from the family business.
Then last week, Dad kicks the bucket.
You think Lawson will
come back for the funeral?
Or the reception afterwards
back at the house.
I'll stake that out while you head
to Malibu for the service.
I gave local law a heads-up.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
How's Bishop?
Oh, she's... okay.
Tell her I said the DRP is bull.
She risked her life to save mine.
There's no way she should get bounced
over an omit on her paperwork.
And I told the brass that.
I'll let her know.
I'm sure she'll appreciate that.
Do you think it would mean something,
if spoke to the brass?
- You're a rookie.
- I'm a rookie. That's...
New shades?
I can hear your mockery.
Then I said it right. Take 'em off.
I'm pretty familiar
with the duty manual,
and nowhere does it say
that I can't wear these.
So if I'm not breaking any rules,
why you sweatin' me?
Take them off or eat them.
Yes, ma'am.
7-Adam-07, assault and battery,
1501 Melrose.
Oh, they got to kick that
to someone else,
'cause I don't need no assault.
We don't pass on calls.
7-Adam-07, show us responding.
My tooth is loose.
Come on.
Ugh.
Hey. Officers.
Sir, what happened?
This guy stomped me inside the
bar 'cause I bumped into him.
I said I was sorry
then, bam, he did this.
What did he look like?
He's a white guy
wearing a red soccer jersey.
That's all I saw before I went fetal.
Stay here, bro. We got this.
I'm gonna call for backup.
Why? I can handle these guys.
Okay. You're primary.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Put the bloody game back on!
Sure... after you play my game.
It's called
"Which one of you hooligans"
"punched a nice man in the face?"
Control, send backup Code 3
for crowd control situation.
Great. My partner's
calling in the cavalry,
which means you have one minute
to make a choice.
Either everyone goes to jail
for 647f, drunk in public,
or you hand over the guy
who threw the punches
and I can turn the game back on.
So... what's it gonna be?
- What are you doing?
- Come on!
Yeah!
Game comes first, mate.
Perfect.
That was awesome.
That was reckless.
Come on. Bad guy's in custody,
no one got hurt,
and I just checked off
"high-risk crowd control."
Code 4. Cancel backup.
None of these people are Craig Lawson.
- No.
- So we wait.
You sure there's nothing I can
do to help you with your DRP?
There really isn't.
I could ask Ben to pull some strings.
He knows some people at City Hall.
Bending the rules
is how I got into this.
It's not gonna be how I get out.
- I can't just do nothing.
- Sure you can.
When an idea pops into
your head, ignore it.
Easy.
You think maybe we should
introduce ourselves
to the family, offer our condolences?
What did I say about ideas popping
in that big old head of yours?
Fine. We'll just...
stand at the back of a funeral viewing.
You don't find that a little creepy?
A little creepy, no.
Super creepy, yes.
But for now, it is our job.
He's clean.
I'm really sorry.
You're always carrying, Fred.
What happened?
Oh, uh...
Got my 30-day chip.
Wow.
Congratulations.
I feel bad I let you down.
It's all good. It's all good.
Say hi to Wilma for me.
All right. You're free to go.
You said he was a sure checkmark
for drug possession.
What can I say? He got clean.
It's inspiring, actually.
Well, forgive me if I don't appreciate
the human-interest story.
I mean, Jackson at least has a chance
with only three calls, but seven?
Okay, people win the lottery every day,
and with higher odds against them.
There are 18 million people
in the Greater Los Angeles area.
We just need seven of them
to break very specific laws.
7-19, store owner reporting customer
trying to pass counterfeit
bills near your location.
Hispanic male, brown hair, blue suit.
7-Adam-19, responding.
I-I don't need a counterfeiting case.
Look at the bright side. You do
need assaulting an officer.
Maybe he'll take a swing at you.
Thank you so much for coming.
Here we go.
Your presence here
is incredibly disrespectful
to my father's memory.
This is a private viewing. I'm
gonna have to ask you to leave.
I'm sorry, sir. We can't do that.
Your brother is a wanted fugitive.
And after all the money that he's
stolen from you and your family,
I'd think you'd want us here
to catch him if he shows up.
Craig's not gonna show up.
My father's dead
because of what Craig did.
So would you please leave
and let us have this time to mourn?
Hey.
- Is that...
- I think it is.
Where the hell is my money?!
- Aah!
- Hey!
Hey!
Stay there! Stay down! Don't move!
Give me your hands! Come here.
I only stabbed him 'cause
he scared the crap out of me.
I thought he was a zombie or something.
Good luck arguing that in court.
So, you faked your father's death
to trick your brother
into coming out of hiding?
I had to. We need the money he stole.
The business is going under.
Where's the money, Craig?!
Same place as your soul... gone.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
We should probably
transport them separately.
You think?
Jackpot.
Guy's out on probation for
a drug possession pinch.
If he's holding, this'll give me one of
the two checks I still need.
If he's holding.
Driver, turn off the engine.
Reach out of the window
and open the door.
Step out slowly. Hands where I can see.
- Where you headed today, sir?
- Work.
Mr. Gemetti, our system says
that you're on probation
for drug possession.
Got anything on you right now?
No, sir.
Mind if I pat you down?
Sure.
I've been clean since
the arrest four years ago.
- Find anything?
- No.
I'm gonna search the car.
Hands on the hood. Don't move.
What are you doing? This guy
has zero signs of drug use.
Eyes aren't dilated, no rapid speech,
or loss of coordination.
Possession does not require use.
He could be on his way home
right now to get high.
Given his history, a search
is completely within reason.
Officer West, wrap it up.
- Bingo.
- That's not mine.
I swear. I-I just bought
this car two months ago.
I've never even been in the back seat.
Your car, your baggy. You're
under arrest, Mr. Gemetti.
- You got to be kidding me.
- Officer West, this is empty.
No, there's clearly residue.
The law states if you can
see it and manipulate it,
it's possession.
We're not booking this guy
for a "lick" bag he didn't
even know was there.
Computer says he bought this car
at an auction two months ago,
and this bag looks older than you.
Hey! What...
Have your boss call me.
I'll tell them you were late
because you were helping
the LAPD on a case.
Thank you.
First you tell me I'm too cavalier,
and then you shoot me down
for being vigilant?
I shot you down because
you're being a bad cop.
Look, I get what's going on.
You spent a lifetime
preparing to be squeaky clean,
like your old man.
Only now you've discovered
dirt under his nails,
so you're spinning out,
rebelling against how you were raised.
I get it. And I'm giving you
room to work it out.
But that never gives you
an excuse to ruin a man's life
over a crime he didn't commit.
Try that again,
and I will end your career
before you even see that exam.
I still need seven calls.
You know how many I needed
when we started this morning?
Seven.
If it makes you feel any better,
I only got one.
- It doesn't.
- Look.
You're gonna be fine.
Yes, you are in the suck right now.
You just have to bear down
and get through it.
And... as motivation,
I booked us a spa day
the day after we take the exam.
Well, easy for you
to think about spa days.
You've got all your boxes checked.
Okay, look, I hate
to play the age card.
- Do you?
- It's the only card I have.
But one of the things
you learn as you get older
is perspective.
I cannot tell you how
many times in my 20s
I thought I was going under for good.
I was married, with a young kid.
I had credit card debts
up to my eyeballs.
It was bad.
But we survived.
We figured out a way
to just keep moving forward.
Well, that's great.
but surviving isn't the same
as succeeding.
No, it's not, but in two days,
we're going to be on
the other side of this.
And odds are,
we're going to be sitting down
taking this test together.
The pressure's getting to them.
It's getting to me.
Never had a rookie make it this far
and not qualify for the exam.
Nolan's over there
giving 'em a pep talk.
How can you tell?
'Cause he's been trying
to give me one all day.
He's right. You're gonna be fine.
Well, either way,
I'm off the fast track.
No more making chief by 40.
Thank God. Being brass sounds awful.
I mean, it's all politics and stats.
Might as well work corporate.
All units, we have a 215 in progress.
Carjacking, Beverly Drive at Oakwood.
7-Adam-19, show us responding.
7-Adam-07, show us responding
for training purposes.
The hell you are. Chen needs it more.
Like hell. We're primary.
Not if you don't get there first.
- Boot! Get to the shop!
- Let's go, Chen!
- ♪ Release the levy
- Oh. Oh!
- Police! Get out of the way!
- Police! Comin' through!
Coming through!
Oh! I'm...
♪ Bangarang
Ben?
Oh, my God.
Dr. Ramirez, dial 6671.
Hey.
Hey, buddy!
Oh, John, this is Paige.
Paige is great.
Do you know what else is great?
Codeine.
Hi. I'm Paige Thomas.
I'm with the LAPD
victim-witness services.
- John Nolan.
- Bad news.
I lost the car.
I know.
I stopped for coffee,
and when I got back to the car,
this guy just...
came out of nowhere and...
boom.
He attacked you.
He pointed a bun at me.
You mean a gun?
What did I say?
It doesn't matter.
I spoke to the doctor.
He said they're gonna
release you tonight,
so I'm gonna swing by, pick you up,
take you home, okay?
Yeah.
- It was scary.
- I know.
I know. Um...
Could I speak to you
in the hall for a moment?
Sure.
I'll be right back.
Hang tight.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Um...
Just hard for me to see him like that.
We've been friends a long time.
Are you gonna be here
until he's released?
Yeah. I'll keep him company.
Thank you.
Respiratory therapist, 4-E.
We gotta catch this guy.
Did Ben give you a description?
Yeah... adult male, white, maybe 5'10",
neck tattoo, and nose ring.
Yeah, we put out a BOLO
on the car. So far, nothing.
He would've gotten it
off the street quickly,
loaded it in the back of a semi.
By now, it's on its way to
a garage or a storage facility.
And in a week, it'll be
on a boat to Dubai or Japan.
- You stepping in?
- Yeah.
I've been hunting a high-end car ring
for the last few months.
Seems like their style...
broad daylight, busy street.
I want to help.
I'm serious.
I can see that.
Is that a no?
I'm sure Detective Wolfe will
reach out if he needs you.
Talia's waiting downstairs.
She'll take you back to the station
so you can clock out and come back.
Nurse supervisor, 1-2.
Every license plate
I run is coming up clear.
There's no way I make this deadline.
Not with that attitude.
We're almost at the end of shift.
I haven't checked a single box all day.
Look, a buddy of mine at 77th
said there's been more stolen cars
in this one neighborhood
in the last month
than all of Mid-Wilshire last year.
I hope so.
Those plates don't match that car.
And that's how you find
a rollin' stolen.
Light 'em up, Boot.
License and registration.
I know why you pulled me over.
Wrong plates.
I'm so sorry.
The plate's stolen or the car?
Neither.
They're mine... I mean my husband's.
Why are your husband's plates
on you car?
My husband and I could
only afford to register
one of our cars.
It's been a rough year.
When the one we registered broke down,
I didn't know what else to do.
I have to get to my night job.
It's illegal to use license
plates from a different vehicle.
I'm so sorry.
And stupid.
I should have known better.
All right. Uh, give me a minute.
I can't do this.
She's just trying to get by.
Case like this, it's your call.
You can cite her for the false plates
and check a box
or cut her loose
and risk not being able
to take the final exam.
I don't want to be that cop.
This whole thing is pissing me off.
I-It's just...
I don't want to do it this way...
running around
trying to tick off boxes.
It's not me.
Okay.
Then give her a warning.
All right, listen,
I'm not gonna write you up,
but you can't ever do this again, okay?
Thank you.
Drive safe.
So, wanna know the good news?
This counts as an ethical dilemma.
Which means you ha checked a box.
Only six more to go.
Easy.
What are we doing?
Having a sleepover.
- Sit and relax.
- That sounds fun.
Why here and not at my place?
Oh, 'cause your high-tech toilets
freak me out a little bit.
One unexpected colonic
is my limit.
- You hungry?
- No.
But I could use a scotch.
Scotch is really not
a good mixer with painkillers.
- Says who?
- Everyone.
Listen.
You know why we're having a sleepover?
'Cause I was carjacked?
That, um, is part of it.
But mostly because of what comes next.
Remember I told you about
that bank robbery I was in?
- Back home?
- Yeah.
It's why you joined the force.
You told me.
What I didn't tell you was...
how bad it messed me up.
And for a month after that,
before I joined the academy,
I...
I would be fine... and then...
...suddenly, I would just
see that gun in my face.
Sweat through my clothes on a cold day.
I broke down crying
at the drive-through
at the Dairy Queen.
No reason.
Well, not for no reason.
No. Not for no reason.
The point is,
yesterday, you felt safe.
Tomorrow, you won't.
But until you do,
I'm gonna be here for you.
How's that sound?
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Chen, you still need six.
West, you've got one.
And, Nolan, front desk duty.
All right, that's it.
Be safe out there.
Make a hole, make a hole.
Coming through.
Hey. Missed you in there.
I bet. Front desk duty?
Yeah. Everyone else is under the gun,
so I'll be spending the day
stamping forms.
Um, I know you told me not to,
but I wrote a little memo
about how great it is,
to have you as a training officer.
I know it doesn't matter.
It does.
You gonna show it to the chief?
Probably not.
Hey. You ready?
Ready.
- Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
I should just throw in the towel.
There's no way we're gonna
check six boxes in one day.
I'm not training a quitter, Boot.
We fight until the bell rings.
There's no other way.
7-Adam-19,
you still need a destruction
of city property?
Roger that.
911 just got a call.
Two blocks over from Wilshire and Pine.
Single car accident
while driving on the sidewalk.
What'd I tell you? We're still in this.
7-Adam-19, show us responding.
Put me to work.
I can't help Bishop today,
but I can help you catch the guy
who hurt my friend.
So get me pulled off the front desk
and assigned to this case.
Okay.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. Yes. Great.
Where do we start?
Have you ever driven a Lamborghini?
The LAPD had this just laying around?
Asset seizure from Narcotics.
You wanna drive it?
Hell yeah!
12-year-old John Nolan
crapping his pants right now!
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
Oh!
Oh, ho!
Oh, my God. Yes!
I...
What happened?
It's a bait car, equipped with cameras,
remote door locks, and a kill switch.
Carjacker steals the car,
we cut the engine,
- lock him inside.
- Exactly.
How will he know where to find it?
C.I.s are set to put the word out
as soon as it's in place.
Car like this will get our
boy's ass in gear real quick.
And we'll be there
waiting to hook him up.
Were you serious
about letting me drive?
The motor pool has your picture
on a dart board.
- What do you think?
- Yeah.
That's... fair.
Control, 7-Adam-07,
can you run plate
5-Paul-Charlie-Ida-410?
Ma'am, were you driving this vehicle?
Yeah.
No.
It's destruction of city property.
That's one more box checked.
5-Paul-Charlie-Ida-410
just reported 10-8-51.
RP says girlfriend took his car
without permission
20 minutes ago.
That bastard!
And grand theft auto
brings your total to three.
It's your lucky day, Boot.
Hey...
Hey! Stop!
Oh!
And that's technically a carjacking.
Thing has a motor. It counts.
Ma'am, do not attempt
to run away again.
- What's your name?
- Alexander Hamilton.
False I.D. to an officer
brings us to five.
I'm gonna need to see
your driver's license, please.
Assault on a police officer.
That's six.
Ooh!
Not bad, Officer Chen.
Go get her.
So, how's Ben doing?
Bit of a rough night.
But he'll make it through.
I know a good therapist,
specializes in violence-related trauma.
Helped me through some rough moments.
I'll pass it along.
Thank you.
Camo cap.
Nose ring.
Neck tattoo.
That's our guy.
We move in?
No, let's wait till he's inside first.
That's a scanner.
Goes through all the remote
key fob combinations
until it unlocks the car.
Hey.
Show me your hands.
Step out... nice and slow.
You know the drill. Hands on your head,
interlace your fingers.
Got him?
Got him.
Do not move.
Gun.
What happened to your hand?
I don't remember.
How 'bout I remind you?
Is there a problem, Officer Nolan?
No, sir.
You're under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right to talk to a lawyer
and have him present
while you're being questioned.
If you cannot afford a lawyer,
one will be appointed to you
at no expense.
Do you understand your rights
as I have read them to you?
- Yeah.
- Then get in.
We got him. I can't wait to tell Ben.
- Take a beat.
- Why?
'Cause this guy's a small piece
of a much bigger operation.
If he's willing to give up his employer,
the D.A. will let him walk.
That guy just put my
friend in a hospital.
- He has to pay for that.
- Yeah,
but the guy he works for has
put people in the ground.
Flipping a carjacker
for a bigger fish is S.O.P.
So if letting this guy go
is the price we have to pay,
then we're gonna pay it.
Is that gonna be a problem?
No, sir.
You okay?
- Fine.
- You're allowed to be nervous.
I'm not nervous.
I'm frustrated.
I've worked harder than anyone
in the past eight years,
and now it might all get
taken away because of this?
Because of one question I answered
before I even started the academy?
That's not gonna fly.
You got to own up to this, Talia.
You are one of our best,
but you can't tell me you didn't
know what you were doing
when you left Dylan's name off the list
but included your
other foster siblings.
Chief Williams may be unpredictable,
but the one thing he's not
gonna stand for is B.S.
- Understand?
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Chief Williams Officer Bishop,
Sergeant Grey, have a seat.
Thank you.
Sir, I'd like to make
a statement before we get...
I'm sure you would.
I know you're here to sing
Officer Bishop's praises,
and you wouldn't be wrong.
I've looked at her file.
She's a fine officer.
Here's what I want to know.
You left your foster brother,
a known felon, off your PHQ.
In short, you lied.
Tell me why that's not a problem.
I can't do that, sir.
What I did is a problem.
I violated the trust of this department
before I even started the job.
I could tell you I did
it to protect myself
and my future here,
but that is also inexcusable.
Because that meant pretending
that my foster brother
was not a part of my life.
I could've helped him.
But I chose to cut him out.
I have a lot to be sorry for.
And I am.
Well, all right, then.
Detective Ruiz, would you begin?
Officer Bishop, Internal Affairs
has combed through your
entire career with the LAPD
to make sure that your
association with this felon
has not further impaired your judgment.
In doing so, I have found
several discrepancies,
errors, and omissions.
I think it's easiest if we just
start with the most recent
and work our way backwards.
Now, in October of this past year,
you failed to secure your LAPD vehicle.
He gave you the keys.
He did exactly what you told him to do,
and you beat him to a pulp anyway.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I just want to know why.
Or is that just the
kind of person you are?
I don't got to talk to you about this.
Detective said if I give up my boss,
I walk free.
Well, I hope he doesn't show.
Oh, he will.
My intel's good.
Walked the perimeter.
We're good to go.
Hey, I heard your boy Jackson
got his last checkmark.
He and Lopez folded
into the strike team.
That's him... black jacket.
And that's Ben's car.
We have positive I.D. on our target.
All units, prepare to move in.
Police! Show me your hands!
- Hands up! Hands up!
- Nobody move!
Hands! Hands!
Nolan, go after him!
Lopez, Jackson, with me!
Hands where I can see 'em!
Man #4 Turn around!
- Jackson!
- I'm driving.
Fine!
We need to flank him.
Take Broadway.
7-Adam-15, foot pursuit west,
alley of Chinatown Plaza!
Suspect headed east
on Hill Street.
We can cut him off in the plaza.
Wait! What are you doing?!
Brake!
Ma'am! Are you okay?
Police! Everybody down!
Gotcha.
Freeze, punk! Don't you make a move!
You okay?
No!
Car thieves... are supposed
to have car chases,
not foot chases.
Control, suspect in custody.
Hi, I heard it wasn't going so well.
Not particularly.
What the hell are you doing
here, Nolan?
Standing up for what's right.
Nolan, don't!
- Don't!
- Hey!
Son?
- Are you lost?
- No, sir.
I'm Officer Bishop's rookie,
and I need to be heard.
No, you don't. My apologies, sir.
- Officer Nolan was just lea...
- Hold on, Sergeant.
If the man needs to be heard,
he needs to be heard.
Better be good, though.
Yeah, it better be.
Sir, um...
Sorry, Chief.
- It's been a bit of a day.
- For me, too.
Yes, sir. Sorry about that.
Here's the thing.
For the last six months,
I have watched Officer Bishop
selflessly give to this city.
She has made people safer,
changed people for the better.
And...
inspired me to be
a better police officer.
I entered this program at a deficit...
older than all the other rookies...
by far.
But Officer Bishop showed me how
to make my life experience
work for me...
so that one day, I might be...
half the cop she is.
I know I'm nobody
in the department, sir.
I'm still on probation, still learning
all the rules and regulations...
Oh, like the three you broke
when you pushed your way in here?
Actually, I can answer that.
Disobeying a direct order,
disregarding chain of command,
and conduct unbecoming of an officer.
Then you do understand that, uh,
there's a certain risk
to your actions here today.
Yes, sir, I do.
But I was raised to stand up
for the people I care for.
I realize what Officer Bishop
did was an ethical violation,
and there needs to be consequences.
But she taught me
that this job is about judgment
and fairness and compassion.
Officer Bishop wasn't trying
to game the system.
She was simply determined to be
the best police officer
this city's ever seen.
And I needed you to know that.
You're the officer
who was with Captain Andersen
when she died.
I was.
Huh.
Sergeant...
when am I administrating
this recruit's oral exam?
A week from today, sir.
Until that majestic day of reckoning,
Officer Nolan,
get the hell out of my office.
Yes, sir. Yes.
So, are you trying to get fired?
- No, sir.
- Then you're just a moron?
- Yes, sir.
- But he's my moron.
Do you think it helped?
I don't think it hurt.
Well, we'll see.
Regardless, the Chief's gonna
be coming for you next week.
Well, let him come. I'll be ready.
You know he can test you
on anything from the rook book,
penal code, and duty manual...
anything at all.
I know them forwards and backwards.
Really?
Page 47, rook book.
How many commas?
You okay?
I really screwed up.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I just...
I don't know who I'm
supposed to be right now.
And when I pushed
to be something I'm not, I...
...almost got someone killed.
The hell you doing, Boot?
You're still one shy on your checklist.
I... It's too late. Shift's over.
Shift's over when we punch out,
and we're not punching out till
we get you a meth possession.
Come on. Grey approved the OT.
Let's go.
Um...
Go. I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Really.
We'll talk later.
Your boot gave a nice speech.
Can I help you with something?
I'm just here to inform you
that it may take a week or two
before we make a final decision
in your matter.
Then I'll see you in a week or two.
However...
...I could give you a decision today.
Right now, as a matter of fact.
And what would that decision be?
Cleared on all charges.
If? It sounds like there's an "if."
You're smart. That's why
you're perfect for this.
For what?
I need someone here
to be my eyes and ears
at the Mid-Wilshire Station.
You want me to be a rat
for Internal Affairs?
I know it sounds bad.
But it will save your job.
The Chief takes my
recommendations very seriously.
Let's be honest...
your Boot's speech was good,
but it wasn't that good.
Think about it.
We'll talk soon.
Sorry. Wish I had better news.
Ah, doesn't matter.
It matters to me.
I want you to have closure.
Did closure help you
after the bank robbery?
Not really.
Which is why I'm out of here.
Tomorrow morning,
wheels-up to St. Barts.
From there, who knows.
You think a change of scenery
will help ease the trauma?
I think a cold drink
on white sand's a good start.
Oh.
Well, disappearing for a few months...
you have that option.
Most folks don't have that.
Got to sit and try
to deal with their PTSD
while still holding
their lives together.
Oh, so I should feel bad I have money?
No.
I'm saying...
escape is a privilege.
But you won't really be escaping.
All the stress and nightmares
and feelings from the attack,
they're gonna come along
to the beach with you.
And I can tell you that
because I've been there.
The only thing that helped me
make it to the other side was...
...becoming a cop.
- You think I should join up?
- No! No.
No.
Nobody wants that.
But you could think about
using the trauma to motivate you.
Make something positive
out of a terrible experience.
That victim's services woman
gave me her card.
I could write her a check.
You could.
And... you should.
But you think I need
to be more hands-on?
I think helping people...
when you can look them in the eye...
is one of the most fulfilling things
I've ever done with my life.
I'll call her in the morning.
Good.
I hate ginger ale.
I know.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com