Shouldn't we be pulling them
over, for being on their phones?
All of them? We'll be writing
23120 tickets till judgment day.
23123.
You tried to slip that past me.
23123 is the hands-free vehicle code.
Congratulations. So, what's 23120?
Driving while flossing?
"No driver shall operate a motor vehicle
"while wearing glasses having a
temple width of 1/2" or more
if any part of said temple extends
below the horizontal center of the lens
"so as to interfere
with lateral vision."
Yeah, that's what...
actually what I meant.
Where's your rook book?
In my locker.
It weighs four pounds.
I was told I'd be fired if I lost it.
You don't keep your gun
in your locker, do you?
You need to know the information
in that book backwards and forwards.
You should be studying
it every chance you get.
I do, every night.
- Mm-hmm.
- You don't believe me?
New job, new city, newly single.
Color me doubtful you're
living a monastic life.
7-Adam-15, armed robbery in progress.
- 3577 Olvera.
- Here we go.
Get down! Get down!
Flat on the ground.
Face down.
I got him, Boot. Get him.
Out of the way!
Hold it.
Show me your hands.
Take off that mask nice and slow.
Hands behind your head.
Interlace your fingers.
Do not move.
What's in the box, big fella?
It's a urine sample for a drug test.
If it got to the lab, then Bo
would've violated his parole
and gone back to prison for two years,
so we boosted it.
Well, now he's going away for longer.
You steal that, too?
It was my dad's.
I've been trying to work
up the courage to propose,
but what if he says no?
The guy's all I can think about.
He's a drug addict and an ex-con.
I don't care.
I love him.
I love you, Bo Sokolovsky.
And I have since the moment
that you hit on me at the zoo.
And I want to spend the
rest of my life with you...
starting in two to five years.
Will you marry me?
Hell, yeah.
It's awesome.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna need that.
That marriage is gonna last forever,
or flame out in five minutes.
Either way, best proposal story ever.
O-Okay, that's wonderful,
but the question I asked was,
"In what circumstance can
a firearm be discharged"
"at a moving vehicle?"
Only if the person in the vehicle
is immediately threatening
an officer or another person
with deadly force using something
other than the vehicle.
Yeah.
I don't really have one...
a good proposal story.
Yeah, well, there's always next time.
Not, uh...
S... Not with me.
- I-I just meant that...
- No, and I-I wasn't fishing.
I was just oversharing. I...
Who knows if I'm even
gonna get married again?
I mean, and this whole cop thing
is a legendary relationship killer.
Though we seem to be
navigating it fairly well, aren't we?
Yeah.
Uh, okay.
List all descriptors needed for
a firearm in a crime report.
- Officer Nolan.
- Mm-hmm. Yes?
Can you focus?
- We need to study.
- Mm-hmm.
What are the descriptors of a firearm?
A serial number, maker's name, model,
caliber or gauge,
color of metal...
length of barrel.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Everyone have a seat.
Today is a special day for our rookies.
'Cause today...
we switch things up.
That's right.
Everybody gets a new training officer.
Nolan, you'll be riding
with Officer Lopez.
West, you'll be riding
with Officer Bradford.
And Chen, you'll be with Bishop.
But learning how to navigate a new T.O.
is not your only challenge.
By the end of next shift,
I expect every rookie to uncover
something personal about
their training officer,
something they don't want you to know.
This will be a test of your
investigative instincts
and your fortitude.
Best insight will win a day off.
Worst one...
handles Saturday night cavity searches.
That's it. Good luck.
So, what's Lopez like to ride with?
Yeah, like I'm gonna
give you a head start.
Tim's gonna eat me alive, isn't he?
You? No. You're a rock star,
a legacy who excelled at the academy.
If Tim could create a cop in a
test tube, it would be you.
Unless he's gonna set
out to dominate you
and prove that you aren't all that.
Is it too late to change my answer?
'Cause, uh, that.
Oh, hey, what about Talia?
Any tips on how to get on her good side?
Oh, I'm sorry, Jackson's right.
No head starts.
Is the kid really a rock star?
Jackson?
Yeah. He's better prepared
than any rookie I've ever had.
Screw prep. How is he out on the street?
So far, so good.
What about Nolan?
He's a talker.
Oh.
Uh, usually Officer Bishop has me drive.
She feels it's a better
way to evaluate how I...
This is my shop. I drive.
Copy that.
So...
I was raised by a single mom.
Everything I own was a hand-me-down
from my four brothers, so I care about
what I wear and how I look.
Now you don't have to
spend the next two days
hunting for insight.
I don't think that's how Sergeant Grey
wanted me to gain insight.
Are you a teacher's pet, Boot?
'Cause I thought I was gonna
get a change of pace with you.
Uh, no, ma'am. Just looking to get
the most out of the experience.
Good. Because if I win
you Grey's day off,
you're gonna fix my garage door.
I heard you were a contractor.
Yeah, no, happy to help.
Probably gonna need a little more than.
"She likes nice clothes"
to win this thing.
So, where are we off to?
Court. I have to testify in a trial.
Should take a few hours.
Quiet time, starting now.
This is gonna be a great day.
I was glad when Sergeant
Grey paired us up.
- You were?
- Yeah.
Being a police officer is in your DNA.
It's gonna be my privilege to...
I've been shot!
Where are you, Boot?
I'm bleeding to death. You
have to call for help.
Where are you?
North Mansfield, cross
street is Beverly Boulevard.
There's a medical
center on Third Street,
but I would see that you
were taken to Cedars.
Better trauma center.
And the best coffee in L.A.
is two blocks down.
So, all the stuff about...
The only thing that's
gonna make me happy
is breaking your spirit.
- Look, uh...
- Save it.
- But...
- I said save it.
You want to risk your reputation
to get it on with Nolan,
that's your call.
I only care if it impacts
your performance.
It won't.
Good, then there's nothing
left to talk about.
And don't even think of
looking for insight into me.
Registration is expired on that tag.
Call it in.
7-Adam-15,
show us at a vehicle stop.
at Loma Linda and Fountain.
Blue Outback, 2-Sam-Adam-Mary-5-6-4.
7-Adam-15,
that vehicle is suspected
in a hit and run.
7-Adam-15, four occupants just bailed,
heading north and south.
Get the driver, Boot! I'll cut them off.
LAPD, get up.
Hands behind your head.
Turn around.
Don't move.
What are you doing?
I told you to get the driver.
This guy was right here.
Am I in trouble for catching a criminal?
What was his crime?
Who were your friends in the car?
I never met them before.
They just saw me walking
and gave me a ride.
Then why did you run?
'Cause everyone else did.
Did you find anything
on him when you searched him?
Driver's the only one we can
legally tie to the vehicle.
You should know that.
Page 117 of your rook book.
Cut him loose.
Never been to the courthouse before.
This is exciting.
That feeling will pass.
Caught this break and
enter 10 months ago.
Since then, it's been two
preliminary hearings,
two motions to suppress. It's endless.
Hey, Lopez. Looking good.
Thanks. How's your wife?
This is the only place in L.A.
where you can find all the law
enforcement agencies together...
LAPD, Highway Patrol,
Sheriff's Department...
everyone acting like the
top of the food chain.
See that guy with the comb-over?
They call him Hot Stuff.
Know why?
Nothing comes to mind.
'Cause he somehow managed
to get sriracha in his eyes
while he was driving.
Ended up in Echo Park Lake.
Oh, and that's Officer Davis.
She collects American Girl dolls
and uses them to recreate
scenes from "50 Shades."
She's single, if you're wondering.
Thank you. How do you know all this?
Ah, well, if you want to keep secrets,
don't work in law enforcement.
I had us attached to a raid.
Figured you didn't get a round
off the day I got shot,
so you'd be itching to
throw some bullets around.
Detective Singh.
Bradford.
When are you gonna make the
jump out of patrol, huh?
Never. I work for a living.
Yeah.
This West's kid?
Yes, sir. Jackson West.
You ready to mix it up, son?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
We got a known gunrunner two blocks up.
We can pin at least three
murder weapons on him.
We're gonna put eyeballs on his place,
make sure he's home, then we go in hot.
You're rolling with the
big boys now, Boot.
- Bless you.
- Thank you.
Shoot.
Officer needs help!
Prisoner on the loose!
Stop! Police!
Sorry. I tried to catch the guy.
Well, now we got to find him.
Fugitive's name is Nestor Garcia.
He's a mid-level drug dealer
looking at 10 to 20 if he's convicted.
Residence is in Boyle Heights.
I volunteered us to check it out.
Leave that in the locker next time.
Officer Bishop suggested...
- Do I look like Officer Bishop?
- No.
Grey switched it up so you guys
get a different perspective.
Mine is you do your homework at home.
Heard you caught a bullet.
Went right through me.
Barely worth mentioning to you.
Singh's been stabbed six times.
Nine.
It was a busy summer.
I'll say.
So, have you known
Officer Bradford long?
Don't answer that.
Watch Commander's got
him looking for insight
into his T.O.
Copy that.
But my silence won't be cheap.
You're not getting my Dodger tickets.
One game. That's it.
Two pizzas?
The gunrunners are at home.
We're in business. Let's go gear up.
Do you, uh, date cops?
I'm not asking...
I mean, just trying to get some insight.
You know, that, um, CHP
officer at the courthouse
- was hitting on you.
- It's not worth it.
That guy can run around
racking up trophies,
but I date one cop, and I get a rep,
so I fish in other pools.
Nestor Garcia, police.
Come out.
What if we were to talk
to the local merchants?
All right.
Hey, how much?
A dollar.
A little steep, but all right.
Thank you.
Mm.
Didn't expect it to be so, uh...
thick.
You know the family next door?
Sure. The dad's a drug dealer.
My mom gets really talky
when she has Chardonnay.
Have you seen him around today?
No, he's probably at the thing.
What thing?
Buy some more lemonade
and I'll tell you.
Are you trying to extort a
law enforcement officer?
No, it's basic supply and demand.
I have something you need,
so I can set the price.
At least he's getting
a quality education.
Too bad he won't get the same
one in juvenile detention.
You got a permit for
this lemonade stand?
There he is.
What's the party for again?
His daughter's quinceañera.
- 15th birthday.
- Oh, sorry.
We don't get a lot of those
in rural Pennsylvania.
It's fun.
Aww.
He escaped custody to share
a dance with his daughter.
That's kind of sweet.
It's selfish, 'cause
now her memory of this
is gonna be us arresting him
in front of her entire family.
He did it for himself, not her.
That never occurred to me.
That's because you had
a dad who was around.
Let me guess. Your dad was M.I.A.,
show up when it's convenient,
bring a toy, act like a savior.
It was a stuffed animal.
Last one he brought, I fed
to the garbage disposal.
And then he got cancer.
So...
do we let them finish the dance?
Of course.
I'm not a monster.
You told me to go after the driver,
and I deviated from your instruction.
- It won't happen again.
- Mm-hmm.
You don't believe me?
I believe you do what you want
and you rationalize it after.
I don't take your advice, and
then you... you punish me?
How is that right?
Boot, you have a fundamental
misunderstanding
of what's happening here.
So enlighten me.
Learning how to be a cop is the
hardest thing you'll ever do.
And instead of focusing
everything you have
on the task at hand,
you split your focus
to be with Nolan.
And you risk losing it completely
if you're ever found out.
You think you're the first
rookie to date a cop?
This city is littered
with the failed potential
of rookies like you.
With all due respect, ma'am,
there are no other rookies like me.
Don't fool yourself, Boot.
They're all like you.
And the only ones who make it through
are the ones who take
their job so serious
that they put everything else aside.
On your toes, Boot. These
guys are armed for war.
Early-warning system.
You just happened to have that on you?
Of course not.
My dad taught me to carry dog biscuits.
Thought he was pulling my leg,
but that just worked like gangbusters.
Police!
Let's go, Boot!
What's wrong? Are you hit?
Clear!
- Through the yard!
- Clear here!
Two down inside. You guys okay?
Yeah.
So, uh, did you have a quinceañera?
Of course, and I looked good.
Who did you dance with?
'Cause you said single mom.
My abuelo.
- Her dad.
- Oh.
He made me laugh the whole time.
My mom was pissed.
Lopez!
Give us a minute.
- Why? What's going on?
- Just do it.
The hell were you thinking
letting me hit the streets
- with a broken rookie?
- He's not broken.
He froze when the
bullets started flying.
You gonna tell me the same
thing didn't happen with you
the day I got shot?
I thought I helped him get past it.
Well, you didn't. Now he's my problem.
Not for long.
Any idea what that's about?
Me.
What happened?
I think I'm done.
- What?
- Yeah.
I froze up when the shooting started.
Same thing happened at
the Selby shootout,
but Lopez covered for me, so...
Look... I don't know how to fix it.
I have to fix it.
I lied to Andersen to cover for the kid.
If you out him, my career is over, too.
Well, that was stupid.
All right, look.
I know just the neighborhood
to take him to.
He'll self-destruct by
the end of the day,
I'll catch him on my
body cam, he'll be done.
No one will know about you.
His father's a commander
at internal affairs...
I don't care. Boot's a menace...
This is exactly why I didn't tell you.
You think Jackson's
father won't blame you
for the kid's failure?
This is political whether
you like it or not.
- What do we do?
- Leave him on the streets?
Hope he doesn't get you killed?
No.
I don't know.
He could be a good cop, h-he's smart.
He has instincts you can't teach.
There's potential.
Screw potential.
Tim.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Listen, you're gonna
make it through this, okay?
Lucy and I are gonna help you.
How?
Walk away, Boot.
- Officer Bradford...
- I gave you an order.
Listen to me. He's worth fighting for.
You and Lopez both know it.
7-Adam-15,
female juvenile reports
being held against her will.
Owens and Arlington. Code 3.
What's going on?
We got a call. Young girl said
she was being held captive
at this location.
Are you kidding me? Sarah's
holding us hostage.
We're bleeding money every minute
she won't come out of the trailer.
We need to see her.
LAPD. Open up.
Am I in trouble?
- Are you being held hostage?
- No.
Then yeah, filing a false police
report is kind of a crime.
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't know what else to do.
I don't want to be here anymore.
I hate it.
Is someone making you?
My foster mom.
She's an agent.
She's been putting me up for things
ever since I was placed with her.
I just want to be back with my real mom,
but Alice won't even let me talk to her.
Sarah, are you okay? W-What happened?
Let's talk over here.
Wh...
I... I don't understand.
- Is something wrong?
- She says you're making her do this.
That's ridiculous.
She agreed to try it.
I-I'm just trying to teach her
a sense of responsibility
and a work ethic.
I do that for all the kids I foster.
Sarah also said you're keeping
her from her birth mother.
Her birth mother is an alcoholic
who just got out of prison.
She's in no position
to care for that girl.
All right, give your
information to Officer Chen.
We'll follow up with the state.
Right.
Here's my card.
If you have a real problem,
give me a call.
Thanks.
Guess you were right
about cops and secrets.
Yeah, I should've taken my own advice.
For what it's worth, you
covering for Jackson
was a stand-up thing to do.
It was selfish, not noble.
I did it to protect myself.
Sir.
I am more committed to this job
than anyone you've ever trained.
I'm gonna get past this.
We ain't playing dress-up here, Boot.
So, what's the plan?
Out me to Andersen?
Drop me off in gang territory?
What, public execution?
All that I'm asking is
that you try and fix me...
...instead of just throwing me away.
I don't do lost causes.
Now, if I were you, I'd
prepare for tomorrow
to be your last day on the job.
Hey Jackson, it's me, again, um...
Just calling to see if you're
all right, buddy, just...
call me back, all right?
Bye.
Did you get him?
No. Uh, left another message.
Hmm.
Tim won't throw Jackson under the bus.
How can you even say that?
All the guy does is torture you.
He's calculating, not cruel.
Plus, he's got a massive ego.
He'll probably take it as a challenge
to his abilities as a T.O.
I hope you're right.
Um...
I have something to tell you.
Talia knows about us.
She told me on day 2,
said it would be a mistake
to keep dating you.
Okay, um...
Okay, first off, what
business is that of hers?
And second, why would you
wait so long to tell me?
I didn't want to screw this up.
And I didn't want you to
confront her and get fired.
Oh.
Look. Talia won't tell anyone,
and we'll just make sure
nobody else finds out.
Okay?
Okay.
So, are you gonna tell me my fate,
or are you just gonna
torture me all morning?
You really in a hurry to find out?
No.
Who is it?
Officer Bradford.
I.D.
You're looking at us through
the peephole, Wallace.
Just open up.
- Who's he?
- Who are you?
My new Boot.
Have you been out of the
apartment recently?
The downstairs buzzer's broken.
Can you fix it for me?
Fix it yourself.
I'll be in the car.
What... What am I supposed to do?
Talk to Wallace.
Can I come in?
No.
Okay, look, I...
I told Nolan.
Told him what?
Not what you want me to tell him,
but that you know.
Bishop.
Got a little girl looking for you.
Says she's following up on the
911 call you took yesterday.
Is that the foster kid?
Sarah, yeah.
Wait in the shop.
Come on.
Sir? Wallace.
Dude, my T.O. says talk to you.
Okay? So I got to talk to you.
Look, I'm not going away,
so just let me in.
Please.
So, how do you, uh,
know Officer Bradford?
We used to date.
You should see the look on your face.
No, uh, a few years
ago, I was hate-crimed.
Tim went with me
to the hospital, and...
I haven't been able to
get rid of him since.
You're a big traveler.
I used to be.
Don't go out much anymore?
Being outside is overrated.
I talked to my mom last night.
She said she wanted me back.
But Alice is blocking her.
It's not her call, Sarah.
I spoke with social
services this morning.
Your mom just did six
months for a hit and run.
She's clean now.
She told me.
I hope so.
But she's gonna have
to sustain it a while
before they put you back with her.
You're just like the rest of them.
Sit down.
I grew up in the system...
four foster families by
the time I was your age,
each of them worse than
where you are now.
At first, I was angry all the time.
It was unfair, you know?
Every other kid got to
have a happy childhood.
But you got to get past that.
You've been placed in a
good home with a foster mom
who's trying to help you be independent,
teach you a skill so you don't
have to rely on anyone.
The sooner you stop feeling
sorry for yourself
and do what has to be done,
the better off you'll be.
I haven't left this
apartment in 15 months.
I tried at first, when I got
home from the hospital.
I even made it downstairs a few times.
That was over a year ago.
What happens when you try to leave?
Have you ever been on fire and
underwater at the same time?
Yeah. Yesterday.
Turns out I have a thing
about being shot at.
And if I don't get past it, I'm done.
Look... I'm hardly the
person to give advice,
but if you're gonna conquer this,
you've got to do it now.
If I'd only forced myself to
go outside on the first day,
I wouldn't be trapped in here.
Lopez, Nolan.
You wanted to see us?
The quinceañera felon
you picked up yesterday, Nestor Garcia?
He's requested to speak with you both.
Why?
A.D.A. thinks it's
connected to a plea deal
he's trying to cut.
She's bringing him in
from the courthouse now.
You let me know how it goes.
Yes, ma'am.
I want to thank you for yesterday.
That dance meant a lot to my daughter,
and the fact that you let me finish,
that means a lot to me.
So, to reward you, I have a gift.
A drug deal is going
down this afternoon...
large shipment,
the kind of bust that'll
get you noticed.
And you're just giving us this
because we were nice to you?
No, I'm doing this to
reduce my sentence.
But I'm giving it to you
because you were nice to me.
So, you'd better hurry up, call the D.A.
to make a deal,
because the exchange is
going down in two hours.
Okay, according to Garcia,
the exchange is going down at
Stoneson Home Supply on Sunset.
W... They're gonna make a drug deal
in the parking lot in broad daylight?
Box stores are the perfect cover.
Busy parking lots, multiple exits.
They hide in the chaos.
At 1500 hours, a car loaded
with 80 kilos of cocaine
driven up from Mexico will
land in the parking lot.
The driver will walk away.
A runner for the buyer
will climb behind the
wheel and drive off.
The whole thing takes 90 seconds.
According to Nestor, the
shipment is in a red Civic
with Nevada plates.
Now, the parking lot only
has two access points...
here and here.
Officer Bradford, you'll be
parked out of sight over there.
Officer Bishop, you'll have
all eyes on this exit here.
And what about us, Sergeant?
What's our position?
We need to know exactly
when the car lands,
so we need eyes on the
whole parking lot.
You will be with me here.
License and registration?
This ain't dinner theater. Relax.
I think I see our welcoming party.
A Ram, three Hispanics inside,
heads on a swivel.
No sign of our red Civic yet.
Stand by.
Copy that.
Thanks.
For, uh, not outing me to Grey.
I had a good talk with Wallace.
Great.
Can you promise me you're cured?
Of course not.
Then if things go sideways on this bust,
you do not get out of this shop.
- Do you understand?
- Sir...
Look, the only answer here is "yes."
I cannot rely on you to have my back,
and I will not have
your death on my head.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
I... I really like him.
I've never been serious
about anyone before,
and I'm playing it casual,
but the thought of ending it, I...
I don't want to.
But then I heard you tell Sarah
to stop feeling sorry for herself,
and to just, you know, make
peace with her situation,
and I realized I can't just
run from a hard decision.
I have to face it head-on...
I'm sorry. How exactly
did you hear that?
I might have wandered into observation
while you were talking to her. I...
Sorry.
Look, I appreciate you being
honest with me about Nolan.
More importantly, I think you're finally
being honest with yourself.
That's all I was looking to provoke...
an informed choice.
Here we go.
Red Civic, Nevada plates,
entering parking lot.
Go, go, go!
7-Adam-15, going after the red Civic.
Aah!
Ma'am! Stay down!
Stay in the car.
I'm opened up!
Let's go! I got you!
Stay down!
I got you.
I can make it. I can get in there.
- For reload!
- I got you!
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Got you.
One suspect in custody.
7-Adam-15, in pursuit of red Civic
heading east on Chapman.
That is a lot of coke.
Yo. Yo, yo, yo, yo. You call an Uber?
I'll understand if you
don't give me a five star.
The moment of truth is upon us.
End of shift.
Time to come clean.
What did you learn about your T.O.s?
Officer West.
Sorry, sir.
I was unable to gain any
insight into Officer Bradford.
That's disappointing.
Officer Chen?
I, too, failed in. my
assignment, Sergeant.
All right.
All right, that leaves
you, Officer Nolan.
You can literally say
anything and win the contest.
Sorry, sir. Just as
stumped as the others.
Okay, fine.
So no one wants extra credit.
I guess we'll start at the basics.
Tomorrow morning, you will have a quiz
on your rook books.
Study hard,
'cause 80 percent is
considered a fail in my house.
Dismissed.
Looks like I fixed your rookie for you.
Thanks.
And I didn't get you anything.
The only thing I need is for
you not to lie to me again.
In the future, I'd appreciate it
if you stayed away
from my personal life.
- Boot, this wasn't about you.
- The hell it wasn't.
My relationship with Lucy is not a game.
- I care about her.
- Really?
'Cause when this gets
out, and it will get out,
it'll brand her for the
rest of her career.
So, if you care about her
like you say you do,
you wouldn't even put
her in this position.
- Hey.
- Hey. Uh...
I need to...
- Can I go first?
- Uh...
Yeah, sure.
When I first met you, I
had just turned my life
upside down, and I was...
I-I was lost.
I was alone, everything was alien to me.
But then you turned me
right-side up again,
and you gave me the confidence
not just to endure the challenges,
but to actually enjoy them,
and I'm so grateful for that.
And now that we're here,
I just don't think...
Um...
Are you breaking up with me?
Yeah, Lucy, I am.
Mm, because, uh,
I was gonna break up with you.
Then why are you mad?
I have been struggling with
this decision for weeks
because I really like you.
And you just ripped off the Band-Aid
like it was no big deal.
Of course it's a big deal.
I don't want to do this.
But I can't be the reason you fail.
Oh, so you're protecting yourself?
No, I'm trying to put
myself in your shoes.
You'll never be in my shoes.
And you'll never know
how unfair that is.
You're right.
You're right, and I'm sorry.
I joined the Academy on a whim.
I knew that my parents would hate it.
But I had no idea how
much I would love it.
Being a cop is the first thing
I've ever been serious about.
And you...
You were the second.
- Lucy...
- Don't. Don't.
Yeah, yeah. It's better this way, so...
I will see you at work.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com