He's clean.
See?
Just out for a stroll.
A stroll?
It is sad the way you guys
are harassing an innocent man.
Officer Nolan, are you familiar
with the Crack Almanac?
- Is it available on Kindle?
- Four basic principles...
Look Out, Cook Out,
Cash Out, Stash Out.
Cook out...
cook cocaine into crack.
- Look out...
- For the cops.
You really could stand
to work on that one.
Stash out.
You want to stash
the rocks nearby
so if the cops catch you,
you're clean.
♪ Out of control,
out of control, out of control ♪
- So, you want me to...
- Yep.
Of course.
♪ Out of control,
out of, out of control ♪
♪ Yeah, dodged the okee-doke,
rolled your hope joke ♪
- ♪ Eyes be overflowed... ♪
- Oh, God.
Oh! That stinks!
See, I don't even...
♪ Surfing on a moonshot ♪
♪ New codes hacked ♪
♪ New lows, new flow,
knew nothing but the dope ♪
- Goat.
- Okay. You know what?
Maybe D'Andre
really is
just out for a stroll.
Ah, but there is still one
principle left, Officer Nolan...
Cash out.
See,
a real good hustler
only wants to be seen
on his corner doing business,
which means if D'Andre is here,
so is his money.
♪ Boom, boom ♪
♪ I'm a real-ass,
grown-ass Manitoba ♪
♪ Flow be like a
S.E.A.L.-Team-Six-ass strike ♪
♪ Son... feel these beatings,
he'll quit preaching ♪
♪ When your stillborn brain
stops thinking ♪
- That's not mine.
- You sure?
'Cause it looks like
a couple thousand here.
Can I see that remote?
I got Henry this same model
for Christmas.
♪ Caught it on a ♪
♪ New quest, who this? ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh... ♪
Cash out and stash out.
Stroll's over. Turn around,
put your hands behind your back.
Left, left, pull up,
pull up, pull up.
Sorry!
*THE ROOKIE*
Season 01  Episode 16
Episode Title: "Greenlight"
Yo, I need a break.
I can't believe
we don't get
a single vacation
or personal day
during our entire
probationary year.
It's how we prove
our commitment.
Wearing wool in August
isn't enough?
Why are you so cheery?
I'm just livin'
my best life.
Oh.
- Jessica.
No.
Yeah, okay, a little.
- Yes, yes, yeah, a little.
- Yeah.
That's great.
You... You seem really happy.
- Thank you.
- Oh, we should do a double date.
I'd love for you
to meet Gino.
Sounds great, but she's
out of town right now.
She's, uh, doing a lecture
at the Department
of Homeland Security.
Can I have your attention?
Let's go, Boots.
Everyone, gather up.
All right, guys, listen up.
Internal Affairs
will be conducting
random integrity tests
this week.
Reversals.
That's right, Officer West.
What's a reversal?
Where cops go undercover
to rat out other cops.
IA officers will be
spending the week
pretending to be criminals
so they can analyze
how we treat them.
So, what Tim said.
Do you think this is a joke,
Officer Lopez? Officer Bradford?
- No, ma'am.
Good.
'Cause I take it very seriously.
If you have to change
your behavior
because of these reversals,
we have a problem.
My officers do things
the right way... every day.
Is that understood?
Yes, ma'am.
Dismissed.
Are reversals
really that hard to spot?
I mean, you can usually
make a cop by the way they walk.
Not these guys.
They train for this.
It's like the Super Bowl
to them.
They go all-in.
About two years ago,
they took over a bank
and masqueraded as robbers
just to test our response time.
They cleared
the bank out first.
Every teller and customer
was a plant.
That's dedicated.
No, it's a waste of time
and resources,
which is why I make it my mission
to seek and destroy reversals.
I don't see
what the fuss is about.
A cop should be held
to the highest standards.
Of course you side with IA.
Your dad's in charge.
Okay, it's not about my dad.
The integrity of a co...
- Hey.
- Morning.
Here to see a client?
Yeah.
I won't keep you.
Did... Did you guys
break up?
No. We had... a few dates.
Then we stopped.
Sounds like
a breakup to me.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
- It's fine. Let's go.
- Okay.
7-Adam-15, disturbance
at the Altobello Hotel.
You're saying
this is my fault?
You're damn right
it's your fault!
Do you have any idea
how much my car costs?
Please, ma'am.
If we could take this inside...
What seems to be the problem here?
Valet destroyed my car.
- That car?
- Yeah, look, the paint job.
Right there.
That scratch
will buff right out.
- You're lying. He's lying!
- This is a civil matter.
Feel free
to take photographs
and send it in
for an insurance claim.
You mean you're not
gonna arrest him?
There's no crime here,
ma'am.
Oh, like hell there isn't.
I know you did it
on purpose, too!
'Cause I caught you
starting at my ass
when I gave you the car.
I see nicer asses
on the regular.
No! Let go!
- Oh!
- Drop that knife!
- Let go of me!
I'm sorry.
Sorry about that.
Whoa. Sorry about that.
I didn't mean
for that to happen.
Yeah, right.
Is that how you get off?
You handcuff hot girls
and rip off their clothes?!
No, ma'am.
I'm just saying,
cops don't have
the best reputation
right now.
And if these tests
help the public trust us,
isn't it worth it?
And how are we supposed
to trust each other
if our fellow officers
are trying
to trick us
into screwing up?
I... ask myself that
every day.
That's different.
I do it
to make you a better cop,
not betray you.
You're, uh...
Yes.
It's me.
♪ Feel the groove ♪
- License and registration?
- Yes, sir. Uh...
I'm so sorry.
I can't believe I did that.
I-I've never run
a stop sign before.
I watch you
on the red carpet.
Like, all the time.
It's always nice
to meet a fan.
Uh, Officer,
is there any way
you could let me slide
on this one,
or just let me off with a...
with a stern warning?
It's just that I'm
really late right now,
and I got a lot of people
waiting for me on set.
You ran a stop sign.
We could arrest you for it.
Arrest me?
Come on. It's...
It's a nice, quiet street.
There's no harm done.
You know,
I could get you tickets
to any big movie premiere
you'd like,
or is there a particular star
you ever wanted to meet?
Okay, sir,
bribery of a public officer
is in violation of co...
What?
Oh, you gotta be
kidding me.
Murphy.
Officer Bradford.
Nice touch,
roping in a celebrity.
Well, he had community service
hours to work off.
You thought we'd let him go
'cause he's famous?
Had I known it was you,
I would've put a strung-out cop
behind the wheel.
I know you have
a soft spot.
Hey, excuse me,
does that mean I can go?
Write him up.
Reckless driving.
Giving false information
to a police officer.
Disobedience
to traffic signs.
Unlawful act
with a green air sticker.
Driving with
an obstructed view.
Unnecessary use of horn.
Failure to exercise caution
when passing animals.
Wha...
Is he serious?!
What if she's
one of the reversals?
It's not your fault
her tacky dress broke
when she tried
to stab a guy.
If she's IA,
she'll report
you used reasonable force
given the threat.
You think it's possible
that the dress was designed
to fail on contact?
You know, like...
those break-away pants?
I'm gonna go finish
the paperwork.
Thanks, you guys.
Right this way.
Please, believe me, I did not
mean to expose you like that.
Um...
The woman with the phone,
I spoke to her.
She was very reasonable.
I watched her delete
all the footage.
You have no idea
who I am, do you?
Uh, you are
Astrid Heisserer.
Uh...
No priors,
no outstanding warrants.
What's your name?
John Nolan.
Badge number.
25253.
If you want to lodge
a complaint, that is your right.
Oh, I'm gonna lodge
something... believe me.
Yo, that's messed up.
You went through
Wesley's phone?
I thought he was
cheating on me.
Cheating? You guys
only went on a few dates.
I knew you wouldn't
understand.
Oh, I understand,
I just don't approve.
And I understand that's not
the tone to take with a T.O.,
- so I take it back.
- Good.
Except the
"that's messed up" part.
That, I stand by.
Whoa.
How much you wanna bet
it's a reversal?
That's pretty convincing
drunk-driving.
$20 it's legit.
Driver, pull over now.
Unless IA's recruiting
out of grade school,
I just made 20 bucks.
Are you okay?
Good. Get out.
I can't.
I have to get her
to the hospital.
She's dying.
Lopez.
My sister OD'd.
Please... help her!
- She's barely breathing.
- Control, start RA to our location.
Female, 20s, overdose.
- Do you know what she took?
- No. I'm sorry.
- Pupils are pin points.
- It's okay.
It's probably heroin.
Get the NARCAN.
Come on, stay with us.
Here you go.
All right, step back.
She's gonna be okay.
This stuff will
wake her right up, all right?
It'll wake her right up.
Come on. Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Come on.
You got her help.
You saved her.
It's all right,
just breathe.
7-Adam-19,
459 in progress, 117 Ayers.
Police!
We're coming in!
♪ Mother, I lie ♪
♪ When I say I don't miss home ♪
Mushrooms?
Hallucinogens.
This is a grow house.
Careful... these places
are usually booby trapped.
Oh, my God.
See? Booby trapped.
Please, just get this thing
off of me.
I-I don't think we should.
He could've severed an artery.
The paramedics
will know what to do.
No, no, no. We don't need
to call anybody else.
There's like half a million
dollars' worth of mushrooms in here.
We split it, you pretend
you never saw me...
everybody wins.
Okay.
- What?!
- Really?
Yeah.
But I want 60%.
So, call Detective Murphy
and ask her if that's okay
with Internal Affairs.
Who?
Wait, you think this
is another reversal?
- Two in two hours?
- That's how they do it.
They try and catch you
when your guard is down.
What are you talking about?
Look, I've got to say,
this is impressive FX work.
But we are in Hollywood,
so, how'd you do it? Hmm?
Metal plates?
Peg leg?
Wait. Wait. What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
Calling your bluff.
7-Adam-19, we need an RA
to 117 Ayers.
30-year-old male,
severe trauma to left leg.
You're lucky
his leg's gonna be okay.
If Murphy hadn't
gotten in my head,
that never
would've happened.
Blame the reversals,
not me.
What happened
between you two?
Did she investigate you
or something?
Indirectly.
Is it Isabel?
Look, Murphy was
her investigating officer.
Okay,
but you're not Isabel,
- so what's her beef with you?
- Not your concern.
Start the paperwork.
- Everything okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Um, we had a reversal,
but Officer Bradford saw right
through it, so...
I heard. IA is stepping up their game
using celebrities. Yeah.
- Stay vigilant.
- Mm.
I wanted to say
I really appreciated
what you said
earlier today...
about cops doing
the right thing every day.
Is that because
you're seeing evidence
of officers
acting otherwise?
No. Not at all.
I-I was just...
Relax, Officer Chen.
I'm not gonna ask you
to narc on anyone.
But part of
protecting and serving
is making sure you refuse to do
anything that crosses a line.
So if anybody
is asking you to do so,
- I expect you to come talk to me.
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay. Tell me, how's that
new apartment working out?
Oh. Uh, it's great.
It's in a quiet neighborhood.
There's lots of coffee shops,
and people walking around.
Comics?
Yeah. Uh...
I found it
in the lost and found.
And by lost and found,
I mean my locker.
Thanks.
Yeah.
So, what happens now?
I... Your sister,
she's... she's stable.
Uh, no reason that she can't
make a full recovery.
Then it's up to her.
But ODs have a way of, um,
putting things
into perspective.
My mom OD'd three times
before she died.
Each time, she swore
she was gonna get clean.
Cassie and I found her when
we went down for breakfast.
She was blue.
Yeah.
You can't lose hope.
That's what everyone says.
'Cause it's true, Jake.
Social Services is on their way
to get you placed somewhere safe
while your sister
gets the help she needs.
Okay?
Sure.
I'll be right back.
Hey. Hold up.
Can we talk?
Okay.
I need
to explain something.
My dad left
when I was a kid.
And my mom never really
got past it.
There was no one stable
growing up in my life,
so I guess
what I'm trying to say
is I think that's
the reason why I-I...
I went through your phone.
- You sound like my clients.
- What?
Everybody's dad bailed.
No one's mom
was perfect.
Doesn't change
what you did.
No, I know, but...
You're a grown woman,
so having a bad childhood
isn't a valid excuse anymore.
Look, I wish I could
trust you again, but...
I don't see how I can.
I'm sorry.
Tim was so convinced
we caught another reversal,
he pried open
the bear trap.
I've never seen someone actually
pass out from pain before.
That's tough.
Not as bad as the helplessness
in that kid's eyes.
What about you?
Good day? Bad day?
I had to pry a psycho off
a valet at a five-star hotel.
Uh, her dress ripped
as I was cuffing her,
exposing
her unmentionables.
Boy, she was pissed.
- Wow.
- What?
That was for sure
a reversal.
Yeah, dress
was probably rigged...
- like break-away pants.
- Mmhmm.
- That's what I thought!
- Yeah?
Oh.
Okay,
I see what you're doing.
Can I get that to go,
please?
No, come on!
Don't be like that.
No, as much as I would love
to keep telling war stories...
Thank you, Dez...
I have another full day
of reversals tomorrow,
and this rookie
needs his beauty sleep.
Hey.
So, they canvassed the area.
No one saw the shooter.
He fired
a couple hundred rounds.
Yeah, no one's admitting
they saw him.
Yeah, patrol found
the car he escaped in.
It was reported stolen
this afternoon.
- SID is all over it.
- Who'd you piss off?
Clearly someone with access
to heavy weaponry.
I didn't recognize
the guy.
According to intelligence,
you've been greenlit
by Southern Front.
- Greenlit?
- Means they put a hit on you.
How's a rookie
get greenlit before me?
I gotta step up my game.
It's not a badge of honor.
Violent white supremacist gang wants
you dead, you're doing something right.
I-I'm sorry, white supremacy
gang and greenlit?
W-Wh... What the hell
is going on?
Normally, gangs
don't target cops...
more trouble
than it's worth.
Unless a cop
disrespects a gang member,
then all bets are off.
You arrested a woman today.
Astrid Heisserer.
Her dress broke.
I-I embarrassed her.
I thought she was IA.
She's not. She's the baby mama
of the leader of Southern Front,
one of the most violent criminal
enterprises in the country.
And because of how
you treated her,
he authorized everyone
in the gang to kill you.
- What about Talia?
- Yeah, what about me?
Nolan is the one
who put hands on her.
He's the one
they're after.
How many Southern Front
members are there?
In the greater Los Angeles area?
Several thousand.
And protecting you will be
our number-one priority.
Step one is to get you
off the streets.
Come with me, Nolan.
I'm gonna escort you home.
K9 unit already swept
the property.
Owner
coming home tonight?
Uh, no, Ben left
for New York yesterday.
So, what's happening
here?
The DA approved
a VARDA alarm.
It bypasses 911,
sends a red alert
to all the cops in the area.
So, what's next?
That's up to you.
I mean, I can't just
go to work, right?
I'd be endangering everyone who
came within five feet of me.
Being a cop
is being at risk.
So you're saying
I should just...
report for duty,
act like nothing happened?
I think we tell criminals what
to do, not the other way around.
- No matter the consequences?
- No matter the consequences.
But, look,
it's up to you.
No one is gonna judge you
either way.
Yeah, right.
Nolan.
This isn't about bravery.
You have a family.
Any cop who's ever worn a badge
understands that.
All set, Captain.
Okay.
It seems the system
is up and armed.
We have a unit
parked out front.
Try to get some sleep.
Don't see that happening.
No.
- Thank you.
- Have a good night.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Guard duty.
I think we have that covered.
Now
it's extra covered.
You call me directly
if anything happens.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
West and Chen
reporting for duty.
Guys, this is very sweet,
but honestly, it's unnecessary.
You'd do the same
for us.
So, how do you
want to do this?
Personally, I'd go with
alternating two-hour shifts
with a static position
plus a rover.
Oh, and I have earpieces
and walkies,
just so we can keep
in constant contact.
You got anything sweet?
Yeah, I think
there's some ice cream.
- Mm.
- Wait, guys.
Guys!
Look, come on.
We need to stay focused.
You know, the whole point
of guard duty
is that we take turns being up
so everyone gets some sleep.
You could've left
at any time.
Yep. No one would've
given you grief.
Yeah, right.
- Ohh.
- We got to get to the station.
Our shift starts soon.
- I should go in.
- What... To work?
Absolutely not.
You're safest right here.
We'll manage without you
for a few weeks at work.
What if it's longer
than that?
My training
would be put on hold,
I'd... stay a rookie
while you guys moved up.
We'd be separated.
That's never
gonna happen.
This, uh...
This will all be over soon.
Yeah.
And if it's not?
Then it's...
good you have a pool.
All right.
Everyone, settle down.
Captain.
Thank you for coming in...
most of you on your day off.
Till this is resolved,
all overtime limits
have been lifted.
As you may know,
Southern Front originated as
a white supremacist prison gang
about 15 years ago.
Since then, they have
branched out in a big way.
Drugs, prostitution,
extortion.
But what sets them apart
is their access
to military weapons.
Their leader,
the so-called "King Midas,"
is currently serving three
consecutive life sentences.
His son, Cole,
he controls the day-to-day
operations on the street.
But make no mistake, his father
is pulling the strings.
Lifting the greenlight would be
a huge loss of face for Cole,
so he's not gonna do it
willingly.
So, we gotta make this
a business decision.
We put a big enough hurt
on their operation,
they'll lift
the greenlight.
Sorry I'm late.
Yesterday, Southern Front
tried to kill one of our own.
Today, we hit back.
- What?
- Nothing.
Look, everyone else sees
this big hero move,
but I see your ego
getting in the way
of you doing
the smart thing.
Look.
If you don't want
to ride with me...
It's not about my safety.
It's about yours.
You're risking your life
to prove a point.
Seems worth it
to me...
if you're making
the right point.
But there's no sense
in taking a needless risk,
which is why Officer Nolan
will be staying far away
from anything
Southern Front related.
And I'll be riding
with him.
Whether I agree
with his decision or not,
he's my rookie.
And I'll take
good care of him.
Yes, ma'am.
Riding
with the captain.
And I thought being greenlit
was scary.
I drive.
Of course.
Officer Nolan.
- Keys.
- Yes.
How exactly are we hurting
Midas' operation?
By attacking Southern Front
where they make
all their money...
the three Ts.
Drug trafficking.
Weapons trafficking.
And sex trafficking.
♪ Circle up, circle up ♪
♪ Circle servant serpents ♪
♪ Peace we demanding
to serve it up ♪
♪ Stirrups on our certainty ♪
♪ The tide will turn,
we're turning up ♪
♪ We're turning tides,
no turning us ♪
♪ The tide is high,
the term is now ♪
♪ The surf is up,
the surge is us ♪
I'll handle processing.
You get started
on the asset paperwork.
I still don't see how
confiscating 20 gallons of lube
is gonna get the gang
to back off Nolan.
Asset forfeiture is where we do
the most damage today.
Law says we can seize
everything and anything
connected to their
illegal operation.
Vehicles, merchandise,
even the massage parlor.
Well, so, why didn't
we hit it last week?
Vice knew that
Southern Front owned that shop.
'Cause
it's whack-a-mole.
You take out one
criminal enterprise,
another one
takes its place.
Usually not a good use
of our time.
But today,
that's exactly what we want.
Make sure Southern Front's
scared one of their competitors
- is about to move in, a...
- Move! Don't touch me, man! Come on!
You gotta be kidding me.
What the hell
are you doing here?
My job. Making sure cops
don't break the law.
One of our officers
was greenlit.
Came within seconds
of being killed.
When do you think that a cop's
most likely to cross a line?
When they're scared,
angry, and want revenge.
They might... I don't know...
yell at a detective.
How about I write you up for
conduct unbecoming an officer?
Knock yourself out.
This is about Isabel,
and you know it.
You know,
it is about Isabel.
It's about the fact that
you covered for her for months.
- That's not true.
- Oh, please.
Any cop can tell an addict
10 miles out.
You knew she was using,
and you let her come to work
every day with a loaded gun.
You had an obligation
to report her, and you didn't.
Okay, that's a lie.
But I'd expect nothing less
from a cop like you.
Uh, hey, I need you
to come check something for me.
I want to make sure I'm doing it
by the book, okay? So, come on.
Hey, you know what?
If I were you,
I'd ask
for another T.O.
Yeah, well,
you're not me.
Ma'am.
I was told
there was a cop coming
with the authority
to negotiate.
Cut the crap.
Only color you care about
is green.
And the LAPD has taken
a lot of that from you today.
Now, if you want to stop
the bleeding, sit your ass down.
Look, I reviewed
the body cam footage.
That girl tried to stab a guy
right in front of my officer.
He used minimal force
to stop her...
no disrespect was intended
or shown.
Your son is overreacting,
and I don't think
it's his first time.
It's time for the adults
to de-escalate matters.
You been in the game
long?
Almost 20 years.
Then you know I can't just
rescind the greenlight.
It's gotta come from Cole.
Any other way,
my guys don't respect him.
Yeah.
Sucks to be you.
Let me be clear.
I'm not here to negotiate.
We cost you $1 million
in lost revenue
and three
in seized assets.
And we're just
getting started.
None of that matters
without honor.
You're way out
on a ledge, Midas.
In half a day, we shut down
seven of your businesses,
put 46 of your men
behind bars,
and just imagine the damage
we can do tomorrow,
when we start hitting
your spots in San Diego,
San Jose, Victorville.
I can keep going.
Your son... is about to destroy
everything you built
because his girlfriend
yelled at him.
Do the right thing...
call off the greenlight.
7-Adam-15,
possible 459 in progress,
1936 Kristol Lane.
7-Adam-15,
show us responding.
I hate this.
Feels like everyone's
fighting my battle for me.
City still needs
policing.
Ah, that was...
Exhilarating.
I was gonna say
"terrifying."
Guess I better
get used to that.
You know, when I, uh... I was
first stationed in Baghdad,
I used to get
these headaches.
Took me a few days to realize
it was 'cause my eyes
kept darting around,
looking for trouble.
That's what it is.
I didn't stop looking,
but it does stop hurting.
7-Adam-15, go to
channel 2 for Sergeant Grey.
Copy.
Andersen.
It worked.
Midas forced Cole
to lift the greenlight.
I guess you are back to being
just another rookie.
Thank God.
Thank you, Sergeant.
My pleasure.
So, does that mean
this little "Odd Couple"
partnership is over?
Hell no!
We got a burglary call
to take.
7-Adam-15, show us Code 6
on the burglary call.
Be advised,
we have an open door.
Going in to clear.
Nolan! Cover...
Hey, there!
Look who's awake.
Packs quite a kick,
doesn't it?
It's got four times the voltage
as LAPD uses.
Could probably cook the eyeball
right out of your skull.
Okay, look, look,
I did not intend
to disrespect Astrid,
okay?
Or you, okay?
And I would be happy
to apologize.
Too late for that now.
Only way this ends
is with you dead.
Yeah, I, uh...
I'd heard that you were dumb,
but it is shocking
to see it in person.
- Dumb?
- Dumb.
Who lured you into an ambush
with a false surrender?
Does your father know
that it was false?
Huh, junior?
I can't imagine that revelation's
gonna go too well, huh?
I think it'll go fine.
Oh, he's dumber
than I thought.
What's my rank?
- What?
- What is my rank?
Come on, you're the leader
of the sixth-largest gang
in all of California.
Surely you can tell
from my uniform what rank I am.
Who the hell cares?
You're going to.
See, it's one thing
to put a hit out on a rookie...
- No offense.
- None taken.
But two bars?
Oh,
for crying out loud.
And a badge
that says "Captain"?
You've just crossed a line
that anybody with half a brain
would run screaming from.
A line that even your father
might whack you for crossing.
Understood?
So, let me tell you
how this is gonna go.
You and your little goonies
are gonna...
No! Hey! Cole!
Hurt me! Right?
I'm the one
you wanna hurt, right?
Killing me, that's trouble
you can handle, okay?
But not her.
You need to let her go.
- Do you think I'm dumb, too?
- No.
No.
No!
No! No!
If the line's
already been crossed,
then there's
no going back.
Which means neither of you
are walking out of here.
As long as your bodies
never turn up,
the murder can't be pinned on me.
No, you're wrong.
And Southern Front'll
weather the storm.
It's gonna be
so much worse.
You need to get her
out of there now.
Hey, listen.
What about this?
What if I...
What if I made a video?
I'll apologize to Astrid.
You just have to let her up.
I already told you
that it's not gonna
- work, man. It's done.
- Hey, think about it.
Me, like this,
you standing over me?
Come on, she'll eat it up.
You'll get laid for weeks.
Okay, yeah.
Okay. Just get her out first.
Right now.
No, you got to make the video first.
We're gonna tape it... take it... Come on!
Yeah, here.
You recording? Hey, baby girl,
this is for you!
Astrid, I apologize.
I-I should not have
laid my hands on you.
You deserved more respect
than that. I am sorry.
Can we please
let her up now?
Nah, you got to
do it again.
You got to put
some feeling into it.
I didn't believe that.
Come on, man!
I didn't believe you!
Do it again! No!
Do another take right now!
Say it with feeling!
♪♪
No!
Cap...
Come on!
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, come on, come on!
It was Cole.
Officers!
Order, arms.
Execution, arms.
I'm so sorry.
You're gonna give up your son
right now!
The hell I am!
He killed my captain!
You got one chance
to save him
and what's left
of your operation.
Find out where he is
and give him to me,
or I'll burn your world
to ash.
Thanks.
There'll be time for grief
later.
We have a job to finish.
Midas gave up his son.
We know where he's headed.
Look, I know
what's in your hearts.
What you want to do
more than anything.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't want it, too.
Word is... you kill a cop,
you never see
the inside of a cell.
But that's...
that's not what
Captain Andersen would want.
Killing this loser
won't honor her memory.
Doing our jobs will.
And we owe it to her
to do it the right way.
Agreed?
All right, let's go.
All units, get ready.
Airship has a visual.
Two minutes out.
You were right.
I was selfish.
I got her killed.
No. Don't do that.
Don't make this about you.
She didn't die
because of your choice.
She died doing her job
the only way she knew how.
Look at it any other way,
you diminish her.
Look, you need to know that
no matter what happens next...
whether we arrest this guy
or we kill him...
- it won't make things better.
- I know that.
No.
You only think you do.
Please don't tell me
to "use it"...
the grief or the anger...
to make myself a better cop.
I can't handle that
right now.
- I wasn't going to.
- Okay?
Grief is grief.
It's...
It's a hole
that can't be filled,
but over time,
it'll shrink enough
so that you won't fall in
every time you take a step.
But trust me, if there's
one thing you can use
to make yourself
a better cop,
it'll be her life...
not her death.
One minute.
Think this guy'll go down
without a fight?
I hope not.
Hello?
Hey. I heard what happened.
I'm so sorry.
Thanks. I-I really
can't talk right now.
I said a bunch of things
earlier.
They don't really matter
right now.
I want to be here
for you.
I want that, too.
20 seconds out.
Get ready.
Okay, I gotta go
maybe shoot a guy.
- Call you later.
- What...
Cole Midas,
you are surrounded by the LAPD.
Step out of the vehicle
with your hands in the air.
I've got
a clean shot, Sarge!
Get out of the damn car...
now!
Okay!
I'm getting out!
Don't shoot!
Nolan,
go arrest that man.
It shouldn't be him.
No, it needs to be.
Hands on your head.
Interlace your fingers.
Eyes front.
Don't move.
♪♪
Other hand.
Over here.
Ugh!
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
- in a court of law.
- Come on!
We both know I won't live
to stand trial.
Yes, you will.
Because the woman you killed
taught us
it's not our job
to punish you.
Just to see to it
that you are.
You coming?
Wh... No, don't...
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Captain's dead, and you're
out here spying on us?
Your watch commander
called.
Said his people
were gonna do this right...
wanted to make sure
that we saw it.
Sorry about
your captain.
I liked her.
I also trashed
the "conduct unbecoming" charge,
so...
You were right...
that was bush league.
Good.
Wait.
Look, I'm only...
I'm only saying this
because Andersen
would want me to.
But you were right, too.
I knew Isabel was using
in the end, and...
I didn't say anything because
I was trying to help her.
She was my wife.
How's she doing?
Better.
She's clean.
I'm glad.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, for now.
All right, back to work.
What?
First time I met the captain,
I fell flat on my face.
Bishop and Lopez
sent me to her office,
told me I needed to introduce
myself before roll call.
- You got punked.
- That's exactly what she said.
Tried to play it off,
but she was
way too smart for that.
Yeah.
She asked for you to be
assigned to Mid-Wilshire.
You know that?
No.
Why?
She didn't even know me.
She felt your experience
would make you
a valuable addition
to our house.
Guess I got
a lot to live up to.
We all do.
Synchronized  by  srjanapala