NOLAN: You think they'd get mad
if we called in sick, week one?
ANNOUNCER:
Previously, on "The Rookie"...
SGT. GREY: It's time to play the
Training Officer match game.
SGT. GREY: Officer Bradford,
you get Lucy Chen.
SGT. GREY: Officer Lopez, Jackson West.
SGT. GREY: Officer Bishop,
you get John Nolan...
- (SIREN WAILS)
- ...the 40-year-old rookie.
I've been trying to find you.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
That was my wife.
I haven't seen her in almost a year.
Show me those hands. Now!
(GRUNTS)
You're a pain in my ass.
That's my job.
Get out your gun and cover me!
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Officer West,
you didn't fire a single shot.
It won't happen again.
Not good enough.
♪ It's dark as hell,
I can't get up ♪
- ♪ I don't know what I'm doing ♪
- (TROLLEY BELL DINGS)
NOLAN: 7-Adam-15, pursuing
two members of a heist crew
carrying stolen money,
dressed as zombies.
Send backup to Westwood Metro Station.
♪ We drank our heads off stupid ♪
♪ My useless brain is ruined ♪
WOMAN: Ohh!
♪ But it's okay, we're killin' time ♪
♪ We pay no mind, ♪
♪ we pay no mind ♪
♪ We pay no ♪
♪ We pay no mind, ♪
♪ we pay no mind ♪
MAN: Whoa.
♪ We pay no mind, ♪
♪ we pay no mind ♪
♪ We pay no ♪
♪ We pay no mind, ♪
♪ we pay no mind ♪
(PASSENGERS MURMUR)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(PASSENGERS SCREAM)
Yo!
(GUITAR CLANGS)
- (TASER CRACKLES)
- ♪ We crashed the car the other day ♪
- ♪ It really didn't matter. ♪
- (GROANING)
- (GRUNTS)
- Ohh!
♪ We fixed it up and drove away ♪
Oh!
- That's...
- ♪ We pay no mind, we pay no mind ♪
MAN: Metro Expo Line.
- (BELL DINGS)
- No.
Nolan, the money!
♪ Yeah ♪
MAN: Westwood/Rancho Park.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ oh, whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you ♪
♪ like I know you want me to do ♪
- (LAUGHS)
- It's not funny.
Yeah, sure it is. Just not to you.
Honestly, who steals stolen
money right in front of a cop?
Somebody stupid or desperate.
- I thought we were here to run.
- Oh, yes, we are.
We just need a little
more warm-up than you do.
- You look great, though.
- Yeah.
- Okay, you think you're cute...
- Mm-hmm.
...but the job's a marathon.
And I'm not gonna be the one
who falls by the wayside
because I didn't train.
Looking good! You're a beast!
We're right behind you!
(SEA GULLS CRYING)
He's right, though.
Tim gets back today, and I feel like
I should have prepared myself
somehow for the abuse to come.
You saved the guy's life.
He's got to cut you some slack.
Does Talia ever cut you slack
or Sergeant Grey?
- It's been good knowing you.
- Uh-huh.
It's time to run, Officer Nolan.
- Let's go.
- Oh!
Be right there. I'm just
gonna stretch a little more.
- (WAVES CRASHING)
- (SEA GULLS CRYING)
SGT. GREY: So, how you feeling?
TIM: Good.
Everything okay with my green slip?
Yeah. Yeah, you're medically
cleared to return to duty.
Which means it's time for the
"so you got shot" speech.
I only give it to officers
wounded on the job.
Lucky me.
Yeah, lucky you.
So, you came in this morning
thinking everything goes
back to normal now,
you can just flip a switch,
and the trauma you
suffered will go away.
It won't.
But you're trying to
muscle your way through.
That's what I did.
SGT. GREY: Trust me, it didn't go well.
I didn't know you got shot.
My last year on patrol.
Spent two weeks in the ICU.
Rushed back thinking I could
put it all behind me,
but it doesn't work that way.
I understand.
I promise I'll... I'll take it slow.
Okay.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
(AIR HISSES)
All right, all right, all right.
Settle down. Settle down.
- (CHAIRS SCRAPE)
- Let's get to it.
SGT. GREY: You ready, Officer Nolan?
'Cause once again, we start with you.
I'm flattered?
SGT. GREY: Don't be.
Yesterday, a four-man
crew disguised as zombies
knocked over a cash advance
near Pico and Robertson.
So, Officers Bishop and Nolan
were able to apprehend
two of the criminals, while
the other two escaped.
SGT. GREY: Somehow, Officer
Nolan managed to let
a civilian steal 10 grand
in already stolen cash.
SGT. GREY: Luckily, CCTV
captured our thief.
Still waiting on an I.D.
Uh, he plays guitar, if that helps.
SGT. GREY: Absolutely.
'Cause they always list special
talents on your rap sheet.
(LAUGHTER)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Captain. How can we help you?
First off, I wanted to
welcome Tim Bradford back.
If you need anything, you let me know.
Yes, ma'am.
Secondly, we just got some
new intel on our zombies.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Turns out
that they're responsible
for a rash of armed robberies
in the last six months,
always disguised differently.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Detectives
want to get the two in custody
to flip on their partners at large,
but there is no guarantee,
so don't stop hunting.
Finally, we got a request
for a civil standby.
Turns out somebody's getting
fired from a tech job.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Supervisor's
worried things may not go right.
Babysitting a termination...
a patrol officer's favorite assignment.
So, who shall I bless with it?
Officer Nolan, are you volunteering?
Just embracing the inevitable, sir.
SGT. GREY: Smart man.
Get the address from dispatch.
SGT. GREY: That's it.
LUCY: You sure you don't
want me to drive?
Why would I want that, Boot?
You think I'd go back on duty
- before I'm 100 percent?
- No, sir.
Or do you think simply doing
your job during a firefight
- means you get special treatment?
- No, sir.
You'll drive when you've earned it.
Yes, sir.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
It's good to have you back.
Damn straight.
How could you possibly know
he was gonna take the money?
Because everyone's an opportunist.
A guy who plays the guitar for change...
he sees a bag of money,
he's gonna steal it
10 times out of 10.
See, your problem is that
you think that people
are inherently good, but you're wrong.
People are good when it's easy.
When push comes to shove,
everyone crosses the line.
Wow.
I must have missed that chapter
in Gandhi's biography.
Yeah, well, until Gandhi
shows up on Western Avenue,
assume that everyone you
meet is one bad day away
from committing a crime.
- (ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
- Understood.
But, you know, Gandhi is dead.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Doing some renovating?
I just took my kitchen
down to the studs.
Big job.
What did your contractor estimate...
two months?
Uh, four.
He's lying.
Longest it ever took me was three,
and that was because the
appliances were on back order.
You tell him he doesn't
beat his estimate,
he's gonna get a call from the LAPD.
- (ELEVATOR BELL DINGS, DOORS OPEN)
- I will.
- Thank you.
- You bet.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Officers. I thought you'd
be here 20 minutes ago.
And Nancy's with you.
We'll make this quick.
Wait. What's going on?
I think you're getting fired.
BANK MANAGER: Oh, thank
God you guys are here.
He's trapped in there.
In where? The bank?
(SIGHS) No. In the wall.
Mike went inside to fix an ATM
last night before we closed,
and we forgot he was in there and left.
The lock must have broke when
he tried to come back out,
and he's been inside all night.
BANK MANAGER: Pushed this
note through the receipt slot
when he heard us come in.
Control, 7-Adam-19 requesting LAFD
to 3301 Ditmer. for a
guy trapped in a wall.
Sir, we're gonna get you out of there.
(KNOCKS ON WALL)
- (PAPER RUSTLES)
- Sir, can you hear me?
LUCY: What's that supposed to mean?
Hypoxia. Go grab the
halligan out of the trunk.
We can't wait for the fire department.
Sir, I need you to get low
so I can open this wall up.
How tall is the space behind the ATM?
Oh, I don't know. It's
pretty cramped in there.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- BANK MANAGER: About five feet.
(GRUNTING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Why am I doing this?
Boot, get in there.
Sir, are you all right?
(INHALES DEEPLY, WHIMPERS)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Just to be clear, Mrs. Wu,
you are not under arrest.
But your former employer has indicated
that you are no longer
welcome back on premise.
Why the hell would I
want to come back here?
Look, I've been where you are.
I know how this feels. It's horrible.
But it can actually be an opportunity...
All right, save the friendly act
for the next person you strong-arm.
You do know that you're a
cop, not a moving company.
We were going the same way. I
had an extra pair of hands.
Exactly... hands you would have needed
if the situation went south.
There's a reason her
boss wanted us here.
- (HATCH CLOSES)
- Yeah, but I'm not seeing it.
There's no harm in just giving someone
the benefit of the doubt.
(GLASS BREAKING)
How does that feel, Chad?!
NANCY: Stupid idiot!
- Or...
- (SCREAMS)
TALIA: Hey! Ma'am!
- NOLAN: Ms. Wu! Ms. Wu!
- NANCY: Stupid...
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-07, silent
alarm tripped at Chili John's.
(RADIO CHIRPS)
You think it's actually
a crime in progress?
9 times out of 10, a silent
alarm is tripped accidentally,
but you always treat it like it's real.
SUE: Put the money in the damn bag!
Put the money in the damn bag!
Are you crazy?! Hurry up! Hurry up!
- SUE: Put the money in the damn bag!
- 7-Adam-7,
we have a 2-11 in
progress at our location.
Requesting backup.
- Do we go in?
- SUE: Put it in the bag!
LOPEZ: No. That'll just escalate things.
- SUE: Come on!
- LOPEZ: We'll grab her on the way out.
LOPEZ: Police! Drop your weapon!
LOPEZ: Stop! Stop!
JACKSON: It's plastic.
LOPEZ: Stop!
- JACKSON: (GRUNTS)
- SUE: Aah!
(HANDCUFFS CLICK)
Sue Cliffords?
- Do I know you?
- You know her?
She played ball for the Trojans.
Best 3-point shooter in the NCAA.
Nice to meet a fan.
NOLAN: Let me guess. You're
waiting for the perfect moment
to say "I told you so."
I get no pleasure in being
right, Officer Nolan.
- Okay. I get a little.
- (SCOFFS)
But were you right? I mean, just because
she snapped in the moment,
that doesn't make her a bad person.
The "why" doesn't matter.
TALIA: Our job is not to
weigh a citizen's morality.
It's to enforce the law.
And when push came to
shove, she broke it.
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-15, we have an I.D.
on your guitar-playing train thief.
DISPATCH: Suspect
identified as Roman Ealy.
DISPATCH: 617 South Cleaver Avenue.
(SIREN WAILS)
7-Adam-15. Reattach us to 2-11.
Show us en route.
Wow. 20 points a game, huh?
You were no joke.
So, what happened?
I thought you got an offer
to play for the WNBA.
Blew out my knee senior
year, lost my scholarship.
And now you commit armed robbery?
What else am I qualified to do?
You know, I met you
once at a party at USC.
You were so passionate
about playing ball,
and I was so not about
majoring in engineering.
Got me thinking about
going a different way,
and, well, here I am.
How nice for you.
You ever think about
doing something else?
Hell, no.
Being a cop is the only
thing I ever wanted.
Sure. But things don't
always go your way.
You got to have a Plan "B" just in case.
One out of three rookies washes out,
so odds are either you, Chen, or Nolan
won't be here in a year.
I thought you were a sure
bet to succeed at first,
but those other two are rocking it,
and you stumbled out the gate.
That was a one-time thing.
I have a long career ahead of me.
SUE: Yeah, that's what I thought.
TALIA: 7-Adam-15, Code
6 on our train thief.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
LAPD! Open up!
Sir, I can see you in there!
Do not make me break this door down!
Yeah. I-I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Now, put your hands
where I can see them.
Hands behind your head.
Interlock your fingers.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Sir, where is the money?
I swear I was gonna return it.
It... I... It, um...
Did you spend any of it?
I-I-I bought some groceries,
and I had the water turned back on.
I-I'm sorry. I-I'll pay it back.
I just... It's been so hard.
My wife died last year...
TALIA: Sir, put your
hands behind your back.
No, pl... please.
I-I've never even gotten
a parking ticket before.
- Can't I do something? I'll...
- BOY: Daddy?
ROMAN: Jacob, go back
to your room, buddy.
It's okay. He can come out.
ROMAN: Okay, come here.
Well, what's gonna happen to him?
Child Protective Services will take him.
If you have any family in the area,
then they can pick him up later.
Uh, yeah, my... my wife's sister,
she lives in Chatsworth.
We'll take her info, make
sure CPS gets in touch.
But for now you're gonna
need to come with me.
Best I can do is make sure your
son doesn't see you in cuffs.
- Please...
- I'm sorry,
but you need to say goodbye.
ROMAN: Okay. All right.
Hey, hey, bud,
I got to leave for a little bit, okay?
ROMAN: You're gonna stay with Aunt Judy.
ROMAN: I'm gonna see
you real soon, okay?
ROMAN: I promise.
I love you.
Sir, you need to come with me now.
(DOOR OPENS)
- Daddy!
- Oh, okay.
- Shh. Shh. Shh.
- Daddy!
- No, no, it's o... it's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Daddy!
- JACOB: Daddy!
- What did I do? I've ruined everything.
JACOB: Daddy!
You okay?
Of course.
Does that ever get any easier...
taking a parent away from their kid?
No.
But feeling bad for the guy
doesn't change what he did.
Still, poor kid.
TIM: Call your insurance
company about your property.
We'll file the report, but the fact is,
most cold burglaries stay cold.
You think of anything else,
my number's right there.
(HORN HONKS)
LUCY: Hey, I'm just
gonna hit the restroom.
Make it fast, Boot.
(HORN HONKS)
(DOORS CREAK)
(BELT BUCKLE CLACKS)
No, no, no, no!
Hey, did anyone run out here?
What?
Someone took my belt and gun.
I hung it on the hook, and I
secured the bathroom beforehand.
There was no one else in there.
Did the walls of the stall
reach top to bottom?
- No, sir.
- Then it wasn't secure, was it, Boot?
Now your weapon is on the street
because you couldn't hold your water.
(CELLPHONE RINGS)
Bradford.
When?
I-I'll be right there.
Get in.
What about my belt?
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
LUCY: What... What's happening?
Where are we going?
- (SEAT BELT CLICKS)
- Emergency room.
(ENGINE REVS)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Oh, that was awesome! Dude, do it again!
MAN: Whoo!
TALIA: These fools are the last thing
I want to deal with right now.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
You want to tell me what
the hell is going on?
We're filming stunts for
our YouTube channel.
MUTT: Logan's brother did
it and made hella cash.
That's not illegal, right?
Making hella cash? No.
But reckless driving is.
- LOGAN: Yo!
- How the hell...
Yo, this is Officer PootyPoot
sending a special shout-out
to all the single ladies out...
Hey! Get out the car now!
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
- NOLAN: Step out!
TALIA: Hands on the hood!
How did you get in there?
The doors were locked.
The passenger side wasn't.
(HANDCUFFS CLICK)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
TIM: Stay here.
Yeah, I'm looking for my
wife, Isabel Bradford.
ISABEL: Ugh. (CLEARS THROAT)
- TIM: Isabel.
- ISABEL: (SIGHS)
I'm fine, all right? They
shouldn't have called you.
Where the hell are you going?
You just O.D.'d.
I'm fine. They can't hold me.
- Let go.
- Stop.
Stop.
Do you know how many dead
junkies I've rolled up on
in the last month?
Seized up, blue-lipped, all alone
because their buddies
didn't want to get caught
- when the cops showed up?
- I said I'm fine.
You don't want to come home!
Okay. I understand.
But if you keep doing this,
you are going to die!
Save the tough love for someone else.
I am not your responsibility anymore,
so you do not get to have an opinion
about how I live my life.
So please stop trying
to be my white knight,
and leave me alone!
(GRUNTS)
Aah.
Are you okay?
SGT. GREY: It's a tragedy.
See, I was at the game where
Cliffords blew out her knee.
You could see it in her face.
She knew her career was over.
LOPEZ: And she didn't have a Plan "B."
Always got to have a
Plan "B" starting out.
- That's what I told the Boot.
- Yeah.
Sir, with all due respect,
this has been my Plan "A"
since I was in diapers.
There's no way I don't see it through.
It's not always about you, Officer West.
This is a job where anything
can happen at any moment.
SGT. GREY: If that bullet
hits Officer Bradford
six inches to the right,
he's paralyzed or worse.
Having a Plan "B" doesn't
mean you're not committed.
It means you're a realist.
(BUZZER, DOOR OPENS)
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
- DISPATCH: 7-Adam-19,
report of a biker gang,
drunk and disorderly
at The Hard Road bar.
Are you okay to do this?
We can ask for another
unit to be assigned.
No. I'm fine.
("SLAM" PLAYS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
How do you identify a
motorcycle club, Boot?
Uh, the three rockers on the
back of their jackets...
they show gang name, logo,
and state of origin.
LUCY: "Dead Bastards MC."
And which one of these guys
is the most dangerous?
See them? Those are Prospects.
TIM: They haven't earned
their top rocker yet,
and there's only one way to get it...
commit a felony in view
of another gang member,
which means what?
Somebody's gonna fight us
when we get out of this car.
Exactly.
Shouldn't we call for backup, then?
Where's the fun in that?
♪ Slam, One shot ♪
♪ give it all you got ♪
- (CAR DOOR CLOSES)
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
- ♪ Take him out from the blindside ♪
- Now, that's just sad.
TIM: Either you're man enough
to come at me or you're not.
Now, who needs a felony?
What are you doing?
TIM: Look, I'm not gonna repeat myself.
TIM: This is a one-time offer,
and it's about to expire.
You beat me, I won't even book you.
I beat you, you go to jail, and
your buddies hit the road.
MAN: Come on, Jordan. You got this.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
- (PEOPLE SHOUTING, CHEERING)
- ♪ Slam ♪
♪ Ooh ohh ohh ♪
- Come on!
♪ Ooh ohh ohh, slam ♪
- ♪ Ooh ohh ohh ♪
- (PUNCHES LANDING)
♪ Ooh ohh ohh, slam ♪
♪ Ooh ohh ohh ♪
Ohh!
Let's go!
(CROWD GROANS)
♪ Take him out from the blindside ♪
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
- (HANDCUFFS CLICK)
- ♪ Slam ♪
- Let's go!
- You lost!
- (LAUGHS)
- Let him go! Yeah, pig.
- Let's go.
- Come on, man!
MAN: It was a fair fight!
♪ Take him out from the blindside ♪
7-Adam-19, type change this
event to a felony assault,
one in custody.
- What the hell was that?
- MAN: Good work, Jordy!
Patrol work, Boot.
You planning on saying otherwise?
- ♪ Slam, ooh ohh ohh. ♪
- No, sir.
- ♪ Ooh ohh ohh. ♪
- ♪ Take him out from the blindside ♪
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Heard you were looking for me.
Yeah.
Buddy in Beverly Hills PD just called.
SGT. GREY: The other two
members of that heist crew
knocked over a jewelers
on Cannon at lunchtime
dressed as werewolves, shot a guard,
made off with eight grand.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Well, I've got news
on the two we have in custody.
Detectives executed a search warrant
on the zombies' apartment.
They found souvenirs from
robberies they committed
with the crew last year
in Dallas and Phoenix.
- So they move around.
- CAPT. ANDERSEN: Mm-hmm.
And with their partners on ice here,
I bet you they are ready
to get out of Dodge.
I'll alert patrol units.
We got to find these guys.
Mm-hmm. Do that.
So, how do you want
to write this one up?
Carefully.
Grey's a stickler for proper procedure.
(BUZZER)
Well, if it isn't Officer PootyPoot.
SGT. GREY: Please come in.
Put them on the bench. You, with me.
Officer Nolan,
leaving a police vehicle unlocked
so that your suspect
can give a shout-out
over the shop radio
is cause for discipline.
Carelessness like that will
not be tolerated here.
- Do you understand me?
- Understood, sir.
SGT. GREY: Now, what's
gonna happen next...
Sir...
I left my door unlocked.
It wasn't Nolan.
My office. Now.
(BUZZER)
Get him processed.
W-What about the booking approval?
You made this arrest.
You saw what happened.
Write it up, Boot.
NOLAN: I'm gonna take
any jewelry you have,
any piercings, anything in your pockets,
your socks, your shoes,
you're gonna give them to me.
- Can I talk to you?
- (DOOR OPENS)
- I'm worried about Tim.
- Why?
He instigated a fight with a biker,
wouldn't let me call for backup,
could have gotten both of us killed.
LUCY: I think he's spinning
out, trying to prove himself.
NOLAN: You think he came back too soon?
LUCY: Maybe.
LUCY: He got hit with a lot of
personal stuff on top of it, too,
and he's not handling it well.
Clearly you have to do something.
Yeah, but what? Tim is my T.O.
I'm not gonna narc on him.
Then you're gonna have to talk to him.
Oh...
It's not gonna go well.
What other choice do you have?
(SIGHS)
Six doses of NARCAN.
Throwing quite a party, huh?
Hey. Biker's processed.
Do we really need all that?
Look, there's a bad batch of fentanyl
making the rounds out there.
Miller went through his entire
overdose kit in two days.
You gonna tell me. how it
went with Sergeant Grey?
He put me on undocumented
oral counseling.
- For leaving a door unlocked?
- I deserve it. I lost focus.
But at least it's not on my record.
Look, I appreciate you
trying to cover for me.
No problem.
But it doesn't mean you're right
about how you see people, though.
You think I did that to
try and prove a point?
(CHUCKLES) Trust me, I'm no Gandhi.
I just don't think someone's
life should be ruined
because of one bad day.
You're my partner...
my training officer...
and I've got your back,
even if you think
I'm one bad lunch order
away from a life of crime.
(DOOR OPENS) NOLAN: I saw
you rolling your eyes.
(TIRES SCREECH)
7-Adam-19, show us Code 6,
Florence and Central Avenue.
Stay here.
("LA CALLE" PLAYS ON STEREO)
♪ Mami mueve esa sintura
pero traime lo para tras ♪
♪ Ahora mismo sige adelante
y bajalo al piso ♪
♪ Go go go go go ♪
TIM: You deaf, Boot? I
said stay in the car.
You're not helping her.
You're enabling her.
You know this because
you're some shrink's kid?
She's gonna shoot up, okay?
That's the reality.
This will save her life.
Addiction doesn't just
destroy the addict.
- (TRUNK LID CLOSES)
- It destroys the family, too.
Who the hell are you to tell me this?
- You think I don't know?
- I'm your rookie.
And I need you to train
me, not put me in danger
because you can't handle
losing your wife.
♪ Go go go go go ♪
Look, at least let me go up.
LUCY: If you do, it'll just
confirm your worst fears.
Do you really want to
see how she's living
or who she's living with?
♪ You already know ♪
Paramedics said it's apartment 510.
♪ Baby, shake it fast, don't stop ♪
♪ Dale dale, brinka, brinka ♪
(FOOTSTEPS FADE)
(DOG BARKING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(DOOR OPENS)
Isabel, just...
- Wait. Wait.
- ISABEL: Go away.
ISABEL: Y-You can't come
in without a warrant.
My name is Officer Lucy Chen.
Tim Bradford's my T.O.
He's downstairs.
If you don't give me five minutes,
he's gonna come up here
and break this door down.
(DOOR CLOSES)
So, what do you want?
- (BOOTS THUD)
- LUCY: Do you know
your husband was shot recently?
We got ambushed.
He took a bullet while returning fire.
That's what you're doing here?
'Cause he seems fine.
Um... it's NARCAN.
It won't get you clean,
just reverse the effects of an O.D.
I know what NARCAN is.
Spent a decade bringing junkies
back from the dead with it.
- You were a nurse?
- No. A cop.
Narcotics.
He didn't tell you?
He doesn't really talk about you. I...
That's good.
So, you guys were on the force together?
Different divisions.
I, uh... I worked out of the 77th,
volunteered for undercover
as soon as I could.
Tim was happy on patrol, so...
we synched our shifts as best we could.
It was perfect... till it wasn't.
So, anyway...
(DOOR OPENS)
LUCY: Uh...
Hey, um, he really got shot?
Yeah.
Yeah. It was scary.
Don't let him come back here.
There's no future here.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES, LOCK CLICKS)
(SNIFFLES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
She was a cop.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I-I, uh, thought. she
was having an affair.
TIM: Staying out late, making excuses.
I didn't realize it was the drugs
until the hook was in deep.
(PERSON SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY)
(DOG BARKING)
Her apartment is pretty decent.
Thanks.
(SEAT BELT CLICKS, ENGINE STARTS)
(CECIL OTTER'S "GRIME" PLAYS)
You could be a nurse or get into I.T.
There's always clown college.
Look, I don't need a Plan "B,"
and if I did, it wouldn't
be from some pamphlet
you grabbed off the community board.
How do you think I got
the idea for the LAPD?
SGT. GREY: Lopez, West,
the zombie robbers
just flipped on their partners.
SWAT's hitting the house.
We're providing tactical support.
Meet in the bullpen in five.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: All
right, let's get started.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Our targets
are Steve Bower, Kai De Vera.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Bit of an odd couple.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Bower's known for
at least six hard-core 2-11s,
a lot of collateral damage in his wake.
De Vera did two tours as a
door gunner on a Black Hawk,
was under the radar till she hooked up
with Bower about a year ago.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Remember, if anything,
she's far more dangerous than he is.
Sergeant Laubacher will be
giving you the briefing.
He's in charge of tonight's
operation, so listen up.
Thank you, Captain.
Targets are at a house in the
hills over the Sunset Strip.
Ingress is limited, so
we'll be coming in hot.
SGT. LAUBACHER: Team one
will be primary entry,
deploying flash bangs
and breaching tools.
Team two... break and
rake the back glass door.
SGT. LAUBACHER: Tactical support.
..you're outer perimeter.
SGT. LAUBACHER: Sergeant
Grey has your positions.
We'll go through detailed
assignments on the drive in.
My team, let's go.
Get to it.
All right.
See, we could do this whole
thing in five minutes
without flash bangs and BearCats,
but SWAT has us on guard duty,
so make sure they take it seriously.
I don't want to be embarrassed
at the next Special Ops picnic.
- Yes, sir.
- We won't let you down, Sergeant.
(RAPPING) ♪ So go ahead
and look it down ♪
♪ Go look down ♪
♪ the barrel of that fun gun ♪
Is there really a Special Ops picnic?
- ♪ You got no more face. ♪
- I didn't think so.
♪ So when the hot sun's setting
on a shotgun wedding ♪
♪ I will not tie the knot ♪
♪ where the shots come heading ♪
♪ At my head, ♪
♪ I will not be caught dead ♪
♪ Walking off to my bed ♪
♪ with a death threat ♪
Sucks we have to be down here.
TALIA: Yeah, well, get used to it.
Patrol is lowest on the totem pole
when it comes to operations like this.
Perimeter watch is a necessary
part of police work.
It's nothing to look down on.
- TALIA: Is he for real?
- LOPEZ: Yep.
Doesn't have a Plan "B," though.
What? Well, that's just crazy.
I've been dealing with
this crap all day.
Officer Nolan, this is
your Plan "B," right?
Uh, more like Plan "D."
First it was astronaut, then law school,
then construction, then this.
If this doesn't work out,
I'm thinking beauty school.
(GUNFIRE)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
NOLAN: Should we go up there?
No. But we should spread out
and cover the perimeter.
SWAT: (OVER RADIO) Shots fired.
Shots fired. Suspects at large.
(DOG BARKING)
(BRANCH CRACKS)
Stop!
(GUNFIRE)
Do we go after them?
7-Adam-15 in pursuit of
armed robbery suspects,
heading south towards Franklin.
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-15, what
street are suspects on?
They're not on a street. They're
running down the side of the canyon.
Aren't we supposed to have an airship?
TALIA: En route.
(SIREN WAILS)
God, does it ever feel normal?
- What?
- Just getting shot at,
people trying to kill
you for doing your job.
- Yes.
- Really?
About as normal as taking a
parent away from their kid,
but we signed up for it all.
If ever you start to get numb to it,
you know it's time to
turn in your papers.
How could anyone feel
numb to any of this?
There! Just jumped the last ravine.
Control, suspects are down on the flats,
heading for Western.
Where's that backup?
7-Adam-19, we're inbound to assist.
There.
(SIRENS WAIL)
(TIRES SCREECH)
LUCY: 7-Adam-19, we'll
take Bower, you take her.
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(ENGINE REVS)
(VEHICLE APPROACHES)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
NOLAN: 7-Adam-15, we are
Code 6 at Saint Gregory's.
We have suspect at
large in the hospital.
TALIA: Did a woman in a green
Army jacket run through here?
Down that hallway.
Get the elevators. and
first floor in lockdown.
We have an armed suspect on the loose.
We have a code grey, code grey.
(SIREN WAILS, TIRES SCREECH)
(SIREN SHUTS OFF)
TIM: Flashlights on, Boot.
TIM: Eyes right. I got
the left side covered.
7-Adam-19, shots fired at our location.
Requesting backup and airship.
The good news is he's trapped.
If I go over this trailer,
I'll come up on top of him.
With all due respect, I should go.
Forget it.
Improvisation is a useful
tool for a rookie to learn.
Good. All right. You
passed tonight's test.
Get your ass up there.
(SIRENS WAIL IN DISTANCE)
Police!
Drop your weapon!
Do it now!
Get down on your stomach!
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
TIM: Hands behind your back.
What do you want... applause?
Get down here.
TIM: 7-Adam-19, Code 4.
TIM: One in custody, one outstanding.
Careful. This girl was a door gunner
for a Black Hawk helicopter,
not some crackhead with a 9-mil.
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-08 is in
place on east entrance.
DISPATCH: Additional units en
route to assist in search.
All right, every exit's secure.
We just need to flush her out.
No.
No what?
Every exit is not secure.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
7-Adam-15 to air support.
Armed suspect has stolen
medevac helicopter
from the roof. of Saint
Gregory Hospital.
TALIA: Request you
respond and intercept.
Drop your gun.
No. But I-I'll put it away.
(GUN SLIDES IN HOLSTER)
Okay, okay, um...
now what?
I shoot you and take my
chances in the hospital
after the cops clear out
chasing the helicopter.
Can I offer an alternate suggestion?
- No.
- Look...
I don't know you, okay?
Just... Just what was on your BOLO.
Two tours, wounded in action.
Y-You're an honest-to-God American hero.
Who's about to put a hollow
point through your skull.
- Still think I'm a hero?
- Yes.
Yes, because you're not gonna do that.
My training offer says that
people are inherently flawed,
that they're only good when it's easy.
And when things get challenging,
they make a bad call
and then another, and then pretty soon
you can't see good in
your rearview mirror.
NOLAN: - She says that once you
cross that line, you can't go back,
but I-I don't... I don't believe that.
I-I think you can.
NOLAN: I think that good people
will make the right choice
when it really matters.
Look, if I... if I'm wrong...
...then you kill me.
But if I'm right...
then you just give up because
this is a line you won't cross.
(TASER CRACKLING) KAI: Aah!
(PANTING)
Remind me not to get on your bad side.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yep.
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
Guess now we'll never know...
(HANDCUFFS CLICK)
...what choice she was gonna make.
You're the only one still in
doubt here, Officer Nolan.
I just saved your life.
Well, in that case...
thank you.
(SIRENS WAIL)
(MACKESON'S "BYE BYE BABY" PLAYS)
Officer Nolan,
did you bail out your train thief?
No.
I did.
He made a mistake.
He's got a kid, and he
deserves to be at home,
not in some prison because
he can't make bail.
Officer Bishop, I didn't
take you for a softie.
I'm not.
But one bad day. shouldn't
ruin a man's life.
Okay.
♪ But when I found your secret ♪
- What?
- ♪ I never could keep it ♪
I want to give you a hug.
Do you want to get Tased?
No. It passed.
LOPEZ: Let's ask the captain.
Ask me what?
What was your Plan "B"?
I didn't have one. I was all-in.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Nothing was
gonna stop me from being a cop.
Turned out pretty well.
- I agree, Captain.
- Whatever.
♪ Bye-bye, baby ♪
♪ You're free to roam ♪
♪ No more maybe ♪
♪ You're on your own ♪
♪ I can't believe you fooled me ♪
- ♪ Maybe you just used me. ♪
- SGT. GREY: Hard day?
(LOCKER CLOSES)
- ♪ Now I can't trust myself. ♪
- Yeah.
♪ So you better find the next one ♪
You didn't tell me your partner
got shot along with you.
♪ You better find ♪
I might have done some poking around.
Dennis Rowland. Bad temper, good heart.
We were together two years.
Bullet went through him, hit me.
I walked away. He didn't.
♪ Baby, you can't stay ♪
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Now, are you ready for
the "So you got shot"
and didn't listen to me and
pushed yourself too hard,
"but now you know I'm right" speech?
Sounds like a long one.
Oh, it is.
Come on. I'll give it
to you over a beer.
♪ You got to go, you got to go ♪
Ah. How's that Plan "B" coming?
Captain says I don't need one.
But I was thinking
it might not be a bad idea
for me to find a hobby,
something outside of the
job I can look forward to.
Mm. What about, uh, pole dancing?
Okay, clearly, I shouldn't
have brought you
into the circle of trust.
(LAUGHING) What?
You know, you were, uh,
pretty cavalier earlier
about not making it as a cop.
Is that how you really feel?
I'm seeing this thing
through no matter what,
no matter what obstacles
are thrown in my way.
JACKSON: You know, one out
of three rookies washes out
during their first year.
And there's three of us.
Odds are, one of us isn't gonna make it.
Screw the odds.
- If I believed in odds...
- (CAN HISSES)
...I wouldn't even be here.
You know what? We're all
gonna make it because
we're gonna have each other's
backs no matter what.
Deal?
Deal.
- Yeah.
- Deal.
Okay, I'm going on a night run.
Who's with me?
Me. Totally.
LUCY: Yeah. We're right behind you.
LUCY: (LAUGHS)
♪ Bye-bye, baby ♪
Improved By: FidelPerez
Sub Upload Date: November 2, 2018