I'll take that. Thank you.
Small of your back?
No!
Mm!
Uh, left ankle?
Oh, so close.
Right ankle.
W... Hold on. It's my turn.
You don't get to go twice.
Favorite body parts?
I don't...
Guessing where we keep
our off-duty weapon.
Oh!
Wait. Hold on. Let me guess.
Ankle holster...
like most old-timers.
Okay, "A," I'm not an old-timer.
You're confusing age with experience.
"B," not even close.
He doesn't even carry
an off-duty piece.
I'm sorry. How did I not know that?
I'm still getting used to carrying
a loaded weapon on the job.
I don't know that I could handle
packing heat in my real life.
Oh, no.
What?
Sgt. Grey is sitting
over there with his wife.
He's coming over here.
Oh, man.
Hey!
Hey. Small world.
Too small right now.
You know, for 19 years,
my wife and I have gone out
on February 13th.
Why the 13th, you ask?
Because the 14th, Valentine's Day,
is for amateurs.
The 13th is calm and relaxed.
It's easy to find a table.
There's no overpriced Prix-Fixe meals.
It's just me and my lovely bride...
good food, a warm conversation,
a place where I can
not think about the job
for a little while.
Sounds nice... sir.
It is, which is why
on my special night,
I don't want to see your faces.
So by the time I walk back to my table,
you will be gone.
Am I clear?
Crystal.
Like ghosts.
Have a good evening.
Okay. Shall we?
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Everything all right?
Yeah, it's fine.
To us.
Get off me.
What's taking so long?
I'm fine, thank you.
Hey!
Can we get our drink?!
Get off me!
Nolan, let's go.
She needs help.
You heard Grey.
Get off me.
Go get her a drink.
What's taking so long? Come on.
Miss, are you all right?
He bought me a drink I don't want,
and he's not taking no for an answer.
All right, time to leave
the girl alone.
Get your own girl. This one's mine.
All I'm saying
is that the house
is gonna be empty soon,
and we can do whatever we want.
Well, it's not gonna be empty.
I mean, Dominique will be
coming home from college.
And that home can be anywhere.
Will you just think about it, okay?
Watch out, watch out.
Whoa!
Oops.
Hello?
Mr. Nolan, it's Dave at Flower Town.
Uh, we're having a little trouble
delivering your Valentine's order
of two dozen roses for your wife.
Oh, uh, Dave.
Yeah, I actually won't be
needing that delivery this year.
What?
Uh...
Sarah and I got divorced.
I'm living in L.A. now.
Oh. I'm so sorry to hear that.
I mean, hell, your standing order
is as old as my shop, 20 years.
Yeah, yeah, it was hard,
but, um... uh...
it's for the best, you know?
People change.
That's just human nature.
It's easy to feel like you failed,
but truth is, at the end of the day,
we raised a great kid.
I don't have to tell you, Dave.
I know you have kids.
Dave?
Sorry, had to put you
on hold there for a sec.
So, what would you like me
to do with the flowers?
You know what?
Just deliver them to the hospital.
I'm sure someone there
would appreciate them.
Thanks.
Ohh.
Wow!
You okay?
I hit my head.
You locked the door.
Weirdest thing.
This guy keeps wandering
into my house uninvited.
You know...
it's Valentine's Day.
Yes, I was just reminded.
It's your first one alone. Ever.
So I thought maybe we could do
something after your shift.
You know, help get your mind off it.
Like?
You can invite some friends over.
I'll cater it. Yeah.
Wolfgang owes me a favor.
Yeah!
Yes?
Yeah, that sounds like fun!
That's awesome!
Okay, good. Now get out.
We didn't really think this through.
I totally forgot what today was.
I probably should've picked
a less loaded day
for our first sleepover.
Um... I didn't get you a gift.
Oh.
Well, then it's gonna be super awkward
when your presents get here.
I guess I can still
cancel the violinist.
I'm kidding.
Forgot it was Valentine's Day, too.
So, we'll just have to settle for this.
Hmm.
When can I see you again?
Um... Saturday?
Oh, I have to drive up
to Salinas Prison
to meet a client.
You could come with.
Make a weekend out of it.
Sounds romantic.
Could be.
Um...
maybe next time.
You're not having second thoughts
about dating the enemy, are you?
Defense attorneys aren't the enemy.
They're just a pain in the ass
we have to deal with on the daily.
'Cause we hold you accountable.
Because...
Uh-huh?
Nope. Not going there.
That's my gift to you.
Well, wish me luck.
I'm going in front of
Judge Bollard this morning.
He eats defense attorneys
for breakfast.
If anyone can charm him, it's you.
Mmm.
All right, we know what today is.
The most dangerous day of our year.
Valentine's Day, sir? Really?
Not Black Friday, not New Year's?
That's right, Officer Nolan.
Breakups and broken hearts.
Jealousy and revenge.
All make for a perfect storm
of heightened emotion
and dangerous situations.
Hell, sometimes violence can find you
minding your own business at dinner.
Sir, again, I can't tell you
how sorry I am.
I'm not the one that needs
the apologies, Officer Nolan.
Yes, sir. Please apologize
to your wife for me.
If you'd like me to make you
another reservation...
I traded shifts for last night off.
The night you ruined.
Yes, sir.
Uh, sir? I don't see my T.O.
Officer Bradford's
taken a personal day.
You're kidding, Tim hasn't taken
a personal day in his entire life.
Be that as it may, he's off today.
So, Chen, you'll be assigned
to the front desk.
All right. That's it.
Everybody be safe out there.
Hi.
I didn't think you'd come.
Yeah, I almost pulled a U-turn.
Twice.
Glad you didn't.
You look great.
For someone who got shot in the head.
No, I-I mean you look like you again.
How are you feeling?
The beginning was really rough,
but it would've been worse
if I didn't already
go through withdrawal in the hospital.
I'm... I'm proud of you
for seeing it through.
You didn't think I would.
No.
But I-I hoped I was wrong.
Yeah, well, I thought about
leaving every day.
What made you stay?
I found something I
wanted more than a fix.
For you to see me sober.
Well... guess my job here is done.
See ya.
Come on.
All right.
So, I'm having
a little get-together tonight.
Kind of an anti-Valentine thing.
Ben's having it catered.
Sadly, I'm not doing anything else.
Well, if Jackson's in, I'm in.
Wow. Way to make me feel like
a consolation prize.
Since when are you
anti-Valentine's Day?
You're a romantic.
Well, I-I mean...
I mean, you seem like one.
Yes, well, traditionally, yes,
but, uh, this year,
I thought I'd just embrace
the single life.
Shouldn't you be
at the front desk, Boot?
Oh. Right.
Sorry. Muscle memory.
I don't need the gear today, so...
S-Sorry.
Ladies!
O-Officers, I'm having
a little get-together tonight.
Love if you could join.
Pass.
Officer Bishop?
Don't even bother with her.
You have plans?
Yes.
No.
Don't start.
Talia.
What comes after awkward?
That.
So you going out with Wesley tonight?
Nope.
Why not?
You're getting a little
familiar, Officer West.
We're not friends, we're friendly.
You do understand the difference.
Yes, ma'am.
Your personal life is personal.
Exactly.
So, uh...
he did get me a gift.
He didn't think I saw it, but I did.
Does that mean I need
to get him something?
I mean, do you want
Lord, no. Men are
impossible to shop for.
Who needs the pressure?
You better run!
Good God.
Men should never run naked.
I'll kill you!
Looks like Valentine's Day
is starting early.
You're tackling the naked one!
You know, being on my own
for once is actually liberating.
Mm-hmm. Keep trying to
convince yourself of that.
I mean, I can see how it might
make someone feel less than.
The secret is just to see the positive.
That's just my plan for the day.
What about you?
What about me?
Well, Lopez was giving you a hard
time about your plans tonight.
I realized I don't know anything
about your personal life.
Are you single? Dating?
In a relationship?
No.
That's... unhelpful.
Exactly.
Valentine's Day is
a manufactured holiday
that does nothing but make
those alone feel lonelier.
And those who are in
relationships feel disappointed
because life isn't a fairy tale.
Is that why Lopez said not
to bother inviting you?
'Cause of your hatred of
all things love-related?
Not at all.
I would love to fail you
on your evaluation
if you bring up Valentine's Day again.
Copy that.
Mind your business!
I'm just checking the blind spot,
make sure there's no one.
7-Adam-15, single car accident.
1530 Crescent Heights.
Unknown injuries.
7-Adam-15 responding.
Control, show us Code 6,
1350 Crescent Heights.
We have a power line down. Alert DWP.
Ma'am, stay in the car! It's not safe!
She's in shock. Don't!
We have to do something.
I'm going.
Ma'am.
Come on! Come on.
Here we go. Easy. Okay.
Control, send an RA to our location.
We have an adult female, 30s,
not conscious, not breathing,
electric-shock victim.
Come on.
Hey!
Hey. Welcome back.
What happened?
Try not to move.
You were electrocuted.
An ambulance is on its way.
Did you save me?
Uh...
uh, well, yeah. Yeah.
Thank you.
Of course.
Next.
Hi. Uh...
I need to talk to a vice cop.
Okay, about what?
Um...
I need to find a hooker.
And not a street-walker.
Uh, she's, uh, higher class than that.
I, uh, met her at a hotel bar
and, uh, spent some,
uh, time with her on Saturday,
and, uh, I'd like
to take her out tonight
on a date for, uh, Valentine's Day.
So you walked into a police station
to find a prostitute?
Well, yeah.
You guys have, like,
binders full of them right?
I figure I can just
page through the girls
till I spot her.
Yeah, uh,
I'm sorry, sir.
The LAPD is not a referral
service for prostitutes.
Okay, uh, you're standing
in the way of true love.
And that's a burden
I will have to bear.
Next.
Indecent exposure?!
Her husband was chasing me.
What was I supposed to do?
Not sleep with his wife?
Hey, what happened?
I barely got into my opening
statement with Judge Bollard.
He kept interrupting me.
Words were exchanged.
He held me in contempt.
I'll take him off your hands
and book him.
Fine by me.
Ooh, I recently had a dream like this.
Oh, yeah?
Uh-huh.
I'm, uh... I'm gonna go get a snack.
All right, counselor.
I'm gonna need you
to empty your pockets.
Uh-huh.
And take off your tie
and your shoes and socks.
Do it nice and slow for me.
You're enjoying this way too much.
Uh-huh.
So what exactly did you say
to piss off the judge?
I was listing cases
of extreme use of force
by law enforcement...
trying to set precedent.
Mm, let me guess...
he ruled those cases were immaterial.
Over and over. It was relevant.
By the time my client got to booking,
his arm was broken.
Was he resisting arrest?
Even if he was,
that doesn't give you permission
to hurt him like that.
Give me permission?
No, I didn't...
I didn't mean it like that.
Hey!
I changed my mind. You book this guy.
I got work to do.
Angela, I didn't mean that.
Let's go.
Okay.
Look, I don't want
to talk about it, either,
but it's part of my recovery.
Can't you just admit
all your sins to your therapist?
I already have.
The whole point is to make amends
with the people that I've hurt.
And I hurt you most of all.
And telling me about all
the horrible things you did
is gonna make it better?
No... But only through honesty
can you learn to trust me again.
Isabel, you...
you didn't do those things
because you're a bad person.
You did them because
you're a drug addict.
And addicts lie, they cheat, steal.
They betray everyone around them.
It's hard-wired into their DNA.
So, are you saying you
can never trust me again?
Because I'll always be an addict.
No.
I'm saying that you hurt me
because of the drugs.
And you won't hurt me now
because you're clean.
You can't know that.
Sure I can.
If you want to tell me
how you put our IRA
into your arm after you left
or how you robbed the neighbors
when it ran out,
go right ahead.
Things are always
so black and white with you. It's...
Comforting?
Maddening.
Look, when we got married,
I felt this huge weight
to live up to your standards.
I never asked you to.
You didn't have to.
I didn't want to disappoint you.
And all I ever did was fail.
Hi... Is Officer Nolan around?
Oh, yeah, I think I just saw him.
Sorry, you are?
I am a very grateful citizen.
Oh.
He saved my life this morning.
Oh!
Okay.
Officer Nolan,
report to the front desk.
Do you know him?
Yeah, a bit.
He seems like a lovely man.
He's okay.
He saved my life.
Yeah, you said.
Oh, hey! What are you doing here?
You should be at home in bed.
I'm on my way home.
The hospital gave me
a clean bill of health...
Ah.
...thanks to you.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Just some superficial burns.
Ooh.
Yeah.
These are for you.
Wow.
That is, uh, extremely kind,
very thoughtful,
and entirely unnecessary.
Um, but now you should really
get home and get some rest.
Well, maybe you can stop by
later and check in on me.
I, um... I do have a, um, long shift
that I really should
be getting back to.
But, again, thank you so much.
This is really nice, and I'm j...
I'm just so glad that you're all right,
and, uh, thank you.
That's...
Yeah.
Well, thank you. Thank you for...
Yeah, thank you.
She seems nice.
Uh, yeah, I saved her life.
She said.
Don't forget your muffins.
Right.
Heavier than they look.
Excuse me. You have an assault victim.
We're here to take his statement.
Room 524... back and to the left.
Thank you.
Have I, um, seen you
hiking at Runyon Canyon?
Quite possibly.
But I don't remember seeing you.
I mean, I look different
out of uniform.
Yeah.
I bet you do.
Come on.
What?
Good afternoon, sir. I'm Officer Lopez.
This is Officer West.
We understand you were attacked.
That's what they keep telling me.
Doctor said your memory's
a little fuzzy.
Is that the kind way
of bringing up my dementia?
No. Uh, that's not what I meant.
You were hit on the head
when you were attacked.
Doctor said you might
have a concussion.
Lucky me.
I get dementia and a concussion.
Can you tell us what you do remember?
No, not really. No.
I know I was downtown.
Don't remember why.
Uh...
there was this guy running.
He slammed into me and
he knocked me down, and I...
...think he hit me, too.
I have these bruises.
Did you get a look at him?
Whether I did or not, I don't remember.
I'm so sorry.
I wish I could be more helpful.
Thank you.
Hey, do you know if Mr. Scott's
got anyone coming by to see him?
Um, I couldn't find anyone to call.
According to his primary doctor,
he lives alone.
No immediate family.
I can do a records search
for extended family.
What? I feel bad for him.
That's nothing to apologize for.
I'll write down his full name
and date of birth for you.
Thank you.
7-Adam-15, 459 in progress.
Female locked in bathroom.
States intruder is in her home.
Control, we are on scene.
Please tell homeowner
to remain in the bathroom.
Clear.
Police.
Did a sweep of the house.
There's no one here.
It's safe to come out.
Officer Nolan?
Have you come to my rescue again?
It's against the law,
to call in a false 911 report.
It wasn't false.
I heard someone in the house.
And you just happened to report it
when we were the closest unit?
What are you accusing me of?
I bet if I check your phone,
I'll find a police scanner app.
You waited until you heard
we were in your neighborhood
to place your 911 call.
How am I doing?
Can I talk to her for a minute?
One minute.
Is that your husband?
Yes.
Killed in action?
Just over a year ago.
And I've been in a daze ever since.
Until today...
until you saved my life.
I feel reborn.
Like... Like you've lifted
a cloud off of me.
It has to mean something.
That's just adrenaline.
You had a near-death experience.
It's not about me.
I'm flattered for the attention.
I am.
But I am not interested.
Okay?
Okay.
Take care of yourself.
I spoke to the court clerk.
The judge is still
not ready to let you go.
You must have really pissed him off.
Yeah, I seem to have
that effect on people.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I get a little carried away sometimes,
but I know you're a good cop.
Most of us are.
Agreed.
You get out early enough, I'll
let you take me out to dinner.
I don't need anything fancy.
Uh...
you know, I already made plans.
I thought I couldn't see you, but, um,
I could cancel.
No, it's... it's not a big deal.
I gotta get back out there.
Okay.
You haven't said a word for an hour.
You're allowed to be angry with me.
You're supposed to be.
I deserve it.
I don't want to be angry.
I just want my wife back.
But I can't have that.
You know, for the last year,
everyone's told me
to just give up on you.
To let you go 'cause you were...
you were gone anyway.
But I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it, I mean,
what kind of husband would I be
if I left you when you were lost?
But you're not lost anymore.
And I will always be a reminder
of your lowest point...
of that shame you felt
when you put that needle in your arm.
So, as...
So, as long as we're together,
you're never gonna be able
to move forward.
This is the end.
Look, I should, uh...
I should get on the road.
Okay.
But, uh...
you're doing great here.
Hey, um...
Yeah?
Thank you.
For what?
For never giving up on me.
Yeah.
Ready to go?
Yeah. Just looking for a next of kin
for Mr. Scott.
Guy led quite a life.
Lived all over
but was an only child.
Never married.
You okay?
Yeah.
Good thing I didn't get him a gift.
Who? Wesley? Why?
I think I misread our relationship.
Hey, just the two I was looking for.
So, something weird
came up in connection
to the dispatch call that
I sent you on earlier...
The old guy who was attacked?
What about him?
Well, I was compiling a list
of the day's dispatches...
totally not my favorite part of
the job, by the way...
and something just popped out at me.
There was an attempted abduction
right by where your
attack victim was found.
The woman fought off her attacker,
and the guy just fled.
Could be that's who
slammed into Mr. Scott.
Did the woman leave
a description of the guy?
She just said he was
Caucasian male, strong.
Thanks, Nell.
Sure.
And our only other potential
witness has dementia,
can't remember what
the guy looked like.
Let's go try and jog his memory.
Hey. What are you,
uh, doing out of bed?
I need to go home.
My mother made dinner.
Sir, do you know where you are?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm in the hospital.
I just had my appendix out.
I'm guessing that was a long time ago.
Okay, let's get you back in bed.
Hey, uh, can you help us?
Sure.
Mr. Scott, you need to get back in bed.
Doctor's orders, okay?
Oh.
Okay.
Here you go.
Uh, do we need to come back?
Oh, no. No.
He's okay. Aren't you, Mr. Scott?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
No worries.
I'm Officer Lopez.
Do you remember me from earlier?
Uh-huh, I think so.
You're in the hospital
because you were assaulted.
Uh, right, right, right, right, right.
Yeah, that's why my head hurts?
Exactly.
We, uh, think the person
who assaulted you attacked
someone else beforehand.
That you were in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Do you remember being
assaulted earlier today?
Yeah.
I remember being knocked down.
And... And...
And I think he hit me, too, 'cause I...
Yeah, you said that.
Is there, um, anything else
you can tell us about him?
He was tall.
He was white.
Um, his hair was long, I think.
I'm sorry. That's all I got.
It's okay.
That's more than we had before.
Try and get some rest.
Is she all right?
The woman he attacked?
From what I hear, yes.
That's good. That's good.
Son of a bitch.
What?
He asked if she was all right,
but you never said the other
victim was a woman.
He's the one who attacked her.
He's got dementia. It was
diagnosed three years ago.
Doesn't mean he couldn't have
tried to abduct that woman.
He hits his head as he's escaping.
Someone finds him disoriented,
takes him to the hospital.
And he's too out of it to object.
Just has to play along.
Makes up a story
about getting attacked.
Or maybe he really did forget about it,
and he's just trying to fill in
the blanks in his memory.
All right, so what do we do?
I'm going back to the station
to mobilize Major Crimes.
They'll get a warrant for his DNA
and check it against
the woman who was attacked.
You stay here and make sure
he doesn't go anywhere.
Do you really think
he could've done it?
I mean, he seems so lost.
Getting sick doesn't make you a saint.
Hey, ready?
I guess so.
Don't act so excited.
Do you think it's weird
that we're the only ones
going to your
anti-Valentine's Day thing?
It's only as weird as we let it be.
Besides, I'm sure other people
will meet us there.
Ah! Officer Lopez,
have you reconsidered
about joining us this evening?
No chance. We're still working a case.
Which means Jackson won't be there.
It's going to be fun. Not weird. Fun.
Who are the flowers for?
Oh, they came in for Talia.
From who?
None of your business.
That's none of my business.
Should I go find her?
No, I'll do it.
Fun.
These came for you.
Okay, thanks.
They look expensive.
What's your point?
I thought you broke things
off with him.
It's complicated.
He went back to his wife?
Yes.
Then it's simple.
He's married, not separated.
And you're done.
Officer Lopez,
detectives looked into
your hospital Vic.
Am I right about him
trying to abduct that woman?
It's much bigger than that.
When they looked into his background,
they got hits on several attacks
on similar women
spanning over three decades.
Over a dozen unsolved cases,
some of them homicides.
I think you may have found
a serial killer.
Was the dementia just a cover?
Not necessarily.
He went dormant after
his first diagnosis.
So what? He, like, forgot he liked
to kill women?
I don't know.
It's possible today was
a "good memory" day...
where he got his taste back.
FBI is sending somebody from Quantico.
Major Crimes is sending
a mobilizing team
to question him tonight.
You sure you got him squared away?
Yes, Officer West is with him.
Go make sure.
Ooh.
Oh.
Sorry. Oh, thanks.
Mr. Scott? Kevin?
Aah!
It's not twisting.
Just put it... put it on the corner.
Right?
Yeah, and then you grind it.
Knu... Knuckle in?
Yeah.
I thought you were gonna
invite a bunch of people.
I did. They could still come.
Well... I found a date.
I met her at the store
where I went to buy the wine.
You were gone 20 minutes.
I know.
Apparently I still got it.
Ooh! That might just be her.
Coming!
Looks very nice. Okay.
Hmm.
See what we have here.
Knowing him, it's going
to be very expensive.
Hey, guys.
I want you to meet Denise.
Oh, my God.
What a small world.
All right, Mr. Scott,
it's time for your...
You too.
She's crazy.
She's in pain
and trying to cope with
the loss of her husband.
By stalking you?
It's a cry for help.
Hey. She seems nice, right?
Yeah, um, so here's the thing.
She's actually just
using you to get to me
because I saved her life earlier,
and now she's transferring the feelings
she had for her late husband onto me.
Okay.
Then you might not want her
wandering around your house.
I really don't. I should go find her.
Where's Kevin?!
I don't know.
Are you okay?
He has my weapon.
Stay here and make sure he's all right.
7-Adam-07, officer attacked
at Shaw Memorial,
suspect is dressed
in green scrubs, armed,
send backup.
Kevin!
Stop! Police!
Stop! Freeze!
Stop resisting.
It's over. You're under arrest.
Denise, I...
My hero.
Denise, this is...
We need to talk.
I know what you're gonna say.
You're already in love
with somebody else.
I-I'm not.
Please.
I saw you two talking on the deck.
It's so apparent.
Yeah, that's not...
I just wish you'd look at me
the way you look at her.
Look, Denise, I-I know you're
going through a hard time,
and I'm so sorry, but honestly,
y-y-you have to believe me.
I'm not the answer to your problems.
I know that now.
Okay, good.
Let's just get you dressed,
and I'll get you a car home.
No.
Okay. Yeah.
Know what? Hey, hey!
We need to make her throw up.
Poison Control said not to do that.
There's a greater chance she
could choke on her own vomit.
Well, let's put her in the shower!
They said sudden change in temperature
could send her into a state of shock.
Why's everything I learned wrong?
Okay, thank you.
They said we just need
to keep her alert.
Ambulance is on the way. Hey!
Hey, Denise.
Need you to stay with us, okay?
Denise.
Hey, I need you with us, okay?
You're gonna stay with us, all right?
Hey.
Paul.
You were supposed to come home.
You promised me you'd come home.
What am I supposed to do without you?
You fight. He'd want you to fight.
Come on.
Right here, right here.
One, two, three.
Come on. Okay.
All right.
I should really go with her.
Have you learned nothing?
Going to the hospital
with your suicidal stalker
is definitely not a good idea.
She's alone.
I'll go with her.
I just hope you see the irony
of me spending Valentine's Day
with your stalker.
I owe you.
Yeah, you do.
Oh, what are you doing here?
I thought you were off today.
I was. I just, uh...
I needed to take my mind off
some personal stuff,
so I figured a stack of
paperwork would do the trick.
Well, I was gonna head over to Nolan's.
He's having, like,
an anti-Valentine's Day thing.
Um, maybe I'll see you there?
No. No, I'm not feeling very social.
Tim.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Nell?
Yeah?
Look, I have no right to ask this,
but I really don't want
to do paperwork right now.
And the thought of going back
to my empty house
is unbearable, so...
...if you'd be up
for a totally platonic
Valentine's Day drink...
...I could use a friend.
I can be that.
Thanks.
Judge says you can go.
About time.
You should still be able to make
your date with Melanie.
How exactly did you know about that?
Ah. Let me guess.
You performed an illegal search
of my phone.
I did it as a civilian,
not in conjunction with a case,
so it's not an illegal search.
Does that make it better?
No.
Melanie is my stepmom.
My dad died last year.
She was gonna be alone,
so I'm taking her out to dinner.
Oh.
I really screwed that up, didn't I?
Yep.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, uh, I just wanted to stop by
and see if you were doing okay.
Oh, I'm fine.
They wanted to send me home, but...
they don't know how thick my skull is.
Um...
do you have time to grab a bite?
Uh, I get a break in 15 minutes.
But the food here is terrible, so...
Oh, well, that's why I brought takeout.
Yeah, I'm an Ova-Lacto Vegetarian
with an immune-mediated response
to nuts, soy, and wheat, so...
Of course.
I'm just messing with you.
I eat everything.
I'm like a goat.
A goat? That's...
I'd say you're just...
just a little bit better looking.
You think I look good now.
Wait till you see me when I get out
from under these fluorescents.
So it's a date?
Oh, it's happening.
Whether it's a date or not
depends on how it goes.
And what's this?
Oh, you know it's gonna take
more than a little bar fight
to torpedo our Valentine's Day.
I love you.
I know.
So, did you give any more thought
to what we talked about last night?
You can take your full
pension in six months.
We could travel the world.
We can make up for lost time.
Doesn't that sound nice?
Yeah, look.
I'm not ready to be done here just yet.
Okay.
But I'm not gonna
stop talking about it.
Of course.
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Sit down.
I hope she's okay.
Me, too.
I have to say, your, uh,
first solo Valentine's Day
was quite the adventure.
That's an understatement.
Can I confess something?
Of course.
It made me feel good.
That she was into me.
You know, ob-obviously
before I realized
she was not doing well.
And I would've never have acted on it.
Just sometimes, though...
especially today...
you just want someone
to tell you that you're pretty.
Does that sound stupid?
No.
It sounds human.
Where the hell is everybody?!
Uh, long story.
I thought you had plans.
I canceled them.
Great! Come in.
Uh, Talia, this is Ben.
Ben, this is Talia Bishop, my T.O.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
John sings your praises
almost every day.
Really?
I don't know about every day.
I might've said a few nice
things about you.
Mm-hmm.
Can I get you a drink?
There's plenty of food
if you're hungry.
Can you make a martini? Extra dirty?
Can I ever.
So you two went to college together?
That's right. We were roommates.
So that means you have
a lot of embarrassing stories
about Officer Nolan here.
Yes, I do.
I don't like
the direction this just took.
So picture this...
Junior year.
John is going through
his hair metal phase.
Hey.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com