♪ I can still taste you
on my lips ♪
It's just not a term
you expect to hear
in 2019, you know?
"Grave robber."
It's like chimney sweep.
Alchemist.
- Fishmonger.
- Keep naming old-ass jobs
and your next one's gonna be
at Medieval Times.
Copy that.
There he is.
If he starts digging up
body parts to make a monster,
you're on your own.
Police!
Geez. You scared me.
- Get out of there.
- It's okay. This is my mom.
And you missed her so much
you had to dig her up?
No,
she's got my jewelry.
She was supposed
to leave it to me,
but they buried her with it,
and now I need it.
To buy drugs?
No.
Okay.
Come on. Come on.
Climb on out
of there.
Hands over your head.
Interlace
your fingers.
I really do miss her.
She's the only person
that ever believed in me.
I've been so lost
since she's been dead.
Then maybe you should this
as an opportunity
to get
your life straight.
You know what?
Get clean.
Make your mother
proud.
Yeah.
Yeah,
I'm going to do that.
I'm gonna
turn my life around.
I'm gonna get clean.
For Mom!
It's gonna be one
of those nights, isn't it?
Yep.
Come on. Get up.
Come on. I got ya.
Come on.
What?
She's over there.
I remember that statue
from the funeral.
I'll put him in the shop.
It still doesn't
feel real.
Yeah.
But life goes on
whether we like it or not.
Okay.
Back to it.
*THE ROOKIE*
Season 01  Episode 17
Episode Title: "The Shake Up"
Oh, I could
get used to this.
Right?
They don't have this
in D.C.
Nope. Just an equal amount
of self-absorbed people.
Mm-hmm. Only they're
far more pale.
Yes.
Which is why
you should spend
more than a few days a month
down here with me.
Oh,
I wish I could.
But I landed this big
security contract in Virginia.
Nice.
Which reminds me.
Um, there's this thing
that I heard about
that I think...
you should volunteer for.
I love volunteering
for things.
What's the thing?
Well, uh, a friend of mine
is an ADA out here,
and he mentioned
that he's gonna be
reaching out to your station
for manpower
for a protection detail.
Some high-powered witness
in a safe house.
Sounds like fun.
And some
valuable experience.
How can I ever
thank you?
Oh, I'm sure I will think
of a few ways.
I'm sure you will.
We're talking about sex, though, right?
Yeah.
Per Captain Weatherby,
the following protocol changes
will take place immediately.
No more putting any boots
on top of lockers.
Any boots left on top of lockers
will be thrown away
at midnight and noon daily.
Second, every officer
must provide a business card
to every citizen
they contact.
If a citizen doesn't want
a business card,
the officer must write
a police report
and document the fact the
citizen refused a business card.
Sir, with all due respect,
this sucks.
Ours is not to judge,
Officer Lopez.
Command believes that the
captain's focus on efficiency
is what Mid-Wilshire
needs right now.
Captain.
Can I help you?
I need an updated
vehicle list.
Yes, sir. I'm in the middle
of roll call.
I'll get it to you
right after.
But since you're here,
would you like to
say anything inspirational
to day shift?
Did you tell them
about the boots?
Yes, sir.
Oh. Okay.
Well, uh...
Keep up the, uh...
good work.
Alright.
Last bit of business.
District Attorney's office
has a witness on ice.
They need our help
watching them.
I usually don't assign rookies
these type of details,
Officer Nolan.
And Officer Bishop
would have to agree.
Forget it. Protection details
are like watching paint dry.
Looks like
you're out of luck.
I'll do it.
And Nolan and I haven't had
a chance to "bond" yet.
Great.
Alright. Bishop,
you'll be riding with Chen.
That's it.
Oh, and remember...
when you take
your shops in at night,
you now have to
drive by the garage
to get a mechanical inspection
and mileage report.
You're welcome.
You're right,
this sucks.
For you. 'Cause I'll be home eating
dinner while you're doing all that.
Officer West
to the front desk. Visitor.
I'll be right back.
Make it fast. Captain's put
a clock on our roll out.
Hey.
Um, what are you
doing here?
You... left something
at my place.
Um, I just can't
really have visitors here.
Look, I just...
I just really want to keep
my personal and work life
separate.
Fine.
You left your off-duty weapon
at my place.
I can't believe
I did that.
Yeah, you were
a little distracted.
Look,
you don't understand.
If anybody found out
about this, I'd get fired.
Immediately.
And, like, what...
Why would you bring it here?
What if you got
pulled over?
You're mad at me
about this?
No, look...
I got to get to work.
I'm sorry, Gino.
I...
Yeah.
Hey, Boot.
What's the holdup?
Uh, nothing.
Sorry.
I just...
Actually, can I, uh...
Can I just get a minute?
I need to hit the locker room.
30 seconds or I fail you
for the day.
Must have left
his boots up.
You up to date
on protection detail protocols?
I think so. Okay. We use
the "Loser System"...
Named for the losers
we protect.
L-O-S-R... Listen, Observe,
Secure, Report.
You listen
for any movement,
changes or information
that impact the mission,
observe
the subject's behavior,
changes in the environment,
et cetera.
Secure... make sure no threats
infiltrate the perimeter,
and, finally, report.
Report any suspicious activity,
no matter how minor,
to your superior officer
immediately.
- That means me.
- What about "e"?
"Loser" has an "e."
"E" is for "engage,"
which is left out
because you are not
to engage the subject
unless it's
a life-threatening emergency.
We're here
to guard this guy,
not braid his hair
and be besties.
- That understood?
- Understood.
I don't even know
how to braid hair.
I was gonna learn if we had
a daughter, but...
Never mind.
Police!
You alright?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thanks. He got me
when I wasn't looking.
You're under arrest
for assaulting an officer.
He's the one
who should be arrested.
He said he'd rip up the ticket
if I gave him $100.
- That's not true.
- Like hell it isn't! Hey!
Sir, there's no use in lying.
Alright?
Whatever really happened
is gonna be on
the officer's
body camera.
Where's
your body camera?
Um...
it's, uh...
It's in the car.
It was on the fritz.
I'll... I'll go get it.
Officer, wait!
Get out of the car!
Get out of the car now!
- Okay, take it easy. Take...
- Get out of the car.
Take it easy, man.
Come on.
Interlace your fingers
and face
- the car.
- Okay, okay, okay.
It's just
a big misunderstanding.
Can't we just... Can't we just
talk this out, you know?
Cop to cop?
You're not a cop.
And impersonating a law
enforcement officer is a felony.
I want a lawyer.
Maybe you
can impersonate one.
That's the safe house.
7-Adam-19 on scene
at the mutual aid call.
Will make contact
in 10 seconds.
Roger, 7-Adam-19.
LAPD,
Bradford and Nolan.
- Uh, Officer Nolan?
- Nolan.
Hey,
I'm ADA Sean DelMonte.
Jessica Russo told me
you'd be helping out.
Sir, Officer Nolan
is a rookie.
I'm his superior officer,
Tim Bradford.
Oh. Sorry. I just assumed
that he'd be in charge.
The last guy Jessica dated
was a Navy SEAL. Seriously?
Yeah. Talk about a strong
handshake, like a vise grip...
Okay, can we get the download
on our protectee?
Of course. Yeah.
Brad Hayes.
Worked Border Patrol
for 12 years down in Temecula.
Rose to second in command.
Then he turned around and
started using what we taught him
to help the other side.
He charged the cartels a fortune
to smuggle people in and out.
Now he's naming names.
No wonder he's
hiding out here.
Yeah, he's testifying
before a grand jury tomorrow.
Look, Sheriff's Department
will coordinate shift changes.
Here's my card.
Use the cell number
in case anything comes up,
no matter how small.
Will do.
Deputy.
It's very nice to meet
both of you.
And, again,
sorry for the confusion.
No worries.
- Navy SEAL?
- Focus, Boot.
Now do a sweep
of the house.
Note ingress
and egress points,
escape avenues,
and sight lines.
Report back in 10.
Yes, sir.
- How's it going?
- Fine. Thanks.
Oh.
No "e" in "loser."
Hey.
There is an "e"
in "loser."
7-Adam-15,
false imprisonment call,
6991 West Ellroy.
Code 2 high.
She's got him
locked up in there!
I haven't been able
to reach him in days.
- Who?
- My boyfriend.
Who's got him
locked up?
His mother.
His mother?
Look, no offense,
but could it be
that he just doesn't
want to see you?
No,
she's really strict,
and she hates
that we're together.
Please,
I'm really worried.
Police, open up!
Police!
Wait! I have a key!
I have a key.
Thanks.
Stay back.
Stop, Mom!
Please!
...who sustains my life.
Turn back the evil
upon my foes;
in your faithfulness,
destroy them.
And by the power
of our Lord Jesus Christ,
may you be snatched away
and driven from
the church of God.
From all the souls made
in the image and likeness of God
and redeemed by the Precious
Blood of the Divine Lamb,
- I cast you out!
- Ow!
Stop!
Get away from him!
- No. No!
- That's enough.
You have to let me
save him.
He's been possessed
by the dark one.
Control, I need RA
to 6991 West Ellroy.
Teenage Hispanic male,
suffering from dehydration.
What did you do to him,
you sick bitch?!
- Hey.
- No! No.
He's been
possessed by your filth.
No.
Sergeant.
Yes.
Did you countermand
my vehicle reassignment order?
I thought it
was a mistake.
You reassigned all
our extra shops to LAX.
What are we supposed to use
if one of our cars breaks down?
Inventory lists
10 mountain bikes.
We'll use those.
Yeah.
Exercise is good
for the soul.
Less helpful in
a high-speed pursuit.
I have got
a doctor's appointment
and then lunch
with the Deputy Chief.
So make sure those
monthly reports are on my desk
- when I get back.
- Yes, sir!
Wow.
- He seems fun.
- Damn.
What are you doing here?
Uh, your wife called me.
She said that you were considering
throwing the new captain
out the window.
And you came
to talk me out of it?
Or open the window.
Whichever one
seems more productive.
He's hurting morale
and our ability
to do our jobs.
He's not the first pencil pusher
you've worked for, right?
And he probably
won't be the last.
So it is your job
to find a workaround.
You think the kid
will be okay?
Physically, yes,
but mentally, I'm not so sure.
I still can't believe a mother
would do that to her own son.
Sadly, it's not the worst thing
I've seen a parent do.
Oh, uh, hey.
Do you mind
if I take this call?
- Mm.
- Thanks.
Wh... What?
Mom, slow down.
W... Is he okay?
Did they send him
to Shaw Memorial?
Okay.
Yeah, no, that's good.
My dad got attacked
by one of his patients.
They think
his arm is broken.
I'll go as soon as
my shift's done, okay?
- Boot, we'll go now.
- Oh. Okay.
I'm gonna go right now,
and I'll call you
right after I see him, okay?
I love you, too.
Um, thanks.
My mom is out of town
at a conference.
Are you sure
this is okay?
Yeah. It's family.
Control,
have a unit meet us
at Shaw Memorial
for a prisoner transfer.
Also, show us
10-6 personal.
The whole house
is about 1,900 square feet.
Upstairs, there's
two bedrooms, a bathroom,
and a very small attic.
Sight lines are blocked
from the east...
I'm bored!
Not our problem.
Oh, it is killing me
not having Internet access.
Or a phone.
They actually gave me
newspapers.
What do they think,
I'm an animal?
Sir, we're here to keep you
alive, not entertained.
So step back.
Let us do our job.
He doesn't like me,
does he?
He probably thinks
I'm a traitor.
We're not here to judge you,
sir. Just keep you safe.
He's very good.
Very reassuring.
I'm gonna have a beer.
You guys want one?
No, thank you.
Shocker.
Officer Nolan.
Yes, sir?
I read about you
in the newspaper.
Your captain got killed
in the line of duty.
- Sounded like a real badass.
- She was.
Your name was all over
that article.
Pretty heroic stuff.
Not heroic enough.
Respiratory therapist, 4 West.
Gino. Hey.
Uh, I'm looking
for my dad.
He was brought in a little while
ago... broken arm?
Uh, yeah.
He's in Bed 2.
- I'm... I'm so sorry.
- Yeah, thanks.
Do we know
what his status is?
Doctor saw him
and scheduled him for X-rays.
Depending how bad the break is,
he might need surgery.
Um, I'll goose
the process along.
- Put in a room request.
- Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Your mother shouldn't
have called you.
Of course she should have.
What happened?
I was in the middle
of some alternative
anger management therapy,
and my patient
lost control.
What's his name?
Why?
Because
he broke your arm.
No, he had
a dissociative episode.
He didn't mean
to hurt me.
It doesn't matter.
The law is clear.
The law is broken!
Ow.
So you think
this is the solution?
To pretend
that this didn't happen?
It's a better solution
than letting you lock him up.
Now I'm in pain.
So if you're more worried
about being a cop
than being my daughter,
maybe you should leave.
You can sit down.
I'm not gonna bite.
I'm good.
Of course.
Suit yourself.
Your partner there
is a real hard-ass, huh?
I had a supervisor
just like him at Border Patrol.
He got off
on pushing buttons.
He's my training officer,
and we're not discussing this.
Hmm. I always forget
that you are a rookie.
It must chap your ass
to be bossed around
by a younger guy like that.
Not at all. It's the only way
I'm gonna learn.
I'm not buying it.
Guy like that?
Oh, man. He is all sorts
of superior.
He probably thinks that
I smuggled people over the border
for the money.
I watched people die
every day,
trying to
cross that border,
desperate for a new life.
And after
a few years of that...
I couldn't
take it anymore.
I decided to do something
and help them.
And so, yeah,
I made some money,
but there are people that
are alive today because of me.
I had no idea you were
such a humanitarian.
Thank you.
What about the people you
smuggled out of the country...
The, uh, cartel members,
fugitives from justice?
Okay, yeah, that was
for the money, but...
Hey, you.
What are you wearing?
I am at the safe house
right now.
Did you meet my friend Sean?
I did.
You dated a Navy SEAL?
I'm gonna kill him.
Yes, I did.
It was for about... two months,
right after my divorce.
Was he Team Six?
Are you asking if my
ex shot Bin Laden?
Yeah, just in a..."thank you
for your service" kind of way.
Got to go.
Yeah, we'll keep it
locked down here.
Let us know ASAP.
D.A.'s office just discovered
a credible threat
against our guy...
A cartel hit team.
Trying to figure out if the safe
house has been compromised.
Well, that looks
a little awkward.
It sure does.
Nurse's station.
Gino, hey. I, um,
tried calling your cell.
Yeah, I... I know.
I didn't answer.
Hello?
Gino?
He hung up.
Why?
What did you do?
Nothing.
Um, do you mind if we stop
by the hospital after lunch?
Not unless you get
food poisoning.
Are they sending backup?
That's unclear.
Sounded like they're scrambling
to assess the situation.
Hey, guys.
Something going on?
You seem stressed.
Nothing.
If there's a problem,
I deserve to know.
It's my life
that's on the line.
Sit your ass back down.
Make me.
Earthquake...
Get on the ground!
Hey!
Everybody under your desks!
Everybody down!
It's an earthquake!
Get down!
Wade!
Go! Come on!
I got you.
That was
a pretty good one.
I'm gonna check the house, make
sure we're still five by five.
Watch him.
Never been through
an earthquake before.
Yeah, they take some
getting used to.
Um...
are those guys
supposed to be here?
Get away from there.
Don't move!
Get down. Get down.
Give me your hands.
Give me your hands!
- What the hell is going on?
- Ow.
Nothing I can't handle.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Any word
on the hit squad?
No. Radios are down.
Phone.
We're on our own.
Okay. Okay.
Let's get you
to this table.
Let's sit you down.
- Good, good.
- Let me take a look.
Alright. That's gonna need
a few stitches.
This is not a priority.
Hey, call out
if you're injured!
- Me, Sarge.
- Hello? Hello?
Land lines are down.
7-Adam-100, status report.
Hello? Hel...
- So are the radios.
- Where's the captain?
At a doctor's
appointment.
Or maybe lunch by now.
Everyone!
Everyone! Listen up!
We trained for this.
First priority is assessment.
Lennox, Hall... sweep
the station for casualties.
If anyone needs to go home
to check on your family,
you're dismissed.
We take care of our own.
Come back when you can.
It's alright.
With comms down,
we skip right to the old-school
part of the manual.
This is a city
with people in crisis.
We will serve them,
we will protect them,
and we will make them safe,
understand?
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Alright.
Let's go! Let's go!
You're gonna need to
hold that to your face.
Make sure
you're holding that up.
Hey, keep this elevated.
Keep it up. Keep it up.
Officers!
Can you help?
Let's get out there.
He needs help.
Calm down.
We'll get to you.
I'm working as fast
as I can.
Hey!
Hey, ladies and gentlemen!
Ladies
and gentlemen, I need you to form
a single-file line
in order of your arrival.
Now, people! Right now!
Single file.
Just line up right here.
Yep.
Listen up, guys.
Settle down.
- Scalp lacerations.
- You can wait.
- Stress fracture.
Gino? Gino.
Just try to sit up.
Try to sit up.
Hey, hey, hey.
Open your eyes.
Hey! Hey!
I need a trauma team!
Possible internal bleeding!
Would it help
if I said I was sorry?
I... I think
the earthquake set off
my fight-or-flight response.
Save it.
I can't get through to
the DA's office or the station.
Radios are down.
Phone lines are overwhelmed.
Get ready to move.
We can't take a chance
this place has been compromised.
That's dumb. Why would we
run around the city?
There's no cover,
no concealment.
I say we stay put from a...
A tactical standpoint.
You don't get a vote.
You hit me in the head.
No one else
in the house, right?
If there is, shoot 'em.
- We got to get out of here!
- Back door!
What if there's
a gunman out there, too?
Then you'll shoot him!
We're sitting ducks here.
- Go!
- I'm not going anywhere!
- Go.
- No.
- Move!
- Aah.
Come on. Come on.
Go. Go. Go. Go.
Come on.
- We need transportation.
- Well, in case you haven't noticed,
there's a sniper
between us and our car.
Hold here.
Head on a swivel.
- This is stupid. We're sitting ducks.
- Shut up.
You are in
way over your head.
Says the guy being hunted
by the cartel hit squad.
Nice car.
Inconspicuous.
Get in the back.
What's the plan?
Back to the station?
No, that's where these guys
expect us to go.
Safest thing
is to get lost.
Go to the last place
they'd think to look for us.
I know just the place.
Yep, this is definitely
the last place I'd look for us.
Ugh, ooh.
I hate to be
that guy, but...
I'm gonna need
some sunblock.
I burn real easy.
I don't have any, but I can
bury you up to your neck
in the sand and put
a trash can on your head.
I'm fine.
- Ooh, I'm not putting that on.
- The wound is gonna leak.
Do you want blood
running into your eye all day?
- That's what I thought.
- Oh, my goodness.
Yep.
- Okay.
- Think we're good?
Wait, wait.
Stay right there.
One picture.
Just one.
- Stop that.
- One. Just one.
Alright, I'm... I'm ready.
Let's go.
Alright.
Radio tower's down.
ETA on repair
is at least an hour.
Phone services are swamped.
Only 20% of the calls
are getting through.
So we're going to mark every
Priority One call on the map
so we can all see
where the trouble spots are.
Sir, captain called in
on my line with orders for you.
Thank you.
Our fearless leader wants me
to immediately dispatch a unit
to Bel-Air
to guard against looters.
And he also wants one
sent to his own block.
Can you believe this guy?
There's no way I'm doing this.
Oh, yes, you are.
He's the captain.
Disobeying orders like that will
do nothing but get you fired.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Sorry to interrupt.
How's he feeling?
Uh, better.
Thank you for saving him.
Of course.
It's my job.
What's gonna happen
to my mom?
Is she going to jail?
That's not my call.
She's facing
serious charges,
but her state of mind will be
taken into consideration.
And if you can advocate
on her behalf,
there's a chance
she could avoid prison
and get the treatment
she needs.
Thank you.
Control, 7-Adam-7,
show us on patrol in Bel-Air.
Still no word from Gino?
Nothing.
What if he's hurt? Or worse.
And the last thing
I said to him was in anger.
Odds are he's fine.
Quake wasn't that big,
and the hospital's retrofitted.
This is a waste
of time and resources.
The last thing people are gonna
do when the city's at a standstill
is drive up to Bel-Air
and loot.
Or maybe not.
Front door's open.
- Stay back!
- Gun!
Come on!
I'll kill you!
He retreated inside!
Let's go!
Stay focused.
Remember your training.
Keep it cool. Keep it tight.
- Hands up!
- Don't shoot!
- Come out of there!
- Weapon! Drop the gun!
- It's only a BB gun.
- What the hell happened to you?
My boss,
he's lost his mind.
Who?
The fat guy in a kimono?
Yeah. Tommy Lamont.
I'm his assistant.
He was on day three of a coke
binge when the earthquake hit,
and now he thinks
it's the end of the world.
I'm still lost
on the welts.
He had us hunting each other
throughout the house
with BB guns to stay sharp
for the oncoming apocalypse.
- You're kidding.
- I wish.
But then when it hit,
he got into the gun cabinet,
and I was terrified he would
forget which was which.
Can you turn off
that alarm?
Yes.
Go do that,
then wait outside.
On me.
Jonah!
Mr. Lamont, LAPD!
Mr. Lamont,
I need you to stand
where I can see you
and put your weapons
on the ground.
I'm not falling
for that.
I saw that episode
of "Midnight Apocalypse"
where they steal
the police uniforms.
This guy is
out of his mind.
Sir, you're not
thinking straight.
- We're here to help you.
- I don't believe you!
It was just a BB.
That alarm is eating
into my brain!
Jonah's taking care
of that.
What have you done
with Jonah?
He's fine!
Jonah is fine.
He's helping us.
Gonna take care of that alarm.
Ah, you tricked him.
He's helping you
steal my rations!
Jonah!
Don't listen to them!
Don't trust them!
We're gonna be here
all day.
Mr. Lamont,
I'm gonna confide in you,
but you
can't tell anyone.
We have a place
all set up.
A bunch of us survivors
are heading that way.
Rations that can last for years,
solar power,
but we need you to trust us
and set down your weapons.
Turn around, and put your hands
on the back of your head.
Get on your knees.
Are you okay? Yeah.
On the bright side,
we finally have a legit reason
to go to
the hospital now.
Jonah!
Call my lawyer.
It would be a lot nicer
- without these cuffs.
- Tough.
Texts are back online.
It's from the ADA.
The hit team
wasn't trying to kill Hayes...
It was trying
to rescue him.
You were in on it
the whole time?
You set us up
to be killed.
No.
Well, yeah.
As much as I love the idea
of being a barista
in Armpit, Arizona,
- I've got other plans.
- How did they know how to find you?
You were sequestered.
No phone, no Internet.
GPS tracker.
Son of a bitch.
- That's not mine.
- We got to get out of here.
Uh-oh.
What do we do now?
You guys should just
let me walk away.
I mean, nobody gets hurt.
Think how
you're gonna feel
if another buddy gets killed
in the line of duty.
Shut up.
So what now?
They can't afford
to kill Hayes,
so they'll have to
come up here and get him.
You do know
there's three of them, right?
It's almost
a fair fight.
Hook him up.
Drop your guns
in the sand!
- Get down on your stomachs now!
- No.
Get down now!
Hands behind your back.
So I'm guessing my
immunity deal's out the window.
Cafeteria
had snickerdoodles.
Can't eat
before the surgery.
Well, you can
have them after.
I know you're
disappointed in me...
...but you and Mom always
taught me to be true to myself.
And... this job
it's...
It's who I am.
It makes me happy.
You hate the system because
it's designed to punish people,
not care for them,
but that will never change
unless people like me
step up and make it change.
I heard you talking
to that patient down the hall.
You were honest with him...
and kind.
I was impressed.
Dr. Chen?
William.
I told you not to come.
Dad, who's this?
A friend.
- You should go.
- I'm so sorry.
I was...
William, did you
assault my father?
It was an accident.
I... I... I didn't...
No, Lucy.
Don't.
N...
It'll devastate him!
Destroy all the work
we've done.
- I'm sorry.
- Let him go.
I can't.
I don't have a choice.
I will be right here
when you get out of surgery, okay?
Don't bother.
♪ I can't hear you ♪
- Sorry, sorry.
- No, no. Don't be.
- ♪ You're too far away ♪
- I deserve to be in a little pain
after overreacting
this morning.
Just... my dad is a legend
in the LAPD.
Half the people there think
I just got in on his name.
Anything I do hits me twice
as hard as any other rookie.
So I, um, just
try to keep my head down
and make everything
about the work.
- ♪ I can't love you ♪
- I'm sorry.
- ♪ How you want me to ♪
- It's not easy.
No, what's not easy
is admitting how freaked I was
when I couldn't get ahold
of you after the earthquake.
I'm sorry for being
such an idiot earlier.
Do over?
Do over.
- So I guess it's our bad.
- Your "bad"?
Your guys were supposed to
give Hayes a thorough pat-down
before bringing him
to the safe house.
How the hell did they
miss a tracking device?
Well, they didn't.
The deputy who patted him down
confessed to slipping Hayes
the tracking chip.
He's in custody now,
too.
So what's gonna happen
to Hayes?
Well, he's facing
a half a dozen new charges,
including two counts
of attempted murder.
He'll do 20 years,
easy.
That's if
he still cooperates.
Officer Chen.
Booking report is only three pages.
- Why do you have five?
- Um... I thought this arrest warranted
a mental health
report addendum.
The perpetrator shattered
your father's arm.
Are you sure you're not
trying to get back
into your dad's
good graces?
I'm pretty sure
that's impossible,
but, um, he's not wrong.
This guy needs help,
not prison,
so I'm gonna do what I can
to help get that for him.
Good.
Wait.
Was that a test?
What, you think Bradford has
a monopoly on 'em?
Thanks for the assist today.
Oh, are you
kidding me?
- That was fun being back in crisis mode.
- Sergeant Grey!
Yes, sir?
I just got off the phone
with my wife.
The patrol that you
assigned to my neighbor...
never showed up.
That's my fault, sir.
I rerouted the officers
to assist a traffic collision.
If you want to
file a complaint,
you'd be well within
your rights to do so.
I would... if I were
remaining in command here.
I've just been promoted
to headquarters.
Good luck with
your next captain.
Oh, good luck
to you, sir.
How the hell
did that guy get promoted?
Made a few phone calls.
Sang his praises
downtown.
I told them how he
single-handedly saved the city.
Doesn't it bother you
that he's going to take credit
for everything
that you did today?
No.
The people who matter know.
♪ How you want me to ♪
So how'd you like
your first earthquake?
It was terrifying.
Well, just wait
- until the big one hits.
- Oh.
Sean texted me
about you.
It looks like
you made a fan.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
And I wouldn't have
had you not told me
about that opportunity,
- so thank you very much.
- Mm.
I'm sorry that you...
almost got killed.
- I know, right?
- Oh.
Is... everything okay?
Y-Yeah.
Was there a reason
you didn't tell Sean
about me being a rookie?
I didn't know
that I was supposed to.
It bothers you?
No, no.
It's just...
You're a very
impressive woman.
Very. It's...
the least impressive thing
about you
is you're
dating a 45-year-old rookie.
That's ridiculous.
Look, I...
I like you.
You like me.
You're not always
gonna be a rookie,
and I will always be
this amazing, so...
Why?
What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
Synchronized  by  srjanapala