Previously on
"The Rookie: Feds"...
He did work counterintelligence
for a decade before he
came out to Los Angeles.
Just asked for the best
investigator they had.
Well, you got him.
We're professionals who break
guys like you for a living.
And if you think
the Russians have your back,
you are hopelessly naive.
The reason I-I haven't opened
the bottle is because I'm sober.
247 days.
Thank you for
sharing that with me.
I lateral transferred
from Oakland PD six months ago,
and I gotta say, I'm still not
vibing with the "LA thing."
You just haven't given
the right people a try.
Once you find your folks,
you gonna see LA
through different eyes.
♪ Coming out, do it right ♪
Hey, girl. Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
All good.
I already ordered.
Did you over-sleep?
Hell, no.
I've been up since
the crack of black, okay?
I lost track of time
reading case files.
Hi, sweetie.
Can I have
a black rice bowl
with the dressing
on the side,
egg whites,
extra fluffy,
uh, immune-booster coffee
with two shots of espresso?
Thank you.
What?
That's the most bougie
breakfast order
I've ever heard.
[ Clicks tongue ]
Let me guess.
You ordered an egg sandwich
with extra cholesterol?
And I'm excited to eat it.
[ Laughs ]
You working
a big investigation--
all those case files?
Oh, no.
Those are slow burners.
I just like to soak up
as much knowledge as I can
about any open case
I can get my hands on.
Gotta keep the Black girl magic going.
You know what
your problem is?
You got your co-workers thinking
you're a Black superhero.
And?
And you're not.
You're 50 years old--
48, thank you.
[ Chuckles ]
And you're doing too much.
Aren't you tired?
I'm exhausted.
But I've worked so hard
and come so far,
I can't take my foot
off the gas now.
Where did you
come from?
[ Whimpers ]
This is-- This is blood.
Whose dog is this?
[ Dogs barking ]
H-H-Hold on.
[ Barking continues ]
Ma'am, looks like you fell
and hit your head.
Are you all right?
I got jumped.
Did they rob you?
[ Exhales sharply ]
All my clients' keys.
They could be robbing
their houses right now.
We're gonna need a list
of names and addresses.
We're gonna need to get units
to all those houses ASAP.
This isn't a federal case, Simone.
It's LAPD,
and I got it.
If you think I'm gonna walk away
while you run towards danger,
you don't know me
at all.
Now, get some backup down here
and an ambulance for this girl
so we can go
run these guys down.
Damn.
What is it that you
think I'm doing?
Calling the nail salon?
[ Whimpers ]
♪ Ah ah, ah ah, ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ah ah, ah ah, ah-ah-ah ♪
Did you see
the breaking news?
Uh, what?
Quite the scandal.
Last night,
this man stayed over
at his girlfriend's house.
They had...
quite the romantic evening.
But when she woke up,
instead of getting
breakfast in bed,
he was gone.
No note, no text, no call.
He ghosted her as if they don't
work in the same building.
I'm sorry.
After you fell asleep,
I, uh--
I got a phone call
from Michelle.
So a woman I've never heard of
got you out of my bed.
No. N--
This isn't helping.
Michelle is, uh...
my-- my sponsor's wife.
Randy didn't show up last night,
so I, uh...
went out to go look for him
and found him in a dive bar--
hammered.
Your sponsor. Oh, no.
Decade of sobriety, back to
counting days instead of years.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Where is he now?
Uh, he's--
he's home safe, drying out.
Do you want to take a walk, talk?
No, i-it's okay.
I'm-- I'm-- I'm fine.
Actually, uh, I need to--
I'll talk to you later?
Of course.
Garza:
It's been four months
since Simone and Brendon
joined our operation,
and I want to commend
the both of you
for getting them
to this point.
I-I appreciate that, Matt,
considering I had a tougher
assignment with Simone.
Excuse me?
I have been turning
a former TV star meat puppet
into a solid field agent.
My job is way tougher.
At least actors
can follow directions.
Do you know how hard I've had
to work to break a wild horse?
Especially one who constantly
reminds you she's Black Beauty?
Yes, Brendon?
Hey.
Uh, am I supposed to be
in here?
You guys keep looking out
at me.
Hey, is that my file?
And Simone's?
We were just finishing up
a Senior Briefing, Brendon.
Oh, sorry.
Where is Simone?
Uh, I have no idea.
Oh, I see Carter
hasn't been teaching
his trainee
about punctuality.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
Oh.
Speaking of.
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Simone, we were
just talking about you.
Because you're late.
Simone: Sorry, boss,
but I kinda got caught up
in an international incident.
[ Garza sighs ]
This better be good, Simone.
Simone: It is.
A dog walker was assaulted
by two robbers
looking to gain access
to her rich clients' homes.
Now, before LAPD
could mobilize,
two of the houses
were already ransacked.
One of them belonged
to Viktar Saroka,
Consul General of
the Republic of Belarus.
A burglary of a dignitary's home
isn't a great look for LA,
but what elevates it
to an international incident?
Wait for it.
Okay, freeze and zoom in.
Boom.
They stole
a diplomatic pouch.
All right, I need to reach out
to the Consulate right away.
Already did.
They're sending someone.
How about
the State Department?
Oh,
I didn't call them.
Those guys are even more uptight
than the FBI.
Mm.
I left that conversation
to you.
Oh, thanks.
♪
Rada.
I was not aware that you were
stationed here in Los Angeles.
Secretary Consul,
two months now.
Rada Rybak, meet Special Agents
Carter Hope, Simone Clark,
and this is
Detective Naomi Voss.
Are you the homeowner,
ma'am?
No, it's Consul General
and his family's mansion.
He sent me
on his behalf.
Um, you, uh...
didn't go inside,
did you?
Naomi: We had to.
Robbery suspects
had assaulted a woman.
We made entry to make sure there
wasn't anyone else in distress.
Yeah, and we found out
that they took
a lot of
the family's property.
Including
a diplomatic pouch.
That's bad.
Which is why the FBI
is already involved.
Any idea of what was in it?
None.
Well, if you knew,
would you tell us?
Diplomatic pouches are
as sovereign as our Consulate.
Belarus business only.
I'm prohibited from sharing.
What about the Consul General?
Would he tell us?
[ Scoffs ] I doubt it.
And he's busy getting ready
for a state dinner.
Still, we need to ask.
It's in both our country's
best interest
to get that pouch
back to you.
And if we know
what's inside of it,
then that'll help us target
where the thieves might try
and sell it, so...
And I'm supposed to trust
that you won't take any pictures
of what's inside
before you hand it over?
Rada, honey,
nobody's trying to play you.
All we want to do
is catch these guys
and get your country's
confidential materials back.
That's all.
I'll see what I can do.
Now,
if you'll excuse me.
Of course.
How do you know her?
Garza: From my
counterintelligence days.
She may be a diplomat right now,
but once a spy, always a spy.
Simone: So we can't trust her?
Trust her?
Simone, that woman
is the second in command
of a consulate for a bleak
and volatile country
that has been at war with itself
since its independence.
With these comrades,
we trust no one.
I appreciate you meeting
with us, Mr. Consul General.
You can appreciate all you want,
but I cannot help you.
Mr. Saroka, we're here
in the interests of diplomacy.
Whatever was
in that pouch
is of great importance
to your country.
So just let us
help you get it back.
Unless there was something
in the pouch
you don't want to disclose.
I confess.
It's nuclear launch codes--
a list of American spies,
and the Holy Grail.
Holy Grail. Yeah.
That's funny.
But, uh, Mr. Consul General,
I can assure you
we are only trying to help you
get your pouch back.
There's no ulterior motives here.
Now I know
you're lying.
You think I haven't been
briefed about you?
I'm no longer
in counterintelligence,
but I respect the suspicion.
Here's my card.
You call if you
change your mind.
And if you don't,
we'll contact you
once the burglars
have been caught
and your property
has been returned.
[ Speaks Russian ]
♪
Nice touch
with the Russian.
You think he's just
being a diplomat,
or is he actually
hiding something?
Both.
[ Buzzer sounds, door opens ]
[ Conversing in Russian ]
Find him!
And find the pouch
before FBI does.
Hey, any luck
tracing that van?
Managed to track it through the
street cameras for half a mile,
but then I lost it in
the Mid-Wilshire dead zone.
But I got enough angles
to create a 3-D rendering
and identify it
as a 2009 Econoline.
System's currently
using a program I created
to match the dents and dings
to other footage of the vehicle
captured within
the last few weeks.
It feels like you want me
to be impressed by this.
Are you?
Only results impress me.
Right?
So, uh, if there's any way
I'm coming up short,
just let me know.
Oh, okay.
You think I've been
holding back?
Your criticism's
usually very...
constructive.
Okay. What--
What is going on with you?
You're even more emo
than usual.
Nothing. Just--
[ Beeping ]
Oh, wait.
What's this?
Oh, my God.
There it is.
Six sightings of the van
in the last three weeks,
four with license plates.
Okay, so if I just type
in the information right here.
There he is.
Owner of the van--
Trip Madsen, 6247 Sycamore,
in Hollywood.
Now I'm impressed.
All right, call in
for a telephonic warrant.
[ Tense music plays ]
♪
[ Knock on door ]
FBI, open up!
We have a warrant!
♪
Simone: Check it out.
Naomi: Looks like the stuff
they stole this morning.
No diplomatic pouch.
[ Screaming ]
Laura: What the--
Okay, we'll take the roof.
You cover the street.
♪
[ Clattering ]
What was that?
♪
[ Glass breaks ]
That way.
Go, go, go.
♪
He must have
jumped down there.
Simone,
suspect's on the loose,
most likely escaping through
the building to our east.
♪
Simone:
No suspects in sight.
[ Breathing heavily ]
We got two on the ground
and I can identify one
as the van driver.
Nothing personal,
but next time you invite me
to breakfast,
I'm saying no.
No sign
of the diplomatic pouch.
Killers must have
taken it with them.
Killers, plural?
No way one person could get
two people off the roof
against their will,
even at gunpoint.
And look, this looks
like a mini photo studio.
Probably to take pics
of the stuff
they steal to sell online.
Maybe they took photos
of what was in the pouch
before they killed them.
But I don't see any cameras.
The photos must be
on their phones.
Let's pray they survived
the eight-story fall.
Reach out to Nazar.
Tell him we tracked down
the diplomatic pouch.
We're back in business,
but we have to work fast.
[ Conversing in Russian ]
[ Snaps fingers ]
What the hell
are you doing?
Give it to me.
Let go of me.
I'll tell my father
to have you killed.
Don't. Don't.
♪
Are you insane?
They love me in Belarus.
Why am I not surprised?
I mean, "Vampire Cop"
was number one there for--
All right, did you get either
of these phones to work or what?
Uh, no, not yet.
Yeah, Brendon
was just telling me
how popular he is
in Belarus.
Why am I not surprised?
[ Beeping ]
Oh, here we go.
Uh, most of the files
are corrupted,
except for
recent photos.
Oh,
they seem like fun.
Wait, wait.
Hang on, hang on.
There it is.
Simone:
Those are currency plates.
Brendon:
For a $20 bill.
[ Sighs ]
[ Viktar
speaking Russian ]
How are you
so epically stupid?
Dad...
[ Mumbles ]
I'm walking
a razor's edge.
There are those back home who
think I'm not hardline enough.
They're sharpening
their knives,
hoping for me
to slip up.
They even put an enemy
in beside me.
And you...
my own son,
you constantly enlarge
the target on my back.
I'm trying to help the family,
not hurt it.
I don't understand
why you don't have
this Boogeyman
put Rada in the ocean.
Enough.
Whatever
you're up to stops.
And if not, I'll send you
to join the infantry in Vitebsk!
Understood?!
The good news is the plates
are counterfeit,
but they are
damn fine ones.
How can you tell?
You see that little hint
of green right there
in the metal's coloring?
That's copper.
U.S. currency plates--
zero copper.
Why would you smuggle a plate
into the United States?
Wouldn't it be safer to bang out
$20 bills in Belarus?
Actually, Belarus is known
for going medieval on criminals.
Los Angeles is the world's
capital for forging.
They will get much
better quality bills here.
There's something
not tracking for me here.
Corruption is rampant in
Belarus-- that's a given.
But counterfeiting
U. S. currency,
that's a fast track
to sanctions and more.
Why would Viktar risk it?
Maybe he's not involved.
I just don't think
we have enough information
to speculate yet.
Where you headed, boss?
To have a clandestine conversation.
♪
Going old school
with that newspaper, hm?
I couldn't resist.
So... out with it.
Why are you here?
[ Sighs ] I told my team
that we couldn't trust you.
But I'm gonna gamble
on the fact
that your ambition
outweighs your loyalty.
And I do have
a sneaking suspicion
that you don't much like being
number two to Viktar Saroka.
No comment.
Let's walk.
We know what's
inside the pouch.
That was fast.
Does that mean you recovered it?
No.
Someone got to it first.
Killed the burglars,
took the pouch.
But we do have photos
of what was inside.
What, are you gonna
make me guess?
Counterfeit plates
for an American $20 bill.
And what is it you want
from me?
Well, at a minimum, insight.
At a maximum,
get us those plates back.
Why would I do any of that
for you?
No. No, no, no,
you wouldn't be doing it for me.
You'd be doing it for you. Mm.
Put your thumb on the scales
of justice, Rada,
and you might just find yourself
becoming the new Consul General.
Oh.
Well, Viktar's too cautious
to do something so stupid.
Focus on Kosta, his son.
That boy is nothing
but trouble.
And Viktar always cleans up
his baby boy's messes.
Yeah, but, Rada, the kid's
got diplomatic immunity.
And there's no guarantee
that I can push the state
to revoke that immunity, so...
Come on, how do we get
these plates back, please?
There's nothing I can do.
No, no, no, Rada,
wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
There's a party tonight,
right, at the Consulate?
The reception. Okay.
Put two names
on the guest list for me.
Viktar will smell
undercover agents a mile away.
I think I have a way
around that.
Garza: Our prime suspect
is Kosta Saroka.
He's the 23-year-old son
of the Consul General,
and he's been in the U. S.
with his father
for the last three years.
He's taken complete advantage
of his diplomatic immunity.
He was arrested five times--
assault, drugs, theft.
Yeah, but he's walked away
every time.
This kid has got
to feel invincible.
For our purposes,
he basically is.
The only way
we can arrest him
is if Belarus revokes
his immunity,
which is a big lift.
And that's why
our first priority
is to recover
these currency plates.
Now, Senator Smith
has pulled some strings
at the State Department
and got us approved
to conduct
a black bag operation.
Inside
the Belarus Consulate?
Brendon and Laura are going in.
No, I can't--
I can't do that.
I'm too famous in Belarus
to go undercover.
Exactly. Which is why you will
be going in as yourself.
Ooh.
Yeah, that's right.
A paid public appearance
at tonight's Consulate reception
by none other than
the Vampire Cop himself
organized by his publicist,
Bibby Baxter.
[ Laughs ]
That sounds like an alias
for a Marvel superhero.
Next time you got to let me come
up with the undercover names,
because you do not d--
do it well, sir.
[ Clears throat ]
While Brendon steals
all the focus,
Laura, you are gonna
find your way
into the Consul General's
office,
where most likely
these plates are locked
in a safe behind his desk.
Oh, ha, that's great.
But my safe-cracking skills
leave a little to be desired.
Then it's a good thing
I already have the entry code.
That is next-level smooth, boss.
Smooth or not, this is not
a normal undercover op.
Brendon and Laura will be
on sovereign territory.
If they get in trouble,
we won't be able to
just bust in
and save them.
Speak for yourself.
If anything happens
to my boy,
you already know
I'm going full mama bear.
Huh.
[ Clears throat ]
Yeah, you got it worse.
What's that supposed
to mean?
Garza: Never mind.
Laura, Brendon,
go get your glam on.
Carter, fire up
the surveillance van.
This party starts
in an hour.
♪
Simone, a word?
Yeah, what's up?
I heard that Brendon was going
undercover at a party.
Oh, girl,
don't worry about that.
I'm gonna be in a van
right outside.
It's not his safety
I'm worried about.
It's his sobriety.
What?
Did you know his sponsor
fell on a wagon?
Off the wagon.
And no, he didn't tell me.
You're closest to him.
Say no more.
I'm on it.
Good looking out.
Thank you.
Simone: Damn, B.
You going to catch
a crook or a date?
'Cause you fine.
You see it.
Yes, I do.
Hmm.
You sure you're up for it?
Yeah.
Laura's got to do
all the hard work.
I just got to show up,
be me--
Well, old me.
Well, the old you used to drink
at parties like this.
It could get uncomfortable.
Yeah, I've been to plenty
of bars sober, you know?
Remember back
at Quantico?
Used to go drinking
with the NATs?
Oh, yeah.
And you would hold on
to one drink all night
until I would always
"accidentally" spill it on you
so you didn't
have to take a sip.
Mm-hmm.
The difference is,
I won't be there.
[ Sighs ] Antoinette
told you about Randy?
Mm. Why didn't you?
You got enough on your plate.
It's-- It's fine.
Don't do that.
Do what?
I always have time
for you.
I know.
I just, you know...
Randy's my guy.
He saved my life.
He told me what to do,
when to do it.
A-And, uh,
had 10 years sober.
You know, if he can go out,
what chance do I have?
Hey,
you got to tell Garza
and be pulled from
the assignment.
I mean, nothing is more
important than your sobriety.
Nothing.
We're rookies.
We've got to prove ourselves
every day.
T-There can't be part
of my job I can't do.
Come on, I-I'll make it work.
I always do.
All right.
All right?
But I will be
in your ear,
and I will be that angel
on your shoulder.
That'll be a first.
[ Laughs ]
I do have a little devil in me,
don't I?
You good?
Yeah.
♪
Love you.
All right.
♪
♪ So articulated down 5th Ave,
got it gon' on ♪
Sassy, classy, jazzy girl ♪
Laura: We're in.
Eyes on Viktar.
No sign of the kid yet.
Oh.
Oh, no. Thank you.
[ Clears throat ]
I've seen
a few heads turn,
but I'm not really getting
the, uh, Belarus love.
Stoker Ramsey?
Vampire Cop?
Bozhe moy, it is him.
Oh, hi.
"You can't kill
what's already dead."
I'm your biggest fan,
Mr. Acres.
Brendon, please.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
Is this
your girlfriend?
No. Uh, no, publicist.
Bibby Baxter.
[ Snickers ]
Oh.
Why are you here?
Paid appearance.
Oh.
Brendon: Right.
How much to take him
home with us afterwards?
Dang.
These Belarusians are thirsty.
Are you tired already?
Don't worry about me.
As your training agent,
one of my jobs is to make sure
you're fit for duty.
Self-care matters.
Carter, I appreciate
the concern,
but nobody is more
about "the me" than me.
I'm good.
Good to know.
We are young, we are free ♪
Laura:
One, two, three.
Yes. Really nice.
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
All right.
Thank you, ladies.
So, uh, what is your
favorite part of the show?
The-- The romance,
the action?
Your body.
We used
to have watch parties
and take a "blood shot"
every time you said
"crime sucks."
We should do one now.
Da.
Oh, uh, what's a--
what's a "blood shot"?
Krambambula.
Red wine and vodka.
Everybody must
take a blood shot.
Ain't nothing stopping us ♪
From doing what we want ♪
[ Whispers ]
You got this, B.
♪ Throw you hands up
'cause it's time ♪
All right.
[ Exhales deeply ]
Crime sucks.
[ Squeals softly ]
Mm.
Mmm.
Ooh.
Ahh.
Wow-ee. Mmm.
Mmm. That was so good. Mm.
My father
has no vision.
Never has.
Oh, I could do
so much for this family.
Oh, hello, boys.
Rada.
You enjoying yourself?
Always. [ Chuckles ]
What are you
smiling about?
Just boys
who play at being men.
We are free ♪
The choice is ours to make ♪
Today is gone ♪
Let me see that picture.
I'm heading in now.
Mm-hmm.
Anya: Another one?
Uh, yeah, line 'em up.
Da!
[ Tense music plays ]
I'm in.
♪
[ Sighs ]
Okay.
[ Safe beeping ]
♪
I've got eyes
on the plates.
♪
[ Gasps ]
Together: Crime sucks!
[ Laughter ]
You know what else
sucks?
Having a tiny bladder.
I'll-- I'll be right back, okay?
Just give me one second.
What is going on
with Laura?
Carter:
We lost contact with her.
Brendon, go to Viktar's office
and check on her right now.
Got it.
♪
Safe is open.
There's no sign
of Laura anywhere.
[ Laura grunting ]
Hey, Laura, are you okay?
Mm.
Here. [ Grunts ]
I gotcha.
They ambushed me,
knocked me out
before I could see
a face.
And they took the plates.
Ow.
[ Door open ]
Viktar: What are you doing
in my office?
Hi. Uh, this is a--
this is a misunderstanding.
Oh, is it?
We have a soundproof
room downstairs
where we work out
these misunderstandings.
We got to get 'em
out of there!
You can't go in there.
Watch me.
Garza: Simone, stand down.
But--
Laura,
tell the Consul General
to answer his phone.
Sir,
your phone is gonna ring.
You should answer it.
What?
Your phone, sir.
[ Cellphone buzzing ]
Hello?
Who is this?
Matthew Garza, FBI.
And these two
belong to you.
Yes, and I want
them back right now. Sure.
After I hold a press conference
about your FBI
committing an illegal break-in
into my Consulate.
Fine, and then I'll hold
my own press conference
detailing a Belarus conspiracy
to devalue the U. S. dollar
by using counterfeits.
You tell me,
Consul General,
who wins that press war?
They're gonna walk out
the front door, Viktar.
♪
Escort them out.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Sighs ]
♪
Antoinette:
It's a lovely dress.
Which I would like
for you to burn
when you're done
collecting all the DNA
from my attacker
off of it.
No use in keeping
a failure dress.
Hey, we know more now
than we did before, right?
Kosta took
those currency plates.
He left the Consulate.
He was there to steal it,
just like us, so...
So father and son
aren't working together on this.
Maybe Viktar found out
what his son was up to.
Tried to stop him.
We just need to figure out
where Kosta's going to next.
Yeah, well,
I have a BOLO out for him,
so let's see
if we get lucky.
Okay.
Finished.
Can you please rush that?
We need hard evidence
to build this case.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Hey, uh, why'd you tell Simone
about my sponsor?
[ Sighs ]
I was worried about you.
The way
you've been acting...
Are you okay?
I-I wanted to tell her.
And I'm fine.
No, you're not.
Yeah-- [ Sighs ]
Randy's my rock.
You know?
And now he's got less days sober
than I do.
I...
N-Nothing makes sense
right now.
But isn't that
the AA mantra?
"One day at a time."
Except I've done everything
you're not supposed to do
in the first year
of recovery.
I moved, I started a new job,
a new relationship.
And despite all of that,
you're doing great.
Am I?
Maybe I've taken on
too much.
What are you
hinting at?
We shouldn't
talk about it here.
Look, Randy's--
He's taking
a newcomer chip.
I-I really need
to be there.
All right?
Call me later?
Yeah, I'll try.
Ooh.
Homework?
Yeah.
I pulled some files
on the Belarusian government
and counterfeiting.
You've had more than a full day.
You should rest.
I know, but I still want
to study a little bit more.
If you stay ready,
you don't have to get ready.
Good night. Night. Night.
See?
That's called work ethic.
You know how hard
it was to teach her that?
[ Scoffs ]
How you doing?
Fine.
Liar.
That idiot kid
could have killed you.
But he didn't.
Doesn't mean
it wasn't scary as hell.
You know I'm here if you
want to talk about it
or grab a beer
and not talk about it.
Thanks,
but I'm gonna go change.
Let's go, uh, uh, uh, uh ♪
♪ Slide up in that...
with a hellcat ♪
♪ Only hang with bad...
'cause I'm like that ♪
♪ Yeah, they hatin' real bad,
askin' how you do that ♪
[ Volume increases ]
♪ I'll make you pop back
like fa, fa, fa, fa ♪
Switch it up ou brand patek ♪
...fat no doctor for that ♪
♪ Moving fast,
can't even detect me ♪
Hey, baby come over ♪
I'm tryin' to see what's up ♪
[ Horn honking ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Oh, my God.
♪ Pullin' all nighters ♪
You fell asleep driving?
Yep.
You could have
killed yourself.
Or an innocent civilian.
You're right.
Okay, I've just been going
so hard for so long.
I guess it just
caught up with me.
♪ Pullin' all nighters ♪
I never want to be seen
as a liability.
You could never
be seen that way.
♪ Pullin' down our masks,
then ♪
Once I get this vintage body
some rest, I think I'll be fine.
It's more than your body.
You need to rest your mind.
Extra sleep isn't enough.
Simone, at this rate,
you're gonna burn yourself out
in six months.
[ Cutty humming ]
Well... [scoffs]
Oh, good morning,
baby girl.
Good morning.
Now,
who do we have here?
Daddy,
this is my friend Naomi.
Oh, your friend
or your friend friend?
Oh, my God.
[ Laughs ]
Why do you have
to make everything so weird?
No, Daddy,
she is just my friend.
Naomi,
this is my dad, Cutty.
Nice to meet you.
Pleasure. [ Chuckles ]
Well, sorry I can't stay around
and charm you ladies,
but I got my weekly
chess match,
and today,
I is bringing the pain.
Good luck.
I don't need it.
I gotta go, too.
You want a ride?
Nah.
Brendon is gonna swoop me.
Remember what I said.
Got it.
♪ Sugar and spice makes
everything nice ♪
♪ But nice don't make no money ♪
Hey, boss.
Antoinette got
a DNA hit from my dress.
The guy who attacked me
at the embassy was Kosta,
just like we thought.
Finally,
some hard evidence.
But he's still out there
with those counterfeit plates.
Yeah, well, he's either
gonna try to sell them
to a third party,
or he's gonna try to make
himself some funny money, right?
Your printer
is a rock star.
Yeah, and expensive.
It's worth every
counterfeit penny.
What about your father?
Just keep
printing money.
Once I make this
family oligarch rich,
he'll fall in line.
How you doing, B?
Great.
How are you?
[ Laughs ]
I would say "great,"
too,
but then I'd be lying
just as hard as you are.
[ Laughs ]
You want coffee?
No, no, I'm good.
We got to roll, actually.
Boss just texted.
So, Kosta's still in the wind.
He wants us to liaise
with the Secret Service,
see if there's any Russian
or Belarusian printers
who are suspected counterfeiters.
We can skip the, uh,
Secret Service part of it.
Why is that?
Because my dad plays chess
with some Russian guys.
One of them, Anton,
is a former Redfella.
You know, Russian mafia.
Uh-huh.
And, baby, he likes to talk.
Clever.
Do not patronize me, Anton.
Ahh.
Daddy, breaking the clock
is not gonna make it any better.
[ Laughs ] Simone,
what are you doing here?
Can't a girl come watch
her daddy in action?
She can.
But you would not.
And you know better than
to distract the player mid-game.
Well, I didn't come
to distract you.
I came to distract
your opponent.
Hey, Anton.
This is Brendon.
He's an FBI special agent, too. Hey.
Can we chat?
About what?
The circles
you used to run in.
Hey, hey, now, hold on.
Anton is my friend.
You're not about
to interrogate--
It's all right, Cutty.
It's all right.
Let-- Let her go,
let her ask her questions.
[ Grunts ]
[ Speaks Russian ]
We just wanted to talk to you
about some Eastern Bloc folks
who know a thing or two
about counterfeiting.
Yeah, somebody is making
fake $20 bills.
You think you can help us
figure out who it is?
I'll entertain you,
you entertain me, huh?
I beat your father
every week.
Not true.
It's true.
[ Scoffs ]
If you can take his place
and, uh, beat me,
then sure, maybe I can
call some colleagues
and, uh, we'll see
what we can find out.
Game on.
Slide over, Daddy.
Teach this young man
a few things.
You made a big mistake.
Should have asked
for a fresh game.
I'm about to beat your father
in three moves.
Maybe that's true for my dad,
but not for me, comrade.
Let's get it.
Arrogance. I like that.
But do you like this?
♪
Brendon, I was just
thinking about it.
You paid for lunch
last week, remember?
Can I pay you back...
with a check?
Oh, snap.
B, I don't know if we locked
the car when we got out.
You should go... check.
♪
[ Chuckles ]
That's what you call
a panic move.
Now, I'm just gonna sit back
and let the clock run out
so you can realize
how screwed you are.
I resign.
You have a very
special daughter there.
Yeah, I was gonna say annoying, but...
I will say special.
[ Chuckles ]
Gonna make
those phone calls now, Anton?
♪
This feels like
a wild goose chase.
Have faith, Carter.
Mr. Vorovin,
it's the FBI.
It's the FBI, sir.
We just want to talk.
[ Gunshot ]
Get down!
[ Breathing heavily ]
He's reloading.
FBI! Drop it.
We got the plates, Carter.
Carter: Cuff him!
A ton of funny money.
We got you on
counterfeiting and murder.
You won't be able
to charge me.
I have diplomatic immunity.
Maybe we can't charge you,
but we can hold you for
as long as the law will allow.
[ Coughs ]
What about you,
sweet thing?
You don't have
diplomatic immunity.
You want to talk?
Don't tell them anything.
Carter:
Take this guy outside
while we have a little chat
with his friend.
I'm not talking.
You just did.
I'm supposed to play dumb.
You're way too smart
for that.
Would you like
to make a deal?
What does this mean?
A deal?
You tell us the truth, and we
take years off your sentence.
Like how they do
on American TV?
Like "Vampire Cop"?
[ Snickers ]
"Crime sucks."
Yes, "Crime sucks."
I love that show.
In my family, we'd watch
it together in Belarus.
Well, maybe we could
make an introduction
if you tell us
what we need to know.
I mean, the guy who plays
Vampire Cop, he works with us.
My family would be amazed.
Cooperate and you'll
make it back home
to see them again
real soon.
Where is Kosta?
On the hunt.
For what?
A woman from the Consulate.
Rada Rybak?
Yes.
Kosta says she is threat
and must be killed
so Minsk can't replace
his father with her.
[ Tense music plays ]
♪
[ Rustling ]
[ Silenced gunshots ]
♪
[ Siren wails ]
[ Grunts ]
Nice seeing you again.
It hurts. [ Panting ]
I need doctor.
Cowboy up, Kosta.
Ambulance is on its way.
[ Siren wailing ]
You okay?
[ Elevator bell dings ]
[ Sighs ]
You doing your Wednesday
FaceTime dinner with Atlas?
Mm. He's gonna get
an earful tonight.
You still struggling
with what happened?
No.
A little.
I don't know which part's worse,
trying not to be terrified
so you can do your job
or being terrified and
still having to do your job.
Mm.
I mean, they both suck.
[ Exhales deeply ]
You know,
I've been thinking,
and I've come to the fair
conclusion that I was wrong.
Brendon is way more work
as a rookie than Simone.
So, you win. Okay.
What are you talking about?
A-A pity victory?
[ Scoffs ]
Come on.
How fragile do you think I am?
No way.
Simon is clearly
the most challenging rookie
in the history
of rookies.
So you can take the W.
How about this,
they're both equal
pains in the ass?
Mm.
And just think it's only 14
more months of training to go.
♪ Warm December ♪
♪ Bitter July ♪
To the new Consul General for
Belarus in the City of Angels.
♪ No matter the weather,
you'd be ♪
Thank you, Matthew.
♪ By my side ♪
♪ I'm struggling without ♪
I was right, huh?
You've been angling
for Viktar's position.
Of course. Yeah.
I knew Kosta was smuggling
and Viktar was covering for him.
Politically,
my hands were tied
until you and your merry band
of special agents showed up.
Glad we could be
of service.
♪ Warm December ♪
Well, once a spy,
always a spy.
You were always so good
at anticipating
other people's moves.
Not Kosta's.
I can't believe that little
bastard tried to kill me.
Yeah.
You know,
one of the great perks
of my new job
is the connections.
So, um, call me
if you ever need a favor.
I will.
Or if you ever want
to grab dinner sometime.
♪ Are you okay? ♪
See, you are much better
at this than I am
because I did not anticipate
that move.
Well, we have
so much in common.
Well, I've been divorced
three times, too.
I guess people like us are
just not meant to be tied down.
Doesn't mean
we can't have some fun.
♪ That I'm falling apart ♪
♪ I'm over this ♪
Hey.
Is, uh, now a good time?
♪ Just walk all over
my broken mess ♪
Look, um, about last night. Stop.
Before you say anything,
I have something to say.
I'm so sorry for what you're
going through with your sponsor.
But you're not getting off
the hook that easily.
Off the hook?
That stuff you said about
taking on too much,
then implying that dating me
was part of that?
No.
If you want to give up
on us
before we've even really
gotten started,
that's on you.
But no excuses.
Just... end it now.
You don't understand.
When I drank,
I-I-I hurt people.
I know what I've gotten
into with you,
and... I'm willing
to put in the work.
♪
Are you?
♪ That I'm falling apart,
I'm over this ♪
[ Speaks French ]
♪ I'm down, I'm fearing
my own loneliness ♪
[ Knock on door ]
LAPD. Open up.
[ Laughs ]
You know you're wrong
for that.
You're right.
My bad.
Let me make it up to you
with a little gift.
What is it?
Something for you to concentrate
on besides work.
Something that will relax
your body and your mind.
♪ And you just walk all over
my broken mess ♪
Knitting? [ Laughs ]
I know you trippin'.
I'm not.
For real, I tripped
when my cousin in Oakland
turned me on to knitting.
At first,
I was real sus.
Then I made a beanie cap,
and I was like,
"Damn, twisting knots
is very therapeutic."
Who knew?
Well, where do we start?
With your hands.
First we start with a slipknot,
and then we'll cast on.
♪ And I fear this
will come to an end ♪
You all right?
So, you really think
this is gonna keep me
from burning out?
I don't know.
But if it doesn't,
we'll find something that will.
♪ I'm down, I'm fearing
my own loneliness ♪
Okay. All right.
You said we need to cast on.
Right.
And then once
I teach you how to purl,
you'll get into the zone.
[ Laughs ]
Into the zone?
Girl, you got
a lot of layers.
But I'm down.
Let's do it.
♪ And you just walk all over
my broken mess ♪
Tighten it.
- Captions by VITAC--
♪