Everything was actually going
fine until we hit the nuns.
- You assaulted a nun?
- No, no.
The suspect I was chasing...
made a beeline for
a group of nuns.
A gathering...
is it a flock of nuns?
I know it's not a murder
of nuns.
- Ow!
- Sorry.
Tell me the truth.
Do I look like a porcupine?
You don't not look
like a porcupine.
Officer Nolan, focus.
We split up.
I came back with a suspect,
and you came back with
a new hairdo and empty cuffs.
Yes. As I was saying...
Ow... the nuns slowed me down,
allowing the suspect to get away,
jumping over a fence.
How many times have I told you
not to hop a fence
without knowing
what's on the other side?
Enough that I shouldn't
have done it?
- Mm-hmm.
- But he was getting away,
so I just... I just...
I went over.
And landed headfirst
on a cactus.
No, no.
First, I had to get away
from the dog.
The cactus was over
the second fence.
This is really
the lowest point
in my rookie experience,
isn't it?
Hey. I'm looking for
Officer John Nolan?
That's me.
You've been served.
Thanks.
Wait. What?
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh-oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
No. I'd say
this is the lowest point.
♪ I'm gonna win for you,
like I know you want me to do ♪
*THE ROOKIE*
Season 01  Episode 18
Episode Title: "Homefront"
Hey. Heard you're
officially a cop now.
Got hit with
your first lawsuit.
Oh, it's ridiculous.
This guy says I dislocated
his shoulder
pushing past him
in a pursuit.
I-I don't think
I even touched him.
And now he wants fifty thousand
to settle.
Don't take it personally.
Being sued's part of the job.
It's why we're required to have
liability insurance.
Union assign
a lawyer yet?
Yeah.
Some guy named Simon Parks.
You're lucky.
Guy's a legend.
Saved my ass
a couple times.
He's a cranky old S.O.B.,
but he gets the job done.
You've got nothing
to worry about.
What's going on?
IA arrested Jenkins.
The Robbery Homicide
detective?
- Yeah.
- Why?
All right. Grab a seat.
See, look, it's never
a good day
when one of your own
gets arrested.
I'm sure you have questions.
Commander West from IA
is here to answer.
Commander?
Thank you, Sergeant.
After an extensive
investigation,
we found clear evidence
that, ten years ago,
Detective Jenkins
lied on the witness stand.
Because of his lies,
an innocent woman
was convicted of
murder in the first.
She's been in jail
this whole time?
Yes. Samantha Bennett.
She was released two days ago.
In addition to charging Jenkins
with perjury,
we've placed him
on the Brady List.
Uh, what is the Brady List?
Uh, it's a record of
law enforcement officers
who've withheld exculpatory
evidence...
It's a list of dirty cops.
IA has reviewed all
of Jenkins' past convictions.
Of them, three others
were deemed suspect enough
to warrant the release
of those felons.
But you're not sure
those three are innocent.
No, but their convictions
were overturned.
When this gets out,
every lawyer in town
is gonna want to get a Jenkins
conviction overturned.
That's tomorrow's problem.
Today, protocol dictates
that we make voluntary contact
with these released felons.
So, Lopez and West, you will
talk to Samantha Bennett.
Bradford, Chen,
you got Max Kegel,
who was doing 25 to life
for drug trafficking.
And, Bishop and Nolan,
take Terry Wright,
who was in for armed robbery
and attempted murder.
If you observe anything
actionable,
send it up to Major Crimes.
And what if we don't see
anything actionable?
Leave it alone.
Observe, report.
That's it.
All right.
Be safe out there.
Oh. My lawyer's here.
Hmm. You're lucky to be
getting Simon Parks.
He's been doing this
for 40 years.
Can't beat that kind
of experience.
- Officer Nolan?
- Yes?
I thought we should meet before
this afternoon's arbitration.
Go over the game plan, answer
any questions you might have.
Great.
Uh, who are you?
Y-Your lawyer.
Simon Parks Junior.
Oh, I-I thought...
You thought I was my father.
Believe me, I know I have
some big shoes to fill,
but I'm excited to get started
on my first case with you.
The oldest Boot paired
with the youngest lawyer.
Sounds like a match
made in heaven.
Right? Now, as far as your role
in today's mediation goes,
less is more.
They will try to get under
your skin,
so let me do the talking.
And 2:00 is 2:00,
so don't be late.
Right.
Um, let me know if you have
any questions, okay?
Did he say "first case"?
Mm-hmm.
So, you and your mother
finally make up,
and now you're giving me
the cold shoulder?
No. I, um... things have
just been really crazy.
Oh, too crazy to respond to
texts? Return phone calls?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I've just been focused
on the job and the exam.
What I know is that you're
not ready to have a man-to-man
about what's going on
with you,
but I expect you to be
by end of day.
So come find me
when you're ready.
What was that about?
Nothing.
Hey, um, do you remember,
uh, that felon Oscar
from the prison bus crash?
Stole a car, tried to
run us over? That Oscar?
Yeah. Um, when I was
booking him,
he told me some stories
about my dad.
What kind of stories?
That he was my dad's CI
back in the day.
Said that my dad used to
give him intel
in exchange for turning
a blind eye.
Lots of cops do that.
Yeah, he also said
that my dad
planted a gun on him.
Got him sent away
for life.
Let me guess.
Oscar insisted he was innocent.
No. He said he was guilty,
but no one could prove it.
So my dad crossed the line.
I don't believe it.
Your dad is
the straightest
arrow I've ever met...
Besides you.
No, no. I understand.
Okay. Thank you. Bye.
Well, the union says
I can't switch lawyers.
They said, and I quote,
"You get what you get,"
which is exactly
what I said to my son
when he wouldn't eat
his peas.
He's a lawyer, Officer Nolan,
not a fish.
You can't just throw him
back because
you think
he's too small.
Thought I might be seeing police
at some point.
Oh, we're just
checking in on you
after your unexpected
recent release.
What, five years into
a 20-year sentence
for attempted murder
and armed robbery?
It's a miracle.
The man upstairs
looking out for me.
- Huh.
- Mind telling us what you've
been doing since you
got back into town?
Of course.
Moved back in
with my old lady here,
been eating way too much
fast food.
Soon as I get the old van
up and running,
I'm gonna start
looking for work.
Right.
You look familiar.
Are you...
Don't I know you
from somewhere?
With your rap sheet,
I'm sure we've crossed paths.
I used to run with this kid
named Dylan.
I think you know him.
Doesn't ring a bell.
You must have me mixed up
with somebody else.
Okay.
Do yourself a favor,
Mr. Wright.
You've been given
a rare second chance.
Take advantage of it.
Stay out of trouble.
Yes, ma'am.
So what do you think?
That he's gonna be
trouble.
Why all the extra shifts?
Why not? I've got hours to
fill when I'm not studying.
Yeah, but don't you need
time off to recharge?
What do you do to unwind?
Work out. And don't
tell me, "If it has 'work'
in the title,
it can't be relaxing."
It's true.
You need a hobby,
something you do for fun.
No, I don't.
Mr. Kegel, I hear you've
had a bit of bad luck
since you got out of prison.
Tell me about it.
Eight years of prison food
without as much as the runs,
and one bad bowl of clams
lands me in the hospital.
Mr. Kegel, I'm sure that
your recent release
has brought up
some strong emotions.
Only good ones.
Hell, I thought I'd never get
to consummate this marriage.
Alicia and I were,
uh, pen pals.
She wrote to me in prison for
a year before we got hitched.
Huh. I've always wondered about
women marrying guys in prison.
What's the appeal?
Oh, well, I read about his case,
and I saw his photo,
and... I just fell in love.
Look. Now that I'm out,
I plan on keeping my nose clean
and my wife
between the sheets.
Oh.
Officers, uh, may I speak
with you, please?
Sure thing.
I just got Mr. Kegel's
test results,
and, unfortunately,
it's not food poisoning.
What is it?
Poison poisoning.
Hydramethylnon,
to be specific.
It's a chemical used
in roach traps.
Mrs. Kegel, can you
come out here, please?
No.
What's going on?
Who made the clams?
My honey bunny. Why?
'Cause they were poisoned.
Guess your wife wasn't
psyched you came home.
What? Is that true?
You were never supposed
to get out of jail.
That was the whole allure.
Besides, it got my mother off
my back about me being single.
And then you came home,
and you were all...
clammy and handsy,
and I just snapped.
Ma'am, I'm gonna need you
to stand up.
Turn around.
Hands behind your back.
Sorry.
Samantha Bennett
really took it in the teeth.
Ten years for a crime
she didn't commit.
Barely a traffic ticket
before she went inside.
And her file says
she has a kid.
Child was only a year old
when her mom went to prison.
Yeah. There's no way
she comes out the same person.
Prison hardens you.
Where the hell are they?!
Somebody help!
- Where's my family?
- Don't hurt me.
Where are they?
Drop the bat!
No. It's not fair!
Arrest her. She's crazy!
Look, Samantha, please.
Put down the bat.
This isn't gonna help you.
Is that what you want?
You want to help me?
Like you helped me
the ten years in jail?
Like you helped to
convince my husband
that I was a murderer?
You know what it feels like
to have the person that you love
turn against you,
believe you're capable
of the worst thing imaginable?
Ten years, he never once
brought my baby to visit me,
said she was better off
without me.
I know you're upset.
I can only imagine
what you've been through.
But this man doesn't know
where your family is.
Do you?
Of course not!
They moved out years ago.
I just... I just
want to see my baby.
I didn't know where else
to go.
Samantha, you need
to put the bat down.
Please don't send me back there.
- Look, I'm sorry.
- Please.
First arbitration.
You nervous?
A little bit.
What are you gonna do?
Be a cop.
Um...
can I ask you something?
Okay.
Who's Dylan?
What?
The guy that Terry
thought you both knew.
I got a vibe that you
weren't being
- completely straight with him.
- You got the vibe?
What kind of vibe are
you getting right now?
That I've overstepped.
I don't know any Dylan.
End of story.
Good talk.
Turn to...
Okay.
Come on.
I'm never gonna find them.
Look, I'm... I'm sure
someone knows where they are.
She probably hates me anyway.
Your daughter?
I missed her whole life.
The best I can hope is that
Tom told her I was dead.
Otherwise, I'm just
mom the murderer.
Yeah, but you're
innocent, okay?
And that will be all over
the news
now that Jenkins
was arrested.
So is the fact that
I'm back in jail.
No, Tom is right.
She's better off
without me.
I'm no good to anybody now.
Don't say that.
This isn't right.
No, but our hands
are tied.
We have to be able to do
something to help her.
This isn't just about her,
is it?
Yeah.
All right,
and maybe my dad, too.
A dirty cop
ruined her life.
Look,
let me think on Samantha,
see if I can figure
something out.
But you need to get your head
straight about your dad.
Either go talk to him
or let it go.
What you can't do is let
the doubt eat away at you.
- Hey.
How's it going
with Jenkins?
Usual song and dance.
He's crying conspiracy,
coercion,
trying to muddy the waters.
I've been meaning to ask you,
how's my boy doing?
Well, you know.
Standing tall some days,
falling on his face others,
like all rookies before him.
Like us back in the day.
Yeah, but he's been acting
a little strange
the last few weeks.
Standoffish.
Something I should know?
You'd have to ask him.
Tell me about his T.O.
- Officer Lopez?
- Yeah.
She's a good cop.
On paper, sure, but I'm asking
about her instincts,
her leadership skills,
her ability to teach my son
things he can't learn
from his rook book.
Percy, I'm not quite sure
how to reply to that.
See, this is specifically why
I asked you to assign.
Officer Bradford
to my son, not Lopez.
He's a known entity,
a cop's cop.
With her, I'm wondering,
does she truly have
what Jackson needs?
Are you asking as head
of Internal Affairs
or a nervous father
overstepping his bounds?
Listen.
I know you outrank me,
but I'm gonna tell you
exactly what I said
when Jackson was assigned
here... no special favors.
Wa... Wade. I'm not asking
for special favors...
That includes keeping
tabs on him.
Is that understood,
Commander?
It is, Sergeant.
Excuse me.
I was just about
to call you.
Let me guess.
You can't make dinner?
Sorry. One of my clients was put
away by that Brady Cop... Jenkins.
I've got to go back through
the case,
see if anything
shakes loose.
Today must be like Christmas
morning for defense attorneys.
Yeah, except instead
of presents,
we have boxes of discovery
to open.
Um...
Oh.
Listen. Hey.
Yeah. Hi.
I, uh...
Mm-hmm?
I have to go see a client on
Saturday, but I'll be back Sunday.
I'm on duty Sunday.
Right. Well,
uh, nice to see you.
Yeah.
- How are you doing? Good? Yep.
- Mm.
So, I heard you tried
to get me replaced.
Okay. Yes, I did. But you said
this was your very first case.
You have to understand that
would make me a little nervous.
They handed you a gun on your
first day, didn't they?
Yes. And that made me
a little nervous, too.
Look, I grew up
in a courtroom.
I learned every trick
my dad knows.
Passed the Bar first time out
with a near-perfect score.
So trust me when I say,
I got this.
I need you focused on you,
staying calm,
attentive, quiet.
Can you do that?
Absolutely.
- Great.
- Yeah.
But just so you know,
I got a couple of years
of Pre-Law under my belt.
I've gone to small claims court
a number of times
to get paid for jobs,
so if you need anything...
I appreciate that,
but lawyering is my job.
Oh, absolutely.
100 percent.
But I've got your back
if you need it.
- I won't.
- Right.
But if you do...
I won't.
You're late.
Apologies, Your Honor.
Sorry. My fault.
I was on patrol.
And I was getting my prostate
squared away.
Still got here on time.
Yes, sir.
Sorry again.
Really? A neck brace?
This happened a month ago.
Officer Nolan, please don't
interact with the plaintiff.
It's called emotional whiplash.
My doctor says it's from
having to relive the incident
over and over again
the past few days.
That's not a real thing.
We need to get a medical expert
in here to swear under oath...
What did I say about
letting me do my job?
Hey, counsel... can we get
this circus started?
Yes, sir. Sorry.
Simon Parks for the defendant.
Jephson Green for the plaintiff,
Your Honor.
It seems you did a little
reckless running on the job,
Officer Nolan.
Your Honor, I was in pursuit
of a wanted felon...
Did that sound like
a question?
You think this is gonna
be easy, don't ya?
Just waltz in here,
charm the pants off of me
with your uniform
and your dimples.
- No, sir.
- I have the power...
to give this man your pension.
Uh, Your Honor, if I may,
we have Officer Nolan's
body cam footage,
if you'll allow us
to play it.
Sure. Sounds fun.
Great.
Oof.
There.
Can we just say case closed?
Seriously...
Should we switch seats?
Do you want to do my job? Would
you let me handle this, please?
All right.
This is the fourth time
that Mr. Lynch
has brought suit against
a police officer.
Prior history, Your Honor,
is just that... history.
It has no bearing on the fact
that Officer Nolan
assaulted my client, causing him
lasting physical injury.
And only Your Honor has
the power to make this right.
Well said.
Forget it.
Dylan, wait.
We need to talk.
Oh, do we, now?
After all these years,
that's how you want
to play this.
Please?
Look, one of your former
running buddies
just got out of Folsom.
Terry Wright.
Have you heard from him?
Seriously, Talia?
You came all the way down here
to ask me about some guy
from the neighborhood
I knew 15 years ago.
Cut the crap. You and Terry
got a lot tighter after I left.
You think I didn't
know that?
Oh, I see.
So you too good
to stay in touch,
but you can keep tabs on me,
stay all up in my business.
I am trying to
look out for you.
You're suspected of pulling
at least five jobs with Terry.
You're lucky you only
got caught once.
You got a lot of nerve
calling me "lucky."
Hey, I never asked to be
taken to another family.
Yeah, but you sure as hell
couldn't wait
to get up out of there.
And can you blame me?
That home was a nightmare.
I would've taken you with me
if I could have.
Yeah, well, it's cool.
Yeah, I took care of myself.
Got clean, got straight.
Been working a warehouse job
for about a year now.
So I got no need for you,
and I ain't got no need
for Terry.
I got to go to work.
Dylan, I...
I ju...
I... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I haven't
been around.
I had to step away
when I joined the police.
Yeah, you were embarrassed.
I get it.
No!
Because a family connection
to a criminal
would have kept me
off the force.
And if they find out now
that I lied
and I left you
off of my personal history,
I could lose my job.
Well, no worries.
I don't know you anyway.
Your Honor, I'd like to submit
some crucial evidence
we've recently received.
Another video
of the assault.
Your Honor, any evidence
should have been provided
during discovery.
Whoa!
Things just got real.
This video just came
to my attention,
and after viewing it,
you'll understand why
we've upped our financial demand
to $50,000.
You can go ahead and up it
to $100 million. I don't care.
I'm not paying it because
I didn't do anything wrong.
No, no. Of course you didn't.
No cop ever does anything wrong.
Will the plaintiff
please refrain from
addressing
my client directly?
Enough.
I love a dramatic turn.
Let's watch.
Now, this is all about
perspective,
and from this perspective,
you can clearly see.
Officer Nolan knock
my client to the ground.
Okay. Wait. It's... uh,
clearly from this angle,
it looks egregious,
but...
Egregious? I'd say it looks
like you deserve a flag
for roughing the pedestrian.
Your Honor, can we take
a brief recess?
Make it quick.
This is crazy.
I didn't do anything wrong.
It doesn't matter. We've got
an unpredictable judge,
and that video just made
our case more difficult,
so I really need you to sit back
and let me do my job. Got it?
Got it.
Come on.
Go ahead.
Have a seat on the bench.
Don't I get a lawyer?
Did you want a lawyer?
Yeah.
But you took all my money.
Yeah, it was stolen money.
You know, it doesn't matter,
because your lawyer
would be pro bono.
Free.
I've got just the guy
for you.
- Mr. Camel.
- It's just "Camel."
You know, like Beyoncé
or Post Malone.
All right.
Let's start somewhere simple.
Why is there marker
on your face?
So Petey wouldn't know
it was me.
That's Peter DiAmato,
the cashier at the convenience
store you robbed.
Robbery? Wait a minute.
My client was wielding
a squirt gun...
Hardly qualifies as
a "threat of force."
It looked real.
It... It had Hawaiian Punch
in it,
which he drank repeatedly
during the alleged incident.
And the theft of $20
from the register?
Petey owed me that money.
Sounds like a harmless prank,
misunderstanding
between friends.
Prank, huh?
Well, comedy is subjective.
Who keeps rubbing my foot?
All right.
Say I let him walk.
What do I get?
I've got 15 minutes.
Don't worry.
I'm good under pressure.
Oh, good.
Bishop?
Why are you digging into known
associates of Terry Wright?
When we stopped by for
the field interview,
I got a strong sense
that he's up to something.
See, look. This station's
under a microscope.
The last thing I need
is one of my officers
getting slapped with
a harassment complaint.
If you have something real,
great.
Send it to Metro.
Otherwise, get back
on the street.
Yes, sir.
7-Adam-15,
assault in progress.
Rustic Ranch Paintball.
Hey, Officer, over here.
Over here.
He's totally
lost his mind.
- Who?
- Jimmy.
He lives for paintball,
but he takes it
way too seriously.
Carl snuck up behind him
and scored,
and then Jimmy freaked out
and started attacking...
Okay. Slow down.
Who's Jimmy? Who's Carl?
That's Carl.
Whoa. Um...
did you call an ambulance?
Yeah, yeah.
They're on the way.
Okay.
Keep pressure on it.
Whatever you do,
don't pull it out.
Where's this other guy,
Jimmy?
Well, he's out there
playing somewhere.
How can we ID him?
Uh, he's about 6' tall,
he's got a camo jacket,
and a skeleton face guard.
All right. You stay here
and wait for the ambulance.
It's scary what happens when
a man focuses on one thing only.
It's a cautionary tale,
really.
Shut it, Boot.
Yes, sir.
All the new video does is show
us why magic tricks work.
The magician doesn't really
saw the woman in half,
and Officer Nolan didn't really
knock Mr. Lynch to the ground.
So the only
reasonable outcome here
is to dismiss this case
with prejudice,
citing Salsbury, Ritter,
and Bennett v. Long Beach.
Well put, young man.
This...
This isn't right.
My pain is real.
Time after time,
police have gotten away
with their crimes against me.
My dog was run over
in a high-speed chase,
and my door was kicked in
by cops serving a warrant
on the wrong address.
And not one officer has had
the decency to just say,
"I'm sorry."
Is this why you're suing me?
Because no one's ever
apologized to you?
Officer Nolan...
Let me be the first.
I'm sorry that you got hurt.
Off...
Well, Your Honor,
in light of the defendant's
admission of guilt...
What?
...the plaintiff ups our
financial demand to $100,000.
Wait.
Your Honor,
we need
a 15-minute recess.
Yeah, you do.
Man, this would be
a whole lot easier
if everyone
wasn't wearing camo.
This job isn't about
easy, Boot.
Have you ever done this?
Played paintball?
No. It's amateur hour.
I'd straight up
murder these guys.
- Okay.
- That's him, that's him!
Exhibit A.
She thinks approaching
from the rear
gives her a tactical advantage.
But in reality, had she
taken the superior position
of the high ground
to the north...
Oh!
...that wouldn't
have happened.
Oh.
But we know Jimmy's
not your average player.
This game is his life.
So where would he go?
Hmm. Somewhere with
a protected view of the course?
Huh. High ground.
LAPD!
Anyone else fires,
they're going to jail.
- Okay. Sorry.
- Guys, guns down.
Guy in the skeleton mask?
Behind you!
Jimmy!
Commander.
About before.
I was out of line.
It's hard having a cop
for a son,
especially when you know
what this job can do to him.
All good.
Water under the bridge.
Good.
Have a good day.
Something else?
You didn't hear this
from me, okay?
Make sure they can bounce
a quarter off your bunk.
- You hear me?
- What do you mean by that?
Detective Jenkins,
this Brady List business...
It isn't going away
anytime soon.
The police commission
is stepping in.
We're talking review boards
and independent audits.
It could get ugly, Wade,
so double-check your officers.
Leave nothing to chance.
Make sure nothing can
blow back on you.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Come on, Dylan.
Prove me wrong.
You done?
No.
Just wanted to let you know
there's no rush
getting back here.
Thanks for the update.
What are you up to?
Getting my nails done.
That's a joke, right?
Look, did you actually
want something
or you just called
to say hi?
I think I'm gonna lose.
It doesn't mean
you did anything wrong.
Crap.
Nolan, I got to go.
What's going on?
You okay?
Everything's fine.
Good luck with
your arbitration.
These two stay.
This one goes.
You, uh, got a minute?
Sure.
You ready to tell me
what's going on?
Come on.
You can talk to me.
Always.
Lopez and I, um...
we arrested a man named
Oscar Hutchinson.
He told me stories
about you and him.
And, um...
And what?
He said you were dirty.
And you believe the word
of a convicted felon,
a murderer,
over your own father?
No. No. I, um... I just...
I-I pulled the file.
You did what?
Boy, have you lost
your damn mind?!
I'm not a boy.
I'm a police officer...
Well, not for long, if you
don't get your head straight.
Remember, you're not just
accusing your father here,
you're accusing a superior.
Yes, sir.
Oscar Hutchinson
is a habitual liar
with a history
of substance abuse,
not to mention
a personal grudge against me.
You think there's a court
in this country
that would find
his testimony credible?
Look, I don't give a damn
if it would stand up in court.
I want to know if it's true.
Of course not!
And today of all days,
you throw this in my face?!
Get out of my sight.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
I need a premise history
on 11215 South 73rd Street.
Copy. Stand by.
Okay. Lots of 11-3
at that address.
I'm getting a hazard code,
as well.
7-Adam-15, show me
on a felony ped stop
in the alley beside
the South 73rd address.
I think they're about
to rob a stash house.
Two at gunpoint.
Send backup.
Police!
Drop the weapons!
Three steps forward.
On your knees.
I told you not to run
with this fool.
I knew you looked familiar.
Talia Bishop,
the prodigal sister.
And you led her right here.
Thought I taught you better.
You should have taken
that second chance, Terry.
Now you're going
back to prison.
I don't think so.
Holster your weapon.
Take off the belt.
Get it from her.
You shouldn't have
followed me here.
I should have just let you rob
a stash house and get killed?
Yo. What do you want
to do with her?
She probably already
called for backup.
We better rob
this place fast.
Stick her in the van.
Make sure she's secure.
Let's go.
Dylan, you don't have to
do this. Don't do this.
Don't do this.
Dylan, it's not too late!
Dylan!
TeGo, go, go, go, go!
Where's Maurice?
Dead. Hold on.
He needs to go
to a hospital.
Yeah, that's not happening.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm hit pretty bad, man.
He could bleed out.
If you care about him,
take him to the hospital.
You can just dump him out.
We're not going to any damn
hospital. Shut the hell up.
However I rule,
it's clear to me
that Officer Nolan has a lot to
learn about the job of policing.
I have to take this.
Like hell you do. You...
Yes, sir?
Bishop's missing.
She called for backup.
When units arrived,
they found her car
outside a stash house,
bodies inside.
Officer,
hang up that phone!
Have you heard from her?
No.
Get back here.
Yes, sir. On my way.
Officer Nolan,
we're not done here.
I am.
Do whatever you need to do.
Make it $1,000, $100,000,
$100 million.
I don't care.
My T.O.'s in trouble.
Dylan,
grab that sweatshirt.
Tie it around your arm...
Above the wound.
You got
to stop the bleeding.
What's the plan?
I'm working on it.
Man, Maurice is dead.
We're riding around this van
with a kidnapped cop.
What kind of plan
fixes this?
One that includes
killing me.
Shut up!
He's not gonna hurt you.
Where do you think
we're driving to?
Quiet place where
he can execute a cop.
Isn't that right, Terry?!
We're not killing her.
Just relax, Dylan.
I know what to do.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Uncuff her from the van.
Look, whatever happens next,
Dylan, I am sorry.
Even though I couldn't
keep you in my life,
I still kept my eye on you.
I saw you turn
your life around.
I know I let you down.
But this... this is...
This isn't you.
You are so much better
than this thug.
Don't listen to her.
Who taught you
how to be a man,
how to hustle, how to
survive on these streets?
I'm the closest thing to
family you've ever had.
She doesn't deserve tears.
Turn around.
You shouldn't have to see this.
No. Come on. Let's...
Let's just leave her.
Let's just get the hell
out of here.
We can't do that.
Just turn around.
Dylan, I love you.
I'm sorry!
Get on your knees.
Man, I'm not
getting on my knees.
You gonna shoot me,
you gonna look me in my face
when you do it.
Dylan, Dylan,
look at me.
Breathe. Breathe.
It's okay.
Come uncuff me.
Come on. Uncuff me.
What did I do?
You saved me.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry,
but I gotta take you in.
I just saved your life.
Save mine.
That's what I'm
trying to do!
Look, I'll go to Mexico.
I'll be gone by the morning.
I swear, you'll never
hear from me again!
You know I can't.
I can... I can keep
your secret.
Yeah, w-with Terry dead,
no one else knows.
It's perfect...
That doesn't matter anymore.
Control,
this is Officer Bishop.
I'm in Baldwin Hills
oil field.
I have one in custody,
one deceased.
Please send additional units,
an RA, and a supervisor.
Hey.
I was looking for you.
You okay?
I... yeah.
Why didn't you tell me
you were into something?
I would have
been there for you.
You had your own life
to deal with.
Yeah, well, I hate
to break it to you,
but you're a pretty big
part of that these days.
Lucky you.
Yes. I am lucky.
Look, I don't know what's
going on with you,
and I don't know who this
Dylan guy you arrested is.
All I know is there's
got to be a reason
you're playing it
close to the vest.
And I respect that.
But take it from a guy
who bottled things up
for too many years.
It helps to talk about it.
You're right.
I do need to talk.
But not to you.
Come in.
Sir, I have something
to tell you.
What is it?
Dylan Scott is my brother.
Come again?
We spent a year together
in the same foster home,
a year that felt like
a lifetime.
I wouldn't have made it
one day without him.
Bishop. Where are you
going with this?
I left him off of my P.H.Q.
when I applied to the academy
because of his
criminal record.
I pretended like
he didn't exist,
and that was a mistake.
It doesn't matter we only
spent a year together.
He's family.
If this was any other day,
I might have the energy
to chew you out
or figure out how to help.
But today...
Today, my hands are tied.
So I have to file
a memorandum with the Chief,
informing him that one
of my best officers
perjured herself on
an official document,
likely torpedoing
her career.
You're dismissed.
We need to talk.
I'm off-duty, Commander.
Maybe another time.
Jackson, please.
So I've been doing a lot
of apologizing today.
I'm not used to that.
I'm not really
good at it either.
Was that your way
of saying sorry?
No, no.
This is. I'm sorry.
Why?
You swore that
you weren't dirty.
And I wasn't.
Look,
you have to understand,
when I was coming up
in the force,
it was a different time.
Two weeks to match fingerprints,
if you were lucky.
And forget about
DNA evidence.
We cut corners sometimes
because we had to.
My whole life, you drilled me
to follow every single rule
to the letter.
And now it's, "Oh, yeah,
we cut corners
'cause we had to."
Who the hell do you
think you are?
Your father.
Not the one that
I thought you were.
Look, I don't know what
Oscar told you
or what you think
I might have done,
but I swear to you,
I wasn't dirty.
I knew plenty who were,
but that wasn't me.
I never falsified evidence.
Never took money.
Never flaked a guy
to make a collar.
You have to believe me.
No, Dad. I don't.
Jackson, please.
All I ever wanted was for you
to be better than I was.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Not really.
I'm sorry, but maybe
this will cheer you up.
Come on.
I spoke to the building super
about Samantha,
told him everything
she'd gone through.
So he agreed to withdraw
his complaint.
- She's free to go.
- That's great.
There's more.
Mrs. Bennett?
Can we get a minute?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I found your husband.
I explained to him
what happened,
that you were innocent.
It was a lot to process.
Before you get your hopes up,
he doesn't want you
to know where he
or your daughter are
just yet.
But I gave him this number,
and I think he'll call once he
wraps his head around the truth.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♪ But I put them
in the shadows at last ♪
♪ Oh, I've looked up and down
and crossed the sea ♪
So what did they end up at?
$100,000?
Nope.
Back down to $50,000?
No.
The judge tossed it.
What? How?!
Oh, when you ran
out of there,
only concerned with
your T.O.'s safety,
I was able to use it
as an example
of your selfless dedication
to the job.
The judge was impressed.
Wow!
Nicely done.
Hey, thanks. I told you
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah, you did.
And I, for one, should
know better than to judge
someone on their age
or their experience.
So I'm sorry.
And... thank you very much.
♪ ...searching ♪
Hey, you know this lawsuit
wasn't really about you, right?
It was about the uniform.
Get used to it.
Hey, I'm a lawyer.
Everybody hates us, right?
No. No.
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
You ready, Boot?
Remember. No mercy.
- Got it.
- ♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
You're having fun,
aren't you?
No.
On me.
- ♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
- Go!
♪ I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready now ♪
Synchronized  by  srjanapala
- ♪ I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready now ♪
- Incoming!