You left your foster brother,
a known felon,
off your PHQ.
I have a lot to be sorry for.
And I am.
I need someone here
to be my eyes and ears.
You want me to be a rat
for Internal Affairs?
- Who the hell do you think you are?
- Your father.
Not the one that
I thought you were.
- We can cut him off in the plaza.
- Wait!
Brake!
When I pushed
to be something I'm not,
I almost got someone
killed.
The least impressive thing
about you
is you're dating
a 45-year-old rookie.
What's wrong with that?
Until I administer
the oral exam,
get the hell
out of my office.
What's a 314?
Uh, indecent exposure.
Nice. A 273g?
Being intoxicated
in the presence of a child.
Well done.
Reminds me of a funny story.
- Mm, mm-hmm, uh-huh.
- Which is for later.
- How about a 237?
- False imprisonment.
Nicely done, and a personal
favorite of mine... a 597h.
Unlawfully attaching
a propeller to an animal
so that dogs
may chase it.
Well done. That's 500 penal
codes down, 1,000 to go.
- Curly fries?
- Yes. - Definitely.
Money. Now.
211, armed robbery.
488, petty theft.
- You a cop?
- Yes, I am. And so are they.
Hands in the air.
Drop your guns.
- Turn around.
You guys, this looks to me like
a criminal conspiracy.
You mean a 182.
Also a 12-0-20.
Oh, illegal possession
of a firearm.
Actually, it's a 417.
The guns are fake.
Ha!
He's right!
Yep, but this knife's real,
and that's a violation of...
- 21510 B.
- ♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- Turn around.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you ♪
♪ Like I know you want me to do ♪
*THE ROOKIE*
Season 01  Episode 20
Episode Title: "Free Fall"
You are trouble.
Why is that?
'Cause I'm supposed to be
focused on this test,
and all I can... think about...
Oh, my God... is you.
And now you're gonna be
moving here full time.
Yeah, well, that job
at Homeland Security
was too good to pass up.
Plus, decent benefits.
Oh.
- Oh.
Come house hunting with me
this weekend.
Yeah, sounds fun.
I'd love to.
Oh, uh, Henry's flying in.
You two can finally meet.
Is that too soon?
I'm sorry. I have no idea
the single dad rules yet.
No, no.
It's... It's fine.
Um...
I'd... I'd...
I'd like to meet him.
- Great.
- Yeah, good.
Okay. I gotta go.
You are gonna do great
on your test.
- Thank you.
- Okay?
Officer Bishop.
Glad you called.
I was worried
you were ignoring me.
No, ma'am.
I was just weighing my options.
And?
You promise I'll be cleared
by the Chief
if I spy on
my fellow officers?
Don't look at it
as spying.
You're helping me monitor cops
who cross the line.
Like the line
you're crossing with me.
Violating the Peace Officers
Bill of Rights.
What are you doing?
I thought hard
about your offer,
but I decided to go
a different way.
By calling your boss.
Sir, I can explain.
You can try.
But I recommend
you do it
after consulting
your union lawyer.
I've spoken
to the Chief.
Your case has been closed,
Officer Bishop.
A formal letter of reprimand
will be placed in your file.
My apologies for Officer Ruiz's
rogue actions.
Let's go.
Letter of reprimand...
Fair resolution.
Should be grateful.
I am.
Good.
80 might be
the passing grade, Boot,
but if you don't get
at least a 90,
you should turn in your badge
on general principle.
Officer Chen, I will take it
as a personal insult
- if you get anything less than a 93.
- Yes, sir.
Have you figured out
what you're gonna do
with all your new
free time?
Might I suggest
a book club?
What are you
talking about?
You know, after I pass,
there won't be any more
daily evaluations to write.
Whether I evaluate you
daily or weekly,
I will continue to judge you
every minute.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
So, all right.
Big day ahead.
Rookies will work the first six
hours of their shift on patrol,
then come back
to take the written test.
Hey, try not to tire them out
this morning.
Just take
the easy calls, okay?
I don't do easy.
But you do follow
direct orders,
am I right,
Officer Bradford?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Easy, then.
Following
the written exam,
you three will report
to the Chief's office,
where he will personally
administer the oral exam.
Remember, he can fail you for
a dozen different reasons, so...
Remind me, Officer Nolan,
how the Chief feels about you.
Oh, big fan, sir.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
All right, see you three
back here in six hours.
All right, that's it.
You're driving today,
Officer West.
I am? Why?
'Cause we both know
you're gonna pass the exam.
I mean, I feel
pretty good, but...
The rules and regulations of
the LAPD are part of your DNA.
You're right.
Test's in the bag.
Which means I have today
to decide whether
to request you be assigned
to a new training officer.
What? Why?
Because I feel like
I failed you.
You were a mess
right out of the gate.
And I thought
I got you past it.
But then you lost it again
last week.
So either you're falling down
or I am.
What happened last week
was my fault.
I let my family drama
get in the way, and...
- it won't happen again.
- It's not good enough.
You shouldn't still
be struggling with
the most basic question...
"Why am I here?"
Why do you want to be a cop,
Officer West?
Because I've always
wanted to be one.
Being groomed for this
isn't the same as choosing it.
You gotta want this job
for the right reason.
For you,
not your father.
So, why did you
choose it?
I have
four older brothers.
Guess it gave me
a pathological need
to stand up
for the little guy.
Which is why I was also
willing to dig deep with you.
But maybe I've given you
too much leash.
Maybe you need
a different instructor
to get your head on
straight.
I don't want
a different instructor.
Look, just tell me
what I have to do.
You never got
a real Plain Clothes Day.
So this morning
you're gonna run things.
Then we'll see
what happens.
7-Adam-19,
silent hold-up alarm
activated at Madame Megan's
Psychic Shop.
2417 Vine.
Code 3.
Tell me!
Tell me right now!
How the hell
did you know?!
Answer me!
Police.
Drop the snow globe.
That's a $900
crystal ball.
Can he just
put it down instead?
You heard her.
Gently.
Up against the wall.
Turn around.
Ma'am, you okay?
Yeah.
I was just giving
that psycho a reading,
and he hulked out.
Don't say another word.
We've got psychic-client
confidentiality.
That's not a thing,
asshat.
So, what exactly
were you telling him
when he attacked you?
We were talking about
his love life.
I said I saw an image of him
and a beautiful woman
surrounded by trees,
and then he freaked out.
Why is that, sir?
Strike a little close to home?
Have you been in the woods
with a woman recently?
No, it was just
a misunderstanding.
Control,
run a name for me.
Last name Fischer,
first name Randy L.
Suspected
on a domestic.
7-Adam-19, be advised
suspect's wife
was reported missing
six weeks ago.
Hands behind your back.
Holy crap.
I was just making that up.
You were?
You think if I were
really psychic
that I'd be working out
of a moldy storefront
in Hollywood?
Although, I can totally see us
destroying my bedroom later.
Um...
7-Adam-15,
report of a dead body,
Seventh Street
bus terminal.
- At least it's behind you.
- Behind me?
Please, that letter of reprimand
is a permanent red flag.
It'll affect every promotion
I go in for.
You say tomato.
Uh, you reported
finding a dead body?
Yeah, he's in
the men's room.
Must've come in on
the late bus from Phoenix...
After the cleaning crew
went through.
All right. We'll take it
from here. Thank you.
Definitely a homicide.
Glove up.
Find an I.D.
Don't touch anything else.
Control, run a party.
Last of Valance,
first of Corey.
D.O.B. 4/14/97, and notify a
supervisor and homicide unit.
Copy that.
At least we know what
we're doing until the test.
Yeah.
Waiting.
Sit on the bench.
I thought I told you
to take it easy.
We did.
Officer West
spotted these two
trying to steal an ATM
from the Save Mart
on Cahuenga.
Writing it up as a 211?
No, sir.
Technically, it's considered
a bank burglary,
not a robbery.
Very good.
Sir, can I ask you
something?
Okay.
Why'd you become a cop?
I gave him
a little homework.
Easy day and all.
I liked the teamwork.
I missed it after the Army.
I need those files right now.
Excuse me.
Hey.
How's it going?
Better now.
So, listen, I can probably
duck out of here early...
Jackson's got an exam
this afternoon.
Any way you can clear your
schedule for some us time?
Actually,
I think I can.
Really?
Yeah.
Call me
when you're off.
You ever dated a guy
with a kid?
Relax.
This is about Jessica.
I think
I freaked her out today
suggesting she meet Henry.
I doubt it. My guess is nothing
freaks that woman out.
What the hell?
Hey, you stepped in
a bit of a wasp nest.
Did either of you
touch the body?
He did. With gloves on
to get the wallet.
Is that all
that you touched?
Yes. Why?
You're freaking me out.
Wait. That is
an active crime scene.
Well, that's secondary
right now.
Hi. I'm Dr. Morgan
from the CDC.
Are you sure you didn't come
into contact with the victim's
mouth, saliva,
or any bodily fluids?
Yeah, I'm sure.
No sign of infection.
Infection?
Your murder victim is part of
a homegrown terror cell
that the DHS
has been tracking,
and we believe
that they're planning
a deadly biological attack
on the City of Los Angeles.
Okay, so, here is
what we know.
At 10:00 last night, this man...
Corey Valance...
Boarded a bus
from Phoenix to L.A.
He had a partner with him.
We have no identification
on that man,
but we do know that they're part
of a fringe nationalist group
which believes
that Los Angeles stands for
everything that is wrong
in America.
The two men arrived
here at 5:00 this morning.
We believe Corey's partner
strangled him
in the bus station bathroom
right after.
You thinking Corey
got cold feet?
It seems likely, yes,
especially since they came here
with this deadly virus.
Well, that explains the
Silkwood shower we just took.
That was purely
a precaution.
There is no evidence
that the biological agent
they were transporting
has been released.
But we do have
every reason to believe
that there is an attack planned
in the near future.
What type of virus
are we talking about?
A weaponized strain
of hemorrhagic fever...
Basically causes you to
start bleeding and never stop.
And that's how
the virus spreads,
through contact
with bodily fluids.
It has an extremely short
incubation period
and a gruesome pathology.
If not treated quickly,
it has a 90% fatality rate.
And if
it's treated quickly?
We believe that drops down
to around 60%.
But the bad news is...
That's not the bad news?
- No.
- The bad news is,
there's only
an experimental vaccine.
We're flying it here
from Atlanta.
But there's only
a few hundred doses.
Nowhere near enough
to combat an outbreak.
So, obviously, the
rookie exam will be postponed.
The Feds are asking us to be
their boots on the ground
while they set up
a command center here.
First order of business...
To I.D. Corey's
partner/killer.
So you'll conduct
field interviews
with the other passengers
on the bus.
Do we think Corey's killer
is operating alone now?
No. We think
there's one more...
A local who picked him up
at the bus station.
So, okay, this is
extremely sensitive.
We can't risk the news
getting out
and causing a panic.
That being said,
you can warn
your immediate families
to stay away
from populated areas,
but no details.
Understood?
All right.
Let's go get these guys.
Mom, it's only for
you and Dad, okay?
- You can't tell anybody else.
- No, I re... I really
can't
say anything else.
- Now, the majority of...
- You knew.
Can you give us a minute,
please?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, thank you.
That's why you hesitated when
I talked about Henry visiting.
You knew L.A.
wasn't safe.
I was briefed about
a possible threat last week.
And you didn't warn me.
You'd just have Henry show up
for the apocalypse.
No, no. I-I didn't know
that this was real.
The DHS and the FBI
hear dozens
of potential terror threats
every month.
And most of them are just talk
or we can shut them down.
That's not the same
as knowing it's safe.
This is my son
we're talking about.
Even if there was the slightest
chance there was danger,
you should've said
something.
You ready?
Yeah.
Honey, you should go
to your parents'.
Look, you know I can't tell you
what's going on.
But it's bad.
You gonna call Wesley?
I want to.
But I don't know if I can
trust him to keep it quiet.
Really?
Yeah, this is the kind of
civil liberties issue
he gets on
his soapbox about.
Yeah, but how would you feel
if something happens
and you didn't warn him?
Hey, it's me.
I'm afraid I can't get together
this afternoon.
Something came up.
Yeah,
I'm disappointed, too.
Uh, I'll call you later.
I couldn't risk it.
Cut. That's lunch.
Everyone back
in 30 minutes, please.
It's not right.
Keeping everyone
in the dark.
We're supposed to be
protecting them.
That's what
we're trying to do.
Yeah, but...
But nothing,
Officer Nolan.
This is where
the job's hardest.
If we alert the public,
we alert the men we're hunting.
Odds are, they'll panic
and set it all off.
And then we'll cause exactly
what we're trying to prevent.
And what if they set it off
anyway before we catch them?
Then it'll haunt us.
All right,
what's this guy's name?
Really?
Um, Brad Dallas?
Oh, hey.
That's me.
Can we have a word with you
over here?
Uh, sure.
Uh, be right back.
Were you on the bus last night
coming from Phoenix?
Uh, yeah.
I was visiting my mom. Why?
Did you see this man
on the bus?
Oh, that's cool.
Is that a yes?
Uh, yeah,
he looks familiar.
He was traveling with someone.
You happen to remember him?
No, I wasn't
paying attention.
I was taking
a bunch of selfies.
You know,
for the 'gram?
But I couldn't post them,
though,
'cause my pores were huge.
Can we see them,
please?
The pictures,
not your pores.
Oh.
Yep,
that's our dead guy.
Yeah, which means the man
next to him's our target,
but he's too dark
to see.
You know who's really good
at Photoshop?
The FBI.
That's right.
We're gonna take your phone,
but we'll get it back to you
just as soon as we can.
W-- Uh... Um...
Stay dry.
Man.
And here I thought
that test was gonna be
the most stressful thing
about my day.
Best case scenario,
it's tomorrow's problem.
And worst case?
Never mind...
Don't answer that.
Police.
Took you long enough.
Bag's in here.
Sir, we're here about the bus
you took from Phoenix.
No kidding.
I called you about the bag.
And what bag is that?
I thought it was mine
on the bus.
I picked it up
by accident.
Noticed as soon as I got home.
Called right away.
Still took you guys like
six hours to get here.
Uh, sir, we're not here
about a bag.
So you don't have mine?
No.
Damn it.
My computer's in there.
I went through this one
looking for an address,
and all I found was
some weird science equipment.
Control,
this is 7-Adam-19.
Patch me into task force,
please.
Sir, did you...
touch anything in there?
Yeah, I cut my finger
going through it
looking for an address.
Some kind
of broken vial.
Won't stop bleeding.
Everything okay
in there?
Yeah.
Just stay out there.
Tim. No!
What's happening?
It's okay.
There's a bad case of the flu
going around.
We were warned about it
this morning at roll call.
Nothing to panic about.
Then why'd
you lock the door?
Standard protocol.
Look,
was there anyone else
in the house with you
earlier today?
No.
My kid's with my ex.
You got
any cold medicine?
I think so.
Go take it.
I'm coughing up blood.
I'm just telling you
how they advised us
to treat this
if we came across it.
Right now,
my partner is radioing
for an ambulance.
Gonna be here any minute.
Go.
Everything all right
out there, Chen?
Uh, yeah.
The CDC's on their way.
Hey, you need
to come out of there.
That's not gonna happen.
Got to keep this contained.
Tim... It's gonna
be all right, Boot.
You keep your head
in the game, okay?
Everything's
gonna be fine.
Where are
those pictures?
Okay, FBI table.
John, uh, wait.
I'm sorry.
I would have never let you
bring your son
into a dangerous situation.
I promise.
Good.
'Cause I really didn't like
being mad at you.
I didn't really like you
being mad at me, either.
Jessica.
Our terrorist is Jimmy Roskin,
31 years old.
Arrested eight months ago
on a hate crime charge
that didn't stick.
Okay, run his photo
against all the traffic
and security cameras
around the bus station.
And check
for known associates.
Looks like we have
our first infection.
Who?
One of the bus passengers.
Luckily, he's contained.
But Tim might be
infected, too.
Come on.
Let's move it on out.
Officer Chen, you
want to tell me what happened?
Yeah, uh, the bus passenger
mistakenly grabbed
the wrong bag, and the virus
must have been in it
because he coughed up blood
on Tim.
What... Whoa.
What are they doing?
We need to
get them out of there.
We will. But first
we have to establish
a proper quarantine.
Did any blood
get on you?
Uh, no.
I was out here.
Tim immediately
closed the door.
Smart man.
Officer Bradford, this is
Dr. Morgan from the CDC.
Hey, Doc.
How you doing?
Fine. But Mr. Langston's
struggling a little.
Can you describe
his condition?
Yeah. He, uh,
started coughing blood
about 20 minutes ago.
Now he's got
a pretty wicked nosebleed.
Why aren't they coming in?
Where's my ambulance?
It'll be here any minute.
Just... stay put.
Save your energy.
Uh, where's the vaccine?
Still in the air. Should land
in the next hour or so.
You can't
make Tim wait in there.
He might not be infected.
Sorry.
Quarantine rules exist
for a reason.
Officer Bradford,
do you mind if I put you
to work while you wait?
You want to know
what's in the bag?
Yes, I do.
Copy that.
Uh, Chen, I'm gonna
turn on my body cam.
You can monitor it
from out there.
Okay.
Please be careful.
All right.
Here we go.
Wait, wait.
What is that bottle?
Looks like
the delivery device.
It's a misting fan.
I think you're right.
Looks like there's a growth
medium inside the bottle.
Add the virus to it,
then spray it in a crowd.
Droplets land
on people's faces,
infect them through
their mouth and nose.
It's as low tech
as you can get.
It's Dr. Morgan.
I know how they're planning
to disperse the virus.
Understood.
Yes.
Okay, keep...
Keep me posted.
How's Tim?
- It's too soon to tell.
- Got something!
Photo of our guy matched back
to a gas station
where the bus depot is.
We got a picture
of the car
that picked him up
but not the driver.
I ran the plate,
but it came back stolen.
Okay,
cut to the good news.
I followed it
through traffic cameras
all the way
to Highland Park.
But I lost it when it got off
the freeway.
That area's mostly residential,
except for the police museum...
But I doubt that's where
they were headed.
More than likely,
that's where home base is.
Or they went local
to avoid highway cams.
Either way,
it's the only lead we got.
Get out there.
I'm sending all available units
to canvass with you.
Yes, sir.
No sign of any I.D.
or target information.
Tim!
Tim, look out!
Tim?
Tim!
I gotta get outta here.
Gotta get
outta here here.
Gotta get outta here.
Tim!
Tim, are you okay?
Hey, answer me.
It's okay! I'm okay!
Well, that was fun.
Are you sure
you're okay?
Kind of depends on your
definition of the word.
You need to get that vaccine
here right now.
All units, be advised
we have a positive I.D.
on the terror suspect
vehicle.
- ♪ I got this life to fix ♪ - We're looking
for a light blue 2013 four-door lon...
♪ Threw it all out in a ditch ♪ ...with
a scratch on the driver's side door.
- ♪ Broken down when I was sick ♪
- Be advised, suspects are armed...
- ♪ Gotta build it back up brick by brick ♪
...extremely dangerous, and pose an imminent danger
♪ I got this life to fix ♪
...to the public if they escape.
♪ Threw it all out in a ditch ♪
♪ Broken down when I was sick ♪
♪ Gotta build it back up
brick by brick ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Build it back up
brick by brick ♪
Well, if you do see him,
or the car, please call 911.
Right.
Nobody knows each other
in this neighborhood.
Back in Pennsylvania,
I knew all my neighbors.
Names, families, even helped
deliver a few kids.
I'm sorry, what?
Robertson twins,
winter storm of 2014.
Hospital roads
were all blocked,
so I had to become
a temporary midwife.
Good thing I brought
my toolbox,
- too, 'cause... right.
- Forget I asked.
Let's go talk to
some real locals.
Well, that was a bust.
Yeah, most people
are at work.
Hey.
What's going on?
Awful lot of cops around.
I'm not really
at liberty to say.
Seriously?
This is my neighborhood.
If something's going on,
I deserve to know.
Okay. But.
You have to keep it quiet.
You can't tell anyone else.
Sure.
We're trying to stop
a terror attack.
We believe one of the terrorists
lives around here.
So you should evacuate...
Maybe even get out of the city.
Okay?
No, not okay.
So far from okay.
Why haven't you issued a warning
or an evacuation?
- People have the right to know.
- We can't, okay?
'Cause it would cause a panic
and alert the terrorists
- that we're onto them.
- That's not your call to make.
This is why I didn't tell you
in the first place.
Because I knew you were gonna
get on your high horse...
High horse? This is about
basic civil liberties, guys.
Give me your phone.
What?
I'm placing you
under arrest.
Wait. What for?
Violation of public order.
Come on.
This isn't gonna hold up in court.
Doesn't have to.
But you're incommunicado
until this is resolved.
Come on.
You sure about this?
No.
Do you recognize
this man?
Or this car?
Yeah, the car, yeah.
I see it almost
every morning on Fig.
That's where I panhandle.
The, uh, driver is
a real piece of crap.
Cursed me out,
saying I ruined his country.
Like I wasn't born
at Cedars-Sinai, you know?
Officer Bishop.
Thank you.
This gentleman
has seen the car.
I don't suppose you know
where the guy lives?
Over off Wayland.
Yeah, I, uh,
keyed his car once
while I was out collecting cans
on trash day.
It's a yellow
apartment building.
Can't miss it.
You sure we shouldn't wait
for a Hazmat team?
There's no time. They might
already be on the way
to their target.
Clear!
Our unknown terrorist
is Brendan Mitchell.
Control,
alert task force.
We have a positive I.D.
on our second suspect.
Help!
Bishop?
We know where
they're headed.
Feds are pulling resources
from all over the Southland.
All major roads heading to LAX
are being monitored.
So while the airport
is shut down,
we'll provide support
at assigned checkpoints
on Century
and Sepulveda Boulevards.
7-Adam-07, copy.
En route
to Sepulveda checkpoint.
You're seriously gonna keep me
in this car all night?
You're the one that wanted to
spend more quality time together.
Sir, this operation's
moving at a million miles an hour.
And these checkpoints were
determined by someone
who has definitely
not tried to make
a last-minute flight
at LAX.
We're not running point
on this.
We all have orders
to follow.
Including me.
Yes, sir. But there is
a hole in the perimeter
that only an L.A. native
or a rookie patrol officer
who's painstakingly studied
every street in this city
would know.
He's right. There are
back roads off La Cienega.
Our guy would know that.
Sir, even with the airport
shut down,
there'll be thousands
of people waiting there.
If these two guys
get through...
All right, let's do it.
Control, this is 7-L-20.
Show us diverting
to La Cienega,
and reroute an airship
over there.
Eyes out
for our blue sedan.
Hey, I, uh... I just checked
with Dr. Morgan.
The vaccine's
minutes away.
You know, you're good at
a lot of things...
Lying isn't one of them.
You think I'm good at things?
Can I get that in writing?
How are you doing?
Are there
any symptoms yet?
I'm sweating like a pig.
But it's probably because
it's 100 degrees
in this room.
It's gonna be okay.
I really believe that.
I'm sure you do.
But if it isn't...
Don't think like that.
It's...
If it isn't...
I'm not going out
the way my man Pete here
just did.
What are you saying?
When the time comes...
...I'm going out
on my own terms.
Be advised. Suspect
vehicle spotted on Centinela,
heading south
onto La Cienega.
California license...
Victor, 5, Bravo, Uniform,
9, Foxtrot, 7.
Up ahead. Blue sedan.
That's him.
Control, 7-Adam-15...
We are in pursuit of suspect.
7-Adam-07...
Joining pursuit.
♪ I'll, I'll be outside ♪
♪ He'll be with a black heart
when I arrive ♪
♪ Hidden in the dark,
life he couldn't start ♪
♪ Bitter 'bout the things that
he thought he was a part of ♪
♪ Ah, ah-ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah-ah ♪ Sgt. Grey:
7-L-20... on your 6:00.
♪ Ah, ah-ah ♪
Hang on.
♪ No, whoa ♪
- You all right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Stay on him.
- Trying.
♪ Wouldn't wanna be ya ♪
All units, be advised,
Airship One disengaging
from pursuit.
Suspect vehicle has entered
a no-fly zone.
Go get him.
♪ No, whoa ♪
♪ Wouldn't wanna be ya,
wouldn't wanna be ya ♪
♪ No, whoa ♪
♪ Wouldn't wanna be ya,
wouldn't wanna be ya ♪
Shots fired.
La Cienega and Hill.
Jimmy!
Jimmy, run! Run!
They're running!
- Ready?
- Yeah, let's go.
Control, 7-L-20.
Suspects are on foot
heading east.
We need a five-block perimeter
set up.
And send Hazmat units
to lock down this area
for containment.
This way!
- Nobody move!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Everybody down! Get down!
He's on the bus
with the virus!
Angela,
it's too dangerous.
We have to.
Ready?
Everybody down!
All I need is a shot.
I'll get you that.
Down!
Nobody move.
Get outta here.
Go, go.
Dude,
let's talk about this.
Hey! Hey!
Don't do that.
You don't
need to do that.
Let me go, or I'm gonna infect
everybody on this bus!
If I let you go, you'll infect
a hell of a lot more people.
Yeah. None of them
are gonna be you!
Damn.
That's some straight shooting
right there.
Appealing to my sense
of self-preservation.
But here's the thing...
I made my peace with dying
when I got on this bus.
So I'm coming over there...
...and I'm arresting you.
Aah!
Clear! Go, go! Off now! Off the bus!
Go, go, go, go!
Did you shoot me?
Just a little.
I guess you're screwed.
Rules clearly say that
if you shoot your rookie,
then you can't hand him off
to another T.O.
7-Adam-07, show Code 4
at our location... suspect down.
Heading east on Crescent in
search of armed terror suspect.
Ma'am,
get back inside.
7-Adam-15,
crossing Wilton on Higsby.
No sign of suspect.
Control,
possible contact,
5824 Elgin.
We're gonna check
the backyard.
Yeah,
this is Jessica Russo.
Call the FAA and tell them that
we're gonna fly some choppers
into LAX airspace and then
have them reroute an airship
to our location ASAP.
Think we got him?
Assume we didn't.
Hey, there.
You hear those sirens?
That's just about
a couple hundred
of my closest friends
coming to back me up.
But you're all alone.
Okay.
Your turn.
Hey, Jimmy!
We got your buddy
in custody.
It's over.
I know you're hurt.
But you're still alive.
And I'm offering a way
for you to stay alive.
Think of all the publicity
you'll get.
You'll be the face
of your cause.
So much better
than being a martyr
in a cold box
underground.
But, Jimmy,
you got to decide right now.
When S.W.A.T. gets here,
they're just gonna light you up.
Okay. Okay.
I-I-I'm coming out.
Don't shoot.
Show me those hands.
What the hell?
He was reaching.
I didn't see that.
Stay back.
He might still be alive.
He might be infected. So we
don't go anywhere near him.
Suspect is down.
I repeat,
suspect is down.
Yeah, area's quarantined
until CDC clears it.
Please tell me
that's the vaccine.
It is.
Wait. Stand back.
You're not wearing
protective gear.
Yeah.
Officer Bradford,
it's time to let me in.
Hey.
Hey, Doc.
We got it.
How are you feeling?
Not bad...
All things considered.
Good.
You're right at the edge
of what we think is
the incubation window.
So the fact that you're not
showing any symptoms doesn't suck.
But we're gonna give you
this vaccine just to make sure.
It's experimental,
right?
That's correct.
So we're just gonna have
to wait and see what happens.
Maybe nothing.
Maybe you grow horns.
But for now,
I'd say you might've
dodged a bullet.
Any chance we can kiss
and make up?
Or can I expect
a lawsuit?
Oh, up
until about 20 minutes ago,
I was drafting it
in my head.
But then you risked everything,
got on that bus,
and saved those people.
You got a little
turned on.
No.
Okay, yeah,
maybe a little.
It made me realize that I was
a little shortsighted earlier.
Maybe I didn't
actually know best
what should happen
in that situation.
So, we're good again?
Again.
Does it seem like
we fight a lot?
Definitely. But...
I think it's our thing,
you know?
Like some couples swing dance
or go to Disneyland.
And I didn't want to r...
Jackson!
Dad.
Heard what you did.
What can I say?
I'm my father's son.
- Good job.
- What?
Oh, um, thank you.
It was all Jessica.
Don't sell yourself short.
You sure you're okay?
No.
I don't think he was reaching
for a weapon.
What are you saying?
I'm saying
she lied to me.
The guy had
a biological weapon.
He was giving up.
Maybe he was,
or maybe that's what
he wanted you to think.
Either way,
his very existence
made him a clear
and present danger.
She's got 20 years
on the job,
dealing with a whole different
level of bad guy...
And I don't know anything
because I'm a rookie?
Look, I'm no Boy Scout,
all right?
If six months on this job
has taught me anything,
it's that there is evil
in this world.
But in that moment,
she chose to lie to me.
Just like she lied to me
about Henry.
So either
she doesn't trust me.
Or she's a liar.
Or she was doing you
a favor.
Giving you deniability if the
shooting ever became a thing.
So you're saying
I should just let it go?
I'm saying it's been
a crazy day.
And you don't know whether
you're coming or going.
So before you risk
your relationship...
And possibly
your career...
By blindly
charging forward,
maybe you should
sleep on it.
Hey. I heard you guys
saved the day.
It was a group effort.
- Glad you're okay.
- Me too.
I-I mean
that you're okay, too.
How's Tim?
I think he's gonna be
all right.
- That's good news.
- What now?
24-hour observation
at the CDC.
I'll bet my pension
he just told doctors
Tim Bradford does not ride
in a wheelchair.
Only way I'm leavin'
out of here is on my own two feet.
Don't you guys have
paperwork to finish?
He's back.
- Yeah, he is.
- So stubborn.
♪ Who knows me like you do ♪
Officer Bradford!
- Tim!
- Officer Bradford!
We need an ambulance! Tim,
what happened in the perimeter?
- What's wrong?
- Everyone, stay back.
- Tim!
- Somebody call help.