ANNOUNCER:
Previously, on "The Rookie"...
NOLAN: Six months ago, I packed
everything I own into a U-Haul,
moved here to become a cop.
Cholesterol level I've never
seen in a rookie.
I'm something of a pioneer.
We got some new blood this morning.
SGT. GREY:
Lucy Chen, Jackson West,
and John Nolan,
who was born before disco died.
I don't give a damn about
your age. Show me what you got.
I hate what you represent...
a walking mid-life crisis.
LAPD isn't a place for
you to find yourself.
Everything is a test, Officer Chen,
and you just got another "F."
Show me those hands. Now!
(GUNFIRE)
- (GROANS)
- 7-Adam-19.
- (SIREN WAILS)
- LUCY: Officer down.
Get out your gun and cover me!
If you don't have what
it takes on the streets,
then you're not a cop.
LOPEZ: Freeze up again,
and you're done.
TALIA: I know about you and Nolan.
Break things off before it's too late.
(THE PACK A.D.'S "HAUNT YOU" PLAYS)
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh, ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
(SIRENS WAILING)
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh,
ahh ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
TALIA: 7-Adam-15, in pursuit of
red Jeep, heading south on Vine.
Do we need to review
high-speed pursuit protocol?
- No.
- What about that PIT maneuver
you failed to execute two blocks ago?
Police regulations recommend
that an officer
not attempt a PIT maneuver
at over 35 miles an hour.
They also state that the risk
of civilian injuries grows
exponentially with every minute
of urban pursuit.
♪ A new house, a new life ♪
(TIRES SQUEAL)
♪ So absurdly safe ♪
♪ You got some kids, stupid kids ♪
Everything you hit requires
a separate accident report.
I know.
♪ But somethin' lurks unseen ♪
♪ Maybe somethin' you ate ♪
So maybe hit fewer things.
(SIRENS WAILING, TIRES SQUEAL)
♪ I died ♪
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh,
ahh ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
TALIA: 7-Adam-15,
in pursuit of red Jeep,
heading up. into the Hollywood Hills.
Requesting backup and airship.
NOLAN: Okay, I'm gonna PIT him.
Okay, just tap him. Just tap... Now!
♪ Just like a bad plot ♪
♪ I won't tell you why ♪
♪ Under a floor or in a wall ♪
♪ is where my secret lies ♪
I can feel you judging me
with your eyes.
It's not my eyes
you should worry about.
It's my pen when I
write your evaluation.
(TIRES SCREECH)
♪ I died ♪
NOLAN: Police! Get out of the car!
NOLAN: Driver, step away
from your vehicle!
- ♪ I died. ♪
- Show me your hands!
♪ I died ♪
TALIA: Get on the ground!
(PANTING)
Seriously?
Go get her, Boot.
NOLAN: Ma'am?
Ma'am, I need you to come back!
(METAL RATTLES)
Really?
Ma'am?
Wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, don't do that.
- Stay back!
- I will. I will.
Don't, don't, don't, don't,
don't, that's not an escape.
That's not an escape.
If you jump, you die.
I know. That's why I'm here.
Just... Just...
Okay, but wait,
just... get... just one second.
Just...
I don't love heights.
Okay.
Tell me about it, okay?
Just talk to me.
- Maybe I can help.
- You can't.
Clark proposed to me
right here a year ago.
We were supposed to get married today,
but I caught him with my cousin,
and he dumped me.
You can't let this guy ruin your life.
(SNIFFLES) Too late.
I lost my job, my apartment.
Even the cat ran away.
(SNIFFLES)
My life is a country song.
I got nothing to live for.
Okay, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
I have...
One second here. Hang on.
- BRIDE: What is that?
- NOLAN: A lottery ticket.
Drawing's on Thursday.
It's $50 million if you win.
Now you have something to live for.
You're kidding.
No, I-I've been
where you are, you know?
Not literally. I've never
actually been up here.
It's... It's... It's pretty.
- But... But I've, uh...
- (CRYING)
10 years ago, back in
Pennsylvania, my...
my construction company
was going under,
I was up to my eyeballs in debt,
tanking my marriage because
I thought I was a failure...
But I went into a liquor store
to buy the biggest bottle
of booze I could find
and I left it on the counter
and I bought. a lottery ticket instead.
And i-it gave me just enough hope
to make it through the bad times.
It's been my ritual ever since.
I buy one a week, but I-I don't
need it anymore.
So, um...
(METAL CLANKS)
I'm giving the hope to you.
(SNIFFLES)
I'm scared.
I know.
Yeah, I know.
But I can help you.
No! No!
(BRIDE SCREAMS)
Are you okay?
BRIDE: No!
I dropped the ticket. (GRUNTS)
- A little help!
- BRIDE: Aah!
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you ♪
♪ like I know you want me to do ♪
What are you thinking about?
(SIGHS) Ending it all.
Something I did? Or didn't do?
What if I hadn't saved her?
But you did.
Yeah, but it could've just
easily gone the other way.
Then you would've dealt with it.
Take the win.
There'll be plenty of losses
to come, you know?
Mm.
You think they'd get mad
if we called in sick week one?
Yes.
But we could spend the day together.
We could do L.A. stuff, yoga.
Yoga? You do yoga?
No, but I'm starting a new life here.
- (LUCY CHUCKLES)
- Maybe the new me loves yoga.
I don't know. Maybe he hates it.
But I'd be with you.
That is painfully romantic.
- Right?
- Mm.
Sadly, if we took the same sick day,
we may give ourselves away.
Yeah.
I mean, we are surrounded by cops,
and odds are somebody's
gonna figure it out.
Well, we'll have to be extra sneaky.
(GROANS) Am I this sore because I'm old
or because being a cop is hard...
- and don't answer that.
- You're sore
because this job's
like running downhill
as fast as you can.
Sure, it's exciting, but one wrong step
and things get ugly, fast.
Yeah.
Except you said Tim did
everything right,
and he still got shot.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER P.A.)
Checkout time, Officer.
Yeah, no.
I'm walking out of here.
Hospital policy.
I don't care.
So, who's picking you up?
A cab.
LOPEZ: Is that all we are to you?
- Hey.
- TALIA: You know, it's funny.
TALIA: He didn't tell us
he was getting out.
'Cause he's a tough guy.
Who doesn't need anybody's help.
Are you two finished?
Nope.
LOPEZ: Smile.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Hey, how's it going?
Great.
All right, fine.
I didn't get much sleep.
Are you worried about something?
No, no. Just, uh, excited
to get back out there.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Hey.
Did you break up with him yet?
LUCY: Uh...
Look, I appreciate you looking
out for me...
Oh, Boot, you misunderstand.
I did you a solid.
You only get but one.
You want to sabotage your career
before it starts,
that's on you now.
NOLAN: Oh.
Very funny, you guys.
(LAUGHTER)
Of course, you know, this means
now I have to throw them.
(LAUGHTER)
All right, the honeymoon's over.
3, 5, 21.
Officer Nolan, you care to guess
what these numbers represent?
Combination to your heart, sir?
(LAUGHTER)
3 is the number
of opportunities you had
to disable Runaway Bride's car
yesterday.
5 vehicles were damaged
because you failed to do so.
And the last number.
Officer Bishop.
$21,000 in property damage
the city has to pay.
Correct.
All in all,
Officer Nolan's first pursuit
reveals room for improvement.
Yes, sir.
SGT. GREY: Onward.
Officer Chen is in need
of a training officer
until Tim Bradford is cleared for duty.
Officer Scott Wrigley, you get the nod.
That's it. Stay safe out there.
Oh, Lopez, West,
see the captain on the way out.
- What do you think she wants?
- Nothing good.
CAPT. ANDERSON:
I was reading over your report
on the Officer Bradford shooting.
First off, neither of you
had your body cams on,
which I understand.
You were under fire.
What I don't understand
is how Officer Lopez
emptied two magazines,
striking the suspect in the leg,
but Officer West...
you didn't fire a single shot.
If I may.
Officer West did not
have a protected position
from which to fire,
so I urged him to stay down
while I engaged the suspect.
Is there anything that
you would like to add?
No, ma'am.
Okay. Get back to work.
Thanks.
I didn't do it for you.
The golden boy with the VIP dad
flunks out on my watch,
I can wave detective goodbye.
I just hope protecting you
doesn't get me killed.
Are you sure I can't carry that?
Absolutely.
I've been on the job 12 years,
never fired my weapon.
You took on a couple
high-powered jokers,
saved your T.O. on day two.
So that makes you a rock star
in my book.
And rock stars don't
pack-mule the gear.
I was just trying to not get killed.
Aww. Modest, too.
(GRUNTS)
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- (CAMERA BEEPS)
I can see why Tim's
been boasting about you.
- He has?
- No.
But I'm not like that.
I give credit where it's due,
and you have earned a free pass today.
So anything you need, just ask.
(SEAT BELT CLICKS)
♪ Whoa ♪
So, just how badly. did
I mess up that pursuit?
Average.
You hesitated to hit a car
because you spent your life
avoiding accidents.
Well, that's true of every rookie.
True, but you've lived longer,
which means those instincts
are harder to break.
This job is all about doing things
that run counter to human nature.
If you can't overcome your
programming, you won't make it.
Failure's not an option, okay?
I've been around guns my whole
life, never froze up before.
It's different when
they're shooting at you.
Yeah. Yeah, well, now I know.
Look. It... It won't happen again.
Not good enough.
LOPEZ: I don't want to spend
every call wondering
if you're gonna freeze up again,
so today, we get proactive,
take all the high-risk calls
and see how you do.
- You better do well.
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
DISPATCH: Wilshire units,
415 at Presbyterian church.
PR states man on PCP attacked a priest.
Units on scene
requesting backup, Code 3.
- Perfect.
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
7-Adam-07, responding.
(DOG BARKS)
A morning of rolling-stop citations
should take us nicely into lunch.
(SCOFFS) We're gonna
sit here all morning?
Hey, writing tickets
is the heart of the job.
Do you want to, uh,
quiz me or something?
Nope.
(SIREN WAILS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
LOPEZ: What's going on?
OFFICER MILLER: Blaster on PCP
walked into the church,
and threw the priest
through a stained-glass window.
Tore the place up.
We're waiting for special ops
and a supervisor.
Big guy?
You could say that.
Okay, cool.
We're going in.
We are?
I mean, hell, yeah, we are.
It's your funeral.
(POLICEMEN CHUCKLE)
(ORGAN BLARING)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(SCREAMS)
LOPEZ: Whoa! He is a big one.
What do we do here, Officer West?
- (SCREAMS)
- (WOOD CRACKS)
Phencyclidine... or PCP...
is a dissociative sedative
that makes the user feel
invulnerable and, uh,
sets his body temp through the roof,
which is why he took off
all his clothes.
He's basically the Hulk,
unable to feel pain.
If you shoot him,
it just makes him mad.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(WHOOPS, GASPS)
So what we need to do is calm him down.
I'm not looking for a dissertation.
You stop.
I want to know how you're gonna
get him into cuffs
and then our shop.
- Come here!
- Carefully.
(SIREN WAILS)
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-15, vehicle on fire,
MacArthur Park, Code 3. Respond.
MAN: Park right there!
TALIA: Stay away from the flame.
Step back from the flame.
What is going on?
Ma'am, did you do this?
Yeah, 'cause Fungus ripped me off.
Who's Fungus?
Fun Gus. My meth dealer.
Your meth dealer drives a Prius?
So why burn your dealer's car?
I gave him $20 for meth, and he
only gave me 10 bucks' worth.
Girl, that's just not right.
I know.
- I work hard for my money.
- TALIA: I bet you do.
So what say we go find this
Fungus and get you squared away?
Okay. Yeah.
Only I don't know where he's at.
The kid I stabbed said
this was Fungus's car.
I lit it up so he'd show.
Wait. You stabbed a kid?
Yeah. Fungus's brother.
- Turn around.
- What?
- Put your hands on the tree.
- He... Hey!
Hands behind your back.
(HANDCUFFS CLICK)
I got a knife here.
Blood's not even dry.
The kid you stabbed, he still alive?
I don't know.
- (ORGAN BLARING)
- (SCREAMS)
(BLARING STOPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
It's okay.
(LIGHT SWITCH CLACKS)
Look, I'm just gonna come
a little bit closer, okay?
- (GRUNTS)
- Okay.
Hey, hey, no, we're good. We're good.
It's okay. We're good, right?
JACKSON: Listen to me,
just a quick second.
You're thirsty, right?
You got to be thirsty.
JACKSON: Okay, you like water?
I can get you water...
nice, refreshing water, right?
Just put these bracelets on.
Put these bracelets on,
and I will give you
all the water that you want.
- (WOOD THUDS)
- JACKSON: Sweet, sweet water.
(DOORS SQUEAK)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER, SIREN CHIRPS)
Special ops, my ass.
Bunch of meter maids.
(SIREN WAILS IN DISTANCE)
TALIA: Where is he? I don't see him.
LIANN: I don't know.
I stabbed him over there.
(CHILDREN SHOUTING PLAYFULLY
IN DISTANCE)
Bishop.
TALIA: Is he alive?
Skin's cool, no pulse.
Don't feel bad for him.
I'm the one who got ripped off.
(BEEPS)
7-Adam-15, our call is now a 187.
Have Homicide respond to our location.
Great morning, Officer Chen.
I'm gonna drop you here for lunch.
What?
Oh, uh, I like to go home
to eat, you know,
get these wool pants off,
air things out.
Be back in 40.
(DOOR SQUEAKS)
It's just such a waste,
losing your life for so little.
See that thing you're doing right now,
looking for meaning in tragedy?
That's an old-life instinct.
- It's not helpful here.
- It's human.
So is stupidity and murder.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
TIM: Why the long face, Boot?
Hey. What are you doing here?
Heard you got Wrigley.
He always dumps his rookies here
while he goes home
to eat mac and cheese in his undies.
So, what, you came to check on me?
I live around the corner.
I was getting takeout.
Right.
So, how's it going?
It's good.
Officer Wrigley is, um...
Yeah, he's... he's cautious.
He's... He's what we call a slug...
just doing his time,
allergic to real police work.
Yeah. Yeah.
You must like the quiet, though.
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
- DISPATCH: Wilshire units,
store owner called
with suspected shoplifter.
Caucasian male, yellow track suit.
- 314 Franklin Drive.
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
That's three blocks from here, Boot.
What, a-am I supposed to respond?
My T.O.'s not here,
and I don't have a car.
You've got legs, don't you?
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
- 7-Adam-21 responding on foot.
Uh, skipping out on the bill?
No, no. Right.
Uh, whatever.
Run, Boot!
- (DOOR OPENS)
- Run!
LUCY: Hey!
LUCY: Police! Stop!
Hey! Hey! Police!
Watch out, watch out.
- LUCY: Stop!
- MAN: Come on!
Police!
Hey.
(GRUNTS)
Stay on the ground!
Hands behind your back.
(SIREN CHIRPS)
- (HANDCUFFS CLICK)
- MAN: Do your thing, girl.
All right, Officer Chen.
Show me how you process an arrest.
Uh... first...
Take the prisoner out of the shop.
- (GROANS)
- Come on.
Then search the back seat.
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
- (DOOR BUZZES)
- (SCREAMS)
- Next, take off...
- Shoes and socks.
Hold the feet.
♪ Way too strong, I can't even hide ♪
(GROANS)
LUCY: Next, remove jewelry.
(GRUNTS)
- All right.
- (GRUNTS)
Get finger and palm prints.
♪ When you talk to me, it's not real ♪
And now your thumb.
- ♪ I got this feeling ♪
- NOLAN: Not your thumb.
Still not your thumb.
- ♪ I got this feeling ♪
- Let's try the big one.
(GRUNTING)
♪ I'm about to do something ♪
- (BEEPS)
- Mug-shot time.
♪ Hey, I'm about to do something ♪
Now turn to the right.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Finally, lock them up.
♪ Do something ♪
(ALL GRUNT)
Aah!
- Aah!
- And get the watch commander...
LUCY: ...to sign off
on all the paperwork.
Officer Chen.
Good.
♪ I'm about to do something, ♪
♪ I'm about to do something ♪
Officer West.
♪ I'm about to do something, ♪
♪ do something, do something ♪
♪ Yeah, watch me now ♪
Also good.
♪ Hey, I'm about to do something ♪
Officer Nolan.
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I'm about to do something, ♪
♪ do something, do something ♪
(PAPER RUSTLES)
(SIGHS)
Did you check this, Bishop?
Yes, sir.
Try reading more carefully next time.
Once again with feeling, Officer Nolan.
Yes, sir.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Sorry.
- Sergeant?
- Yeah.
TALIA: I know you have
a problem with Nolan, but...
I feel like I'm taking
friendly fire here.
Is that how you see it?
'Cause Officer Nolan's not
the only one being tested.
You're ambitious,
anxious to make detective.
Nothing wrong with that.
Unless you're more interested
in your next job
- than the one you got.
- No, sir.
Good.
'Cause training Officer Nolan's
gonna require you to dig deep,
and failure could impact
your promotion.
You're dismissed.
LUCY: I feel like Goldilocks.
This training officer's
too hard, this one's too soft.
I don't know.
An afternoon of traffic stops
sounds good right about now.
Who are you, and what have you
done with Officer Extra Credit?
And, yes, that's what we called
you back at the academy.
Always the first to volunteer,
the most prepared rookie
in the history of the LAPD.
I'm still that guy.
Officer West, time to go.
Is he okay?
Um, he said he's having
some trouble sleeping.
I'm gonna check on him later.
Mm.
What?
You're a good guy, is all.
(LAUGHS)
(HORN HONKS)
So, did you struggle as a rookie?
No.
- Really?
- TALIA: Yes.
This job is all about making
split-second decisions in chaos.
My childhood was pretty, uh, turbulent,
so I got really good
at reacting quickly.
Look out!
- (TIRES SQUEAL)
- (GRUNTS)
WOMAN: Oh! Oh!
Ma'am, are you all right?
Just stay right there, okay?
We have an ambulance coming.
NOLAN: All right?
- Help! Help!
- 7-Adam-15,
requesting an R.A. for a female,
20s, struck by a car.
Help me! Help me! (SOBBING)
NOLAN: There's duct tape on her wrists.
- Don't let him get me.
- Who?
- No, please, don't let him take me.
Please don't let him take me again!
- NOLAN: Who?!
- Oh, my God!
DOCTOR: Dilated pupils.
- Sh-sh...
- Emma!
No, no, they're trying
to help you, okay?
DOCTOR: She's been heavily drugged.
- Emma.
- Who... Who is Emma?
Who's Emma?
DOCTOR: You need to get out
so we can treat her.
No! No!
DOCTOR: Nurse! Officers, out, now!
- CHRISTINE: Emma!
- (VELCRO RIPS)
No.
You okay?
At least it can't get worse.
See, clearly, you misinterpreted
my lecture about vehicle damage,
'cause hitting civilians is not
what I was advocating.
Sir, it wasn't Officer Nolan's fault.
She ran in front of our shop.
MOTTA: Way to go, Mad Max.
Officer Nolan,
Detectives Motta and Paige,
Major Assault Crimes.
Did you manage to get an I.D.
from the photo we sent?
I'm sorry. Does your rookie
think we work for him?
- Of course not.
- He's just highly motivated.
Christine Holbeck, 27.
Missing-persons report was filed
by her roommate a week ago.
Our victim happen to mention
who took her?
No, she was drugged. She has no idea
where she was held or even
how long she was running.
- Before you ran her over?
- It was an accident.
She mentioned a name... Emma.
She said she, uh...
She was sorry she left.
Could she be another victim,
someone who's still there?
PAIGE: We'll run the name,
see if anything turns up.
Well, what can we do to help?
Canvass while we wait for her to detox.
Done. I'll assign Bishop
and three other units,
get overnight to pick up the baton.
Let's go.
(MOANING)
Will you let me know how she's doing?
Yeah.
LOPEZ: I pulled a high-risk
warrant to serve.
Brenner Plank, a member
of the Aryan Nation
who enjoys long walks on
the beach and felony assault.
Hope you're ready for a fight.
Can't wait.
I don't get it.
A woman running for her life
with duct tape around her wrists?
How does nobody see her?
It's L.A.
7-Adam-15, show us Code 6.
- (SIGHS)
- All right.
13 down, 100 more to go.
How does kidnapping women
become somebody's normal?
Don't worry, that's a "how do we
get this guy" question,
not a search for meaning.
I know your position on that.
No, you don't.
You've been hardwired
to ask why, but out here,
the why is mostly irrelevant.
Look, "how we find the guy"
is the right question to ask.
But honestly, I'm not sure
you're prepared for when we do.
See, at some point, you're gonna
be faced with a doorway
to a very ugly place,
one people have tried to avoid
their whole lives.
Are you gonna be a cop in that moment,
or are you gonna be a guy
who's in over his head?
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-15, GTA in process.
Unknown make and model,
white and orange in color.
- Details to follow.
- We're not gonna respond to that.
Crime doesn't stop while we canvass.
No. It's just a matter of priority.
Yeah, well, that junkie seemed
pretty low priority
till she turned out to be a murderer.
7-Adam-15, show us responding.
(LIFT WHIRS)
Sir, I need you pull
the scissor lift over.
Sir, stop the lift,
and pull over right now.
CROCKETT: No.
(ENGINE REVS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Sir, that scissor lift
is not street legal.
And you stole it.
- Right.
- Should've opened with that.
CROCKETT: I didn't steal it.
I liberated it.
Supervisor owes me two weeks'
pay, so I'm gonna pawn this.
Unfortunately, it
doesn't work like that.
I need you to stop the lift
and come down.
- No.
- Sir, I do not have time for this.
- Nolan.
- Stop the vehicle.
Sir, I don't have time for this.
You're escalating the situation.
Do not hit that... Si...
(CRASH)
(METAL SCREECHING)
It's gonna be a lot
of paperwork, isn't it?
Yeah.
(CAR ALARM WAILS)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
JACKSON: Too bad he wasn't home.
I was in the mood to hook an Aryan up.
Oh, we're gonna go right back.
Just need you to grab snacks
first, definitely some caffeine.
Copy that.
(RADIO CHATTER CONTINUES)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO)
Bathroom?
Thank you.
(CASH REGISTER BEEPING)
(CASH REGISTER CLICKING)
(METAL SQUEAKING)
Do I need a key for the bathroom?
(TOILET FLUSHES, DOOR OPENS)
Thank you.
- Police!
- (GRUNTS)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Ohh!
(GRUNTING)
- LOPEZ: West!
- (GUN COCKS)
(PANTING)
We should be out there looking.
You're part of a team now.
Overnight has units canvassing,
and you'll be on it
when your shift starts.
Tell me this, and be honest.
- Hm?
- Am I too set in my ways?
- No.
- You changed your whole life,
moved across the country
to become a cop.
Yeah, but that's all external.
Talia thinks my age makes me
risk-averse
and less able to change
and over-invested
in helping this girl.
I'm sure I'd feel just as
invested if I'd, you know...
Hit a kidnap victim with your car?
Oh, my God, I just hate
saying it out loud.
Okay, look.
You want to help everyone.
That's why you joined the force.
But the hardest thing
for any rookie to learn
is that we can't.
(SIGHS)
Yeah?
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Why don't we ever stay at your place?
Because I live in a one-bedroom
with a view of a methadone clinic.
Oh, right.
How come I've never met this
mystery landlord of yours?
Because he's in Spain.
No, um, China.
I actually have no idea where he is.
After college, his trust fund vested,
and he just never stopped moving.
But the upside is, I get
to live here for free,
and it works out for both of us.
- Hmm.
- Speaking of which,
you could keep some of your things here
so you don't have to always just
run home in the morning.
I know.
I just think we should,
um, keep it casual.
(FOOD RATTLES)
Her name is Emma Vasquez.
Reported missing three weeks ago.
Detectives think she's the one
that Christine left behind.
I've approved extra shifts and O.T.
until we find this girl.
SGT. GREY: Everyone canvasses
between calls. Anything else?
CAPT. ANDERSON: Yes, one more thing.
Officer Nolan.
The motor pool is considering
taking out a hit on you
for all the damage you've caused
to their vehicles.
I talked them into, uh,
a different solution.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
- (LAUGHS)
- Sweet.
Try not to damage her, huh?
(KEYS CLACK)
I'm never gonna live this down.
You're welcome?
You know, I was thinking maybe
we should go to the hospital
before we start canvassing,
just to see if Christine
remembers anything.
Detectives are on that.
Yeah, I checked the detectives' table.
Motta and Paige are actually
working a lead right now.
Emma cannot wait.
(TRUNK LID CREAKS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(HUBCAP CLATTERS)
6-P-C-I-4-8 and a 1.
Do you like this kind of policing?
I like going home to my family.
My kids like having a dad.
SCOTT: Your training officer got shot,
and you still don't realize
how close to dying you came.
Yeah, I do.
SCOTT: And yet you're still
anxious to get back out there,
which means deep down,
a part of you liked it.
That's not me, so I write the tickets,
I take the low-risk calls
so cops like you
can get your thrill on.
CHRISTINE: He grabbed me in the garage.
Must've snuck in after I pulled inside.
I never saw him.
Just felt a needle go in my neck,
and then everything went black.
Do you remember anything
about the house?
He kept me in the basement with Emma...
...wore a mask when he came to see us.
I don't think it was
because he was gonna let us go.
(SNIFFLES) I think he liked it.
Anything else?
Anything that can help us
find this place?
It sounds crazy, but I...
I heard a voice saying "wait"
over and over, day and night.
Emma couldn't hear it, but
I could swear it was there.
What are you doing?
I'll come check on you later.
TALIA: We came by
on our way to canvass.
Protocol is key here, Talia.
Everything goes through us.
- You know that.
- Hey, what is the problem here?
We're all trying to catch the same guy.
Why is your boot talking?
- Again with this?
- It's all good.
TALIA: Let's get to work.
What is their problem?
They think they're better than us.
When you make detective,
are you gonna behave like that?
Hell, yeah.
But it'll actually be true.
You got something?
I think I might know what the voice is.
ROBOTIC VOICE: Wait. Wait. Wait.
Wait. Walk. Walk.
TALIA: It's called an
accessible pedestrian signal,
designed for the visually impaired.
And there's only one
on our search grid,
'cause there's a school for the
blind right around the corner.
Our guy's house would have
to be right here
in order to hear that voice
from a basement.
And I would peg that one
for mid-century kidnapper.
(DOG BARKS)
Let's ask the neighbors first.
Security guys are always nosy.
(DOORS OPEN, CREAK)
ROBOTIC VOICE: Walk. Walk. Walk.
7-Adam-15,
- show us Code 6 and out of our vehicle.
- ROBOTIC VOICE: Walk. Walk. Walk.
3017 Bailey Avenue.
- (RADIO BEEPS)
- ROBOTIC VOICE: Walk.
- (BOTTLES CLATTER)
- Walk. Walk.
- (DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
- Walk. Walk. Walk.
Hello, there, sir.
Good morning. How can I help you?
Ah, your neighbor over there,
across the street on the corner,
- do you know him at all?
- Yeah, yeah.
Um, yeah, he doesn't get out much.
Uh, kind of keeps to himself.
(DOG BARKS)
All right. And, uh, what
about these two girls?
You seen them around?
No. Uh, are... are they okay?
Well, we sure hope so.
Nolan!
(SHOTGUN COCKS, FIRES)
- (GUN COCKS)
- Nolan!
I'm going in!
(DOOR CREAKS, SLAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
- TALIA: 7-Adam-15 requesting help.
Shots fired, 2311 Bailey Avenue.
7-Adam-21 responding.
I'm going, whether you're in
the car with me or not, so...
Nolan!
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
NOLAN: (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(SHOTGUN COCKS, FIRES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Emma?
(PANTING, SOBBING)
NOLAN: It's the police. Emma?
I'm Officer Nolan, Emma.
- Please help me.
- I'm here to get you.
EMMA: Look out!
- NOLAN: (GROANS)
- EMMA: No, no. No, no, no, no.
- EMMA: No. No.
- (SHOTGUN CLICKS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
- (SHOTGUN COCKS)
- EMMA: No. No, no, no, no.
(ENGINE REVS)
- (CRASH)
- EMMA: (SCREAMS)
(GLASS SHATTERS, SIRENS APPROACHING)
No, don't leave me, please!
NOLAN: Shh. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Whoa, hey, are you okay?
Yeah. He's on the move.
I need someone to stay with Emma.
I'll do it.
SCOTT: 7-Adam-21...
need an R.A. and supervisor
at 3017 Bailey Avenue.
(YUNGBLUD'S
"21ST CENTURY LIABILITY" PLAYS)
(SIREN WAILS)
TALIA: Suspect heading east
on foot into Rosedale Cemetery.
- Send backup and airship.
- (RADIO BEEPS)
(PANTING, GRUNTS)
(SIREN CHIRPS)
(GRUNTS)
Stay down!
(SIREN WAILS)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(BRAKES SCREECH)
♪ I'm a 21st Century liability ♪
Freeze!
♪ Bang, bang, bang ♪
♪ It's all bo... bo... bo... bo... ♪
- (NOLAN GRUNTS)
- Don't move!
♪ I'm a 21st Century liability ♪
- (GRUNTS)
- Nolan!
♪ I'm a 21st Century liability ♪
- (MUSIC STOPS)
- That's enough.
He's done.
(KURT GROANS)
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
- Hook him up.
- (KURT GROANS)
- Okay.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
(VEHICLES APPROACHING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(HANDCUFFS CLICK)
PAIGE: They should've called us
before they went
into the suspect's house.
Why?
'Cause it's our investigation.
Last I checked,
it was my investigation,
and a girl's life was at stake.
And come to think of it, I think
you should be thanking them
for rescuing the girl
and closing your case.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Look at that.
Isn't that nice,
all my kids getting along?
You two, get out.
Got to admit it, that felt pretty good.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: You should
temper yourself, Officer Bishop.
May I remind you, you drove
your shop into a house.
CAPT. ANDERSEN: Give me a minute
with Officer Nolan.
Yes, ma'am.
How are you doing?
Okay.
I've always known
that people can be capable
of horrible things, but to
see it firsthand was...
Can't let it infect you.
Look, as a civilian,
you can be driven by emotion,
but as a cop, you rise above it.
It is not your job to punish
that man for what he did.
Do you understand?
Overcoming that impulse
will be the hardest thing
that you do in this job.
(RALEIGH RITCHIE'S
"WERLD IS MINE" PLAYS)
Have a good night.
Nice work today, Officer West.
- Thank you.
- ♪ I wanna live forever ♪
You took a very bad man off the street,
proved you got some fight in you.
♪ I wanna rule together ♪
So, this mean we're good or...?
(CHUCKLES) No.
♪ I wanna make some
money, money, money ♪
- ♪ I wanna waste some time. ♪
- But we're getting there.
♪ I wanna be your buddy, but, honey ♪
♪ This world is mine ♪
♪ This world ♪
♪ I'm stuck, stuck on a loop ♪
♪ And I can't vacate ♪
- ♪ Truth is I can't stay safe. ♪
- (CHUCKLES)
♪ Ready to be free of this pain, ♪
♪ and I can't wait ♪
- (INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
- (LAUGHS)
♪ I can't do right or do wrong ♪
♪ Keep quiet, or retire, ♪
♪ or be cool and move on ♪
♪ Don't wanna incite a riot ♪
♪ Wanna eat till I'm green, ♪
♪ living clean with a diet ♪
- ♪ No. ♪
- All right. Keep it safe.
One ticket at a time.
♪ Feet don't fail me now, ♪
♪ I just wanna go ♪
SCOTT: Great working with you,
Officer Chen.
Yeah. You, too, sir.
♪ I sleep, eat culture ♪
I'm cleared for duty.
Turned in my paperwork.
Oh.
You had me assigned to him, didn't you?
Everything is a test, Officer Chen.
Lucky for you, you passed this one.
Now, if you had been cool
half-assing it with Wrigley,
then I'd know you weren't serious
about becoming a good cop.
(CHUCKLES)
With all due respect, sir,
you're a pain in my ass.
That's my job.
Now, get some rest.
See you tomorrow.
♪ I'm stuck, stuck on a loop, ♪
♪ and I can't vacate ♪
♪ Truth is I can't stay safe ♪
♪ Ready to be free of this pain ♪
♪ and I can't wait ♪
♪ I can't do right or do wrong ♪
♪ Keep quiet, or retire, ♪
- ♪ or be cool and move on ♪
- Last one.
Good job today.
♪ Don't wanna incite a riot, ♪
- ♪ wanna eat till I'm green ♪
- Thank you, sir.
Most rookies spend the first
few months with blinders on,
but you looked out for that girl.
And as a present for your
maturity, I got your paperwork.
Police report, property damage report,
use of force report, pursuit memo...
- Thank you.
- ...and collision memo.
- (FOLDER THUDS)
- Godspeed.
- Sorry.
- He didn't get you anything.
Yeah, he did.
What are you doing?
Helping.
♪ I wanna live forever ♪
Ah. Hey.
It's, um... Officer Nolan.
Did something happen?
Yeah. Uh, we caught him.
Emma's safe.
(VOICE BREAKING) Thank you.
Thank you.
♪ This world is mine ♪
NOLAN: I don't understand.
(CHUCKLING) I mean,
how did you do this?
This shop is brand-new.
(CHUCKLES) Bribery.
So please drive very carefully.
Right.
(TIRES SQUEAL)
Improved By: FidelPerez
Sub Upload Date: October 24, 2018