CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(whistle blows)
(playing the blues)
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(machine whirs)
(screaming)
(groaning)
(squeaking)
Bart, can we go
to Banana Republic?
There’s a mannequin there
I have a crush on.
Milhouse, that is the most
pathetic thing I ever...
Oh, my God.
She’s beautiful.
-Bullies!
-(humming)
Wait. They’re employees.
They have to be nice
to us. Let’s go.
Oh, shoe-boy?
I’m looking for something
in a cross-trainer.
What size do I smell like?
You’re dead, Simpson.
Dude, don’t lose it
in the workplace.
We’re already on thin ice
with Mr. Freedman.
The shoe size calibrator
is for measuring feet
and nothing else.
Yes, Mr. Freedman.
I’m sorry, Mr. Freedman.
That tie really brings out
your eyes, Mr. Freedman.
You’re lacing it wrong.
I want it overy-undery,
not undery-overy.
Re-lace them all.
(cries out)
MR. FREEDMAN:
Attention part-time
sales representatives.
I’m leaving this job to work
at Jolly Tamale
because the hours are better
and my mom’s really sick.
When you leave,
what happens to your rule
about not whaling on customers?
That rule leaves with me.
-(gulp)
(laughing)
Idle teens at 1:00.
Intercepting
in three, two.
’Sup, guys?
Heard the new rap CD?
Yo, I don’t know
what I dig more,
hip-hop, krunk,
or serving my country.
Are you guys hitting on us?
No, man, we just want
to talk to you
about something near
and dear to us.
What? Being gay?
Close. The Army.
Because of exciting
current events,
the Army needs new members.
New members who want
to earn money for college,
and see a part of the world
that tourists never go to.
Doesn’t the Army have to fight
in wars?
(chuckling)
Not wars,
global struggles.
You guys like globes?
Let’s go, dudes.
(grunting)
Damn it.
Even the dumbest teenagers
in the dumbest town
in the dumbest state know
better than to join the Army.
Well, we’ll just have
to go younger.
What’s this assembly for?
A surprise
Doodlebops concert?
Standardized tests, standardized
tests, standardized tests.
How many of you
like video games?
(kids cheering)
Well, what if there was
a violent video game
that you could play for free,
plus it’s real life
and not a game at all?
Wouldn’t that be slammin’?
Who are these wonderful people?
Now we brought
along a movie.
Do you guys know
where we can find
some awesome kids
to show it to?
Dearborn, Michigan?
No, here.
You got it.
♪♪
I’m imagining
that knight is me.
(beeping)
KIDS: Ooh.
(crowd cheering)
(rock music playing)
(cheering)
ANNOUNCER (over speaker):
The Army. It’s everything you
like.
KIDS: Ah.
Now you can’t legally join
the army until you’re 18,
but if you pre-enlist now,
we will save you a spot
in America’s next
unresolvable conflict.
(cheering)
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
(chuckles)
Listen to those
half-pencils scribble.
Thanks for fitting us in,
Sergeant Skinner.
Well, I’d do anything
for my beloved Army.
Well, how about
re-enlisting?
How about you bite me?
Great news, Ma.
I agreed to join the army
when I turn 18.
What? Homer!
Our son joined the Army.
Eh, big deal,
by the time Bart’s 18,
we’re going to control
the world.
We’re China, right?
Now listen, Bub.
You go down to those recruiters
and tell them Bart is too young
for the Army.
I don’t want this to be
the only memory I have of him.
How come I can’t join the army,
but Lisa gets to be in PETA?
I think she just answers
their phone.
Hey.
(laughs)
Uh...
Fur is murder!
When’s the Krusty
movie coming out?
Whoa. Uh, hey.
No, you can’t.
Uh, this one’s ruined.
Give me the backup.
Now the babies.
And the monkey-head mittens.
Yeah, I’m a real class act.
Okay, Mr. Simpson,
we’ll tear up
your son’s contract.
Sorry, guys.
You know, his mother’s the one
who made me come down here.
Sounds, uh, like
you’re kind of tired
of being bossed
around at home.
Go on.
Would you be
interested in, um...
well, I don’t know,
joining the Army?
Wouldn’t that take me away from
my family for two whole years?
Hey, a big target like you will
be home a lot sooner than that.
Whoo-hoo! Where do I sign?
Now where’s my parade?
Where’s my parade?
We have this issue
of Parade Magazine.
Ooh, "Who makes what
in America."
Army private:
14,000 a year. D’oh!
Homer, with all the things
you’ve done--
go into space, attend
clown college, join the Navy--
I never thought
you’d join the Army.
(car horn honks)
Whoa, even the Army
has Humvees now.
Homie, don’t do this.
You have a wife and three
young children at home.
I have to, Marge.
Who else is gonna keep oil under
a hundred dollars a barrel?
You? Don’t make me laugh.
(laughing)
You couldn’t...
Aw, oh, oh, don’t, no.
(baby talking):
Daddy’s just teasing.
Of course you could.
You could keep it
under a hundred.
Yes, you could.
(whispering):
No, she couldn’t.
Attention!
(shouting):
Ordinarily, I would
spend the next two hours
questioning your sexuality,
running down your hometowns,
and telling you to drop and
give me various numbers.
Are you gonna ask us
our major malfunctions?
’Cause mine is
I care too much.
Unfortunately, the demand for
troops has never been higher,
so we’ve got to speed things up.
While you’ve been standing here,
your hair’s been cut,
and your clothes
have been replaced
with army fatigues.
♪ Step by step ♪
♪ Heart to heart ♪
♪ Left, right, left ♪
♪ We all fall down ♪
Here’s your nicknames:
Brooklyn, Hollywood,
Kissimmee-St. Cloud, Florida,
Maverick,
Blanket Hog, Newman’s Own,
Master of Suspense,
England’s Rose,
Nickname Pending,
Bram Stoker’s Dracula,
and Snowflake.
"Snowflake?"
What happens to me
in the summer?
A troublemaker, huh?!
You’re gonna sit here
and eat donuts,
while the rest of the unit
does push-ups!
(men grumbling)
(grunting)
I don’t understand.
How does punishing them
teach me a lesson?
Just for that, they’ll do
the push-ups one-handed,
while you eat
Alaskan King salmon
and I give you
a foot rub!
(chanting):
♪ I like rubbing
people’s feet ♪
♪ Corns and bunions
are a treat ♪
♪ I can give
massage real well ♪
♪ If you know why,
don’t ask, don’t tell. ♪
Congratulations, you have all
completed basic training.
Our base commander will now
give you your assignments.
Okay, listen up!
Man, you’ve got
an awesome voice!
Well, thank you.
Can you say,
"Side effects may include
drowsiness and loss
of appetite"?
Side effects may include
drowsiness and loss of appetite.
Hmm, sounded better in my head.
Now, we’ve graded
your aptitude tests
and assigned you specialties
to match your skills.
Frontline infantry.
I joined to make
recruitment films.
Well, you know
where you’re gonna get
good footage, don’t you?
Ooh, tell me.
Frontline infantry!
(crickets chirping)
Everyone got an
assignment but us.
I wonder what makes us
so special.
(laughing)
Gentlemen, I’ll be frank.
Never before has the Army
accepted recruits
with test scores
as low as yours.
That’s an odd way
to start handing out medals.
I’m not handing out medals!
But I am gonna give you
a special assignment.
The Army is conducting
war games,
and we want you
to play the enemy.
HOMER:
Don’t you get it?
They’re using us as patsies
to make the Army look good.
Are we that stupid?
Um, this avocado
just gave me a wedding ring.
So they’re not
shipping you overseas?
Nope.
I’m gonna stay here
and let them test
their laser-guided
super weapons on me.
Like that one.
(Marge gasps)
Don’t worry, Dad.
You’ll do great.
Okay, these are war games,
and I’m head of my team.
I have to think
like a great military leader.
Ah, stay crunchy
in milk.
I will!
Stay crunchy, men.
Stay crunchy.
This’ll be like shooting cats
off of Grandma’s sofa.
Oh, my God, I just remembered.
It’s Chinese New Year!
(whistling, explosion)
Gung hay fat choi!
(all groaning)
(screams)
Americans!
After them!
Sir, you can’t just
invade an American city
without
authorization.
I sure as hell can!
Congress
slipped it
into the National Broccoli Day
Proclamation.
I was wondering why you were
carrying that thing around.
I thought we were gonna have
a day off or something.
Think again.
Now, move out!
♪♪
Is this war?
No, sir, just
a simulation.
Whew, this pain feels so real.
Uh, it is real.
Oh. Guess I’d better
do my part.
(screams)
Bring it on, chumps!
(whimpering):
Fingers, fingers, fingers.
LENNY:
What you doing, Moe?
Drawing a wang
on Marmaduke?
Heck, no.
I’m challenging myself
with one of these,
uh, Sudoku games.
What, that
Japanese puzzle
in which no numeral
can be repeated
in a row, column, or box?
That’s how it works?
I was just drawing wangs
on the numbers.
(panting)
Moe, Moe, you got to hide us
from the Army.
The Salvation Army?
You got it.
Not that Army,
the one from Stripes!
Okay.
Thanks, Moe.
How can I ever
repay you?
Hey, some things mean
more to me than money.
Like a whole lot
of money.
Why did you just say
that sentence fragment?
Uh, it, uh--
long story.
(tires screeching)
War game’s over, losers.
Hey, they’s
using live ammo.
Well, what have we got?
Rise, my pretties.
Find our enemies
and capture their image
in your filmy fortress.
(whimpers)
I think we ought to
just go up there
and surrender.
I’m not gonna surrender.
You’ve seen what the US Army
does to prisoners.
How would you like
to be stacked naked in a pile
with a hillbilly girl
pointing at you and laughing?
That was
our last Christmas card.
Yeah, Marge always
loves your cards.
Well, you may not be
the smartest guys in the Army.
COLONEL:
Homer Simpson!
We have captured your unit!
We’re telling off-color jokes
and laughing as a group.
Come and join the fun bunch.
(sighs)
I’d give anything
to hear Homer’s voice.
(water running,
Homer shrieks)
HOMER: "H" means "hot"?!
(gasps)
(chuckles)
Stupid Army,
searching for me
with that giant helicopter
in the distance.
(gasps)
It’s not giant
and it’s not
in the distance.
It’s small
and it’s in our room!
(shrieks)
Predator drone!
(whimpering)
♪♪
(brakes screeching)
(birds chirping)
♪♪
This means war.
I thought
it was already war.
I hate you.
Attention, Springfield!
We are rounding up and detaining
all men who are fat or bald,
or have ever been amused
by the antics of Homer Simpson.
Excuse me.
I don’t belong here.
I am not bald.
I am balding!
Ugh, why will no one
honor the "ding"?
I honor the "ding,"
sir.
The hell are you
talking about?
Sir, maybe we should
just quit.
This operation has cost
over $50 million since lunch.
US government policy
is very clear.
Never back down.
Never admit a mistake.
That’s why we’ve won
over half the wars we’ve fought.
(sighs)
Mom, we’ve got to stop them
from pacifying our town.
Don’t worry.
I have
a secret weapon--
one more deadly
than any gun.
-Lisa’s face?
-A phone tree.
Huh?
Well, you’d
better hurry.
I don’t think Dad
can last much longer
where he’s hiding.
(coughing)
Dorothy’s daughter comes
every Sunday
and brings all kinds
of wonderful soups.
(annoyed):
Oh...
And Melvin’s son
brings a banjo.
And he works our names
into his songs.
(anguished):
Oh...!
Hello, Helen?
I’m calling about the recent
destruction of our town.
Well, I have a little plan
to fix their wagon.
(telephones ringing)
-Hello.
Hello.
Yes, Nelson,
of course I’ll help.
And a haw-haw to you.
So that’s the plan.
We’re meeting
at the reservoir at 8:00 p.m.
I flushed a potato
down the toilet.
Now we have to
live in a hotel.
Terrific.
Now call
Lindsay Naegle.
Marge, why did you
have us bring our liquor
to the reservoir?
We’re going to dump it in
the water to get the Army drunk.
Wow, uh...
this’ll be the first time
I ever watered down my booze.
(laughs nervously)
Moe, why are your
eyes darting back
and forth so much?
Oh, I-I’m just thinking
about a-a great tennis
match I saw once, yeah.
Uh, uh, now I’m thinking
about ping-pong.
A... ver-very fast chess game.
A... snappy David Mamet play.
What the hell...
happened to us?
I’ll tell you
what happened to us.
Y-You used to be cool and
then you got promoted.
I’m still cool.
Oh, really?
When’s the last time
we took the tank
and went down to
Hansen’s Point?
Just the two of us?
All right, all right,
here’s the plan.
We’re gonna take
a li-little nap,
and then we’re gonna wake up
fresh as daisies.
(snores)
Colonel, we’re here to discuss
the terms of your surrender.
Surrender?
Never.
Hmm, let’s see what
your hangover has to say.
(blows horn)
Great Cheney’s Ghost!
You win.
Colonel, I hope
you’ve learned
that an occupying
foreign force
can never defeat
a determined local populace.
Among the many things
we learned in Vietnam...
Horn, please.
(blows horn)
Simpson, you may have won,
but you still have to serve
the remainder of
your tour of duty.
All right,
but no combat.
Don’t you
worry, ma’am.
A man of your
husband’s ingenuity
can be put to
very good use.
Dudes.
Want to make
some extra spending money?
Get a free pair of boots?
Hey, baby,
you like obstacle courses?
Thinking it over, huh?
I’m cool with that.
Hey, pal, like the way
you handle that mop.
You like killing?
Hey, ladies.
Are you tired of waiting
for sanctions to work?
I know I am.
COLONEL:
Frontline infantry.
Absolutely frontline infantry.
Coast Guard!
Where do they find
these people?
Frontline infantry.
Lord...
Navy.
Have a seat.
Frontline infantry.
Where did you come...
Frontline infantry
was made for you.
Frontline infantry.
Lowest test score.
You make me sick.
Frontline infantry.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem