CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(beeping)
(squeals)
This place is looking
a little run-down.
Yeah, hasn’t
been the same
since they murdered
the Mayor’s dad here.
(dogs barking)
Ooh, a J.C. Penney’s...
used to be here.
(groans)
Now it’s a collection
of candle kiosks
and Persian CD stores.
How you doing, bro?
We’ve got the latest by Nabil,
Uma Shang Shang,
The Flower Song!
-(Persian music plays)
-♪ Uma shang shang ♪
♪ Uma shang shang,
uma shang shang ♪
Is like Bruce Springsteen
the Boss, ya?
-I guess.
-If you buy now,
I give you, uh,
toothache cream.
Toothache cream.
-Deal!
-We have deal.
(video games bleeping)
Where’s the beef?
You ain’t so bad.
These games are so old.
Who got these high scores?
Pilgrims?
Hmm, never saw this one before.
(coin clinks,
electronic beeping)
What’s going on here?
Am I destroying these triangles
or trying to assemble them?
What does this button do?
(moans):
Now my ship is pooping
more triangles.
(electronic chimes)
Oh, no, I won a free game.
(electronic beeping)
Ooh, gummy worms!
That candy’s been here
an awfully long time.
I’d think twice if I were you.
Don’t tell me
how many times to think!
(sloshing)
Mmm...
(humming)
You are not bringing
that thing home.
Then stand back.
(chomping)
This doesn’t taste
like I thought it would.
(continues chomping)
(sighs)
Well, if you’re through,
let’s check out that
discount book warehouse.
We already own a book.
MARGE:
Wisconsin From Above.
Veterans’ Day Parades.
Ooh, Smiles of Ireland!
Redheaded twins?
(groans):
Their mother must have
her hands full.
Hmm.
Cool, a carpenter’s library.
This doesn’t look easy,
but I’ll bet it is.
Well, I like the idea
of you as a handyman.
And I love the idea
of you reading.
Oh, yeah?
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah...
(gasps):
Ooh.
-Oh!
-Blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
-(excited moans)
-Blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah...
Okay, now you do me.
I never want
to go back to that mall.
There were eels
in the photo booth.
Eww!
Bart, here’s a letter
from your school.
A fire? I didn’t start a fire
in the teachers’ lounge.
I mean, what fire?
I mean, a letter from school?
Please elaborate.
Someone at your school
has a life-threatening
peanut allergy.
Cool! Who is it?
The letter doesn’t say.
But from now on,
no peanut products
are allowed on
school property.
Hmm, let’s see
what you’ve got.
Peanut butter
and jelly sandwich,
trail mix, starring peanuts.
Good grief, more peanuts!
(groans)
(engines revving)
NASCAR ANNOUNCER: Harley
Mozell is hit from behind
by J.T. Delacroix!
And Earl Tilleson!
Oh, and Buddy Rollette!
And the Pecker Brothers,
Danny and Dell!
And the ol’ Grizzly himself--
Weasel Johnson Junior!
Look at that carnage.
We are worse
than the ancient Romans!
(tires screech, crash)
Homie, don’t you want
to build something
with your new
fix-it books?
I did. I made
a foot rest.
Oh, don’t you have any
follow-through on anything?
What’s the point?
We’re all slowly dying.
(disgruntled groan)
(creaking, lamp breaks)
Oh, the floorboard
broke my nightstand.
Hmm...
(humming)
I did it!
What’s that strange feeling?
(gasps):
It’s "of accomplishment"!
(birds chirping)
Wow, Mom, you
made all this?
It’s like you’re
the Jesus of carpentry.
Aww, what a sweet
blasphemy.
This is a
valuable skill.
People might even pay you
to build things for them.
I could start my own
carpentry business.
I’m already arranging
the clip art
for the letterhead
in my mind.
(fanfare)
Perfect!
(knocking)
Can I help you, Miss?
I’m here to fix
your bookcase.
You answered my flyer.
Hmm, yeah.
-And you’re the carpenter?
-That’s right.
I see. Not that I have anything
against female carpenters,
but I have some pictures hanging
that you might find,
um... unsavory.
Goodbye.
A lady carpenter?
I don’t know.
What if you get pregnant
and I’m left
with half a hot tub?
And don’t tell me
you’re infertile.
I ain’t falling
for that again.
(groans)
It’s so unfair.
I’m as handy
as any man.
You sure are, sweetie.
I love this bed you made.
I guess people just
expect their carpenter
to be some fat guy
with his butt crack showing.
(snoring)
(suspenseful music plays)
Homer, your butt
just gave me
a brilliant idea!
Yep, it’ll do that.
"Simpsons Manly-Man Handyman"
at your service.
Ah, superlative!
Please install a doggie door
sized for a teacup poodle.
No problem.
Why don’t you go inside
and stir your Flubber
while I get to work?
Marge, the coast is clear.
(hums softly)
(gasps)
I’m terribly sorry.
I thought I heard
the sound of a
woman measuring.
Oh, uh, that was me.
You know that old saying:
"Measure like a girl,
hammer like a guy."
Yes, but you’re holding
your hammer backwards.
Oh, uh... you know
what they say,
"Hammer with the wood,
and it’s all good."
It’s all good.
All right, then.
(grunts)
(humming)
A dash of glue,
a turn of screw,
and a gazebo’s built that’s
perfect for two...
or more.
Uh-oh! Switch!
Eh... eh... eh!
And... done!
Mm-mmm!
Simpson, you’re
a master craftsman.
Listen,
what would you say
if I told you a woman
did most of the work?
I’d have this gazebo torn down
and built into a coffin...
-for your manhood.
-(shrieks)
Why did my hypothetical
scenario scare you so?
Uh, like all manly men,
I have a vivid imagination.
Well said.
Let’s take off our shirts
and wrestle.
(both grunting)
GROUNDSKEEPER WILLIE:
Okay,
give me all your peanuts,
Goobers, and Fluffer Nutters.
Oh, why should we have
to give up our salty snacks
just to keep one allergic kid
from exploding?
Who is this selfish jerk
anyway?
It’s not me--I swear.
I’m only allergic to honey,
wheat, dairy, non-dairy,
and my own tears.
(sobs)
Oh, no.
Call my allergist...
and my optometrist.
(all laughing)
Willie, you can tell me.
Who’s the mystery wuss
who can’t eat peanuts?
I’ll never say his name.
"His," eh?
Hmm, so it’s a dude.
Who says it’s a dude?
A principal can be a man
or a woman these days.
Hmm.
I’ve taken all the
peanut products.
Just like the English
took our sheep
and our women in 1291.
Then, they sent them back,
which was worse!
Yes, yes,
every day we go through this.
Why don’t you
just incinerate the contraband?
Will do, but first,
Willie gets his gob-full.
Careful
with those peanut crumbs!
My allergy is so sensitive,
a single molecule
would make my throat close
like a museum at 4:45.
(gasps)
Hello, Marge.
Picking up supplies
for Handy Homer?
It must feel good to know
that you’re "helping."
Oh, I help more than
you might think.
Sure you do.
You provide food
and sexual release
for your handy husband.
(grunts angrily)
Looks like
you broke something.
Better call Homer!
(both laughing)
(groans)
Of course I can make a credenza,
whatever that is.
Just give all the details
to my secretary Shirley.
This is Shirley.
Yes, fine,
he’ll be there tomorrow.
Goodbye.
That Shirley
is quite a gal.
-We should fix her up
with Barney.
-Homie...
I think you’re taking a little
too much credit for my work.
I mean, look at
your t-shirt!
Marge, giving me credit
was your idea.
Now, could you
rub my butt?
I sat on it so much
it’s a little sore.
Oh...!
Look, I’m sorry
you’re upset,
but if we tell the truth now,
I’ll be humiliated
in front of the whole town.
Then you won’t be married
to a man.
You’ll be married
to some kind of gay jellyfish
floating
outside the Florida Keys,
cruising for rich snorkelers.
You don’t want that.
I guess I don’t.
(sighs)
Bart, Skinner’s going
to be really mad at you.
Yes, you might say
he’ll "blow up."
(laughs evilly)
Whatever.
I’ve got some paper
to mâché.
(grunts)
Simpson!
Report to
detention at once.
Ah, I’m not a big fan
of detention.
You might say
it drives me nuts.
(gasps)
My allergen.
♪ Beat on the brat,
beat on the brat ♪
♪ Beat on the brat
with a baseball bat ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh-oh... ♪
"I’m a cootie eater.
I’ve been one all my life.
I like the cooties so much,
I have a cootie wife."
(groans)
Why does Lenny need
a windmill, anyway?
Ah, he wants
to grind his own corn.
Maybe it’ll finally shut him up
about the high price
of cornmeal.
Oh, switch.
(grumbling):
Oh, yeah,
switch, switch, switch.
Wow, great
job, Homer.
Yeah, and to think you
built this whole thing
with your own two hands.
Who do you think would help me,
my wife?
Your wife?
(scoffs)
Give me a break.
The only thing women can
build is credit card debt.
(both laughing)
Credit card debt.
(muffled yelling)
Homer, did you leave a power
drill on in your toolbox?
It’s making
this horrible noise.
Yeah, I hear it, too.
Maybe we can cover it up
by singing a fun song.
♪ We will, we will rock you ♪
(banging)
(banging to the beat)
♪ We will, we will rock you ♪
-(banging)
-(yelling continues)
♪ Buddy, you’re the boy
make a big noise ♪
♪ Playin’ in the street
gonna be a big man some day... ♪
I’m sorry, I’m sorry,
I’m sorry, infinity.
I never expected them
to climb on the cabinet
and ride it down the
biggest hill in town.
(groans)
Homer, it’s time
people knew the truth.
I’m doing the work
and I want the credit.
Look, I understand
that you’re mad.
Which makes now
the perfect time
to tell you the mayor’s
hired us to fix
the old Springfield
roller coaster.
(dramatic music)
By the way, nice job installing
this wall-chart bracket.
(loud whisper):
If the kids ask,
I did it.
(groans)
You’re gonna
have to fix
that roller coaster
yourself, ’cause I quit,
and I’m taking this with me!
(groaning)
Darn these countersunk
molly clamps.
(cats screeching)
This is not going
to end well.
Now, as I see it, the problem
with this roller coaster
is there are too many
boring going-up parts.
We need to replace them
with kick-ass going-down parts.
(men murmuring)
Oh, yeah,
going-down parts.
Uh, Mr. Simpson, shouldn’t we
begin by securing the struts?
Hmm...
Let me mull that over.
(Homer sobbing loudly)
What are struts?!
(wailing): Oh...
(sobbing):
Oh, I don’t know
anything about struts.
This guy’s all
bubble and no level.
So what? He’s paying
us 50 grand.
HOMER (sobbing):
And I promised these guys
money I don’t have!
And they’re gonna be so mad!
(sobbing loudly)
Ah, let’s go home.
Maybe I can sneak home
without them seeing me.
(grunting)
(screaming)
(sobbing loudly)
(sloshing)
(British accent):
Are you ready to be
lightly assaulted?
(laughs maniacally)
(bats squeaking)
(screaming)
(groans): Oh.
Mm.
(sing-song):
Good morning.
(groans)
I brought you breakfast in bed.
Ugh!
Eat it.
(clears throat)
Excuse me.
I’m supposed to stand
in your store window
and breast-feed
Bilbo Baggins.
Your cowering suggests that
Bart has found your kryptonite.
Kryptonite?
What’s that?
The "ite" suffix
suggests a mineral.
I do not know whether to laugh
or cry at your ignorance.
I shall laugh. Ha-ha!
Kryptonite is Superman’s
greatest weakness.
Wait, maybe Bart
has a kryptonite!
Perhaps.
But for now, you may
suckle your Baggins.
(muffled):
I’ve got you now, Bart.
Mm-hmm.
(groans): Hmm.
(making siren noises)
(sobbing)
Dad, here’s
a thought:
If you just gave Mom credit,
maybe she could help you.
Sweetie, you
don’t understand.
If I can do this myself,
then all those lies
I told will be true.
Don’t you want
Daddy’s lies to be true?
I’d like a daddy who lived
in the real world.
To Daddy,
the real world
gets fainter and fainter
every day.
(groans)
Good morning, Seymour.
You may be wondering
what I’m doing with
this hat full of maggots.
Actually, I’m not
wondering at all.
Simpson, you’ve been
waving your nuts in
my face for too long.
Eat shrimp and die!
No! I’m allergic!
Stick-on-stick.
Just like the
knights of old.
No one teaches me history!
(dramatic music playing)
♪♪
-Peanut?!
-Shrimp?!
Either of us falls
in, we’re doomed!
Kids don’t die!
(both screaming)
I... was... El Barto.
No...!
(applause)
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
honored guests
and out-of-town
roller coaster weirdoes.
(ascending gasp)
(screaming)
Your father’s finally
gonna get exposed
as the credit-
stealing fraud he is!
(sighs)
Perfect.
I give you...
the Zoominator!
ALL: Ooh...
And now to get stinking drunk!
(loud creaking and rumbling)
(crowd gasping and shouting)
I’m not getting
married on that!
You won’t get married
on Colossus,
you won’t get married
on The Zoominator,
on The Pharaoh’s Curse.
Just say it-- it’s me!
Oh, no, baby, no!
Dad!
Put aside your selfish male ego
and tell the truth!
Sure, I’ll tell them the truth.
The truth is...
that I’m perfect and everything
I touch is perfect!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, my God,
he’ll kill himself!
(gasps)
He’ll never hear me say,
"I told you so!"
I never felt safer!
(whimpering)
Uh-oh.
Oh, why must we preserve
America’s historic
roller coasters?
(whimpers)
(screams)
(Homer screams)
(both scream)
Thank you, honey!
Everyone!
(voice wavering):
My stupid male pride
made me lie to you.
Everything I claimed... I did
was actually built by Marge!
ALL: Aw...
Homer, I was
pretty upset with you,
but in the
end, I... I...
-I-beam!
-(crowd gasps)
HOMER:
Avenge... me.
(sighs)
Marge, I realized something
when I was trapped
under all that rubble:
Marriage is the real
roller coaster.
I’m just glad I have
you as my safety bar.
Oh, I forgive you,
my darling.
Get well.
As for you,
young man,
the next time you
save your principal,
try not to risk
your own life.
What kind of lies
are you feeding her, Simpson?
Mind your own beeswax!
(grunts)
(dramatic music playing)
-(grunts)
-Ow!
(both grunting)
Ow.
(sighs)
I’m gonna go look
at the new babies.
(grunting continues)
♪♪
(gagging and coughing)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem