CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
("Pop! Goes the Weasel"
playing)
(music stops)
(moans)
(kids laughing
and chattering)
Otto, Bart won’t
give me a seat.
You know I can deal
with your problem
or I can rock out.
But I cannot do both.
(singing to music):
♪ We’re an American band ♪
♪ We’re comin’ to your town ♪
♪ We’ll help you party down ♪
♪ We’re an American band... ♪
(whines):
Otto, help me.
(music stops)
Fu-u-u-u... nk.
(groans)
(birds chirping)
What am I hearing now?
(gasps)
Nature?
The ultimate bring-down.
Why...
(grunts)
was I...
born?!
BART:
Don’t worry, dude.
We’ll hook you up
with some tunes.
CHILDREN (singing):
♪ Old McDonald had a fart ♪
♪ Fart, fart, fart,
fart, fart ♪
♪ And on his fart
he had a fart ♪
♪ Fart, fart, fart,
fart, fart. ♪
That’s not a song.
Real songs are about
deals with the devil,
far-off lands,
and where you’d find smoke
in relation to water.
Mister driver?
One of my bus mates
has purloined my French horn.
Why can’t you talk
like a dude?
Oh, knock it off, Kearney.
Why are you still in
this school anyway?
We were in third
grade together.
Stupid school
doesn’t know how to teach me.
♪ The farts on the bus
go round and round... ♪
(making farting sounds
to music)
Oh, wow, this is
about 90% less funny
than you think it is.
-W-Wait... the radio.
-(farting)
That’ll drown ’em out.
-(disco music playing)
-(groans) Disco?
-(gentle music plays)
-Easy listening.
-(country music plays)
-Country Western?
-(slow music plays)
-World music?
-(R & B music plays)
-Urban smooth?
-(jazzy salsa music plays)
-Salsa fusion?
-(radio shuts off)
-(moans)
(gasps):
Metallica?
(tires skidding)
Am I on drugs?
Yes, you are,
but that really is Metallica.
Now if you’ll excuse me,
I’m late for a gumdrop parade
on Foo-Foo Island.
(laughing)
What’s up, Metallica?
Need a lift?
We don’t take rides
from strangers.
I’m no stranger.
Remember this?
Metallica ru-u-u...les!
Oh, yeah,
Springfield Arena, 1997,
Row XX, Seat 64.
I was about to quit the band
when I saw your lighter.
You saved me
that night.
So what are you
waiting for? Hop in.
(chuckles):
Hop in what?
(tires screeching)
Look at me, I’m Otto.
I’m a hundred years old,
and I drive a school bus.
(Bart laughing,
tires squealing)
Oh, man.
Maybe me and Metallica
can go splitsies on a cab.
(engine accelerating)
Hey, loser, we got a ride
from a real fan.
I used to sleep
with Lars’s grandmother.
Never listen to
our music again.
(playing
"Master of Puppets")
(music continues)
Bye-bye, take care,
watch your step,
eat my shorts,
have a good one.
She’s all yours, dude.
Oh, and I think
I ran over a moose.
This is for every bus driver,
-lunch lady,
-(Bart cries out)
gym coach, hall monitor...
Otto.
Are you meting out
corporal punishment?
-Can’t... talk... now.
-(Bart cries out)
I’m spanking a child.
You are temporarily suspended
from bus driving, with pay.
No...!
Hand in your beaded
seat-cover.
And your gun.
MARGE:
I hope you’re happy, Bart.
Thanks to your hijinks,
I have to drive you and
your friends to school.
Let me drive.
I go through yellow lights.
One more crack out of you,
young man,
and I’m showing everyone
your baby pictures.
(Bart gasps)
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Carpool!
I brought my own car seat.
Look.
(panting excitedly)
Hey, Lisa, my safety bar
matches your eyes.
(laughing)
Carpool, Nelson!
Just a sec, I’ve got to finish
my science project.
(squeaks, chitters angrily)
(chitters)
Whoa.
"Squirrels don’t like rocks."
Okay, just one more
kid to pick up.
Ew, it’s Michael.
That weird kid who
never says anything.
He’s so gross and stupid.
BOTH: Hi, Michael.
Hi, Michael.
Hey, dork, you’re sittin’
on my shadow.
Sorry.
What, you’re too good
to sit on my shadow?
Aw, I forgot my math book.
No problem, I’ll just drive
up to your house and get it.
(tires squealing)
NELSON:
Whoa.
Your mother must dance
at the nicest strip club
in town.
Michael, my son.
Here is your book,
and never forget:
the divisor
goes into the dividend.
Yes, Papa.
BART:
That was Fat Tony.
Your dad’s a mob boss?
(nervous laughter)
Please don’t have me whacked.
I was just kidding around.
We were all having fun.
Wasn’t it fun?
(nervous laughter)
Oh, fun is so fun.
There is no Mafia.
Columbus Day
is better than Christmas.
(all chatting)
(kids gasp)
KIDS (whispering):
He’s Fat Tony’s son!
His dad kills people!
His daddy putted bullets
in my daddy.
My daddy had to potty
in a bag.
Ah, look at
all this puke!
Why did I come in
on my day off?
Oh, Fat Tony’s lad!
(grunts)
God bless you.
(playing slowly
and discordantly)
Oh, stop, stop!
Who’s the out-of-tune idiot
on third clarinet?
That’s me.
I p--you didn’t
let me finish!
I... from now on you’re
not third clarinet,
you’re first
everything!
Now if you excuse me,
I’m brewing tea
and I have to go jiggle
my bags!
You’re sitting
with me?
I’m not afraid of you.
Well, you shouldn’t be.
I’m not like my dad.
I understand.
I’m not like my dad either.
Oh.
(crunch)
Ew!
There’s a triple-A battery
in my macaroni and cheese!
It counts
as a vegetable.
I can’t eat this.
You know,
I cook a little.
Maybe I can make
you something.
All we need is some
fresh ingredients.
Well, you’re not going
to find any here.
(wind howling, ghost screaming)
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
get in the bowl.
Dandelion greens,
a sprig of wild dill,
fresh blackberry
juice for dressing.
It’s delicious!
Are you just
saying that
’cause you’re
afraid of my dad?
No, it’s great!
Ooh! Except for the bee!
It’s good
to see you laughing!
(car screeches to a halt)
You could make
a great chef someday.
(sighs):
My dad wants me to go
into the family business.
Which is, uh...
"waste management."
(grimly):
We are going for a ride.
(all scream)
By which I mean the carpool.
Perhaps we will get yogurt.
(all sigh in relief)
(grimly):
Now who wants to sleep
with the fishes?
Because I brought
this Finding Nemo bedspread.
(sigh in relief)
FAT TONY:
The Calabresis!
My archenemies
in waste management!
♪ I woke up this morning ♪
♪ I got myself a gun. ♪
Milhouse, may I borrow
your three-ring binder?
"Garfield" or "Love Is?"
Uh, I prefer the cat.
He hates Mondays.
We can all relate.
(all sigh)
(blaring horn)
-Eh.
-Not that bad.
BART AND LISA:
Mom!
I apologize for
my tardiness.
I "ran into" some
old acquaintances.
On the surface, that sounds
perfectly pleasant.
Papa, can Lisa and her family
come over for dinner?
We’d love to!
You know,
I’ve never met your wife.
Sadly, my Anna Maria was whacked
by natural causes.
Oh, you’re a widower.
I bring flowers to her
grave every Sunday.
Ooh, flowers every week!
I wish I was dead.
(doorbell rings)
Welcome to my home.
(gasps)
Must have cost
a fortune.
Actually, you can really
keep costs down
when you don’t pay
for materials or labor...
or permits...
or land.
Wow, your paintings
have brush marks.
(gasps)
And your statues have wieners!
Your words honor
my family.
In the words
of the old country:
Mangiare, i miei amici!
(chuckles):
He’s talkin’ like the guy
in Fat Albert.
(imitating Mushmouth):
Howba areba youba?
Homer!
D’oh!
(imitating Mushmouth):
Whyba youba doba thatba?
Boss, the Calabresis are
here for the sit-down.
The sit-down’s tonight?!
Again this Palm Pilot
has failed to remind me.
I believe this needs to be
hot-synced.
What are you doing?
I thought you meant
"hot-sync" it.
You know how it is with us--
everything means kill.
Sit-down item
number one:
your recent murderous overtures
with regard to my person.
We meant no disrespect,
Fat Tony.
We were simply trying
to kill you.
When we saw you driving
that carpool,
we figured you’d gone soft,
and were therefore whackable.
You’d be fools to kill me
for my son, Michael,
would take my place.
And wreak a terrible vengeance.
I made soufflés!
(oohs and aahs)
I’ve tried to make those, but
they always end up as brownies.
You said you meant
to make brownies.
Any other lies?
(chewing loudly)
Mm...
Oh, this must be
what angels taste like!
Oh, Michael,
one bite of this soufflé
and your father will realize
your gift deserves to flower.
Why can’t you
do anything?
So, we are at
peace once more.
Let us indulge in exaggerated
displays of affection!
This guy, I love him!
Get over here!
My brother,
over here!
You’re my everything,
You color my
world, over here!
Over here.
Over here, over here.
Papa, I brought
you some dessert.
(all chewing loudly)
My God, this is like
a lap dance for my taste buds!
Ah, yeah!
The flavor
just drove my sweet tooth
to a vacant lot
and whacked it.
Hey, kid, what bakery
did you boost these from?
Well, actually,
I made them.
Papa, I want to be a chef.
(laughter)
A chef, huh?
Hey, look what
we got here.
It’s Chef
Boy-ar-gay!
What’s he gonna do
if we rub you out,
serve our soup cold?
(laughter)
Well,
gazpacho is served cold.
So take that.
(laughter)
Hey, Tony,
catch you later.
Your kid’s got a
bright future--
catering
your funeral.
You know what I like?
Those little
baby hot dogs.
Do they small down big ones
or do they make ’em different?
Michael, you have
made me appear weak
in the eyes of my enemies.
Fat Tony, it’s
not important
what other people
think of you.
What matters is how
you feel inside.
(screams, groans)
Papa!
♪♪
Your father’s gonna be
absolutely fine
in about three months.
But for now, he can’t talk,
write, or blink.
(laughs)
With Fat Tony
doing the morphine mambo,
the Calabresis are gonna try
to put him down for a dirt nap.
Dirt nap, eh?
Hmm...
(snoring)
Homer,
our house is on fire!
-Help me save the children!
-(kids screaming)
Sorry, Marge,
can’t hear you!
(laughing)
What am I gonna do now?
Kid, the only way you’re
gonna live to grow shprazoot
on your abonjoola is if
you take your dad’s place.
Let’s go.
Hey, can we go by
the Lexus place?
I want to test drive
that new hybrid.
You are a hybrid:
half idiot, half moron.
Whoa!
Where did that come from?
I don’t know
what to do.
This is all
my daughter’s fault.
But I’ll make it up to you.
Bart and I will run your
business till your dad’s okay.
Well, what do you know
about being a mob boss?
Everything!
And I learned it all
from the greatest
gangster film ever:
Shark Tale.
This guy in here
owes us money.
Leave him to me.
Ow!
I hurt my fist and my palm.
I thought you guys
were looking out for me.
Ow!
(sobbing)
All right, tap jockey,
you owe Fat Tony 50 bucks.
Cough it up!
Look, Mister,
I-I don’t got the cash.
My clientele--
they’re all bums.
They never pay!
(grunts)
Just get the money!
Homer, the mob is putting
the screws on me, see.
I ain’t getting killed
’cause you won’t pay your tab.
Now give me 50 bucks!
(whimpering):
Take it, take it!
Just don’t hurt me!
Okay, pretty boy, where’s
Fat Tony’s 50 bucks?
Look, all-all I got is 25.
I swear! I swear!
It’ll do for now!
(humming)
(laughs nervously)
Hey, hey,
it’s Fat Tony’s crew!
How’s the big guy doing?
I sent flowers, but you
probably didn’t get them.
You know florists.
(chuckles)
Glug, glug.
Krusty, Fat Tony hasn’t
received his weekly payment
for keeping McDonald’s
and Burger King out of town.
Well, I’m a little short
this week.
Could I just pay you $5
to keep out Hardee’s?
-(punches landing)
-KRUSTY: Ow!
My schnoz! My punim!
My pupik!
(punches landing)
My genechtagazoink!
(Krusty groans)
(horn honking)
Homer, where’d you get
that truck?
Uh, it-it fell off a truck.
Uh, you know, a truck-truck.
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
Where’d you get that?
Eh, it fell off
a truck-truck truck.
(horn honking)
(brakes squeal)
MARGE:
Homer, Helen Lovejoy never
returned my casserole dish
from the church potluck.
Could you pick it up?
No problem.
I’ll be back in ten minutes.
Hi-diddily-ho, mob-areenos!
(sighs)
I, uh...
I got your, uh, phone bill
in my mail by mistake,
and, uh...
I-I’ll just pay it.
(laughs)
(both laughing)
Dad, you want I should
plug him in the ankle?
You monster!
Just cut his Achilles tendon
with this knife.
(both laughing)
Bart, Mr. Simpson,
we are getting out of
the mob business, right now.
But this is
the only life I know!
I’m sorry.
I just can’t live with myself,
seeing you this way.
-Can I still talk with my hands?
-I’m afraid not.
-What about with my ears?
-No.
(groans softly)
My friends,
I surrender.
I’m handing over
all my father’s territory,
in exchange for the safety
of my family and the Simpsons.
Sorry.
We can only guarantee
we won’t hurt them.
Yeah.
You know, they’ve still got
to eat right and exercise.
Walk the dog
once in a while.
He’s a furry little
fitness machine.
Well said.
As for me, from now on,
my only business is cooking.
You did the right thing, Mikey.
You weren’t cut out
to be a wise guy.
But you, you got
a future in this business.
Call me.
Thanks, but I’m going
into bootleg DVDs.
(chuckling)
It’s so great that Michael’s
doing what he loves.
And I can stop
looking the other way
from what my husband’s doing.
Lady.
Man.
(leeringly):
Lady.
(sighs)
(all grunting and choking)
(men groaning)
I want to be buried
next to my wife,
under that bridge in Jersey.
(sniffs, gasps)
Someone poisoned
these meatballs.
Homer?
Hey, if I poisoned them,
would I be doing this?
(groans)
This is a chef’s
worst nightmare.
I won’t be using
this recipe anymore.
Well done, my son.
In making peace
with our enemies,
you were able
to take them down.
Perhaps you and I are not
so different after all.
Papa, I’m just
glad you’re okay.
Now get some rest.
Why didn’t you tell him
it was an accident?
It was an accident, right?
Michael?
Don’t ever ask me
about my business, Lisa.
Michael?
Vroom! Vroom! Vroom!
MICHAEL:
Vroom! Vroom!
(continues making
engine noises)
♪♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem