CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D-oh!
(screams)
(tires screech)
HOMER:
Whoo-hoo!
Mom, Bart’s drinking
coffee!
It’s not coffee,
it’s hot Pepsi.
MARGE:
You’re the worst
husband in the world!
HOMER:
Yeah, well, I wish I’d
married Patty and Selma.
I wish I’d married
Lenny and his friend.
Man, Mom and Dad
are really going at it.
I hope everything’s okay.
MARGE:
Don’t you spit
sunflower seeds at me.
HOMER:
You used to love it!
Mm...
(chuckles)
Recording that fake fight
was a great idea.
Now the kids won’t bother us
during our morning snuggle.
Dear Lord, thank you
for the physical intimacy
we are about to enjoy.
And as always,
have fun watching.
BOTH:
Go... lovemaking!
Mm...
HOMER:
And I hate the cutesy way
you make jack-o’-lanterns!
I like scary Halloween,
not funny Halloween!
(tape player clicks)
♪ I been through the desert
on a horse with no name ♪
♪ It felt good to be out
of the rain ♪
County fair music?
(Homer giggling)
MARGE:
Whoo, whoo.
Milhouse,
steady my Duds.
Trust me, Bart.
It’s better to walk in
on both your parents
than on just one of ’em.
NELSON:
Hey, dinks, give me
your lunch money!
But what will I eat
at midday?
I can’t solve
all your problems.
Just hand over the money.
Thanks, wads, and I hope
to see you both Saturday.
BART:
Huh?
Come to my party or die.
(grunts)
-Come to my party or die.
-(grunts)
I hate Nelson’s parties.
He makes you look
at his baseball cards
and tell him they’re good.
They’re not good.
I don’t like him.
I’ll bet Nelson
won’t even have gift bags.
Unthinkable!
Is that legal?
Wait. What if nobody goes?
He can’t kill all of us.
He’s right. Individually,
we are weak like a single twig.
But as a bundle, we form
a mighty faggot .
(all exclaiming)
Well said.
If we all stand together,
Nelson’s helpless.
Hell, no,
we won’t show.
(all chanting)
Hell, no, we won’t show!
Hell, no, I won’t mow!
Willy, you’re fired
with complete loss
of pension.
Damn it!
You actually convinced people
not to go to Nelson’s party?
Yep, he’ll be all alone
on his birthday.
Oh, I wish
I could see it.
Boo-hoo, I’m Nelson.
No one likes me.
Bartholomew J. Simpson,
how can you be so mean?!
What are you
going to do about it?
Hey!
I’ll whack you with
the whole salad set
if you don’t start
thinking about others.
You are going
to that party.
Mom, I can’t go!
No one else is.
Well, if no one else
jumped off
the Empire State Building,
would you not jump?
Kind of...
Aw, come on, Bart.
The party will be fun.
Nelson’s not bad.
All he needs
is a little kindness.
(laughs)
Lisa, you’re never gonna
get a husband
by being sarcastic.
All right,
no husband.
You’re getting
a husband!
And you are going
to that party. Hmm? Hmm?!
Dad, don’t make me go.
I’ll give you
a back rub.
(grunting)
(moaning)
Oh, your elbow’s like
an angel’s kiss,
but you still have to go.
Why?
Son, we all have
to do things
we don’t want to:
like have jobs and families
and responsibilities
and having to be Mr. Funny
all the time.
You think I wouldn’t rather
be living nude in the forest
like some ancient pagan,
just dancing around
playing the pan flute?!
And here we are.
(tires screech)
Okay, just walk in, say "happy
birthday" and get out.
Whoa!
This party doesn’t suck.
Pizza, that’s a nice touch.
Uh-oh,
do I hear a dial tone?
’Cause this party
is off the hook!
(laughs)
What up, B?
(grunts)
Um, happy birthday,
Nelson.
Uh, I know it seems
a little quiet.
Must be a lot
of traffic today.
Is Highway 88
backed up?
Oh, yeah,
it’s a parking
lot out there.
Of course,
that explains
everything.
Stupid Highway 88!
(chuckles weakly)
(grunts)
(air hissing)
-Huh?
-Whoa!
Hi, kids, my spidey sense
is tingling.
Tingling because it’s
a certain someone’s birthday.
Yeah!
Uh, where are
all the kids?
They’re coming!
They are!
I love you, Spidey!
Uh, listen, I only got
ten minutes of material.
Maybe I should come back
a little later.
Don’t go.
My party peeps are en route,
I swear!
Nelson,
nobody’s coming.
But how could
nobody come?
I ordered them to.
Well, that’s the thing.
Sometimes you can be
kind of a jerk.
True...
but I thought
I had some friends.
Maybe you can have fun
with just me.
Okay. Why not?
Stop having fun, kids.
I’m Dr. Octopus
from Marvel Comics’ Spiderman.
I’m inventing a ray
that turns birthday presents
into homework.
Yah!
Come on, Bart.
Let’s knock him down.
(both grunt)
(both laughing)
(grunting)
Wait, I have an idea.
(both exclaiming)
Look at our kids,
playing like champs.
Yeah. How’d you afford
this kickass party?
Carnival ride
hit me on the head.
Hmm...
So how was
Nelson’s party?
Not bad.
We had pizza, cake
and then sang songs
with Nelson’s grandma.
But it was
a one-time thing,
and now I’ll never
see him again.
NELSON:
Hey!
It’s my birthday bud!
Yeah, yeah, it was,
uh, super fun.
Good times.
Hey, Ralph,
have I got
half a sandwich for you.
Bart, where you going?
I saved you a seat,
best friend.
(gasps)
Ha-ha!
Hey, best friend,
I got you a present.
An entire case
of pool cue chalk.
Huh? Huh?
We can make the tip
of anything blue.
Um, Nelson,
I was just thinking about us
being best friends.
Whoa! Me, too!
We are so connected!
Look, um, I don’t have
time for new friends.
I got a lot
on my plate.
I’ve got a big report due
on the Nile River--
topic sentence,
bibliography, page numbers--
it’s nuts.
-(grunts)
-Dude...
You made me get water
on my cheek.
(grunting)
Bart is my best friend now,
which means no one
picks on him ever again.
Okay! Okay!
I forgot
how cool Bart was.
-Yeah, he’s awesome.
-Good guy, good guy.
Isn’t he?
I’ve known him for years,
but I ran into him at a party
and we really clicked.
That’s right, we’re
best friends now.
So why don’t you go pick on
someone smaller and weaker?
Good idea!
Let’s go over
to the Sunshine Preschool
and wail on toddlers.
Yeah, we’ll jump ’em
while they’re napping.
MARGE:
Homie...
Huh...?
When you’re done putting
Lisa to bed we can, uh...
finish what we started
the other day.
Woo-hoo!
Marital sex!
Okay, tucked in tight,
glass of water,
nightlight on,
no barn owls,
don’t do drugs,
love you, good night.
Dad, can’t you read me
a story for a little bit?
But your mother
smells like coconut.
(groans)
Okay, sweetie, which
book should I read?
Angelica Button and
the Dragon King’s Trundle Bed.
It’s the ninth book in
the Angelica Button series.
Oh, yeah,
this is that fantasy book
that even grown-ups like.
Broken,
lonely grown-ups.
"Chapter One: The Ruby Stone
in the Door-Portal".
Are you asleep yet?
No.
(sighs)
"Angelica trembled
as she looked up at
the stern but wise whiskers
of Headmaster Greystash..."
(British accent):
Angelica Button,
you are a mere Earthkin.
What business have you
with the Merlinical Council?
I bring warning!
The Minister of Niceness,
Lord Evilton,
is not what he appears!
Preposterous-sss!
Foolish Earthkin!
Send her to the sorrow
mines of Mount Purgatorium.
No!
(gasps)
Lisa, wake up.
They’re taking Angelica
to Mount Purgatorium.
Oh, Dad, I’m tired.
We’ll read more tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
But she’s in trouble now.
I’ll just read ahead
without you.
No! We have to read
it together.
Oh, of course.
Whatever you say, sweetie.
Nighty-night.
(snoring softly)
(straining)
(snoring)
NELSON:
I like to come up here
and make fun of the sunset.
Hey, gas ball,
you suck!
Nelson, do you ever wish
you weren’t a bully?
Mm, sometimes.
But it’s not up to me,
it’s who I am.
I mean, a shark can’t stop
swimming or it’ll blow up.
Man...
I never knew you were so deep.
Here, this is for you.
(gasps)
A Nelson vest!
The sleeves were
torn off by wild dogs.
BART:
From then on, my life changed.
♪ He’s a rebel and he’ll
never, ever be any good... ♪
All of a sudden,
I was a somebody
in a school full of nobodies.
I could go anywhere,
do anything.
For us, to live
any other way was nuts.
♪ That’s no reason why I can’t
give him all my love ♪
♪ He’s always good to me,
always treats me tenderly ♪
♪ ’Cause he’s no rebel,
no, no, no ♪
♪ He’s no rebel,
no, no, no, to me... ♪
(chuckles):
Ah....
Ah.
(snaps fingers)
So, Scotty,
how do you like school?
(high-pitched voice):
Closed!
(laughing)
BART:
Life was perfect.
Lisa, I’m home!
Time for me to read to you!
Lisa’s sleeping
over at Janey’s.
Apparently, her mom makes
good mac and cheese.
WOMAN (British accent):
Homer? Homer.
You must read ahead.
Fiction is your passion!
Lady, you’re nice,
but I’m married.
Just read the book,
you shaved ape.
(grunts)
Ow! I can’t read ahead.
I promised Lisa
I wouldn’t.
Just take a peek at the title
of the next chapter
and see if you can resist.
"An Unexpected Occurrence"?!
What could it be?
(laughs)
We hooked him, Galahad.
Yes, quite.
HOMER:
"Angelica was trapped in the
Suffoclock of Sandy Doom..."
(whimpering)
"...as Headmaster Greystash
fought a battle to the finish
with dark wizard
Maluicious Krubb."
Time to choose, Greystash.
If you save Angelica...
you die!
(muffled shouting)
(grunting)
Goodbye...
Angelica.
Greystash.
(sobbing):
He killed Greystash!
Thanks for the spoiler
there, big mouth.
-Hey, Bart.
-Milhouse.
Bart, why are you hanging
around with Nelson so much?
He’s a bully.
Hey, don’t use
the "B" word around me.
It’s offensive.
Yo, bully.
What up, my bully?
How come they
can say it?
(sighs):
They just can, okay?
It’s weird to see you
as somebody’s sidekick.
Whoa, Bart Simpson
is nobody’s sidekick.
Then why are you
wearing that vest?
Because my chest is cold
and my arms aren’t.
I see.
Then I suppose you
can just fly kites
with whoever you want,
right here in front
of everyone.
Come on, Bart.
Throw the dork a bone.
Hmm...
All right, I will.
(both laughing)
Blue and red,
the colors of friendship.
Huh.
(angry grunt)
Hey. Huh! Huh!
(groans)
(panting)
You’re late.
I was waiting
to smash this frog with you,
and it peed in my hand.
(croaking)
Sorry. I was, uh...
stealing loose grapes
at the grocery store.
Really?
You call this
stealing loose grapes?
We were just having fun.
Don’t get upset.
Oh, right.
Stupid Nelson always gets upset.
He’ll probably do
something stupid--
like smash his own camera!
(grunting)
Look what you made me do!
Nelson, get in here!
The cat’s eyes are runny,
and I need you to dab ’em.
Coming, Ma!
See you later,
lying traitor!
Something in your eye,
Mr. Mooch?
Well, there’s something
in my eye, too.
(sobs)
Ma, what happened
to the curtains?
I made ’em into a dress
for karaoke singing.
Hey, Bart, do you want
some ice cream?
(whispers):
I just hit a major
marshmallow vein.
Oh! I think it goes
all the way to the bottom.
-No, thanks.
-What’s wrong?
Me and Nelson were
best friends,
and now I think
he’s gonna kill me!
Bully problem, eh?
You know what they say--
all bullies are cowards.
It’s not true-- they’re brave,
’cause they’re strong.
(groans)
(yells)
Bart, we need to talk.
(grunts)
I feel so bad about
freaking out on you.
It’ll never happen
again, I swear.
Um... okay.
Best friends?
Forever?
No!
I can’t do it.
You’re a nut bar,
a whack job!
A kooka-dooka!
Please, just
leave me alone.
Best not to get
involved.
Agreed.
(whimpers)
Looks like you’ve
made your choice.
Make sure your affairs
are in order.
I’ve set up a trust.
It bypasses the inheritance tax.
Only till 2008.
Look into it!
(sobbing):
Oh...
Oh, Greystash...
Greystash!
Oh, hello, Lisa.
Come on, Dad, read
the last chapter.
Everyone says there’s
a big surprise.
I bet Angelica discovers
that she’s a wizard.
Uh... how would you feel
if something bad happened
to Greystash?
It would be the day
my childhood ended.
(screams)
Come on, read, read!
(whimpering):
Mm... mm...
"Angelica was trapped
in the Suffoclock
of Sandy Doom..."
Time to choose, Greystash.
If you save Angelica,
you die!
Why are you stopping?
We’re almost
at the happy ending.
HOMER:
No book is gonna make
my daughter sad.
Time to do what I do best--
lie to a child!
"Greystash looked Krubb
right in the eye and said..."
Mustache power:
activate!
("Stars and Stripes Forever"
playing)
(kisses mustache)
(roars)
Oh, man, I can’t believe
you beat me, but you did.
I somehow escaped
from the hourglass!
And now,
to go on living!
(laughing, cheering)
The End.
Is that really how it ends?
What happened
to the Merlinical Council?
Uh... they went
to Star Wars Land
and fought star wars.
Dad, you can read
to me anytime.
HOMER:
Now Lisa won’t know about death
till it strikes
someone close to her.
Eh... Dad’s ending is better.
Okay, field-trippers,
welcome to the Springfield
Tide Pools,
nature’s most fecund
ecosystem.
Who will spot
the playful abalone?
The mighty winkle?
I think it might be you, Sherri.
(gasps)
Now, remember, these pools
can be dangerous,
so everyone pick a buddy.
Bart’s my buddy.
Good boy, Nelson.
Squeeze him extra
tight for safety.
Ah...
We sure are far from
the rest of ’em.
(nervous chuckle)
Funny how that
happened, huh?
-Come with me.
-(Bart whimpers)
(grunts)
Nelson, please
don’t kill me.
Remember when we made
fun of Cinco de Mayo?
I called it "Stinko de Mayo."
We laughed so hard.
Bart...
you are a bad friend.
S-Say again?
You never liked me for me.
You liked that I protected you
and gave you a vest
and stole milk boxes
for you.
I hate milk!
It comes
from cow wangs!
There you go again.
You act all nice,
and then you go crazy.
Well, maybe
I get jealous.
But it’s just because...
I never had
a best friend before.
Um, Nelson, was the water
always up to our necks?
(water rushing)
Nelson?
Help! Help!
Put this on.
Where did you get it?
Dude gave it to me.
(inhaling)
Aah! Man lips!
KIDS (chanting):
Skinner loves Bart!
Shut up! I’m just
giving him CPR,
the kiss of life.
And if anyone loves Bart,
it’s Nelson.
Where is Nelson?
I’m sorry, Nelson
never woke up.
-What?!
-Never woke up,
because...
he never passed out--
he’s right over there.
(musical grunting)
Hey, thanks
for saving me, man.
Course I saved you--
you’re my field trip buddy.
And nothing else.
You mean...?
Exactly.
You’re barf to me now.
(musical grunting)
(sighs):
Oh, Nelson...
I’ll never forget that week
we were best friends.
(lilting Western
musical theme playing)
Haw haw!
I touched your heart!
(slurps)
(loud sobbing)
Greystash!
Gee, you’re really upset
about this Greystash thing.
Don’t say his name.
In your mouth,
it sounds like dirt!
Homer, it’s just a book.
No man should outlive
his fictional wizard.
No man!
(sobbing)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem