CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(Marge shrieks)
-(rapid gunfire)
-(whimpering, shrieking)
(organ plays softly)
(sobbing, sniffling)
So, how did
Malt Liquor Mommy die?
Stop calling her that.
I'll tell you
how she died.
You know that sign that says
"Do not stand up
on the roller coaster"?
-Yeah.
-She overdosed
right in front of it.
Oh. Class all the way.
Marge, could
you let it go?
You won. She's dead.
Mm-hmm.
We are here
to mourn the tragic loss
of Amber Pai Gow Simpson,
a gifted cocktail waitress
who hoped one day
to learn computers.
(chuckling)
Amber said she wouldn't let
her eighth-grade education
stop her from
achieving her dreams.
And yet, it did.
Bart! Do you want
to leave the funeral
early?! Do you?!
Yes. Of course.
CARL:
"You were Homer's wife
for a two-day spurt
Your name was Amber,
just like the alert..."
(paddleball caroms)
MARGE:
Bart, put that away!
Thanks a lot.
I lost my place.
Um... Ah, here it is.
"The End."
(scoffs)
(growling)
-Uh-oh.
-(glass crackling)
(choking)
(gasping)
Everyone relax, huh?
I know the Heimlich.
I learned it
a few years ago.
It was 1997,
and Titanic was proving
unsinkable at the box office...
(choking)
(loud choking)
Somebody do me!
(choking)
(grunting)
Whew!
(gasps)
(all choking)
(grunting, coughing)
(laughing)
Your son is
out of control!
You've raised
a savage beast!
Yeah! Put a leash
on him, lady!
Oh...
First, let me assure you
that Bart's antics
are perfectly normal
for a seven-year-old.
Actually, he's ten.
Oh, dear.
Dear, dear, dear, dear, dear.
Spare us your
medical mumbo jumbo.
Just give us the pills.
Clear-cut his brain
down to the nub.
Mr. Simpson,
it would be easy for me
to pour drugs
down your son's throat...
Thank you,
Doctor. Marge?
But for Bart,
I'm going to prescribe
a more unorthodox treatment.
Cymbals... snare...
high hat... tom-tom...
sticks, mallet and brushes.
This is a drum kit!
Drumming demands energy
and concentration,
one of which Bart has,
and one of which Bart needs.
(skillful drum playing)
Homie, look.
He's enjoying it.
(syncopated annoyed
grunts, D-oh's)
I've never seen
him happier.
(drumming to
"The Hardest Button to Button")
(drumming to song continues)
Whoa! Trippy!
♪ We started living
in an old house ♪
♪ My ma gave birth,
and we were checking it out ♪
♪ It was a baby boy
so we bought him a toy... ♪
(clattering, song stops)
Hey, kid, why don't
you watch where
you're drumming?!
Sorry, White Stripes.
No hard feelings?
Let's kick his ass!
(song resumes)
(drumming)
(screaming)
(skillful drumming)
Oh! Why couldn't
he give up this
like he gives up
everything else?
I know!
I'll use that
white-noise machine
I got you
when your father died.
(crashing waves)
(shouting):
Transport yourself to the shores
of Nova Scotia,
where cod and halibut
frolic in...!
He's just drumming louder!
So it's a noise war
he wants, huh?!
Then I'll throw in some
rush-hour traffic!
(screeching tires,
horns honking)
And a circus fire!
(people screaming
animals roaring)
(shouting):
Sleep tight, my angel!
Oh...
What?!
(shouting): Oh!
Oh! Let me know...
when and if
you want sex, honey!
(drumming, traffic,
animal noise continues)
(drumming continues)
Oh, he's gotta fall asleep
sometime, doesn't he?
(drumming)
(despairing moans)
You guys
need a break.
Why don't I take Bart with me
to the children's bebop brunch
at Jazzy Goodtime's?
Is it in
a safe neighborhood?
-(drumming louder)
-Just make it happen!
Boy, get dressed!
You're going
to a jazz brunch
as punishment for all
the racket you're making!
I thought you wanted me
to drum.
I'm sending you
mixed messages.
Now, get the hell
outta here.
I love you so much.
Damn you!
(blows kiss)
(playing jazz tune)
(applauding)
What it is, hepcats?
You want me to
scat-sing the menu?
Absolutely not.
Oh, God bless you, sir.
Hey, Bart, you want
to jam with me?
Okay. If you give
me your omelet.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm a professional musician!
(playing "Take Five")
♪♪
Not bad for
a newbie, Bart!
You just may be
the second-best
player up here.
In case you're wondering
who the best one is, it's me.
Ah! Crazy man, crazy!
Oh, yeah!
(rattling)
(indistinct talking)
(gasps)
They're looking at me!
All right, Lisa, time to show
these jazz legends
how we swing in the suburbs.
(wailing on sax)
That's a wrap, kids.
Now go have
some Jazzy Bread.
(whispering):
That's bread that fell
on the floor.
-Mhmm.
-MAN: Excuse me.
Are you Lisa Simpson?
(gasps):
Yes, I am.
I'm, uh,
Defonzo "Skinny" Palmer.
This is Marcus
"Marbles" Le Marquez.
Pleased to meet you.
We were about
to play a quick set,
-and we were
wondering if you...
-Yes?
-Lisa Simpson...
-would do us the honor...
-Yes!
-of sitting in...
-(gasps)
that chair in the audience.
We wanna jam
with your brother.
(shocked gasp)
(playing upbeat jazzy tune)
♪♪
Look! Bart's onstage.
And he's contributing
to the entertainment!
(cheers, applause)
Yeah!
I was jamming
with Skinny Turner
and Marbles Le Marquez!
And they want me
to join their trio!
Whoo-hoo! What's next?
A contract with
Groove-tone Records?
Take the G-train, baby.
Groove-tone!
(grumbling):
Oh, I can't believe it.
Stupid brother...
Lisa, why aren't you
smiling with us?
'Cause I've wanted to jam with
jazz musicians all my life.
How would Bart like it if I
just hopped on his skateboard
and instantly became great?
Ah... whoa...
(yells)
Mild! Mild! Mild!
Mild! Mild!
(grunts)
(groans)
Lisa, you've got
to be more careful.
I need you to teach me
all about the world of juzz.
It's jazz! Jazz!
(sobbing)
You don't even know
the name of the thing
you are stealing from me.
(chuckles):
Bart, you're so steady
on those skins,
we're gonna call you "Tic Tock."
Oh-- I always
wanted a jazz nickname.
Fine.
We'll call you, uh...
Downbeat.
'Cause
you're bringin' us down.
(groans):
That is the most unfair...
Downbeat, Downbeat,
please.
We're shootin' the breeze
with Tic Tock.
Oh, man, I am so juzzed.
Bart, a rising star like
you needs a manager,
and Gil's your guy!
Oh, I'm a jazz daddy
from way back.
With the skit-skat
skittily boom-de-boom,
and the ding-dong daddy...
Is that jazz?
That's jazz, right?
Cha-cha-cha
with the curly fries.
Hey!
Oh, son.
I like you more, now that
other people like you.
It's mergatronic, Daddy-Ho.
Bart, does that
even mean anything?
Xavier Cugat!
(plays drum flourishes)
(crowd applauding)
Bossie, the music business would
chew you up and spit you out.
You just keep your eyes
on the prize, girl.
(chainsaws whirring)
(suspicious moo)
Mom, I'm gonna lose it.
Bart's on the cover of both
local jazz magazines:
"Blowin'"
and "The Sugar Sheet".
Here's the only thing I've
been on the cover of.
(sobbing)
Mm, look, uh, how 'bout
we go to the pound,
and get a puppy
just for you?
(stops sobbing)
That might work.
(dogs barking)
Oh, they're all so cute.
Yeah, you know
what's even cuter?
Picking one without
talking to me.
Well, I kind of like this guy.
(barks weakly)
(coughing)
Oh, but this one is precious!
(panting)
(hacking)
(yipping playfully)
(yipping)
Okay, this little guy's
coming home with me.
Who's gonna get neutered
tomorrow?
You are! Oh, yes you are.
(eerie tones playing)
Lisa Simpson...
you doomed me.
(gasps):
I did? How?
By choosing the cuter puppy.
You picked looks over
personality,
youth over experience,
no history of rabies over
unknown rabies status.
And now I'm going to die.
I never wanted
that to happen!
(ghostly):
You suuuuuck! You suuuuuck!
(scratching)
Ah, thanks, sweetie.
You suuuuuck!
Well, if you want him,
you can have him.
And if you
get tired of him...
I won't get tired of him.
It's just too bad
you can't take ol'
Smiley here.
(whimpers)
Yeah, he'll be in God's
Dumpster tomorrow.
I'll take him, too.
And I'm gonna put
ol' Henry here to sleep...
because he knows
my darkest secret:
I like putting
animals to sleep.
(sighs)
I'll take him, too.
("Little Green Bag" plays)
♪ Yeah... ♪
♪ Lookin' back on the track
for a little green bag ♪
♪ Got to find just the kind
or losin' my mind ♪
♪ Out of sight in the night,
out of sight in the day ♪
♪ Lookin' back on the track,
gonna do it my way ♪
(musical interlude plays)
(song fades)
Okay, guys.
No one knows you're here,
so be quiet.
And if you get hungry,
there are rats living in
the Christmas decorations.
(squeaking)
And then today at lunch,
Lenny and I went to the park
and rented a rowboat.
Carl sketched us
from the bank.
Summer days...
(growling, shrieking,
trumpeting, barking)
What are
those noises?
They sounded
zoological.
(shrieking,
trumpeting, growling)
Shut up!
(gasps):
I just said "shut up."
I'll punish myself
by going upstairs.
Bart!
What are you doing here?
Uh... not smoking reefer.
Uh, that's right.
We all not
smoking reefer.
(growling, yelling)
(screams)
No, Buttercup! No!
(yells):
My arm!
It hurts where
the tiger's biting it!
(gasps)
Bart, that was
a nasty bite you got.
You'll recover...
but you'll never drum again.
Says you.
(moans)
I was a great drummer,
and now I'm nothing,
just like Phil Collins.
I feel so terrible.
I just wanted
to save those animals
while Bart
became a drummer,
but I never thought the two
stories would intersect.
And what about my new job
as a Mexican wrestler?
Beware of Taco Belly. Whoo!
Eat your heart...
(gasps)
No mas! No mas!
(elephant trumpets)
Uh, yes, I would like a bird
because I'm often
lonely in the lab.
(moans)
Birds help.
See, Lisa.
We're making progress.
(gun cocking)
Drop the marsupial!
If those animals aren't gone
by midnight tomorrow,
Animal Control is
gonna round 'em all up.
And kill 'em.
(engine struggling)
(sighs)
Can I, uh, can I
borrow that ostrich?
Sure.
How cool is this?
(laughs)
I guess that's it.
These animals
are all gonna die.
Not if I can
help it, Lisa.
Do you have an idea?
Uh, no. Sorry if it
sounded like I did.
(jazz playing)
Hey, guys,
great news.
I can drum again.
Sorry, Tic Tock.
Your tick is on...
but your tock is gone.
Well, I've got
a confession to make.
This right arm...
it's not mine.
Whose is it?
I don't know.
Tic Tock, maybe you
could get yourself
some of that sweet, sweet...
what do you call it?
Arthroscopic
micro-surgery
to reattach
the ulnar nerve?
Yeah, that's
the jingle.
The doctor did say
surgery might help,
but it costs $78,000.
Well, I bet we
could raise it
with a benefit
concert. Huh? Huh?
Outta sight!
In the pocket!
Groovay, groovay!
Now, you boys know
you don't have
the follow-through
to put something
like that together.
Somethin' like what together?
A benefit concert!
Benefit concert!?
Outta sight!
In the pocket!
Groovay, groovay!
Oh, this benefit concert
is gonna be Scooby Dooby.
I'm very happy for you, Bart.
(sighs)
Why are you sad?
Thinking about your marriage?
If we can't find
a home for those animals,
they'll be put to sleep.
Your sister's very upset.
Oh... I feel weird.
It's like a potato
chip full of shame,
going down
my throat sideways.
Honey, what you're feeling
is called "empathy."
Oh... now I'm gonna
learn a new word.
"Empathy" means
you're looking at Lisa
and feeling what she feels.
Your sister poured her heart
into rescuing those animals
to forget the pain of
being upstaged in jazz,
and now...
(moaning)
How can I end this torture?!
You could do
something nice for Lisa.
(agonized moan)
You're my mother.
How can you say that?
(moaning)
(drums playing)
(playing jazz tune)
(cheering)
Hey, hey! We got more jazz
superstars on the way, folks!
Gooey Martin, Willie Mimms,
Drop Jaws Turner,
Sketch Friendly, Tootsie
Childs, Sammy Biltmore,
No-Talent Jones,
Anwar Benitez, Bossy Marmalade,
Bad-Check Mazursky,
Ray-Ray Takamura,
Shaky Premise,
Bootsy Croutonne, Richard Sakai,
The Pre-Marital Sextet,
C.S.I. Miami, D.W. Jitters
The Chubb Group,
Cantaloupe St. Pierre,
and many, many, more
funny names!
(laughs)
And it's all to fix
this very talented arm.
Ow!
Oh, right,
the nerve damage.
Here's
the benefit money,
Now I'm gonna go vomit
to keep my weight down.
That's right.
That's how Krusty does it.
(feeble laugh)
I wanna thank everyone
for this special night.
Jazz folk may have
the smallest apartments,
but they also have
the biggest hearts.
(cheering)
But the biggest heart I know
is in my sister Lisa.
(audience gasps)
WOMAN:
What about me...
...Tootsie Childs?
Lis, you poured your heart
into rescuing society's most
vulnerable critters-- animals.
So I want all the money
we've raised tonight
to go to building...
The Lisa Simpson Home
for Abandoned Animals!
(gasping)
Oh, Bart, thank you
so, so much!
(cheering)
You know
what we should do?
Hold a benefit concert.
Outta sight!
In the pocket!
Groovay, groovay!
Hey, am I still married
to your sister?
Naw, she died.
♪♪
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem