(thunder rumbling)
(wind howling)
MAN (gasps):
Whoa!
(grunting)
(groaning)
(squeaking)
Hello, boils and ghouls.
I am the Crypt Keeper,
or should I say
master of scare-i-monies?
(laughs)
(laughing)
Priceless, sir.
You made the word
"ceremonies" frightening.
I know what I did.
(scoffs)
MOE:
Hey, can we get going here?
Listening to you two is
more torture than the torture.
(grunts)
Actually, no, this is worse.
Although the right nipple spike
seems a little dull.
(grunts)
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that’s barbaric.
Whoa, look at that!
My blood’s a genius.
Fancy Roman numerals
and everything.
Look!
A shooting star!
Hey, that’s great.
Let’s look at it after.
Whoa!
That almost tore
my head off.
Oh, you always find an excuse
not to make out.
Whoo! A space marshmallow.
Where do you think
you’re going?
Dad, no!
It could teach us the secret
of interstellar travel.
If he’s so smart, how come
he can’t stay out of my mouth?
(grunting)
How could you
eat that goo?
You don’t know
what galaxy it’s from.
Marge, I ate it. It’s over.
Whoa. Oh, no, you don’t.
(snorting)
If I can keep down Arby’s,
I can keep down you.
(hooting)
(stomach rumbling)
(zombie-like):
Must eat, then poop,
then eat some more,
then eat while pooping.
(wind whirring)
(panting, grunting)
Still hungry.
BART:
Dad?
Son, let me have
a lick at you.
(both grunting)
Homer!
You won’t eat
my stuffed peppers,
but you’ll eat our son?
Nag, nag, nag.
(gasping for air)
(yowling)
Is that the cat?
Uh, no, just gas.
(grunting)
(meowing weakly)
Food. Ooh. Food.
(grunts)
Ooh!
(gasps)
Ooh, teenagers.
Mmm. Oh...
No, today’s teens
have enough problems
without me eating them.
Barbeque sauce fight!
(all squealing)
Oh, I gotcha!
(screaming)
The flames are sealing
in my juices.
I’ll savor you.
(gasping)
(all screaming)
Mmm. Extra-virgin.
(gurgling)
(screaming)
Tell my friends I died
kissing a girl!
No.
(gasps)
Ooh. Beer-battered Germans.
(overlapping chatter)
(crowd gasping)
What did we Germans ever do
to deserve this?
Oh, right.
Must eat more fat people.
Thank God I’m in America.
(to the tune of
"Baby Got Back"):
♪ I like big guts ♪
♪ And I cannot lie ♪
♪ Double chins
with the chafing thighs ♪
♪ When a dude walks in
with the hanging jowls ♪
♪ My stomach starts to growl--
I’m gettin’ hungry ♪
♪ So I masticate,
chomping on the overweight ♪
♪ I eat fat people for days ♪
♪ Like potato chips
by Lay’s ♪
♪ Try to eat just one,
but it can’t be done ♪
♪ I’ve got to eat a ton ♪
♪ Baby likes fat ♪
♪ Baby likes fat. ♪
(laughs)
I used to think these shirts
were just for fat slobs.
(gunshots on TV)
It’s blob rule on the streets
of Springfield.
And to make matters worse,
we’re also being attacked
by a 50-foot Lenny.
Everyone’s paying attention
to Homer.
CARL:
I still like you.
Thanks, Invisible Carl.
(screaming)
Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm.
FLANDERS:
Hi-de-ho, Bloborino.
Eh. Mm.
MAN:
Homer?
Hmm?
-I need to talk to you.
-(gasps)
Dr. Phil McGraw!
You’ve got a weight problem,
and you know it.
You’re right.
Starting tomorrow,
no bread before dinner.
Homer, don’t sell me an outhouse
and tell me it’s the Taj Mahal.
Yeah, Homer,
stop doing that.
It’s time to open up
a can of honesty.
You’re thinking about eating me
right now,
aren’t you?
Aren’t you?
That’s ridiculous,
talking fudge.
Homer, your family’s here.
And you got to help me
help them
help you help me
help you.
Marge, I missed you.
All this eating has put me in
the mood for a little lovin’.
(purrs sexily)
I have to be
honest with you:
I can’t love
a 4,000-ton cannibal.
What happened to "for better
or for worse?!"
Dad,
you’re eating Dr. Phil.
It’s amazing.
He tastes
just like Jeffrey Tambor.
(grunting)
Food does not equal love!
Marge, to keep you in my life,
I’d do anything.
There must be some way
to turn my problem
into a positive
for the community.
BOTH: Hmm...
Hmm...
In you go, boys.
We’ve got everything--
warm beds, square meals,
homeless women.
(all clamoring)
I got a bad feeling
about this, Blue.
(sniffs)
(yelps)
Get in there.
(screaming)
Nice to be indoors, isn’t it?
♪♪
Finally, I’d like to announce
that starting Monday,
this show will be
broadcast in HDTV.
Here’s how I’ll look.
-Eh?
-(kids scream)
That’s right:
look at your hero!
(laughs)
Good night, everybody.
Aren’t you coming, Bart?
Nah, I’m gonna go
backstage and complain.
This Krusty Brand alarm clock
sprays acid in your face.
-(acid fizzes)
-Oh!
You already
showed me before!
Whoa, Krusty’s
prop room.
Cool! It’s that clown car
all those midgets drowned in.
Wha..?
(gasps)
Hey, kid.
This ain’t a museum.
That’s a museum.
For kids, $49 bucks.
Krusty, what’s that monster?
It’s the Golem of Prague.
(thunder crashes)
Legendary defender
of the Jewish people,
like Alan Dershowitz,
but with a conscience.
(chuckles):
I kid Alan. We’re friends.
Anyway,
back in the 1600s...
a rabbi created
this magic creature out
-of humble clay.
-(potter’s wheel squeaks)
The golem would perform
any task
that was written on a scroll
and placed in its mouth.
♪♪
(thunder crashes)
(crowd gasps)
(gunfire)
Now he works for me.
So the wife says,
"I don’t have to pay for it.
I put it on my charge plate."
You suck, clown!
You made my lady cry!
(grunts)
(crowd screams)
♪♪
"Come to my house
at midnight."
Now if you’ll excuse me,
I have to rehearse
my "Desperate Houseflies"
sketch.
Buzz, buzz.
Ooh, here comes
that sexy young garbageman.
(chuckles and sighs)
I’m gonna need
a shoebox full of blow
to get through this dreck.
(footsteps approaching)
(groans)
Bart,
there’s something
I have to tell you
father to son.
I passed out on your turtle
and killed it.
Someday you’ll thank me.
Hey, Milhouse.
(gasps):
It worked!
Now, there’s
something I’ve wanted
to do for
a long time.
Can’t you read
my writing?
I didn’t say kick
Homer’s "walls".
What’s goin’ on?
-Ow!
-That’s better.
(thud)
Yo, Simpson.
Give us your
lunch money.
Mmm... I don’t think so.
In fact, why don’t you give me
your lunch money?
Well, who’s gonna
make us? That golem?
No, my go--
Yes, him.
(screaming)
Finally, someone who
does whatever I say.
Hey, Bart,
I shaved my head
like you told me.
-Get lost.
-Yes, Master.
Bart,
did your mystical
Jewish monster
beat up those bullies?
Oh, it’s always
the Jews’ fault.
Hmm, well I think your golem
doesn’t like hurting people
and I’ll prove it.
"Speak."
(monstrous groan)
(coughs)
Finally, I can talk!
This is the voice I’ve got?
Sounds like I should be selling
egg creams in Brighton Beach.
That’s what we call
Jewish humor.
You don’t have to understand it
’cause the words sound funny.
Meshuggeneh. Hilarious.
Hello? Huh?
It’s funny, believe me.
Do you feel bad
about what you did?
Of course I feel bad.
My stomach feels like
it’s hosting
the Chabad Telethon
and Norm Crosby’s going long.
(retches)
"Kill the czar"?
Now that’s an old one.
Hey, boy, where’s
your mud buddy?
I have a little job for him.
(sinister laugh)
Oh, he was driving me crazy,
so I sent him on an errand.
(screaming)
Skinner! Just let him
kill you already.
That’s the man I was
telling you about.
(Skinner screams)
Skinner!
I wish we’d been closer.
Get him out
of here, Willie.
You’ll make better mulch
than you did a man.
I may be bifurcated,
but I still have feelings.
I feel so guilty. I’ve mangled
and maimed 37 people
and I told a telemarketer
I was busy when I wasn’t.
I’m not a good man.
He sure is neurotic
for a monster.
The cure to any
man’s problems
is a good relationship.
Hmm.
Yeah, get him a woman.
That’ll end his misery.
(laughs)
(groans)
Ow, ow!
This hurts so much.
Just write a scroll
asking him to stop.
Writing’s for nerds.
Ow!
You got
a surprise for me?
The surprise would be
if I found
some good live theater
in this town.
Then people could
have some drinks,
watch Fiddler. Very nice.
Will you shut up.
(gasps):
Is she for me?
Hanukkah came early this year,
which it sometimes does.
Hello, everybody.
(nasal laugh)
Ugh! What’s with this outfit?
It looks like a lion ate
a parrot and then threw up.
(nasal laugh)
-Well, back
to the drawing board.
-No!
What are you? Nuts?
She was made for me.
I now pronounce you monster
and whatever you are.
Shayna punim.
Not so fast.
You’re wanted for the murder
of Seymour Skinner.
Oh, come on, Chief.
We’ve got a latke
bar downstairs.
Latkes?
What the hell are those?
They’re pan-fried...
-Case dismissed.
-Wonderful!
(glass breaks)
♪ Gloomy Sunday ♪
♪ With shadows
I spend it all ♪
♪ My heart and I have decided
to end it all... ♪
I don’t get it.
What’s so "Great"
about this Depression?
Well, I like how
everything’s sepia-toned.
Makes me feel
all nostalgic.
I never thought it
would come to this
when I fought in the
first World War.
"First" World War?
Why you keep
callin’ it that?
Oh, you’ll see.
♪♪
ANNOUNCER (over radio):
We interrupt this dance music
from the Meridian Room
in Capital City’s
fabulous Hotel Hitler
to bring you
a special bulletin.
Hey, I’m not done dancing.
This bulletin better swing.
Reports are coming in of giant
metal cylinders landing
on the outskirts
of major American cities.
(screams)
Cylinders?
Astronomers say
the ominous capsules
originated from Earth’s
closest neighbor.
Flanders?
Mars.
So, it’s a war of the worlds.
Good thing we got the sun
on our side.
Go ahead and hide, you coward.
I’m in the small town
of Grover’s Mill.
where a crowd has gathered
around one of the strange
Martian cylinders.
It’s opening.
A tentacle is emerging.
(kids scream)
Settle down, children.
Have a cigarette
to calm your nerves.
Oh, my stars.
It’s firing a beam
of pure energy.
(laser buzzing)
It’s burning people alive.
(people screaming)
Okay, boys, we’re
under attack.
Let’s drive ’em out of town
the way we did with the Irish.
Hey, I’m Irish.
Oh.
Oh, wait, I’m Polish.
The devastation is incredible.
They’re grinding up
the bodies of human beings.
(grinding)
Now they’re riding horses
in the rain.
-(clip clop)
-(water falling)
Now they’re playing
the xylophone
while bowling near
an airport.
Now, before we all die,
one last selection from
the Nathan Newley Orchestra.
(singing):
♪ I’m young and healthy ♪
♪ And you’ve got charms... ♪
Gee, Mr. Welles,
this sure is a swell show
you’re puttin’ on
for the folks.
Well, I just hope our
saucy little radio prank
will give these "folks," as
you call them, a giggle, a gasp,
and provide a good lead-in
for Misters Amos and Andy.
(people screaming, gunfire)
Burn everything.
You know, Homer,
we haven’t actually
seen these aliens.
That’s alien talk.
"Big Band Stu,"
says 23 Skidoo.
Ooh!
(a la Franklin D. Roosevelt):
We have nothing to fear
but the aliens and their vastly
superior killing technology.
Boys, we have to assume
our guns are useless.
Throw ’em in the lake.
Good. Now, the
police car.
Wait, did you
get my sweater
out of the front seat?
Uh, yeah.
-Well, where is it?
-(sighs)
I’ll go get it.
Wait, I have an idea.
The Martians are
only killing humans,
so we should pretend
to be animals.
Ingenious.
Everyone, remove your clothes
and wallow in filth.
(braying, meowing,
and barking)
-(meowing)
-(mooing)
(animal noises continue)
(clucking and meowing)
(barking)
Bow-wow.
What is everyone doing?
We’re outsmarting the Martians.
(braying)
Martians?
You do know that radio broadcast
was a hoax?
Moo?
Yeah, it was an Orson Welles
radio play
of War of the Worlds.
See.
-(sighing)
-(muttering)
I’m proud of what I achieved
during my rioting.
It was either kill him
or kill no one.
(Kang laughs)
Foolish Earthlings.
Now is the perfect time
to strike.
They’ll think
it’s another hoax.
(grunting)
Dad, a flying saucer
blew up that statue.
Lisa, that was
just a radio show.
Uh, Paw.
Please, you must believe me,
this is no hoax.
This is a real invasion.
Oh, yeah? Why don’t I just
punch you in the nose, Bud?
"Nosebud."
Chief, you’ve got
to alert the military.
Fine, fine,
I’ll do it right now.
(rings)
US Army. What’s the threat?
Uh, we’ve been invaded...
by a pompous, radio ham.
How’s it feel when the hoax
is on the other foot?
I must admit it’s unpleasant.
You fool.
You’ve doomed us all.
Eh, tell it to the Great
Gildersleeve.
(screams)
Well, they didn’t
eat the skin.
It’s--that’s healthy.
Colonel Kang, your report.
Uh, well...
the Earthlings continue
to resent our presence.
(explosion)
You said we’d be greeted
as liberators.
Don’t worry.
We still have the people’s
hearts and minds.
I don’t know.
I’m starting to think
"Operation: Enduring Occupation"
was a bad idea.
We had to invade.
They were working on weapons
of mass disintegration.
Sure they were.
♪ I don’t want
to set the world ♪
♪ On fire ♪
♪ I just want to start ♪
♪ A flame in your heart ♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
(screaming)
Enhanced by Fotokem