♪ ♪
KIM: Oh, hey, guys.
It's Kimberly.
Remember me? It's been a minute.
Did you miss us?
KHLOE: Get it. (Whoops)
KIM: 'Cause we missed you.
KOURTNEY: I didn't come to
play, hos. KIM: But don't worry.
You didn't miss anything.
KHLOE: Baby on board!
(Kourtney chuckles)
KIM: Not much has changed.
KHLOE: Are you obsessed
with being a mom?
KYLIE: Yes, I am.
KIM: We've been keeping a low
profile. Been nicer to our mom.
KRIS: Do I look fat?
KENDALL: Yeah.
KIM: And my sisters and I are
closer than ever.
KHLOE: Don't, stop...
KIM: You don't do (bleep)!
KOURTNEY: You're just (bleep)
a bitch.
KIM: Get the (bleep) out of
here and go.
Get the (bleep) out of here
and go!
It's like we can communicate
without speaking.
KHLOE: Shut the (bleep) up!
What is up your ass?
KOURTNEY: (bleep) like, no!
She pushes and pushes.
I'm not up for it!
KIM: I'm just not taking her
(bleep) anymore.
She's the least exciting to look
at, so she can be out.
KOURTNEY: Really? Have you
(bleep) looked on the Internet?
Do you see what people say about
me compared to you?
KIM: And we're still one big,
happy family.
KOURTNEY: We are a disgusting
family, and I'm ashamed to be a
part of it.
KIM: She doesn't want to be a
Kardashian anymore.
KHLOE: She could shove
"Kardashian" up her (bleep)
vagina. SCOTT: Am I not invited
because Kourtney wants to bring
her new boyfriend?
KRIS: We can't just have him
for 10 years as part of our
family... he's still part of our
family.
KENDALL: What about my dad?
KHLOE: Don't start with the
bull(bleep) now and the fake
(bleep).
KIM: Just do anything that
you think will get a check.
KHLOE: Have fun living up
Kylie's asshole.
♪ ♪
MJ: So beautiful.
KHLOE: There's a lot of cons
going into this family, but the
pros outweigh them.
MJ: Yes, I know.
(chuckles) KIM: Are you ready?
Then let's begin.
Can you keep up?
♪ ♪
KENDALL: I love how fancy
this is.
KRIS: Hi! >> KOURTNEY: Hey.
KRIS: H-Hey.
YOUNES: Hi, how are you?
KRIS: Hi! Mwah!
YOUNES: Oh, there she is.
KIM: Oh, my gosh, this is so
cute! Hi. LONG-HAIRED MAN: Hi.
KIM: I'm so excited you're here.
LONG-HAIRED MAN: Me, too.
Y-You're very skinny, holy crap.
KIM: Really?
LONG-HAIRED MAN: Yes.
GUESTS: (overlapping chatter)
SLENDER WOMAN: Hi!
KIM: Hi.
Thank you guys for coming.
SLENDER WOMAN: Of course.
KIM: We're celebrating my
37th birthday.
I can't believe I'm 37.
You know, I'm really
looking forward to this year
coming up.
We're expecting our daughter
soon, Khloe is just pregnant
and wanting to spend more time
in Cleveland, and so she's not
at my birthday dinner,
but it's totally fine.
KOURTNEY: I swear Khloe's
hormones are insane.
KIM: I feel like you guys are
not vibing.
KOURTNEY: No, we're not.
KIM: You think she's, like,
being a bitch?
KOURTNEY: No, she's not being
a bitch, she's just being
sensitive.
If I don't write back,
she's like, "You're not
responding."
If I don't do this,
she's like, I don't know.
KIM: But, like, you know what
it's like to be pregnant.
Like, just give her a break,
you know?
Like, it is what it is.
KOURTNEY: Khloe and I, the
last, like, six months, have not
been as close.
I just feel like I'm constantly
being criticized and picked on.
KHLOE: Stop talking about
these trips, then, if you don't
want to say who you're going on
the trip with.
That's so (bleep) stupid.
KOURTNEY: Okay, so shut the
(bleep) up.
KOURTNEY: Produce a show,
like a... some kind of, like,
interior show.
KHLOE: Okay. KOURTNEY: What?
KHLOE: Well, this already
sounds like too much of a
commitment for you.
KOURTNEY: In the past, I used
to just brush things off, but I
just don't want to tolerate it
anymore.
KRIS: Okay, you guys, I want
everybody to raise a glass to
Kim.
I love you very much.
And you're the best mommy.
KIM: Thank you.
KRIS: You're the best wife.
KRIS: And you're my favorite
daughter tonight, for the...
Until midnight.
KIM: It's fine.
We've all come to conclusions
that it's Kylie now,
and I'm okay with that.
(laughter)
I had a good ten-year reign.
KRIS: Happy birthday, Kim.
GUESTS: Happy birthday!
(guests whooping) ♪ ♪
KIM: Ew, the dog peed. Kourtney.
KOURTNEY: Peed? KIM: Right here.
KOURTNEY: This ottoman, like,
needs to be cleaned on a daily
basis. KIM: Um, so you know what
I've decided, and I'm not taking
no for an answer?
KOURTNEY: Huh?
KIM: We are going to do our
c... our family Christmas card
this year.
I know it sounds good in theory,
and blah, blah, blah,
and, "Oh, yeah, sure,
we'll do it."
That's what everyone's gonna
say.
But we have to, like, really
take this seriously.
KOURTNEY: So, did everyone
agree?
KIM: I mean, so far I only
asked Mom, and she just doesn't
want to do the planning.
We just need a family.
Christmas card. KOURTNEY: Yeah?
I don't disagree.
KIM: I tried to do it before,
you guys didn't like it.
So, like, I have a good
photographer, a good concept.
I'll rent out a studio, I'll
make it so easy for everyone.
It's really important to
me that our family does a
Christmas card this year because
last year we didn't do one, and
it's been a tradition for so
long.
It's one day out of our lives
for the year.
We have these memories
forever.
It's just something fun that
we can all do together.
Do you like this contraption?
KOURTNEY: No...
KIM: Try it, it, like,
massages your fingers, 'cause if
you text too much...
KIM: Okay, so I'm gonna call
Khloe.
KOURTNEY: I just have a lot
going on right now.
But I'm down to do the shoot.
KHLOE: Hello?
KIM: (gasps) Hey, Khlo.
KHLOE: Hey, Keeks.
KIM: So, I think that we need
to make memories with the kids
and do a family Christmas card.
We have to do a photo shoot
that's not for a magazine.
Like, we need to capture these
moments. KHLOE: I'm totally down
to do one. >> NORTH: Mama...
KHLOE: I just think getting
everybody together is gonna be
a challenge.
KIM: Okay, I'll... It will be
a challenge, but I will plan it.
NORTH: Mommy, I have one...
I will get it on
everyone's schedules.
Okay, one second, sweetie.
KHLOE: No, totally, I'm down
for whatever, I'll be there.
KIM: Who wants a family.
Christmas card?
PENELOPE: Not me.
KIM: Me.
KOURTNEY: I knew you were
gonna say that!
KIM: Okay, me and Northie
will do it together.
NORTH: And Lovey and Lovey
and Lovey! >> KIM: And Lovey.
Should we have MJ? NORTH: Yeah.
KHLOE: Well, this is fun, you
guys.
I can't wait for this
photo shoot... I'll be there.
KIM: Okay. I'll let you know.
KHLOE: Okay, love you!
KIM: Okay, bye. ♪ ♪
(paparazzi chatter excitedly)
SCOTT: Lotta action going on
here.
KIM: Hi. >> SCOTT: Hi.
KIM: How are you? SCOTT: Good.
KIM: I'm getting my lashes done.
I won't get up, I'm like
Mariah Carey on the couch.
SCOTT: Okay.
No, I don't-don't blame you.
KIM: Oh, my God, Kanye told
me that he saw you and your
girlfriend at Nobu... how funny.
SCOTT: Oh, I saw him at
dinner the other night, yeah.
KIM: Yeah. He told me.
SCOTT: Small world.
KIM: Such a small world.
D-Do you ever find yourself
in a moment where you're like,
"Grow up"? >> SCOTT: With her?
KIM: Yeah. SCOTT: Not at all.
KIM: That's cool. SCOTT: Yeah.
KIM: I was thinking, like...
SCOTT: I feel like she tells
it to me.
Honestly, everything's been
going pretty well lately.
This is the first time
I've ever been with anybody
other than Kourtney, so it's
definitely different, but it's
been a really good thing for me.
KIM: When Kendall and Kylie
were hanging out with your
girlfriend 10 years ago,
who'd have ever thought, like...
If you would have said...
SCOTT: I don't really put
that together. (Laughs)
KIM: You're gonna be one
of Kourtney's boyfriend one day,
like, you would have never in a
million years think that.
SCOTT: It's a little bit
different for me to talk about
what's going on now, and
sometimes I feel guilty that
I've moved on.
SCOTT: You know, there's just
some things that are
uncomfortable, I think, to talk
about with other people.
JENNIFER: I know it
might be weird to see me up
here... I am an MTV Best Kiss
award winner, but I really am...
SCOTT: She's funny.
JENNIFER: I don't get caught
up in all those celebrities.
STYLIST: This is gonna be
amazing.
JENNIFER: Yes, I don't care.
KIM: Tune in to Jimmy Kimmel
tonight, guys, to see me and.
Jennifer Lawrence.
JENNIFER: Please welcome.
Kim Kardashian West!
(audience cheering)
So... are you excited?
KIM: I'm excited.
JENNIFER: All right, buckle
down and get comfortable.
My first question:
Do you think it's a coincidence
that Reggie Bush's wife looks
just like you?
I don't. (Laughter)
(Jennifer laughs)
So, recently, I went over to
your mom's house for dinner.
KIM: Yes.
JENNIFER: It was everything
I could've ever dreamed of.
KIM: Was it? JENNIFER: Yeah.
KIM: I've never seen my mom
more drunk in our lives.
JENNIFER: Take it easy.
KIM: We were worried.
JENNIFER: I was way more
drunk than your mom.
(laughter) ♪ ♪
KHLOE: Oh, my God, she's coming.
I don't understand the
(bleep) attitude.
KIM: I'm so afraid of her.
KHLOE: I'm, like, so afraid
of her.
KIM: I don't get it. Hey.
(Kourtney coughing)
KIM: She's, like, not paying
attention.
KOURTNEY: What do you want me
to do, sit here and stare?
KHLOE: Damn!
KIM: Mm-kay. Well, guys,
I really wasn't going to plan a
baby shower, but I think it's
important for North so she
starts feeling that, like, it's
coming. Things are happening.
KHLOE: Okay.
KIM: So a vision came to me
about cherry blossoms.
KHLOE: They're so beautiful.
KIM: And that's my favorite
thing at the moment.
KHLOE: And that's the theme
for your baby shower?
That'd be so pretty.
KIM: Yeah, I think so, too.
With the photo shoot going on,
it's so much work, I just need,
like, a little bit of help.
KHLOE: I will help you with
the baby shower, I won't help
you with the photo shoot.
KIM: Okay.
All right, well, thank you
for the help. KHLOE: Of course.
Let me know what you need.
I'm happy to help.
KIM: Cool.
Thanks for being so present.
KHLOE: It'll be fun and
beautiful.
KOURTNEY: Who let you choose
black covers for your furniture?
Disgusting.
KIM: She likes black things.
KHLOE: I didn't...
KOURTNEY: Usually people get
a color that's, like, neutral to
your floor.
Who chooses black?
KHLOE: It confuses me how.
Kourtney is confused that we're
butting heads.
KHLOE: That's nice, Kourtney.
Well, thanks for coming over,
thanks for being so lovely.
KOURTNEY: (snorts) Anytime.
KHLOE: When I come into your
house, I'll make sure to say
just a critical comment.
KOURTNEY: Oh, you do, you do.
Every time.
KHLOE: When have I... every
time, I always say how great
your house looks, I look at all
your new (bleep) that you show
me.
KOURTNEY: Well, don't we have
a meeting?
This isn't here to sit and talk
about this.
KHLOE: What is up your ass?
Seriously, what the (bleep) is
wrong with you?
But why are you so bitchy these
days?
KOURTNEY: I'm just... a born
bitch.
KHLOE: You should be proud of
that.
Trust me, if I wasn't pregnant,
I'd probably (bleep) drowned you
in the pool.
You're just mean.
(North yelling)
I have a real question for you.
Do you think you and Kourt
will finally get married?
KIM: Do you foresee?
KOURTNEY: I can't get there
till 11:00.
And then, I want to be home by
6:00, so we have to, like, wrap
around 4:00.
KIM: Kourtney is making this
so hard. KRIS: You are annoying,
Kourtney.
KOURTNEY: Why, because Kim
wants it around her schedule?
KIM: Who has a busier
schedule?
Maybe if you had a (bleep)
business that you were
passionate about, then you would
know what it takes to run a
(bleep) business, but you don't!
♪ ♪
(Reign shouts)
REIGN: Mommy! (Khloe chuckles)
SCOTT: Oh! I know these kids.
KHLOE: Hey, guys.
What... >> SCOTT: Hello, Reigno.
REIGN: Look, look!
SCOTT: That's a dog.
(laughs)
KHLOE: What is that dog on?
SCOTT: Hi, Poosh!
KHLOE: That poor dog.
SCOTT: Can I have a hug?
KIM: Do we think it's time to
cut Reign's hair? >> SCOTT: No.
KHLOE: It's a little long.
But you guys can't put it in
girl half-up, half-down.
Put it in man buns.
SCOTT: I put this family
together.
I made those kids.
(Kim chuckles)
Right there? I made 'em!
KHLOE: I have a real question
for you. I know you're happy.
Do you think, in a few years...
SCOTT: Huh.
KHLOE: You and Kourt will
finally get married?
KIM: Do you foresee?
SCOTT: We always said we
would try to get back together
when we were, like, 40.
KHLOE: How old are you?
SCOTT: So, she's got a couple
years... I mean, I'm much
younger.
I'm in my early 30s.
She's pushing 40.
KHLOE: Do you, or or you're
just over it?
You're like, "You're crazy."
SCOTT: She is crazy.
KIM: But she thinks you're
crazy, you think she's crazy.
Like, do you think it's just
too much?
Like, there's too much
history there?
SCOTT: Eh, it's fine.
KHLOE: We kind of think she's
crazy, too, right now.
SCOTT: It's like one of those
things.
I mean, when we were together,
I feel like everybody had a
problem with us being together.
Now that we're not together,
everybody's got a problem.
So you can't really win.
But at the end of the day,
my dream is not to talk about my
relationship with my ex's
family.
KIM: Kanye asked me if we
wanted to name our daughter
Khloe.
KHLOE: Aww. >> SCOTT: Ah!
KIM: Khloe West and Khloe
Kardashian?
KHLOE: That's so cute.
KIM: I know.
But I was like, that's really
confusing.
KHLOE: The kids call me KoKo,
they don't care.
(Kim laughs) (Scott laughs)
♪ ♪
(phone ringing)
KHLOE: Hello? >> KIM: Hey.
KHLOE: Hey.
KIM: So for the Christmas
card shoot, um, who...
What glam do you want?
KHLOE: Probably Hrush and
Andrew or whoever's around.
I'm a little chubby right now,
so hopefully, we can make that
work. KIM: Yeah, we will make it
work. >> KHLOE: Love you.
KIM: Love you. Okay.
KHLOE: Okay.
KIM: Bye. (Phone ringing)
KOURTNEY: Hello? >> KIM: Hey.
KOURTNEY: Hi.
KIM: Okay, so, I'm just
working on glam.
You want Andrew and Hrush for
makeup?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, or Ariel.
And then, I can't get there till
11:00.
And then, I want to be home by
6:00.
So we have to, like, wrap,
maybe, around 4:00 to 5:00 so
then we could drive home.
KIM: Well, Kendall has
another shoot that she's coming
from, so she won't even get to
the studio until 7:00.
Trying to figure out the whole
family's schedule is really a
task all in itself, but.
Kourtney is making this so hard.
She just won't budge.
Khloe and I have so much
going on, we're still, like,
reorganizing things, changing
our schedules to make it work
for everyone else.
KOURTNEY: I just want to be
home by 6:00 to have dinner with
the kids and put them to bed.
KIM: We will figure it out.
KOURTNEY: Okay.
KIM: Okay, bye. ♪ ♪
SCOTT: Chonch! >> CICI: Hey!
SCOTT: How are you?
CICI: Oh, my God, so good to
see you.
SCOTT: I got you a gift.
CICI: You're the guy?
SCOTT: I didn't know if you
wanted anything... hey.
BILL: Good to see you.
SCOTT: How are you?
Got a little beard going.
BILL: Yeah.
CICI: He wants to be like
you. >> SCOTT: Who doesn't?
CICI: Yeah.
SCOTT: Ha, ha, ha, ha!
CICI: A little hi, how are you?
SCOTT: How are you?
CiCi, for people that don't
know, pretty much a cousin, but
also a lifelong friend of
everybody in the family.
She's an unbelievable woman.
To me, she's kind of like
a second mom, almost.
I mean, she's always been that
one person I could really trust
and has always really been there
for me.
CICI: We're gonna sit next to
each other.
SCOTT: All right.
CICI: Honey, come sit down.
BILL: I am. CICI: Oh, okay.
He loves that chair. (Laughs)
SCOTT: I like those chairs.
CICI: Of everything in the
house, he has to sit on the
stool.
Um, how's life?
SCOTT: Life is good.
What do you really want to ask
me, Chonch?
CICI: Are you sober?
SCOTT: No, why, you want a
drink? (Laughs)
Here and there, I'll have wine
or champagne or things like
that. But in balance, I mean...
CICI: Okay, good.
SCOTT: I don't really have
any reason to go wild anymore.
CICI: Okay, good.
SCOTT: So...
CICI: Um, what about this
woman? >> SCOTT: What about her?
CICI: Like, is it serious?
(Scott clears throat)
SCOTT: I mean...
CICI: I mean, for you to be
with a woman besides Kourtney.
SCOTT: More than once.
Is pretty serious.
CICI: Yeah, and trips and...
Like, when you walk through
the...
(phone ringing)
SCOTT: Oh, thank God.
(both laugh)
SCOTT: I'll answer, whoever
this is. Hello?
I don't want to answer, but...
CICI: So now...
SCOTT: Yeah.
CICI: I'm, like, thinking to
myself, there must be something
there.
SCOTT: Yeah, I mean, it's
definitely, like...
CICI: Well, that's good.
SCOTT: The first girl...
CICI: I guess.
SCOTT: I've ever been with
other than Kourtney that was,
like, a real relationship.
CICI: You're kidding.
SCOTT: I mean, no, but...
I mean, yeah. CICI: I love it.
SCOTT: I mean, one part of me
is like, really happy that I'm
able to, like, care about
somebody again, but there always
is, like, some feeling in the
back of me that feels guilty
because I'm moving on from
Kourtney, you know what I mean?
But...
CICI: But hasn't she moved
on? >> SCOTT: Yeah.
I do appreciate how much you've
always been Team Scott and...
CICI: Always.
SCOTT: Been trying for me.
It's definitely nice to hear
CiCi be there for me and be
excited that I'm doing okay and,
you know, telling me that I am
in a good place and, you know,
it's a lot because she has
seen me in a lot of different
places, so I think she, out of
everybody, would know.
But I just wish that everybody
would be happy for me.
CICI: Remember when you came
to visit me in the hospital?
We talked and talked and you
go, "I haven't talked like this
in three years."
SCOTT: Yeah. (CiCi laughs)
'Cause it is hard, because
sometimes, everybody around here
is so busy.
CICI: No, they're always on
their cell phones.
You get, like, two minutes of...
SCOTT: Sorry, what'd you say?
(CiCi laughs)
♪ ♪
KANYE: Can you see her with
the-with the slide heels, also?
STYLIST: Yeah.
KIM: You want to see it with
something else? KANYE: Mm-hmm.
KIM: I think all of these,
for sure, we need.
I prefer it with the sneakers.
I mean, if you want to, out of
these, I'd say these. ♪ ♪
Yeah.
Okay, I think we have this.
This week is crazy busy.
I have so many meetings, I have
a photo shoot for KKW BEAUTY, a
Yeezy campaign, and I'm trying
to plan my baby shower and I'm
trying to book our Christmas
card and plan all of that.
It's really intense.
ELI: Hey. >> KIM: Hey.
Oh, right. >> ELI: I know.
KIM: I can't believe I am
getting my sisters to do this
holiday card.
ELI: How are you guys...
KIM: It's been, like, years.
ELI: How are you guys even
in, like, the same place at the
same time?
Can I use this?
KIM: We are making it happen.
ELI: That's crazy.
KIM: So I love this.
ELI: Yeah.
KIM: I-I think this will be
the vibe. >> ELI: Yeah.
KIM: I'm thinking if we do
this top one, that we'd kind of
have messy hair.
ELI: Just, like, super
modern.
KIM: Just like, literally,
like, Kate Moss-y and just kind
of not so glam.
ELI: Yeah, it'll be so casual.
KIM: Yeah. ELI: See... you know?
KIM: Yeah. ELI: Uncomplicated.
KIM: Okay, I think that's good.
ELI: All right, awesome.
Let me know when you're ready.
KIM: The amount of work it
takes to wrangle...
Putting together a shoot like
this is, like, a huge puzzle.
Figuring out what glam's
available and which sister's
gonna come in at which time.
Kourtney's only giving me, like,
a five-hour window.
This just is not enough time to
figure this out and to pull
this all off.
So I don't know what to do.
I just can't wait to get
through.
KOURTNEY: Why can't we glam
at 10:00?
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
KIM: I just have other
meetings and I have to take
them.
KOURTNEY: Okay, and I'm
leaving at 4:00 p.m., and I
don't care what anyone says.
KRIS: Be nice.
KIM: No one wants you in the
(bleep) shoot so get the (bleep)
out of here.
KRIS: Okay, no, no, no...
KIM: Get the (bleep) out of
here and go.
Get the (bleep) out of here and
go.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: You ain't got a water
for this hike?
BENNY: No. SCOTT: You all right?
BENNY: You wear straight
white jeans, huh?
SCOTT: Yeah, I don't care.
I'm nuts, I'm living on the
edge. >> BENNY: Yeah.
SCOTT: Watch that (bleep). Damn.
BENNY: Mm-hmm.
SCOTT: That's horse manure,
my friend. That's horse manure.
(Benny laughs) >> BENNY: Yep.
How have you been, though?
SCOTT: I've been amazing,
for, like, the first time in my
life.
BENNY: You've never been
in a... like, another
relationship. This is new.
So it's an adjustment.
SCOTT: It is new.
BENNY: I mean, it is what it
is, everybody's got feelings.
SCOTT: I... Yeah.
BENNY: I mean, most important
thing is just for you to be good
and healthy and happy, so...
SCOTT: Yeah, and I am.
It's just a nice time to move
forward and just be positive
and happy and live, like, a
normal life again.
BENNY: Yeah, just let...
SCOTT: 'Cause...
BENNY: Let it take... go where
it goes.
SCOTT: Let nature take its
course.
BENNY: Let it do its thing.
SCOTT: I'm ready to do my
thing.
I think that Kourtney and I have
been through a lot and I don't
know, it's an ongoing struggle,
but you know, I think
Kourtney's doing well now,
I'm happy for her.
And after talking to CiCi, some
weight has lifted off of me and
I don't feel the guilt anymore.
And I feel that I'm able to now
live my life the way I should.
BENNY: (clears throat) It's
good that you've got someone to
hang with, you know what I mean?
SCOTT: Yeah, yeah, she's
good. >> BENNY: Good that she...
SCOTT: She's a copilot.
(Benny laughs)
SCOTT (sighing): Oh, man.
BENNY: Could we get an Uber
from up here?
SCOTT: Uh... Oh! More manure!
BENNY: This is a (bleep) trail.
SCOTT: This is definitely a
(bleep) trail.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Is something wrong
with the Wi-Fi, Khlo?
KHLOE: Oh, Kourtney.
KOURTNEY: It just won't post
my snaps.
KHLOE: Okay, well, I don't
know what to tell you, babe.
KOURTNEY: Mm, well, your.
Wi-Fi sucks.
KHLOE: Oh, it's so nice
seeing you. No, really.
That's great.
I love when people just come to
someone's house and complain
the whole time. >> KRIS: Oh.
KOURTNEY: Hey, Mom. KRIS: Hi.
KHLOE: Esperanza's here.
KOURTNEY: Um, Kim is...
KHLOE: What?
KOURTNEY: Really, um, wild
on the-the scheduling for
tomorrow.
KHLOE: Why, what's happening?
KOURTNEY: They had me
glamming at, like, 5:00 p.m. or
something and our shoot shooting
until 8:00.
I was like, I really want to get
home, relax, have dinner with my
kids, give them a bath...
KHLOE: Kim's been working so
hard on this, though.
KOURTNEY: Okay, but let's
move it up, what's the point?
KHLOE: So, get her out of the
glam room and let's ask her
these questions.
KOURTNEY: Kim! KHLOE: Kourt.
KOURTNEY: Hmm?
KHLOE: Get off your ass and
go get her. >> KOURTNEY: I will.
My (bleep) Snapchats keep
failing.
It's putting a lot of my
energy... it's draining.
Hi. We're all asking why can't
we glam at 10:00?
KIM: I just have other
meetings and I have to take
them. KOURTNEY: Let's just start
early and we can be done at
4:00.
KIM: But Kourtney, I have two
really important meetings, one's
a packaging meeting, one's my
baby shower.
If I don't have those meetings,
I cannot do either one.
KOURTNEY: Why can't you do
those today?
You know I have an important day
tomorrow and you said I would be
done early.
KIM: I honestly cannot
believe Kourtney.
Now she wants to pull my kids
out of school to do the shoot.
But I think we should keep my
kids in school, we should do our
meetings and glams so that when
they're out of school, we'll
just do a quick photo shoot.
Everyone understands if I don't
do this packaging meeting, then
I won't be able to launch my
collection, and I think it's so
selfish of Kourtney and I'm just
sad that she doesn't understand
that.
KRIS: Kim, it sounds like you
might be having a little bit of
a hard time just figuring it
out. Do you need some help?
KIM: Well, if Kourtney wasn't
so difficult...
KOURTNEY: If I'm out by 4:00,
that's all I need.
And I don't think I'm gonna get
there and change my mind.
And if no one's gonna be ready
on time, and I'm, like,
lingering around, then I'm
leaving at 4:00 p.m. and I don't
care what anyone says.
KIM: That was when my meeting
was, so...
KRIS: Where's the meeting?
KIM: It was supposed to be at
my house.
KRIS: Okay.
KIM: Unless I do it at 7:00
in the morning.
KOURTNEY: Do it at 7:00 in
the morning.
KRIS: Who are you meeting
with? Stop. Be nice.
KOURTNEY: Do it tonight.
KIM: No one wants you in the
(bleep) shoot so get the (bleep)
out of here.
KRIS: Okay, no, no, no...
KIM: Get the (bleep) out of
here and go.
Get the (bleep) out of here and
go.
No one wants you in the (bleep)
shoot.
I'm planning it.
KRIS: You guys just be nice
to each other.
KIM: I'm planning this shoot.
So we don't want you in the
shoot. I'm planning it.
KOURTNEY: I... Did I already
say this morning?
I didn't care to do it.
KIM: Then don't be in it
'cause you're so (bleep)
annoying.
KOURTNEY: I said this
morning, I don't care.
KIM: Perfect, then shut the
(bleep) up.
KOURTNEY: No, but it's like
I'm not scheduling around Kim.
KHLOE: Ladies, ladies, ladies.
KIM: So (bleep) annoying.
KRIS: You are annoying,
Kourtney. You're being annoying.
KHLOE: Hold on, ladies.
KOURTNEY: I'm not. That's
why, because Kim wants it around
her schedule?
KRIS: Do you know what we're
fighting about?
KIM: I've had my schedule
picked.
Who has the busier schedule?
Maybe if you had a (bleep)
business that you were
passionate about then you would
know what it takes to run a
(bleep) business.
But you don't, so don't even act
like you know what I'm talking
about.
KRIS: Kourtney, you just have
a way of rubbing people the
wrong way. KIM: Kourtney is out.
She will not be at the shoot
because she is the one that has
the annoying schedule.
I can't handle this anymore
'cause I... everyone is
dropping left and right from all
these schedule changes.
I need Kourtney to not be so
(bleep) annoying with a stick
up her ass like she (bleep) runs
this (bleep) because she
doesn't.
She's the least exciting to look
at, so she can be out.
She doesn't do (bleep).
She doesn't know what it's like
to actually have (bleep) work
to do.
You don't do (bleep).
KOURTNEY: You're a very
distraught, evil human being.
I'm not here to (bleep) be
mistreated by my (bleep)
bitch family.
NORTH: Welcome to the baby
shower!
KRIS: Thank you so much.
KENDALL: Is Kourtney coming?
KHLOE: I don't know.
KIM: I need Kourtney to not
be so (bleep) annoying with a
stick up her ass like she
(bleep) runs this (bleep)
because she doesn't.
She's the least exciting to look
at, so she can be out.
She doesn't do (bleep).
She doesn't know what it's like
to actually have (bleep) work to
do 'cause I don't know what the
(bleep) she does, so...
KRIS: Wow.
KHLOE: Kourtney's leaving?
KIM: Good.
KHLOE: She's not leaving.
KIM: Of course she should.
KHLOE: What a pussy.
KRIS: She was so rude.
KIM: But she'll think that
I'm rude and I was rude, but I
wanted to be rude 'cause she's
so (bleep) rude all the time.
KHLOE: Well, 'cause
everything revolves around her.
KIM: I'm just not taking her
(bleep) anymore.
KHLOE: Let me call her and
see why she left.
(phone dialing) KOURTNEY: Hello.
KHLOE: Hey. >> KOURTNEY: Hi.
KHLOE: Are you crying?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, I'm not here
to (bleep) be mistreated by
my (bleep) bitch family.
Kim saying that I'm the least
interesting to look at.
Who even speaks like that?
KHLOE: I mean, she's just
mad, so she's saying that.
People say things when...
KOURTNEY: Khloe, you don't
say things like that.
You guys just have really
different values than me.
I choose to be a mother to my
three kids.
I'm not here looking for another
job.
I already work enough, more
than I would like to.
KHLOE: Don't talk.
KIM: You don't do (bleep).
Take it off speaker.
KOURTNEY: It's not funny.
What's natural to me is being a
mother.
KRIS: No, everybody calm down.
KHLOE: I'm taking off speaker.
KRIS: Don't be mean, Kim!
(Kourtney continues talking)
KRIS: Oh, my God.
KHLOE: I'm sorry you feel
that way.
KIM: So you would think that,
you would think that-that you
would honestly think that we
have more jobs, so work around
our schedule.
You do whatever the (bleep) you
want to do and you don't do
(bleep), so be accommodating to
the people that actually do
(bleep). KOURTNEY: You're a very
distraught, evil human being.
I don't want to see you, okay?
I don't agree with who you are
as a human being.
KRIS: Say you're sorry.
KIM: Okay, well, if I said
something that hurt your
feelings, I'm sorry.
KOURTNEY: You're just a jerk
like that.
KRIS: Just say you didn't
mean it.
KOURTNEY: No, (bleep) you,
Kim. You meant it.
So (bleep) you. >> KRIS: No.
KOURTNEY: I am not going to
live my life around people that
make me not feel good on a daily
basis.
KHLOE: And you shouldn't.
KIM: Well, clearly you're
going through something else
'cause you're acting like a
(bleep) lunatic.
So maybe deal with that.
KHLOE: Oh my God, Kimberly.
That's not okay to say.
KIM: No, it is.
KOURTNEY: I don't choose to
be around somebody who talks to
me the way that you speak to me.
KIM: What I said to you was
rude and I wasn't even being
serious, so I said I'm sorry for
that.
But you're the most (bleep)
entitled person on the planet
when you work the least.
That's what I'm saying.
KRIS: Bring it down, bring it
down.
KOURTNEY: Why can't we
do the schedule at (bleep) 10:00
a.m. to 4:00?
I'm not here to do photo shoots
all day.
That is not important to me.
That is not one of my jobs.
KIM: So don't come. Perfect.
KRIS: Kourtney, we're just
trying... no! No, no!
KIM: I'll do the Christmas
card, me, my husband and my
kids, just me and him and the
kids.
KRIS: No, Kim. Kim, don't do
that.
KHLOE: Hello?
KOURTNEY: All everyone
(bleep) says is, "What's your
job?"
If I had enough money, I
wouldn't work.
I wouldn't do the show.
I would be a full-time mom.
That's what I want to do.
KHLOE: No one is saying you
need a second job.
My only argument was the job
that you do have, like, you're
not present for, but if you...
KOURTNEY: The guilt that I
carry every day from not being
at home when they get in from
school.
Not doing homework.
My kids suffer.
Honestly, it's like... we have
a disgusting family.
Like, I'm ashamed to be a part
of people that, like...
KHLOE: Oh, my God, you're
ashamed?
KIM: No one cares!
KOURTNEY: It's just gross
and I'm not going to be filming
with some (bleep) (bleep)
like Kim when she talks that way
about her own sister.
KHLOE: Well, okay, I love you
and I hope you feel better.
KRIS: Sorry, Kourt.
KOURTNEY: 'Kay, bye.
KHLOE: Bye.
Well, I don't think we're
disgusting or whatever she said.
KRIS: This is reminding me
of, years ago, when I used to
have to break up an argument
between my girls, and once a
referee, always a referee.
I feel like we're back in grade
school.
She's crying so hard.
KIM: I mean, was I rude
saying no one cares about
Kourtney?
Like, yeah, I know I'm being
rude.
I know I'm being rude.
KRIS: All of you cut really
deep. KIM: No, no, I know, but
she's cut really deep my whole
life.
I'm happy to apologize to her,
but I'm not gonna be like, "But"
please come to our shoot,"
'cause I don't care.
Kourtney's so (bleep) selfish.
I do not expect her to show up
to the Christmas card shoot, but
I've already booked it and we're
gonna do it with or without her.
KRIS: I'll see you at 8:00
tomorrow morning. >> KIM: Okay.
KRIS: For the meeting, okay?
I'll see you when I see you.
KHLOE: Oh, great, love you.
It's been wonderful.
KRIS: Love you, yeah, love
you guys, bye.
KHLOE: You feel okay?
KIM: I feel fine.
KHLOE: Okay.
KIM: I'm just not gonna
tolerate her (bleep) rudeness.
And I'll be ten billion times
ruder back to her every single
time until she just cries when
she sees me. KHLOE: Oh, my God.
KIM: Yeah, everyone walks
on (bleep) eggshells around her.
She's (bleep) rude.
She's so goddamn entitled.
She's such a mess, a (bleep)
gremlin.
I'm not gonna play around with
her anymore.
KOURTNEY: I'm just here to
say that I'm not gonna spend my
time, whether it's my sister or
not, with anybody that talks to
me that way.
KIM: So I said one (bleep)
up thing to you today.
KOURTNEY: I cannot handle and
be around you when you're just
(bleep) a bitch.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I have been working
on being better at communicating
my feelings, and I was so upset
earlier that I really didn't get
to say how I was feeling and I
really just wanted to come back
and say how I feel.
So I'm still upset, so I don't
want to sit here and like,
linger...
KHLOE: Oh, my gosh.
KOURTNEY: For days, but
I'm just here to say that I'm
not gonna spend my time, whether
it's my sister or not, with
anybody that talks to me that
way or thinks that way about me.
Everybody has different
priorities.
KIM: Well, I don't want to
spend my time with people that
don't make things that we plan a
priority and try to change
everything and aren't
considerate of other people's
work obligations, 'cause some
people do have to work.
I do have to make this deadline
for the holiday collection or
I'm screwed.
KOURTNEY: So do it.
KIM: How is the person that
is the least busy...
KOURTNEY: How am I the least
busy? KIM: The most difficult?
You're not ever accommodating,
and everybody says it.
So if everyone says it...
KOURTNEY: I wasn't even going
to do the shoot that day, and
you asked me to do it on that
day, and you said it will be
this amount of hours, so we can
either not do it, or we can
do it at the time when I said.
KIM: I'm missing my baby
shower planning, and I'm missing
my meeting that's really
important so that I can do that
for you, and the problem...
KOURTNEY: Do whatever.
KIM: That I have with you
is you're just not considerate.
You're not like, "Thank you."
KOURTNEY: Okay, I don't
care, to be honest,
especially after you sit there
and talk to me like that today.
I just don't care.
KIM: Talk to you, Kourtney?
The way you've talked to me my
whole life, I could say so many
(bleep) things and, like, I'm
not harping on it.
So I said one (bleep) up
thing to you today.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, today.
KIM: So get over it.
KOURTNEY: At the end of the
day, when you die and when I
die, it doesn't matter how much
money is in our bank account,
but what matters to me is my
memories.
KIM: I don't care about that.
KOURTNEY: But it is to you,
because I don't give a (bleep).
KIM: I would think a memory
with your kids would be
important.
Like a Christmas card.
KOURTNEY: It is.
I'm not gonna be around people
that bring me down on a daily
basis and criticize if I'm this,
if I'm that...
I'm just doing my best.
So I-I cannot handle and
be around you when you're
just (bleep) a bitch.
Your words have-have meaning,
and they come from somewhere.
You didn't just make them up.
It's-It's really unkind.
KIM: I'm sorry if I said
something that was hurtful.
KOURTNEY: It's really unkind.
No, you're not sorry, Kim.
You (bleep) said it.
You can't take back words
that you say.
Words come from somewhere.
KHLOE: Okay, but she could
mean an apology if she does.
KOURTNEY: She could change
her outlook.
Do you think she's changing
her outlook?
Do you think she in any way
doesn't-doesn't feel the same
way that she felt this morning?
Cause I 1,000% know that she
doesn't feel any different.
KHLOE: I think we both have
to stop judging... or all of us
have to stop judging each other.
KOURTNEY: But every time I
come in this house or anywhere
lately when we're filming,
you guys judge.
KHLOE: The only thing that I
say to you is, Kourt, you gotta
be on time.
That's all I say to you.
KOURTNEY: And I've made an
effort to try to be on time.
KHLOE: I haven't been here
and I've... now I'm here, you
were on time today, and I said
thank you.
But that's all I've said to you.
And I said fully,
if you don't wanna have other
jobs, I don't care if you want
to or not.
I moved to another state, like,
I don't care about that stuff.
KOURTNEY: Good, and I will
move to another state at some
point, or another country.
But now is not the exact moment
in time.
But I cannot wait for that day,
and hopefully, like, just don't
have to have these fake
relationships.
KHLOE: With your sisters?
KOURTNEY: That I feel like
is forced. Why on earth...
KHLOE: I mean if you feel
like you're forcing a
relationship, then you shouldn't
have that relationship, if
that's really how you feel.
KOURTNEY: No.
KHLOE: I mean, who knew that
you felt like you were forcing
relationships?
KIM: Like, don't think I'm
gonna give you what you want.
I've said sorry, I've said...
KOURTNEY: I don't give a
(bleep).
I'm not looking for anything.
I didn't come here to get
anything from you.
I didn't expect you to change
your point of view.
That's nothing that I would
ever expect from you.
You are a very specific
individual, and that's fine.
And I never judge you for it.
KIM: Okay.
KOURTNEY: I'm gonna get my
kids and go home and hang out.
♪ ♪
KIM: Hi. STYLIST: Hi, gorgeous.
ELI: Once we get everyone
together, we'll have to see,
and then make some changes.
So, let's pick, like, your
number one, and then, like,
a second option.
KIM: Hi. What's going on, guys?
ASSISTANT: We're trying out
boyfriend jeans.
ELI: Boyfriend jeans.
KIM: Will you make a pile
for me? ASSISTANT: Yes, I will.
KIM: Okay.
I moved my meetings till
earlier so that we could
all accommodate Miss Queen.
Kourtney.
KOURTNEY: There's tags on
this.
KIM: And then Kylie couldn't
come... she wanted to shoot hers
privately at home.
Rob's trying to lay low
right now.
Kendall's gonna make it right
at the end.
It's just, like, craziness, so I
thought, why not just show the
craziness of our family?
We're just gonna do candid
pictures, and we can post them
for the 25 days of Christmas.
Hi, Grandma. >> MJ: How are you?
KRIS: Queen in the house.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
KOURTNEY: Yesterday, I was in
a fight with Kim.
We were actually fighting
about this shoot.
HRUSH: Mm-hmm.
KOURTNEY: Just the scheduling
of it.
She's like, "Well, don't come."
You're the least interesting
one to look at anyways."
HRUSH: Not true.
KOURTNEY: Obviously, but,
like, she's just so evil.
KIM: She was, like,
hysterically crying.
"You guys are awful people."
Like, "I don't want to
surround myself with people..."
Like some bull(bleep) that her
(bleep) therapist says,
like full therapist lingo.
KOURTNEY: I don't wanna take
anything else on, I just don't.
HRUSH: But that's good, too,
that you know exactly what you
want out of life.
KOURTNEY: I'm here at the
shoot today for my kids because
I really don't want them to miss
out on these moments.
So, we can just get through
the day and do this photo shoot.
KHLOE: Why aren't you starting?
KOURTNEY: Cause this girl's
sitting out there.
Where's Mom? Where's everyone?
Let's just go do this.
I can't sit and wait all day.
Come on Reigny, come on Mase,
we're gonna shoot. (Sighs)
KHLOE: This is not the
(bleep) holiday spirit,
I can tell you that much.
KOURTNEY: I just don't have
time for the shoot today.
KOURTNEY: (sighs) I just
don't have time for the shoot
today. ELI: Kourt, can you just
scoot in a little bit more?
Like, arm around Kim.
KHLOE: It's just weird.
There's tension...
ELI: Kim, if you can lean
into Kourt. Yeah.
KHLOE: I am uncomfortable.
Like, this family is known for
just sweeping things under the
rug... like, that's a big thing
we do. ELI: All right, you guys,
look over here... smile.
KHLOE: Ah. Love these family
moments.
MJ: Wait till next year.
KHLOE: Holy (bleep).
ELI: Next year we're gonna do
a nativity scene.
KHLOE: I'm not doing a group
photo anymore, this is our last
group photo.
KIM: Okay, we're done?
ELI: Yeah.
KIM: Thank you >> KHLOE: Yay!
(Kim whoops)
KHLOE: I'll help MJ.
KOURTNEY: All right, I'm
gonna take my kids...
Thank you so much.
ELI: Can we clear this?
KOURTNEY: We gotta go, guys.
KHLOE: Good-bye, guys.
KOURTNEY: Come on, P. ♪ ♪
STYLIST: Did you just come
from somewhere else?
You had another shoot today?
KENDALL: Yeah.
Kind of ironic that I'm shooting
our family Christmas card by
myself, but it's kind of how we
roll in this family.
ELI: I even like it
off the shoulder.
KENDALL: So, yeah.
Somehow they're photoshopping me
into the whole family shebang.
Who is... Oh, my God, that's MJ.
I was like, who is that?
ELI: Oh, my God, can you sit
in so she has someone
to lean into?
Yeah, that's great. Okay.
Yeah, uh...
I'm like, it's different
shooting a model than
toddlers... that's for sure.
KENDALL: That's so pretty.
ELI: That's so (bleep) gorgeous.
All right, let me take a photo,
this time...
♪ ♪
NORTH: Welcome to the baby
shower!
KRIS: Thank you so much!
KIM: Northie, come take a
picture with me.
These are some of our last
moments before baby sister
gets here.
KRIS: So pretty.
NORTH: Is she coming today?
KIM: No, not today.
In a month, or two.
NORTH: But it's the baby shower.
KIM: Malika!
MALIKA: You look beautiful.
Both of you, my little mommerz.
KHLOE: Thank you.
MALIKA: Would you have ever
thought?
KYLIE: Honestly, not at the
same time.
KIM: Oh. Those are
gluten-free, but the other ones
are not, and they're so good.
Can I take one pic with
with you guys touching my belly?
CHRISSY: (laughs) Yes. Oh.
KIM: The baby shower turned
out so beautiful.
We put it together last-minute,
but it was my exact vision
of this cherry blossom forest.
I wanted it to be girlie
and just sweet.
It was just all my closest
friends, and it was perfect.
KRIS: Thank you for all
coming to yet another Kardashian
baby shower.
We're so excited for Kim's baby
number three.
(guests whoop)
My... seventh grandchild.
Yeah.
FRIEND: Lucky number seven!
KRIS: You're next, Kendall!
NORTH: Lucky number seven!
KRIS: It's such a special
time for all of us, and we're
just so grateful for the joy and
the pleasure of just having this
big, huge family.
So thank you for coming.
KIM: Love you! Love you, Mom.
KRIS: We're happy for you,
Kim. KIM: You have to try those
little doughnuts.
They are so good.
To die for.
KHLOE: Um, Kendall and I, we
were just saying, it's so cool
that you did that Christmas card
shoot, and that you wrangled
everyone together.
And if it wasn't for you,
we wouldn't have a Christmas
card this year.
KENDALL: You see that picture.
MJ took of all the kids on the
couch at Dream's birthday?
KHLOE: No.
KENDALL: She goes, "Look at"
this, and there's gonna be three
more."
And I was like, oh, my God.
KHLOE: That's what's crazy.
KENDALL: I don't need a kid
because of all of this.
KIM: You look so skinny.
KHLOE: Kylie is wild.
KIM: Let's sit, eat cake and
go to bed.
KHLOE: Who the hell...
Kourtney, I can't talk to
you now.
KENDALL: Wait, so is Kourtney
coming? >> KHLOE: I don't know.
You should read the text
message.
I was like, "Get your ass over
here."
KIM: Do you want cake?
I'll have cake, thank you.
KHLOE: She never responds
anymore.
She's so emotionally removed
from all of us.
FRIEND: Where's Kourtney?
Are you guys still fighting?
KIM: Yeah.
I really hoped Kourtney was
gonna get over herself and just
show up, but she didn't, so I
don't think she's big on family.
'Cause if she was, she would be
at my shower.
KIM: On the next episode...
KHLOE: Kourtney, why are you
even here?
If you don't care to fix
relationships with your sister,
then you can (bleep) off.
KIM: You come over here with
such an attitude...
KOURTNEY: Khloe pushes and
pushes... I'm not up for it!
KHLOE: Mom was art shaming me.
I want to art shame her back.
SCOTT: Why don't we get a
fake Basquiat?
Holy... yes! Yes! (Whoops)
KHLOE: I am actually a
(bleep) good-ass artist.
SCOTT: It's like watching
Jesus work.
Captioning sponsored by
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS