Keeping
Up with the Kardashians...
KOURTNEY: I cannot be around
you when you're just (bleep) a
bitch.
You guys make fun of me for
going.
KHLOE: We don't make fun of
you for going to therapy, we
make fun of you for literally
hating us because of your
therapist.
KOURTNEY: In the past, I used
to just brush things off, and it
really didn't bother me, but
because I've started going to
therapy, I'm more aware of my
feelings.
I don't want to spend my time
around people that are mean.
I'm evolving.
I don't want to be the bitchy
person that I was before. ♪ ♪
KRIS: Hey. >> SCOTT: Hi.
KRIS: Wait a second.
Have you ever thought about
reshaping your earlobes?
SCOTT: What?
KRIS: Yeah.
SCOTT: What's wrong with my
earlobes?
KRIS: I think they're a
little large. (Laughs)
SCOTT: Oh, my God.
I don't even know what you're
talking about, to be quite
honest.
KRIS: If we do, like, right
there. >> SCOTT: How about no?!
KRIS: They just slice it
right there and stitch it up.
SCOTT: You want me to slice
my ear?
KRIS: Look, this one's even
bigger.
Do you have your ear pierced?
SCOTT: Yeah, when I was a kid
I had it pierced. >> KRIS: What?
You have your ear pierced?
SCOTT: That's why you're
freaking out?
You're telling me to cut my ear
off! I got a hole in it.
KRIS: That's why it's so...
Look at this!
You had your ears pierced.
SCOTT: I had one pierced.
KRIS: Oh, does this mean you
were gay at one time?
SCOTT: Yes, 'cause I had an
earring in my left (bleep) ear.
(Kris laughing)
KRIS: No, look, you just get
a little, like, nip and a tuck
right there.
SCOTT: You're sick.
KRIS: And it takes ten years
off of your life.
SCOTT: You've been in.
Hollywood too long.
KRIS: No, it takes ten years
off your life, I promise.
SCOTT: I don't need to take
ten years off my life.
KRIS: You have to.
SCOTT: I'm definitely not.
SCOTT: And now you're making
me very uncomfortable.
(Kris laughing) ♪ ♪
KHLOE: Good girl! Come on.
Come on, old lady.
Come here, Goober.
Act like you know how to run
again... good old lady.
KOURTNEY: How old is she?
KHLOE: She's like 13 or 14.
KIM: That old? Really?
KHLOE: Yeah.
KIM: So that was what?
I was 20... oh, you're right.
I was, like, 25. So, 25. So, 35.
KHLOE: What's wrong with you?
KIM: So I would say about 12
or 13, I could've been 24.
KHLOE: So 12 or 13?
KIM: Could've been about 23.
Yeah, so about 13, 14.
KHLOE: That's what I said.
KIM: Yep.
KHLOE: Yeah.
KIM: Just doing the math in
my head. Oh.
KHLOE: Okay, a few more runs.
Do you want to do it?
Do you know how?
KOURTNEY: I've been dying to.
KHLOE: Okay.
KIM: I played a game where I
gave her a lot of food, so...
KHLOE: Yeah, Kim gives her
cereal.
Gabbana was Kendall and Kylie's
dog their entire lives.
And then when they all grew up
and moved out, she became,
like, the family dog.
And then when Caitlyn and my mom
got separated, I took Gabbana
in.
Oh, you dropped it.
You can do it.
Dive. Yeah! Good girl!
So she's kind of been the family
dog and everyone has their own
great relationship with her.
Even Kim loves to hate her.
KIM: Oh, my God! Seriously!
Ew! I smell like a wet dog.
KHLOE: I love that whenever I
come home from Cleveland,
Gabbana is always there.
She likes you.
KIM: I know, but you're
getting my shoes all dirty.
Okay, Khloe, Khloe, Khloe.
KHLOE: Gabbana, sit down.
Sit. Sit. Lay down.
Just chill.
You're scaring me how you're
breathing. (Gabbana barks)
Oh! Oh, my God, I've never heard
you bark, really.
This is why I have to hide the
balls.
KIM: But she wants to run.
KHLOE: But she doesn't know
that then she's gonna...
KIM: Have a heart attack?
KHLOE: Like, she'll be
limping all night, I have to
give her a pain med for her hip.
(Gabbana barks) No. No more.
We're done. (Gabbana barks)
KIM: That's really sad.
KHLOE: She had two hip
surgeries.
KIM: I know, but that's,
like, so sad.
KHLOE: You look really good,
though; It looks like you
finally got your rhythm.
No, Gabbana, I didn't throw it.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Hello! How are you?
You know, this is the first
baby store I've been to.
KRIS: I came here when I was
pregnant with Kourtney, and
Robert's grandmother bought me
my first crib. >> KHLOE: Aw.
KRIS: And so this has always
been, like, this tradition.
Have you met Khloe?
KHLOE: No, hi. How are you?
LAUREN: Hi, Khloe.
I'm Lauren, nice to meet you.
KRIS: Now when did you first
start working here? In 70...?
LAUREN: I've been here since
'77.
KHLOE: Oh, my gosh. KRIS: '77.
KHLOE: I thought she was
really exaggerating.
LAUREN: No, she really wasn't.
KHLOE: Wow, that's exciting.
KRIS: So she's been helping
me for my entire journey with
all the kids.
KHLOE: Look at that.
KRIS: So cute.
KHLOE: Yeah, it's so cute.
They're just so little.
KRIS: It makes me sad because
I remember coming in here the
first time, like, to shop for
Kourtney...
KHLOE: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: And now she's just
so mean. (Laughs)
I'm like, when they're so little
they don't...
KHLOE: Talk to you like that.
KRIS: Treat you funny and
talk back, and I don't know why
she's being so...
KHLOE: I don't know why you
guys are in such a weird place.
KRIS: I just wish she would
make an effort to treat me the
way that I feel like I would
love to be treated, 'cause I
love her so much.
She's my firstborn daughter.
My relationship with Kourtney
over the years has been kind of
fabulous, but lately there's
definitely a shift.
KOURTNEY: What are you doing
here?
Amanda and I are about to work
out. >> KRIS: I could join your
workout.
KOURTNEY: I really don't want
to ruin our workout.
Don't come to our workout,
randomly show up when you're not
even invited.
KRIS: I really don't know
where this is coming from.
And it makes me really, really
sad.
KHLOE: Here's that.
KRIS: No, I got it. I got it.
KHLOE: No, stop.
KRIS: This is my treat.
KHLOE: You're not buying...
KRIS: This is my thing.
Yes, I am.
KHLOE: That's crazy, Mom.
KRIS: I did this for Kylie.
This is my, this is my
happiness.
KHLOE: Oh, that's so nice of
you, I didn't think you were...
KRIS: I didn't give birth to
you not to be able to do this.
Don't look.
You're so rude.
KHLOE: That's very nice.
KRIS: When you're doing this
for your daughter, you'll look
back on this and think, "Now I
get it. Now I know what she was"
"feeling." ♪ ♪
KHLOE: I don't know what
people wear.
I just still can't believe this
fits a real person. (Laughs)
Do I keep something this small?
KIM: Oh, my God, yeah.
That's, like, right at the
beginning.
This is cute. >> KHLOE: Cute.
KIM: This is a little...
This is a very Penelope...
KHLOE: Oh, that is literally
Penelope's soul.
KIM: You'll also pick out a
style. Like...
KHLOE: I don't know her style
yet.
KIM: You know what's a fun game?
KHLOE: Foosball.
KIM: Yeah, what is foosball?
We should look into that.
KHLOE: Isn't it, like, the
table? >> KIM: Oh.
(Khloe laughs)
I was like, let's play that.
Let's get teams.
No, the funnest game ever is
the Kylie pregnancy game.
KHLOE: Why?
KIM: Just to see what people
think; Like, there were pictures
of her out on TMZ, and she
looked so skinny.
KHLOE: I know, 'cause it's
the angle... they got her from
face on.
But if they got a side shot,
it would've been over for her.
KIM: If would've been over.
Over.
I literally woke up at 6:00 in
the morning, and I saw it, and
I was like... (gasps)
And I called her and Travis.
They were like, "What's wrong?"
What's wrong?"
They thought something was
wrong, and I'm like, "There's
pictures of you on TMZ."
KHLOE: No.
KIM: He must think we're,
like, freaks.
Your pregnancy has been the
best-kept secret of our
generation.
KYLIE: Like, I'm not trying
to keep it secret, I'm really
doing this for myself.
KIM: Like, this never...
Like, your friends deserve
awards.
KYLIE: Mm-hmm.
KIM: 'Cause seriously, now
you know you have some real
ones.
KYLIE: Yeah.
KIM: 'Cause that wouldn't
have happened in my, in my day.
KYLIE: Don't tell anyone my
secrets. >> KIM: I won't.
KHLOE: These are bizarrely
small, correct?
KIM: Yeah, no, they're...
They stretch, so, like, I would
put North in them all the time
when it would be freezing.
KHLOE: So are we keeping
these? No.
A baby can't wear these.
KIM: If you want to wear a
dress, yeah, and you layer.
Yeah.
KHLOE: At this age, what is
she... where is she going?
This is like you're putting her
in Spanx at three months.
♪ ♪
(Kourtney whooping)
SIMON: You just came?
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
SIMON: We just finished our
shoot, you missed it.
LARSA: How are you?
Very nice seeing you.
SIMON: I put on the zip lace.
KOURTNEY: No you didn't.
LARSA: How are you?
Nice seeing you.
SIMON: For real... I went...
I put on the Good Legs.
They fit.
KOURTNEY: The hugs, do you
need a hug class?
SAVAS: I mean, what do you
want me to crush your chest?
KOURTNEY: No, no. Do you need
a hug class?
Watch. You give a hug like this.
LARSA: She's really good at
that.
KOURTNEY: Your hug, your hug
is like this.
SIMON: Yeah, like...
KOURTNEY: Your hug is... your
hug is like...
SAVAS: What do you want me to
do?
I don't want to break your
chest.
KOURTNEY: You just go like
this. You give a nice hug.
Yes. See that? Where's Khloe?
She's working or something?
She's busy?
LARSA: We're gonna go hang out.
KOURTNEY: Um, I saw the
therapist yesterday.
KHLOE: Hello?
Okay, you yelled at me, so I'm
taking a break to come talk to
you.
KOURTNEY: I was telling them
about my therapy session.
She said because Mom cheated on
Dad, I have, like, an issue with
betrayal because I knew what it
felt like.
KHLOE: But did she say that's
why you're mean to Mom?
'Cause you're mad at her?
KOURTNEY: No, but Mom (bleep)
me in so many ways, we were
talking about it all day
yesterday.
KHLOE: Mom (bleep) you in so
many ways?
KOURTNEY: Lately, in therapy,
a lot of topics that have been
coming up are about childhood
issues and how that affects so
many of my relationships today.
KHLOE: How'd she (bleep) you?
LARSA: Where did that come
from? >> KHLOE: Right. How...?
KOURTNEY: I told you, Larsa.
If I had a problem, I wouldn't
go to her, ever. Did you?
LARSA: But if you had a
problem, she'd be there.
KOURTNEY: I don't know.
Did you? 'Cause I didn't.
KHLOE: I don't go to anyone.
I'm like...
KOURTNEY: Okay, but...
KHLOE: But Kylie and Kim go
to Mom all the time, so, like,
she is available...
KOURTNEY: Okay. To them.
KHLOE: To the kids who need her.
KOURTNEY: I never went to her.
KHLOE: But she's still a
great mom.
KOURTNEY: I would go to Dad.
That's fine.
KHLOE: Oh.
KOURTNEY: I just said she was
not my person that I found
comfort in.
So if you needed advice, I would
never go to her.
KHLOE: Okay, I'm gonna take a
(bleep) photo, guys.
LARSA: Holy! It's a lot.
It's a lot going on here.
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God.
Did you hear Kylie's in labor?
KIM: What?
I don't have my phone on me.
KOURTNEY: If she really
wanted you there, then she would
invite you there.
KIM: No, I know.
(Gabbana whines)
KIM: It's nearing time.
Obviously, when you have a dog
for so many years, you know at
some point, you know, she's not
gonna be here.
KHLOE: For some reason you do
not give Mom the benefit of the
doubt and it's really unfair.
You only remember with Todd or
this or that, but...
KOURTNEY: I don't sit there
and dwell about Todd.
KHLOE: No, we're not saying
that.
KRIS: You have your own Todd
right now.
KOURTNEY: No, I actually
don't. I'm actually not married.
♪ ♪
KRIS: You look really pretty.
(Khloe chuckles)
You look very much like a jewel
tone.
KHLOE: Oh, wow.
KRIS: Like my little jewel.
You're like a jewel.
KHLOE: It's a nice day.
I like when it's a little crisp.
KRIS: Love. Like, love.
KHLOE: I'm also used to
Cleveland weather where it's,
like, super chilly.
KRIS: I love Cleveland.
KHLOE: Me, too.
KRIS: It's my new favorite
place. >> KHLOE: It's so weird.
KRIS: That view is epic.
KHLOE: I know.
I love it there.
KRIS: No, it's really
peaceful. >> KHLOE: I love it.
KRIS: I was really surprised
Kourtney went.
KHLOE: God, you and Kourtney
are, like, at each other's
throats these days.
KRIS: Mm-hmm.
I think that she's going through
a phase in her life where she
has some anger inside that I
don't quite understand.
KHLOE: You think?
It bothers me, like, even how
she, like, says the memory she
has with you, and, like, I get
annoyed by that 'cause they
couldn't be further from the...
KRIS: All she had was
Cinderella fairy dust and
magical wands.
I mean, it was, it was the
best... she was doted on as a
child.
KHLOE: Caviar wishes and
champagne dreams, ladies and
gentlemen.
KRIS: Exactly what it was.
KHLOE: I think she thinks
she's, like, speaking her truth
more and she's... 'cause she
says, "I've been"
nonconfrontational for the past
"ten years and now I'm finding
my voice again."
I don't really know what that
means, but if she feels that
way, that's good.
I don't want to push that away
from her, but I think there's
also a way that we could all get
along here.
KRIS: I wish your dad was
around to say, "You had the"
best, most magical childhood of
any child ever."
That's what we prided ourselves
on.
KHLOE: No, but I don't think
it's the childhood, I think
she's blaming you specifically.
KRIS: For what?
KHLOE: She probably felt like
she was always picking a side
and it was always my dad's.
In the divorce, she always
picked his. KRIS: Yeah. She did.
KHLOE: In the trial, she
picked his.
KRIS: She did. She was
convinced.
KHLOE: She wanted to live
there over your house.
Like, she's always picked his.
So there's something.
KRIS: That's interesting.
KHLOE: When my parents got
divorced, Kourtney took my dad's
side.
KOURTNEY: My parents got a
divorce because my mom had an
affair.
KHLOE: Did Mom ever meet up
with Todd?
KIM: I don't know, but
he e-mailed her again and said
he wanted to meet up with her.
KOURTNEY: That's the worst
idea I've ever even heard.
KRIS: I've paid a price for
what happened to me in my life
and I would hope that none of
you would have to go through the
same things I went through.
KOURTNEY: Okay. I don't want
to keep talking about this.
I don't relate to it.
I don't understand it.
KHLOE: She holds and harbors
all this resentment towards my
mom.
Okay, that's fine, but let's
work things through.
I don't understand, like, why
Kourtney would want to just hold
on to that negative space that
they're in.
For her, I think it's a way to
heal.
Like, if she discusses... I don't
know.
I'm still trying to figure it
out.
KRIS: But then she's got to
accept that circumstance in her
life and not put it on someone
else to be responsible for her
happiness.
I still have scars, right here.
See these three scars?
KHLOE: Why are you bringing
up the negative?
KRIS: This. Because that's
where she pinched me when she
was a teenager.
KHLOE: She didn't pinch you,
she scratched you.
KRIS: This was more than a
scratch if I'm still carrying it
around at 62.
KHLOE: A pinch is nothing.
She dug her nails into you.
KRIS: That's right.
KHLOE: She clawed you.
KRIS: She clawed me.
KHLOE: Well, I really feel
like the only way to, like,
resolve any of this or even
just for, like, you can talk to
me until you're blue in the
face, but I'm not Kourtney.
KRIS: Yeah.
KHLOE: So I feel like at some
point you and Kourt have to
talk, but, like, enough with the
bull(bleep). Like, talk.
I feel like she... the things
that she says to, like, me and.
Kim about you... KRIS: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: Like, she should say
to you.
KRIS: She should.
KHLOE (British accent): Look
at me trying to be so
responsible all of a sudden.
KRIS: I'm proud of you.
I just figure that I'm...
It's... you guys are so cyclical.
I just, like, I'll get...
KHLOE: What are we?
KRIS: It's a cycle. You know.
KHLOE: Cyclical? Wow.
You are smart.
KRIS: I know. ♪ ♪
KIM: Well, so you need
vision boards.
KHLOE: So what you do first
is that I cut out words...
KIM: Honey, I have vis...
I have mood boards all over my
closet...
KHLOE: I mean, not... Yep.
KIM: Of looks.
KHLOE: So I normally tear
sheets and I cut.
So you have your system and I
have mine. If you want...
KIM: Mine are more fashion-y.
You know what, the problem with
me doing a vision board, I'm
here with you, and we'll take
out... we'll cut out words.
How about words?
'Cause pictures can offend me.
KHLOE: We've got to buy
magazines with more pictures and
less words. >> KIM: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: The cutest dog, this
Chow Chow.
KIM: That's my fav dog, so...
KHLOE: But they're really
aggressive.
KIM: Really aggressive.
KHLOE: Let's pull it out in
case we want to put it on our
vision board. >> KIM: Yep.
(Gabbana whines)
Did anyone see that?
KHLOE: She had a little bit
of a seizure.
KIM: She fully convulsed.
No, I think she's...
That's really sad.
KHLOE: Yeah, she's getting
old. I don't know what to do.
I think about it all the time.
It took her, like, 15 minutes to
get up the other day.
It was really sad.
KIM: It's nearing time.
Any month now.
KHLOE: Any month now?
KIM: That's so sad.
She literally convulsed.
KHLOE: Look at her stomach.
KIM: She, like, shook.
KHLOE: Yeah, I saw that.
Okay. Oh, okay. Just relax.
That's so sad.
KIM: That breaks my heart.
Gabbana is really getting old,
and I'm just sad because Gabbana
and Khloe are really, like, two
peas in a pod and Gabbana's
always been there for Khloe
during so many hard times.
And obviously, when you have a
dog for so many years, you know
at some point, you know, she's
not gonna be here.
(Gabbana panting)
KHLOE: Hi, Gabbana.
Hi, Gabbana. Hi.
(Kim gasps) What?
KIM: Cher says, "I think the
Cher hair trend is..." that's
what the interviewer said, and
then her answer is,
"A good look.
I saw Kim Kardashian West
do it and thought it was so
great."
KHLOE: How awesome!
Does she not look impeccable?
It's out of control how good she
looks.
KIM: She will forever be the
O.G.
(Khloe laughs) ♪ ♪
(indistinct conversation)
PENELOPE: I'm done.
KOURTNEY: You're done?
PENELOPE: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: I don't think you
ate. >> PENELOPE: I ate bread.
KHLOE: Kourt.
Kourt, I have something to say
to you.
I was talking to MJ today, she
said something how Mom said to
her, something like, "Oh, you've"
"never cooked for us" or
something, and MJ was like,
"You know, it's so funny, Mom's
memory of me."
And I was like, "That's like
Kourtney; Kourtney's memory of."
Mom is very negative."
And she was like, "Yeah, she
remembers when Mom was going
through her divorce."
For some reason you do not give
Mom the benefit of the doubt,
ever, from your childhood, and
it's really unfair.
Never was Mom locking you in a
cabinet, leaving you with food,
or no food, for, like, weeks on
end, like...
KIM: I had no idea she was in
labor.
KOURTNEY: Kylie is about to
have her baby, and it's pretty
crazy that it really hasn't been
confirmed.
As you know, I've been going to
therapy lately, and my therapist
says your intimate relationships
bring up childhood issues, and I
feel like I've been... not
intentionally, but, like, I'll
act somewhat resentful.
KRIS: I just, I never want
you to be disappointed in me.
KHLOE: For some reason, you
do not give Mom the benefit of
the doubt, ever, from your
childhood, and it's really
unfair.
You only remember with Todd or
this or that, but...
KOURTNEY: I don't sit there
and dwell about Todd.
KHLOE: No, we're not saying
that.
KRIS: You have your own Todd
right now.
KOURTNEY: No, I actually
don't.
I'm actually not married, and
I'm not having an affair.
You can't compare one to the
other.
That's absolutely not true.
I don't think it's even about
talking to my mom about it.
I think it's, like, we all have
different experiences with my
mom, and I think it's not
something, really, that my mom
can fix. KHLOE: I'm just saying,
sometimes our memories get a
little warped by our age.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KHLOE: I'm just saying, but
don't be so hard on your mom.
♪ ♪
(Honey barking) >> KHLOE: Ooh!
Just plopping on down.
When do you figure out
breastfeeding schedules?
Do I determine that?
KOURTNEY: Well, I used to,
like, feed on demand, but
usually after, I think, a month,
and I think it's every four
hours. >> KHLOE: That's not bad.
So, you and Mom, like, all this
tension at dinner the other
night. Why?
KOURTNEY: Obviously, issues
have come up in therapy, since
I've started going, of issues
that I have with her, but I'm
not, like, looking to hold on to
them for my whole life and,
like, have an issue with her.
KHLOE: Mm-hmm.
But I think it's confusing,
like, to all of us, like, why
now when you are almost 40?
And you are a mom, I would think
you would be more compassionate
or understanding as a mom that's
dating and trying to figure out
her life, like...
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: Probably how confusing
it is just for you.
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: And I think that
you're not as understanding as I
thought you would be with Mom.
I know Kourtney for some reason
feels more comfort in talking to
a stranger about family stuff
rather than talking to the
source, and I would be fine with
that if then Kourtney took
whatever her and her therapist
talked about, and then came to
the source.
But, like, that's the part we're
missing.
And that's what's frustrating
to us all, 'cause we could never
resolve something, or work
through something, or just even
fight about something if we
don't know what's going on.
It's always us pulling teeth and
guessing what's wrong with her.
I think you feel almost
embarrassed to say that you do
care.
Like, you're allowed to care.
You should want your mom's love
and affection and...
KOURTNEY: Yeah, I'm just
saying truly in my everyday
life, I'm not, like, sitting
there...
KHLOE: Because you got used
to not... >> KOURTNEY: Right.
KHLOE: You got used to not
having it, but that doesn't mean
you still don't want it.
Why don't you talk to Mom?
Like, calmly, and don't raise
your voice, don't say, like,
trigger words, like, just
communicate.
(Honey barking)
KOURTNEY: Honey is wild.
KHLOE: Honey needs to be on...
KOURTNEY: She just needs
attention.
KHLOE: I don't think kids
should have a dog until they're,
like, older.
Unless the parent will take
care of it. ♪ ♪
I've been at work all
day long, and I come home, and.
Gabbana just can't get out of
her bed.
I love you.
Like, right now, she doesn't
even shake her tail or anything.
Which is just not like her, and
you can tell, like, she's
breathing a little strangely,
but, like, she's tense right
here.
Well, she feels tense and, like,
I had to put her legs back
together 'cause they slid apart,
but you can tell she just can't
move from this position.
And I don't know why.
She just couldn't get herself
up, and I just knew that
something was wrong with her.
I mean, do we think she's dying?
Look at her, she won't move.
Thankfully, both of my
assistants are so sweet, they
both come over, and they help me
lift her and take her to the
vet.
VETERINARIAN: So, she has
what I suspect to be cancer
called hemangiosarcoma.
We ultrasounded her heart and
saw a heart-based tumor; That's
why she was having trouble
breathing.
Her heart rate is slowing
significantly, and I, um, think
her end is, unfortunately, near.
(Khloe makes kissing sound)
KHLOE: I love you.
Oh, I can't handle this...
KRIS: We're hours away.
(baby crying)
I can already tell that Kylie is
gonna be the most amazing mom.
KOURTNEY: How did she do for
her labor?
KRIS: She did really, really
well.
It was really exciting.
I delivered the baby.
I pulled her out. >> KIM: Ew.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: What are you doing?
Just trying to make us feel
worse about ourselves?
You couldn't have, like, worn
something baggy and depressing?
You had to be, like, this
gorgeous? >> KIM: Thank you.
KHLOE: Like, I've already had
a bad day, you need to come out
here with your abs? KIM: Sorry.
KHLOE: It was such a horrible
night.
Gabbana passed away at, like,
2:00 a.m.
We had to put her to sleep, and
it's so sad, but I am so
thankful that she chose to go
after I was able to hug her and
kiss her and say my good-byes to
her.
We took her to this vet here,
and they were like, "A mass has"
grown in her heart... and it's a
certain kind of cancer that
forms really fast."
And then they said, "We have to
put her down tonight."
KHLOE: I just never, in a
million years, thought she was
gonna die last night.
That's what the crazy part is.
KIM: I was, like,
hysterically crying.
And I was like, "Why? I don't
even like dogs," but I was
hysterically crying over
Gabbana.
KHLOE: You secretly loved
her, secretly.
Like, you would always give her
cereal.
KIM: It's so sad.
KHLOE: Kourtney said she
cried.
Tristan was like, "I appreciate"
"her. I've not..." 'cause he's
never owned a dog, and he was,
like, "I never liked dogs until
Gabbana."
He's like, "She was a great
little lady."
I was like, "Oh, she was."
KIM: The house felt empty
today. >> KHLOE: It is empty.
The house is empty.
The house will never be the
same. ♪ ♪
You know, none of us want
Gabbana in pain, so I think
we're all happy that Gabbana's
in a better place.
Hey, Goober.
I was really nervous to tell.
Kendall and Kylie.
And Kendall was devastated.
PENELOPE: Look at Gabbana!
KRIS: Gabbana has really been
a best friend to every single
member of our family, but kind
of at different times.
She's been there for Khloe
through a lot of really bad
times.
KHLOE: Aw, she wants the red
one.
KOURTNEY: Oh!
KHLOE: She's just such a
sweetheart.
KOURTNEY: She's a sweet girl.
KIM: You have great teeth,
Gabbana.
(Khloe laughs) She does.
Gabbana has, like, always been
that soul there by Khloe's side.
KHLOE: Isn't our dog so cute?
SCOTT: And you're a good dog.
KHLOE: Hey, Goobs.
It's so crazy to me that a dog
could touch your life the way
Gabbana's touched my life.
I mean, she's been with me
through so much, and when I've
been alone and had nobody,
Gabbana was always there, and I
always felt protected, even
though she wouldn't hurt a fly.
And I always just had a buddy
and a companion.
I could always hear her in my
home, and now I hear silence,
and it's just crazy she's just
gone.
♪ ♪
KRIS: Are you tired?
You must be exhausted.
KHLOE: (sighs) Yeah.
I mean, I'm just so
uncomfortable in this body.
(groans)
KRIS: This is like a variety
show.
It's pregnant, menopausal,
perfect.
KHLOE: What fetish are you into?
(Kris laughs) ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I typically don't
love confrontation, and sitting
in front of Khloe wasn't the
best time for me to have this
conversation with my mom,
but if my going to therapy and,
you know, figuring this all out
is making me resentful towards
my mom, which is not how I want
to feel and it's not how I want
to treat her, then I feel like
it is worth having a
conversation with her, just to
let her know that's not my
intention and that it's really
about me working on myself.
Um, so I wanted to talk to you.
KRIS: Mm-hmm.
KOURTNEY: Because I feel like
I've been somewhat resentful,
but I don't want to be feeling
this way.
KRIS: Kylie! Hey, Ky.
Hi, Stormi.
KHLOE: Oh, my gosh.
KOURTNEY: I wanted to talk to
you because I feel like I've
been somewhat resentful, but I
don't want to be feeling this
way.
As you know, I've been going to
therapy lately, and my therapist
says your intimate relationships
bring up childhood issues, and I
just don't think it's fair if
I'm not communicating it, and I
don't want to go back in time
and be, like, "Let's talk about
all the reasons," you know.
I even asked my therapist, like,
I don't want to be feeling this
way, like, this is, like, why am
I coming to therapy to just,
like, I didn't feel this way
ever, you know?
KRIS: Mm-hmm.
KOURTNEY: Like, for years.
You know, she was like, "It'll
pass, you just have to, like",
get through it."
And I feel like it has passed,
and I'm not, like, feeling that
way anymore, but I just wanted
to explain that to you so you
understand where it's coming
from.
KRIS: I know that sometimes
you've made jokes or-or even
talked seriously about your
childhood, and at the time...
KOURTNEY: But I'm not here to
go back in time and start
dwelling on childhood stuff.
KRIS: I know, but I'm just...
KOURTNEY: I'm just saying, it
got brought up from me going
to therapy.
What we usually do as a family
is we criticize each other,
we're judgmental, and we give
each other an attitude and
we're bitchy.
So, moving forward in life, I've
made it a point with my sisters
already to, like, not accept
that anymore.
KRIS: All I want for you is
your... the best, most joyful,
peaceful life that you can have.
And whatever it takes for me to
be a part of that, that's all I
want.
That's the joy of my life, is
you guys. I have nothing else.
Just, I never want you to be
disappointed in me...
KOURTNEY: I'm not.
KRIS: So if there's
something you want to say, or
something that, you know, you
need to have me work on, I'm
100% ready to work on it because
I love you so much.
You're my firstborn, and I
wouldn't trade that for
anything.
I don't want you to be
disappointed in me, and if
there's something that, you
know, you ever want to talk
about, I just want you to
remember that I just want you to
be happy.
That's all I care about.
So...
KOURTNEY: Moving forward, I'm
gonna just tell you if some... if
I don't like something, or if
something is hurtful or whatever
instead of, like, just being a
bitch about it. >> KRIS: Okay.
KOURTNEY: A lot is still up
in the air, but, you know, I've
gone through a phase of being,
like, more sensitive to things.
It's nothing bad, it's just
understanding and then
understanding how that affects
our current relationships.
Like, if there's a certain
behavior that, like, Younes will
do or something that's similar
to things that my mom would do,
just, like, subconsciously, it
will just bring up similar
issues. There is, like, that
uncomfortable place when you are
growing, but I think it's
something I have to deal with
myself.
KRIS: But just for the
record, you had a pretty great
childhood.
KOURTNEY: Mom, I did, but
there's things that just give
you issues in everyone's
childhood. >> KRIS: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: Um, anyways...
I love you.
KRIS: I love you, too.
You're my little chick.
I love you so much.
KOURTNEY: I love you.
I feel dizzy.
KRIS: Okay, that's 'cause
you're shorter than me. ♪ ♪
KRIS: Want to hold hands?
KOURTNEY: Let's go for a
stroll.
KRIS: Let's hold hands and
skip. KOURTNEY: You know, when I
went to Big Sur, I skipped for a
good, like, hour and a half
straight.
KRIS: Can I tell you what.
Mason did when we were at
Disneyland?
KOURTNEY: Look how cute.
KRIS: So I grabbed his
hands... >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KRIS: And I said, "Come
on, Mason, let's skip like we"
used to."
We were skipping, he was
skipping with me.
It was so funny.
KOURTNEY: He's so funny, Mase.
KRIS: He really is funny.
In such a good way, he reminds
me of Scott, you know?
'Cause he's got that cute
personality. KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: And he's so handsome.
KOURTNEY: Oh, look, what is
this little store?
KRIS: Let's go in here.
This is cute. This is so you.
KOURTNEY: I like this one
better for you than the navy.
KRIS: For jet skiing?
You don't like them?
KOURTNEY: They're just not
you. The black is more you.
KRIS: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: The navy is not
you.
KRIS: I think Kourtney and I
have gotten through that rough
patch and started a healing
process.
That's a really big step in the
right direction, especially for
her.
She's always gonna hang on to
the past a little bit, but what
I'm hopeful for is that we can
look forward to an amazing
future together because I love
her more than anything.
KOURTNEY: Oh, this is what I
was telling you, this.
I have these. >> KRIS: Sex dust?
What do we do with the dust?
KOURTNEY: You put it in,
like, water or a shake.
KRIS: Oh, I need some sex
dust for sure.
Some sex dust and some cheese
puffs, I'm all good. ♪ ♪
COURTNEY: Okay.
KIM: I can't even sit down.
Am I sitting down?
COURTNEY: Yes.
KIM: Okay.
COURTNEY: You're on the mat.
No, we're not gonna get on the
mat yet, though.
KIM: Oh, okay. Okay.
Your Instagram is, like, so
motivating. COURTNEY: Thank you.
KIM: Like, you make me want
to get in better shape.
COURTNEY: Well, that's what
we're doing.
KIM: I know, I know. (Bleep)
My quads.
COURTNEY: Okay. Ready?
KIM: Okay. Yeah.
COURTNEY: Five...
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God, did you
hear Kylie's in labor?
KIM: What?
KOURTNEY: Yes.
Why aren't you there?
KIM: Wh-What do you mean?
KOURTNEY: She didn't want me
there.
KIM: She really wanted me there.
KOURTNEY: I mean, she didn't
tell me to come there.
KIM: I know, she planned it
with me to have me there, but
then she asked me, and I was
like, "Well, I think Khloe is",
like, a better delivery room
person."
But I didn't know she is, I
don't have my phone on me.
KOURTNEY: If she really
wanted you there, then she would
invite you there.
KIM: No, I know, but, like, I
had no idea she was in labor.
♪ ♪
KIM: I had no idea she was in
labor. KOURTNEY: All right, but
don't act like, "Oh, she really
wanted me there."
'Cause you would be there if she
really wanted you there.
KIM: No, before we discussed
how it was gonna go.
Okay, it's not a fight over who
she wants in the delivery room.
Who cares?
KOURTNEY: No, but I think it
is 'cause you're trying to be
like, "Oh, she really wanted"
me."
KIM: She wanted me there and
I said, "Khloe is the one."
So she must've picked Khloe over
me. >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
Kylie is about to have her baby
and it's pretty crazy that it
really hasn't been confirmed, so
I don't want to be the one with
the info or getting blamed for,
you know, someone finding out
the secret.
KIM: I'll go to the hospital
right after. You know...
KOURTNEY: By the way, North's
in there eating candies.
KIM: Stop, I know. I...
Oh, stop.
Girl, that's enough candy.
I heard you've been eating so
much candy.
No, no, no. We have dinner soon.
We'll have some later.
No, no, no. Too much candy.
The cavity bugs will come, and
all your teeth will fall out
and it will just be so bad.
What?
NORTH: Candy. I want candy.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I think Kylie wants
you to bring Chicago over and
take a photo with the two of
them.
KIM: I know. I was going to
yesterday and then I just got
tired.
Can you believe that Kylie got
out of the hospital with not one
report?
KRIS: I know. It was amazing.
KIM: That's amazing.
And now Caitlyn can never say we
have big mouths and we leak
everything.
We kept that a secret.
KRIS: I mean, that was a lot
of anxiety for me.
It was crazy.
It was like, people were saying,
"We're gonna post," you know,
"We're gonna announce this."
And I'm like, "No!"
But she did it.
KIM: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: Perfect. And it was
such a positive experience for
her.
KIM: Totally.
Everyone was just like, "Okay",
we get it.
We get why you kept it, you
know, private."
KRIS: It's only been a
couple of days since Kylie had
baby Stormi.
I can already tell that Kylie is
going to be the most amazing
mom and is so in love with her
baby.
♪ ♪
KYLIE: Aw. Two burgers.
One for me, one for the baby.
And two different fries.
KRIS: We're hours away.
(Stormi cries)
KIM: Kylie's always wanted to
be a mom, so this is really
exciting for her.
She just didn't want anyone
changing her happy moment and
her happy pregnancy, so, um, I'm
really proud of her, that she
stuck to her guns and was able
to tell her story her way.
KOURTNEY: How did she do for
her labor?
KRIS: She did really, really
well.
She just kept saying, "I just"
"don't feel any pain," and you'd
see these contractions like
crazy.
And she would go, "I just, I'm"
not feeling it."
And I'm like, this is really
weird. She was such a trooper.
She really was. She was so calm.
It was really exciting.
I delivered the baby.
KOURTNEY: She told me.
KRIS: I delivered her.
KIM: You did? >> KRIS: Yes.
KOURTNEY: She told me.
KIM: I didn't hear that.
KRIS: Yes! I delivered the
baby! I pulled her out.
KIM: Ew. (Kourtney laughs)
♪ ♪
KIM: You look so cute right now.
KHLOE: What? KIM: And skinny.
KHLOE: Okay, now I know
you're lying.
KIM: No, I'm serious.
KHLOE: Hi, Chi Town.
What's going on, girl?
Are you trying to wave at us?
Hi, girl.
I have a present for you,
Kendall. KENDALL: What is this?
KHLOE: Gabbana's actual paw
print.
KENDALL: (gasps) Oh!
KHLOE: I got it made for you.
KENDALL: Thank you, sister.
KIM: That's so cute.
KHLOE: I know you wouldn't
want one. (Laughs)
KIM: I mean, like, I would
have, like, a paw print on a
piece of paper.
KHLOE: The only one that
would want one is Kenny.
KENDALL: I love it. Aw.
KHLOE: Don't ever say I
didn't get you anything.
KENDALL: I love it.
KHLOE: Kendall and Gabbana
have always been really close
and had a great relationship.
KIM: I think it's time to eat.
KHLOE: The bond we all had
was so strong and beautiful and
it's crazy she's just gone.
KIM: Yummy.
KRIS: This looks so good.
KHLOE: Does everyone know the
necklace I got Kendall?
KRIS: What?
KENDALL: It's Gabbana's paw
print.
KRIS: Kendall. Aw.
COREY: Aw, that's tight.
KENDALL: Isn't it cute?
KHLOE: And I got her ashes
today, but I have Gabbana's bed,
and I haven't felt the need to
get rid of it yet, but I feel
like now I want to sub Gabbana's
bed for a baby bed.
I think it's time.
KIM: That's really sweet.
KHLOE: Today was actually the
first day that I felt like I
could take her bed out of my
room.
Whenever I would come back from.
Cleveland, Gabbana would be
there and she was just my buddy.
But now whenever I come back
from Cleveland I'll have a baby.
I'm grateful that Gabbana left
me at a time where she knew I
wouldn't be alone.
COREY: Well, have you seen
the facilities yet, where you're
giving birth?
KHLOE: No.
KOURTNEY: Don't go see them
in advance. >> KHLOE: Why?
KOURTNEY: 'Cause it's not a
good idea.
SCOTT: You know what the
rooms look like.
KOURTNEY: She's not giving
birth there.
KHLOE: I'm not giving birth
at Cedars.
SCOTT: So you should go look.
KOURTNEY: No.
The first time, we didn't look.
I had no clue what was
happening and it's so much
better that way.
SCOTT: Is it?
KHLOE: Tim went this weekend
and assessed it all.
SCOTT: Okay.
KRIS: Kylie!
KOURTNEY: Hi, Ky. Hi, Stormi.
KHLOE: Oh, my God!
Hey, bo-bo. Mwah.
KIM: Oh, my goodness.
KHLOE: Ours are gonna be
twins, I think.
KIM: Oh, she just gave me the
craziest side-eye.
Did you see that?
KYLIE: Yeah, she's...
KIM: She literally went like
this.
KYLIE: 'Cause she knows you
kissed me first before my mom.
KHLOE: And she'll never let
that down.
KENDALL: What happened?
KHLOE: Kim got to kiss her
before Kylie did.
KIM: It was, like, days later.
Who knew that she didn't kiss
her on the mouth?
KYLIE: She was like, "Ooh!"
And jokingly was like, "Ooh,
"look, I'm your first kiss," and
kissed her, and I was like...
(gasps)
KHLOE: Kylie's like, "That is"
not funny."
KIM: Stop. Will you text that
to me? >> KHLOE: Oh, my God.
KENDALL: Let me see.
KIM: We're gonna have, like,
a book of, like, the triplets.
KYLIE: I know.
KIM: Okay, so now that it's,
like, all said and done...
KYLIE: Mm-hmm.
KIM: What is your real
take on pregnancy?
KYLIE: I like it. I miss it.
KIM: You miss it?
KYLIE: Yeah, I had, like, the
easiest pregnancy ever.
Like, you just feel... you never
feel alone and, like, I was
really sad to not be pregnant
anymore. >> KIM: That's so cute.
KYLIE: Khloe, I'm just so
excited for you.
I can't wait.
KRIS: I'd like to raise a
glass and make a toast to Khloe,
another little Kardashian that
you're bringing into the world.
Next there'll be nine.
KOURTNEY: Cheers, everyone.
ALL: Cheers.
KOURTNEY: Yay to Khloe.
KYLIE: Cheers to Khloe.
Stormi's not gonna be the new
girl in town anymore.
KIM: Chicago was, like, the
new girl in town for, like, a
day. >> KYLIE: Two weeks.
KOURTNEY: And now Stormi's
got three months, maybe, as the
new girl.
KYLIE: Anyone else pregnant?
KRIS: Nope. Not me. I'm good.
KIM: Nope, but...
COREY: Wait a minute. Wait,
wait, if you get...
KIM: Just kidding. (Laughter)
Keeping Up
With the Kardashians...
WOMAN: You're always working
and you need to have a better
work-life balance.
WOMAN: To our world tour.
WOMAN 2: Our world tour.
KENDALL: Tour.
KHLOE: Are you and Kanye good?
KIM: We had a fight 'cause I
wouldn't get him a Band-Aid.
KHLOE: Kim, like, you
completely left Kourtney on that
(bleep) e-mail.
KIM: I was talking about.
Kourtney in the e-mail as if she
wasn't on the e-mail.
Captioning sponsored by
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS.
Captioned by