♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God, people
are going so crazy.
KIM: They hate me. They hate me.
KOURTNEY: People hate Kim
from her comment on the show.
SCOTT: What?
KIM: Thanks for posting.
SCOTT: Why, what's the problem?
KIM: I... We got into a fight.
I said, "You're the least"
exciting to look at."
KOURTNEY: No, she didn't say
it to me, she said it to...
KIM: No, Khloe.
Yeah, she was walking...
SCOTT: Yeah, I remember that.
KIM: Yeah, and I go... no, it
was to Khloe and my mom... I go,
"She's..."
What I meant is you're the most
boring.
People think that is like I
said, "Kill your mom."
KOURTNEY: No, but people are
like, "I've been abused by my
family for years, and I know"
that it's very hurtful."
KIM: I knew they would do
this to me.
I-I knew it would happen.
SCOTT: Yeah, but I feel like
anything you say, you got to be
careful. >> KOURTNEY: But I...
No, it was... It's...
Let's not justify it.
SCOTT: It was very mean.
Why? But that's your sister.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, but...
SCOTT: You say bad things
about her, too.
KIM: All right, all right,
let's not rehash.
KOURTNEY: But I'm saying, and
then somebody...
SCOTT: You call her a porn
star every time I talk to you.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, right.
Somebody just wrote, um, this
thing, like, "You should thank."
Kim for your career."
SCOTT: I do all the time.
KOURTNEY: And then I was...
SCOTT: I swear.
KOURTNEY: But I was gonna
write back and say, "If it"
wasn't for my personality and
being funny, then our show
"wouldn't exist." (Scott laughs)
SCOTT: For sure, without you,
this whole thing would be dead.
(Kourtney laughs) ♪ ♪
KANYE: This room is, like,
the vibe for how all houses
should be.
And I'm feeling like the
couches should be, like, real
big (bleep).
(laughs) KIM: So, I saw on the
schedule that you're going to
Paris for Virgil's show.
KANYE: Yeah, I just think...
I complain about people that
I've done business with missing
important moments of mine and
missing important moments of
ours, so I can't do the same
thing to Virgil.
Like, this is my brother.
You know, I got to be there for
him for this moment, no matter
what.
I don't care if we just got into
an argument right then.
If we're family and we're
brothers, I have to be there.
KIM: Virgil Abloh is one of.
Kanye's oldest, best friends.
They have worked together for
over a decade.
Grew up in Chicago together, and
he is now the art director for
the Louis Vuitton men's.
KANYE: I mean, Virgil just
put in the most time.
You know, away from his family.
We're-we're brothers.
We interned at Fendi together.
We learned how to design on.
Photoshop together.
We used to always make this joke
that somebody shrunk our JPEG
because we... the-the designs
always stayed as JPEGs.
They never, like, became real,
actual clothes.
And, you know, I remember when.
Virgil showed me the designs
with the stripes on the back,
the Off-White stripes.
Those stripes definitely earned
him his stripes, I'll tell you
that.
KIM: Virgil has his first
Louis Vuitton fashion show
coming up in Paris, and, you
know, Kanye's just super excited
for him.
KANYE: I don't want to put
any pressure on you to go to
Paris.
I know that was really hard the
last time you were in Paris,
so...
I just think for the culture,
for Kim K. To show up to the
first black designer at Louis.
Vuitton's show who was the best
man at my wedding... just, the
world would just really love to
see you there.
Be surprised to see you there
and love to see you there.
But it's just no...
there's no pressure.
KIM: I have to think about it.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Look what I got.
KENDALL: It's huge.
KHLOE: I like to do, um, you
know, different types of
workouts. >> KRIS: Oh, my God.
I think you get in right here in
this hole.
KHLOE: I don't know.
What the (bleep), I just get in?
KRIS: I think you just have
to kind of jump in.
KENDALL: Wait, I'm getting in
the other side.
KHLOE: This is so cool.
(Kris laughs)
KRIS: All right, have a race!
KHLOE: Wait!
KRIS: On your mark, get set...
KHLOE: Wait! >> KRIS: Go!
Come on, come on, Khloe!
KENDALL: You bitch!
(Khloe shrieks) KRIS: Come on.
KENDALL: It's so hard.
(grunting)
KRIS: Come on. Let's go.
Run! Run! (Khloe shrieks)
Run!
KENDALL: How the (bleep)...?
This is so hard.
KRIS: Oh, Kenny, I'll come
help you.
KENDALL: It's really hard.
KRIS: Help her. (Laughs)
KHLOE: Jesus. KENDALL: Yay.
It's really hot. (Khloe exhales)
We'll give her the sunny side.
KHLOE: Yeah.
KRIS: It was exhausting just
watching you ladies.
KHLOE: Yeah.
KRIS: Well, I just got a call
from Shelli, and she said she's
doing an event at the Forum,
and she wants to put together
this huge poker tournament and,
um, do it along with the City of
Hope, so all the proceeds will
go to the City of Hope.
They do a lot of cancer
research, and I think that this
is such a near and dear cause
to my heart and, I know, to your
heart, so I just think it would
be a really nice thing for us to
do.
KHLOE: I don't know how to
play poker.
KRIS: I don't know how to
play poker, either.
She's been asking me to play
poker with her for years.
You can just sit there and look
cute, sweetie.
KHLOE: Oh, well, that's easy.
I have never played poker
before, but given the cause and
that my Auntie Shelli is asking,
I will do anything for her.
I find it to be an honor that we
are even asked to be a part of
this.
KENDALL: All right, y'all.
I'm totally down, I'm very in,
but I have to go.
Muy importante.
KENDALL: Bye. KRIS: Bye, Kenny.
Have a good day.
KENDALL: You, too, beautiful.
KRIS: Love you.
KHLOE: Won't it be sort of
embarrassing if, like, all of
us... what is it, five of us or
four of us... that if we go and
then we don't even win and don't
know how to play...
Like, that just makes...
That's the only thing that makes
me a little uncomfortable.
KRIS: Well, Shelli also said
that she's happy to make sure
that we have a tutor or a coach
or a teacher.
KHLOE: Great.
I'm ready to learn.
Let's raise some money.
KRIS: Let's go get it!
KHLOE: Let's raise some money!
KRIS: Yeah! ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: No, hurry, hurry!
(Penelope shrieks)
PENELOPE: Help her! Mama!
MASON: Mama!
KHLOE: Get out of the way. Okay.
KOURTNEY: I'm okay.
Let's push KoKo in instead.
KHLOE: Wait, but are they all
gonna cry if I do this?
I don't...
PENELOPE: Yeah, we'll cry.
KHLOE: No, you're not gonna cry.
MASON: Oh, Mama!
KHLOE: She wants this.
I can't do it. Oh!
Oh, my God.
I wasn't watching what...
(laughs)
KIM: So, I think I'm gonna go
to Paris and go to the Louis
Vuitton show.
KHLOE: Oh, my...
That is, like, that's really
major on your part.
KIM: Yeah. Even though I'm
nervous, I think, like, it's
really important to Kanye to go.
I feel like it's, like, the
right thing to do, like, for.
Virgil even though, like...
KHLOE: And I think it's
important that eventually you
have, like, to go back, and it's
like, what better time?
KIM: And it's so quick.
We're only gonna go for a day.
KHLOE: How do you feel now?
KIM: I mean, I think it's,
like...
KHLOE: It's time.
KIM: I definitely want to be
there to support Kanye and
Virgil, but the last time I was
there, you know, obviously,
like, a horrific experience for
me. REPORTER: It was the middle
of the night when five masked
men broke into the TV star...
REPORTER 2: Scary situation
for reality star Kim Kardashian.
West.
REPORTER 3: $6.7 million and
a ring worth $4.5 million.
KIM: You know, I'm going
really cautiously, and I think
going for such a short period of
time definitely helps me
mentally.
But I guess you never know what
could happen.
HUANG: As you know, we've
been doing ultrasounds to kind
of make sure that we have plenty
of eggs to harvest.
KOURTNEY: I'm coming to the
doctor to start the process of
freezing my eggs.
HUANG: See the dark circle
here? >> KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
HUANG: Okay, so here's one
follicle.
KOURTNEY: Only one?
Maybe it's just not the best
time.
KIM: I hope that I can start
to remember all the magical
things about Paris and why Kanye
and I fell in love with it here.
There's so many people, so much
paparazzi. (Paparazzi clamoring)
I'm just, like, hypersensitive
to this right now.
HUANG: Hey, how are you?
KOURTNEY: How are you?
HUANG: Hi. Good to see you.
KOURTNEY: Good to see you.
HUANG: How have you been?
KOURTNEY: I have almost
started the process of freezing
my eggs a few times, and the
timing is finally... feels right
with my schedule, and so I'm
coming to the doctor to get a
checkup to make sure that
everything looks good to start
the process.
HUANG: As you know, we've
been doing ultrasounds to kind
of make sure that we have plenty
of eggs to... to harvest.
And so some months you'll have
more, some months you'll have
less.
We want to get a month where you
have more. Okay? KOURTNEY: Okay.
HUANG: 'Cause if we do this,
I want to make it worthwhile.
So we want to get... I would say
for you, knowing kind of what we
know about you, five to ten.
KOURTNEY: Okay.
HUANG: Okay? 'Cause if we
can get five to ten, even as you
get older, these will stay
younger.
Okay? So we'll take a quick look
right now.
KOURTNEY: Okay.
HUANG: All right?
So, you're gonna feel a light
touch, okay?
Sorry about that.
A little bit of pressure.
That's it.
So, we're gonna look at the
right side first, okay,
Kourtney?
See the dark circle here?
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
HUANG: Okay, so, here's one
follicle.
All right, so on this side, just
that one, okay?
KOURTNEY: Only one?
HUANG: On the right side.
So, here's where more follicles
are.
See this right here?
KOURTNEY: Uh-huh.
HUANG: That's your left ovary.
So, on this side you have about
four.
KOURTNEY: When the doctor
tells me that I have five
follicles, I'm kind of shocked.
Why am I even doing this when I
have five?
Should I come back another month
when I might have more?
Like, maybe it's just not
the best time.
HUANG: In two years, five is
gonna be down to three or four.
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
HUANG: And then a few years
later, it's gonna be down to one
or two.
You decide, uh, and I'll help
you with that decision.
KOURTNEY: Okay, thank you.
♪ ♪
KRIS: I don't know how to
play poker, and I don't think
you guys know how to play cards,
so I don't want to go in...
KIM: Well, I know how to play
cards; I just don't know how to
play poker.
KRIS: What kind of cards do
you know how to play? KIM: Gin.
KRIS: Oh.
KIM: I'm, like, a master gin
player. >> KRIS: I drink gin.
Anyway, Shelli set us up with
some pros to teach us all how to
play poker so we don't totally
humiliate ourselves while we're
at her tournament. Oh, my gosh.
Oh, this is so serious.
PHIL: Ready to learn some
poker? KHLOE: Yes. I'm excited.
KRIS: Hi. >> LIOR: Hello!
KIM: How are you?
KRIS: I've never done this
before... I'm really scared.
ANTONIO: No one here is a
professional poker player except
for me.
KRIS: I have definitely got
the best pro.
He's a three-time world
champion.
There's no way the girls are
gonna come close to winning when
I've got this guy in my back
pocket.
KHLOE: What's the most money
you've ever won?
PHIL: Over a million dollars
a couple times.
KHLOE: What?
Listen, Phil is (bleep) legit.
He has 15 bracelets.
That's kind of like (bleep)
trophies, I guess, in another
language.
KIM: So, do you play gambling
games or not really?
LIOR: I am actually not...
I'm not allowed to.
I'll show you why in a second.
KIM: I've heard that in poker
you're not necessarily playing
your cards, you're just playing
the other people.
So for me, I decided to meet
with a mentalist.
KRIS: A mentalist is gonna
teach you how to play poker?
KIM: Yeah, he does all these,
like, card tricks and stuff.
Why wouldn't he be... you know,
tips? >> KRIS: Poof, it's magic.
KIM: You're gonna totally be
my secret weapon.
LIOR: So, a mentalist can
influence people or read people.
So, forget about the game,
forget about the rules because
they're gonna teach you the
rules.
KIM: Mm-hmm.
LIOR: In poker it's all about
understanding how the people in
front of you think...
KIM: Mm-hmm.
LIOR: And understand if
they have good hands or bad
hands.
PHIL: You're only gonna play,
like, my top ten hands.
That's pocket aces, pocket
kings, all the way down to
sevens... >> KHLOE: Okay.
PHIL: And then ace-king
and ace-queen.
And fold everything else.
That's extreme, but if you play
just those ten hands...
KHLOE: Okay.
PHIL: Then I think you
have a great chance of winning.
KHLOE: I actually appreciate
Phil's method of teaching,
because I don't really have the
brain capacity to hold onto all
this other mumbo jumbo (bleep).
LIOR: I'm going to show you a
few techniques.
When we get asked questions, our
eyes move sometimes.
So if you're looking at me, up
to the right: Telling the truth.
KIM: Okay.
LIOR: Up to the left...
I make something up.
I'm lying to you.
KIM: Good to know... I'm gonna
ask Kanye some questions.
LIOR: Ah, very good.
KIM: It is so crazy that you
can just find out so much from a
person just by little things
that they do.
LIOR: It's all about lying,
deceiving...
KIM: Scheming... LIOR: Scheming.
KIM: Yes. LIOR: And do this.
KIM: I got it. LIOR: You got it?
KIM: I'm a pro already.
LIOR (laughs): You're a pro.
ANTONIO: Get something going.
You could even go all in.
KRIS: You want me to put all
my stack in there?
ANTONIO: That's what I would do.
KRIS: Okay. All in.
ANTONIO: She's all in.
OTHERS: Oh! No!
ANTONIO: Aces and fives.
KRIS: Oh...! MAN: Nice hand.
ANTONIO: You took him down.
KRIS: Wow! Yeah!
I feel really confident that I
know the rules, I know basically
how to play the game now, so I
definitely feel like I've got
one up on the girls. High five.
ANTONIO: You get the money.
KRIS: High five, guys. Whoo!
(Antonio laughs) ♪ ♪
KHLOE: Cute. What's its name?
KOURTNEY: Oh... PENELOPE: Mary.
KHLOE: Mary? Or Barry?
KOURTNEY and PENELOPE: Mary.
KHLOE: Mary. Can I hold Mary?
What's the other one's name?
KIM: Jesus? >> PENELOPE: No.
KHLOE: And it doesn't bite?
PENELOPE: It doesn't, but
when they start to shake, you
can give it to me.
KHLOE: Oh, no, what does that
mean?
Aw.
KOURTNEY: So, I just went to.
Dr. Huang. >> KIM: Yeah?
KOURTNEY: And he said I only
have five follicles.
There may be one or two that
he's not seeing...
KIM: Why don't you risk it
and try to get pregnant on
your own?
KOURTNEY: Well, no, I don't
know if I want to.
KHLOE: Yeah, I was gonna
say, slow your roll.
We're not encouraging that to
happen.
KOURTNEY: This is just for
security. >> KIM: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: What do you guys
think? Just do it?
KIM: I'd say do it, and get
those five to seven.
KOURTNEY: Mmm.
KIM: You know, if you're
never gonna make more than
seven...
KOURTNEY: I've put it off so
many times.
The timing is finally right.
It just feels right, so I think
just having that option really
gives me peace of mind.
KHLOE: Did you get that note
from the HOA?
KIM: No.
KHLOE: That they found...
they said... they just have a
picture of a turtle, and it
said, "We found a turtle.
If anyone owns it..."
I'm like, what if it's a wild
turtle from the Commons or
something?
KIM: How would you even be
able to identify your turtle?
KHLOE: That's my point.
♪ ♪
COREY: Call Kylie while
you're over, will you?
KIM: She's gonna be there.
COREY: She gets in L.A.
tonight. >> KIM: Yeah.
She already left.
I think she went to Cannes
first.
KRIS: What time is the show?
KIM: 2:30.
KRIS: You're a really good
friend. >> KIM: I know.
KRIS: I mean, you'll go back
to a place where...
you're not the most comfortable,
and...
But it's a good putting your toe
in the water, don't you think?
KIM: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: Like, you'll go,
you'll... >> KIM: Yeah.
I have so many special memories
in Paris.
KRIS: Oh, my gosh.
Kim, it's beautiful!
KIM: Cutie!
KOURTNEY: They didn't say "I
do" yet. >> KHLOE: Say "I do"!
(humming "Here Comes the Bride")
KIM: I hope that this trip...
will just be so good that I can
start to remember all the
magical things about Paris and
why Kanye and I fell in love
with it.
KRIS: I love you so much.
I'll be praying for you.
(horn honking)
KIM: Yeah, like, how far are
you from the show?
Can you honk?
'Cause he's just talking to a
guy. >> KANYE: Go around him.
Please go around him.
KIM: We are running so late.
It's taking forever.
I really hope that...
we make it on time.
KOURTNEY: I've been so
up-and-down emotional, 'cause
I've been doing the shots for
the egg freezing.
It's, like, crazy.
I feel like I want to jump out
of my skin.
I hope that going through all of
this is worth it.
I-I can't take it.
♪ ♪
KIM: It's kind of nice
landing this early, before the
city's up. >> KANYE: Mm-hmm.
A lot of bike shops out here.
People ride bikes a lot out
here?
There's, like, bike shop after
bike shop.
Or maybe it's just, like, the
bike district.
See? Another bike shop.
Another... That's one.
That's a bike shop.
That's not a random statement
I'm making... I literally just
saw ten bike shops.
Is this the bike district?
KIM: Mm-hmm.
KANYE: Look at this.
KIM: Maybe. Oh, wow.
KANYE: That's such a fresh
landmark.
(Kim laughs)
Wait. What hotel are we at?
Alexander or Laurent?
KIM: Mm, no.
No more staying at small hotels.
You know?
KANYE: Yeah.
KIM: Being here in Paris,
honestly, it's, like, really
nerve-racking.
But I'm not trying to focus on
anything negative.
♪ ♪
KIM: Maybe, like...
I like this hoodie.
Should I get Kanye and see if he
has any opinions?
WOMAN: I think so.
He's right here.
KIM: Oh. Didn't see you.
I think no to this.
KANYE: What about this?
KIM: Sure, you can try that.
So, the Louis Vuitton show is a
men's show, so it is hard, and
slim pickings of clothes, 'cause
I have to wear men's clothes,
but Virgil sent over racks and
racks of clothes for me to
choose from.
I do like this, though.
WOMAN: That kind of looks
cool, yeah.
KIM: Even if you're not,
like, walking in a show, it's so
important to be wearing
something from the collection.
KANYE: I like the, um...
blue.
KIM: That's cute.
You know, you-you...
It's all about the look.
Like, you have to look good if
you're sitting front row at a
Paris fashion show, especially
for Louis Vuitton.
I love this, like, from the
front, but it's too risky.
I either like the turquoise
with, like, a bike short, or I
like...
KANYE: I like the turquoise
the best.
KIM: Yeah. Yeah.
(phone whooshes)
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Phil is taking me to,
like, a legit big boy poker
game...
in, like, some back alley, some
smoky little lair.
Like, it's a little... I don't
know... sketchy, but I'm into all
of it.
I'm really into it.
I have Scott with me.
Hi, everybody. >> MAN: Hey.
KHLOE: It's very, very
serious, actually.
PHIL: $800. MAN: It's $800.
PHIL: $800 to go.
Are you also gonna stake him in
this game and give him $2,000?
MAN: He didn't want to play.
I just offered.
SCOTT: I'm not looking for
any money.
KHLOE: What happens if I
don't have enough money... you
just put it all...?
PHIL: That's okay. You can
put it all in.
KHLOE: I'm all in.
PHIL: Okay, Khloe, I have a
pretty big hand. Ace, king. Oh!
KHLOE: What a (bleep)
ass(bleep).
PHIL: Wait, hold on.
MAN: That's a bad guy.
KHLOE: Yeah, he is such a dick.
MAN: He's a bad person.
KHLOE: I was so excited for
my little (bleep) hand, and you
(bleep) me.
PHIL: Okay, this is what I
want to say.
Khloe, you played this hand
perfectly.
KHLOE: Okay, thank you.
PHIL: I told you to play
ace-queen, you played ace-queen.
You hit an ace, and you got all
the money in.
KHLOE: I did everything I was
told to do by Phil, and I still
(bleep) lost, but I did lose to
the pro... Phil.
PHIL: So, I mean, this is the
perfect storm for you, except
you just...
KHLOE: You were better.
PHIL: You just happened to
run into ace-king.
KHLOE: The more and more that
I play poker, and the more
comfortable I get, and, like,
understanding what's going on
here, I actually really enjoy
this game.
Um, I think it's fun, and I
think I could be really good at
it.
SHELLI: I just told Phil
that-that you told... that-that
you're... that you told me how
great he was and that your, um,
advice was to cheat and not get
caught.
KHLOE: Yes, basically.
That's what I'm gonna do.
Someone just hand me cards under
the table.
I'll have Scott on the floor.
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Let's go.
MAN: Is she gonna walk out
and get papped on?
WOMAN: Yeah, there's a lot of
paparazzi outside.
KIM: I'm gonna have to, like,
take pics there.
Then you'll have to wait till
we're done.
Where's our security?
KANYE: It's, uh... just...
KIM: Babe, where's our security?
MAN: Kim, tell us. KIM: Huh?
(indistinct chatter)
KIM: This cannot be
happening. (Elevator bell dings)
(indistinct chatter) Whatever.
We just need security, like, out
of the room and out to the car,
oh, my God. ♪ ♪
FEMALE VOICE: Going down.
(horn honking)
KIM: Yeah, like, how far are
you from the show? Can you honk?
KANYE: Go around him.
Please go around him.
KIM: Yeah, I want to go in.
KANYE: Or we could get out
and walk to it.
DRIVER: I think it's better
to wait.
KIM: We are running so late.
It's taking forever.
I really hope that we make it on
time. KANYE: We can get out here
and walk it? >> KIM: Yeah.
(chatter, shouting)
There's so many people, so much
paparazzi.
Just reminds me of everything
that went on the last time I was
here.
I'm just, like, hypersensitive
to this right now.
(overlapping shouting, chatter)
Let's just go. Kanye, let's go.
Kanye, let's go.
(shouting, chatter)
KIM: Who do we have here?
Kendall.
Oh. Oh, hey.
Guys, I'm gonna say this is a
really (bleep) proud moment of
my life.
KOURTNEY: What do you think
about this?
(Kourtney laughs)
KRIS: Have you been working
with your poker pro?
KENDALL: There's poker
teachers?
I have never played poker
before, not even for fun, so I'm
gonna have to just really wing
it.
Maybe hope for beginner's luck.
Okay, I guess we're done.
(horns honking)
(overlapping crowd chatter)
(chatter, screaming)
KIM: It definitely is a crazy
rush to get there, but we made
it just in time, and it's really
important 'cause this is such a
big deal.
WOMAN: Please? MAN: Kim, please?
MAN 2: Please.
MAN 3: Kim, straight here.
(overlapping shouting) ♪ ♪
KIM: The show is so amazing.
Everyone came out to support.
The clothes, the bags.
The bags are like to die for.
Everything just looks so good.
(cheering, applause, whistling)
(sniffling)
Kanye and Virgil have
the sweetest moment, and they're
both crying, and, like, all of
our friends were crying.
It's just such an emotional day.
The fact that Virgil's come this
far... it's just...
It's like a symbol, like, that
just, they made it, like, they
did it.
They're, like, taking over the
fashion world when everyone told
them they couldn't do it.
(indistinct chatter)
♪ ♪
KRIS: Look at my girl.
KENDALL: What?
KRIS: You're amazing.
(horse snorts, whinnies)
Kendall, if this modeling thing
doesn't work out, you could be a
horseback rider.
(Kendall laughs softly)
Like a real pro.
KENDALL: Your commentary is
insane. >> KRIS: What?
KENDALL: I said your
commentary is insane.
Good boy.
KRIS: Have you been working
with your poker pro?
KENDALL: What?
KRIS: Your poker teacher.
KENDALL: There's poker
teachers? No one told me.
KRIS: Well, do you know how
to play poker? >> KENDALL: No.
KRIS: Then what are you
thinking?
KENDALL: I don't know.
I've never played.
What do you mean, what am I
thinking?
I didn't know anyone was getting
a coach.
Yeah, what the (bleep)?
I can't believe they all have
someone that helped them and
taught them and, like, no one
told me.
So that's pretty... annoying.
KRIS: Auntie Shelli was
supposed to organize for
everyone to have a teacher.
KENDALL: So you're blaming it
on Auntie Shelli?
KRIS: It's coming up really
soon. Like, days away.
KENDALL: That's cool.
Well, now I'm nervous.
I have never played poker
before. Not even for fun.
So I'm gonna have to just really
wing it.
Maybe hope for beginner's luck.
I think I'm sitting next to.
Cameron Azoff, so I'll just talk
to him the whole time.
KRIS: You know, this is,
like, a serious tournament.
KENDALL: You're a serious
tournament.
Um, it's for charity though.
It's a win-win situation, right?
KRIS: It's a win-win.
And you're just as cute as a
button.
Yes, you are. Yes, you are.
KENDALL: Have you heard-heard
from Kim?
How's she doing in Paris?
I'm so annoyed I'm not there.
KRIS: I think it's a little
emotional for her.
But she's good.
She was having a good time.
KENDALL: I'm sure she's fine.
She's a boss.
(horse snorts)
Okay, I guess we're done.
♪ ♪
LARSA: Boo bear!
STEPHANIE: Why, hello.
KOURTNEY: Hi, guys. I was
gonna ask which glasses you
like better.
LARSA: I like the ones you're
wearing. >> KOURTNEY: Really?
LARSA: Yeah, they're so cute.
With your yellow.
KOURTNEY: How are these?
LARSA: No, I like those.
KOURTNEY: These? LARSA: Uh-huh.
KOURTNEY: What do you like,
these?
STEPHANIE: Yeah.
LARSA: I liked the yellow for
a second till I saw those.
KOURTNEY: I've been so, like,
up-and-down emotional, 'cause
I've been doing the shots for
the egg freezing, and it's,
like, crazy.
I feel like I want to jump out
of my skin.
Like, I'm so crazy.
Like, I just... I-I can't take
it. LARSA: I feel like it does
make you emotional.
Like, when I did it, I was
emotional.
KOURTNEY: But I have all
these... >> LARSA: Oh, my gosh.
KOURTNEY: Marks.
LARSA: That's a lot, Kourt.
I feel like you're not doing it
right.
STEPHANIE: They just look
like-like puncture bruises.
KOURTNEY: The injections
themselves really weren't a big
deal, because I have a really
high pain tolerance.
But I think everything was just
really heightened, and, like,
some days I would feel, like, so
anxious.
You know, it's just, like, very
emotional.
So that, I think, is the hard
part.
I was standing up in the
bathroom, and I was like, "I
just want to come out of my
skin."
And Younes is like, "What, you
have, like, anxiety?"
But I don't get it."
And then he thinks everything's
about him.
So then I'm like, "No, this has"
nothing to do with you."
LARSA: Right. It's like
your body's just responding.
And they're upping up your...
They're upping up your hormones,
so it's making it twice as
crazy. KOURTNEY: I mean, I feel
fine.
I just cry myself to sleep every
night. STEPHANIE: Yeah, that's
totally normal.
KOURTNEY: Honestly, I don't
know if I'm gonna have more
kids.
I just feel like it's just for,
like, safety.
I hope that going through all of
this is worth it, because, you
know, I really don't want to put
my body through this again.
The emotions of it all are just
a lot.
KIM: Today is the big day of
the tournament.
ANNOUNCER: Good luck, everybody!
Shuffle up and... deal!
KENDALL: I don't know if I'm
doing this right.
MAN: I'm all in.
KIM: I'm a little nervous
going all in.
It's such a risky move.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Go, Bayside!
KOURTNEY: Thank you.
KHLOE: My sisters and I are
going to Saved by the Max, and
it's basically a pop-up
restaurant, like they had in
Saved by the Bell.
It's just a dream come true.
KIM: It's like we're at the.
Max, you guys. >> KHLOE: Right?
KIM: I'm so Kelly Kapowski.
KHLOE: You are, and our
waiter's name is Zack.
And it's really his name.
KIM: Really?
I bet they make them have those
names. KHLOE: How was... Paris?
KIM: It was so good.
Like, honestly, I'm so glad we
went. Like, he had to be there.
It would've been weird if...
KHLOE: Oh, my God, when I saw
the video online...
KOURTNEY: Of them crying.
KHLOE: Of them crying and
hugging, I think it made
everyone cry and, like, want
a best friend.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: And I think they just...
KHLOE: It was the cutest
bromance.
KIM: But it was, like,
literally, for, like, a good 60
seconds, they were hugging and
just crying.
Yeah. And it was just so fun.
KHLOE: How was your anxiety?
KIM: For a second, I was,
like, um... I was so stressed out
over my security of, like, just
the movement of everyone.
But other than that, it was
fine.
Like, I didn't really have a lot
of anxiety. >> KHLOE: Good.
KIM: I don't think I'll ever
really forget my experiences in.
Paris, the good or the bad.
And I think that's okay.
Like, it all, you know, has
made me who I am.
And thinking about it, I feel
like I could go back and I could
spend more time and feel safe
and comfortable.
KHLOE: Zack used to be so hot.
KOURTNEY: Can I see?
KHLOE: Hold on. Let me read
it. >> KOURTNEY: Is that recent?
KHLOE: No, it's not recent.
He's, like, 600 years old now.
KIM: He's, like, basically
our age.
KOURTNEY: I think he's my age.
(Khloe laughs) ♪ ♪
KRIS: I wanted to help my
girlfriend raise money for the.
City of Hope, but I forgot to
tell her I didn't know how to
play poker. (Laughing)
♪ ♪
KIM: Today is the big day of
the tournament.
I don't think I'm gonna win, you
know, the hundreds of people
playing at each table, but I do
hope that... my sisters and my
mom... that I could be the winner
out of the fam.
KHLOE: I think that
Kimberly's actually gonna be
really good at this game.
She's a really good bluffer.
Kendall, you look so cute.
KENDALL: Don't I look like
poker? >> KHLOE: (scoffs) Sure.
KENDALL: Like, if poker were
an outfit.
KHLOE: Uh, more like if
Twister was an outfit.
KENDALL: Okay. Right.
KRIS: Hi, guys.
I love when the family all gets
together and does something fun
and competitive.
Are you nervous?
KENDALL: No. I just don't
think I'm gonna do very well.
KRIS: No Negative Nellie.
What's your strategy today?
KIM: Just... I'm gonna be me.
Hey, guys.
KHLOE: You... I hate you so
much.
I've never seen a body like this
in my life.
I think Kim's entire life
strategy is just distract,
distract, distract.
No, Kim, you look unreal.
KRIS: Let's go, guys.
KHLOE: Oh, my God, shh.
And mine is patience.
Patience, patience.
ANNOUNCER: All right,
tournament players, it is time
to start playing poker, which is
what you came down to do.
KHLOE: Are you a legit poker
player?
MAN: I've played before.
KHLOE: Oh.
MAN: I'm here just for fun.
KHLOE: Okay.
I feel really confident with the
little system me and Phil have
going on. ANNOUNCER: Shuffle up!
KHLOE: I'm gonna be patient,
do everything I'm told, get
other people drunk, and collect
that money, honey.
♪ ♪
MAN 2: I'm all in in the dark
for charity.
DEALER: Really? MAN 2: Yeah.
MAN 3: All right, I'm gonna
go all in blind.
KHLOE: Relax.
MAN 4: Wait a second.
KHLOE: Everyone...
DEALER: Got five all in.
KHLOE: Everyone's really wild
at this table.
PHIL: Okay, hold on.
Five all ins on the first hand.
These folks are rebuying.
MAN 3: Six all ins!
PHIL: They're here for charity.
KHLOE: Oh. No, the real is
you guys are all men.
You guys are having a dick
measuring contest.
You all are like, "I have..."
MAN 5: I'm not in this
tournament to win. KHLOE: Yeah.
KIM: All right. MAN 6: Wow.
DEALER 2: All in.
MAN 7: Oh, yeah.
DEALER 2: All right,
everybody, turn 'em over.
Oh, wow. >> MAN 7: No!
ANNOUNCER: Okay, folks, if
you want to rebuy, it's your
last chance.
KIM: I got to step it up.
I got to get some better cards
myself.
So, the first round is over.
And in the second round, you
can't buy any more chips.
So, if you go all in and you
lose all of your chips, you're
out.
You cannot buy in anymore.
KRIS: Khloe, can I borrow
some money?!
KHLOE: No, it's about
charity! Buy the (bleep) in.
KIM: It is time to get serious.
May the best woman win.
(whooping)
KRIS: I got some more money,
Khloe!
DEALER 3: Flip your cards over.
Okay, you've got a queen.
King with an ace!
(laughing, whooping)
DEALER 4: Turn 'em over,
everybody.
MAN 8: Oh, Khloe. Ship her
the chips! (Khloe whooping)
DEALER: He's bet $8,000.
DEALER: He's putting all in.
KRIS: Oh, he's so bad!
Mother(bleep)...
CASEY: All right. Hey.
WOMAN: You better not take
her out, Casey.
KRIS: It's all right.
PHIL: Okay, Kris Jenner
is all in. Kay, Kris Jenner.
The board: Jack, eight, eight,
three, four.
Jack, eight, eight, three,
four, with three diamonds.
Kris Jenner has...
a pair of jacks with a nine
kicker.
And this gentlemen has three
eights. >> KRIS: Oh...
PHIL: Wah, wah, wah.
KRIS: I'm kind of
disappointed that I got knocked
out.
I didn't expect to win, but I
would have liked to have stayed
in a little bit longer.
KIM: Yeah.
KRIS: Just ran out of money.
PHIL: Oh, wait a minute,
Kim is all in.
Like mother, like daughter.
Kim, if you go out this hand,
you outlasted your mother by one
hand. Okay.
The board is nine, seven, four,
deuce.
Kim, show us what you have.
Kim has a pair of deuces.
KIM: I'm a little nervous,
I'm not gonna lie.
Going all in is such a risky
move, 'cause my cards were not
good. I was totally bluffing.
PHIL: Against a pair of nines
with an eight.
Kim needs a deuce.
There's two deuces.
She needs a king.
There's three kings.
KIM: The crowd's around my
table, everyone's watching,
everyone's looking.
This is, like, the crucial
moment.
I'm either in or I'm done.
PHIL: Last card, please.
She needs a king or a deuce.
MAN: We got to get a king for
Kim.
(cheering) >> PHIL: Oh, my God!
It's a king!
KIM: That's so exciting.
This is so crazy.
I literally thought I was done.
Yes! (Lively chatter)
I really needed a specific card
to win, and I got that card.
MAN: What a row they have at
that table.
KHLOE: Who won? Kim won?
MAN: Yeah.
KHLOE: She has no idea what's
happening.
It's my sisters and I, neck and
neck at the end.
Stakes are high.
DEALER: Minimum bet now is
$400, guys. >> KENDALL: Raise.
DEALER: Player's all in.
MAN: Good luck, Khloe.
I'm all in.
DEALER: Player's all in.
KHLOE: Okay, don't be a dick.
KIM: I'll fold.
I am quickly running out of
money.
I keep getting dealt really bad
cards, and I hardly have any
more chips left.
MAN: Lock it up. Uh-oh.
KHLOE: (bleep)
MAN: Queen on the river.
I did everything Phil taught
me, but it's just not my game.
I'm out of the tournament.
Kim, Kendall... win, win, win.
DEALER: $1,000 to call.
KENDALL: So, what does that
mean?
I just get it?
DEALER: Means you just get
it. >> KENDALL: Cool.
My sister and my mom, who went
and got experts, are dropping
like flies, and I'm still here.
KIM: Go all in.
DEALER: Player all in!
PHIL: Okay, Kim...
show us your hand, Kim.
♪ ♪
PHIL: Eight-nine versus
king-queen.
Kim's a two-to-one underdog.
Give us the flop.
It's a really good flop for
the king-queen.
Tyler is in really good shape
here. It's over.
Kim is going to bust out.
Kim... Kim, thank you so much
for coming to the City of Hope.
Let's give Kim Kardashian a
round of applause, please,
everybody.
KIM: I didn't win the entire
tournament, as... I don't know
if any of us really expected
that we would...
PHIL: Kendall, you outlasted
big sis.
KIM: But we raised half a
million dollars and, you know,
just being all together and
trying something new that we've
never done before, and knowing
that it's giving back is just a
fun way to spend our weekend.
KRIS: Can take it off my
bucket list. >> KIM: Really?
KRIS: Yep. PHIL: Mother.
KENDALL: Yep.
PHIL: Last one standing.
KENDALL: I'm not surprised
that I'm the last one standing.
It's just what they get for not
including me and not getting me
a teacher, too. Thanks, guys!
Bye, guys. Bye. (Cheering)
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: It is the morning
of my procedure, and going under
anesthesia always makes me
really nervous, so I am hoping
that all goes well and that, you
know, I get the most eggs out as
possible. LARSA: Ooh. Boo bear.
How you feeling?
KOURTNEY: A little anxious,
but...
LARSA: You're gonna go under,
so you're, like, scared, you
have three kids...
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
LARSA: Like, that's the part
that's scary to me.
Like, whenever I've been put
under, it's, like, my kids,
like, oh, my God, what if I
don't wake up? KOURTNEY: Yeah.
Don't say that to me now.
LARSA: Oh, sorry. Sorry.
That was not the vibe. Sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
NURSE: That's normal.
You're gonna do great.
KOURTNEY: Okay.
LARSA: I feel like it's so
fast, right?
NURSE: It's so fast, and
it's, like, the best nap you've
ever had.
It's just like, "Oh, that's good
sleep, I don't want to wake up."
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
NURSE: Yeah. That's what most
of our patients say.
LARSA: Yeah, it's like a good
night's rest.
KOURTNEY: Yeah. I need it.
NURSE (laughs): Yeah.
We all do when it's this early.
LARSA: Yeah, totally.
NURSE: Ready to go, so I'm
gonna walk in with you.
If you, uh...
KOURTNEY: So, I get up?
NURSE: Step down on that
side. All right, perfect.
And we'll have you go out to the
waiting room, and then we'll
take good care of her.
LARSA: Okay.
LARSA: All right, bye.
I love you.
KOURTNEY: Bye. ♪ ♪
KIM: Who do we have here?
Kendall.
Cutie. Oh. Oh, hey.
Guys, I'm gonna say this is a
really (bleep) proud moment in
my life.
In Macy's, giant-sized cutouts
of every family member.
KOURTNEY: What do you think
about this? (Laughs)
KIM: Wait, so, how was your,
um, how was your retrieval?
How many did you get out?
KOURTNEY: I got out seven.
KIM: That's a lot.
That's exactly how many I got
out.
KOURTNEY: It is? KIM: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: I got out eight,
but two they said weren't good,
and then they incubated them,
and they got one out of the two.
So I got seven.
KIM: Oh, that's amazing.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
The procedure was much easier
than I thought, so I'm really
happy about that.
I mean, I just feel good.
Like, life is good.
I have the insurance if I want
to have kids, or maybe I'll
never use them.
But I think it's just nice to
have.
It's something that, like, gives
me peace of mind and I don't
have to worry about, and I think
it was all worth it, and I'm
just happy that it's done.
KIM: Wait, was it easier than
you thought it was gonna be?
KOURTNEY: Way easier.
Way easier than I
thought. >> KIM: That's amazing.
KOURTNEY: So, I don't think I
need to do it again.
KIM: Definitely, you don't
You don't need that many.
KOURTNEY: No. If anything...
KIM: 100%. You don't need
any more.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: I'm really proud of.
Kourtney taking the real steps
to freeze her eggs.
But I think it's just, like, all
really symbolic.
Making good decisions and moving
forward and putting herself and
her own happiness first.
Let's take a pic by mine real
quick.
KIM: Like this? Is this my pose?
Oh, but I'm like this.
MAN: Got it.
KIM: Cool.
On the next episode...
KANYE: What? Put 'em here.
I'm the one and only Kanye.
West. (Ringtone playing)
KIM: Hello? What?
Right now.
When he gets ramped up, he can't
control what he says.
You know, Alice Johnson, the
only person that could get her
out of prison would be the
president.
We have one shot to plead our
case.
Alice, you're out.
Captioning sponsored by.
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS