♪
KIM: How cute is this place?
SCOTT: It's a nice little
establishment. >> KIM: (gasps)
Stuffed Oreo churros. Hi.
I would love a churro donut.
CASHIER: Got it.
KIM: Oh, you know what?
We'll get a sampler, too.
SCOTT: Get a sampler. Enjoy.
KIM: We'll get both. (Sighs)
Thank you. Dig in.
OMG. Mmm. Try some.
SCOTT: I'm not gonna have any
just because I'm gonna see my
son later and I'm scared that
Kourtney will smell that on me.
KIM: What? SCOTT: She's nuts.
KIM: Okay, I'll just do this.
Okay, I feel like the truth's
out right now. Mmm.
SCOTT: At least you're...
living your life.
(ringtone plays) KIM: Hang on.
SCOTT: Uh-oh.
KIM: Oh, who is it?
SCOTT: Freak itself.
KIM: Answer it.
Say you're at a specialist,
holistic place.
SCOTT: Hey.
KOURTNEY (on phone): Hi.
Are you in the Valley or in the
city?
SCOTT: I'm at Sherman Oaks at
this holistic doctor that's
supposedly, like, number one at
all diets all around the world.
KOURTNEY: Oh, good.
SCOTT: He's...
He's from Thailand and says that
he's got something that nobody
else has heard of.
KOURTNEY: Like...?
(Kim and Scott laughing)
What is...?
KIM: Just, just...
SCOTT: No, honestly, he's got
cat urine.
KOURTNEY: Pick me up a
bottle. SCOTT: I will, I will.
It's expensive so I'll take care
of it.
KOURTNEY: Okay, thank you. ♪
KIM: One black two-piece and
one gold two-piece.
JONATHAN: Hi, guys. KIM: Hi.
JONATHAN: What's up?
What are we doing here?
Who's office is this?
KIM: This is the tailor.
JONATHAN: I'm so jealous you
guys are going to Japan.
KIM: Have you ever been?
JONATHAN: No. You know I
haven't been.
I've been asking you to come for
five years now. DANIELLE: Yes.
KIM: I decided to go to Japan
to shoot a Yeezy campaign.
We just thought it would be such
cool vibes.
Let's do a full shoot out there,
and kind of debut season seven
out in Japan.
KHLOE: And Kourt and I have
been dying to go to Japan so
we're not gonna let Kim go solo.
KIM: Yeah.
KHLOE: Pregnant and all, I'm
bumping it up in Japan.
JONATHAN: What are we doing
here? What are you guys doing?
KIM: Kanye's people, like,
designing season seven, like,
around my trip to Japan.
So it's like, basically...
JONATHAN: Oh, my God.
He really takes this stuff
really seriously. It's amazing.
KIM: Yeah.
Yeezy doesn't really, you know,
play by the fashion rules of
having to have his collection
out by a certain time.
I mean, we just finished season
six. And it was such a genius
campaign of just wearing all the
looks and getting shot by the
paparazzi.
And Kanye got such a good
response that for Japan, I'm
hoping to get shot by, like,
fans and they post it, or
paparazzi, so that we get
images, and we'll get tons of
content for my app and my.
Instagram.
I love these cropped bombers.
I could totally do these.
And when I showed up to the
office, and I saw, like, 40 or
50 people working on this with
the entire bottom floor filled
with samples, I was like, "Oh",
my God, you guys are really
serious.
But I love working with Kanye in
that way, 'cause he'll listen to
me on things that are important
to me.
And then I'll trust him on
colors and fabrics, so it really
does work so well.
JONATHAN: So you don't have
to do, like, fashion shows
anymore.
That's amazing.
KIM: I love this vibe.
I think it's just, like, cooler
and fresh.
JONATHAN: So freaking cool.
How many people are there doing
this? >> KIM: Like, at least 40,
wouldn't you say?
DANIELLE: Yes, something like
that. >> JONATHAN: (bleep)
KIM: Japan is, like, for the
forefront of fashion.
You have to be, like, cool girl.
JONATHAN: Can't wait to see
this. ♪
CONCIERGE: Welcome to the
Four Seasons.
KRIS: Thank you.
This looks nice.
Ooh, fancy.
SHEILA: Beautiful, huh?
KRIS: I know, I love this place.
SHEILA: It says you and me.
You and me, babe.
KRIS: I know, it's always you
and me, babe.
SHEILA: I know.
KRIS: For how many years?
SHEILA: A hundred.
KRIS: Uh, it seems like that.
SHEILA: It does, right?
KRIS: I think you've been
through every single important
thing with me that I've had, for
like, my entire life.
SHEILA: Aw.
KRIS: From births to...
SHEILA: I love you.
KRIS: I love you, too.
Sheila's one of my oldest and
closest girlfriends.
SHEILA: Oh, hi.
Joyce, that's you!
You have your blanket?
KRIS: We watched each other's
children grow up, and we went on
family vacations.
I will always be so grateful for
this friendship.
SHEILA: Can I tell you
something?
This is, like, really kind of
sad.
I was going through a bunch of
pictures last... I found great
pictures of us.
KRIS: You did?
SHEILA: But, like, I just...
You know, there's, like, a spark
in my face back then.
You look the same.
You look fantastic.
KRIS: I look the same 'cause
I've had a little help here
and there. You know?
SHEILA: But I mean, like,
it's really funny because you
see, like, these young, you
know, vibrant... I don't know,
maybe I'm going through
something.
Oh, you know...
KRIS: What don't you think
looks the same on you?
'Cause I think, when I look at
you, you're beautiful.
SHEILA: I've always hated my
neck. It's just stuff, you know?
We all kind of, you know, go
through stuff like that.
We look in the mirror, and we
kind of go, "Oh, I didn't know"
that was there."
It's really interesting.
They say when someone... a woman
has a long neck... if you want a
long neck... well, guess what.
(Kris laughs)
It ends up droopy. KRIS: Yeah.
SHEILA: I think everybody
feels something like that.
KRIS: 100%. >> SHEILA: Yeah.
KRIS: And if you don't feel
it, Kim is telling you about it.
(Sheila laughs) ♪
KHLOE: We are all going to
Japan, so I have to meet with.
Dr. A, my ob-gyn, to make sure
that I'm all good to travel.
ALIABADI: So, how have you been?
KHLOE: Good.
ALIABADI: Your baby's moving
well? >> KHLOE: Yeah.
ALIABADI: Uh, you want to
travel to Japan?
KHLOE: Mm-hmm.
ALIABADI: So you can.
I want you to take a baby
aspirin before you go on the
plane and before you come back
here.
KHLOE: Okay.
ALIABADI: Okay, because
flights put you at risk for
blood clots in your legs.
KHLOE: Okay.
ALIABADI: Keep yourself
well-hydrated, walk around the
cabin; That's like a layer of
protection. >> KHLOE: Okay.
ALIABADI: All right, you're
28 weeks and six days.
Tomorrow, you'll be 29.
KHLOE: Yes, ma'am.
Almost. Ten weeks. (Laughs)
Yeah, this is so weird.
ALIABADI: The little head.
KHLOE: Stay little.
I saw Kylie's baby.
(Aliabadi laughs)
It was like, "How was that"
inside of you?"
That was so funny.
ALIABADI: Oh, look at this;
Look at the finger.
KHLOE: Oh, my gosh.
That's why I feel her kicking.
ALIABADI: She's perfect.
It's a good size.
It's not a small one.
KHLOE: Oh, perfect.
♪
(Khloe grunts)
KOURTNEY: (laughs)
It's Kanye West!
KHLOE: Keeks, you look so
cute. >> KIM: Thank you.
Do you like my pink hair?
KHLOE: I love your hair.
KANYE: You guys like the
first season seven look?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, I love it.
KIM: All my looks are season
sevens.
KOURTNEY: I was just thinking
I like the, um, material of the
sweater.
KHLOE: I love this.
KIM: Yeezy season seven
officially kicks off today,
'cause I'm heading to Japan in
one of the first looks.
Kanye's coming to say bye at the
airport, but it's also, like, a
professional send-off, too, just
to make sure that everything
looks amazing.
KHLOE: Ye, we love you.
We'll get you some porn.
KANYE: Japanese porn?
KHLOE: Yep.
KOURTNEY: I actually like
Japanese porn.
♪
KIM: I only have a few days
to get 20 looks shot.
You know, Japan is the campaign.
We can't, like, recreate it.
There's dozens of people working
on this, so it is a lot of
pressure.
It's my husband's collection,
and I want to make sure that I
do a good job, and that he likes
how everything turns out. ♪
KHLOE: We have finally landed
in Japan, land of the samurais
and geishas. It's so gorgeous.
KIM: Wait, go ahead for one
sec; I'm gonna get a solo shot.
KOURTNEY: This outfit is so
intense.
KIM: So, I got to be real
with you guys, you look like
(bleep) clowns.
♪
KHLOE: It's so gorgeous.
KOURTNEY: Scott FaceTimed me
with the kids, and I tried to
call back, and he's like, "The"
kids are all asleep."
I'm like, "What time is it?"
I had no idea that it was, like,
time for bed.
KIM: I'm so excited to be here.
KHLOE: It's so beautiful.
KIM: Yeah, no, it is.
♪
KHLOE: We have finally landed
in Japan, land of the samurais
and geishas.
KIM: I would think more land
of, like, anime and cherry
blossoms. >> KHLOE: Well...
♪
These are beautiful.
Oh, my goodness, thank you.
KIM: Oh, they smell so good.
How pretty.
We are staying at the Shangri-La
Hotel.
It is so amazing.
KOURTNEY: This is the way to
travel.
KHLOE: You guys, taking a
bath with this view...
KIM: Yes, it's so good.
DANIELLE: Why don't you
shoot this now?
KIM: I could run downstairs
real quick and do it.
DANIELLE: Yeah, maybe put
that on right now.
KIM: That? >> DANIELLE: Yeah.
KIM: And then meet them for
dinner.
KOURTNEY: I wanted to do a
turquoise...
STYLIST: Turquoise what?
HAIRSTYLIST: I think we have
to just depend it on the outfit.
Um, do you know what you're
wearing tonight, or do you want
to...?
KOURTNEY: This is what I was
thinking.
HAIRSTYLIST: Yeah, I love it.
KIM: Okay. Let's go.
Will you come with me?
DANIELLE: Mm-hmm.
KIM: Good, I'm glad we're,
like, knocking this one out.
I'm getting a little bit nervous
just because there's so many
looks for this campaign.
My sisters must think I'm crazy.
And I have to get every single
look, so we have to start, like,
right now. ♪
I forgot my jacket.
I'm gonna run in and grab it.
Do you think they know what
we're doing?
MAN: Going back to the room,
right?
KIM: Yeah. Do you think we
got enough?
All right, so we're gonna wear
the dress.
The gray dress right now. ♪
KOURTNEY: Khloe? Where's Kim?
KHLOE: She's taking some
pictures outside or something.
KOURTNEY: Ooh la la.
You ready, sugarplum?
KHLOE: Yeah. KOURTNEY: Let's go.
♪
KOURTNEY: This skirt is
sticking to me.
Ooh, what is that little thing?
Look.
KIM: So cute.
Wait, go ahead for one sec;
I'm gonna get a solo shot.
My sisters look so... crazy.
Like, it's actually
embarrassing.
Kourtney with the Japanese
inspired outfits, and Khloe's
wearing silver sequins,
turquoise eye shadow, huge
chandelier earrings.
They're just, like, completely
clashing and just making my
outfit look really bad, and
they're ruining everything.
KOURTNEY: Wow, this outfit is
so intense.
It's, like, stuck in all the
wrong spots.
KIM: Oh, yeah.
KOURTNEY: Ooh, oh, my gosh.
WAITER: This is our vegetables.
KIM: Oh, thank you.
KHLOE: Thank you.
KOURTNEY: Look how cute these
tomatoes are.
Oh, my gosh. They're so cute.
KHLOE: They match your nails.
KIM: I can't even eat dinner
'cause I'm so disgusted with my
sisters' crazy outfits that
completely don't go with my
look.
Like, I can't take it.
KOURTNEY: Ooh, I love a good
radish.
WAITER: This is sea urchin
and raw bean sauce.
KIM: Thank you.
KHLOE: Looks delicious.
Thank you.
KOURTNEY: This is so good.
The custard.
KIM: No, it really is.
I need the Yeezy collection to
be debuted and not to have all
this crazy distraction in the
background.
Like, I'm gonna have to control
this before it gets really bad
and my whole trip is ruined.
KOURTNEY: Mmm.
KIM: You got it on your chin.
(Khloe laughs) ♪
KOURTNEY: When we first
walked in, didn't you guys think
this was two stories?
KHLOE: I did.
KIM: Yeah. For sure.
KOURTNEY: I thought, like,
your room was upstairs, I
thought glam was upstairs.
KHLOE: I did. I thought it
was two stories.
KIM: Um, so I got to be real
with you guys.
KHLOE: Mm-hmm.
KIM: You look like (bleep)
clowns. >> KHLOE: Oh.
KIM: I'm not (bleep) kidding.
This is not, like, a tourist
thing where it's, like, "It's
Halloween, dress up like a"
"(bleep) Japanese geisha," unless
we're at a geisha house.
KOURTNEY: I thought my hair
looked good last night, and I
thought my outfit was, like,
fun for Japan.
KIM: Your outfit would've
been, like, great if you didn't
have (bleep) blue eye shadow.
KOURTNEY: But I-I actually
liked that we were all in sync,
like, your blue shoes, my blue
shadow and Khloe's blue...
(laughs) earrings.
KIM: No, but she was green
and yellow.
KHLOE: I didn't know the
yellow was happening.
KOURTNEY: Where's yellow?
KIM: It was a yell... half
yellow and half green,
turquoise.
KHLOE: It was like an evil eye.
KOURTNEY: (laughs)
You think I looked like a clown?
Well, you look like you just won
the Tour de France and you're
cycling around town.
I mean, look how cute I am.
Even my cartoon character looks
great, and has the best style.
KIM: So I'm just saying, you
have to, like, tell the glam
people.
Especially... we're in Japan.
Like, everyone just thinks, "Oh,
my God, we're in Japan, everyone"
go full Japan."
And, like, probably the people
that live here make fun of
people like that, and I
literally am, like, cropping
myself out of, like, turquoise,
yellow, da, da, da.
Like, I just think you got to,
like, chill.
KOURTNEY: But also, I don't
think my things were that crazy.
KIM: Like, you can be cooler.
I'm not telling you guys who to
be or what to wear or anything,
but I'm telling you who to be
and what to wear.
It could be time for, like, a
fashion overhaul, so that you
stay, like, young and relevant.
KRIS: I wanted to run
something by you.
SCOTT: Hit me with the
runner.
KRIS: I'm trying to figure
out how to surprise Sheila with
a facelift.
SCOTT: I mean, even though
it's really a sweet gesture,
are you at all nervous that you
could offend her in any way?
KIM: I don't even know what
this style is.
I feel like we're stuck.
It's, like, trying too hard.
KOURTNEY: I love it.
Kim is just being rude.
It's not that serious.
♪
SCOTT: Wow! >> KRIS: Wow!
SCOTT: Agoura Hills meets
Beverly Hills.
KRIS: Mwah.
Yeah, the A meets the B.
SCOTT: Hey, B.
KRIS: How do you like my
little spot?
SCOTT: This is so cute.
KRIS: Isn't it great?
SCOTT: I had no idea.
It's a hidden gem, I tell you.
KRIS: So what is this beanie
look you've got going on here?
You look like you could go rob a
house down the street.
I would go with a black beanie.
SCOTT: We're not gonna have
to pay for this meal.
Get the (bleep) out of here.
KRIS: Dine and dash?
SCOTT: Who cares?
I'm gonna take the check, throw
it and run.
KRIS: We're gonna eat and
run? >> SCOTT: With this hat on,
they're not gonna stop me.
KRIS: I have never done that
before. Yum.
So I wanted to run something by
you.
SCOTT: Hit me with the runner.
KRIS: Okay.
I'm trying to figure out how to
surprise Sheila with a facelift.
When I had my face done, that
was really a hard thing for me
to go through.
And who was there every single
step of the way?
Sheila.
It just occurred to me, like,
she's wanted to do this for
years, but this is just not
something she would do.
I want to do this for her and be
there for her like she's always
been there for me.
I'm so excited.
SCOTT: You're giving her a
facelift?
KRIS: Like, I want to jump up
and down.
I'm so excited, that I just,
she's been such an amazing
friend, and she's just always
there for me.
SCOTT: I mean, even though
it's really a sweet gesture, are
you at all nervous that you
could offend her in any way?
KRIS: Like...
SCOTT: Is it, like, "Hey,
your face looks old"?
Just think about it.
KRIS: Scott's getting in my
head and making me feel like
this is a mistake, and all I'm
really trying to do is show her
how much I love her.
SCOTT: Listen, no... if you
(bleep) me that I needed
something done... >> KRIS: Yeah?
SCOTT: Even if maybe I
didn't, I would definitely go
stare and look at whatever that
was.
KRIS: Kim does it to me 24/7.
SCOTT: Kim does it to
everybody in the world.
You know, she-she catches
everything.
I don't even really like looking
at Kim, because sometimes she's
like...
KRIS: It's scary, right?
She'll stare at us.
SCOTT: She's like, "Uh, uh...
is that a pimple right there?"
And I'm like, "I-I don't know."
♪
KHLOE: Oh, my God, what are
those things?
KOURTNEY: Ninja stars.
KHLOE: Ninja stars.
KIM: This is so cute.
Oh, let's go down here.
KHLOE: Are you just doing a
photo shoot?
KIM: Basically.
TOMOKO: So have you done
fortunes?
KOURTNEY: No. TOMOKO: It's good.
It will tell you your fortune
for this year.
KOURTNEY: "Shake the box
politely a few times, a stick"
marked 'fortune number' will
come out."
TOMOKO: This is your fortune.
KOURTNEY: Wait, it says
"bad"?
TOMOKO: This temple is famous
for having many bad fortunes.
KIM: Okay, I am not going to
do... I don't want to have a bad
fortune.
TOMOKO: What we normally do
is give this bad fortune to the
temple.
KOURTNEY: Okay, so I give
them back? >> TOMOKO: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: Good-bye, bad fortune.
KHLOE: Good-bye.
KOURTNEY: See you.
Feel my brain...
Fill our hearts, all of us.
♪
KOURTNEY: Ah. Now what?
(ringtone playing)
KIM: Hello?
Hey. Sorry, I couldn't hear you.
KANYE: How'd it go today?
KIM: Good. I wore, um, the
2XU leggings with the reflective
boots in this, like, we went to,
like, a marketplace that was
really cute.
KANYE: That wasn't a look.
KIM: Yeah, it was, with the
silver top and the black puffer
vest with the glasses?
KANYE: Silver top...
KIM: The silver spandex top
that I wore already with the
spandex matching bike shorts,
with that top.
KANYE: Oh, yeah, that looked
fire. >> KIM: Yeah.
Because I'm on the complete
opposite time schedule as back
home, Kanye is seeing my looks,
like, way after I did them,
like, as the paparazzi pictures
go out, and, you know, of
course, it's like, Yeezy's his
baby.
He wants to make sure everything
comes out perfectly, so it-it is
a lot of pressure, and it makes
me a little bit nervous, just
because I want him to like every
look.
Okay. Okay, bye.
Scott just wrote me, "The outfit"
in Tokyo was the jump-off.
The bike shorts with the puffer?
"You look like you're from the
future."
(Khloe laughs softly) ♪
TOMOKO: It is a plate, and
you write down your wish, and
then your wish will make true.
KHLOE: I'm so excited to be
in Kyoto.
This is what I envisioned Japan
to be like, more.
KIM: I have a big day
planned, going to the geisha
house and the Bamboo Forest and
the Owl Cafe. KHLOE: Hoot, hoot.
KIM: Hoot, hoot. (Both laugh)
♪
KHLOE: It's so pretty.
Oh, my God.
What a cool picture if you stood
right here. >> KIM: Should I?
KHLOE: Hurry up!
That is such a cool picture.
(alarm blaring) >> KIM: Aah!
KHLOE: It says, "Do not
enter." Hurry up!
It says, "Do not enter."
And the buzz.
I didn't know it was gonna do
that, sorry.
All I thought about was Fried
Green Tomatoes.
(laughing) ♪
KHLOE: Thank you.
KOURTNEY: How cute is this
presentation?
KHLOE: So beautiful.
TOMOKO: They are going to
perform.
♪
KIM: Is that real? No. No.
(gasps) It's real.
Look at the babies.
KHLOE: Why are you staring at
me like that?
Yo. What the (bleep) you want?
KOURTNEY: Khlo, come here.
TOY: Khlo, come here.
KOURTNEY: Khlo.
KHLOE: What? >> TOY: Khlo.
KHLOE: What is that?
I swear I thought you guys were
on the phone with North or
something.
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God, I'm
obsessed with that.
TOY: Oh, my God, I'm obsessed
with that.
KHLOE: Stop. ♪
KIM: I don't even know what
this style is.
I feel like we're stuck.
I just, I just want you to be
more like I said, like cool
girl.
It's, like, trying too hard and
then, like, oh, we're in Japan,
it's crazy colors.
Oh, everything is Asia and Japan
because I'm in Asia.
KOURTNEY: I have no more.
Asian, Japan vibes.
ANDREW: You-you want her
dressed more like Kendall?
KOURTNEY: Except for my
pajamas.
KIM: Yes. Like, more like a...
Like, like Kendall-y.
I think that's what you can do.
You look like a (bleep) grandma.
100%.
I think you don't look anything
special.
Like, you don't look anything,
like, innovative and I think you
have it in you.
It's just you better evolve
before you fizzle out.
KOURTNEY: Now I think Kim's
just being rude and rude to
everyone in glam.
You know, we're all doing fun
looks together.
It's not that serious and I
think Kim and I don't always see
eye to eye as far as the
importance of, like, traveling
and living in the moment.
Where's Khloe?
KIM: Just like, these YSL
shoes, like, come on.
KOURTNEY: You don't see them
with my outfit.
SHEILA: This is so great.
This is so fun.
Well, we've been through a lot,
all of us together.
KRIS: Um, well, I have a
surprise for you.
KOURTNEY: I don't have seven
stylists.
(laughter)
KIM: I don't have time for.
Kourtney's, like, (bleep).
KOURTNEY: You're so (bleep)
jealous. (Laughter)
KIM: Kourtney?
♪
SHEILA: Hi! >> KRIS: Hi!
SHEILA: What's going on?
Ooh, I love that.
Look how cute you look.
KRIS: Hi, guys.
(all blow kisses)
I have a little sniffles so I'm
not gonna hug anybody.
JOYCE: Oh, that's not good.
SHEILA: It's okay.
This is so great.
This is so fun.
So, I have to surprise you guys
with a photo. >> KRIS: What?
We are so cute.
SHEILA: Is that not cute?
KRIS: Oh, my God.
JOYCE: We're so young there.
SHEILA: I know.
Seriously, I mean...
JOYCE: Really?
KRIS: Don't you wish we had
these sweaters?
JOYCE: I have mine.
SHEILA: Oh!
JOYCE: No, I'm only kidding.
KRIS: You do?
JOYCE: No, no, no, no, no.
SHEILA: How cute. Look at the
big, red earrings.
KRIS: Oh, my God.
JOYCE: Were we all matching?
I mean, were we all in red and
white?
KRIS: I think so. Yeah.
SHEILA: Yeah.
KRIS: Red, white and black.
And Sheila had on the red
earrings to match.
SHEILA: Well, we've been
through a lot, all of us
together.
KRIS: Um, well...
I have a surprise for you.
I know my girlfriend better than
anybody else, especially better
than Scott.
But I have to be really careful
with Sheila because she's so
kind, and she's so sweet and
she never wants to hurt
anybody's feelings, so she might
be inclined to say, "Okay, thank
you," even if she really doesn't
want it.
And it's making me nervous.
Uh, Joyce already knows, but...
SHEILA: What do you know?
KRIS: I have arranged for
Garth Fisher to do whatever you
want him to do.
SHEILA: You're kidding,
right?
KRIS: On your face and your
neck. >> SHEILA: Stop.
KRIS: Yeah. Yeah.
JOYCE: So what do you think?
SHEILA: Stop. No. Come on.
KRIS: Would you do it?
I mean, I just said yes.
SHEILA: Yes. Yes!
(Kris laughs)
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
JOYCE: She booked you.
You're going.
KRIS: Yeah, yeah, she's going.
SHEILA: But wait...
KRIS: And Joyce and I are
going with you.
SHEILA: Can you be with me?
KRIS: Of course, we already
booked ourselves.
SHEILA: Stop.
JOYCE: We're booked out.
SHEILA: Oh, my... stop.
KRIS: 'Cause if you're not
gonna use it, we will.
JOYCE: We will.
(laughter) >> SHEILA: What?
KRIS: I feel super relieved
that Sheila's so excited about
her surgery.
I really am because I never want
to feel like I pushed her into
doing something she wasn't ready
for. >> SHEILA: Wow.
KRIS: We are so excited.
Joyce and I were like... we
couldn't sleep last night.
JOYCE: I'm so excited for
you. >> SHEILA: Oh, my God.
KRIS: Isn't this exciting?
SHEILA: He-he's the best.
JOYCE: He is the best.
SHEILA: The best.
KRIS: The whole day he booked
out for you.
SHEILA: I can't believe it.
That is beyond.
KRIS: Anybody have any
Kleenex by any chance?
SHEILA: This is clean, it's
just...
KRIS: Oh, no.
(laughing): No, I don't know.
SHEILA: I-I'm trying to be nice.
JOYCE: She used it once.
SHEILA: Well, no, I stuffed
it in here and it's from this
morning.
KRIS: Okay. I'm gonna pass on
that one.
SHEILA: Seriously. ♪
STYLIST: Where is Justina?
Does anyone have that picture?
KOURTNEY: What picture?
STYLIST 2: We're building a
case for you.
ANDREW: Stuff that Kim was
saying to you.
She literally came for
everybody.
Can't really say (bleep).
KOURTNEY: No, after
yesterday, I wanted to wear a
white T-shirt and jeans.
ANDREW: Oh, for real.
STYLIST 2: And she's like,
"Oh, my God, fur coats are the
"worst," and I'm like, okay.
(laughter)
Burn all my clothes.
KOURTNEY: Hello? I have three
children and a full-time job.
I'm not gonna do... I don't have
seven stylists. (Laughter)
KIM: Kourtney and all of the
glam people at this point hate
me 'cause I've just killed all
their dreams.
KOURTNEY: Big shoulders are
awful. How rude.
STYLIST: I don't give a
(bleep), honey. (Laughs)
KIM: And I don't care.
KOURTNEY: You're so (bleep)
jealous.
STYLIST 2: (bleep) rude.
(laughter)
KIM: If you can't take the
criticism, you shouldn't have
come on this trip.
Kourtney? Ooh, what a cute room.
I would've done a photo shoot
right there.
KOURTNEY: You missed out.
KIM: Um, well, I just wanted
to say, like, I know that I've
been, like, kind of snappy and
just, like, very opinionated,
but I'm here for the Yeezy
campaign.
I don't have time to be, like,
beating around the bush here.
KOURTNEY: But I feel like
we're also here to, like, have
fun, wear some fun stuff, do
some fun hair and makeup,
whatever.
And by the way, I have liked all
my outfits.
KIM: I don't know.
I saw what I saw and I saw
(bleep) clowns.
KOURTNEY: Nobody wants to
wake up and be criticized from
head to toe, like, the whole day
long. KIM: But the old Kourtney
would've been like, "(bleep)
you," or, like, "Whatever."
You know?
KOURTNEY: So would you rather
me just say, like, your (bleep)
outfits suck?
You're wearing a puffy vest.
You have pink hair and, like,
turquoise shoes.
I didn't come here to wear
leggings that are see-through
and show my ass off.
(Khloe laughs)
Do you know how easy it is to be
a bitch?
I could be a bitch all (bleep)
day if that's what you want.
But guess what?
It takes a lot more courage to
show your feelings than to sit
there and be a bitch.
KRIS: I'm personally praying
for you.
GARTH: We're all set to start
now. >> WOMAN: Come with me.
KRIS: She-She.
It's surgery day and I'm so
nervous. I hate this part.
KIM: This is what gives me
anxiety in life.
I'm starting to freak out
because there's so many looks
that we haven't shot yet.
We really have one shot.
Right here, right there.
Stop, stop, stop. Stop here.
Stop here.
STYLIST: Oh my god, this is
so crazy.
♪
KRIS: Hi. How are you feeling?
SHEILA: Uh, I got really...
I got really nervous.
KRIS: Yeah.
Well, this is for you.
It's just a little goodie.
It's a little blankie for the
hospital. SHEILA: I love this.
Oh, I love it.
KRIS: That'll be your snuggly
blanket in the hospital.
SHEILA: Oh, thank you.
Why does this bring me back to
1988?
JOYCE: 'Cause it is.
SHEILA: I mean...
KRIS: My first boob job.
(laughter)
You remember?
The last time I was sitting on
this couch with the two of you
was when I had my face done.
Now it's your turn.
JOYCE: Your turn.
SHEILA: No. My turn, yes.
JOYCE: It's your turn.
SHEILA: It's hard to believe.
KRIS: So, anything you need,
you just let us know.
SHEILA: Thank you, thank you.
KRIS: But, um, I'm personally
praying for you.
And you're gonna be great.
RANDY: Right?
KRIS: Yeah, yeah.
COREY: It's amazing.
Like, every time something goes
down with one of you three, the
gang is...
JOYCE: That's how we roll.
KRIS: It's a big deal.
It's surgery day and Sheila is
so nervous.
It's gonna be amazing.
SHEILA: All of you guys,
thank you.
KRIS: You're gonna be so strong.
But there's nobody that I would
trust more with my girlfriend
than Garth Fisher.
SHEILA: Here's the star.
KRIS: So I'm really confident
that today's gonna go really,
really well. You ready for her?
GARTH: We're all set to start
now.
KRIS: This is really just a
big love letter to her for all
of her friendship.
SHEILA: Here, come with me.
KRIS: She-She. So exciting.
SHEILA: I can't believe that
I'm going in now.
KRIS: I hate this part,
because you just want to be put
to sleep, and let's move on.
TRISTAN: Hey. >> KRIS: Hi.
So, what did you want to talk
about?
TRISTAN: Thinking up some
push present ideas.
KRIS: Push present ideas?
TRISTAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Aw.
TRISTAN: I remember KoKo
saying she wanted something
where she could pass it down,
you know, generation after
generation.
KRIS: You know, Corey bought
me, for Christmas a couple years
ago, this really beautiful
little diamond ring that's,
like, you can put it on any
finger.
TRISTAN: Yeah.
KRIS: Um, you know, until you
get that really huge diamond
that's gonna go on her ring
finger. >> TRISTAN: Of course,
eventually. >> KRIS: Yeah.
TRISTAN: Yeah. I think
jewelry's kind of the safest
bet. >> KRIS: And she'll be so
excited and surprised.
Okay, love you.
TRISTAN: I love you, too.
KRIS: A push present.
That's so cute.
GARTH: Hello, how are you?
RANDY: Good. How are you?
GARTH: She's doing great.
Of course, what you're gonna
have to do is get her a new
passport and driver's license.
(laughter)
She, uh, she looks great.
I mean, everything went perfect.
SAMANTHA: Good.
KRIS: Long day, but the
surgery went amazing.
I know it's gonna be a bit of a
recovery process for Sheila, but
I cannot wait to see the end
result.
RANDY: Kris, thanks.
KRIS: Oh, I'm just so happy
that she did so well.
RANDY: Yeah, so...
Look at that.
KRIS: Oh, Corey gives the
best shoulders.
You got to do that for her,
she'll love it. (Laughter)
♪
KIM: So, let's go over
everything we need to shoot
before tomorrow.
So, hair up, four looks.
DANIELLE: Okay.
KIM: Change into that.
Bring this in the car and
switch.
DANIELLE: Okay.
KIM: So we have eight looks
that we're doing with this hair
at Harajuku on different street
corners. And then baseball hat.
(bleep)
This is what gives me anxiety
in life. ♪
KIM: Can we shut the door?
I'm literally changing on every
street corner, so it's just
done.
Can we drive?
I'm starting to freak out
because we have to get so many
looks done.
But making sure the look looks
amazing without a mirror is
really hard.
And if something is not right,
there's no way we can redo it,
because the pics are already out
for the world to see.
So, we've got one shot.
Right here, right there, right
there, right there.
Stop, stop, stop.
Can you drive?
Let's go.
Whoo! (Laughter)
Should we get... should we
literally get out and go to.
McDonald's?
Since there's a McDonald's in
the last Yeezy shoot?
Can I have an apple pie?
And two cheeseburgers.
And fries.
We got every single look shot.
It was a lot of work, but we did
it.
And with how amazing and pretty
the city is, this campaign's
gonna be super dope.
You guys want some fries? ♪
KOURTNEY: It's freezing.
WOMAN: Hello, why don't you
come and take a pic.
This is big monster.
His name is Chompy. >> KIM: Aw!
Cute! STYLIST: I feel like your
outfit's cool for this kind of,
like, crazy vibe.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, it's perfect
for this place.
KIM: Like, I either feel like
we have to go all-out Harajuku,
like this...
KOURTNEY: Is that what you
want me to wear?
STYLIST 2: Yeah, it's like
every once in a while she
unleashes, and it comes out.
KOURTNEY: "You look like
a clown!"
STYLIST 2: Yesterday was
horrible and disgusting.
KIM: I feel like I always,
like, pride myself on just being
honest.
STYLIST 2: Yeah, but, like,
your delivery is a little...
it's harsh.
KRIS: Sheila has been
recovering at home in bed, so I
think it's time for her to come
out and show us how beautiful
she looks. >> SHEILA: Hi.
♪
KIM: I feel like I always,
like, pride myself on just being
honest.
STYLIST 2: Yeah, but, like,
your delivery is a little...
it's harsh.
KOURTNEY: That's what I said,
I said it's not what you say,
it's how you say it.
STYLIST: Sometimes it
softens the blow if you say
something nice first.
KOURTNEY: It's called
sandwiching.
STYLIST: Yeah.
STYLIST 2: Or giving a
suggestion like, you know, we
did this yesterday, we should
try this...
KIM: That's a good one.
STYLIST: Where it's, like,
constructive, yeah.
KIM: But I just feel bad that
I was, like, so critical.
So I'm working on it.
STYLIST: I think that's
really great.
KIM: So I will definitely
work on my delivery, but my
message, I think, it pretty
clear.
KOURTNEY: Just, first go in
with a compliment so people
don't feel attacked.
KIM: Okay, so I would be
like, "Oh, okay, your skirt's"
cute.
"The eye shadow's ridiculous.
So, it's cute."
KOURTNEY: But you don't have
to say "ridiculous," you could
say, "I like your skirt, I feel
like the eye shadow might be a
little too over the top."
Maybe if we just compliment
Khloe on the days we do like her
hair, then she'll take the hint.
KIM: Then we'd never be
complimenting her.
Oh, they want to dance with you,
Kourtney. KOURTNEY: No, you go.
KIM: No, I don't dance.
KOURTNEY: I don't dance.
♪
KIM: Kanye's so happy with
how the shoot turned out, and I
feel like it was a really good
trip for all of us overall.
I mean, there was definitely
some rocky points, but I think
we have moved past that.
So, now it's the last night, and
we are doing this, like,
impromptu shoot, just to be us
again and hang out together and
just have fun.
STYLIST: You should do...
You should pick it up with your
hands and do that.
Eat the pasta.
Wait, but you should take it.
Like, that's so cute.
PHOTOGRAPHER: It definitely is.
KHLOE: I could eat.
If there's one thing you guys
want me to do, ask me to keep
eating.
KIM: Can you see my boob?
STYLIST: No, everything's
covered, you're good.
KHLOE: Where are you go...
What are you...?
KOURTNEY: Somebody get me a
cigarette and a bottle of
champagne.
STYLIST: You are amazing.
KIM: Who wants a performance?
KHLOE: Girl, you better work it.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Work.
KHLOE: Work that hoochie.
I want you, like, standing on
this table.
KOURTNEY: With a bottle of
champagne and spray it.
STYLIST: (laughs)
You're so extra.
KHLOE: Just act normal.
STYLIST: Yes!
KHLOE: You are so (bleep)
annoying!
I thought this was a great trip.
I loved it.
I loved Kyoto the most.
And I'm happy I got to go for my
first time with my sisters.
KOURTNEY: Aw, that's so
sweet. KHLOE: You can be such a
bitch sometimes.
Oh, no, face it that way, and
not this way, towards the wall.
KOURTNEY: This is so hard.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Like that.
Like that. >> KHLOE: Whoa!
(laughter) ♪
KRIS: Sheila has been
recovering at home in bed,
staring at the ceiling, and
trying to be a good girl and not
move.
So, I think it's time for her to
come out and have a little bit
of dinner and show us how
beautiful she looks.
COREY: What's up, young kids?
SHEILA: Hi.
KRIS: I feel like I have my.
Sheila from the '80s right back
with me.
How great does she look?
RANDY: She does look amazing.
KRIS: And it's really kind of
fabulous.
(phone ringing)
SHEILA: Is it Scott?
KRIS: Hi. We're celebrating
Sheila's face-lift.
SHEILA: Oh, God. (Laughter)
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
KRIS: Doesn't she look like
a teenager?
KHLOE: Aunt Sheila, you look
so good. SHEILA: Oh, thank you,
sweetheart.
Thank you for everything.
For checking in and...
KHLOE: Oh, my gosh.
SHEILA: I love you so much.
KHLOE: Uncle Randy, do you
even know who you're banging at
night?
SHEILA: Oh, my God!
RANDY: That's the best.
She might get rid of me.
I'm afraid of that.
SHEILA: Never.
KRIS: It's his prom date.
Oh, wait, what's going on?
KHLOE: You got your hair cut?
KRIS: Yeah.
SHEILA: Oh, it looks cute,
though. >> KHLOE: I can tell.
You look like a little boy.
(laughter)
KRIS: That's exactly what I
was going for.
(laughter)
KIM: On the next episode...
KRIS: Ooh, what is this?
Did your friend make those?
SCOTT: Yeah, that guy Art
Vandelay.
KRIS: Thank you so much for
my painting.
SCOTT: Oh, right.
KHLOE: All good things must
come to an end. >> KRIS: What?
KOURTNEY: To help out with
the Watts Center, we're doing a
softball game.
KRIS: I brought my secret
weapon. Take that, Jacksons.
Hey, everybody, Alex Rodriguez!
I'm so optimistic that this is
going to make the community a
better place.
WOMAN: This is a dream.
Captioning sponsored by.
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS