Keeping
Up With The Kardashians...
KIM: I'm dying to go to my 20
year, um, reunion is in two
weeks. >> WOMAN: Hello...
KIM: There was, like, a group
of us that were best friends,
and I'm so excited to reconnect
with them.
AMBER: Cheers to life, ladies.
(phone chimes) (Kylie gasps)
(phone chimes) KIM: Oh, my God.
There's a video of Tristan
making out with a girl last
night. KOURTNEY: The whole thing
makes me disgusted. KRIS: Hey.
Are you contracting?
Aw, (bleep).
I got to go. I got to go.
KIM: When there's something
crazy that goes on in our
family, we drop everything that
we're doing and go.
KHLOE (over phone): I don't
want any negativity in the
delivery room.
I don't want anyone to talk
about it, make me feel
uncomfortable or him
uncomfortable.
MALIKA: He's definitely gonna
have to face you guys.
KOURTNEY: It's gonna be hard
to even look at him or be in the
same room with him.
KIM: I think I'm just gonna
look at him and be like, "To be
continued, mother(bleep)."
"It's not over." ♪ ♪
KHLOE: 9:37 p.m.
On a rainy night, Uncle Savas is
driving me to the hospital now.
SAVAS: Listen, I'm like Dale.
Earnhardt Jr. Right now.
(Khloe laughs)
KHLOE: Let's not crash.
I feel really (bleep) scared.
I'm so nervous.
These are becoming really
painful, my contractions, so I
have to go to the hospital,
hopefully get an epidural, feel
better.
Savas can't handle the epidural
part, so I'll just be solo dolo.
I really pray that my mom, my
get to the
hospital in time.
There's no Wi-Fi on the plane,
so I haven't heard a thing.
I don't know how far out they
are.
Hopefully, I get a text message.
Okay, well, more to come.
SAVAS: More to come.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: When do they land?
MALIKA: In, like, three and a
half hours?
KIM: They left at 6:00, we
left at 7:00.
By the time we get to the
hospital from the airplane, I'd
say four hours.
MALIKA: Okay, so she would
have been in active labor for,
like, eight hours.
So her body has been ready to
have the baby for a minute.
KOURTNEY: I'm really praying
that we make it there in time.
Khloe is in active labor, so
we're cutting it really close.
How (bleep) insane to be doing
this by yourself.
Walking in, checking in, getting
your IV, sitting on the bed.
I would be (bleep) be (bleep) in
my pants.
♪ ♪
SAVAS: How are you doing
right now?
KHLOE: I am...
having contractions.
SAVAS: Listen, stop acting
like you're pregnant, man.
Let's wake up.
KHLOE: Oh, my God, I'm so
nauseous, it's out of control.
SAVAS: For real? You need
some water or something?
KHLOE: Just... shut up.
(Savas laughs)
SAVAS: Don't worry, man.
Tristan is on his way.
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
SAVAS: Want me to give you a
needle or something?
(Khloe laughs)
All right, where are we putting
this needle right here?
KHLOE: That is not at all
what the epidural looks like.
So you're crazy.
SAVAS: Wait, was the
epidural, the needle big?
KHLOE: It's not in me yet.
SAVAS: Oh, sh...
KHLOE: It goes in my back.
This is just... in my hand.
Savas that definitely adds a
layer of humor to this entire
experience, when I've never done
this before.
It's just, like, scary.
So it's good to have someone
that's just here to be your
support system, just to make you
laugh.
You know, it's... it's a good
energy to have around.
SAVAS: Here it is. 11:02.
KHLOE: (bleep)
SAVAS: Don't worry, you'll be
good.
KHLOE: I can't believe this.
Like, this is freaking me out.
TRISTAN: Hey, what's up?
Oh, we're here.
SAVAS: Hey, Simon, Tristan.
KHLOE: This is crazy.
Just so you know, this whole
experience is wild.
It's important for me to stick
to my birthing plan, because
this is something that I've
waited for my entire life.
I don't want to take away
anything from this moment, and I
have always been a believer of:
Don't make permanent decisions
off temporary emotions.
I want Tristan here with me.
I want to experience this
magical moment, and I want this
for me and my daughter, and for
him, at the end of the day.
And I'm mature enough to say
that.
I'm mature enough to, you know,
personal feelings aside.
And you know what, me and
Tristan will deal with him and I
at a later time, when this isn't
affecting our child.
Your dad just had his last game
of the season.
TRISTAN: Thank you, Lord.
KHLOE: Well, now it's
playoffs. >> TRISTAN: Playoffs.
That's what it's all about.
Now you're going to come bring
us the good luck for the
championship, right?
KHLOE: Yes.
TRISTAN: There you are.
KHLOE: Ooh. The hand sanitizer.
TRISTAN: There you go.
You're about to come join us any
minute.
SAVAS: All right, what are we
doing?
Where we at right now?
What are we doing?
KHLOE: We got the epidural.
TRISTAN: Yes, she got the
epidural.
Now we are awaiting, watching.
Two and a Half Men.
KHLOE: The date is April 12.
TRISTAN: It's April 12.
KHLOE: 2018.
SAVAS: What time is it right
now?
TRISTAN: The time is...
SAVAS: 12:21.
How you feeling?
KHLOE: I feel good.
The epidural is a life changer.
You weren't in the car with me
and Savas, but Savas kept trying
to talk to me, and I was like,
"Shut the (bleep) up!"
I was like, "You can't talk to
"me." >> TRISTAN: What'd he say?
KHLOE: Just, like, "Hi."
Like, it could be nothing.
I was like, "Shh! Shut up!" ♪ ♪
KIM: I cannot believe we made
it, guys.
KOURTNEY: Me, neither.
MALIKA: She's, like, nine and
a half, they might let her push.
KOURTNEY: How far out are we?
DRIVER: 25 minutes.
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God. Hurry.
Sorry. We have to get somewhere.
KIM: We landed, and we're
getting the updates as they're
coming in.
My mom, she ends up landing,
like, ten minutes before us.
We're rushing to get there as
quick as we can.
We can't miss this, 'cause that
would, like, break my heart.
KOURTNEY: I'm just stressing.
KIM: Yeah.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KHLOE: Good to see you!
KRIS: We made it.
SAVAS: We have a special
guest.
KRIS: We didn't think we were
gonna make it.
SAVAS: Look who came.
KRIS: Huh?
SAVAS: I said, look who came
for Khloe.
KRIS: Oh, look who came for.
Khloe. I wouldn't miss this for
anything. Thank God I'm here!
SAVAS: How was the flight?
KRIS: So nerve-racking,
because we didn't think we were
gonna make it.
ALIABADI: I always make it.
(laughter)
KRIS: And I think your
sisters are right behind us,
because Kim just texted.
KHLOE: Yeah, they're gonna be
here. >> SAVAS: Wow.
KHLOE: Get this show on the
road.
SAVAS: What time is it?
It is 1:26.
TRISTAN: 1:26, baby... Yeah!
KHLOE: I was like, "Oh, my."
God, what are the chances?
They're on a plane with no.
Wi-Fi.
KIM: We're here. We made it.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Hi.
KIM: I am so relieved that we
made it and that we will be able
to help Khloe through this
delivery.
Like, thank God.
MALIKA: You look good.
KOURTNEY: Khlo, who was here
with you? Simon?
KHLOE: Savas, and Simon was
with Tristan at work.
KIM: Can you believe we made it?
Like, I can't believe we made
it.
KHLOE: The contractions were
brutal.
KIM: Is there a bathroom in
here?
KOURTNEY: Did her water
break, or no?
ALIABADI: I just did it.
TRISTAN: That's a big one.
KHLOE: Are you going to say
hi to each other, or no?
TRISTAN: You're there. KIM: Hi.
TRISTAN: She went to the
bathroom.
I don't play.
KIM: The vibe in the room is
calm.
I thought there would be way
more tension.
As much as I want to go off, I
just don't think it's the time,
so I'm gonna keep it cute.
I don't have to have a lot of
interaction.
I just have to be there for her.
(phone rings) KHLOE: Oh, my God.
Hi, Kyles.
KYLIE: Wait, what's wrong
with you?
KHLOE: I needed to get the
baby's oxygen back up.
KYLIE: Oh, okay.
I feel like I need to be on
FaceTime for this.
I just need to.
KRIS: Can you see Khloe?
KYLIE: Yeah, I can see the
belly, which is all that
matters, really. (Kris whoops)
KRIS: We're having a baby.
(man laughs)
KYLIE: It's so fun.
KOURTNEY: It is fun, Kylie.
I like your attitude.
KYLIE: I'm so excited.
KOURTNEY: Oh, yeah, Mom.
KRIS: Let's go.
KHLOE: I'm really excited to
have everyone there.
But, oh, my God, I'm getting
that much closer to actually
having to give birth, which is
still just...
(exhales)
Tristan has to stay up here.
We've got enough issues.
I don't need that to be another
issue. (Kris laughs)
ALIABADI: Okay, who is gonna
help with this?
Do you want to help deliver?
KRIS: Yeah.
ALIABADI: Okay, excellent.
Let's do a practice push.
TRISTAN: Just relax.
Relax, relax, relax, relax.
KHLOE: Mom, what the (bleep)
do you think you're doing with
your phone by my vagina?
KRIS: I was just FaceTiming.
ALIABADI: No, she can't see
your vagina.
KHLOE: I don't want my vagina
on anyone's FaceTime.
(FaceTime rings)
Who the hell are you FaceTiming?
KOURTNEY: Kendall.
KHLOE: Hey, Kendall.
KENDALL: I want to meet her.
Where is she?
KHLOE: She's in my vagina.
KOURTNEY: She's not here yet.
We're still pushing.
ALIABADI: The surgeon is
coming. KHLOE: Oh, my... Oh, no.
TRISTAN: Oh.
KHLOE: (bleep) is crazy.
(Kris laughs)
KRIS: All right, Khlo.
ALIABADI: Push this baby out.
Come on.
DOCTOR: Just be strong.
All that you got.
ALIABADI: One more.
You can do it, one more.
KHLOE: Can't wait to meet her
and just, you know, spend the
rest of my life with her.
ALIABADI: Yes, yes, yes.
You can do it, you can do it.
(Khloe grunting)
(baby crying)
DOCTOR: Good morning.
KIM: Me, Kourtney, Kendall
and Kylie are coming back.
Monday.
KHLOE: Tristan said to me
that he wants to talk with my
sisters and my mom.
I don't have the energy for that
right now.
ALIABADI: The surgeon is coming.
KHLOE: Oh, my... Oh, no.
TRISTAN: Oh.
KHLOE: (bleep) is crazy.
KRIS: All right, Khloe.
(laughter) ALIABADI: Okay, she's
starting.
You're gonna push four times
since you're getting a long
break.
KHLOE: Okay.
ALIABADI: All right, let's
go. KHLOE: I have no idea what's
happening. KRIS: It's starting.
ALIABADI: Deep breath in.
(Khloe inhales)
Hold it.
DOCTOR: It's better when you
have your chest down like that.
ALIABADI: And push.
DOCTOR: As hard as you can.
ALIABADI: Push this baby out.
Come on.
Two, three... harder... four,
five, six...
KIM: Khloe midlife will never
be the same in the best way
possible.
KRIS: You're amazing.
ALIABADI: One more, let's go.
So, take a deep breath, and go.
Come on. Push hard.
KIM: You are so ready to be a
mom, and I'm so excited for this
journey for you.
DOCTOR: Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, hold it there.
Little more, little more, little
more. Go, go, go, go.
ALIABADI: She's crowning.
KYLIE: Does she have hair?
ALIABADI: Lots, like Stormi.
KYLIE: Ah!
DOCTOR: All your power.
You can do this.
Really strong, all that you got.
ALIABADI: And go.
DOCTOR: One more.
ALIABADI: Two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
KHLOE: It's just so
overwhelming.
You're experiencing a miracle
take place.
And I've always dreamed of being
a mom, and I think I came to the
place where I didn't know if
that was actually gonna happen
for me.
And so the fact that we're in a
delivery room for myself this
time, for me to give birth, it's
just unreal.
And I feel so blessed.
This is something that I've
waited for forever.
KRIS: Yes, that's awesome,
Khloe. You can do this.
KHLOE: Can't wait to meet her
and just, you know, spend the
rest of my life with her.
DOCTOR: Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
♪ ♪
(Khloe grunting)
ALIABADI: Look, look, look,
look, look. (Baby crying)
(all exclaiming)
DOCTOR: There's your baby.
KHLOE: Hi, little baby.
DOCTOR: There she is,
sweetheart.
TRISTAN: Welcome to the
world. >> DOCTOR: Hi.
TRISTAN: Girl.
KHLOE: Happy birthday.
TRISTAN: She's here.
DOCTOR: Oh, my goodness,
there's your dad.
ALIABADI: It's 4:00 exactly.
TRISTAN: 4:00 exactly?
ALIABADI: 4:00 exactly.
TRISTAN: It's your birthday.
DOCTOR: It's your birthday.
You'll have a happy home.
KENDALL: Hey, girl, look at you.
KYLIE: Oh, my God, she's so
cute.
TRISTAN: Look how cute she is.
KOURTNEY: She's so cute.
TRISTAN: Yes, yes.
KHLOE: We've been waiting for
you for quite some time.
The minute I met my daughter... I
cannot believe I'm even saying
the words "my daughter"... I was
so in love with her.
And she's just perfect.
TRISTAN: Hi, cutie.
KRIS: I got to deliver the
baby, which is once in a
lifetime. She's perfect.
She's precious.
She's such a blessing, and she's
beautiful.
KHLOE: She's so much smaller
than I thought. (Baby crying)
DOCTOR: You're okay, momma.
KRIS: Hi.
I know, that's your mommy.
KIM: Khloe's baby, I thought,
would come out, like, ten feet
tall and really big, and her
baby is so tiny, so beautiful.
She's so sweet, and Khloe
already is loving being a mom.
DOCTOR: Six pounds, 13 ounces.
TRISTAN: Really got to get
this all in the archives.
KOURTNEY: Seeing my new niece
is incredible.
I feel so blessed that I get to
witness my sisters having their
babies and that we're so close
no matter what's going on.
DOCTOR: Could we do
skin-to-skin with Daddy?
KHLOE: Yeah, of course.
DOCTOR: Done and done, okay.
KHLOE: Alexa, is that my camera?
ALEXA: Yeah.
KHLOE: Can you take pictures
of Tristan and her? ALEXA: Yeah.
KRIS: Tristan has the baby.
Tristan has the baby.
TRISTAN: Want me to move her
head?
(baby fussing)
DOCTOR: No, she's got...
she's got a place to breathe.
She's okay.
KRIS: So cute.
KHLOE: Tristan, how do you
feel? >> TRISTAN: Great.
(baby fusses) It's okay.
It's all right, it's all right.
It's okay, baby True.
KHLOE: With Tristan, you
know, it's...
My focus is not if we're gonna
be together or not.
My focus is just on my daughter.
And having these beginning
moments with my daughter and
seeing him be such a great
father to her, that's really
what's important to me.
TRISTAN: They say girls
change your life.
KOURTNEY: We can only pray.
(women scream) ALLISON: Hi, oh.
Oh, wow.
KIM: My reunion is amazing.
We're at Marymount High School.
ALLISON: Yay!
KIM: We are walking the same
halls.
KOURTNEY: All right, I feel
like we should go.
KHLOE: I have a baby.
It's really crazy.
KOURTNEY: It's good you get
to go home, get settled.
KIM: And we'll be back Monday
for our big family talk with.
Tristan.
♪ ♪
KRIS: I think she looks just
like Tristan.
KHLOE: Oh, my goodness.
KOURTNEY: She's smiling.
KHLOE: I have a baby.
It's really crazy.
ANDREA: Yes, my princess.
We've been waiting for you, and
you're finally here. Thank God.
TRISTAN: Good morning.
ANDREA: The new dad.
KOURTNEY: Mom, look how cute
this photo is.
I said, "Someone post it."
KRIS: Aw.
Can you send that to me?
It makes me cry.
I couldn't go get a card.
That's for you.
KHLOE: Oh, my God, you saved
this?
KRIS: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: My dad really gave
this to me? >> KRIS: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: Oh, my God, what's...
Don't cry.
KRIS: I waited a long time to
do this.
ANDREA: Yeah, it's a blessing.
KHLOE: Oh, my God. Mom.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Mom, you've kept this for
that long? >> KRIS: Uh-huh.
TRISTAN: I'll get you, um...
KRIS: It was the present that
your dad gave me the day you
were born.
KHLOE: Mom, you're so cute.
KRIS: Yeah.
KHLOE: My mom is just so
thoughtful, and she thinks so
far ahead.
And I cannot put into words how
sweet it is of my mom, saving
these three bracelets that my
dad gave her as her push
present.
She saved them for 34 years.
And I'm really grateful for
that. TRISTAN: Now we'll save it
and give it to her when she has
her daughter.
KHLOE: That's exactly what
we're gonna do.
KRIS: I'm so proud of you.
TRISTAN: Wait for her.
KHLOE: Thank you. ALIABADI: Hey.
Let's go to Mama.
KHLOE: Hi, baby.
KOURTNEY: Khlo, do we have a
name for her?
KHLOE: I think True.
It's the only name that I think
about. >> KOURTNEY: T-R-U?
KHLOE: "E." KOURTNEY: T-R-U-E.
MALIKA: I think that's
beautiful.
KOURTNEY: It is.
KHLOE: Her name is True.
Thompson.
I knew I wanted the initials.
T.T., 'cause I love that my
initials are K.K.
And I was at dinner one night at
my mom's house and MJ was there
and I told her that.
Tristan and I want to do either
a name that starts with a "T" or
a "K."
MJ: How 'bout Tommy?
We could call her Tommy.
KOURTNEY: Tommy Thompson?
MJ: How about True?
KOURTNEY: I love the name True.
MJ: That's your grandfather's
name.
He was a good man. KHLOE: True.
MJ: I love that.
KHLOE: We kept going back and
forth, and True was the only one
that really always made the cut.
And then everyone says you have
to wait till you meet the baby.
But I don't know who looks like
a True.
I don't know if, like, when Kim
was naming North, if they were
like, "Oh, she looks like a
North."
Like, what the (bleep) is a
North?
What the (bleep) is a True?
They just become these names,
and they're so cute.
KOURTNEY: Is she gonna have a
middle name?
KHLOE: I don't think so.
MALIKA: She could be a True
Kardashian.
KOURTNEY: True Kardashian.
What if her name was True.
Kardashian Thompson?
KRIS: I kind of like it.
MALIKA: I'm not mad at it at
all.
(True burps)
KHLOE: Oh! There you go,
young lady. (Laughter)
KOURTNEY: She makes the
cutest noises.
MALIKA: Yeah, she coos.
KHLOE: Okay.
KOURTNEY: Tristan, I was
FaceTiming Reign.
TRISTAN: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: He was like, "Aw!"
And then he goes, "I love her.
KoKo, she can share all my toys."
"My Legos..." >> TRISTAN: Really?
KOURTNEY: "my..." Yeah.
TRISTAN: Aw, that's so nice.
KIM: That's cute.
KHLOE: You know, I was super
anxious about having everybody
in the hospital room, because it
was really crucial and important
for me that it was a very
healthy, happy, positive
experience.
And it was... Everyone put their
differences aside for that
moment.
I'm really grateful for that.
TRISTAN: I'm proud of you.
KHLOE: But, I mean,
obviously, there's a big
elephant in the room.
I think it's important for you
two... you and Kourt and him
have a talk.
KIM: Well, me, Kourtney,
Kendall and Kylie are coming
back Monday.
We're leaving Tuesday night.
KHLOE: So Monday will be
fine. We'll make time Monday.
TRISTAN: Mm-hmm.
KHLOE: Tristan said to me
that he wants to talk with my
sisters and my mom.
Um, I have my own personal
feelings, 'cause this happened
to me.
But my sisters also have their
feelings, and they are very much
entitled to that.
KIM: You ready? TRISTAN: Huh?
KIM: You ready? TRISTAN: Always.
KHLOE: When there's drama,
people love to be like, "Well",
this is my relationship.
I don't need to involve people."
Well, in this family, you do,
so...
TRISTAN: See you all later.
Safe travels.
I'll see you all in a little
bit.
KIM: Yeah, hey, bye.
See you later. Have a good game.
Don't slip.
KOURTNEY: All right, I feel
like we should go. KHLOE: Yeah.
FRIEND: Are you still okay
with us, like, coming out here
on Monday?
KHLOE: Why don't we talk, um,
just a little closer?
FRIEND: Okay.
KHLOE: 'Cause things are just
being weird these days.
So we'll just talk and see.
KOURTNEY: Are you happy we're
coming back or do you think
you're gonna be overwhelmed?
KHLOE: No, I'm happy.
I-I feel bad.
KOURTNEY: I feel like also
it's good you get to go home,
get settled. (True crying)
KHLOE: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: And then we'll come
back.
KHLOE: I just have to get out
of here.
KOURTNEY: Is somebody writing
you? >> KHLOE: Mm-hmm.
Too many people.
But writing about both things.
I'm like, "Shut up."
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KHLOE: I don't have the
energy for that right now.
Like, everyone leave me alone.
KOURTNEY: I feel like
everyone just wants you to know
that you're supported.
KHLOE: And I appreciate that.
I do. But...
it's also everyone has their own
(bleep) that I know nothing
about, and mine is thrown on the
public of everything.
And it's just... it's a lot
harder to filter through stuff
when it's this public and when I
gave birth the following day.
There's too much.
It's so much harder to deal with
it when it's so public and
everyone is giving you their
opinions and their input and
their unsolicited advice.
Even feeling like, "Oh, God, the"
nurses and the doctors"...
Everyone kind of, like, looking
sideways at the whole situation.
That's hard, and it's
humiliating.
KOURTNEY: I feel like people,
like, force you to try to, like,
get out of it.
KHLOE: Yeah. I just need to
figure out my own... without
feeling, like, guilty if I'm,
you know, letting you guys down
or this.
Or it's like I can't even worry
about that.
He obviously (bleep) up, major.
But I'm not sure how I feel
about anything right now.
In two weeks, I might say, "You
know what, I don't trust you",
and this isn't for me."
Or I might say, "This is
perfect. Let's keep it going."
But I'm just, like... I'm
thinking way too much about
this. This is too (bleep) shady.
KIM: I feel like the worst is
over.
KHLOE: I don't know.
I feel so exhausted.
KIM: And we'll be back Monday
for our big family talk with.
Tristan. (True cries)
Khloe is literally acting like
nothing happened.
Maybe that's her way to cope.
KOURTNEY: No, that's what I
said.
I just said, "You're being too"
"nice." >> CICI: What happened in.
Cleveland?
KIM: We went back to have
this, like, family talk with
Tristan.
No cameras were there, and we
really wanted it to be a private
talk.
I told him, "I think you're more"
remorseful 'cause it's affecting
your job."
KRIS: I know she really never
saw it coming.
♪ ♪
KIM: So, for my reunion, do I
want to, like, dress up?
Do I want to not? Like...
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: Like, what about, like,
something like that?
Where I can still have my
stomach out.
KOURTNEY: I think that's very
Kim K.
KIM: What about that?
Don't want people staring at my
ass. KOURTNEY: They're going to,
and, like, let them.
You should stand in a line and
say, "Does anyone want to touch
my ass?"
KIM: Since Khloe had her baby
early, despite all of the chaos,
one silver lining is just that
I'm gonna be able to go to my
reunion tomorrow.
I mean, it's been 20 years.
That's a really long time.
I want to see the faces of
people that I, you know, went to
high school with and see how
everyone turned out and what
they're up to.
So I'm really excited to go.
What are we gonna say on Monday?
KOURTNEY: Oh, when we go
back, you want to say something?
KIM: Yeah, he wants to have a
talk with us.
KOURTNEY: Oh, who said?
KIM: Tristan did.
KOURTNEY: He said it to you?
KIM: He said, "I would love"
to talk to you and Kourtney.
I think we all need to sit down
and talk."
And I said, "Oh, I'm ready."
Then I was like...
I was like, "This will be like."
Mayweather and Pacquiao, and I
am Mayweather.
So are you ready?"
KOURTNEY: But you're making
it into a joke?
KIM: No, I think it'll be
really serious.
I mean, it was definitely
awkward to see him, don't you
think?
KOURTNEY: I think he was
being the best he could.
KIM: And Khloe was literally
acting like nothing happened.
Maybe that's her way to cope.
KOURTNEY: Well, no, that's
what I said.
I just said, "I don't want him"
to think that you're being too
nice.
Like, did you have a
conversation with him that you
just can't wrap your head around
it right now and you need to,
"like, have your moment and
enjoy this... this moment?"
And she was like, "Yeah, he
knows."
But I also don't want it to be
where it just goes away then
'cause time has gone by.
I feel like that's what used to
happen with Scott and I all the
time.
♪ ♪
(True crying) NURSE: Go ahead.
I'll take care everything off.
WOMAN: Hi.
KHLOE: I know. I know, momma.
(True crying)
You don't like to have your
clothes off. That's good.
Ooh. Hello. (True cooing)
Hello.
Can I put her clothes back on,
or not yet?
NURSE: Let me take a look at
her here. >> KHLOE: Yeah.
NURSE: Yeah. Let me take a
look at her real quick.
KHLOE: The first couple days
of being home from the hospital
have been great.
I feel a lot better now that I'm
home.
I like my own space, I love my
routine, and I feel good.
I'm so in love with True, and
your obsession becomes more and
more and more every single day.
And when you think you're at
this, like, capacity of love,
you're really not.
I don't know how, but it just
keeps growing and growing and
growing.
(True crying) >> NURSE: Shh.
WOMAN: Will the flash bug her?
KHLOE: She better get
used to it.
(laughter)
NURSE: That's pretty true.
♪ ♪
KIM: We're gonna go to school
really quick to see our
teachers.
NORTH: No, no, no, no, no!
KIM: Just to see our teachers.
SARAH: Oh, my God.
KIM: Do you think they'll be
there?
SARAH: Probably. I'm sure,
like, a lot.
KIM: Oh, I brought yearbooks
in the car.
SARAH: Oh, good, good, good.
I was gonna ask you.
AMBER: Oh, don't even try.
SARAH: I was gonna ask you to
bring them.
KIM: 'Cause I need to know,
like, who's on drugs, who's
normal. All right, got to go.
SARAH: Should we go? Let's go.
It's so cute.
KIM: Wait. I didn't bring
an ID. AMBER: No! Kim, shut up.
SARAH: I mean, I'm sure
they'll know who you are.
(laughter)
KIM: I loved high school.
I loved my experience.
There was, like, a group of us
that were best friends.
(applause and cheering)
But Amber and Sarah... I really
haven't seen them in 20 years.
Sarah was so artsy and
free-spirited, and Amber was
total party girl, really smart
and just funny.
AMBER: And Khloe just had her
baby.
KIM: She just had a baby.
AMBER: How is she? She good?
SARAH: And you were there
last night?
KIM: So I was talking to my
best friend Jonathan, and I was
like, "Should I fly back?
Like, we're all in Cleveland."
Like, what should I do?"
And Jonathan was like, "You know
what?
At your ten-year, it's like, oh,
you're just catching up."
SARAH: Yeah.
KIM: Like, you're still...
No one knows what they're doing.
No one has their careers, it's
just like measuring your...
AMBER: Like, too little time.
KIM: Yeah. 20 years, like...
AMBER: 20 years is...
KIM: This is where you're at.
Like, this is all or nothing.
AMBER: Right.
KIM: And then, next year, you
guys might as well just wheel in
a wheelchair. AMBER: Literally.
SARAH: I remember when you
would get a bikini wax into,
like, shapes and show us,
remember?
AMBER: Oh, yeah, you did.
SARAH: Like, in little
hearts and, like...
AMBER: You got, like, a heart
or a star.
SARAH: A Playboy bunny.
AMBER: At, um...
KIM: Pink Cheeks.
AMBER: Pink Cheeks.
SARAH: Pink Cheeks!
Oh, my God.
AMBER: I said... I was like,
"I have to go. Kim's going."
SARAH: Pink Cheeks.
AMBER: That's so funny.
SARAH: We're almost there.
KIM: 20 years.
I've been waiting for this, I've
been so excited.
I've been DMing everyone,
finding them on social media,
getting on a group chat.
I can't wait to reconnect with
them.
AMBER: Oh, my God, I'm so
nervous.
KIM: Okay, here's Allison.
(Amber gasps)
(shrieking, laughing)
KIM: She sat there and was
like, "If you want to live this
life of dating these Instagram"
whores and doing your thing,
live that life."
KIM: Then he got mad.
CICI: He got caught.
KIM: Yeah.
KRIS: Yeah, but how many more
of these things are we supposed
to prepare ourselves for?
KIM: Can you believe
Tristan's mad at me?
KOURTNEY: It's his fault.
KIM: I am, like, not
tolerating it.
KOURTNEY: I don't think we
want to cause her any more
stress.
KIM: I'm, like, done.
Done with him, over it.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: Here comes Allison.
(Amber gasps)
(screaming, laughing)
AMBER: Hi. How are you?
ALLISON: Oh, wow.
KIM: Okay, so, Allison showed
up...
ALLISON: Hi, guys. Here I am.
KIM: We are...
Are you so excited to be at.
Marymount High School?
ALLISON: I don't know what to
expect, I'm so nervous.
KIM: I know. I'm so nervous.
We spotted some girls.
ALLISON: Already?
KIM: Yup.
ALLISON: Oh, I hope I know
their names.
SARAH: Are you wearing your
name tag for real?
KIM: Should I wear my name
tag?
ALLISON: I think you should.
I think it'll look good on you.
KIM: Marymount High School.
ALLISON: Yay!
KIM: We are walking...
SARAH: Marymount!
KIM: The same halls.
My reunion is amazing.
The famous Kelly Stoll.
WOMAN: Kelly, get in here now!
KIM: Kind of everything I
wanted it to be, just seeing all
my friends.
And the school has changed.
Like, it definitely got an
upgrade and looks amazing.
This is so crazy, these halls.
Just even going into the
bathroom, where we used to spend
so much time, is so trippy.
We are the class of '98.
This is where chemistry was,
through this building.
This is where I-I did really bad
in this chemistry class.
(laughs)
I am so glad that I got to go to
my reunion, and I didn't miss
out anything, and it all turned
out perfectly.
SARAH: Kelly, will you take
your tooth out for my Instagram?
KELLY: No, no.
(screaming)
ALLISON: Oh, my God, Kelly,
why?
SARAH: Put it in, put it back
in now. ALLISON: I just want to
understand why you haven't,
like, fixed that.
Like, 20 years later, it's,
like, still coming out.
KELLY: I know, I got to keep
that (bleep) in.
KIM: Just hold onto that tooth.
Just seeing all my friends...
It's been a long time that we
all just really hung out
together.
Look, I put a heart next to you,
Clair.
So, I'm really happy to
reconnect with them.
You guys, I haven't stayed out
this late.
You would think it was like 3:00
a.m. is how I feel.
AMBER: Oh, my God.
KIM: I just, like,
literally...
SARAH: No, tonight was...
KIM: Went to bed last
night at 9:00.
SARAH: Tonight was a big night.
How's your mom?
KIM: She's so good.
SARAH: She's good?
KIM: Yeah. She's in Cleveland
with Khloe. >> SARAH: Nice.
KIM: You know?
SARAH: Is she okay?
KIM: I mean, I think she's in
such shock.
I think it was such disbelief.
SARAH: While she's having
a... >> AMBER: It's the timing
that's, like... >> SARAH: Ugh!
AMBER: The double kick, like...
KIM: Yeah.
SARAH: It's like joy... it's
like extreme joy and extreme...
KIM: I cannot imagine.
AMBER: And, like, the
intensity of, like, your
hormones and the emotions are
just like...
SARAH: Ugh!
And it's supposed to be, like,
so much joy. >> KIM: I know.
It really, really, really is so
(bleep) up.
AMBER: It is so (bleep) up.
SARAH: Yeah.
♪ ♪
ALL: ♪ Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear
Kourtney... ♪
KOURTNEY: Whoa, don't look at
my face, though.
ALL: ♪ Happy birthday to
you. ♪ (Whooping)
KIM: ♪ And many more. ♪
KHLOE: My sisters are back in
town, and they're gonna have
their talk with Tristan.
I didn't think this conversation
was gonna be good on camera.
I've always been very respectful
that this is not Tristan's
career, and having conversations
like this isn't comfortable for
him on camera.
And he might not want to be as
vulnerable as he normally would
if he were in private.
KRIS: Kim, do you want any
more veggies?
KHLOE: And, you know what, me
and Tristan will deal with this
at a later time, because there
are some things that...
it's deeper than...
being documented.
It takes more time than just,
you know... an episode.
♪ ♪
KIM: Sushi? I can't lose her.
KRIS: Sushi's gonna be
somebody's sushi over here,
because there's hawks and
everything else that eat little
dogs.
CICI: I've been dying.
How's Khloe?
What happened in Cleveland? Ugh.
KIM: Honestly, I mean, I'm
glad we went.
We got to see the baby... but...
CICI: Yeah, of course, and
you got to support Khloe.
KIM: Yeah, but it was...
The more I think about it, the
more pointless it was.
KRIS: Well, he was very
remorseful and he was very
feeling, obviously, sick over
everything that happened.
KIM: But I told him I think
you're more remorseful 'cause
it's effecting your job.
You know?
CICI: Or how he's looked upon.
KIM: Totally. Totally.
I think he's more embarrassed
that he looks stupid.
CICI: How people-how people
are-are looking at him.
KIM: Booing him and I think
it's more of that than anything.
And I told him that.
We went back to have this, like,
family talk with Tristan.
No cameras were there and we
really wanted it to be a private
talk, but we all expressed
exactly how we felt.
KRIS: When something like
this does happen, everybody has
a story.
CICI: Yeah, it's the dirty
secret, so now the secret's out,
and that's what it is.
He's... He got caught.
KIM: Yeah.
KRIS: Yeah, but how many more
of these things are we supposed
to prepare ourselves for?
KIM: She sat there and was
like, "Tell me, how many more
people has it been?"
How many more of this?"
Like he's gonna tell you?
I think the convo was going okay
at the beginning...
and then it got heated and,
I don't know, it just kind of
took a left turn.
Then he got mad because my mom
was like, "You can make your
decision."
If you want to be... if you want
to live this life of dating
"these Instagram whores and doing
your thing, live that life."
Mom's like, "If this doesn't
work out with you guys, we're"
always going to rise up."
Overall, I think it was
definitely necessary for us to
all just, like, let out how we
all felt.
And since he is the father of.
Khloe's baby, I definitely
wanted to take the time to hear
what he had to say.
KRIS: You know, Khloe has
been so invested...
Like, moved to Cleveland and
nested in this house and made it
a home and, I mean, it's
beautiful because of you can see
the whole place is Khloe.
It's got, you know, Khloe
written all over it.
KIM: Oh, totally. Totally.
KRIS: She said something
really interesting.
She said, "I didn't have a baby"
just to have a baby and move
on."
She said, "I had a baby to
create a beautiful family."
And that's what broke my heart.
You know, that she...
CICI: Which is true.
KRIS: You know, she really
never saw it coming. Ellen.
KHLOE: How was it?
KIM: I just want to tell you
what I said, 'cause she asked me
about you.
♪ ♪
HAIRSTYLIST: Do you want to
go shorter?
KIM: We can. What do you think?
HAIRSTYLIST: I feel like it's
either this length or it's,
like, mid-neck.
KIM: Yeah. Let's go for it.
And it
really sucks when you have a
whole PR schedule planned and
then a family drama happens soon
after or close to your press
schedule.
ELLEN: What's going on?
You... The... Boy, oh, boy.
So, Khloe, um, poor Khloe.
KIM: I don't even know how to
describe it besides it's just so
(bleep) up, like...
ELLEN: Yeah.
KIM: Like, like it's... I...
ELLEN: Yeah. >> KIM: I...
ELLEN: Are they together?
Is... Are they... Is she still
trying to make that work?
KIM: I think she just wants a
clear head and just wants to be
alone with her baby.
She's gonna get through it.
We're such a close family.
She has such a good support
system and all we can do is be
there for her and the baby.
(applause)
TRACY: I was holding my
breath when the, uh, the Khloe
stuff came up.
KIM: Did I say everything
okay?
TRACY: No, I thought you were
great.
I think you said what everyone
else was thinking, you know?
KIM: I mean, it's (bleep) up,
but I also want to respect
Khloe and like, let her tell her
story her way.
I should call her just to give
her a heads up. >> TRACY: Yeah.
(line ringing)
KHLOE (on phone): Hello.
KIM: Hi. What are you doing?
KHLOE: Just feeding.
What are you doing? Ellen.
KHLOE: Oh, fun. How was it?
KIM: It was really good.
I just wanted to tell you what I
said, 'cause she asked me about
you. >> KHLOE: Oh, okay.
KIM: I said, "Yeah, you know,
it's... I'm not gonna lie, it's"
"really (bleep) up, and my heart
breaks for her but she's so
strong and blah, blah, blah."
So I do want you to know that I
did say it's (bleep) up.
KHLOE: I appreciate how you
feel, but right now I'm dealing
with my own (bleep), and I just,
like, don't really care.
KIM: But I think if I didn't
say it's (bleep) up and my heart
breaks for you, it would... I
mean, we'd be, like, idiots,
like, ignoring it.
You know what I mean?
KHLOE: I mean, it is (bleep)
up, and he's a complete piece of
(bleep).
Honestly, you can feel however
you want, but I just got other
(bleep) to deal with right now.
KIM: Okay.
All right, I love you.
Okay. Okay, bye.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Here, wear these.
'Cause then when we go on the
trampoline you can take 'em off.
PENELOPE: No, Mom.
I hurt my toe.
KIM: Okay, can I wear them?
Thank you.
PENELOPE: No. No.
KIM: No, they're for me.
Thank you.
PENELOPE: No, it's mine.
KIM: No, you don't want to
wear it, so I do.
PENELOPE: I want to wear it.
KIM: You want to wear it?
But I want to wear it.
Okay, fine, here you go.
Spider check.
KOURTNEY: Okay, you can take
off your shoes.
KIM: Can you believe.
Tristan's mad at me?
Khloe just wrote me and said...
I sent her my... a clip of my
interview with Ellen.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: I-I called her right
after and said I just want you
to know I said it's like effed
up. And so she texted me that he
said I'm trying to start
stuff, and I'm an instigator,
and blah, blah, blah.
(Penelope squeals)
KIM: So I unfollowed him on
Instagram and I'm like, he
should be embarrassed.
So I literally wrote her and
said, "Look, let's change the
subject."
I love you and I support you."
But I'm, like, done.
Done with him. Over it.
PENELOPE: Done.
KOURTNEY: I feel like there's
only so much we can do as much
as we... it's like, everyone has
to learn their own lesson.
(Penelope screams)
KIM: She just should have
stood her ground.
You know what I mean, like, you
can't just, like, right away.
KOURTNEY: No. No.
You just... She should just do
what's in her heart.
And she should either... like,
give it a chance, and if that's
what makes her feel best for her
family, I've been there.
KIM: Like, that's not
realistic.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, I don't think
his intentions are right.
I don't think he's gonna change,
but I'm just saying, if she
wants to feel like she's trying
for her own heart, and know that
she's doing her best, then I
don't think there's anything
wrong with that.
I think it takes a lot more
strength to do... to hang in
there and try for your family
than to just walk away.
(Penelope speaking indistinctly)
KIM: I won't make her feel
bad about anything, but I just,
generally, don't care to, like,
be around him.
KOURTNEY: I mean, it's her
decision, and I don't think we
want to cause her any more
stress. KIM: I mean, ultimately,
whatever makes her happy.
I'll stay out of the way.
On the next episode...
Just to, like, a night off
to happen. >> ALL: To Cher.
KIM: I was able to pull off a
backstage meeting with Cher.
I feel like I'm gonna faint.
MAN: Okay, are you guys
ready? >> KIM: Oh, my God.
She's like, "Oh, please, I don't
want you guys to fight."
I'm like, "I unfollowed him and
I'm just letting you know."
KOURTNEY: Does he follow us?
KIM: (gasps) He blocked me.
Tristan is just too petty for
me.
Where's my bestie?
Captioning sponsored by.
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS
Captioned by.
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org