♪ ♪
KHLOE: Cool. Kourt.
KOURTNEY: Oh, cool.
STYLIST: You look amazing,
love. >> HAIRSTYLIST: So good.
KOURTNEY: I'm wearing that
pink blazer over there, hanging.
KHLOE: Oh, pretty.
(phone buzzes)
Mom. KRIS: Look, I'm on the 405.
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
KOURTNEY: She wanted to get
there early, I guess.
KHLOE: I know, but I wanted
to get there a little...
I don't want to be there late.
KRIS: I mean, knowing you,
I'm shocked that Kourtney's
there. I'm so proud of her.
KHLOE: No, I'm at Kourtney's
house.
KRIS: Oh. (Laughs)
KHLOE: Kourtney's...
KRIS: Well, there you go.
KHLOE: You know.
KOURTNEY: I'll be ready in
five minutes.
KHLOE: Today is the day of
my shower, and I had been
planning this baby shower for
forever, so it's just really
exciting.
And I have about a week before
I go back to Cleveland, and
I'll be there permanently until
the basketball season's over and
we come back.
But right now I am so ready to
enjoy my baby shower.
The only thing I have left to do
is to get Kourtney out of the
(bleep) door.
KRIS: See you there,
tootsies. >> KHLOE: Bye.
Okay, Kourt, I love you.
STYLIST: Are you leaving?
KHLOE: But we're going.
Can't be late to my own shower.
STYLIST: You're all set.
KOURTNEY: Glasses or no
glasses? >> KHLOE: Why not?
I think you look so (bleep)...
I'm so sorry.
I'll give you a dollar.
You look so cute.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: We're going to your
baby shower, Khlo.
Here it is. The Hotel Bel-Air.
KHLOE: Hey, did you know this
is where I met Tristan?
PENELOPE: I know that.
KHLOE: You do?
KOURTNEY: How do you know?
Oh, my gosh.
KHLOE: Hello. (Gasps)
Are you kidding me? Oh, my God.
It is to die for.
KOURTNEY: Khloe's baby shower
is one of the most magical,
beautiful baby showers I've
ever seen.
KHLOE: Like, Tristan's gonna
die when he sees this.
KOURTNEY: It's like walking
into this wonderland of pink
everything, and everyone's
dressed in pink.
Khloe just really had this
vision and made it all come to
life.
KYLIE: Oh, my goodness.
Is this not the cutest thing
ever? >> KHLOE: Where's Stormi?
KYLIE: It's huge in there.
KHLOE: It's, now I'm...
She's hu... Don't scare me.
I'm so afraid to push it out.
KYLIE: No... MARIA: Was it hard?
KYLIE: No.
KHLOE: No, I was with...
MARIA: Really?
KHLOE: Kylie literally was...
KYLIE: It was the easiest
thing ever.
KHLOE: Like, they were like,
"Push," and she was like this:
"Did I do it?"
MARIA: Oh, my God, that's
amazing. >> KHLOE: I know.
KIM: Ooh, so pretty.
There's honestly nothing like
your first baby shower.
Just to be able to celebrate
with everyone that you love.
And we have been waiting for
this moment for so long.
I'm just so excited for her.
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
You look so different.
KIM: I know, don't I look so
different?
KHLOE: You really do.
KIM: I'm like, "Aah."
MARIA: I love how calm you are.
KHLOE: Really, I am calm?
MARIA: Yeah, your demeanor is
so calm.
KIM: Grandma, do you want to
help pick a name?
MJ: Oh, I like that.
KIM: True, your grandfather.
MJ: My grandpa... uh, your
grandpa. >> KIM: No. Bob's dad?
MJ: Your grandfather.
KIM: Bob's dad?
MJ: Yes, he's your real
grandfather.
KIM: Okay.
Um, what... what name was it?
MJ: He's your real... T-R-U-E.
KIM: No, but... Oh, T...
His was T-R-U-E.
MJ: Uh-huh. I love that.
KRIS: Should we sit down and
if anybody wants to eat...
KHLOE: Yeah.
KRIS: I, for one, am starving.
KHLOE: Okay.
KRIS: I'm getting low blood
sugar. KHLOE: Okay, whenever you
want to eat. Jesus.
Please sit with her.
CICI: I'm sitting with her.
Oh, yeah.
KHLOE: Holy (bleep).
I'm so happy with how it turned
out. >> MJ: Be careful with this
here. (Laughs) Be good.
KHLOE: That's how we got here.
MJ: All right. Okay.
KOURTNEY: Look how beautiful
this room is.
KRIS: Hi, everybody.
CICI: Hi.
KRIS: And welcome to KoKo.
Wonderland.
Thank you so much for coming.
Um, get a few tears out of the
way, and then I'll roll into
this, 'cause I always cry.
It's so silly.
But, um, I just want to say that
out of all my kids, I worried
for a second about whether or
not Khloe would have a baby.
And it's such an amazing
blessing.
KHLOE: Thank you.
KRIS: Uh, we are beyond
excited and thrilled to welcome
another... my ninth grandchild.
(all cheering)
That's a lot of people.
That's a lot of human beings.
KHLOE: It's Andrea's first
granddaughter. >> KRIS: Andrea!
Tristan's mom... >> WOMAN: Yay!
KRIS: Is here with us today.
Andrea.
ANDREA: I am so happy and
excited for my daughter.
I don't have a daughter.
But, um, when I'm... when I'm
texting Khloe, I always put,
"To my daughter."
KHLOE: That's so sweet.
ANDREA: Ladies and gentlemen,
we thank so much for this day.
It's a blessing for Khloe and
Tristan.
GUESTS: Amen.
KRIS: Thanks for being here.
KHLOE: Aw. Hello.
TRISTAN: What's going on?
You look good, this is nice.
KHLOE: How are you?
Babe, isn't it so pretty?
TRISTAN: This is really nice.
KHLOE: It must be raining out
there. TRISTAN: You showing even
more today.
KHLOE: I know, it just keeps
getting bigger and bigger.
TRISTAN: I like it, though.
Yeah, you look really good.
KHLOE: Thank you.
ANDREA: Oh, you like it?
TRISTAN: Yeah, you look good.
I heard you killed the speech.
Kendall said you killed the
speech, it's all they talked
about.
KIM: We were all crying. Hey.
KHLOE: I am in awe.
I literally feel like I'm
dreaming.
There's no way that this is
real and that this shower's for
me.
And I'm so thankful for every
person that has helped with
this.
My baby shower team, Mindy Weiss
and Jeff Leatham, knew exactly
what I wanted, and I couldn't be
more blessed.
ALIABADI: Congratulations.
KHLOE: Having Tristan's
family here and Tristan being
able to come to the shower, it's
absolute perfection, and I love
every minute of it.
Babe! >> ALIABADI: Tristan!
He's such a gentleman.
KHLOE: He's so cute, I know.
ALIABADI: But he's so good.
KHLOE: It's hard...
ALIABADI: He reminds me...
My husband's like that.
KHLOE: It's hard to be mad
at him.
ALIABADI: Right. Come, come.
TRISTAN: Okay.
KHLOE: He said okay. ♪ ♪
KYLIE: I'll make cinnamon
streusel muffins.
KOURTNEY: Do you want me to
help you?
KYLIE: Sure.
KOURTNEY: This is what you
do? You make boxed things?
KYLIE: Well, you know, um,
they got rid of their
cinnamon cake.
Remember Mom used to make that
cinnamon cake? KOURTNEY: Stop.
KYLIE: And drizzle...
KOURTNEY: The coffee cake.
KYLIE: Yes.
And drizzle cinnamon.
I tweet them every day.
You don't see my tweets?
KOURTNEY: I bet Kim is
probably horrified.
KYLIE: Horrified.
So, they replaced it with this.
KOURTNEY: This looks nothing
like it.
KYLIE: Nothing.
KOURTNEY: And then we need
two eggs.
I'm so excited for all of our
stuff coming up.
KYLIE: I'm so excited.
KOURTNEY: We have our shoot.
KYLIE: I know.
I haven't done anything in a
long time, so I'm a little
nervous.
You know, my body is not, you
know, what it used to be.
I'm just getting, like,
comfortable with my body again.
A lot of us women go through
this.
But it is a shock to the system
to... just... see your body,
especially at such a young age,
change so drastically and just
not be the same size.
I got to get in there.
KOURTNEY: I'm only gonna have
two bites so I don't get sick.
KYLIE: That's a huge bite.
Oh, my God. Ew.
"I'm gonna have two bites."
Takes the whole thing.
(Kourtney laughs)
KOURTNEY: That could be the
best dessert I've ever had. ♪ ♪
KIM: Welcome to my condo.
LARSA: Ooh, I love it.
KIM: I figured it's, like,
the perfect location to have my
office. >> LARSA: Yeah.
KIM: So I don't have a ton
of people in my house.
These are the plans.
So, like, here, you'll walk in.
There'll be a round table with
just little stools.
This is the master, and I'm
gonna make it a bedroom so I
could film YouTube tutorials
sitting, like, looking in your
bedroom, kind of?
LARSA: So cute, yeah.
Super personal.
KIM: You know, one day I can
maybe give this apartment to one
of my kids.
If they'd want to, like, live in
it.
LARSA: Totally. How's Chicago?
KYLIE: She's good.
LARSA: She's so cute.
KIM: She's so cute.
LARSA: And she's still so
good, right?
KIM: The best baby ever.
LARSA: How do you keep
getting lucky with all your
kids?
Like, you're supposed to have
one bad kid. >> KIM: I know.
LARSA: Like, doesn't sleep,
or it doesn't eat.
Like, your kids are all so good.
KIM: Yeah, Kanye wants to
have more, though.
Like, he's been harassing me.
LARSA: How many more?
KIM: He wants, like, seven.
He's, like, stuck on seven.
LARSA: Okay, he needs to name.
Seven... >> KIM: Yeah.
LARSA: And, like, lighten
up on the kid situation.
Seven kids is crazy.
KIM: That's crazy.
I could never, especially in,
like, the world we live in.
I feel like the world is just so
different now than when I grew
up, so I've been kind of
hesitant about having more kids,
just because it literally keeps
me up at night, thinking about
how my kids will survive in a
crazy world like this.
All this... shooting after
shooting that goes on.
LARSA: Yeah.
KIM: Just, like, the worry
that you have.
LARSA: I hear you.
It's scary.
And people have been trying to
kidnap you, rob you, take you.
So that kind of plays into all
that. >> KIM: All that stuff.
Lately, there have been so many
devastating school shootings.
The most recent shooting was in
Parkland, Florida, and that was
just... I don't know, it just hit
so close to home.
As a parent in general, the
thought of bringing your kid to
a school and having them not
come home because of a senseless
shooting is something that
definitely consumes me a lot.
It's like, every day, there's
something so traumatizing that
just makes you not feel safe.
We're gonna go to this march for
gun violence in Washington,
D.C., and we're gonna take North
and, hopefully, it'll be
meaningful to her.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
♪ ♪
KYLIE: This is gonna be, kind
of, my first photo shoot, and
it's kind of hard and
discouraging.
KHLOE: I'm leaving L.A. and,
when I come back, I'm bringing
back a baby.
Here we come.
That's (bleep) crazy.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: When she makes
pasta... >> WOMAN: Uh-huh.
KOURTNEY: You boil the
water and you put salt all in
it. No olive oil.
WOMAN: Okay.
KOURTNEY: Then when you're
done... >> WOMAN: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: She has to stir
it while it's cooking.
WOMAN: Okay.
KOURTNEY: Every two minutes.
Stir it. Check it. Stir it.
When it's done, she has to make
sure there's no white on the
rim.
WOMAN: Okay.
KOURTNEY: But she can't
overcook it.
So she has to time it to what
the box says. >> WOMAN: Okay.
LARSA: You listening to her?
KIM: Write that all down or
tell her now before you forget.
LARSA: You're like a chef
these days.
Very meticulous about your
pasta. >> KIM: Yeah.
So, Kanye told me he was taking
North to school today, and he
was explaining to her, you know,
that we're gonna go to this
march for gun violence in
Washington, D.C., and we're
gonna take her and how, like,
he grew up and how dangerous the
neighborhood was in Chicago.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: Kanye is from Chicago,
and he always talks about the
gun violence.
And with everything that's going
on in the world, we just wanted
to do something and be a part of
something that we both really
believe in.
If we just speak up and get
things done, I think we can
change the world for the better.
LARSA: Wow.
KIM: Yeah.
Hopefully it'll be meaningful to
her. ♪ ♪
KHLOE: My sisters and I are
shooting a Calvin Klein
campaign.
And the fact that I am gonna be
the first visible pregnant
person shooting for Calvin Klein
is really major.
And this is actually my last day
that I'm allowed to travel.
So I can't miss my flight
tonight.
Or else I'm stuck in L.A., and I
have to have my baby in L.A.
MASON: Fat Amy.
(Khloe laughs)
Fat Amy's in there.
KOURTNEY: Hey, Khlo, come here.
I think you have... KHLOE: What?
KOURTNEY: A pee stain.
KHLOE: I do? I do.
MASON: Did your water broke?
Your water broke.
KOURTNEY: I'd rather tell you
in here than when you go out
there. KHLOE: Yeah. What do I do
about it?
SCOTT: How do you see that?
KOURTNEY: Let's get you a new
pair.
KIM: No, let's just blow-dry it.
KOURTNEY: No, you'll just see
it.
KHLOE: Why would I want to
wear pee-stained underwear?
Can't we just get a new pair?
We're at a Calvin Klein shoot.
I think they could afford it.
Don't tell them I peed in their
underwear.
SCOTT: It's just... it's...
MASON: KoKo peed in her
underwear!
SCOTT: ♪ KoKo peed in her
Underoos. ♪
MASON: Khloe peed in her
underwear!
SCOTT: Hee-haw! Hee-haw!
Marty, open that door.
KOURTNEY: Everyone outside...
everyone outside is laughing!
SCOTT: No. No! Let me see.
(laughter)
KHLOE: No, they're not.
(indistinct chatter)
(chuckling, chatter)
KOURTNEY: Kylie.
KHLOE: Let me see.
KYLIE: My body?
KHLOE: Yeah. >> KRIS: Wow!
KOURTNEY: Kylie, you look
amazing!
KHLOE: Kylie, you look amazing.
KYLIE: I'm still 158.
KHLOE: And your belly button
is back to normal!
KRIS: Me, too!
KHLOE: I'm 198 right now.
So if you want to (bleep) play
this game...
KOURTNEY: I am not kidding...
You look insane.
KHLOE: Kylie, your belly
button went back to normal.
That gives me so much...
KYLIE: It's just a little...
It's a little... it's, like,
different.
KHLOE: No, it looks great.
KYLIE: This is gonna be, kind
of, my first photo shoot after.
Stormi.
And doing, like, my first few
fittings and getting back into
it, it's kind of hard and
discouraging.
KHLOE: Kylie, your body looks
(bleep) crazy.
KYLIE: It just doesn't.
KOURTNEY: No, it does.
KIM: Kourt, Khloe, they're
waiting for us. ♪ ♪
KHLOE: This is my final
hurrah in California.
I'm ending it at a Calvin Klein
campaign with my sisters.
Not too shabby. ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I am really excited
for Khloe to finally experience
motherhood.
She's seen all of us go through
it, and it really changes you so
much.
KIM: We won't see her until
she has her little baby girl.
So, you know, it's, like,
obviously so fun that we get to
all spend this last day
together.
But I'm definitely gonna miss
her.
KHLOE: Give me a hug.
I'm not gonna see you.
KYLIE: That's crazy.
KHLOE: Don't worry, babe.
It's just a couple months.
You won't even know.
And then I'll bring back a baby.
And you'll come and bring.
Stormi. Don't cry.
Don't "cwy."
KYLIE: (clears throat) I am
gonna bring Stormi, you know
that.
I am gonna bring Stormi.
KHLOE: Yeah. Do whatever you
want. Whatever you want.
Um, we're in the middle of a
heartfelt moment.
I feel like you're sabotaging
it.
HAIRSTYLIST: Sorry.
(Khloe laughs)
KHLOE: Okay, I love you.
I'm leaving L.A. and, when I
come back, I'm bringing back a
baby.
That's (bleep) crazy.
But exciting.
But crazy. ♪ ♪
Here we come.
Everything's going well.
So I feel a lot better.
Sleepless nights, but
everything's working out. ♪ ♪
SCOTT: Looks like we are back
up and live.
For the longest time, I've
always wanted to go to Cleveland
to see where Khloe lives.
And I feel like now is the time
to bring the podcast back.
Looks like a bomb hit this
place. >> KHLOE: I like it here.
KIM: Are you ready to march
today?
NORTH: I'm ready.
KIM: I'm so sorry for your
loss. >> LORI: Thank you.
CAMERON KASKY: Look around.
We are the change.
KIM: I knew hearing these
kids speak was gonna be really
emotional, but I didn't know
that it was gonna be so
inspiring. (Cheering)
PHOTOGRAPHER: Gorgeous.
KIM: I definitely feel for.
Kylie.
My body changed so much during
my pregnancies.
So I know her struggle.
I know what she's going through.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: Khlo?
Khlo-ver. >> KHLOE: What?
SCOTT: You know, for the
longest time, I've always wanted
to go to Cleveland to see where
Khloe lives.
But I just didn't know if there
was really anything to do there.
KHLOE: Scott. >> SCOTT: Yes.
KHLOE: What the hell are we
gonna do together?
I've been bored.
All I do is sit and do nothing.
SCOTT: Podcast. KHLOE: Yes!
If we get back to our podcasting
ways.
SCOTT: (bleep) yeah.
Baby got pod.
SCOTT: A long time ago in the
Hamptons, Khloe and I had a.
The Lord and truthfully I
miss it. The Lord and His Lady.
KHLOE: And we're legit in a tub.
SCOTT: Uh, I have a life
jacket on just in case things
get, uh, tough in here.
We're coming to you from the
bay. >> KHLOE: From the bay.
SCOTT: In Long Island.
KHLOE: Uh-huh.
(Scott and Khloe screaming)
KHLOE: Oh, my gosh.
(Scott screams) >> SCOTT: Bitch!
(Khloe laughs)
SCOTT: You know, I feel like.
Khloe's probably pretty bored in
Cleveland, so I figure, now is
the time to bring the podcast
back.
Looks like we are back up and
live.
KHLOE (with British accent):
The Lord and The Lady.
Next, we're gonna take
Cleveland.
SCOTT: Oh, here's the 3rd
Street Deli I've heard about
that has an amazing pastrami
sandwich.
KHLOE: Corned beef and rye.
SCOTT: There you go, fella.
Looks like a bomb hit this
place.
(Khloe laughs)
And they forgot to clean up.
KHLOE: I like it here.
The Lord and the Lady are
officially back on the air.
Scott and I, no matter what, we
will always just jive.
We're two jive turkeys, and we
just get it together.
SCOTT: We're a jiving turkey.
(Khloe laughs)
When that pod comes out,
we just know how to cast.
KHLOE: We do.
SCOTT: Should we see if
anybody wants to be on our
podcast?
KHLOE: Oh, hi. How are you?
SCOTT: You want to be on our
podcast?
WOMAN: Okay.
SCOTT: How are you feeling
today? WOMAN: Good. How are you?
SCOTT: We're good.
How are you? What's your name?
TANISHA: Good. Tanisha.
KHLOE: Are you guys from.
Cleveland?
WOMAN: Yeah, we're from.
Cleveland.
SCOTT: Do you love it here?
WOMAN: Yeah, we do.
SCOTT: You would want to move
if you could?
TANISHA: Well, I'm from New.
York. >> SCOTT: There you go.
Where are you from in New York?
TANISHA: Uh, New Rochelle.
KHLOE: He's from New York.
SCOTT: I'm from New York as
well.
Would you move if somebody came
down and said, "Hey, we're
willing to move you for free to"
a nicer place"?
WOMAN: Uh... yeah.
SCOTT: Okay, thank you.
TANISHA: It's for free.
Hell yeah.
KHLOE: Who's gonna say no to
that? SCOTT: If somebody loved
where they were.
If somebody asked to move me
from New York City at the time
for free, I'd say no.
KHLOE: Oh, okay. SCOTT: Hello!
KHLOE: Hello. (All laughing)
♪ ♪
KIM: Are you ready to march
today?
NORTH: I'm ready.
KIM: Do you know what we're
marching for?
NORTH: For the families.
KIM: For the families, yeah.
And for all the kids in the
schools, for gun violence.
Kanye and I are at the March for.
Our Lives rally in Washington,
D.C.
These marches are happening all
across the country, and I really
have always advocated for better
gun laws and gun control, so I'm
really happy that we are
supporting and being a part of
something that's really
powerful.
I'm so glad we brought North.
DEMI LOVATO: Hi. How are you?
(indistinct chatter)
KIM: We get to hear her sing
today, boo. Demi's my favorite!
MILEY: What's up?
How are you? Good to see you.
Hi. What's up, honey?
DEMI: How are you?
MILEY: What's up?
(applause and cheering)
(applause swells)
CAMERON KASKY: My name is.
Cameron Kasky.
Welcome to the revolution!
(applause and cheering)
It is a powerful and peaceful
one of, by, and for the young
people of this country.
Since this movement began,
people have asked me, "Do you"
think any change is going to
come from this?"
Look around. We are the change!
(applause and cheering)
KIM: Hi. How are you?
It's so nice to meet you.
ILAN: I'm Ilan Alda.
My daughter was Alyssa.
KIM: I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
ILAN: Thanks for your
support, coming out here.
This is my wife, Lori.
KIM: Hi. How are you?
I'm so sorry for your loss.
LORI: Thank you.
(applause and cheering)
KIM: I can't even imagine,
you know, as a parent.
ILAN: That was my daughter.
KIM: Oh.
SPEAKER: Everyday shootings.
CROWD: Everyday shootings.
ILAN: And we're creating a
non-profit foundation, just
about making schools safe.
KIM: Yeah.
ILAN: So my kids, your kids,
all of these kids can go to
school and just be safe and be
kids.
KIM: Absolutely.
CROWD: Everyday shootings.
SPEAKER: Are everyday problems.
CROWD: Are everyday problems.
SPEAKER: We're tired of being
forced under the rug.
KIM: So they're telling a
story. >> NORTH: They are?
KIM: 'Cause their friends
maybe died, or their family
members died from guns.
NORTH: From guns?
KIM: Yeah. That's not okay.
That's why we're here, is to
tell everyone it's not okay to
kill people with guns, right?
NORTH: Right.
KIM: I knew hearing these
kids speak was gonna be hard and
really emotional, but I didn't
know that it was gonna be so
inspiring.
I think I finally feel like
there's a little bit of hope in
this world if kids like this are
our future, and I hope that.
North one day remembers that her
dad and I brought her here.
And I hope that she just
remembers that she was a part of
something positive that was
happening to change the world
for the better.
YOLANDA: My name is.
Yolanda Renee King,
granddaughter of Martin Luther.
King and Coretta Scott King.
(applause and cheering)
(Kim whoops)
My grandfather had a dream that
his four little children will
not be judged by the color of
their skin, but by the content
of their character.
I have a dream that enough is
enough!
(applause and cheering)
And that this should be a
gun-free world, period!
(applause and cheering)
Will you please repeat these
words after me?
Spread the word!
CROWD: Spread the word!
YOLANDA: Have you heard?!
CROWD: Have you heard?
YOLANDA: All across the nation.
CROWD: All across the nation.
YOLANDA: We. >> CROWD: We.
YOLANDA: Are going to be.
CROWD: Are going to be.
YOLANDA: A great generation.
CROWD: A great generation.
YOLANDA: Now give yourselves
a hand.
(applause and cheering)
SCOTT: Yo, I'm here today
learning CPR.
(whooping) >> KHLOE: Scott, shh.
This class I'm actually really
invested in, and Scott is not.
SCOTT: Bah! KHLOE: Oh, my God.
KIM: Today, I am meeting with
several kids from the March for.
Our Lives movement.
CAMERON: 17 people died at.
Stoneman Douglas, but 96 die
every single day.
KIM: So, what do people do
after the march to actually
help?
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Have you ever done
CPR? >> SAVAS: Yeah.
KHLOE: You have?
I've never done it.
SAVAS: You know you have to
break their bones and (bleep).
KHLOE: What? Break?
SAVAS: Yeah, in order to
perform it. I swear to God.
KHLOE: That's scary.
SCOTT: Getting ready for a
podcast.
KHLOE: I just think it's good
learning CPR for just life.
What is this? GoPro?
SCOTT: These are GoPros.
KHLOE: Yeah, but for what?
SCOTT: For the cast, so when
you're vibing, you're like, "Yo",
I'm here today, learning CPR in
a beanie."
KHLOE: But what's the
difference from this?
SCOTT: Now you have visual.
KHLOE: You're stepping it up.
SCOTT: I'm upping the game.
KHLOE: Okay.
(knocking)
SCOTT: Holy, we've got a.
CPR'er, people.
Come on in. I think I'm choking.
KHLOE: Tristan is on the
road, but I am so excited to
take the CPR class with Scott.
I really want to learn this
information.
If, God forbid, anything happens
to anybody, this is actually a
class that could be useful for
our futures.
SCOTT: It's definitely pod
worthy. Hi. How are you?
LORI: I'm Lori.
Nice to meet you.
My son Shane, daughter Chloe.
SCOTT: With a "C"?
CHLOE: Yeah, with a "C."
LORI: With a "C."
We're not as unique as that
Khloe.
WOMAN: You have a plug nearby
that I can...?
SCOTT: Somebody plugged it in
here, if you know what I'm
talking about.
KHLOE: Oh, be quiet.
SCOTT: Got a little baby
popping. (Whooping)
KHLOE: Scott, shh!
LORI: Well, this is gonna be
fun, I can see that.
SCOTT: You ain't kidding.
Look at all those beautiful
kids.
You got a mixed baby in there?
LORI: They look kind of
mixed.
SCOTT: Look at the package
on this one. >> KHLOE: Scott!
LORI: Once the baby is a year
old...
KHLOE: Shh.
LORI: It changes to child.
KHLOE: Okay.
LORI: And from eight up, it's
an adult.
SCOTT: My son's an adult!
KHLOE: Don't be a distraction.
LORI: You come across your
baby, and it looks like
something's wrong.
You have to check for a
response. >> SCOTT: Huh. Bah!
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
LORI: If the baby is not
breathing, and there is no
response, you start compressions
immediately. Okay. Um...
KHLOE: You're draining.
Like, honestly, I'm exhausted.
(sighs)
I will apologize for Scott.
SCOTT: Please don't.
KHLOE: Okay.
I love Scott, and I love hanging
out with him, but I really want
to learn how to give a baby CPR.
Like, this class I'm actually
really invested in, and Scott is
not, and he's hamming it up for
the podcast, probably more than
usual, but it's (bleep) annoying
right now. >> SCOTT: Baby.
LORI: You're gonna seal your
mouth around the baby's mouth
and nose and blow.
Way too much, Scott.
SCOTT: I got him, though.
LORI: Back off on that.
SCOTT: He's back. ♪ ♪
KIM: Hello. >> JACLYN: Hi.
JAMMAL: Nice to meet you.
KIM: Hey, nice to meet you.
ARIEYANNA: Arieyanna.
KIM: Hi. Nice to meet you.
ARIEYANNA: Nice to meet you.
KIM: Today I am meeting with
several kids from the March for
Our Lives movement.
After going to the march, I was
super inspired, and I just want
to meet them and see how they're
getting the word out, because
if there's any way that I can
help out, I would love to.
I appreciate what you guys are
doing.
And I always see people tweet
about something they feel
passionate about or something
that they feel like is wrong in
the system, but then nothing
really happens.
So, what do people do after the
march, or, like, what do they do
to actually help? You know?
JACLYN: Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Marches just spread awareness,
and people need to learn,
actually, how to activate that.
JAMMAL: Parkland was, like,
an anomaly in a case where...
of how fast people mobilized and
how fast, like, it gained
national attention, and, then,
there's communities every day
who just don't have that voice.
KIM: Yeah. I mean, Kanye
would talk about Chicago all the
time and how he grew up, and I
just am like, "This is crazy."
Like, this can't be."
ARIEYANNA: Being from, like,
the ghetto or, like, the West
Side of Chicago, and you don't
really... even if you're living
in it, you don't really truly
understand it till you see it.
Like, I always hear the
gunshots, but it didn't become,
like, really real to me until
I was walking down the street
trying to go to the store, and I
saw yellow tape and blood on
the sidewalk.
♪ ♪
JAMMAL: It's different when
you go up to someone and it's
like, "I've lived through this,
like, I've lost friends, I've"
"lost family to gun violence," so
it's, like, taking, I guess, our
experiences, like, to their
front doorstep and letting them
know that, like, communities
like Chicago, Baltimore, L.A.,
like, they face this every day.
CAMERON: 17 people died at.
Stoneman Douglas, but 96 die
every single day, and we don't
talk about that. >> KIM: Mm.
It's just, it really, really
sucks to live in a world where
it's just, there are so many
shootings, like, every day.
CAMERON: 97% of people want
universal background checks.
Like, for you to buy a gun,
they'd need a background check.
Over 80% of the NRA membership
wants that, but they block it
every year. >> JAMMAL: Yeah.
JACLYN: Mm-hmm.
CAMERON: Like, you can't get
97% of people to agree on
anything, right?
KIM: Yeah.
CAMERON: Like, literally
anything, but we agree on that.
KIM: I one billion percent
believe that we need stricter
gun laws.
We need background checks.
You shouldn't be able to walk
into a store and buy a gun.
And to hear that the kids have
met with people numerous times
and nothing's been done is
just so sad.
So, realistically, is there
anything, or is that cycle just
gonna always be there?
Like, what would it take?
JAMMAL: It's about, we have
to start choosing people who
represent us and elect them into
office.
KIM: You mean people with
some morals?
CAMERON AND JAMMAL: Exactly.
JACLYN: This is the only
place in the world with this
raging epidemic.
Clearly, it's preventable.
People in between the ages of 18
and 29, if they all got out
there and voted, they would make
the decision that election.
CAMERON: What we're trying to
do is to make voting more
ingrained in pop culture, more
ingrained in its being cool.
KIM: I still don't know
(bleep) about voting.
I literally only know the
president election every four
years, and that's it.
JAMMAL: Yeah.
KIM: So when people say,
like, "Get out and vote," like,
what is there to vote on?
CAMERON: Every two years, we
have the opportunity to
completely reshape the House of
Representatives and a lot of
the Senate, and so, this
November 6, there is going to
be an election in America that
can solve gun violence.
KIM: Kanye always says he
wants to have more kids, and I
was like, "I just can't."
Like, there's... our world
is so (bleep) up, and then we
were there, I was like, wait a
minute, I feel like the whole
next generation is so together
and is gonna change the world,
and, like, we can have another
one. We'll figure it out.
(laughter)
But I was so inspired, and I
just, I felt like...
it was so...
just powerful.
Like, it literally gave me hope.
Seeing these kids taking up
their time to talk about issues
that are so important, I think,
is just so selfless and so great
of them.
I honestly feel like there's so
many adults out there that can
learn a thing or two from these
kids. JACLYN: Your vote is your
voice. And your power.
KIM: Oh, totally, I'm voting
in this...
(laughter)
No, I'm voting this...
I'll make my entire family vote.
Thank you guys so much.
CAMERON: You're in this fight
with us, so...
JACLYN: Thank you.
SCOTT: Khlo, let's cast!
KHLOE: I'm so tired.
Can we do this later?
SCOTT: Do you really want to
bring a child into this world
with this kind of energy?
KHLOE: No! And that's why I
need to take a nap.
SCOTT: Podcasters, this is
what it's like dealing with a
pregnant woman.
KHLOE: Don't make me throw
this at your face and chip your
tooth. >> KYLIE: Say no to that.
Nothing in my closet fits me.
I feel like my hips have just
spread. >> KIM: Curves are hard.
KYLIE: Some people, they're
just body shamers.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: You put the baby all
the way up here? So far?
WOMAN: You'll work off that
baby weight just coming up...
SCOTT: This is adorable.
KHLOE: Isn't it cute?
SCOTT: Oh, my God, this
baby is gonna come into a very
nice place. I love it.
It feels super, super cozy and
warm.
I could live in here.
KHLOE: It's like a peaceful
pink cloud.
SCOTT: To me, it looks like a
sweet, tender, loving of
peach cream ice cream pie.
KHLOE: Well, it's pink.
SCOTT: Oh.
KHLOE: Is it not pink to you?
There's a pinkish hue.
SCOTT: (bleep) hue.
(Khloe laughs)
KHLOE: That was a good one.
Have you been down to my room?
SCOTT: Mm-mm.
KHLOE: Do you want to go
check that out?
SCOTT: (bleep) yeah, I do.
We've definitely been getting
our pod on, and in my eyes, it
should keep going and going and
going and going.
There's other stuff to catch.
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
SCOTT: So, some thoughts here.
KHLOE (groans): Hold up, let
me lay here and you just tell
me. >> SCOTT: Okay, so. Let's go
over this.
First of all, the vents being
painted different colors as the
walls and then the lights,
I mean, it's crazy.
Fan, by the way, is horrific.
KHLOE (laughs): Tristan's
gonna love this.
SCOTT: Having a television on
a wood stand, also crazy when
you have all these beautiful
windows.
KHLOE: So, where would you
put the TV?
SCOTT: Projector over the top
with a hidden box, then sync a
screen into here, 12-foot
projector, HD 4K.
KHLOE: No, you're lying.
You're just listing out letters.
SCOTT: Swear. I have it in my
bedroom.
(Khloe laughs)
Honestly, it's not so bad.
You just need new furniture,
new paint, new floors and a new
bed. (Khloe laughs)
KHLOE: I think I'm gonna,
like, gonna go into early labor
because of you.
Honestly, when I'm around you,
I'm telling you, I am
hysterically laughing, but I'm
afraid my water's gonna break.
SCOTT: So, is this a nice way
of telling me to get the hell
out?
(both laugh)
KHLOE: You're kind of at risk
for my baby.
SCOTT: You're making me laugh
so hard, but get the (bleep)
out of here.
KHLOE: You might have to
leave, 'cause I really gotta go
to sleep.
I am nine months' pregnant, and
I am just exhausted.
So being around Scott, it seems
a lot more challenging on my
soul.
SCOTT: You realize I've been
around pregnant women before.
KHLOE: And you realize I have
the best energy and personality
than any pregnant woman you've
been around.
SCOTT: Or just in general,
but yeah.
KHLOE: Yeah. Kourtney was,
"I'm pregnant, and I'm not doing
this, this and this."
She was very limited.
SCOTT: That's her unpregnant.
KHLOE: Yeah. Very hormonal.
SCOTT: Eh. I didn't really
talk to her much.
It was probably the better
times.
(laughing)
Have you felt this thing?
KOURTNEY: What about that
other plant?
SCOTT: This (bleep) is, like,
real heavy.
KOURTNEY: That means you
got to start going to the gym.
(Scott grunts) ♪ ♪
KYLIE: Say no to that.
KIM: Ky. Hey, don't be scared.
KYLIE: We're getting rid of
everything.
KIM: Why?
KYLIE: All the old stuff that
just...
KIM: Is there anything fun?
I feel like I might find some
gems in here.
KYLIE: Like, nothing in my
closet fits me.
KIM: You're looking, like,
really skinny.
KYLIE: Thank you.
I'm getting rid of stuff that
I just feel like is never gonna
fit me, like, I know I'm not
gonna fit into, like, a 25 jean
ever again.
And after the shoot, I'm just
feeling a little insecure.
I feel like my hips have just
spread for life.
KIM: To the point of no return.
KYLIE: Yeah. Like, my
favorite jeans, they're never
gonna fit me again.
KIM: I know. Curves are hard.
It's just figuring it out.
KYLIE: I feel like some
people don't get it.
Like, some people are like,
"Oh, my God," just body shamers.
KIM: Trust me, I get it, but
the pressure to snap back, like,
it took me a good six to eight
months.
Once I got there, I was like,
okay, I'm never leaving.
I think this should go in the
yes pile. >> KYLIE: Okay.
KIM: I will tell you this.
Double Spanx it up and get out
of the house.
Like, you just have to do that.
KYLIE: I know. I never...
I never cared for Spanx.
Like, I never... (Kim gasps)
Now I get it.
KIM: Yeah, I literally would
wear, sometimes, I'm not joking
you, three pairs of Spanx.
KYLIE: Yeah.
KIM: Just to get out of the
house.
And I know it's, like, really
early and Stormi's so little,
but, like, you just have to roll
with it, you know?
You just have to, like, be
confident, get some things that
make you feel good about
yourself, and find your balance.
KYLIE: No, I agree. Thanks.
KIM: Word from the wise.
KYLIE: Honestly, you do
inspire me a lot.
If Kim can do it, I could do it.
KIM: (laughs) K, let's go
play basketball.
KYLIE: Okay.
KIM: You'll go crazy if you
sit up here all day.
KYLIE: I would love to beat
you in basketball.
KIM: I definitely feel for.
Kylie.
I mean, I gained so much weight.
My body changed so much during
my pregnancies.
So I know her struggle.
I know what she's going through.
But honestly she looks so
amazing and she just has such a
good sense of style, she'll
figure out a way to start
dressing herself and adapt to
her new body.
♪ ♪
Ready? Go.
Why aren't I getting any?
I never play basketball.
KYLIE: Ah! (Laughs)
KIM: Dude... I suck. ♪ ♪
SCOTT: Khlo! >> KHLOE: What?
SCOTT: Khlo, let's cast.
Here she is, coming down.
Khloe K.
KHLOE: What are you doing?
SCOTT: We're about to cast.
KHLOE: Right now?
SCOTT: I mean, time's
a-ticking.
Sun's almost down and I want you
to be able to get a good night's
rest.
I'm leaving town tomorrow.
KHLOE: I was in bed, just
relaxing. I'm so tired.
SCOTT: Tell your listeners
how tired you are.
Sit down.
KHLOE: Can we do this later?
SCOTT: You don't seem tired.
KHLOE: Scott, seriously?
I'm so exhausted and wiped out
and I don't know why you just
won't let the pod breathe for a
minute.
SCOTT: Listen, you can
breathe on your own time.
I'm here and I'm here to pod.
Luckily, you don't have much
longer, Khlo.
A couple more weeks and that
baby will be in the streets.
KHLOE: Okay, so what...
SCOTT: But let's talk baby
names before we're done.
KHLOE: Okay.
SCOTT: How involved is T-Dog,
Tristan, the melting pot, on the
name process?
KHLOE: But, you know...
SCOTT: I don't know.
KHLOE: The words aren't
coming out.
He's actually really involved.
SCOTT: That's nice.
KHLOE: Yes.
SCOTT: That's very nice.
KHLOE: Scott, can we just do
this a little later?
SCOTT: So let's get serious.
I do want you to get your bed
rest, but we started this pod
and I don't want to ruin it.
How about you give me a solid 14
minutes of good energy and you
go take a 14-hour nap?
KHLOE: Scott.
SCOTT: 12 minutes.
KHLOE: I don't have good
energy.
SCOTT: Do you really want to
bring a child into this world
with this kind of energy?
KHLOE: No, and that's why I
need to take a nap.
SCOTT: Oh!
KHLOE: And if you would let
me take a nap, there would be
much better energy, but you're
not letting me take a nap, and
I'm at my wit's end, and...
SCOTT: Podcasters, this is
what it's like dealing with a
pregnant woman.
Get ready, people. (Laughs)
KHLOE: Don't make me throw
this at your face and chip your
tooth.
SCOTT: I don't want a chipped
KHLOE: Stop talking in the
(bleep) mic, it's so stupid
at this point.
SCOTT: Why do you keep
putting the mic up, then?
KHLOE: 'Cause I'm (bleep)
used to it, 'cause that's what
you had me doing.
SCOTT: And so am I.
KHLOE: You know what, if I
had the energy to storm out of
here, then I would have five
minutes ago.
SCOTT: You can't storm
because you're too big to swim.
KHLOE: But I have the energy
to waddle my fat ass out of
here, so that's about to happen.
SCOTT: Ladies and gentlemen.
KHLOE: You're so (bleep)
annoying.
SCOTT: The Khlo-ster is out.
KHLOE: This was supposed to
be fun; It's not fun.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: Khlo-ver. KHLOE: Yeah?
SCOTT: I'm in a chill mood.
I come bearing gifts.
I want to apologize for getting
a little too crazy and getting
you too anxious.
KHLOE: Thank you, Scott.
SCOTT: I kinda just felt like
we did our podcast in the.
Hamptons. >> KHLOE: Right.
SCOTT: So it sounded fun,
like it would give us something
to do in Cleveland, but now I've
come to terms that not only is
it annoying, it's
semi-worthless.
I thought you were bored, but I
see that you probably just need
some time to relax.
KHLOE: I mean, honestly,
the first day I had a ball.
I was just so tired.
And, like, instead of being
chill about it, you're like,
come on, we gotta get this, we
gotta hit this.
And I'm like, what? What?
Who are we really recording for?
SCOTT: I'm not sure.
I don't know.
I came here to see you 'cause
I love you and I'm sorry.
KHLOE: Thank you, Scott.
SCOTT: It was fun while it
lasted. >> KHLOE: Uh-huh.
(Scott laughs)
There were significant
memories made here, and I'm
very grateful.
SCOTT: This wasn't the most
perfect visit, but I feel like
you're still gonna miss me and
want me back once you're back in
action.
KHLOE: Scott, I miss you just
thinking about this.
SCOTT: Thank you.
KHLOE: I miss you right now
and I'm right next to you.
SCOTT: I know the feeling.
I'm right there with you.
I got you a little something.
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
SCOTT: Because that's all I
can do now.
KHLOE: Oh, my goodness.
SCOTT: A nice little pic for
you to have.
KHLOE: Oh, Goobercy.
SCOTT: Little Goobercy.
KHLOE: Oh, Goober. (Kiss)
This is a very sad photo.
This was the day she died.
This was at the hospital, when I
was, like, putting her down.
(laughs)
I love the idea. I love...
SCOTT: I can't believe it.
KHLOE: That you thought
about me.
You got me a frame and you
printed out a photo of me and
Gabbana, I love that.
I'm just gonna switch the
timeline of the picture.
SCOTT: Aw...
KHLOE: Only because it's a
little too raw for me.
SCOTT: I had no idea.
KHLOE: Yeah, that was my last
good-bye.
Seriously.
SCOTT: Wow. I don't know what
I was thinking.
Kris was like, the black and
white looks more serious.
KHLOE: It was very serious.
SCOTT: Yeah. I am killing it
out here in Cleveland.
KHLOE (laughing): Yeah.
SCOTT: This is not my town.
All right, I'm gonna get back to
L.A.
I love you, Khlo-verfield.
I'll be back for the delivery,
don't worry. KHLOE: Oh, my God.
SCOTT: Okay, love you, call
me if you need anything.
KHLOE: Love you. Thank you.
♪ ♪
KIM: Are you so excited?
KYLIE: I'm actually kind of
nervous.
KIM: Oh, you'll be fine.
I was thinking, like, to do a
full, like, '90s thing, but.
Kendall, like, shot me down and
said that was so lame.
Kylie and I have a collab
coming out soon for Kylie.
Cosmetics, so we have our
campaign photo shoot together.
And I hope this will get Kylie,
like, back into her, like,
mindset of just feeling sexy
again.
Kylie is a beautiful, amazing
mom, and I just want her to feel
confident in that.
'Cause she really does look so
good. ♪ ♪
(photographer speaking
indistinctly)
PHOTOGRAPHER: Wow. ♪ ♪
Gorgeous. ♪ ♪
KIM: Mario, are they good?
MARIO: Huh, yeah.
KYLIE: Yeah, these are cute.
The photos turned out so
amazing, and at the end of the
day, I'm not gonna let me
feeling a little insecure about
my new body get in the way of
how confident I really do feel.
I just feel way more powerful
than I ever have and also now
I have a little girl looking up
to me.
So I want to be the best person
that I can be.
Come on... I need you.
What T-shirts?
KIM: We'll put on two white
tees. >> KYLIE: Yeah.
♪ ♪
PHOTOGRAPHER: Wow. So beautiful.
Gorgeous. The water looks cool.
KYLIE: Oh, these are really
good.
KIM: Oh, good.
KYLIE: It's everything.
Keeping Up with the Kardashians.
SCOTT: You excited?
KENDALL: I don't know.
SCOTT: Today is the day that
we are going to jump out of a
perfectly good airplane.
There's no turning back now.
(phone chimes) (Kendall gasps)
What's the problem?
Stop. >> KIM: Hey.
KRIS: What the (bleep) is that?
KIM: She's literally gonna go
into labor over this.
KRIS: We should've come last
night; I knew it.
(bleep) Captioning sponsored by.
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS