♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Do you want to just
take photos, or do we want to
work out?
LARSA: We're gonna box, then
we're gonna take good photos.
TRAINER: Okay, okay.
Minor injuries, you guys are
good?
No bad knees, shoulders?
KOURTNEY: I have a bad
shoulder, a bad knee and a bad
ankle.
KIM: I just have a bad attitude.
KOURTNEY: I swear.
LARSA: You're in the right
place. KOURTNEY: I had a crazy
workout on Saturday, and it...
TRAINER: Okay, so if there's
just certain things that you
can't do, feel free to just
switch off on your own, just try
not to hurt yourself.
KIM: Wait, Kylie should be here.
The Met is in one week, and she
hasn't worked out once.
KOURTNEY: She's 20 years old.
KIM: Once a year, there's the.
Met Ball.
You know, it's a really big deal
to be invited, it's an honor.
And that's something that I
really look forward to
attending.
KOURTNEY: We are making it
known today that late 30s/40s
is the new 18/21. ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I'm gonna decide
about the pool table stuff.
I just, honestly, don't use it.
KIM: You never use it.
KOURTNEY: But I, like, kind
of like having it.
Like, what else would I put
there, you know?
KIM: So, you know Alice
Johnson, the lady that I've been
trying to get out of jail?
KOURTNEY: Okay. I didn't know
her name.
KIM: It was her first time
offense that was non-violent,
and she got life in prison
without the possibility of
parole, which was really crazy.
KOURTNEY: How long has she
been there?
KIM: 21 years.
Six months ago, I stumbled
across a story of Alice Marie
Johnson.
ALICE: My name is Alice
Marie Johnson.
I'm a 62-year-old mother,
grandmother and
great-grandmother.
In less than two weeks, this.
October 31, will mark my 21st
year of confinement in federal
prison.
KIM: I first started with
retweeting the story, and I just
kept on watching it over and
just feeling how unfair this is
and hoping that I could reach
out and make a difference.
You know, she's, like,
definitely served her time.
She didn't kill anyone.
This is, like, a non-violent
offense, your first time, and
you get life without the
possibility of parole?
Like, that's just not fair.
We all make mistakes.
We all (bleep) up.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: And everyone else that
was actually dealing the drugs
pleaded guilty, went in jail for
a few years and got out.
So she pleaded not guilty and
got found guilty.
So everyone else is living their
life out of jail.
KOURTNEY: And you're trying
to get her out?
KIM: Yeah, but the only
person that can grant her
clemency, which means to, like,
forgive her punishment, you
know... >> KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KIM: And get her out of
prison would be the president.
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KIM: My first phone call was
to Ivanka.
I just felt like as a woman, she
would really feel for this woman
the way that I connected with.
Alice.
And she did, and she connected
me with her husband Jared.
So, I actually have a meeting
with the president of the United
States next week to discuss.
Alice Johnson.
It's just tricky because, like,
they've asked me to go and talk
to Trump about why Alice should
get out.
And I've been so straightforward
with Jared that, you know, I
have different views,
I was at Hillary fundraisers.
So, you know, this might not be,
like, a popular opinion, but
I'll talk to whoever I need to
talk to in order to get the job
done.
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KIM: But I'm excited to go to
the White House, I'm not gonna
lie.
I just want to go and see where
JFK and Jackie slept.
I just want to touch one thing
of Jackie's.
(chuckles) ♪ ♪
KHLOE: Oh, you're feeding the
baby.
TRISTAN: Look at-look at Mommy.
Look at Mommy.
KHLOE: "Hi, Mama."
How is she doing? TRISTAN: Good.
We just started. >> KHLOE: Aw...
"Hi, Mama." I miss you.
TRISTAN: "I miss you, too,
Mommy."
KHLOE: What did you dress her
in? TRISTAN: She's got a little
morning gown on.
KHLOE (chuckles): Oh, wow.
This is my very first day back
at work, um, ever since being on
maternity leave.
Okay, well, thank you for being
such a good dad with her.
TRISTAN: All righty.
KHLOE: Okay, babe, I'll check
on you in a little bit.
TRISTAN: All right.
KHLOE: Okay, bye.
Good American is definitely one
of my other babies, but it's
crazy 'cause all I can do is
think about True and wanting to
be with her, and "what am I
missing?" and just everything.
I really hate that I'm not home.
You both are coming to the trip?
ANDREW: We're just going in,
flying in to New York and then
we're flying into Seattle?
KHLOE: I think so.
We are launching Good American
activewear in New York, in.
Seattle, but I have a ton of
anxiety thinking about spending
a night away from True.
I know she's gonna be at home
with her dad and in the best
place possible.
She's just not with me.
How cute is this?
It's how I monitor the baby.
(laughs)
I'm spying.
MODEL: That's dangerous.
I want that (bleep).
KHLOE: Yeah, but I feel bad.
WOMAN: Does he know you can
watch?
KHLOE: Mm...
MODEL: (laughs) That'll be a
"no" then?
HAIRSTYLIST: That'll be a
"no." >> KHLOE: Well...
MODEL: Whoo!
♪ ♪
KIM: Kourt?
KOURTNEY: I'm in the closet.
KIM: Hi.
KOURTNEY: Wait, I thought you
were on a plane, 'cause I
thought you were going to meet...
Going to Washington, D.C.
KIM: I know, I was supposed
to, and then it got canceled.
KOURTNEY: What got canceled?
KIM: Last minute, my meeting
with Trump.
KOURTNEY: Oh. On their end?
KIM: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: Okay.
KIM: So it's been, like, just
literally, I was, like, ready to
go, plane ready, attorneys
ready.
When I came on board trying to
help Alice grant clemency for
herself, she had a team of
attorneys that have been helping
her for, you know, a decade.
You know, the whole team really
worked hard on getting letters
from senators and politicians.
We got the help of the
prosecutor, and there was
misinformation in her file that
wasn't even true about her case,
and so we had to correct all of
that.
So there was so many different
hurdles, and now the meeting
gets canceled because we need a
little bit more support.
SHAWN: Okay, so I had a
conference call this morning
with the team.
They are saying that they want a
thousand letters.
KIM: A thousand letters?
SHAWN: Yeah.
And we already submitted a bunch
of letters.
So I guess the question for
Jared is: How many letters do we
really need, and where would
these letters need to come from?
KIM: Okay. Got it.
Things keep moving and changing,
and it's all really frustrating.
But I definitely don't want to
let Alice down, so it just
pushes me even more to want to
fight for her.
All right, I'm gonna e-mail.
Jared now.
"Who... how many letters,
realistically, and who from?"
SHAWN: And don't forget to
remind him about all the letters
that we sent already.
KIM: Totally. Okay, bye.
SHAWN: Okay, bye.
KOURTNEY: Penelope was... has
a question.
KIM: Okay.
KOURTNEY: She wants to know
if she can go with you to pick
up North from school.
KIM: Yeah, but I don't have
another car seat.
Can they put one of her car
seats in my car?
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: Oh, perfect.
♪ ♪
(ringtone playing)
Hold on, sorry.
It's really important.
Hey, babe.
Just in the middle of
interviews.
What?
I didn't know you were going.
You told me you weren't going,
so you said it wasn't happening,
and then you called me and said,
"I'm here. Bye."
And I tried calling you, and you
didn't have your phone on.
You weren't answering, so...
Okay. Bye.
Right now.
KRIS: So, I'm going to do
today, and of
course something always happens.
So, Kim and Kanye called me.
COREY: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: And they said I just
can't be the person talking
about Kanye, so Kanye and Kim
called me and said, "Listen, you
got to cancel Ellen."
I said, "Well, I wouldn't do
that."
I'm not gonna cancel Ellen."
And they said, "Well, you're
just not the person who's
qualified to talk about Kanye."
Like, "You'll just make it
worse."
I just want to make everything
better, you know me.
I want everybody to get along,
I want everybody to be happy.
I want everybody to understand
one another.
Communicate.
Even though Kanye went on TMZ
this morning and made some
controversial comments, you
know, my loyalty really lies
with Kanye.
COREY: Babe, I thought this
would help ease your tension a
little bit.
KRIS: Aw, thank you, babe.
I just can't control everybody.
COREY: Yeah.
KRIS: Thanks, babe.
COREY: I'll be right there
next to you, though.
You'll be all right.
KRIS: It's really my job to
be there to support Kanye and be
somebody that's in his life that
offers him love and support,
and not criticism.
ELLEN: We're gonna get this
out of the way, 'cause I think
people are-are tuning in, and
they are thinking you're gonna
just... that we're gonna talk
about Kanye the whole time, and
we're not.
KRIS: Kanye always does
things with really good
intentions.
So I'm gonna let him explain
himself.
ELLEN: Okay.
KRIS: I just keep rolling on.
Trying to keep up.
ELLEN: Yeah, with the.
Kardashians.
KRIS: With the Kardashians.
ELLEN: Yeah. (Cheers, applause)
KIM: I'm in New York for the
Met, and there's so much going
on with Alice's case and Kanye,
but I am so excited to be here.
JONATHAN: Um, how's Kanye doing?
KIM: When he gets ramped up,
he can't control what he says.
JONATHAN: He can't let it go.
KIM: He's like, "Yeah, I say"
crazy (bleep), but I've always
said crazy (bleep).
But that's why I'm Kanye."
JONATHAN: Kanye. Right.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Hey, guys! (True fusses)
KRIS: Hi! Oh! Guess who I get?
Oh, little missy. KHLOE: Uh-oh.
KRIS: Hey, Mase.
Are you excited about the trip?
KHLOE: I am really... I have a
lot of, like, anxiety about
being away from her for this
long.
KRIS: Yeah. (True cries)
KHLOE: Aw, she's tired.
I know, Mama. It's time.
KRIS: I feel bad that Khloe's
a little bit stressed out right
now; She's a new mom.
She's just figuring out
motherhood.
It's hard leaving your first
baby, so it's gonna take a
little bit of creativity to keep
her mind off of what she's left
behind at home and on her Good.
American launch.
KHLOE: I love you guys.
I'm gonna go put her down for a
nap and hang out with her.
KRIS: Somebody's getting tired.
COREY: Call if you need
anything.
KHLOE: Thank you.
Say, "Bye, Mama."
♪ ♪
KIM: Ooh, fancy.
JONATHAN: Did they send this?
KIM: Oh, my God!
Look at those pillows!
Oh, my God, I have to use this
on my bed for the trip.
JONATHAN: 100%. For the vibe.
KIM: I'm in New York for the.
Met, and, you know, there's so
much going on with Alice's case
and Kanye, but here is what I've
realized: I'm always gonna be
me, so I could be, you know,
getting ready for this big
fashion event, doing a new
shoot, doing whatever I...
And still making calls to the
White House, like, that's just
me, it's who I am, and it is
what it is.
JONATHAN: I love it!
It looks so...
KIM: "I can't wait to see
you, Donatella."
JONATHAN: That's the note
we've been waiting for.
Um, how's Kanye doing?
KIM: He's doing good.
Everyone thinks he's, like,
having a breakdown or, like...
SIMON: Because of the TMZ thing?
KIM: And just because of his
tweets.
JONATHAN: Well, TMZ was wild.
KIM: When I saw the clip, I
was like, okay, I rushed home.
I was hysterically crying.
So I go home...
he's totally fine.
The thing is, when he gets
ramped up...
JONATHAN: He has to do it.
KIM: He can't control what he
says.
JONATHAN: He can't let it go.
He can't let it go.
KIM: But he loves being
ramped up.
He's like, "I feel powerful when"
I'm ramped up, like, I don't
want to be, like, so suppressed.
Like, yeah, I say crazy (bleep),
but I've always said crazy
"(bleep).
But that's why I'm Kanye."
JONATHAN: Kanye. Right.
KIM: You know, I-I always
know what Kanye's intentions are
and what he's trying to say, but
I also know that they're gonna
write a headline, and people are
gonna assume that that's exactly
what you meant, you know.
But all the headlines just
took...
PRODUCER: They take the sound
bite and do whatever.
KIM: Yeah, that, as a wife,
is really frustrating to see the
media take everything and run
with it.
JONATHAN: Should we pop the
champagne?
Do you even drink champagne
anymore, ever?
Kim, did you ever drink
champagne?
SIMON: Kim, are you a
champagne drinker?
KIM: I hate champagne.
JONATHAN: So do I.
People love it. >> KIM: Hate it.
SIMON: Too much sugar.
I actually stopped drinking
everything for nine months.
JONATHAN: What do you mean by
"everything"?
SIMON: So no sugar, no pot,
no drinking.
KIM: So I'll just...
SIMON: Yeah, die. Yeah.
(Kim laughs)
♪ ♪
(crowd screaming)
KHLOE: My Good American
launch, we're starting in Times
Square of New York City, and I
took a red-eye, and I'm gonna be
here less than the amount of
time it took me to fly to New
York.
EMMA: Good morning, my gorgeous!
How amazing did it look outside?
KHLOE: So (bleep) good.
EMMA: There's so many people
out there.
They were camping out from last
night... I'm dying.
KHLOE: I'm so excited.
It's lovely.
Hi, how are you?
WOMAN: Two amazing women,
cofounders of this beautiful
collection: Khloe Kardashian and.
Emma Grede. (Crowd cheering)
KHLOE: Hi!
Good morning, New York City.
WOMAN: First of all, you guys
look amazing.
EMMA: Thank you.
KHLOE: Thank you.
WOMAN: Second of all, I have
a confession.
We're all actually here to talk
about baby True.
KHLOE: Yes. Yay! EMMA: Me, too.
KHLOE: I wish she was... I
wish you were surprising me with
her coming out, 'cause it was my
first time ever not sleeping,
like, with her last night.
WOMAN: Really? Oh!
That's so sweet. KHLOE: I know.
I know this Good American launch
is such a huge thing for my
company and for myself, and it's
a positive thing, but all I'm
thinking about is True.
Is she okay?
How did she sleep last night?
And so... I just feel very
anxious.
(crowd clamoring)
KRIS: This is the fun part.
Ah! (Laughs)
KIM: Hi.
KYLIE: You look gorgeous.
KIM: Oh, thank you.
(crowd screaming)
(knock on door) >> KHLOE: Oh.
Hello? Oh, my God!
KIM: I am so excited to be in
Wyoming for Kanye's listening
party.
It was all such a last-minute
thing. >> CHRIS ROCK: The world
premiere of the one and only
Kanye West.
(crowd cheering)
♪ ♪
KIM: Okay, one hour, guys.
(ringtone playing)
Oh, my God, Jared Kushner's
calling me.
Hello? Good, how are you?
(gasps)
(mouthing) Okay. Amazing.
So the White House has agreed
to set up a meeting, and that
makes me so happy because I just
know that explaining what Alice
has been through, I feel like,
how could you not feel for her
and see her, like, pure soul and
have sympathy for her?
All right, I'll talk to you
then.
Thank you. All right, perfect.
Have a good night. Bye.
PRODUCER: This is so
exciting! >> KIM: I know.
I don't want to get too excited.
PRODUCER: I know, I know.
KIM: But I feel like it's
gonna happen.
PRODUCER: Yeah, it sounded
very promising.
KIM: Ten minute warning.
PRODUCER: Guys, we really
have to be in the car; Should we
just finish the rest in the car?
STYLIST: Yeah, I'm done, I'm
done.
PRODUCER: On the way there.
(ringtone playing)
KIM: Hello?
KYLIE: It's so crazy here,
actually, there's just a lot of
people outside.
(crowd cheering)
ALEXANDER WANG: Do you have
also, the one with the stone on
the leg?
Wow, the black is everything!
STYLIST: You want to see how
the other one looks as well?
KYLIE: We can do it.
STYLIST: Love it.
ALEXANDER WANG: Yeah, I
agree.
KYLIE: Also, my stomach is
like... so hungry. (Laughter)
(overlapping chatter) KYLIE: Oh.
That's pretty, too. So good.
This is my favorite look,
by the way.
(laughter) ♪ ♪
MAN: Beautiful.
KRIS: This is the fun part.
Ah! (Laughs)
It's when I can't talk anymore
for the rest of the night.
KENDALL: Oh, my God, my mom
is so cute.
MAKEUP ARTIST: Oh, God!
She's so cute.
CREW: Should we call the
elevator?
KIM: Yep. >> CREW: You good?
KIM: Yep. Hi.
KYLIE: You look gorgeous.
KIM: Oh, thank you.
(crowd screaming)
My mom looks beautiful. Cutie.
Her hair looks good.
MAN: Can you stop slow?
KIM: We can open it.
MAN: Oh, there? Okay.
♪ ♪
KENDALL: You guys rock.
Thank you.
WOMAN: Go, girl. Have fun.
(crowd shouting)
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Hi, how are you?
Khloe. Nice to see you.
MAN: Very nice to meet you.
Come on in. I'll walk you up.
KHLOE: Thank you.
I'm in Seattle for a Nordstrom's
appearance. (Line ringing)
Hi! Hi, girl.
You're so cute, Mama.
I miss you!
We're not gonna smile?
You just don't like to talk to
me on FaceTime?
Only Tristan she likes on.
FaceTime.
Send me more pictures later, and
I hope you guys have a good
evening.
Bye! Bye, Mama. I love you.
(phone beeps) (knocking)
Oh. Hello? Oh, my God!
JAKE: Have you gotten any
advice about talking to Trump?
KIM: No.
I don't know if anyone can give
you advice. JAKE: (laughs) Yeah.
That's probably true.
KIM: We have one shot to
plead our case.
It's a really scary feeling.
SHAWN: If he does this,
that's major.
JAKE: It's major.
(knocking) >> KHLOE: Hello?
Oh, my God!
Pierre? Oh, my God!
(laughing) Oh, my God.
I've missed you.
Pierre is the mime that I found
for my mom.
KRIS: No, no, that's not for
sale. Stop it.
I... No, no, no, no.
KHLOE: Oh, there's Kris.
KRIS: Pierre!
KHLOE: Mom, this was not...
KRIS: Thank you very much.
KHLOE: Really what we
expected. This is wild.
KRIS: I just wanted you to
have a laugh.
I know this is a-a really
stressful tour.
KHLOE: Well, when I saw
Pierre, I started jumping and
hugging him, so we're good.
KRIS: (laughs) I'm so happy.
That makes me happy that it made
you smile.
KHLOE: The fact that
instantly when I see Pierre I
have, like, this surge of
energy, I really, really love
this stupid mime.
Oh. No, Pierre.
Come on, guys.
We're going to have fun.
How is this happening?
(Andrew laughs)
HRUSH/ALEXA/ANDREW: Hi!
ANDREW: We're going to the
pier. ALEXA/ANDREW: With Pierre.
KHLOE: Okrrr. (Camera clicks)
(laughs) No, no, no.
Just one. >> ANDREW: Oh, my God.
(Khloe laughing)
ALEXA: Whoa, I'm getting
nauseous.
KHLOE: Hanging out with.
Pierre is honestly just
hysterical, and I can't stop
laughing and just having the
best time.
This is just the medicine I
need.
No, no, no. I don't like the
Ferris wheel.
Come on. Pierre! Not today!
(Andrew and Alexa laugh) Pierre!
(laughs): Pierre. Pierre.
Hello! Hi! ♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
KIM: I am so excited to be in.
Wyoming for Kanye's listening
party.
It was all such a last-minute
thing.
But I feel like, after TMZ,
Kanye's changed his whole album.
And I'm just excited so many
people came out to support.
Kanye is doing press while he's
here in Wyoming, so he's gonna
have a chance to talk to
Charlamagne and just express how
he feels.
So I'm glad that now we can just
have fun and just listen to the
music and have a good time.
CHARLAMAGNE: When people see
you running around in the-the.
Make America Great Again hat,
your bl... your blackness will be
questioned.
KANYE: Yeah, see, that's...
CHARLAMAGNE: When you out
here saying you love Trump, your
blackness will be questioned.
Especially a guy that's directly
trying to oppress us, trying to
marginalize us.
KANYE: I'm not saying the
policies.
I'm talking about the fact that
this person was not supposed to
do that.
How many times do you hear
somebody say, "Everybody hates
Trump," right?
I got love.
I'm leading with love.
That's my main message that's
getting clouded.
It's like, nah, why don't we
step forward with love?
Why don't we see what we can do
with love?
'Cause it seem like we not
getting too much done with hate.
KIM: I obviously support him
and will always, but he likes to
speak for himself and I like to
speak for myself.
You know, as his wife, I just
have to express how I feel and
have those private conversations
with him and just help him
better communicate what he
really means to say.
CHRIS ROCK: All right, ladies
and gentlemen, welcome!
I hope everybody's appreciating
what's going on.
This-this is... this is not done
every day.
The world premiere of the latest
opus from the one and only Kanye.
Ye. (Crowd cheering)
♪ ♪
KIM: Today is the day we
present the case to the
president at the White House.
JAKE: You guys nervous?
KIM: I'm a little bit
nervous, but I feel like this
watch is Jackie O's that I got
on auction, so I feel very...
Got the Kennedy...
Hopefully, not the Kennedy
curse.
I've got the Kennedy strength...
with me.
SHAWN: Yeah.
JAKE: Have you gotten any
advice about talking to Trump?
KIM: No.
JAKE: No?
KIM: I don't know if anyone
can give you advice.
JAKE: (laughs) Yeah.
That's probably true.
KIM: My thing is, I might not
know a whole lot about the laws
and prison reform, but that's
why Shawn is here...
(Shawn laughs)
and, you know, to kind of
talk about just more of the
details of her case.
SHAWN: Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, if he does this, that's
major.
JAKE: It's major.
KIM: We're literally just
about to pull up.
I've never been to the White
House before.
I'm excited, I'm nervous.
I know we have one shot to plead
our case.
Knowing that someone's life is
in my hands... it's a really
scary feeling.
We have to just do justice by
Alice.
Like Jared said, "I've seen it
go."
"I can only give a 99%, and we're
as close as 99%" is what Jared
said.
But he's like, "I can never give"
100% because you never know what
he might do."
♪ ♪
(line ringing)
KIM: Hello?
Hey, I just walked out.
WOMAN: He was like...
SHAWN: Thank you.
KIM: Bye. Thank you so much.
It was good.
I mean, I think it's...
I mean, I think it's gonna
happen.
I don't know.
SHAWN: It does seem like it,
right? >> KIM: But it's, like, a
process. Wait, wait. Wait, babe.
I have these people on the
phone.
I'll call you right back.
SHAWN: Hi.
KIM: Hi. >> BRITTANY: Hi. Hi.
KIM: Okay, so, we think it
went really, really well.
BRITTANY: Great.
SHAWN: So, when we walked in,
he was finishing up a meeting
with Jeff Sessions, John.
Kelly... Who else was in there?
I mean, it was just all of those
men were in there.
All of those guys left, except
for John Kelly kind of hovered.
And it was a lot of
chitchatting, you know.
They talked a little bit about
The Celebrity
and things like that.
KIM: A lot of Kanye talk.
"I love Kanye, I love him."
Um, "He's so great."
I mean, just, like, overly...
SHAWN: Yes.
KIM: You know, 'cause Kanye
has been positive about him.
Um, but I did want to keep this
very separate from Kanye,
because I think, you know, we
just...
And he said the same thing...
That he wanted to keep this as a
completely separate
conversation.
But Jared has said that, you
know, Kanye reaching out and
speaking out has been very
positive for this.
SHAWN: We talked about the
fact that her codefendants...
Most of them are out.
They didn't like...
You know, they didn't like the
fact that she was in, and they
were out.
KIM: So he did say this is
the right thing to do.
I mean, you know, 21 years for
just drugs, like, he-he... he
said that.
I just... I just hope...
Like Jared said, "I've seen it
go."
"I can only give a 99%, and we're
as close as 99%" is what Jared
said.
But he's like, "I can never give"
100% because you never know what
he might do."
♪ ♪
KHLOE: We are here at
Nordstrom Seattle, and we are so
excited. This is crazy.
EMMA: This is so nuts.
KHLOE: Oh, my God!
And look at the photos!
EMMA: So crazy!
KHLOE: Emma, they said you
could walk on it.
Look at these assholes,
sitting on my (bleep) face.
Okay, guys.
I know, it's your dream.
Good morning, everybody.
GUNNAR: Three, two, one.
20 jumping jacks. Let's go.
KHLOE: The rooftop event just
looks so powerful, and it makes
such a statement, and it's so,
so cool.
A very "pinch me" moment.
I will say I'm super thankful
for my mom and Pierre.
He kept me so distracted when I
was super anxious about leaving
True, and I just got to laugh
and have a really good time.
It's just been a really great
experience. Hi!
(crowd screaming, shouting)
Oh, my God, hi!
Oh, hi! That's so nice.
EMMA: Sorry, love.
Can I get through?
KHLOE: Oh, hi.
How... Are you driving?
Oh, my God!
I didn't know you were driving.
♪ ♪
FEMALE VOICE: Please announce
yourself.
KIM: Hi. Hi, guys. It's Kim.
SHAWN: Kim! Hi, Kim!
Oh, my God, Kim!
KIM: This is so crazy.
SHAWN: You did it. Oh, my gosh.
Did it.
I'm at a shoot, so I cannot cry,
but... SHAWN: (laughs) Oh, I'm
already doing it.
KIM: But this is so crazy.
SHAWN: You did it. Oh, my God!
KIM: I cannot believe we
pulled this off.
SHAWN: I can't believe it.
You made this happen.
There was no way this would have
happened without you.
Hello?
BRITTANY: Hi. It's Brittany.
SHAWN: Hi, Brittany.
KIM: Hi, Brittany.
BRITTANY: Hi. Who's on?
KIM: It's Kim and Shawn.
SHAWN: Shawn and Kim and
Jennifer.
JENNIFER: Hey. Hey, y'all.
Okay, one second.
I'm trying to take a deep breath
so I don't jack this all up.
Okay. I'm okay.
Okay. KIM: One of the attorneys.
All of her attorneys.
BRITTANY: Ms. Alice?
ALICE: Hello?
BRITTANY: Yeah, I'm here.
KIM: Ms. Alice? ALICE: Yes?
JENNIFER: That's Kim.
ALICE: This is Kim!
SHAWN: It's Kim. ALICE: Hi, Kim!
How you doing?
Angels, my war angels.
KIM: I cannot believe it.
We did it.
ALICE: Huh? KIM: We-we did it.
ALICE: What happened?
KIM: We did it.
You don't know?
SHAWN: No, she doesn't
know.
You're telling her the news.
KIM: Oh, my gosh!
Alice, you're out.
ALICE: Yes? (Screams, laughs)
SHAWN: You're coming home!
ALICE: Oh, bless you.
(crying) >> KIM: I can...
I-I'm sorry, I thought you knew.
Oh, my God, the news just broke.
The president just called me,
and he told me that, um... that
you are out.
He signed the papers, it's been
released to the press,
everything.
SHAWN: You're coming home.
KIM: So we did it.
(women laughing)
SHAWN: I wish we could all be
together and have a big hug.
KIM: I know.
SHAWN: I'm just crying in my
office. (Laughter)
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, we're all here, Alice.
ALICE: I am.
You did it, you did it, you did
it, Kim.
You didn't stop fighting.
You did it. KIM: Well, I am...
I'm, like, I can't cry.
I'm on set of a photo shoot, and
I have all this makeup on, and
I'm like, "Don't cry, don't cry",
"don't cry." >> ALICE: Don't cry.
Please don't mess your picture
up.
KIM: But I will cry as soon
as I see you.
I will... I got... I have to
come out and meet you and see
you, and the president was so
nice.
He said, "You know, a lot of
people fought against this."
But he believed in you, and he
called everyone, and everyone
said you were just such an
amazing person, so he is so
happy to do it for you, and he,
uh... he was really, really
happy.
I am so grateful that we are
giving someone their life back
and giving them a second chance.
And I'm just so happy for Alice.
Alice, I will connect with you
in a little bit.
I'm gonna go back to my shoot.
I will connect with you, um, you
know, after you settle in with
your family.
I'll give my cell phone number
to Shawn.
If you guys, you know, want to
call me later, I'll be
available.
Um, and then, you know, we'll
plan the... I'll come down in a
few days just to give you a big
hug.
ALICE: Thank God you called me.
KIM: Okay. Okay.
Bye, everyone. Love you.
ALICE: Bye.
NEWS ANCHOR: Breaking news.
All right, we are coming to you
live where we are now seeing
Alice Johnson, uh, being
reunited with her friends and
family after being behind bars
for 21 years. ♪ ♪
KIM: Girls, do you know why
we're going to Tennessee?
NORTH: Why?
KIM: We are going to meet a
woman named Ms. Alice Johnson.
We have to go meet Ms. Alice
because Mommy and Shawn helped
her get out of jail.
She was in jail for 20, almost
22 years.
So, Alice and I have been
discussing when we're gonna meet
face-to-face.
Like, we have to meet, we have
to connect.
We have to just give each other
a big hug.
Just that video of seeing Alice
run out of prison and get to her
family and hug everyone was just
such a satisfying moment.
Just to know that she's been
behind bars for 22 years, and
she's now home.
It's really amazing.
I think, honestly, for the first
one, it couldn't have gone
better.
SHAWN: Yeah.
KIM: And that's what, like,
so many people don't get.
Like, this has nothing to do
with politics.
Like, (bleep) politics.
I don't really know anything.
This just has to do with, get in
front of the person that is the
only person in the world that
can make this decision...
SHAWN: Right. Right.
KIM: And try to change
their mind.
♪ ♪
Oh, look at everyone in the
window.
This is exciting.
Shawn, do you want to come with
me?
(Alice screams, laughs)
KIM: I'm so happy to meet you
and to hug you.
ALICE: Oh, my God.
KIM: I can't wait to meet
your family.
ALICE: Oh, my God, Kim.
You never gave up.
And you did it! You did it.
You did it! (Laughs)
KIM: This is Shawn.
You have to meet Shawn.
ALICE: Hi, Shawn.
SHAWN: Hi.
KIM: She helped me with
everything.
(Alice crying)
We're so happy to be here.
I want to meet your whole
family.
She just is the sweetest person,
and it's so great just to see
her back with her family.
Oh, my gosh. Nice to meet you.
WOMAN: Thank you so much, Kim.
ALICE: This is my sister Thelma.
KIM: How many sisters do you
have?
(all laughing)
ALICE: His sister.
KIM: Hi.
ALICE: This is their mother,
Tammy, my niece. >> KIM: Hi.
ALICE: My nephew, Randall.
KIM: Hi. How are you?
ALICE: My niece, Sherry.
These two are singers.
KIM: Hi. Oh, wow.
She has her life back.
She has a full second chance
and she's with her grandkids
and her kids and she's so
grateful.
Hey, babe. Do you have a second?
Okay. Hold on.
I want you to talk to Alice.
She has to say one thing.
It's really cute. Hold on.
ALICE: Hi, Kanye.
Oh, I am wonderful.
I'm sitting here in front of
your beautiful wife.
I want you to know that the
people here in Memphis love you.
They love you here.
It's like, this is something
to give not only prisoners
hope, but America hope again,
so you played a big role in
this.
Thank you. Thank you.
Here's your wife.
I love you, Kanye.
KIM: Hey, babe.
Okay, get back to your meeting.
Okay, bye.
ALICE: I'm telling you, this
is something that everywhere I
go... if you could only just walk
down the streets of Memphis... I
know you can't, but I do.
People recognize me now, and
they're in tears, hugging me and
telling me how happy they are
that I've come back home.
I don't know these people, but
they're so happy for me.
It's just love.
It's... I'm telling you, it's
like a lovefest, if you want to
call it that.
I've seen that word before, a
"lovefest," but this is what's
going on here.
KIM: On this journey of
getting Alice out, I have
learned so much about criminal
justice and really how messed up
our system is.
Jared was texting me and said,
"Honestly, we couldn't have"
picked a better person to open
up his heart, and for this to
"get started, because now he
doesn't want to stop."
So... That's all you.
That's all you, so thank you.
ALICE: Thank you.
KIM: There's so much that has
to be done, and I know Alice's
case is the one that spoke to
me, but now that that is, like,
in me, I can't stop at Alice.
Like, there has to be so much
more that I could do.
ALICE: This is only a small
portion of my tribe.
(laughter)
KIM: Well, you're very lucky
to have a big support system and
family.
ALICE: Thank you.
WOMAN: Thank you, Kim!
(cheering, applause)
KIM: I mean, just seeing.
Alice with her huge family.
That's like me and my big
family.
If I couldn't be with them for
two decades, that would break my
soul.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: Reign, come on.
KOURTNEY: Where are we
sitting? Sit next to Daddy.
KIM: Hi. >> KRIS: Hey. Hi.
KANYE: Hey.
SCOTT: Reign, you say "hi"?
KOURTNEY: Make you a plate?
Do you want to sit right here
next to me?
MASON: Kanye, I like your new
song. >> KANYE: Word?
KOURTNEY: Uh, Mase.
KANYE: Thank you.
KOURTNEY: You're allowed to
listen to that?
MASON: Yeah.
KHLOE: Uh, he made me listen
the whole car ride home.
MASON: Yeah.
KANYE: For real?
SCOTT: What part do you like
the most?
KHLOE: Oh, you can't ask.
No, no. But, but he's good.
He won't say "ho" or... Sorry.
Whatever. Uh...
KANYE: What parts do you
like?
MASON: I just like the whole
thing. >> KIM: That is so funny.
Every time I think that I've
had a crazy year, I live the
next year, (laughs) and it's
even crazier.
KRIS: What did you put in
your dad's ear?
NORTH: A flower. >> KRIS: Oh.
SCOTT: That's funny? ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I definitely think
the last year has been a big
growth period for me, in just
figuring out, like, what I want
in life and making it happen.
KRIS: Oh! Uh-oh!
♪ ♪
KENDALL: I think I'm always
learning about who I am, but I
think that this year I learned a
lot.
(laughs)
Slowly finding my place in this
world. >> KYLIE: Tickle, tickle,
tickle.
This last year has definitely
been very transformative, and I
feel like a new person.
It's definitely been
life-changing for me.
KOURTNEY: Hey. Hey. (Laughs) ♪ ♪
Open up.
SCOTT: It took a long time
for me to figure out what's
important.
I think I'm closer now with all
the people that I love than I've
ever been.
I'm very happy with where I'm
at, and I just want to keep
building from here.
(Khloe laughs)
KRIS: We're all crazy.
KRIS: The most beautiful
thing that happened to us this
year was the birth of three new
grandkids. I feel blessed.
(Tristan smooching)
KHLOE: I have come to a place
in my life where I am super
comfortable, and I really make
a conscious effort to drown out
the white noise that really
doesn't matter.
As long as me and my immediate
family are happy, that's enough,
and that is what makes me happy.
♪ ♪
KIM: Saint, are you my
favorite boy in the entire
world?
♪ ♪
I feel like I used to live my
life so much about just being
passionate about me.
Now my priorities have shifted,
so I'm really excited for this
year and what's to come, and the
more that I can do to help other
people. Captioning sponsored by.
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS
Captioned by.
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org