♪ ♪
JONATHAN: Hi.
Oh, there's, like, thousands of
trampolines.
KOURTNEY: Who's ready to
jump? (Indistinct chatter)
JONATHAN: Gotcha. I got ya!
PENELOPE: I'm not jumping.
KOURTNEY: Why? I'm gonna
jump. Mase.
JONATHAN: Wait, Mason, but
you got to do this.
You got to run into the wall.
MASON: No, I don't.
JONATHAN: Yeah, look.
(Kourtney gasps) Whoa. Ooh, ooh!
MASON: I'm out.
KOURTNEY: Why? You're out?
JONATHAN: That's crazy (bleep).
That's some crazy (bleep).
KOURTNEY: My kids are so
cranky.
They like to sit on the side.
JONATHAN: Look how mad they
both are.
KOURTNEY: I'm telling you,
two minutes later, they'll be
fine. Oh, my God.
(shouts) Whoo!
Oh, my God... (laughs) I fell.
I'm gonna try it again.
(laughing): Oh, my God.
I'm literally, I'm gonna pee my
pants.
(Jonathan laughs) Oh, my God!
JONATHAN: That's what I'm
talking about!
MASON: I want to try.
JONATHAN: Hit...
You got to hit the wall.
KOURTNEY: Mase.
MASON: Whoa. KOURTNEY: Whoo!
MASON: Come on, P!
KOURTNEY: My kids came back.
JONATHAN: Well, you called it.
(Kourtney laughs) ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
KHLOE: So I just left my
first doctor's appointment in.
Cleveland ever, and we are about
two weeks out, two and a half
weeks max from me giving birth.
Something that I'm super
grateful about is that the show
basically documents all of these
great moments in time, and that
we get to have kind of really
expensive, well-produced home
videos.
And since I was on maternity
leave from the show, I decided
to film everything myself, um,
or have a friend shoot it,
so I'm able to have a great
video for True one day.
I'm so nervous.
I don't know why... well, I know
why, it's just scary.
I'm just scared of the labor,
'cause that just scares me.
Oh, and I've been having
contractions, which is kind of
cool 'cause they're not that
painful.
But that's why we're not
concerned, 'cause they're not
that painful.
(laughs)
It's the homestretch, two weeks,
and then I get to be with her
and see what she looks like, and
meet her and... But I'm excited.
♪ ♪
KENDALL: So all of this is
gonna be painted all green.
We're gonna, like, fix this
door a bit.
SCOTT: Wait, did you sell the
other house quickly, or you
still have it?
KENDALL: Literally, in less
than a month.
We sold it so fast, that's why
I'm homeless right now.
So this room's just like...
SCOTT: Formal?
KENDALL: Yeah, exactly.
This is gonna be used to, like,
hang out, or whatever.
This is the TV room.
SCOTT: This is nice.
KENDALL: So we're putting,
like, a big hundred-inch here.
SCOTT: Are they gonna recess
it into the wall?
KENDALL: No.
I just don't really care.
SCOTT: It's kind of nice.
(Kendall laughs)
I want to see this yard.
KENDALL: This is it.
SCOTT: It looks damn good.
KENDALL: They're gonna redo
it completely, basically.
Like, fill it in more.
SCOTT: And how's that tub?
KENDALL: It's not horrible.
Comfortably, three people, four
people.
SCOTT: Yeah.
Depending on the size.
I think you'll like it up here.
KENDALL: Yeah.
SCOTT: It feels safe and secure.
KENDALL: And I can, like, get
to Calabasas and, like, my
horses easier.
SCOTT: Haven't you been
riding a lot more lately?
KENDALL: Yeah.
I just got a new horse.
SCOTT: That's fun.
KENDALL: She's real cute.
SCOTT: It's nice to do
things.
KENDALL: I feel like I have
no one to do anything with.
SCOTT: I mean, I would say I
would come horseback riding with
you, but I probably wouldn't.
But I'm down to do any other
kind of fun activities.
KENDALL: We should do stuff.
Yeah, I feel like you're my only
person left that likes to do fun
things.
SCOTT: Well, also,
everybody's, like, bedridden
with a child.
KENDALL: Yeah. Right.
I'm literally the only one
without a kid.
SCOTT: I used to always run
around with Khloe, but now she's
got a baby coming.
Kylie was, like, your go-to.
She's got a kid.
My kids are, like, growing up.
KENDALL: Looks like the
universe is just drawing us
together. >> SCOTT: It's just...
That's all we need in life.
(Kendall laughs)
You know, I feel like me and
Kenny have always had a lot in
common.
You know, we're both models.
Just kidding.
You know, we're both really into
doing stuff that gets our
adrenaline going, and with
everybody having babies now,
Kendall's pretty much the only
person that can basically move.
Oh, is this, for-for some odd
reason, I, like, knew...
KENDALL: (gasps) Oh, my God.
SCOTT: You were going
after that machine.
I don't know why.
You started thinking about
doing activities, it looked like
a big bowling ball.
KENDALL: We can just build
this house together.
SCOTT: There's a lot of...
Whoa! Whoa!
You got to get on a helmet.
KENDALL: I know.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: I have been on this
birthing ball for how long,
Malika?
MALIKA: Um, like, the last
three hours.
KHLOE: And I love this thing.
It's supposed to, like, help the
baby get into position, and.
Malika is with me because
Tristan is on the road and...
MALIKA: I'm baby daddy two.
KHLOE: And so she's my second
baby daddy.
And he wanted her to be here
in case anything happens,
'cause I'm very close to
delivering, but so far...
MALIKA: I can't wait.
I can't wait, I can't wait.
KHLOE: Come on, birthing
ball, let's birth.
MALIKA: Come on, baby.
♪ ♪
KIM: Hi.
OLIVIA: Oh, my God, the brown
hair. Nice to see you.
KIM: I'm having a really bad
hair day.
Have you guys ever been here?
OLIVIA: No. >> KIM: Yeah.
OLIVIA: I haven't been...
KIM: But she's so nice.
Natalie and Olivia are
friends that I have kind of
recently become friends with.
NATALIE: Kim.
What if it becomes trendy to
have a hairy armpit?
KIM: That... I cannot stand
when girls are into that.
NATALIE: I know, but I feel
like it's creeping in, like, the
hairy armpit things.
OLIVIA: Well, I'll never do
it, so I don't care.
KIM: It's kind of different
now that I'm a mom.
Sometimes it's fun to have
friends that aren't my mom
friends, that I can just have a
good time with.
NATALIE: I have been so
hungry lately, I can't control
myself.
♪ ♪
KIM: (groans) I can hardly
sit from my workout.
They have, like, a green apple
sake. >> OLIVIA: Do they?
Should we do it?
We'll do the apple sake.
NATALIE: Let's try it.
KIM: Like, the tiniest,
tiniest, tiniest bit.
OLIVIA: Kim, one day...
KIM: I have to be, like, in
Vegas to get wasted.
OLIVIA: Okay, one day, we'll
get wasted.
NATALIE: Well, having a drink
at lunch isn't gonna get you
wasted, Kim.
OLIVIA: Don't booze-pressure
her. NATALIE: I'm booze-shaming
her. (Laughter)
NATALIE: Peer pressure, peer
pressure.
Drink, Kim, drink.
OLIVIA: I think now that
you're a mom of three, we got to
get you gooned.
KIM: Yeah, but then if I
can't get up in the morning to
take the kids to school, it's,
like, a whole other thing.
NATALIE: But I think you're
really underestimating the
amount of, like, mothers that
are drunk all day long.
(Kim chuckles)
Kim, just trust us, okay?
OLIVIA: What you do, you
could do a starter pack with us.
On the low. NATALIE: Yeah, see?
We could even stay in.
KIM: Just at home?
NATALIE: Yeah, at home.
OLIVIA: Three girls just
getting gooned, I don't know.
KIM: My 20-year, um, reunion
is in two weeks.
OLIVIA: Are you kidding?
KIM: That's a time where I
would drink.
I would get totally drunk.
NATALIE: Yeah, that would be
a great time.
OLIVIA: Well, especially
because it was a girls' school.
So it really is time with the
girls.
NATALIE: Yeah, get sloshed
with your old-timers, yeah.
OLIVIA: "Sloshed with the"
"old-timers." >> KIM: Yeah.
20-year reunion.
How crazy is that?
Just to even think.
NATALIE: Okay, let's just not
say that. >> KIM: It's wild.
NATALIE: Are we that old?
(laughter)
KIM: I have honestly been
waiting to go to a high school
reunion since I graduated.
There was, like, a group of us
that were best friends, and I'm
so excited to reconnect with
them. I will say, this is pretty
amazing, though.
This tastes like, yeah.
NATALIE: Tastes like apples.
KIM: Did you fill this up?
OLIVIA: Yes, she did.
KIM: Just a little refill.
OLIVIA: Cheers to life, ladies.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Malika and I just left
the doctors.
Get into frame.
MALIKA: I just saw my baby.
She's so cute.
KHLOE: Ugh, I look crazy.
I'm one and a half centimeters
dilated.
My cervix is really...
MALIKA: Soft and ready.
KHLOE: Smushy.
So basically, any time.
With every day, I definitely was
excited, but I was more anxious.
'Cause, you know, it's just the
unknown.
You don't know what's gonna
happen.
And I think people put such a
scary... just, perception of
birth into your head, so it's
just, like, it's a terrifying
thought to think, "Oh, my God,
I have to deliver a baby out of"
my vagina."
Like, that's just, sounds so
terrifying.
MALIKA: Khloe's about to go.
Yeah!
SCOTT: I thought, you know,
if me and Kenny got out, in the
open sand, it would be kind of
fun.
(Kendall screams) (phone chimes)
(Kendall gasps)
SCOTT: What's popping?
(phones chiming)
What? Stop.
KIM: There's a video of.
Tristan making out with a girl
last night.
Khloe's gonna die.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: I feel like you really
could just, like, kill somebody
and then drop their body back
here and no one would ever find
it. >> WOMAN: Hi.
SCOTT: Hey.
WOMAN: Hi, this is Sylvia.
SCOTT: How are you? Scott.
KENDALL: Hi, I'm Kendall,
nice to meet you.
SCOTT: You know, when I was a
kid, I used to always ride ATVs
or quads or whatever you want to
call it, and I remember it being
a really good time in my life.
So I thought, you know, if me
and Kenny got out in the open
sand, it would be kind of fun.
KENDALL: Good, how are you?
JORGE: Welcome to Enjoy the
Mountain, this is Jorge.
KENDALL: I'm Kendall.
JORGE: Kendall, nice to meet
you. >> SCOTT: Hey, Scott.
How are you?
JORGE: You can grab the
handlebar now, please.
Just steer left, right and
point forward again.
Where the front wheels are
pointing, that's where it's
gonna go.
I'm gonna go first, then it's
going to be you, then you're
gonna be the last one, okay?
(engine whirring)
Ready, Kendall? ♪ ♪
KENDALL: Whoo!
SCOTT: The whole ATV'ing is
fun, but it's not exactly
extreme.
I mean, I'm pretty sure
grandmothers could ride these
little dirt bikes around town.
KENDALL: Whoo! (Laughs)
JORGE: You made it. Good job.
You did a good job. Well done.
How was the ride? KENDALL: Fun.
JORGE: It was fun?
KENDALL: Thank you.
(exhales)
SCOTT: It was therapeutic.
Wasn't really an extreme sport,
but...
KENDALL: No, it was fun.
SCOTT: It felt nice.
It was, like, relaxing.
Is that a spray tan or is that
dirt?
KENDALL: No... that's my arm.
That's the dirt. SCOTT: Holy...
KENDALL: Spray tan?
SCOTT: You're an animal.
All right, I'm ready to hit the
showers.
KENDALL: Yeah, same. ♪ ♪
KENDALL: Mase's vibe is so
funny, he wants to be like you
so bad. >> SCOTT: Really?
KENDALL: He wears his little
chains and he has his little
cool guy attitude.
And I'm just like, "You're so"
funny."
SCOTT: Today wasn't really an
extreme sport, but I'll tell you
what I really want to do more
than anything though, is go
skydiving.
KENDALL: Oh, my God. Like, no.
SCOTT: Yeah, I've always
wanted to.
KENDALL: It makes me so nervous.
SCOTT: I think it makes
everybody nervous.
That's the point, kind of.
You know, I've always wanted to
skydive.
I've actually always wanted to
become, like, a licensed
skydiver, just so when I went
on planes, I could bring a pack.
Just in case if things got
ugly, you could just jump out
and be good.
I don't know if that's legal,
but that always seemed like a
good idea. KENDALL: So scary...
SCOTT: I think you got to
just give, like, a "I don't give"
"a (bleep)" vibe and then once
you're out, it's probably an
unbelievable experience.
I'm actually a little surprised,
'cause I kind of thought she
would be into it hands down, but
she seems a little reluctant.
KENDALL: This was my
agreement: I will go, I will get
get in the plane and I will go
up.
SCOTT: Oh, well, that's fine.
KENDALL: But I don't know if
I can guarantee that I will
jump out.
SCOTT: Nobody can guarantee
that.
KENDALL: No, but I heard that
if you get in the plane and you
take off, they make you jump.
SCOTT: No. Not a chance.
No chance.
That's fully illegal.
(Kendall groans)
They're not gonna push you out
of the plane.
♪ ♪
KHLOE: So this is my new life.
All I do is sit on this
birthing ball.
Sleeping, I can't get
comfortable, sitting.
And really, the only place I
feel comfortable is this ball.
It's really just a (bleep)
workout ball, but they call it a
birthing ball, and you bounce,
you do whatever.
Oh, my gosh, can we talk about
the breathing?
When I am watching these videos
back and I am hearing... ugh...
The breathing, I sound like a
full-blown beast and I can't
handle it.
I mean, I have a little
munchkin sitting on my lungs,
so I guess it's to be expected,
but holy cow. (Exhales)
I'm out of breath right now.
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
KIM: You know what I would
dream for?
I would dream to sit in bed
and have no one bug me and
watch whatever shows I want.
SARAH: Right. You would do
that for two days and then you'd
be like, "I'm so lonely, where"
"is everyone?" Trust me.
KIM: Yeah, but there is
nothing like, just a good
night's sleep.
I got pushed in my sleep...
SARAH: Yeah, but I've done
that my whole life.
KIM: All (bleep) night long.
I have the biggest bed and
I got pushed and kicked...
SARAH: Boo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
KIM: All night long.
SARAH: You have three
beautiful kids, though.
I'd so much rather get kicked
off the bed than have the whole
bed to myself.
Our bodies are made for
spooning, Kim.
I spoon my dog, that's it.
KIM: That's disgusting.
People like you are sick in the
head. >> KOURTNEY: Honey.
(phone ringing)
Oh, you're in Stormi's room.
How cute are you?
So I feel like, maybe we should
just go to Cleveland earlier...
KYLIE: I agree.
KOURTNEY: And see Khloe,
and, like, be there.
KYLIE: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: Early, like, for
the birth.
KIM: I just, like, have my 20
year high school reunion, that I
really wanted to go to, but...
and Khloe's like, "go to that",
that's more important."
KOURTNEY: On the 14th?
KIM: Yes.
Khloe has been timing out her
pregnancy and we think her
baby's gonna come sooner than we
anticipated, and, like,
literally, the doctor thinks it
could happen right on the day of
my 20-year reunion.
SARAH: Kim, I feel like you
need to go to your high school
reunion.
You've been talking about it
for two years.
KIM: I know, right?
But what if Khloe, Khloe's
having her baby?
KYLIE: I think Khloe's just
saying, "Go to that, it's more"
"important, or do this," but I
think she really wants us to be
there.
Imagine how she, like, how you'd
feel like.
Different states, already weird.
She has the baby and none of us
are there, it'll just...
I know, like, she's stressed
now, but after, she's gonna want
us, like...
She's gonna be like, "(bleep)"
where are they?"
KIM: So 20 years, I've been
waiting for this.
I've been so excited.
But I feel like Khloe really
needs me right now, so, I don't
know what to do.
So what do I do?
Birth, or 20-year reunion?
KENDALL: Getting a little
nervous.
SCOTT: Today is the day that
we are going to jump out of a
perfectly good airplane.
MAN: There's no turning back
now.
KENDALL: I don't think I can
do it.
WOMAN: We're wondering how
you balance your
responsibilities?
KRIS: Well, I think as far
as... what, you want to answer
that?
KOURTNEY: They said you have
to check your phone right this
second.
KRIS: Oh.
Khloe's in full-blown labor and
I'm in charge of bringing the
doctor.
We should have come last night.
I knew it.
(sighs) (bleep)
♪ ♪
KHLOE: Just got out of the
shower.
Um, the baby has been really
low, which is good.
The baby's dropped, what they
say.
Um, yeah.
I mean, I feel good, I'm just
anxiously waiting for...
the baby to get here.
(sighs) My little, my babe.
So, exciting.
The countdown is real.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Do you like me?
KRIS: Hi, boo-boo.
Wait.
Kim didn't realize that you
lived here now. >> KIM: Yeah.
KRIS: Do you love living out
there in the guesthouse?
Do you feel safe?
KENDALL: I don't live out
there, I live in here.
KRIS: Oh, you do?
KENDALL: Yeah. KRIS: What room?
KENDALL: The master...
KRIS: Stop, you took over.
Khloe's master?
KENDALL: She told me I could.
KRIS: That is a badass move.
KENDALL: I bet you she would
have... KRIS: I like your style.
(chuckles): I love your style.
KIM: You know, I've been
dying to go to my high school
reunion.
I'm literally in a group chat
with my friends right now.
KRIS: Stop.
KIM: But I'm nervous 'cause.
Khloe's supposed to... that's the
weekend that the doctor is going
out to see Khloe.
KRIS: What day is the high
school reunion? >> KIM: Friday.
KRIS: Oh, wow. >> KIM: Yeah.
If I want to go to the reunion
on Friday night, can you just
fly out a little bit later and
I'll fly with you?
'Cause my reunion's at, like,
6:30.
KRIS: I've already told
Dr. A that we're gonna get on
a plane Friday morning.
And I just want to get there,
'cause this is giving me anxiety
just not being there.
I just want to settle in and
make sure she has everything she
needs.
You know, there's a lot to do.
Because God forbid she goes into
labor.
Then at least Doctor A's there,
I'm there.
I mean, I wish I could leave
now.
So we're gonna go.
You can't get on that plane.
You need to go to your reunion,
I get it.
KIM: All right, well, you go,
and I'll think about it.
KRIS: All right.
KIM: It's like, I really want
to go to my 20-year reunion, so
I'll just, I-I cannot plan...
It's like, my 20-year reunion's
really important to me, also.
KRIS: Yeah.
KIM: They're both are.
I-I want to go to both, and I
feel like I can go to both.
KRIS: Uh, Khloe's birth,
20-year reunion.
It should be Khloe's birth.
KIM: I know, but I just feel
like I can do both.
So I'm just, like, I-I have to
be really last-minute on this.
KRIS: Of course you do.
Okay.
KIM: Like, I just can't make
too many plans.
KRIS: It'll be fine.
I'm gonna be in Cleveland.
So you have fun.
KIM: Okay.
KRIS: Okay? You do you.
I'm gonna do me. >> KIM: Okay.
KRIS: Okay.
How about you, Kenny?
KENDALL: I don't know. ♪ ♪
KENDALL: How are you?
SCOTT: Scott, nice to meet
you.
So today is the day that we are
going to jump out of a perfectly
good airplane.
And I'm very excited.
I got to tell you.
SCOTT SMITH: You excited?
KENDALL: Mm... I don't know.
SCOTT SMITH: So you haven't
jumped before, have you?
KENDALL: Never.
I'm getting a little nervous.
SCOTT SMITH: Pull those leg
straps up over your knees.
And then slip your arms back.
KENDALL: How many times have
you jumped?
Do you have, like...
SCOTT SMITH: About 17,000.
KENDALL: Stop.
SCOTT SMITH: Been jump...
This summer will be 40 years.
KENDALL: Really?
SCOTT SMITH: Mm-hmm.
KENDALL: Has anything crazy
happened to you?
I mean like, scary?
SCOTT SMITH: I've had a
couple sprained ankles over the
years.
KENDALL: Obviously, my only
real fear is, like, the
parachute situation.
SCOTT SMITH: Parachutes are
super reliable these days.
But again, they're...
KENDALL: "These days."
SCOTT SMITH: (laughs)
40 years ago, they weren't,
weren't quite as good as what we
have right now. Yeah.
KENDALL: So if we get up
there and I change my mind, is
that okay?
SCOTT SMITH: That's fine.
KENDALL: Okay.
SCOTT: I feel like this is
the worst part.
KENDALL: No, I'm tripping out
a little bit.
Oh, it's time to get on the
plane. I'm so scared.
I can't breathe.
Do people, do people black out
often?
SCOTT SMITH: Not very often.
KENDALL: I'm getting nervous.
SCOTT: It's no big deal.
SCOTT SMITH: I think we're
ready.
KENDALL: Why am I doing this?
SCOTT: It's because you're
not just a model.
KENDALL: (bleep)
(Scott laughs)
I need to go home!
Oh, my God, it's happening.
SCOTT: So anyway...
KENDALL: Oh, my God, I'm
freaking out.
Ah! Oh, my gosh.
SCOTT: No turning back now.
KENDALL: What did I agree to?
SCOTT SMITH: All right, you
ready?
KENDALL: I don't think I can
do it.
WOMAN: You're all right.
MAN: You got this. You got this!
KENDALL: How fast does it all
happen?
MAN: About eight minutes.
SCOTT: I've been wanting to
do this forever, so I'm
comfortable.
But Kenny definitely doesn't
seem too comfortable.
And it kind of feels like
there's a very good chance
she's not going to jump out of
this plane.
KENDALL: I don't know.
SCOTT: I mean, listen, Kenny
said she wanted to get her
adrenaline rumbling around.
So this is it.
KENDALL: Oh, my God.
I don't think I can do it.
(Kendall gasps) >> KIM: Hey.
MALIKA: What the (bleep) is
that?
KIM: She's literally gonna go
into labor over this.
KOURTNEY: The whole thing
just really makes me disgusted.
KENDALL: Love you, Scott!
SCOTT: There's something I've
wanted to tell you! KENDALL: No!
SCOTT: I've always loved you!
SCOTT SMITH: Green light,
green light.
MAN: All right, start with
your right. (Kendall screams)
♪ ♪
KENDALL: Oh, my God.
I don't think I can do it.
MAN: You want to...
Want to take a look?
KENDALL: I don't think I can
do it.
(whimpers)
MAN: When you're ready to go,
we're good to go.
KENDALL: I can't.
I'm, like, literally shaking!
I'm sorry.
CAMERAMAN: Just count to three.
You can do this. I promise you.
These guys got you.
(Kendall moans)
MAN: One, two, three.
(Kendall screams)
♪ ♪
MAN (laughs): Yeah! Nice job.
SCOTT: (bleep) yeah, brah.
MAN: Pretty awesome, huh?
KENDALL: Whoo! Oh, my God!
PRODUCER: How was it?
SCOTT: Oh, it was sick.
KENDALL: It's crazy how many
emotions you go through.
MAN: Yeah. (Kendall whooping)
(laughs) >> MAN: Ah, ha, ha!
KENDALL: I did it!
MAN: Whoo-hoo!
SCOTT: Ha, ha! KENDALL: Whoo!
We did it! SCOTT: That was sick.
KENDALL: I almost didn't go!
SCOTT: You know, I feel like
everyone sees Kendall as just
this beautiful supermodel, but
they don't realize that she's
pretty wild, too, and is into
doing pretty much anything.
I'm, like, a proud older
brother.
We both did it, and it's a good
experience, it's something we
can have forever.
All right, you ready to go back
up?
KENDALL: No! SCOTT: Ah, ha!
KENDALL: Scott, let's stand
in front of the plane.
Try and, like, get, like, a lot
of plane.
Like, maybe, like, maybe stand
there, and get it, like, that
way. >> SCOTT: How's my bulge?
KENDALL: I can Facetune it
bigger for you.
SCOTT: Nice! (Kendall laughs)
♪ ♪
MAN: Three, two, one.
SCOTT: That was (bleep) dope.
Thank God you did it.
KENDALL: Yeah.
SCOTT: I was nervous for a
second.
So what was it like, right when
you were about to jump?
Was that, like, the scariest
point?
KENDALL: I was, like, on the
verge of tears; I was, like,
I was like, I'm gonna, I'm not,
like, I can't do this.
And I kept looking at everyone
being, like, "Are you sure? Are
you sure? Do you promise me?"
Do you promise me?"
And then they were like, "We
have 30 more seconds.
If you want to go, you have to
"go now, or else we have to
circle around."
And I was like, "My dad would
yell at me right now if I wasn't"
going."
My dad would be like, "Get up
and get off the plane."
SCOTT: Right.
KENDALL: Like, I know that my
dad...
So I was like, "Oh, my God, I
have to do it."
And I was like, "Fine! One, two,
three," and then he jumped.
SCOTT: Yeah, I think that's
just how it is, like, you just
don't feel like you can do it...
KENDALL: Uh, I think it's
that way.
SCOTT: But then if you're
like, "Okay, go..."
KENDALL: Yeah.
SCOTT: It's gonna happen.
KENDALL: Mm-hmm.
SCOTT: Yeah, that was an
amazing experience, though.
KENDALL: Yeah. (Phone chiming)
(gasps) >> SCOTT: Hmm?
(phone chimes) What's popping?
KIM: Wait, hold on one second.
SCOTT: Group? What? Stop.
Bro, that's pretty serious,
isn't it?
KENDALL: Wow. (Phone chimes)
SCOTT: Is that for sure, for
sure?
KENDALL: I don't know, that's
what I'm trying to find out.
That's insane.
SCOTT: I mean, you know the
only person to ask right now...
is Kim.
KENDALL: She's the one who
texted...
SCOTT: Oh, that's what I'm
saying.
What's her take on it?
KIM: Hold on.
(quietly): Yikes. Ugh...
There's video of Tristan making
out with a girl last night.
PRODUCER: Oh, no! KIM: I know.
Khloe's gonna die.
KENDALL: "The woman who"
filmed the clip said, 'I was
there and he was on the table
right next to us with a group of
friends.
"Everybody watched them make out
several times.'"
KOURTNEY: I mean, I can't
even imagine being in Khloe's
shoes.
Just how, like, reckless it all
seems.
This is really shocking, and
obviously, heartbreaking.
The whole thing makes me
disgusted.
KENDALL: I'm, like, in shock
right now; I don't even know
what to say.
SCOTT: This is out of...
KENDALL: Like, (bleep)
idiot. It's a sick joke.
SCOTT: (bleep)
KIM: Kylie just sent Khloe
the article.
Like, do I call Khloe?
KENDALL: Oh, no. SCOTT: What?
KENDALL: She def knows, but
she's not responding to the
texts.
KYLIE: No one had the courage
to tell Khloe 'cause we knew she
was days away from giving birth.
We didn't want to stress her
out, but we knew that it was the
right thing to do.
So I'm the one that told Khloe.
I didn't want to hurt her
feelings, but I felt like she
should hear from one of us,
versus on the Internet.
KENDALL: Oh, my God.
SCOTT: What?
KENDALL: Oh, my God, I'm
gonna cry for her.
SCOTT: No...
KIM: She's literally gonna go
into labor over this.
(phone ringing)
Hey. MALIKA: What the (bleep) is
that? >> KHLOE: Hello?
KIM: Hey, are you okay?
Honestly, so many more stories
have come out, so many friends
are calling me with, like, so
many more things.
We thought she finally found her.
Prince Charming, and then,
(bleep).
KRIS: Hey. Are you contracting?
Oh, (bleep). I got to go.
KIM: Like, go.
KRIS: I got to go.
KIM: When there's something
crazy that goes on in our
family, we drop everything that
we're doing.
KHLOE: I don't want any
negativity in the delivery room.
I don't want anyone to talk
about it, make me feel
uncomfortable or him
uncomfortable.
MALIKA: He's definitely
gonna have to face you guys.
KOURTNEY: You are (bleep)
with all of us when you
disrespect one of us.
(phone ringing) >> KIM: Hey.
MALIKA: What the (bleep) is
that?
KIM: Are you with her?
MALIKA: No, I'm not.
KIM: She's literally gonna go
into labor over this.
MALIKA: She's, like,
literally about to go into...
she's, like, literally about
to have the baby.
You couldn't (bleep) sit down?
KIM: Yeah, it's really
(bleep) embarrassing.
(phone chimes)
Hold on.
Khloe's texting me right now,
I'll call you back.
(line ringing)
KHLOE: Hello?
KIM: Hey, are you okay?
KHLOE: Yeah.
KIM: Do you want me to come
down there? KHLOE: No. I'm fine.
KIM: Are y-you... did you say
you're trying to come back here
to L.A.? KHLOE: I would love to.
I need to figure that out.
KIM: Well, do you want me to
get you a plane and figure it
out?
Do you want me to...
KHLOE: I need to ask if I can
travel.
I'm gonna call Dr. A and see if
I can get out of here.
KIM: I mean, I think you-you
just have to worry about
yourself right now, and just be
calm, because...
KHLOE (crying): I can't be
calm. Not right now.
KIM: Okay.
KHLOE: I'm trying to figure
it out. I'll call you back.
KIM: Okay, bye.
I mean, I definitely feel
helpless, because she's
confused, she doesn't know what
to do, and we don't really know
what to do, but we want to be
there for her.
And honestly, it's like I'm in
shock. We love Tristan.
Like, this is just nothing that
we suspected.
We thought she finally found
her, you know, Prince Charming
happy ending, and then, (bleep).
It's just, why her?
Like, it just, it really, really
sucks.
SCOTT: They're both in the
same house right now?
KENDALL: No, she kicked him out.
He's, like, he left the house.
We're trying to get her to come
home. >> SCOTT: (bleep), man.
What... by the way... what the
(bleep) he even doing out in
the streets right now like that
anyway?
KENDALL: Right.
SCOTT: Like, I mean, she is
about to pop off, like...
Got to chill at home for a
minute. (Slurps)
I've really turned into such a
gentleman.
♪ ♪
KIM: You have an Instagram
account?
MJ: Yes.
KIM: What is your Instagram
account? MJ: Kimkardashian.com.
(both chuckle)
KIM: But what's your.
Instagram name?
MJ: I just push "Instagram."
KIM: Oh. MJ: I have the app.
KIM: Yeah. >> MJ: (chuckles)
Isn't that what you do?
KRIS: Hey, Mom.
MJ: Hi. KRIS: You look cute.
MJ: Well, thank you.
KRIS: Hi, Kimbo.
KIM: Hi, Mom.
MJ: Love your shoes, Krissy.
KRIS: Thank you.
MJ: They're so cute.
KRIS: Thanks.
KIM: Oh, so, I called Khloe
today, and I was like,
"Honestly, so many more stories"
have come out, so many friends
are calling me with, like, so
many more things."
MJ: I just found out, so I've
just, you know, I'm still
crying, so I can't...
KIM: Oh, you just found out.
MJ: Yeah.
KIM: Oh. MJ: I'm really sad.
Ruined my makeup. >> KIM: Yeah.
MJ: All the way over here.
KIM: You know, I told her,
"What is, what are you gonna get
out of him?"
I go, "Think about it.
You're gonna be worried and"
nervous and have an insecure
life, 'cause if he's not
faithful now..."
MJ: He'll never change.
KIM: Yeah, he'll never change.
When one thing comes out, you
kind of hope, like, "Okay, well",
maybe the video's old or maybe
it's a misunderstanding, maybe
"something," 'cause a picture
doesn't always tell the full
story.
But then, you know, two more
stories come out.
This is just, like, crazy.
And now, you know, you know it's
true.
MJ: Find-find a different type.
You know? >> KIM: Yeah.
MJ: An accountant or something.
KIM: Yeah. Preach, Grandma.
MJ: A preacher.
KIM: An accountant. (Both laugh)
KRIS: Okay, so I need your
attention.
KIM: Yeah?
KRIS: This university... Brown.
University... they have a class
called "Keeping Up with Keeping."
"Up." >> KIM: Yeah.
MJ: How cute.
KRIS: And I'm gonna surprise
the class by Skyping in.
Then I thought what I could do
is say that you're here, too...
KIM: Okay.
KRIS: And surprise you,
and MJ can pop in.
MJ: They'll be so excited.
KRIS: Where is Kourtney?
MJ: Upstairs getting her makeup.
KRIS: So I'll get on with
them now.
KIM: I can't believe they
have a class like that.
KRIS: Isn't that wild?
KIM: Yeah, to get credit for
school on our show... like,
that's crazy.
KRIS: The timing isn't great
with what's going on with Khloe.
KIM: But we can't really
reschedule the call, so, if
anything, it's like a good
distraction to get...
KRIS: For sure.
KIM: You know, our minds
off of everything. (Laughter)
KRIS: Hi, guys.
(indistinct chatter)
What are you...?
Oh, my God, it's all women?
ALL: Yes!
KRIS: Oh, that's so cool.
Well, hi. Happy Wednesday.
KIM: I could probably help
out with some reports.
(laughter)
That's crazy that you guys
actually get credit for this.
WOMAN: It's not that crazy,
because you guys are just so
relevant to American culture
that... and I think really, it
makes a lot of sense for us to
be studying you guys.
So, in general, why do you feel
like your family's become such
polarizing figures?
Where do you think that some of
that both positivity and
negativity comes from?
And then, how do you, I guess,
deal with that?
KIM: Sometimes I feel torn
about it, 'cause sometimes,
like, if I post a photo...
KOURTNEY: Hi, guys.
WOMAN: Oh, my God.
KIM: Welcome to the party.
KRIS: There she is.
KOURTNEY: Sorry. I was glamming.
KRIS: You're late, but go on.
KIM: Well, I think we've gone
through every crazy thing that
you could possibly imagine, and
we've shared that.
I think just people can relate
to that, whether they want us to
win or not.
I mean, it's so funny to me, the
people that are so bothered.
Like, I get it.
If it's not your thing, like,
it's not your thing, so don't...
You know, change the channel or
whatever, but at the end of the
day, people can criticize all
day long. We have each other.
(phone ringing)
KOURTNEY: Is that your phone?
KRIS: I don't know.
KIM: No. Um...
You don't know your ringtone?
KRIS: It's like everybody
else's. >> KOURTNEY: That's not
everybody else's.
KIM: It's not everyone else's
ringtone.
That's a really annoying, loud
KRIS: So, it's annoying,
okay. >> MJ: So they are normal.
KRIS: Just push the button.
WOMAN: We're wondering how
you balance your
responsibilities as both a
character on your show and also
a producer?
KIM: Kourtney?
KRIS: I think as far as...
What? You want to answer that?
KOURTNEY: They said you have
to check your phone right this
second.
KRIS: Oh. Okay, I got to go.
She's gonna answer that
question.
I'll be right back. KIM: Okay.
KOURTNEY: Um, I think...
I mean, we're always thinking
of, like... What?
KIM: Kourtney's not that good
at this role.
KOURTNEY: At producing?
(laughter)
No. I mean, people are always
coming up with fun things...
KRIS: Hey. No, but I can try
and get another plane.
Why? Are you contracting?
Ah, (bleep).
Okay, we should have come last
night. I knew it!
All right. No, I'm-I'm good.
I'm just, I'm gonna be calm.
I just, let me figure it out
and see how fast we can get out
of here.
She's in labor, like, full-blown
labor, and I'm in charge of
bringing the doctor.
Ah, (bleep).
I mean, what's gonna happen if.
Dr. A isn't there to deliver the
baby?
We've got to get there right
now.
It just doesn't get any worse.
KRIS: Hi. So, listen, Khloe's
in labor, so here's the thing.
Can you get to the airport by
5:00?
ALIABADI: Let me... Yeah.
Let me go see my last patient,
and I'll run out.
KRIS: Okay. Bye.
(whispering): I got to go.
Wrap it up.
I got to go. >> KIM: Okay.
KRIS: Do you want to just
pause them, or...?
KIM: Okay. One sec.
KRIS: I can't wait one
second.
KIM: Um, we have to go, but,
um, we are so excited that you
guys... this is actually a real
course. >> KRIS: She's in labor.
MJ: She's what?
KRIS: I think she's in labor.
MJ: I thought so, with this.
KRIS: Yeah, yeah, so I got to
go get on a plane.
WOMAN: Oh, thank you so much.
KOURTNEY: Okay, bye, guys.
KIM: Thanks, you guys. Bye.
KRIS: Okay, I got to go.
I just moved the plane up, and I
think she's in labor.
KIM: Okay, well, to when?
KRIS: I knew we should have
gone last night, I knew it.
KIM: Do you want me to go
with you?
KRIS: No, you come in a
couple of days.
I'm going, I'm bringing the
doctor.
KIM: I'll go.
Like, I don't care.
KRIS: Uh, the only thing that
frightens me is that she's gonna
have this baby before I can get
there, and then she's giving
birth alone.
KIM: Hey, are you okay?
KHLOE: Yeah.
KIM: Um, how are you feeling?
Do you want me to come with Mom,
'cause I could go?
KRIS: I got to go.
Bye, everybody.
I love you. >> KHLOE: Should the
contractions feel like period
cramps?
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: I'm here with Kourt and.
Grandma.
KHLOE: But they keep going
from different times, so I don't
understand if I'm feeling them.
KOURTNEY: Write it down.
KHLOE: Oh, no, one was at
9:43, one was at 8:21, one was
at 10:00 something.
KIM: I feel like I should go.
KHLOE: 9:28.
KOURTNEY: Yeah. >> KIM: Okay.
KHLOE: And now, another one
was at 3:50.
KIM: Okay, I'm gonna run and,
um, get my bag, and I'm gonna
come with Mom.
I'll call you right back.
KOURTNEY: Call Corey.
KIM: I'm on my way. Bye.
You know, when there's something
crazy that goes on in our
family, we just always drop
everything that we're doing and
go be supportive to them.
I obviously wanted to go to my
reunion, and I wanted to make
both work, but since my reunion
is in two days, it's like, game
over, it's doesn't matter.
I'm gonna go to Cleveland and be
there for her.
KHLOE: Mom's already
stressing me out.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KHLOE: When I said, "Hey, I"
think I'm having contractions,"
she said, "(bleep)."
And I go, "What?"
KOURTNEY: No, she comes in
the room.
She comes in the room and goes,
"I got to go.
I got to go, guys."
(Khloe laughs) Um...
KHLOE: She's just too much,
and then, I love Kim, and I love
all you guys, but, like, Kim...
You know, it's like everyone
wants me to make a decision
right this second, and I just
want to go and give birth, and
focus on that, and, like, try to
enjoy this, and try to enjoy it
with him.
PENELOPE: Mom, can we go
through my backpack?
KHLOE: As bad as... like, as
crazy as that sounds, I want to
enjoy this with him.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KHLOE: I don't want any
negativity in the delivery room.
I don't want anyone to talk
about it, make me feel
uncomfortable or him
uncomfortable.
Like, let's just act normal
for...
Give me a minute.
KOURTNEY: Yeah. Okay, I'll
keep you posted on what's going
on.
KHLOE: Okay, thank you.
KOURTNEY: Okay, bye.
MJ: Love you, Khlo.
KHLOE: So, the date is April
11, and it is 7:03 p.m., and
I've been having contractions
for quite some time, so I'm
waiting.
My family is getting on an
airplane from L.A., and the
doctor, so I just hope everyone
gets here in time.
And we're just excited to meet
you. Try to hold on a little bit
longer in there.
You've been cooking very well.
I love you, baby. Big belly.
ALEXA: I hope someone can get
in the air soon.
PRODUCER: Yeah.
They said five minutes.
I just asked.
MALIKA: I'm gonna have no
cuticles by the time I get to
Cleveland, I swear.
KOURTNEY: We had to find two
planes at the last second.
My mom's plane lands first with
the doctor.
They're leaving from LAX, and
then, Malika and Kim and I are
taking a jet from Van Nuys.
We just really want to make it
there in time.
KHLOE: When are you guys
taking off?
MALIKA: Um, we're waiting on
the plane right now.
WOMAN: The plane's getting
fuel right now.
They said we should be able to
get on it in five.
MALIKA: So, not too much
longer. >> KHLOE: Okay.
MALIKA: I will see you shortly.
Where's Sav? KHLOE: Downstairs.
MALIKA: Okay. I'll call him.
KHLOE: Okay.
MALIKA: All right. Bye, babe.
Hi.
SAVAS: What's up?
MALIKA: Let's have a little
chitchat.
It's very easy to think you need
to rush or panic... you know what
I mean... because she's gonna be
acting a fool in the passenger
seat...
SAVAS: Yeah, yeah.
MALIKA: Somewhat ignore that.
Also, you know, she's very
tough.
She's gonna try not to let you
help her do a lot of things.
Don't-don't-don't listen to her,
don't argue with her.
Just take it and move.
Let her focus on her
contractions. SAVAS: All right.
MALIKA: All right, thanks. Bye.
(indistinct chatter) Hi, Kimmy.
Can you believe it?
KIM: I know, I'm so excited.
MALIKA: I'm, like, look, we
all know the problem.
Let's just get on the solution.
KOURTNEY: Let's just what?
MALIKA: I said, we all know
the problem.
Let's just get on the solution.
KOURTNEY: I don't think there
is one.
MALIKA: Have the damn baby
and let her figure her life out.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
MALIKA: You know what I mean?
That's all... to me, that's the
best thing to do at this point.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, totally.
MALIKA: 'Cause she's gonna
feel...
KIM: She just doesn't want us
to, like, start drama in the
hospital, so...
MALIKA: Yeah, she said,
specifically, you be nice.
KIM: Yeah, so...
MALIKA: I said, "Don't worry.
I got Kimmy for you."
KIM: Yeah.
I'm gonna look at him and just
be, like...
MALIKA: That's what a big
sister's supposed to do.
Okay, not the second one, babe.
Do the look one, but not the...
KOURTNEY: I think the look
one's lame.
I think I would only do that.
MALIKA: You two are gonna be
a real problem for me.
He's definitely gonna have to
face you guys, but for her,
we're not even...
Like, just... "Hi."
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KIM: I don't even think "Hi."
MALIKA: Keep it cordial.
KIM: I think just like...
MALIKA: And you know what?
I actually like that.
'Cause that's decent.
KOURTNEY: I know how
important it is for Khloe to
have Tristan there, and I
actually really respect that,
but it's definitely going to be
awkward.
It's gonna be hard to even look
at him or be in the same room
with him.
It's like you are (bleep) with
all of us when you disrespect
one of us. KIM: I think I'm just
gonna look at him and be like,
"To be continued, (bleep).
It's not over."
KIM: On the next episode...
KHLOE: I really pray that my
sisters get to the hospital in
time.
KOURTNEY: How (bleep) insane
to be doing this by yourself?
KIM: How far out are we?
MAN: 25 minutes.
MALIKA: Oh, my God.
KOURTNEY: Hurry!
KIM: We can't miss this.
(Khloe groans, True cries)
KIM: I unfollowed Tristan on
Instagram.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: He said I'm trying to
start stuff and I'm an
instigator.
I'm, like, done, done with him.
Over it.
Captioning sponsored by
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS