TRISTAN: She's here! Hi, cutie.
KHLOE: Tristan obviously
(bleep) up, but I'm not sure how
I feel about anything right now.
In two weeks, I might say, "You"
know what, this isn't for me,"
or, "Let's keep it going."
Right now my focus is on True.
That's really what's important
to me.
KIM: Tristan, like, he should
be embarrassed.
I unfollowed him on Instagram.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: I'm, like, done.
Done with him. ♪ ♪
KIM: So, you wrote Khloe.
KOURTNEY: I just wrote her
saying hi.
KIM: She's like, "Please, I"
don't want you guys to fight."
I'm like, "I unfollowed him, and
I'm just letting you know."
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
Does he follow us?
KIM: I don't know.
That's gonna be a rule.
I'm not following any boyfriend
or anything, 'cause it's so
awkward when I have to unfollow.
You have to practically be
married in, at this point.
That's my rule.
(gasps) He blocked me.
What a (bleep) loser.
Literally, what a (bleep) loser.
I'm calling her right now.
(line ringing)
KHLOE (on phone): Hello?
KIM: Wait, he blocked me on.
Instagram.
Like, how old are you?
KHLOE: He's 27.
Only 27-year-olds even know how
to block.
I don't even know how to block
someone. >> KIM: Oh, it's on.
KHLOE: Oh, no.
Please don't do the "It's on."
What does that mean?
KIM: It just means when I see
him... I'm going to, like...
KHLOE: Yeah.
KIM: Spit on him.
Whatever, I'll save it all for
him; I won't stress you out.
I'll...
KHLOE: No, please tell me,
because I just have to know how
long I have to keep you guys
separated.
KIM: We can coexist.
I'll be nice.
KHLOE: No, I don't know if
you guys can coexist.
It's so crazy.
KIM: Yeah, I don't think we
can, actually. KHLOE: Hold on.
I got to go. >> KIM: Bye.
(phone beeps)
Your boyfriend's a (bleep)
loser. ♪ ♪
(dog barks)
SCOTT: Can you, like,
introduce me to the dog?
KENDALL: Six, come here.
SCOTT: Hi. (Kissing noises)
Well, is she like a little bit,
like... obsessed with me, or...?
KENDALL: She likes you.
It's 'cause you're petting her.
SCOTT: Oh.
So, what went on at the high
school reunion?
Were a lot of people there?
KIM: Yeah, it was amazing.
Me, I got a party bus.
I got a big Sprinter.
SCOTT: What?
KIM: I picked up Allison.
Do you know Amanda Lee?
SCOTT: Yeah.
KIM: My friend Sarah Hudson.
Amber Jenkins.
SCOTT: Well, you were fun,
right? At one time?
Like, you were, like, wild,
right, some of your years,
right? >> KIM: Yeah.
SCOTT: Yeah, it's so weird.
I can't, like, picture you
being, like, a wild child.
KIM: Really?
SCOTT: Can you?
KENDALL: No, but I heard
stories about you.
KIM: Like what?
KENDALL: I can't say it.
SCOTT: I've heard some stuff.
KIM: You can say it.
SCOTT: You went to, like,
Disney and you were all high or
something. Or Six Flags, or...
KENDALL: Yeah, I didn't know
you, like, got high.
KIM: I got married on ecstasy.
KENDALL: I had no idea.
KIM: No, the first time.
I did ecstasy once and got
married; I did it again, I made
a sex tape.
Like, everything bad would
happen. SCOTT: You were high on
ecstasy when you were in that
sex tape?
KIM: Absolutely.
Everyone knows it.
Like, my jaw was shaking.
Like the whole time, I'm like...
SCOTT: I thought that was
'cause of sucking the ol' zazee.
KIM (laughing): No, this is
my move. Yeah.
SCOTT: No, I-I can't see that.
KIM: When I first started to
travel, I remember one night.
Paris and I stayed in Ibiza.
We go to a foam party.
We leave the club at 7:00 a.m.
I'm like, "Guys, we're going to"
the beach."
So we go to the beach.
There was, like, buoys in the
water that made a big square,
and I'm like, "Let's sleep in
the ocean."
We locked arms on rafts, and we
spent the night in the ocean on
rafts.
KENDALL: I just can't believe
that that was you.
KIM: I still can do crazy
things. >> KENDALL: Okay.
SCOTT: Sure. KENDALL: Prove it.
(Scott laughs)
KIM: Kendall honestly has,
like, no clue.
I definitely went through a wild
phase.
I would say in, like, my late
teens.
I'm not like that anymore.
But, like, I still have fun.
Don't get it twisted.
I'm always the life of the
party.
SCOTT: Hi.
KENDALL: You can tell her
"off." She likes you.
SCOTT: Oh! This goddamn dog's
a whore.
(Kendall laughs) ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: What about these?
KHADIJAH: Those are cute.
KOURTNEY: You want to put
these in?
PENELOPE: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: So, two people from.
EWG, it's this nonprofit
organization, Environmental.
Working Group, are coming over.
KHADIJAH: Okay.
KOURTNEY: They have this app
that I've been using for years.
And it's called Healthy Living,
and you can scan, like, cleaning
supplies, beauty products,
food... like, different things.
KHADIJAH: Mm-hmm.
KOURTNEY: And they score it.
They give it a score to tell you
how good or bad it is.
KHADIJAH: That's pretty cool.
KOURTNEY: Having three kids,
it's important to me to be
conscious of product
ingredients. Hi.
NNEKA: Hi.
KOURTNEY: How are you?
NNEKA and KOURTNEY: It's good
to see you.
KOURTNEY: Hi. How are you.
JOCELYN: Hi. Nice to see you
again.
KOURTNEY: Some of the women
from EWG reached out to me about
their mission and ways I could
potentially get involved.
I really didn't realize how, you
know, that these products
weren't regulated.
Now I feel like I need to look
up every kid product that I'm
using.
I've done it before, but I feel
like it's, like, you constantly
have to be doing it.
And, like, even if it says
natural.
JOCELYN: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: That's crazy that
that doesn't mean...
KHADIJAH: That scares me so
much. JOCELYN: Right? And, like,
the color of the bottle doesn't
matter, and, like, a lot of
people are like, "Oh, it looked
really natural."
KHADIJAH: The packaging's
cute. Yeah.
JOCELYN: "It said recycled."
And just 'cause it's recycled
doesn't mean the actual
chemicals inside of it are good
for you or for the environment.
NNEKA: We realized that most
people don't know that personal
care products aren't very
regulated.
I just thought that all the
products on store shelves met
this very vigorous standard.
JOCELYN: Oh, me, too. Yeah.
NNEKA: That's not required
now.
Right now, we as consumers are
all the guinea pigs, because
these products aren't tested.
KHADIJAH: That's really scary.
NNEKA: Some baby wipes
have an ingredient called
methylisothiazolinone.
Kids started to get these rashes
that spread their entire face,
and the company had to take the
ingredient out of the wipes.
KHADIJAH: So crazy.
NNEKA: Triphenyl phosphate,
that's a flame retardant.
It's in nail polish, and it
soaks right through your
cuticles and gets into your
body.
JOCELYN: So, like, the same
flame retardant we, like, would
treat our couches or rugs with?
NNEKA: Yeah.
Red lipstick will have lead.
KOURTNEY: No matter what.
NNEKA: It just will. Yeah.
If you're pregnant, you should
avoid it.
JOCELYN: We did a test, and
babies are born pre-polluted
with over 300... 287 industrial
components.
NNEKA: And also, when you
look at the European laws,
there's more than a thousand
ingredients banned or restricted
versus the 11 here.
That disparity is just too...
it's too striking.
KOURTNEY: It's crazy that
it's up to us to really do the
research and figure it out, you
know.
NNEKA: The law hasn't been
updated since 1938, so we're
working really, really hard to
update the personal care law and
get a bill passed that would
ensure that products are safe
before they go on store shelves,
and we'd love your help to get
some attention.
JOCELYN: You're welcome to
come to Washington to lobby with
us, or...
KHADIJAH: Lobby, Kourt. Yeah.
KOURTNEY: I would love to.
JOCELYN: Yes!
KOURTNEY: I feel like my
sisters are always saying, "Oh,
you don't have a passion."
You don't have your own
project."
But this is something that I do
feel strongly about.
We should be able to walk into a
store and safely shop for
personal care products.
And I know I'm not the most
political person, but if going
to Washington is going to help
push their cosmetic law through,
then I'm happy to do it.
Well, thank you, guys.
JOCELYN: Oh, yeah. Thank you.
NNEKA: Absolutely.
KOURTNEY: I'm so happy you
guys are here, but the second
you leave, I'm going upstairs
with Khadijah, and we're gonna
scan...
KHADIJAH: And we're gonna
pull everything out on the
counter. NNEKA: Like, scanning
everything. ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Why are you so
close? Is that a...?
Or am I just really far?
KIM: So close?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, don't I...
I just look so far back.
KIM: Oh, I don't know.
Oh, like, so close to the thing?
Can you call Khloe?
KOURTNEY: Have you talked to
her? (Phone ringing)
KIM: Yeah, I mean, a little
bit... just, like, "How's the"
baby?" and, "What's going on?"
KOURTNEY: I call her.
I try to call her every day, but
just try to talk about the baby.
One time, she was like, "You're
stressing me out."
I get anxious whenever you guys
call."
KHLOE: Hello. KOURTNEY: Hi.
KHLOE: Hi. >> KIM: Hey.
KHLOE: Hey.
KIM: How's Cleveland?
(Khloe laughs)
KHLOE: Everything's good.
KOURTNEY: How's True?
KHLOE: She's so good.
She's so cute.
KOURTNEY: She's so cute,
I can't take it.
KHLOE: Oh, my God. Thank you.
She's already getting so much
bigger.
KIM: Well, good.
We can't wait to see you, so...
KOURTNEY: I know. When are
you coming?
Like, come already.
KHLOE: We will be home soon.
KOURTNEY: Wait, so...
how's Tristan?
(Khloe laughs)
KHLOE: Uh, he's good.
He's good. >> KOURTNEY: What?
KIM: How's my boy?
KHLOE (laughs): He's good.
I'm just, you know, in a tough
situation, 'cause my sister and
my boyfriend hate each other.
(Kim chuckles quietly)
KIM: I still can't believe
that Tristan blocked me.
I mean, that's just too petty
for me, and I could go there in
the petty department.
I know Khloe wants us to be cool
with Tristan when they get back,
but I still, you know, hold this
resentment towards him.
KHLOE: I'm strong enough that
I can deal with everything
personally, but she deserves to
have bonding time with both of
her parents.
It's not her fault what's going
on.
KOURTNEY: Nope, it's not.
KIM: It's not easy for me
just to forget the fact that he
broke Khloe's heart.
I can't really get over that
right now.
Hi, guys. >> OTHERS: Hi.
KIM: I'm going to Vegas with
all of my high school friends.
To a night off to have fun.
SARAH: And to Cher.
KIM: We're going to the Cher
concert.
I'm gonna try to relive my
crazy, wild years.
Oh, my gosh.
FABER: Tomorrow at the
briefing, your job is to urge
Congress to do their job.
KOURTNEY: Who is this in
front of?
FABER: Reporters and about
60 staff.
KOURTNEY: I definitely have a
fear of public speaking.
FABER: Your voice right now
is really important.
(Scott gasps)
SCOTT: True... dat!
KHLOE: It's exciting that we
get to see the family again and
all her cousins, but Kim and
Tristan have not been in the
same room together since they've
had that talk in Cleveland.
KIM: Should I go say hi to
my bestie?
♪ ♪
KIM: After talking to Kendall
and Scott, I decided I need a
fun night out.
So I'm going to Vegas.
Hi, guys. >> OTHERS: Hi.
KIM: I'm bringing all of my
high school friends, like, my
clique.
We used to hang out all night
long back in the day. SARAH: Hi!
KIM: I've got Sarah, who is
the free-spirited artist.
Hi. >> AMBER: Hi.
KIM: Amber, the life of the
party.
You look so cute!
Simone, the trendsetter.
AMANDA: Hey.
KIM: Amanda, the quiet one.
FLORIANA: Hi.
KIM: And Floriana, the mama
bear. How are you?
FLORIANA: So jelly of all
this hair.
SIMONE: You're in your Cher
hair!
KIM: It only took three hours
to put in. No big deal.
Oh, my God, is there still clips
in my hair?
We're going to the Cher concert.
Cher is the most iconic singer
on the planet, and she's, like,
my biggest style inspiration.
AMBER: Are you guys all
dressing up like Cher?
KIM: I have two wardrobe
changes.
She literally has the best
clothes, the best hair, the
best nails, the best, like,
everything.
Shelli Azoff knows how much I
love Cher, so she gives me this
box, and I, like, open it, and
it's this turquoise bracelet,
and then it's this scarf, and I
was like, "Oh, that's so nice."
"Thanks." AMBER: Wait, it's hers?
KIM: It's, like, the scarf
was something that she used to
wear during Sonny and Cher days.
AMBER: Oh, my God.
KIM: And then the bracelet
was Cher's for years, and...
FLORIANA: Wow.
KIM: But it was, like, really
sentimental to her, so I'm
wearing it tonight.
SIMONE: Did you bring it?
FLORIANA: I was just gonna
say, add the scarf or no?
KIM: I didn't bring the
scarf, 'cause it just didn't go,
but I really want to wear...
AMBER: I can't wait to see it.
KIM: The turquoise
bracelet. Yeah.
AMBER: I told my coworker
I'm gonna go see Cher.
She says, "Wait, who's Cher?"
SIMONE (gasps): What?! No.
KIM: How do you not know that?
SARAH: How do you not know?
KIM: Like, I would feel sad
to be working with that person.
(laughter)
♪ ♪
ANDREW: How was your flight?
KOURTNEY: It was good.
ANDREW: Yeah?
KOURTNEY: So, the reason
we're here... >> ANDREW: Yeah?
KOURTNEY: Is I'm running
for president.
(laughing)
I am so excited to be in D.C.
I brought my friend Sarah.
She's one of my best friends
since high school.
She's a beauty blogger, and she
is really into politics, so I
thought she was the perfect
person to bring along.
We're going to meet with the EWG
staff to talk about what we're
going to be doing while I'm
here. Hi. How are you?
JOCELYN: Hi. Have a seat.
KOURTNEY: Hi. Kourtney.
WOMAN: Nice to meet you.
You picked a good day to be in.
Washington. >> HOWARD: Why?
WOMAN 2: 'Cause it's just
gorgeous.
KOURTNEY: It is.
JOCELYN: So, we just wanted
to start off by thanking you for
taking your time to be here on
behalf of this issue, and it
means a lot to have a voice like
yours. FABER: To be honest, I've
never seen as many staff respond
as quickly to the news that
you're going to be on
Capitol Hill.
KOURTNEY: Really? How exciting.
ADRIENNE: We need powerful
outside voices such as yours
being here to really advocate
for the causes that we believe,
so thank you for being here.
FABER: Congress is really
close to finally producing a law
that sets limits on what kinds
of chemicals can be added to
cosmetics and other personal
care products for the first time
in 80 years, and having you here
is exactly what we need right
now to get this bill into a law
and across the finish line.
So tomorrow at the briefing for.
Senate staff, your job is just
to tell your story and why you
care and urge Congress to do
their job.
KOURTNEY: And this is... who
is this in front of?
FABER: There will be some
reporters there, and then
there'll be about 50 or 60
staff.
They're the people who
ultimately will decide: Is this
important enough for Congress to
act on this year?
So your voice right now is
really important.
KOURTNEY: This is the closest
that EWG has gotten to pushing
their cosmetic law through.
I didn't realize that I'm, like,
the final push.
HOWARD: You're gonna crush
it. FABER: Yeah, you're gonna do
great. All right.
KOURTNEY: All right, see you
in the morning.
I definitely have a fear of
public speaking.
I don't really know, like,
what I'm gonna say.
I just don't want to mess up.
I was about to have a heart
attack.
HOWARD: They just kept being
like, "Thank you for being the"
voice.
Like, you're helping to get
this onto the floor."
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God.
HOWARD: I was like, "Wait.
Kourt's the spokesperson?"
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God.
HOWARD: Like, she's the
make-or-break of this?
I was dying!
♪ ♪
KHLOE: We are back in
California.
I really haven't seen anyone
since I've been in Cleveland,
since I gave birth, so today
Scott gets to meet True for the
first time.
SCOTT: What's going on?
KENDALL: Not much.
Just here, you know, chillin'.
(Scott gasps)
SCOTT: True... dat!
KENDALL: Have you met her?
SCOTT: No.
KENDALL: Swear. >> KHLOE: No.
Do you know how to hold a baby?
SCOTT: I have three.
KHLOE: She just ate.
SCOTT: Whoa, she's so soft.
Who's your boo-boo?
KRIS: What are you doing?
SCOTT: Who's your baby?
KRIS: Mama just took the
cutest pictures today.
SCOTT: I can't believe you
have your own child.
Khloe has been so good with all
my kids, and I just feel like,
finally, thank God it's her
turn. >> KHLOE: Is that funny?
(blows raspberry)
SCOTT: And it's so obvious
she's already such a good mom.
KRIS: How come you look just
like your dad?
You're a little Tristan twin.
SCOTT: True is so cute.
She is such a ball of love.
She's literally just one big
cute bowling ball of a baby.
So, True, how do you feel? Okay.
(Kendall laughs) How are you?
KRIS: Are you adjusting okay?
KHLOE: Um, it's fine.
I mean, it's great.
SCOTT: You don't have that
water view anymore.
KHLOE: Don't have that water
view, but I got a mountain view
now.
At first, I was a little
nervous, like, just, like,
anxious.
Like, to go from, like, no one
ever visiting or anything to,
like, the overwhelming...
KRIS: Stimulation? KHLOE: Sure.
It's exciting that we get to see
the family again and all her
cousins, but Kim and Tristan
have not been in the same room
together since they've had that
talk in Cleveland.
So it's just awkward for me.
I'm in a very uncomfortable
position, and I don't know how
they're both gonna act.
I'm like, what is gonna happen
when they get face-to-face?
KOURTNEY: We're going in the
morning to speak to the Senate,
and literally, I don't speak.
Part of me wishes that I didn't
have to do this.
I was trying to think of ways to
get out of it.
KIM: I was able to pull off a
backstage meeting with Cher.
Do they have any water anywhere?
I feel like I'm gonna faint,
'cause I'm meeting Cher.
Oh, my God! AMBER: Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
SIMONE: Oh, my gosh.
KIM: Marymount Sailors, you
guys.
AMBER: Oh! No way.
SIMONE: Oh, my God.
AMBER: We always had the best
balloon surprise.
(all laugh) >> SIMONE: So cute.
Wait, what? Oh, my God.
SARAH: Oh, my God, Amber.
FLORIANA: Amber!
AMBER: Why are we so gangster?
(all laugh)
KIM: The high school reunion
continues in Vegas. ALL: Cheers!
SIMONE: We have to, uh, look
each other in the eyes.
AMANDA: Wow. Very serious.
FLORIANA: So intense.
AMBER: Amanda? Jokes?
KIM: Can I get in my Cher
outfit? (Sarah laughs)
AMANDA: Let's do it.
KIM: My favorite thing in
life to do is to wear Cher
looks.
I love recreating looks that
she's done.
FLORIANA: Cher's here.
SARAH: Ready?
KIM: Yeah. >> SARAH: Go.
KIM: If I could dress up like
Cher every single day, that
would literally make my life.
Oh, (bleep).
My nail keeps coming off.
AMANDA: How did you put them
on?
Did you literally just, like,
glue them?
KIM: Like, press on, like...
SARAH: Like, Lee Press-on?
KIM: Yeah.
(all laugh)
SERVER: How's everyone doing?
Does anyone need a drink or
beverage?
KIM: Yes. Can we get...
shots of...
AMBER: Shut up. KIM: Tequila.
SARAH: What? AMBER: No. No.
KIM: Do we want tequila?
SIMONE: Kim!
KIM: Okay, okay, vodka.
Vodka, okay, vodka.
Tonight we're drinking.
I'm definitely gonna, like, just
have fun and try to relive my
crazy, wild years.
To reuniting after 20 years.
And I'm so glad that we're in.
Vegas, and just to, like, a
night off to have fun.
SARAH: Yes.
FLORIANA: Absolutely.
SARAH: And to Cher.
ALL: To Cher!
SIMONE: Yes. We have to look
in the eyes.
AMBER: Okay.
Just do it, just one shot.
Go, go. (All whooping, laughing)
KIM: Oh, my God. ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I just took a photo
of us in the bathroom, but tell
me if it's even okay.
ANDREW: Yeah, why not?
KOURTNEY: Should I write,
like, "businesswomen"?
ANDREW: You're twins.
Like, literally.
KOURTNEY: Should I write...
ANDREW: No, "career girl"
special."
WOMAN: "A businesswomen
ANDREW: No, no, it's "career
girl special."
Actually, I think you're right.
(all laugh)
So, how did the meeting go?
KOURTNEY: It was good.
We were gonna cancel the press
conference tomorrow.
ANDREW: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: But it's not really
a press conference.
It's, like, that's when I'm
speaking in front of the Senate.
ANDREW: Oh, okay.
HOWARD: And then House staff
later, 'cause they do it
separately.
ANDREW: So, are you, like...
KOURTNEY: So, the Senate
staff...
ANDREW: Are you behind the
thing with your, like, little
name...
KOURTNEY: No, so literally, I
don't speak.
Like, when I had to speak for
Jen Atkin, I thought I was gonna
start crying. I was like...
ANDREW: Well, luckily, you
brought yourself to Washington
to talk in front of, like,
politicians.
WOMAN: What are you gonna do?
KOURTNEY: So I was trying to
think of ways to get out of it,
and, like, be like, "My
publicist doesn't want me to do
this."
ANDREW: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: And I didn't even
tell my sisters or anyone that I
was coming and doing this.
They're so judgmental on my...
whatever I'm doing.
After they say that I never have
my passion.
HOWARD: That's because they
just want to be you.
Don't worry about it.
KOURTNEY: They really do.
My sisters can just be very
critical.
I already put enough pressure on
myself as it is.
Like, I'm worried, what if I say
the wrong thing tomorrow and
let everyone down?
Part of me wishes that I didn't
have to do this.
HOWARD: I think you just need
to show that you're serious,
and I think you are serious
about it. ♪ ♪
(all laugh)
SIMONE: Oh, my God, Kim, you
look amazing.
KIM: And I have new nails.
SIMONE: Oh, you do.
KIM: Yeah, I-I'll do anything
for, like, a good look.
Like, it doesn't matter.
SIMONE: Wow.
SARAH: What are we doing?
FLORIANA: I want to get in.
KIM: Ooh, the smell of this
vodka.
Oh, I'm gonna throw up.
ALL: Cheers!
(Simone whoops) (Sarah whistles)
AMANDA: Look in the eyes.
AMBER: Look in the eyes.
SIMONE: I'm done looking in
the eyes.
AMBER: I'm not done.
SARAH: I can't even see any
of your eyes anyway.
(Simone laughs)
FLORIANA: Oh, my God, are you
guys that wasted?
Oh, my God. She is.
SARAH: And I'm gagging.
KIM: Oh, my God.
FLORIANA: You're good now.
KIM: Guys, one more shot?
One more shot?
SIMONE: Like, are you
really...? KIM: Yeah, why not?
I never go out unless it's with
my kids.
(all whooping) >> SIMONE: Okay.
KIM: We're going to see Cher!
So, I was able to pull off a
backstage meeting with Cher
after her show.
I met her one time at the Met
Ball.
My friends are so excited just
to meet her and to hang out with
her a little bit. ♪ ♪
AMBER: Kim, so, what are you
gonna say when you meet Cher?
Are you gonna be like...
FLORIANA: I dare you.
AMBER: You're gonna be like,
"I'm obsessed with you."
KIM: She knows.
AMANDA: She knows.
AMBER: Do you play it cool,
or are you like, "I'm obsessed"
with you?"
KIM: No, I'll say I'm obse...
I like to, I like to be, like...
AMANDA: Honest.
AMBER: Totally honest.
KIM: Like, she's the queen.
FLORIANA: She still is.
KIM: I was like, "I would"
love you to be my mom.
I'm obsessed with you."
Like, you got to give it up,
you know?
Like, there's no one like her.
SIMONE: Nobody. 100%.
We're here? >> KIM: Yeah.
FLORIANA: Oh, (bleep).
KIM: You guys!
(all shrieking) >> SIMONE: Cher!
♪ ♪
KIM: In high school, we would
get so dressed up and go to
concerts all the time, so
nothing has changed.
We're all so dressed up, going
to a concert.
It's just in Vegas, and we're 20
years older.
It's, like, it's so funny just
to see us all back together.
(audience cheering)
("Welcome to Burlesque" playing)
CHER: ♪ You may not be Guilty
But you're ready to confess... ♪
KIM: Ah. Like, this is
everything. I love Cher.
CHER: ♪ Welcome to Burlesque
Oh, everyone is buying
♪ Put your money in my hand
If you got a little extra
Well, give it to the band... ♪
KIM: Oh, my God.
This concert is so much fun, and
my friends are having a good
time. >> AMBER: Uh, which one...
FLORIANA: Oh, Amber.
AMBER: Oh, my God.
(all laugh)
KIM: Chris, do I need a hair
touch-up?
APPLETON: That was so good.
KIM: It was so good.
APPLETON: She's amazing.
KIM: Her body.
APPLETON: Banging.
KIM: Oh, my God.
I'm dying to see if Cher
remembers what I'm wearing.
Is she coming? Is she coming?
I completely, like, copied one
of her looks.
AMBER: Oh, my God, Kim.
You look so cute.
KIM: I'm really curious to
know if she's, like, flattered
or thinks it's, like, beyond
desperate.
Do they have any water anywhere?
I feel like I'm gonna faint
'cause I'm meeting Cher.
Oh, my God!
MAN: Okay, you guys ready?
(Kim gasps)
AMBER: Oh, my God.
KHLOE: It's Taco Tuesday,
Kimberly. >> KIM: What?
No one invited me?
I-I mean, I know that she's
trying to just keep me and
Tristan apart.
Like, I wouldn't want drama
myself.
JOCELYN: So, you will be
walking into a full room.
KOURTNEY: I didn't really
realize this was, like, a
full-on press conference.
(indistinct chatter)
I hope that I don't let my
nerves get the best of me.
KIM: Is she coming?
Is she coming?
I feel like I'm gonna faint
'cause I'm meeting Cher.
Oh, my God!
SIMONE: I feel like I heard
her.
She might be, like, right there
waiting in the wing. Oh, my God!
Hi! >> KIM: Hi, queen.
(Simone whoops)
CHER: Hi. Hi. Hi.
AMBER: Oh, my God.
CHER: Hello, ladies.
ALL: Hi!
KIM: These are my high school
friends.
This was, like, we were all best
friends in high school.
CHER: Where-where is your...
where is your high school?
KIM: It was in Los Angeles,
right across from UCLA.
Called Marymount.
All-girls Catholic school.
CHER: Cool.
I went to Catholic school for
about a minute and a half.
(all laugh)
Before recorded time.
KIM: How are you?
I have to give you a hug.
CHER: I'm good, how are you?
KIM: Good.
CHER: Wait a minute, I
remember this.
KIM: Do you rec...?
I-I knew you would.
Wait, my nails... some of them
fell off, but...
CHER: No, it's good.
It's a good...
Yeah, yeah, you did a good job.
KIM: I made this yesterday.
CHER: You did?
KIM: Yeah, I bought, like,
three jackets and cut it up and
tried to get something similar.
CHER: Cool, very cool.
Oh, nice, girl.
Good girl.
KIM: Thank you so much.
I try.
CHER: Reminds me of the old
days.
KIM: My dream of life is to
see your closet.
Did you archive everything?
CHER: Did I? Everything?
KIM: Do you have, like...
CHER: I don't have, uh,
no, I don't have everything.
I kept the things I love.
I kind of wish I would have kept
a few more things, but...
KIM: Yeah.
CHER: But I have the ones
I love.
KIM: You're my everything
inspiration.
CHER: Keep going.
KIM: No, seriously.
(laughter) Seriously. Like...
CHER: No, I don't mean...
I don't mean keep going and
telling me anything.
I mean, "Keep going."
You keep going. >> KIM: Yes.
(laughter)
CHER: Are you Armenian, too?
FLORIANA: No, I'm Argentinian.
But I got a little of
everything.
CHER: Okay, good. (Laughs)
KIM: But seriously, I mean,
everything you've done for the
Armenian community has been
amazing.
CHER: I want to go back.
KIM: They love you.
I want to go back.
SARAH: Maybe you guys
should go back together.
KIM: Yeah. I would love to.
CHER: The reason we should go
back is 'cause all kinds of bad
things are happening, and we
need to make a presence.
FLORIANA: You guys really
should. >> KIM: Anytime.
CHER: All right, well, we can
make a... we can make a thing.
KIM: Well, thank you for, you
know, meeting with us after the
show. I know you're probably
exhausted.
Just wanted to say hi.
CHER: Like a little sister.
KIM: Just excited.
Just excited to see the show.
CHER: It was good to see you
guys.
It was good to meet all of you,
really. >> FLORIANA: Thank you.
So nice to meet you. CHER: Okay.
KIM: Thank you.
CHER: Good-bye, girls.
FLORIANA: Thank you so much!
Thank you!
KIM: Bye.
I was just happy to, like,
literally just be in her
presence.
You guys, we just hung out with
Cher, no big deal.
I honestly haven't been out like
this in so long.
It's probably 1:00 or 2:00 in
the morning, and we're flying
home.
I'm so tired, but it was so
worth it. FLORIANA: Look at Kim.
AMBER: I know, Kim's all
ready to nap.
♪ ♪
KIM: I can't believe I'm
doing long nails.
(manicurist laughs)
MANICURIST: Well, they're not
cut yet, so they're really fun.
KIM: I know.
(phone rings) >> KHLOE: Hello.
KIM: Hi. >> KHLOE: Hi.
KIM: I'm getting long nails
for you.
KHLOE: Oh, my goodness!
That's so great!
KIM: I know.
I knew you would love it.
I'm feeling very much like you.
KHLOE: Oh, my God!
Can someone shut the door here?
KIM: Where are you?
KHLOE: It's Taco Tuesday,
Kimberly.
Get with it, okay? >> KIM: What?
No one invited me?
KHLOE: We didn't know you
would want to come.
KIM: So, I mean, I know that
she's trying to just keep me
and Tristan apart, and I get
that.
Like, I wouldn't want drama
myself, but, I mean, what can I
do?
KHLOE: Okay. KIM: All right.
Love you. I'll call you later.
KHLOE: Okay.
KIM: Okay, bye.
Very mature... things we've got
going on here.
MANICURIST: Right. (Laughs)
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Sarah, the clutch
or my fanny pack?
But I would just hold it, like,
over my shoulder like that.
HOWARD: I like that, but I
think that's more business-y.
So I don't know what vibe you
want.
You look very profesh.
KOURTNEY: Thank you.
It's a pretty big day.
I'm going to speak to Congress
and the Senate.
I'm still a little bit nervous
about how it will go.
HOWARD: Thank you.
KOURTNEY: All right, where
are we going?
HOWARD: This way. KOURTNEY: Hi!
WOMEN: Good morning! Hi!
KOURTNEY: I'm sorry we're
late.
I don't know what happened.
ADRIENNE: You look amazing.
No, the traffic can be insane.
Good morning. Hi.
WOMAN: Good morning.
Nice to see you.
KOURTNEY: Nice to see you.
HOWARD: Yeah. We had a really
good dinner.
KOURTNEY: We had a good dinner.
JOCELYN: Hi. Nice to see you.
KOURTNEY: Wait, are we so
late?
Are we, like, walking in to,
like... Okay.
JOCELYN: Yes. Yeah.
Um, Scott and Pen started it
already.
We have it set up as a
conversational style, and
everyone... so you will be
walking into a full room.
KOURTNEY: Okay.
JOCELYN: There's, like, an
aisle and stuff.
We're gonna go to the right.
KOURTNEY: Hi.
GUARD: Step through.
KOURTNEY: I didn't really
realize this was, like, a
full-on press conference.
So I hope that I don't let my
nerves get the best of me.
FABER: So, maybe just to
start, maybe talk a little bit
about when you first became
concerned about the chemicals in
cosmetics.
KOURTNEY: Um, well...
(clears throat)
KIM: Khloe's in town, and I
just haven't seen her.
SCOTT: How's that even possible?
KIM: I just feel like
Tristan's here, and she's so
nervous for him and I to see
each other.
I don't want to have any more
distance between me and Khloe,
so I'm going to extend an olive
branch.
Where's Tristan?
Should I go say hi to my bestie?
KHLOE: I don't want just to
have fighting in the house.
FABER: So, maybe just to
start, maybe you could talk a
little bit about when you first
became concerned about the
chemicals in cosmetics.
KOURTNEY: Um, well...
(clears throat)
When I had my first son, I
started learning a lot about the
foods that, you know, I was
giving him, and then it
snowballed into learning a lot
about products, and... you know,
I would find out that they had a
lot of harmful chemicals.
To me, it was just really
shocking that you can buy baby
products and products for
children that are not safe.
It shouldn't be up to parents or
consumers, really, to have to do
that much research.
FABER: Right.
KOURTNEY: You know, it's time
that Congress does its job.
(laughter, applause)
FABER: There you go.
KOURTNEY: I never really
thought that I would be here
speaking in front of Congress
and Senate. BALDWIN: We're still
plugging away on this issue,
and thank you for your advocacy.
KOURTNEY: Yes.
BALDWIN: Really appreciate
it. KOURTNEY: We're so happy to
be here.
I feel like I'm getting my
points across well and people
are really understanding why
it's so important.
PALLONE: Yeah, you know,
I have two daughters,
and as they were growing up,
they always assumed that if they
were buying something, somebody
had looked at it and said it was
safe.
And when I told them that that's
not true, they were like, "How"
"can that be?" >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
I was nervous, but I'm just
happy that I could be here to
lend my voice and hopefully
make a difference.
HOWARD: No, no, no. Like...
KOURTNEY: Wait, should we
take a photo?
Paxy, do you want to take it?
Do you want to take it?
PAXY: Do I ever!
KOURTNEY: I have to look like
a boss.
HOWARD: Ow! Ow! Oh.
PAXY: Okay, ready?
HOWARD: Oh, what? Here I come.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: This is, like, the
nicest gym ever.
KIM: Really?
SCOTT: Well, I mean...
it's, like, pretty.
Like, all the equipment's
black, and the floors are nice.
What else is shaking?
KIM: Um...
SCOTT: This is some good, uh,
good piece of equipment.
(screams)
No one heard that, did they?
KIM: So, I feel like Khloe is
living a full double life.
SCOTT: What do you mean?
KIM: She's in town, and I
just haven't seen her.
SCOTT: How's that even
possible? KIM: I just feel like.
Tristan's here, and she's so
nervous for him and I to see
each other.
I feel like I get into this
protection mode, where I just,
like...
SCOTT: Yeah, I mean, I think
everybody...
KIM: Go into, like,
worst-case scenario.
SCOTT: Wants to be
protective of their family.
KIM: Yeah.
SCOTT: But I think sometimes
when people get too caught up
when it's, like, a negative
protection and not always being
there when the positive, then
everybody feels kind of, like,
attacked.
KIM: Is it annoying when,
like, family members start
ganging up on you?
SCOTT: Listen, no matter what
you say to somebody, when
there's something happening in
their life, it's not actually
going to be taken in.
Like, I know back in the day,
when your mom or Khloe would get
involved with me and Kourtney's
stuff, it only would draw us
farther away from the family.
Never pulled anybody in and made
people more comforted.
And now, look, it's, like,
you're being protective 'cause
you love your sister, but guess
what, now your sister's in
Calabasas, home, and doesn't
want to see you.
So it's, like, what did you
solve? Whatever.
A good set. ♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: I just want a
couple bites.
Oh, thank you.
HOWARD: Oh, thanks.
KOURTNEY: Khloe just wrote to
the group chat, "Why is Kourtney"
in D.C."? (Howard laughs)
And I go, "I'm lobbying."
And she's like, "Yeah, right."
I'll call Khloe. (Line ringing)
KHLOE: Hello? KOURTNEY: Hi.
So, I came to Washington, D.C.,
and I literally, this morning I
had to get... go in front of the
Senate, and literally, I...
It was a Q & A, so I was sitting
in a chair, like, with this guy
who... from this organization
called EWG.
So I'm here to try to, like...
I was lobbying, and just to,
like, get them to try to make
some changes.
HOWARD: She killed it.
I have a video.
KHLOE: Kourtney, I'm so proud
of you.
Oh, my God!
KOURTNEY: And they...
KHLOE: I'm so, so proud of you.
KOURTNEY: Thank you.
And so, um, I was like, "Of
course it's coming out..."
KHLOE: I can't believe you
had the... KOURTNEY: The balls?
KHLOE: Like, the... Yeah.
KOURTNEY: I just feel like
you guys are so judgmental about
everything I do, and you guys
will be like, "Oh, please.
You're going to help with the"
"beauty laws," or something.
I don't know. Organic.
KHLOE: Prove me wrong every
day of the week.
I'm fine with that.
KOURTNEY: Um...
KHLOE: I love when you prove
me wrong.
Listen, when I looked online, I
was like, "What?!"
(Kourtney laughs)
What year is this?
I go, "Where have I been?"
HOWARD: That's amazing.
KOURTNEY: The news got out
that I'm in D.C.
It was nice to hear Khloe say
how proud she was of me for
really going and trying to make
a difference.
I feel so good about the way
that I spent the last two days,
and I've learned so much.
And I really want to just keep
doing more of this.
I have to make a phone call
later. I've just been, you know,
meeting with Congress and
Senate.
HOWARD: You're passing
legislation.
KHLOE: You've been lobbying
all day.
KOURTNEY: And the House of
Representatives.
Is that what it's called?
(laughs)
♪ ♪
KIM: Knock, knock.
KHLOE: Who's there?
KIM: Hi, guys.
KOURTNEY: Kim, you're so
skinny, you look like a
bobblehead.
KHLOE: Oh, I love when I look
like a bobblehead.
KIM: What?
KOURTNEY: You're so skinny.
KHLOE: That's the best
compliment.
KIM: Thank you!
I don't want to have any more
distance between me and Khloe.
I want to, you know, hang out
with our babies and enjoy my
time with my sisters.
So I'm gonna extend an olive
branch, 'cause, I mean, that's
really all I can do.
Where's Tristan?
KHLOE: In the theater.
KIM: Should I go say hi to
my bestie?
KHLOE: Can I go with you?
KIM: No, I can handle it.
KHLOE: Oh, my God.
Kim going into the theater to
see Tristan, obviously, like, my
heart is racing.
I have a ton of anxiety.
I don't want just to have
fighting in the house.
KIM: Where's my bestie?
KHLOE: Uh-oh.
Give me your audio thing.
I need to hear what's happening.
Oh, my God. >> KIM: Hi.
TRISTAN: What's going on?
KIM: Um...
Have you ever played pickleball?
KHLOE: She's like, "Have you"
ever played pickleball?"
KIM: It's like a mix between
tennis and Ping-Pong.
KOURTNEY: Are you on a phone
call?
KHLOE: What phone would I be on?
KIM: So, it's a smaller
court, like a tennis court, but,
like, tiny.
TRISTAN: So, there's no
pickles? >> KIM (laughing): No.
TRISTAN: Oh, okay, okay.
KIM: No pickles.
I have no idea how to even start
a conversation with Tristan.
Pickleball is the first thing
that popped into my head.
It was super awkward, but he's
an athlete.
I just thought maybe talking
about sports would be common
ground. I'm such a good athlete.
Have you ever seen me ski?
TRISTAN: You can ski?
KIM: What?
Have you ever seen my video,
or was I blocked at that point?
TRISTAN: No, no, uh, no, I
didn't see it. KIM: Okay, look.
KHLOE: She's showing him the
videos, um...
KOURTNEY: From skiing?
KHLOE: From skiing to prove
what a good athlete she is.
TRISTAN: Holy (bleep).
KIM: So I'm a good athlete.
TRISTAN: You're legit.
KIM: No, no, no.
TRISTAN: You do winter
sports. KIM: I'm legitimately a
really, really, really good
athlete.
TRISTAN: So you're coming for
Lindsey Vonn's spot?
KIM: No.
TRISTAN: You know who that
is? >> KIM: Yes, of course.
She dated Tiger Woods.
TRISTAN: Yeah, she did.
KIM: And she's a professional
skier.
I'm really, really good.
KHLOE: I like that they're
having a moment, so I won't
intrude.
KIM: I bet you I can beat you
in some kind of sport, though.
What do you...?
TRISTAN: Only winter sports.
KIM: It's on. Challenge.
TRISTAN: May the best of us
win. Yeah. >> KIM: Challenge.
TRISTAN: Calabasas versus
Hidden Hills. Yeah.
KIM: Yes. Yes, that's a good
one.
I just challenged Tristan to a
game of pickleball.
I realized that, why am I
fighting this fight if no one
else is?
I'm not gonna spend my time
angry at someone else for
something that they didn't do to
me. I'm gonna move on, if that's
what Khloe chooses to do.
I'm gonna be supportive of her.
TRISTAN: First of all, I
thought you were gonna play
this.
KHLOE: I am, 'cause I can't
do pickleball? Can you?
You don't even know what that
is.
I just heard of it yesterday.
TRISTAN: Actually, I did.
I did know, I know how it is
now. Yeah.
The combination of Ping-Pong
and, uh, tennis.
KHLOE: Oh, true.
KOURTNEY: It has a lot of rules.
KHLOE: No, there's a lot of
rules.
You have to stay out of the
kitchen and do some...
TRISTAN: I just thought that
Kim had the least athletic gene
out of all three of you guys.
KHLOE: This one does.
KIM: Kourtney does for sure.
TRISTAN: She works out every
day. KOURTNEY: How good am I in
the gym? TRISTAN: You're good.
You've gotten much better.
Your lather's becoming a sweat
now. >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: Do you think I should
ask this guy to unblock me?
TRISTAN: Dismissed.
KIM: There's no going back.
TRISTAN: There's no going
back now.
You're here now.
(birds singing)
KHLOE: Oh, and this is what
we're getting True.
LARSA: Are you cool with him
now? KIM: Yeah. It's all good.
My relationship with Tristan...
It's a work in progress, but it
is just really important to move
forward.
We're such a close family.
We're one big family.
You just have to just move on
and get over it.
TRISTAN: (bleep)
KHLOE: Don't hurt yourself.
KOURTNEY: Oh, my God.
Did you hit the tree?
TRISTAN: No, no, I almost...
I didn't know it was that
bouncy.
KHLOE: Do you know how to do
this? TRISTAN: I'll go with no
socks. LARSA: Tristan, I'm glad
you're living your best life!
KHLOE: Have you ever been on
a trampoline?
TRISTAN: Uh... maybe.
KOURTNEY: This is, like, a
real deal trampoline.
KHLOE: We're gonna get that
for True.
No, don't do that.
KOURTNEY: Were you gonna try
to flip? >> TRISTAN: Yeah.
I don't know if I...
KHLOE: Can you flip in real
life? >> TRISTAN: I can do a
cartwheel. KHLOE: No, you can't.
TRISTAN: Back in 2005...
KHLOE: Kourtney can.
Show him your cartwheel skills.
Look at this.
(laughing): Oh, yeah.
You know I can't do it.
LARSA: This is the life.
(children squealing)
NORTH: One, two...
KIM: Being here, swimming,
hanging out with my kids, with
my family... this is the dream.
This is what I love to do.
I mean, even having Tristan
here... it's just...
We're all together.
It's so much fun, and this is
what life's all about.
KOURTNEY: We're gonna...
we're gonna race.
KIM: One. >> KOURTNEY: One.
ALL: Two. Three.
(indistinct chatter)
KOURTNEY: My top fell off!
KIM: On the next episode...
KRIS: I just got a call from
Shelli.
She wants to put together this
huge poker tournament.
MAN: Ready to learn some poker?
KIM: Don't underestimate...
No, underestimate me.
I prefer it. I'm all in.
(Kris whoops)
So, I think I'm gonna go to.
Paris and go to the Louis
Vuitton show.
KHLOE: How do you feel now?
KIM: I'm going really
cautiously, but you never know
what could happen.
(indistinct shouting)
Captioning sponsored by.
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS
Captioned by.
Media Access Group at WGBH