♪♪
[ Sizzling ]
[ Fussing ]
[ Babbling ]
No, no,
we don't eat the fire truck.
How's the s'mores coming?
Someone's getting hungry.
[ Yells, grunts ]
Fireman!
"Heatblast," actually, but --
Whoa!
[ All gasp ]
Aah! Aah!
Yah!
Heabwast.
Aww. Close enough.
Hope the kid likes fireworks.
Yah!
♪♪
Whoa!
Hah. Pretty -- Uh-oh.
[ Both grunting ]
Ben, are you trying to burn down
West Potomac Park?
No.
Just one evil tree.
Just be careful.
We're among amazing
historical monuments.
Like the Washington Monument,
the Lincoln Memorial,
the Natural History Museum,
and the Jefferson Memorial,
just to name a few.
Don't wreck
the precious monuments.
Got it. [ Gasps ]
Surrender, Tennyson.
I'm just warming up, Hex.
As am I.
I have only begun to unlock
the power of Pan's flute.
[ Flute playing ]
♪♪
Hey, Mr. Heatblast. Uh,
sorry for running off like that.
We wanted to thank you for
getting rid of that giant...
tree...monster.
-[ Growling ]
You might wanna run.
Enjoy D.C.
Huh?
[ Flute playing ]
♪♪
Huh?
Hyah! Hyah!
Ben! The flute!
You gotta focus.
Hyah!
♪♪
[ Flute playing ]
Never had
a single lesson.
You...nuisance!
If not for you,
this world would be mine.
I swear it shall be.
The next time we meet,
you won't be so lucky.
That wizard talk for
"I'm running away again"?
Uh, no.
Uh, oh, uh...
You -- Quiet!
Ye-- Yep.
Another baddie
bites the dust.
Yeah, hopefully, the last
one of the summer.
Whew!
Wait, "last"?
Vacation just started.
Nothing
even happened yet.
"Nothing"?
We've been around the globe,
defeated Vilgax,
beat the High Override,
went to Italy,
and saved the world.
Don't forget traveling
through time and space
to stop Forever Knight.
[ Straining ]
Oh, oh!
[ Raccoon snarling ][ Grunting ]
[ Roars ]
It's been
such a wild ride.
[ Sighs ] I'm actually
looking forward to school.
What?! Not me.
How am I supposed to go back
to math tests
after surviving
the ultimate tests of power?
This is
the best summer ever.
Getting the Omnitrix,
beating up bad guys,
having quality hero --
Uh,
I mean family time...
Ben, summers are stupendous,
but they eventually end.
And education is essential.
I've been learning
in the field.
Life lessons.
School's the last thing
I need.
-Hey!
-S'more me.
Mmm. Oh.
Just give him a minute.
He'll see the forest
for the trees.
Mmm. Oh. [ Grunts ]
♪♪
Education important...
Yeah, right.
President Washington, you fought
for freedom with your crew.
Wasn't that better than school?
Fine.
Don't answer me.
S'more:
It's not that simple, kid.
S'moresie?
You're alive?
Yes, Benjamin.
Or maybe you're just
really hungry.
You see, Benny, even
Washington wasn't perfect.
Everything's complex.
They don't teach ya
that in school.
Exactly. School doesn't
teach you anything.
You're missing
the point, kid.
I don't think
that this is about school.
You're scared of losing
your summer identity.
And your summer...
...family.
[ Straining ]
No, I think you're right.
I'm just really hungry.
Hungry for
a healthy family unit.
Wait.
No, no, no!
We were really
gettin' somewhere.
[ Tink! Tink! ]
-Thanks for the snack, dude.
-Wait, S'morsie.
There's still so much
I have to ask you.
Give him back, thief!
Nothin' personal, kid.
A monkey's gotta eat.
We owe you one.
A mysterious snack thief
and a talking monkey sidekick
appear outta nowhere?
Looks like summer vacation
isn't over just yet.
It's hero time.
♪♪
[ Panting ]
Bobo,
you said he had food.
This is just a s'more.
S'mores
are technically food.
Ah.
Let's take a break.
I know it's not exactly
dinner for two,
but it should be enough
to last us the night at least.
Don't want my best friend
to go to sleep hungry, right?
[ Both chomping ]Ha, sleep.
Like we'll have time
for that.
Cannonbolt: S'moresie![ Both gasp ]
What was that?
Aah!
B-Bobo, it's an E.V.O.
What do we do?
S'moresie!
Aah!
♪♪
You're not getting away,
snack stealer.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oof!
What'd you do
with the s'more?
How do you know
about that?[ Punches landing ]
Let go of him,
you big ape.
Look who's talking.
I got him, Rex.
He ain't so tough.
I'll save you.
[ Straining ]
Alright, this is the last time
I'm gonna ask nicely.
Where. Is. My. S'more?
We -- We ate it, dude.
It's gone.
[ Growling ]
[ Screams ]
Great idea, kid genius.
Now he's  really mad.
[ Roaring ]
S'morsie will be avenged!
Looks like I don't have
a choice.
[ Beeping ]
Please work.
Hyah!
What?
I-I did it, Bobo.
Are you seeing this?
It worked.
I made the sword.
Take the monster down first.
Then we can celebrate.
Oh, right. Yah!
♪♪
All I know is that you guys
started this fight.
And I'm gonna finish it.
[ Groaning ]
Good job, kid.
Let's move.
[ Groaning ]
Maybe he's more than just
a snack thief.
Get back here!
It's still standing
after that?
That ain't
no ordinary E.V.O., kid.
Look at that symbol
on its chest.
Looks like it's using
some kind of tech.
You know what that means.
S'morsie!
Why do
I have to do everything?
Nowhere left to run.
Now, Rex.
Do your thing.
[ Beeping ]
Oh, no.
Kid. You alright?
Uh...
maybe I went
a little overboard this time.
Hmm?
[ Straining ]
Got it.
[ Screams ]
Uh, honey,
I think we should go.
A lot has happened today.
Fine.
Just one last picture.
Who knows when
we'll be back in D.C.?
Say "cheese."
[ Groaning ]
What  is
that thing?!
My phone!
Did you get it?
I think so.
Snack...thief.
Whoa! That's new.
Come on.
It's definitely time to go now.
Aaahhh!
Honey! Aah!
Look out, Bobo.
[ Both groaning ]
[ Groans ]
Wait, the monster
was just that kid?
I thought...
Huh.
Guess he's not
an E.V.O. after all.
Oh, no.
Wha-- What happened?
Hey, are you guys alright?
[ Gasps ]
♪♪
[ All growling ]
[ Gasps ]
What happened?
Why am I covered in fur?
[ Gasps, screams ]
Where did these extra arms
come from?
Whoa. Whew!
Almost lost my balance there.
Oh, no, no.
I'm still goin' down.
Aah! Ooh!
-[ Giggles ] Play.
-Huh?
Play.No, Baby Humungousaur.
No. Aah!
Crushing...my ribs.
-Bye.
-Whoa!
You turned back
into a human somehow.
Yeah,
show us how to do it.
You -- I...
I don't think that's
how it works.
What are
you talking about?
You have to fix this.
[ Giggles ]
[ Sighs ]
This is not how I wanted
my last summer adventure to go.
[ Beeping ]
Yes, I'm timed back in.
Wait, what?
[ Straining ]
Whoa.
-Hmm?
-Huh?
Aah! Oh!
Huh? What is this?[ Crowd screaming ]
♪♪
[ Straining ]
Stop!
See?
You did something.
Show us how to go back
to normal.
What did you do
to my Omnitrix?
I-I don't know.
Maybe I can --
No, Rex.
We can't stay.
You know who
should show up any second.
But...this happened
because of me.
We gotta look out
for ourselves, kid.
Let the monsters
take each other out.
♪♪
Wait, robot boy.
Come back.
I need your help.
You're not going anywhere
until you fix this, kid.
Uh, Grandpa? Gwen?
I could really use
some help right now.
[  Sirens wailing ]  Max? Manhattan is...
Well, look.
[  Wailing continues, crash ]
♪♪
[  Giggling ]
What's going -- Aah! Aaaaah!
What on earth?
Huh?
♪♪
[ Both screaming ]
Okay, watch. Ha ha.
We've all had a good laugh.
Now go back to normal.
[ Wind blowing ]
♪♪
Please be a good guy.
Behind you.
Huh? [ Gasps ]
♪♪
Have you
been contaminated?
Ew. No.
I got my flu shots.
Three possible
E.V.O. contams confirmed.
Three whats confirmed?
Hey. Careful.
They're people.
Hold that thought.
Aah!
♪♪
Aah! Uhh!
Secure the perimeter.
Targets heading your way.
Thanks for the assist.
Woulda handled it no prob
if my watch wasn't wiggin' out
Aah!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's chill.
Possible contamination
source in custody.
You know what?
I'm gonna find my family.
Nice meeting you, uh...
Agent Six.
You're coming with me.
That's a big negative,
Mr. Agent Six.
Your "source" and his chimp
went that way.
Chimp?
Providence.
This is an Omega Event.
Prepare contingencies
while I try to contain this.
All units engage.
Alright, now we --
♪♪
You wouldn't hurt a kid,
would you?
Aah! Uhh!
♪♪
Oh, no.
[ Beeping ]
♪♪
Oh, yeah.
Hoo-hoo!
Shock Rockin' 'n' rollin'.
This is how you try
to convince me
you're not a threat?
Uh, sometimes I don't
plan so good.
♪♪
Oh, we are gonna be in
so much trouble
if we mess up
this monument.
Make it easy on yourself
and surrender.
Providence would prefer you
in one piece.
I don't know
who this Providence guy is,
but you can tell him --
no, thanks.
Ah, that -- that hurt.
You don't skip leg days,
do ya?
Providence
is an organization,
created to contain extinction
events before they start.
Well, where were you when
that kid broke my watch
and stole my s'more?
Huh?
Wait. Did you say "extinction"?
-Yes.
Which is why I have to
contain you
and your E.V.O.
generator first.
Then I'll deal with Rex.
Whoa, whoa.
I'm no "Eve-O," bro.
I'm one of a kind.
Well, 10 aliens of a kind,
but...
Ah, never mind.With that device,
you are a liability.
Even more than Rex.
Yes.
A liability whose own folly
shall be his undoing.
[ Groans ]
I'm a Shock --
Uh, nibblets.
Playtime is over.
You wanna play, huh?
Yah!
Ben: That's the guy.
He whammied my watch
and ran away.
We  were runnin' away,
which was a great idea,
but Mr. Guilty Conscience
changed his mind.
Good.
Stop fighting and stand down
so you don't cause
any more damage.
Get outta here, kid.The name's Ben.
And you don't get to tell me
what to do.
[ Screams ]
Come on, watch.
I don't wanna sit out
my last big adventure.
I need aliens.
Like, now.
No.  My aliens.
More of  my aliens.
Under Providence protection,
you'll make a perfect asset.
I'm not an asset.
Now get off!
I can't do that.
I always deliver.
♪♪
Step away from the robot
and his monkey.
I'm not a robot.
I've got nanites
in my body.
Don't correct
the walking chandelier
when he's
actually helpin' us.
This guy's no joke.
He's the sixth deadliest man
on the planet.
No kidding?
He didn't make the top five?
Both targets in position.
All units converge,
and we can end this here.
[ Wind blowing ]
♪♪
[ Gun cocks ]
What now?Bobo and I usually run.
I usually wreck stuff till Gwen
comes up with a better plan.
Is Gwen a monkey?
Ha!
I so wish she heard that.
Rex!
You chumps messed
with the wrong...
hero.
Aw, man.
Don't suppose
you'd give me a second
to time back in?
[ Gasps ]
Incoming.
[ Laughs evilly ]
Hex?
He's a bad guy.
Net him.
Net him good.
Open fire.
♪♪
Your watch has always been
such a help to you.
Now, thanks to your new friend,
it shall help  me.
Yah!
♪♪
Behold, an entire army born
of your misbegotten powers.
I will start with
the Eastern Seaboard,
watch it crumble
under alien assault.
Then I will take command
of that alien army
and march across the world.
No.
Those are my aliens.
Wrong, child.
They are  my aliens.
Whoa!
[ Screaming ]
Can we agree to put the past
behind us
and kick common butt for now?Deal.
Let's de-net your kid sidekick
and get some help.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
[ All scream ]
♪♪
Nice aliens.
We're just gonna scoot by.[ Beeping ]
What's the green light
mean?
Green. Means. Go!
♪♪
Hang tight.
You can run. But you cannot hide
from yourself.
Whoa!
Nailed the landing.
Gwen?
Grandpa?
I brought a smelly critter
and his monkey.
Hello?
Eh, must be out looking for me.
Overprotective fam.
You know how it is.
Know how it is?
Nah, not so much.
Ooh, this ain't good.
News from New York, Boston,
and as far south
as Charleston of humans
transforming into
grotesque creatures.
[  Siren wailing ]
The president
has declared "roar,"
because he's a monster!
We're doomed!
It's an army of me.
At least they ain't E.V.O.s.
Okay, can somebody tell me
what's an "E.V.O."?
Come on.
Ain't it obvious?
Exponentially
Variegated Organisms.
[ Chomping ]
Well, that explains
everything.
See,
when nanites infect people,
we think it'll turn them
into monsters.
I may be the only one
who can control them...
sort of.
In the meantime,
mummy-face bad skin
said he was gonna control
an army of yous.
Eh, looks like
he meant it.
Gonna disagree with you there,
monkey.
He broke the watch.
He started
a "distinction" event.
You mean  extinction event,
genius.
And the name's Bobo.
Rex is
the victim here, too.
Providence nabbed us
from his parents' lab,
wanted to stick us in a cell,
so we stuck it to them.
Been on the run ever since
tryin' to protect the kid
from Six and his goons.
♪♪
What happened
to your parents?
Good question.
I kinda have a hard time
remembering stuff.
I don't like
these generator levels.
Mom? Dad?
Rex. Run.
Run!
Providence thinks
I'm a dangerous freak.
Maybe they're right.
Hey, you saved me from the sixth
most dangerous dude on earth.
So let me help you now.
How?
Isn't your watch roasted?
Good point.
If the Omnitrix leaks out
all of its DNA,
my hero days are over.
I might as well go back
to school.
Unless...
you can -- I dunno --
undo what you did?
I...
I wish I could.
♪♪
Kid's new at this, Ben.
Like, brand-spankin'-new.
Hey, I was new once.
Didn't stop me from doing
something to save the world.
What can I tell ya?
Yay, you.
♪♪
[ Thud, glass shattering ]
Grandpa? Gwen?
Guys?
Nooo!
♪♪
Gwen, Grandpa, wait.
It's me,
your favorite Tennyson.
More like
least favorite.
I prefer my enemies like
I prefer my mignon --
filleted.
Ugh. Tell Hex to work
on your one-liners.
Quippy one-liners are a delicate
art which I take pride in.
For example, umm...
uh...
Aliens more like, uhhh...
Ummm...
Uhhh...
Uhhhhhhh...
Uh, true art takes time.
Don't make me have
to go alien again.
Don't make me laugh.
♪♪
Come on.
You guys are the wind
beneath my wings.
Just not when
you're possessed by Hex.
♪♪
I've got a plan.
You follow him,
and I'll cut 'em off.
Good plan.
Not that way.
That way.
Even when I'm getting chased
and my world is crumbling
right before my eyes,
I am still lookin' good.
[ Clicks tongue ]
♪♪
Cannonbolt Max:
[ Speaking indistinctly ]
[ Breathes deeply ]
Stop!
[ Speaking indistinctly ]
Wait, what?
Where'd he go?
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
You're not yourselves.
And you're also not me.
♪♪
Just stay put while I find --
Oh!
Ooh. Ohh...
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, cuz.
Chill!
[ Groans, grunts ]
Batter up.
♪♪
Target acquired.
Bye-bye, little ravioli.
♪♪
Whoa.
Hey.
What are you doin'?
You said not to break
the monuments.
[ Gasps ]
Whoa.
Come on, Gwen.
Let's talk this out.
We all know how much
you like to talk.
Whoa!
Gwendolyn!
[ Screams ]
I'm telling Grandpa.
Please, no.
Shake it off, guys.
[ Speaking indistinctly ]
We're family, remember?
Hex is our family now.
No, thanks.
We have enough weirdos
in our family already.
[ Gunfire ]
Hey. Providence goons.
Actually, glad to see ya.
I could use a --
♪♪
Together: Hup, hup, hup, hup,
hup, hup, hup.
Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup,
hup, hup, hup, hup, hup.
Man, I didn't even know
my own strength.
Aah!
Owww.
Urgh!
Uh, uh!
Gwen! Quit it!
Wah, wah, wah!
What a baby.
Yes, poor, poor, brat.
Wiped from the face
of the Earth
by his own flesh
and alien blood.
Magnificent.
Onward, my minions.
♪♪
Somebody help me!
That was
a great action set piece.Gwen, stop! Somebody help!
I'll cherish it always.
So, can we run away now?
We have to help him.
We tried.
His watch thing flakes
out all the time.
He's kind of a doofus.
And Six is
still around here somewhere.
But I did this.
At least some of it.
And look at Ben.
Fighting without his powers.
We all make mistakes,
but trust me, kid --
I lived in a cage.
It ain't pretty.
What do you want?
You want freedom,
we gotta go.
Now.
So, what...
we're gonna run? Forever?
Come on, watch. Are we just
gonna run forever?
Whoa! Ugh!
Bobo: It's time
for that dumb idea.
Move it, beach ball.
Thought you were too new
to hero.
No good running
if we're just meeting up
with meaner versions
of you.
But don't say
I didn't warn ya.
Four Arms Gwen: Uhh!
♪♪
Careful! He's old!
So I'm supposed
to do nothing?
Oh, no.
Whoa.
Back to running.
He'll get tired
eventually.
He had a full meal,
and it's almost his nap time.
Now to deal with Gwen.
I knew she was a pain,
but I never thought...
Did someone say "pain"?
Uhh, no.
Uh, wasn't me.
It was some other guy.
He had like, uh, greasy hair
and a red watch,
and, uh, I think his name
was Kevin or something.
He went that way.
[ Laughs evilly ]
Get off me, foul creature!
Pot?
Meet kettle.
Don't hurt her!
You want help or not,
kid?
[ Beeping ]
♪♪
I'm here, Bingo.
[ Groans ] Gwen.
You're makin' me look bad
in front of the talking monkey.
You looked bad
way before that.
I kinda like her.
♪♪
What are you doing?
Uh, chopping?
That's sort of
all I can do.
That,
and talk to machines.
They need our help,
not a smackdown.
Best way to do that,
newbie, is to get Hex.
Tell them that.
[ Groans ]
Opposite corners, you two.
And that's enough
with the sword.
So much power wasted
on the young.
Tennyson can wait.
His robotic rival's power is one
that could come in quite handy
as I take
over everything.
Attack the machine generator.
Ugh.
It's like herding sphinxes.
The other child
with the powers.
The new one.
Hey!
Chill out, kid.
Rex is scared.
He don't remember
where his parents are,
where he's from, nothin'.
He's bein' hunted by people who
wanna use him like a lab rat.
And now he's bein' attacked
by aliens.
What would you do?
Maybe all he needs is
a good knock on the head.
What he needs is a friend.
A human friend.
I already tried that.
But now my family's
in danger.
Kids.
In one ear and out the other.
Rex lost everything
that was important to him.
He needs someone
he can depend on.
A good listener.
Wait, what'd you say?
Sorry.
I zoned out there.
Just realized you're
a talking monkey.
Are you serious?!
You didn't hear a word
I just said?
Somethin' about how you used
to be a real boy or something?
No!
What are you -- nuts?
Listen.
There's no time to talk.
I gotta save my family.
Hold up.
♪♪
[ Ding! ]
[ Rex straining ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Heads up.
Slapback is here.
Together: If you want somethin'
done right, do it yourself.
Aah!
♪♪
[ Both chuckle ]
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
Get off of me!
Both: Just shut the sword off
before someone gets hurt.
Agent Six:
Everyone, stand down.
♪♪
While you two have been
swapping insults,
the E.V.O. infection has
spread to cataclysmic levels.
The cleanup team
is on its way.
-We're doin' laundry?
-We never do wash our T-shirt.
Not that kind
of cleanup.
"Scorch the Earth and flatten
every livin' thing" cleanup.
No.
Six?
[ Beeping ]
♪♪
You can't do that.
These are people.
Both: It's my family.
We can fix this.
You can't even work together
for five minutes
without making things worse.
Now come with me.
Unless you want
to get wiped out.
Unfortunately,
under my new rule,
all living things
do as  I command.
Including you.
♪♪
[ Both scream ]
There has to be
somethin' we can do.
Yeah, nah,
we're totally doomed.
[ Both growling ]
[ Growls ]
[ Both panting ]
We need
space and time.
Now!
♪♪
Come on.
In here.
[ Footsteps approaching ]Aah!
Hey, hey, hey.
[ Growls ]
[ Roars ]
[ Sighs ]
Congratulations. You delayed
our demise by minutes.
Do you have a plan to stop
your alien infection
from spreading
that doesn't involve hiding?
Ugh. Can we please stop
calling it my "alien infection"?
Wait, if we can stop it,
can you call off
the whole cleanup thing?
That's a big if.
[ All scream ]
Children.
You can't turn them into newts.
Actually, I can.
Say "salamander."
[ Laughs ]
Your bad guy banter
is dumber than your face.
How dare you?!He's right --
His face  is dumber.
And he rambles.
We call it "monologuing"
in the hero biz.
Silence! It's over.
Agreed.
If you don't stop this,
Providence weapons will scrub
this entire area in minutes.
And as they fall outside,
you'll fall inside.
It'll only take one ship
to wipe D.C. off the map.
Then we'd better stop Hex
and clean up this mess fast.
Three against one
is pretty good odds.
[ Scoffs ] I'm above petty
scrapes with has-been heroes.
♪♪
[ Trumpets ]
Whoa.
Too bad
he's not on our team.
-Team?
-Okay.
Our uneasy alliance?
Quit yappin', you two.
Big boy at 2:00.
[ Trumpets ]
Thanks.
This beast needs to fight
something its own size.
[ Laughs evilly ]
[ Rumbling ][ Gasps ]
Humungousaur!
[ Laughs evilly ]
[ Trumpets ]
♪♪
[ Groaning ]
You better set right
your sorcery, wizard.
Or we'll all pay.
Me? I'm just controlling
my legions
and taking over the world.
This little rodent
created them.
Stop blaming...me.
♪♪
He's evolving.
That was one heck
of a wallop, kid.
He's makin' a break for it.
On it.
Finish off his parlor trick.
On it!
Ugh. [ Groans ]
Why does it sound so much cooler
when he says it?
[ Grows ]
[ Trumpets ]
♪♪
[ Ting! ]
You been holdin' out
on us?
I'm telling you --
I have no idea
how I'm doing this.
Well, keep doin' it.
It's awesome.
If we're done pattin' ourselves
on the back with gigantic hands,
there's an Eastern Seaboard
that needs savin'!
[ Pounding ]
[ All roaring ]
♪♪
Huh!
Watch your back, sixth most
dangerous man in the world.
Is there a test for that?
Or is it like
a beauty contest?
Stay focused.
We need to --
I know.
Clear a path.
I've got mad strategy skills
from all my battles this summer.
[ All yelling ]
How much time is left?
Not enough.
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
I coulda told you he'd do that
if you'd asked me.
Such crude weaponry.
Crude this!
Nice kicks.
Those are some punk busters.
I want a pair.
Sorry.
No idea how I made 'em.
Stay on mission.
♪♪
Your "crude"
is my timeless.
Timeless?
I have lived for thousands
of years.
♪♪
You truly believe
you can harm me?
[ Gasps ]
♪♪
Copies? Meet original.
Are you serious?
It's like you're tryin'
to make me look bad.
[ Gasps ]
-Heads up.
I mean heads down.
Whoa.
What else can you do?
No clue.
But I'm gonna keep doing it
until I get it right.
[ Chattering ]
Uh, he ain't lookin'
so hot.
Come, my alien army.
I have some pests
for you to eliminate.
Come on, Six.
No way a wizard is the fifth
deadliest man on the planet.
No. Here we go.
Hey, Rex.
We're ending this now,
together.
[ Beeping ]
Juice me.
-I told you.
I don't know
what I did.
Or how.
Just do it.
Dig into
your hero reserves.
I know you've got em', Rex.
You wouldn't be here
if you didn't.
Then we'll just reverse
the DNA flow
and turn everyone
back into humans.
Easy-breezy.
I can't verify
"easy-breezy,"
but you have about
90 seconds.
We can't run that fast,
kid.
Even with
your fancy new boots.
I can do this.Alright!
[ Beeping ]
♪♪
[ Both gasp ]
Both: Yes!
♪♪
No.
No!
Wh-- Where am I?
What am I?
Oh, no.
It's Albuquerque
all over again.
[ Groans ]
I think those marshmallows
went bad.
-You're okay!
-Cancel the air support.
The infection has been
contained and reversed.
Repeat --
Situation has been contained.
The missile's incoming, sir.
[ Groans ]
I can handle it.
Go.
Uh, right.
Must you always
ruin everything,
you insufferable
little child?!
You're nothing.
A child? Maybe.
But a child
who can do this.
It's hero...
time!
Rath stomped ya once.
Rath's gonna stomp ya
again.
Kitty's got claws.
Forget the world.
All I desire now
is your total annihilation.
Less talk, more --
Whoa!
♪♪
Get off!
Stop it. Stop!
I guess every hero has to have
their first day.
Alien kid.
Big cat.
Needs a friend.
One friend coming up.
Batter up.
Hang tight, Hexy.
♪♪
[ Groaning ]
Mark my words, mortals --
You haven't seen the last
of Havoc-Mancer Hex.
So, you gonna take us in
or what?
In consideration
of your actions today,
I'm taking a vacation...
for exactly five minutes.
How fast and where you run
during that time is up to you.
But make no mistake, Rex --
If you ever lose control
of your powers,
I'll be there.
Count on it.
Deal.
Fine. Be that way.
Five minutes.
Whoops. Gotta go.
Bobo. Hold up.
What?
♪♪
Clock's ticking.
Yeah, let's go.
Is something wrong, Ben?
Other than the fact that
we got turned into aliens
and we nearly destroyed you?
[ Scoffs ]
Destroy me?
Puh-leeze.
The secret government guys
with the missiles
were gonna do that.
What?Never mind.
But fighting a battle
without you guys
made me think about
this summer, and how,
ever since I got the Omnitrix,
you've been there for me.
That's the real reason
I don't want this trip to end.
I know when things change,
we're supposed to learn from it,
but does that mean I gotta learn
to do all this hero stuff
without you?
I don't think
I wanna go it alone.
And you'll never have to.
We'll always be family, Ben,
no matter what.
I gotta admit,
I like the sound of that.
A lot.
♪♪
Family.