♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Are you getting
all bit up by mosquitos?
I don't know.
I'm getting bit up by something.
Man, I can't believe you said
this was a good
swimming hole.
I said it might be good.
It's not, though.
- True.
- Wanna just go?
- Yeah.
This place smells
like green beans.
- My name's Woobeewoo.
- Oh, whoa.
I need your help.
My people are in trouble.
I'm a Mudscamp.
Yeah, Woobeewoo.
Of course we'll help.
Why didn't you just
say something before?
I'm shy.
It took me a while
to work up the nerve.
Oh, right on.
You good now?
We'll see. Come.
I'll take you to my village.
Here we are --
the village of my people.
It doesn't have
an official name,
but I call it
"South Woobeewoo."
Uh, this way.
This is the village elder.
He'll fill you in on the deets.
Greetings, heroes.
Bleh!
Oh! Ugh!
I'm so sorry about that.
You know, we -- we secrete
stink-oil all day
out of our awful-sauce glands.
You know, I guess I should
have warned you.
Anyway, let me cut the cheese.
- Cut to the chase.
- Yes.
You know, I mean, of course,
cut to the chase.
I mean, for many --
for many moons now,
our village has been
under siege by the Megafrog.
He's 100 stories of 110%
10-speed terror like bam --
like fresh out the grease.
I mean, he cases us all
up and down,
from first base to home,
trying to eat us alive.
We -- we've always
managed to escape,
but it's crazy scary.
I mean, w-what if you got ate?
Think about it.
All alone in a stomach
full of acid.
"Mommy!
Mommy, mommy, help me!"
"Billy, is that you?"
"Mommy, you sound exactly --
Mommy, you sound
exactly like me!
exactly like me!"
"Billy, uh..."
Anyway, if this keeps up,
we'll have to move
to the city and get jobs.
We don't know how --
how to do anything cool.
Look, see?
The-- they're already
practicing, the poor fools.
They don't know
what they're in for.
Whoa! Relax, buddy!
You're talking to the right
couple of guys.
Yeah, man.
Me and Jake will bust
this Megafrog up
right up his bumblestop!
That is excellent news.
I mean, here,
take this, please.
It's not much, but --
but it's all we have.
It's -- it's a bag
of lollies.
That's nice.
Thanks, man.
Now, farewell, heroes.
We're counting on you --
for reals!
Hmm.
Getting anything?
Yeah, but it's hard
to make out.
Could just be some footprints...
or old doody.
Word.
Hey, I have an idea.
We can use those lollipops
to leave a trail.
That way we won't get
lost out here.
Yeah, that's a great
idea, man.
I was just gonna throw 'em all
on the ground anyway.
Womp. Womp.
Womp.
This way.
The thing with frogs is they got
a real subtle smell.
It's kind of like
when you open
a new thing of, um, CD-Rs.
Like electric celery?
Yeah... but subtler.
Mm-hmm!
Just as I suspected.
Sweet.
These will take us
right to him.
Come on, Jake!
Oh, ha ha!
Heh-heh! Heh-heh! Hmm.
Huh.
We've passed this butt tree
like three times.
Oh, yeah.
We should probably
backtrack --
get reoriented
and all that.
Word.
Wait, these prints are
all messed up.
Whoa! Yeah.
Guess we better follow
the lollipops back.
- Where's those at?
- We ran out a while ago.
Sna-a-a-p.
Totally lost. Dang!
Do you think maybe
the Megafrog
made all those footprints
on purpose
so we'd use up all our lollies
and get totally lost?
What? Nah, man.
Frogs are mighty dumb.
You know that.
He's probably running around
like that 'cause he's lost.
Plus, we're not even lost.
I just got to stretch up
past these trees
and see where we're at.
Dang! It's all misty.
It's kind of nice up here,
though.
Man, forget that!
I can't see anything
through that mess.
Plus, I got struck
by lightning!
We're gonna have to set up camp
and wait out the storm.
Cool.
I call fire patrol!
Yeah, me, too!
Do you remember how to make
a fire with sticks?
Yeah, man. It's easy.
Uh...
rub 'em together, right?
Oh, yeah.
I don't think
it's working, man.
I think I saw some guy
do it like this once.
That's not it.
I think you're onto something,
though.
Yeah, here we go.
Friction!
Come on, boys! Come on!
Mwah!
I don't know.
You just gotta get
some momentum going.
Ouch!
Glob-globbing stick!
Glob-globbing swamp!
Oh, hey, you got
the fire going.
Right on.
Jake, how did you --
What the...?
It's the Megafrog!
Quick, put the fire out!
Jake, look.
He's just sitting there.
What's he doing out there?
I don't know,
but let's pound him
while he's vulnerable.
Okay, sweetles.
Ow!
What?
Whoa!
Oh, yeah!
Wha?
Jake, wake up. Look.
Ow, my head hurts.
Look at that thing.
Oh, what?!
Yeah.
Hey, whoa!
That gives me a great idea!
We could make a Finn and Jake
out of sticks and stuff
and lure the Megafrog
out here...
then badonk him
right while he's all confused.
Yeah.
That's a great idea, man.
That's a great idea,
Jake.
Fuh, fuh-fuh.
Fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh-fuh-fuh-fuh.
Fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh,
fuh-fuh, fuh, fuh-fuh-fuh.
What?
What is it, Jake?
F-F-F-Fro-o-o-g!
Wha?
Jake, run!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Jake, stretch us
out of here!
Come on, Jake!
Ow.
Jake, let's hide in this cave!
Hmm?
Shmow town, dude!
That guy's gonna dingle our bones
into tapioca pudding!
Finn, that is gross,
man!
Don't use language
like that!
Chop that!
Ohh!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Aah! He's eating me!
Aah! Gently eating me!
No teeth! Mostly tongue!
Hmm? Hmm.
I need your help.
My people are in trouble.
I'm shy.
I mean, he chases us
all up and down,
from first base to home.
We've always managed
to escape.
Getting anything?
Yeah, but it's hard
to make out.
I'm shy.
First base.
Yeah, but it's hard
to make out.
- I'm shy.
- It's hard to make out.
Hmm. That's it!
Jake, wait!
Sick, dude!
Huh?
I know how to stop him!
Nyah chow!
Aah! This is rad!
I'm hot again!
Thanks, little dudes!
I really appreciate it.
I don't get it, though.
I kissed just about everything
I could get my lips on.
How come it only worked
with you?
You can't break your
own curse by kissing somebody.
Somebody's gotta kiss you.
- Oh. Weird.
Well, thanks, man.
I don't know a lot of dudes
who'd do that to help a guy out.
Whatevs.