Yo, beemo, you done
charging up that phone, or what?
Almost... finished.
Thanks, beemo.
All right, man.
We're gonna figure this out
right...Now.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, check it!
This is Jake on my camera
phone!
Wh-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-oa!
Whoa, whoa!
Yo, finn!
- Say hi to my new camera phone.
- What up, camera phone?
Lalalalalalalalalalala
lalalalalalalalalalalalalala...
...Lalalalalalalalalalalalala!
Marceline!
You guys want to come party
in the nightosphere with me?
I'm visiting with my dad, and
- it's crazy boring.
- Whoa!
Wait a minute, marceline.
Last time I saw your dad, I
sliced open his soul sack.
Oh, no, he's totally chill
- now.
- Okay, but I'm keeping
an eye out for your old man in
case he pulls any...
Sneak attacks.
Don't be a wiener dog.
Jake, you coming?
Whoo! Yeah, baby!
All right, so...This is the
nightosphere, I guess.
It looks banaynays.
Marceline says they got tons of
crazy ways out here.
Right, marceline?
Marceline! Marcy!
There you are, marceline.
Hmm?
- Rrragh!
- Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
- Oh. Hello, dog. Hello, finn.
- Stay away from me,
old man!
Nice one.
Now, finn.
Come on, there's no bad blood
here.
Come here.
Let's bury the hatchet.
See how I'm not killing you?
Dad, stop.
All right.
I don't want to embarrass my
little girl.
So, young lady, have you
thought about my offer?
Ugh!
What offer,
marceline's dad?
I want marceline to take over
the nightosphere -- finally
join the family business.
Business?
Dad, what do you even do?
Oh! Ha!
Come on, come on, come on, come
on.
Check it out, sweetie.
See how chaotic it is out
there?
How everyone's confused and
frustrated?
The nightosphere is sustained
by chaos.
Eh, I just don't see myself
doing this biz.
Okay, but I know you'll come
around eventually.
Or maybe you won't.
I don't know.
You're an independent woman.
Aaah!
Well, I'm gonna take a nappy.
Oh! I almost forgot.
Dad!
Whoops!
You should put this amulet on.
It'll Grant you wishes for,
like, ponies -- or whatever
kids like.
Dad, I'm 1,000 years old.
Ha! Yes, you are, sweetie.
Daddy's little monster.
Look, let's just play
something, okay?
Okay.
♪ I know you just want to
give your little girl the
world ♪
♪ but, daddy, I'm not just your
little girl ♪
♪ I've got my own life, I got my
own plans ♪
♪ I hope you understand and like
the way that I am ♪
♪ 'cause I want your respect,
and I want to be here ♪
♪ but I don't want to rule the
nightosphere ♪
Pffft! Whatever, dad.
Ooh--
aaaaaaarrgh!
Jake, grab the amulet!
Oof!
Ow! My hippocampus!
Well, that explains how
we got amnesia'ed.
But what about banana?
Hey, man, there's
another video.
We got mad prison-overcrowding
down here, fellas.
So, I got to put you in the
cage with the stuff.
Sorry about that.
But, you know, not really.
Oh, my stomach!
- Yeeeee!
- That amulet's
controlling marceline!
We have to go back and help her!
We're gonna get back using that
one portal spell we know.
Hah!
Maloso vobiscum et cum spiritum!
Whoa, dude.
She told us never to come back.
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Jake, can you turn into a gross
demon?
Mm-hmm.
- Grosser!
- Raaaaaah!
- What's your
- disguise?
Paper-plate mask, yo!
- Nice!
Let's go! Hyah!
Who's next? Who's next?
Uh...Me, my lord aberdeer.
What do you desire, cowering
speck -- pain, pleasure, or
weird punishment?
Uh...Pleasure?
No! Weird punishment!
And what do you desire --
"p," "p," or "w.P."?
I...
Pain?
Okay.
Aw.
Come on! Come on! Next!
I'm just gonna go.
You sure, dude?
Don't you want abs?
Yeah, give me abs.
I think we can charge
up there and rip the amulet off
her neck.
Hey! What are you guys doing?!
You can't run up to the front of
the line!
These good people have been
waiting forever!
Shame on you both!
Everybody, shame them!
Boo, sir!
I boo what you're doing!
Step back -- back!
You will not cut the line again!
You stay back here and wait your
turn like the rest of us!
- Understand?!
- Yeah, okay! Okay!
I'll be watching you.
Sorry, dude.
You got out of line.
Dang it!
- Who are you?!
- Waah!
- Don't kill us, marceline!
- It's us --
- finn and Jake!
- Your friends,
remember?!
Eh.
Oh, grob!
Aaaaaah!
Run!
Marceline.
What are you doing?
Just grabbing a midnight
snack.
It's marceline.
That's her out there!
I know.
Isn't it fantastic?
No!
We have to save her!
- Save her?
- From the amulet!
But this is what I've always
wanted -- my girl following in
- her daddy's footsteps.
- But that's not what she
wants!
That's balderdash, baby.
The wearer of the amulet is
filled with chaotic evil, which
is how I grew up, so...
Maybe we can get these
dudes to help us.
These
guys won't help you.
They're all complacent sheeple.
Wait. That's it!
We're gonna freestyle a
political rap to get these guys
to rise out of their systemized
- demon apathy!
- Okay.
Yeah. Unh.
Political rap!
Yo, yo!
Demon apathy!
Yo, zappity!
Get ready!
Government!
Where you went!
Yo! Farmer's market!
Ride bikes! Get on it!
Geodesic domes!
Science!
You heard?
I never thought of it that
way before.
This system is broke, yo!
Marceline.
Ugh. Sick.
- Jake! The tree house!
- Aaaah!
I'm too freaked out to move,
finn!
These demons are nibbling my
legs!
- Jake, take her!
- No, finn!
You'll be filled with chaotic
evil!
Aaaaah!
Marceline.
No one leaves the nightosphere!
Wh-o-o-o-oa!
Oh!
Marceline!
Uh, I wonder what happened to
him.
Kids these days.
Am I right?
Dude. Seriously.
Dad, you tricked me.
Dad, that sucks!
I know. I'm sorry.
But I thought you'd want to --
want to make your old man proud
and, you know, take over the
nightosphere.
Yeah, I want you to be proud!
I want you to be proud of me!
No, I didn't mean --
baby, of course I'm proud of
you.
Dad.
And your friends, they're all
right!
That political rap?
Pretty great!
Okay, okay.
I got to go now, dad.
Woof! What a nightmare.
Man, finn, my dad actually likes
you.
I don't want to hang out with
- you anymore.
Finn?