My GPS shows Finn
and Jake over there.
I think that's where
the Ice King has them hostage.
I'm sure the boys are fine.
The Ice King isn't usually
a serious threat.
Besides, this'll be easy
with the two of us.
We've got science on our side.
Your tea is ready.
Pouring. Pouring.
It's okay, Lady.
Jake knows you love him.
Don't worry.
Just try to relax.
I'll work on my holo-entry.
It's been three weeks since Finn
and Jake disappeared
while battling the Ice King.
I've activated a secret GPS
implanted in Finn's ear.
It has led us to an uncharted
black ice cave.
But I've spent hours calculating
every possible danger
and am well-prepared.
Then I'll pull out
my electrode gun.
Then I'll use
my ball-blam-burgler-ber!
Lady, it'll be fine.
We've got science!
Hmm, I suppose that's true.
Let's roll.
Ugh, I can't get a signal
in this chamber.
Let's see if they show up
on my heart monitor.
Hmm.
There they are.
Through this sphincter.
Hold up, Lady.
No, no, no!!
Aah! Aah!
Don't worry, Lady.
Ball-blam-burgler-bler-ber!
My field of vision!
Hey!
Lady, phase through the wall!
Come on. There's no turning back now.
This is total bunk, you copier!
You're only in love with her
because Mn in love with her!
Ice King.
I've been playing this game
a lot longer than you, pal!
I've been working my moves,
smooth-talking her,
showing her magic tricks!
Don't ignore me!
Come back!
I'm picking up three heart signatures.
Ice king must be talking
to Finn and Jake.
Go to the right, Lady.
Aah! Ugh!
Ew.
Lady!
Lady, are you okay?
No, Lady, I won't leave you
while you're hurt.
Come on.
What are you playing at, Ice King?
Three heart signatures.
Getting closer.
Hey.
Princess.
What a pleasant surprise.
- Ricardio!
- Yes, it is I.
Did you find my dungeon stimulating?
Where are Finn and Jake?!
What do you see in those two?
A boy?
And a dog?
You deserve more
mature companionship.
Poisoned with Zanoits!
You see, I thought I only
wanted your heart.
But I was wrong.
I was unfair to you.
I want...
the full package.
Princess...
- What?
I'm a man now.
I made myself this body
for you, Princess,
synthesized from
ice King's living tissue,
his bones broken and reassembled.
It hurt! Ooh, boy!
How about a hug?
Give me a hug! I need it!
Silence, Simon!
All for you, Princess.
Now marvel at these powerful,
articulate limbs!
- Stop!
Attached with supple
and delicate sinews.
Lady!
Now, my darling,
we can finally be united...
as man...
and wife.
Okay, Ricardio.
I'll do it.
I'll be your wife.
- Ah!
- If you can beat me...
at hand-to-hand combat!
Oh, my!
How Valkyrian!
Princess, you are absolut- oh!
You think we're intellectual equals?
It only took me seconds
to get you off your guard!
And this "body" you designed
is self-congratulatory garbage!
See, I know a thing or two
about building a body
out of biomass,
and you don?' leave
your heart exposed!
I just wanted to impress you.
You didn't.
Get out of my sight.
Princess?
Princess!
Ricardio is back!
He's in the black ice cave, and
he's peacocking hardcore!
I know. And he poisoned
you both with Zanoits.
But I took care of it.
What happened?
How did we get here?
I dragged you all here
on Lady's back.
It took two days.
And another day to make you guys
an antidote.
And 15 minutes to build
the Ice King a new heart.
Hey, Finn.
I made it out of Ricardio's sinews,
and some toffee and maracas.
Coochie-ooochie-coochie!
I'm glad you guys are up.
Please make the Ice King leave.
Shooka-shooka-shooka!
Ice King, please leave!!
How are you feeling, Lady?
Yes, he's awake.
Oh, Lady, I should have never
put you in danger.
I saw on the heart monitor.
I didn't know.
- Hee-hee-hee!
- Jake!
Lady! Oh, Lady!
I am pregnant!
I'm puppies!?