That was awesome!
All right, all right, my turn.
You guys are full
- of magic air.
Gross!
No!
Princess?
You...Okay?
Yeah.
It's just...The air smells bad
from your magic tricks, and now
I feel sad.
I left all my scented candles at
the castle.
They'd really cut through the
magic stank.
Just go back to the
fire kingdom and get them --
problem solved.
Then I'll have to
see my dad.
I'm still mad at him for
imprisoning me in that lantern.
So unfair!
Uh...We can go get
them?
Really?
That would be really nice.
But don't let my pops see you.
I don't want his majesty
thinking I need anything from
him.
It ain't me!
Whoa!
Oh!
Flambo!
For a second I thought the
- princess was farting.
- Flambo, we need you to
cast "flame shield" on us.
All right!
These candles must be
they.
They smell
like an old lady's bathroom.
Hey!
Don't disrespect my lady!
I say it as a
compliment!
Like it reminds me of my
grandma.
I love my grandma.
No one come-s-s-s here.
Not s-since flame princes-s-s
fled the cas-s-tle.
Now gues-s-s what we're gonna
- kill flame king with.
- A conspirator
with a hiss voice!
How about...Water?
Even wors-s-e!
We'll us-s-e ic-c-e!
And a conspirator with
an untied shoe!
Ice? Why ice?
'Cause it's more painful, you
s-s-impleton!
Cold as ic-c-e ball-s-s!
A perfect death for
the flame king!
Did you hear
- that?
Jake, come on!
We got to stop those guys from
- killing flame princess' dad!
- Right, right.
Dirt bags!
Where'd they go?
Hey, is that new?
Yeah, I think it is.
Yes, it is new.
Hmm, what do you guys think
of this painting?
I like it.
Hey, is this one of those
paintings where the eyes follow
- you?
Hmm. Hmm.
Come on, let's get out of
here.
I don't want to miss snack time.
Snacks!
- Snacks!
- Snacks! Snacks! Snacks!
Now what?
...and most unnatural
murder-s-s.
Hear that?
It sounds like a voice with a
- hiss.
- The kind we are looking
for!
The s-serpent that did
s-sting...
- Stop!
...thy father's life, now
wears hi-s-s crown-s-s!
- Dude, the voice!
- We must follow the
voice!
To die, to s-sleep, to
s-sleep, perchance to dream...
- Which way is the hiss
voice coming from?
Aye, there's the rub, for in
- that s-sleep of death...
- This way!
- ...what dream-s-s may come.
- Which way?
I s-seem to be s-saying a lot
about our s-super-s-secret
- plan...
- To the left!
You!
- You! You! You!
- Double you! Double you!
I don't think it's
them.
Double you! Double you!
Whoa!
- Jake!
- I'm okay!
I think I hear that hissing
voice down this way!
Whoa!
- Why didn't you catch me?
- Oops!
Tell me next time.
I can't think in the future.
- Vent ahead.
- Jake, I want to see.
- No hissing.
No untied shoe.
Vent.
This needs something more!
- Yes! Yes!
- That's the Stuff!
Whoa! It's him!
- Hmm?
- My bluebies!
You buffoon!
Where's your partner with the
untied shoe?
What partner?
What are you blueberries
talking about?
Give it up, man!
I heard your hiss voice!
- I don't have a voice!
- There's a snake on your
- shoulder!
- What?
Aah!
Hmm.
Suffering...
...Succotash!
Now to chop you two big
blueberries into small,
bite-sized blueberries!
Shakespeare.
Five minutes to curtain,
everyone!
- Five minutes!
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Ooh!
Oh!
Pfft! Actors!
What's going on with
the costumes?
This is a theater troupe!
We're getting ready to perform
for the king!
Everyone in the kingdom shall be
in attendance!
Of course, you know all this,
being fellow actors from the
exact same troupe.
I have an idea.
We'll go onstage, act like two
conspirators.
You will have one shoe untied, I
will talk with a hiss voice.
We'll talk about how we want to
kill the king.
As we do this, we'll study the
faces of the audience and look
for guilty reactions.
- That's brilliant!
- Thanks!
It's an original idea by me.
- Ahem! Hey, conspirator!
- Hey, co-conspirator!
Let's talk about how
we're gonna kill the king!
Shh!
S-somebody might hear our evil
plot!
Man, I am so lost.
Psst! The audience!
Uh, uh, uh, uh...
Uh, uh...
You think that's one of
them?
Maybe.
Let's keep going.
- So, what are you packing?
- Water, man -- enough of
it to put out the king's fire!
Uh, uh...Hmm.
I think he's starting
to crack.
Water?
You know what's even more
painful?
If we pour ice in his ear!
That's how we'll kill
the flame king!
Pbht!
Kill the flame king?
This is treason disguised as a
play!
Guards, seize them!
What?! No!
Please!
We were trying to warn you about
assassins!
Hmm.
- Search them!
Huh?
Sire, it's your daughter's
scented candles!
Sickos!
- Off with their heads!
- Whoa, what?!
No, please!
S-stay s-still.
"S-still"?
Untied shoelace?
It's them!
S-so long, s-suckers!
Naked babies, naked
babies, naked babies!
Naked babies, naked babies,
naked babies!
We found 'em!
The executioners are the real
king-killers!
S-silence!
Wait, wait, wait...That
voice.
Guards, take off their hoods!
Aah!
My identity!
Ugh!
Furnius and torcho!
Hello...Uncle!
Arrest the executioners!
Hmm...I thought I had you two
extinguished.
You cannot quench the
flame-s-s-s of revenge!
You snuffed out our father to
become king!
Oh, yeah...Ha ha.
Take them to the punishment
room!
I'll des-s-Troy all of you...
Release me!
- ...with ic-c-c-e!
- Wait, so you -- you
extinguished their dad?
Mm-hmm.
And...Everyone is evil
here?
Mm-hmm -- all evil.
Then...Is
flame princess...Evil?
Or maybe chaotic neutral?
She's evil.
Okay...So your
daughter's evil -- we've
established that.
But do you think if a good guy
really liked her...Could he
change her to good?
Hmm, well, there'd be
penalties to her experience if
she acted out of alignment,
but...Yes.
Someone could change her.
Change her to good?
Aww!
Evil, evil, evil, evil.
Evil, evil, evil...Evil!
Aah!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ we can wander through the
forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪