Aah! My arm!
Ohh! My face!
Hmm.
This happens sometimes.
Wait, what?!
Oh, my gosh!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Somebody broke into my
house and stole my lumps!
Peebo?
Hey, hey, how-a mah haah!
Eww!
Uh...
Okay. Calm down.
How am I supposed
to calm down?
Lumping thief is out there,
getting fresh with my lumps!
Gross.
Whoa! Whoa!
Gals, we'll find this crazy
freak and return all of your body parts.
Thank you so much, Finn!
I shall give you a kiss.
It's... it's okay,
Hot Dog Princess.
We'll be right back.
I said I don't know!
I have nothing
to do with this.
Stop lying.
We found your fingerprints
at the crime scene.
What?! Really?!
Uh... no.
Oh, well, then why
would you say that?
Ice King,
we know you did it!
Finn, I'm as
concerned as you are.
There's some sicko out there.
What if he comes
after my Princess?
Your Princess?
Yeah.
Let me introduce
you to my new wife.
Oh, wait, you mean I'm
the guy stealing all the p...
Yeah, okay.
I get it now.
What happened to them,
husband?
Hmm?
Um, ah!
They're sleepy.
They're our limp,
sleepy children.
Come on, wife.
Let's have a nice
family meal.
Okay.
Wife, you sit right here.
Isn't this nice?
Uh-oh.
I mean, that's good.
Oops!
How fun! You're so fun!
Mmm.
Oh, marriage is fun.
See?
When you wash and I dry,
we get done faster.
And then tomorrow night,
we switch.
Here.
Let me show you a trick,
my darling.
See?
You let it soak, and then
we'll wash it in the morning.
Enough chores.
Come along, dear.
I want to show you
something special.
♪ Let me show you
something special ♪
♪ I can introduce your
parts to something new ♪
♪ Every moment
now is special ♪
♪ Just as long as I
am spending it with you ♪
♪ You and you and you ♪
♪ There is so much beauty
in this land of ice ♪
♪ The air is cold ♪
♪ But my feelings feel
so warm and nice ♪
♪ Every turn and spin ♪
♪ Will remind us
where we've been ♪
♪ Will remind us when we've
found something special ♪
Here it is.
I hope you like it.
Hmm.
You like?
Is there something
wrong with me?
The way I am...
it's not normal, is it?
Oh, pretty baby wife.
You're the most normal
thing in my whole life.
We're like two normal jelly
beans sitting at the bottom of the jar,
floating in a sea of olives,
waiting for somebody to guess how
many jelly beans are in the jar,
which I mentioned.
I don't think I understand.
Just look into my eyes and
know that everything is okay.
Are you feeling normal yet?
Okay.
See that?
We're normal, just like
the normal people are.
Oh.
Lady, don't take my pizza.
Huh? What's a...
M-m-mons... mons... mons...
Finn, what?
Are you saying "Mama"?
What are you?
Hi!
M-m-m-monster!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Aah! Ugh.
Oh, don't mind the kids.
It's just a phase.
I need a glass of water.
Oh, I'll go get...
No. It's okay. I'll get it.
You are not normal.
You are a monster!
Hey, hey, hey.
Monster! A monster!
What's going
on in here?
Nobody's a monster.
All I see in this room is
a young, kind-hearted,
intelligent, hot-looking
Ice King
and his beautiful
Princess bride.
That's you, sweetie.
I don't feel beautiful.
I feel like a freak.
I will prove to you that
you are beautiful.
To me, my penguins.
Goonter, Gunther, Gunder,
Goonder, come on!
Gunter, Gunthe,
Gaunter, Ginther, follow!
Don't rearrange the chairs,
please.
You're all gonna clap and cheer,
or I'm gonna smack your buns.
Whoo! Yeah!
Clap louder.
You got to be all "Whoo!"
If you look at her
with these mirrors,
her ugliness will
have no effect on us.
Well, where is she?
Oh, I think she's right over...
Hey!
Baby, you want to
talk about it?
You should just find
another Princess to marry.
I'm unlovable!
Girl, I love you as much as all
the other Princesses in the
world combined.
You don't really mean that.
I'll prove it.
See?
You have Elbow Princess' hips and
Doctor Princess' heart and intestines,
Slime Princess' bottom.
You have all my favorite parts
of my favorite Princesses.
I'm... just... a bunch...
of stolen parts?
Oh, the parts don't matter.
It's you that matters.
But who am I?
You're my wife, and I will
always love my wife,
no matter what.
You'd love me even without
these other Princesses' parts?
Sure, baby.
Even without all
your fine lady parts.
Now give us a hug.
Mmm.
Hey, Ice King!
Huh?!
Your wife's face can't
make us faint anymore.
Don't listen to them, babe.
They're being negative.
Haahh!
Aah!
Run, my happiness.
I'll distract them with
ice magi...
Ouch.
Aha!
Aah!
Yaaahhh!
You give up?
Yes!
I give up.
Finally.
Let's get those princess
parts back to the ladies.
Yeah, mans.
Wait, where'd your wife go?
Huh?
Let me go! Let me go!
Though my parts be scattered,
I shall always be your wife.
She...
gave away all my stuff!