♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ we'll go to very distant
lands ♪
♪ with the Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ the fun will never end ♪
♪ it's adventure time ♪
You gonna do the thing
again?
Yeah, man.
- What?
- Nice.
Hey,
princess Bubblegum.
Hey, everybody.
Finn's here!
Yay!
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Man, dancing is rough.
Yeah.
I'm having some sweat issues
here.
I'll go get us some snack-ity
- juice.
- Hey, man. I'm Jake.
I'm Jake.
Hmm.
Check it out, Jake.
I got us some peanuts...
And punch!
Pbht! Choking!
Don't give up on me, man.
Hyah!
Yay!
- Whoa, Finn. Nice book!
- Yeah. It's pretty cool.
It's the enchiridion -- the
hero's handbook.
Hey, guy.
Are you all right?
He's all good.
Everybody get back to your
dancing.
Uh, Finn?
I think that bear is following
- us home.
- Whoa.
I think you're right.
Hey, bear.
You gonna come hang out with us?
What do you say, bear?
- Awesome.
- I don't know, Finn.
- This guy seems kind of weird.
- Yeah.
He's totally weird.
Hmm.
Jake. Hey, Jake.
Jake?
- What?
- Come here.
- You got to check this out.
- Yeah, okay.
Check this out, man.
This bear is tops blooby!
Watch this.
Ah...
...Choo!
You got to try this, Jake.
He does everything I do.
Oh, stop.
Come on, Jake. Try it.
It's awesome!
Um, yeah, okay.
Sweepy, sweepy, sweepy!
Sweep, sweep, sweep!
Sweeping.
He's got me down pat.
Sweeping's weak.
Mm.
Sweeping weak.
Whoa!
This guy's all right.
This guy just busted me
in my chops, Finn.
Hey, come on.
He's just a bear.
- He don't know nothing.
- Mm. Yeah, I guess.
Well, anyway, it's getting
pretty late.
Probably time for everyone to go
back home to their own houses.
Yeah, I guess you're
right, Jake.
It is pretty late.
He should probably stay here
tonight.
You can sleep in the bathtub.
- Brathtrub.
- Sleep in.
- "Brathtrub!"
This guy's tops blooby.
- Finn?
What?
Hey, princess Bubblegum.
Hey, everybody.
What? Hey.
Hey, princess Bubblegum.
Hey, everybody. What? Hey.
Aah!
What are you doing?
Shh. Come with me.
You got to see something.
This bear's wiggy, Finn.
He's wearing your clothes and
- dancing around all crazy.
- That sounds rad, man.
What?!
No. Just --
- Aw, man!
Oh, you got to believe
me, Finn.
I swear.
He was, like, all wigged out.
He was dancing.
- I do believe you.
- Oh.
It's just, you know,
who cares?
Dancing, wearing clothes -- he
ain't hurting nobody.
He's just doing it up, you know?
He's just cool, and he likes my
style.
That ain't a crime.
No.
I guess not.
Okay, great.
I'm going back to bed.
- You coming, smart guy?
- Yeah, okay.
Ahh!
You're not even a
little weirded out by this?
No, man.
He's just doing his instincts.
He's just doing his
instincts.
He's like a parrot or
chameleon or something.
...like a parrot or chameleon
or something.
He's funny.
Anyway, I got to go
pick up beemo from soccer.
I'll be back soon.
And remember -- don't eat my
special Finn cakes.
Finn only.
Yeah, I get it.
You don't need to tell me that
every time you make Finn cakes.
Bah!
Hey, what are you doing?
Why, you little...
Trying to set me up, eh?
You think you're so smart, but
this time, I'm ready.
Oh, my glob! What?!
Jake! You ate all my Finn cakes.
- What the stink?!
- Uh, nope.
The bear did it, and I've got
proof.
- I taped the whole thing!
- The bear ate all my
cakes, and you just sat there
and watched him do it?!
- What's wrong with you!?
- Uh, what? No, man.
He was trying to frame me, Finn!
He's trying to steal your
identity!
Why can't you grok that!?
He's a bear, Jake.
He's a wild animal.
He doesn't know things.
- He just does stuff. He's cool.
- Oh, fine.
Well, that's just great.
Then you and m.C. Cool friend
can go stink it up together at
your stupid, cool Finn party all
by yourselves, 'cause I'm not
going!
Wait -- what?
What party?
What? Your party, man.
Tonight? In the woods?
But I didn't make this
flyer.
Huh?
Well, who did, then?
The bear.
I knew it.
See, dude?
He's not just jacking your
style, he's jacking your whole
you!
Jacking yo' you up.
- What the what?
- He got in close and
used you.
Now he's feeding nuts to your
ex-girlfriend.
- Sure, I'll have
- another nut.
- She's not my -- we
- never went steady.
- Bleh.
He's trying to replace
you, and he's already got
everyone convinced he's you!
He didn't really like you.
He used you.
Troops brooby!
Troops brooby! Troops...
Ow!
Not cool, man.
You're not me.
You're just a bear acting like
me.
It's okay, everyone.
The imposter is gone.
Finn, nobody
really thought the bear was you.
- Wait. What?
- We just thought it
was one of your jokey-joke
jokes.
- Hey! Hey, bear!
- Wait up, guy.
Hey, I -- I didn't mean
to make you feel so bad about
yourself.
- I'm really sorry about that.
- Me, too.
But you're a super-rad
bear, so why not just be you?
- I want be hero like you!
- Aww.
I guess he's got a
heart of gold after all.
Hold on, bear.
I got something for you.
It's the enchiridion -- the
hero's handbook.
Everything you need to know
about being a hero is in this
book.
Take it and learn.
Finn, are you nuts?
We can't give that book away.
- It's, like, crazy important.
- Whatever, man.
We never use it except for,
like, sitting on it when the
grass is wet and stuff.
Drink your fill of knowledge.
Someday, you'll be a great hero.
Thank you, Finn.
Thank you.
Ooooh!
Did you bring the book?
Yes. One step closer.