What you building?
Um, it's just a little
stick fort.
Oh, rad.
Look.
It's just my size.
Hey, get away from my fort,
you big, stinky monster!
I like it when you get
small, Jake.
Yeah, me too.
Whoa!
Peppermint Butler?
Finn, Jake, the princess
wants to see you.
As princess of Candy Kingdom,
I'm in charge of
a lot of candy people.
They rely on me.
I can't imagine what might
happen to them if I was gone.
And after my brush with death at
the hands of the lich,
I realized something.
I'm not gonna live forever,
Finn.
I would if I could.
But modern science
just isn't there yet,
so I engineered a replacement
who can live forever.
I call her Goliad.
Aw, she's cute.
- Hi, Goliad. I'm Finn.
- And I'm Jake.
Hi, Finn. Hi, Jake.
- Hi, Goliad.
- Hi, Finn.
What did you use to
make her?
Oh, um, pretty standard
candy-creature soup.
Some amino acids.
Some algebra.
And I threw in
one of my baby teeth
so she'd have my DNA.
Whoa, DNA?!
Yeah. All it takes
is just one little tooth.
Or... a single hair.
It's a-a-a-all it takes.
Princess Bubblegum,
are you okay?
Yeah! I'm good!
Haven't slept for a solid
83 hours, but...
Yeah, I'm good.
Oh, you should
go to bed.
I can't go to bed.
Goliad has huge,
mondo mama brains.
I still need to fill them
with knowledge...
On how to rule a kingdom.
What? Let us teach her.
Uh, okay.
I guess that would be
all right.
Yes!
Teachers!
Teaching teachers!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Come on, Goliad.
See you later, Princess!
Get some sleep.
Wh... hum? Hmm?
Huh?
Bye, guys.
Look, Goliad.
This is a preschool.
I'm gonna go set up some
obstacles and all that
for you to learn on.
- Mm.
- Is that okay?
- Yes. Thanks, Finn.
I'm excited to learn.
Okay. Great.
Jake, you go and get some kids
from inside
to help with the lesson
and such.
Okay.
Come on, Goliad.
Yes, Jake.
Um, hmm.
Uhh...
Rotten, stinkin', jerkin'...
Whaaa! Ohh!
Rah! Rah! Rah!
Now, now. Settle down.
Jake, these kids
seem pretty scary.
Oh, no.
These kids ain't nothing.
Kids croove doozyploon!
Check this out.
Hey, there, kids.
Who wants to play...
- Get him!
- Get that stink!
Uh, easy now, children.
Get the brain!
Get in his brain!
Get in his eyes!
Listen up! You kids better
stop donkin' around!
You're gonna mess up Goliad!
It's my way or the highway,
get it?
I'm Don Juan Cherry Tempo!
Now march, glib blobbit!
Don't be acting all crazy.
Whoa, holy shmow!
Oh, hey.
Y'all are just in time.
You ready to pop this croc's
back, Dr. Goliad?
Yeah, I think so, Finn.
I've learned a real lot already,
so far.
So much...
from Jake.
Yeah, you know, Finn,
maybe this isn't
such a good
idea, actually.
Oh, no. It's cool.
I got helmets for everybody.
Okay, Goliad.
You ready to lead?
Ready.
Okay.
In 3, 2, 1.
Go!
All right, listen up!
You kids better stop
donkin' around
and get up that ramp!
You're gonna mess up Goliad!
I'm Don Jon Cherry Temp...
Cherry Tempo!
It's my way or the highway,
glob globbit!
Stop, stop!
No, Goliad, no!
Leading isn't about
scaring people.
You got to stay calm
and use your head.
Use that beautiful brain,
girlfriend.
My brain? Are you sure?
Yeah. Don't be shy.
Try it on me. Lead me.
Okay, Finn.
Okay.
Hmm.
No, Goliad.
That's wrong, too.
You can't just control people
or whatever.
It's messed up.
No, Finn. This way's good.
Everyone did what I wanted...
really fast, no mistakes,
calm, like you said.
This definitely is
the way to lead.
Definitely.
Uh, no, no.
Wait. Is that true? Hmm.
Come on, Goliad.
Let's go see
Princess Bubblegum.
Princess!
Goliad's got mind-control
powers!
She got the wrong idea
about leadership.
Oh, I was afraid
this might happen.
Where is she now?
We left her outside
in the garden!
Hello, Goliad.
Hello, Princess.
I hear you learned
a lot today.
Yes. I led the children.
But Finn said you
used yelling and mind control.
Yes. It was good.
Goliad, let me tell you
something about leadership.
You see this fat bee?
She gets pollen
from this flower,
but she's gentle
and makes the flower happy
and pollinated.
They both get what they need,
and that's how
a leader should be.
No, Princess.
Bee cares not for flower.
If getting pollen hurts
or kills flower,
bee would not care.
Bee is stronger than flower.
Goliad is stronger
than bee.
Goliad is stronger than all.
Oh, no.
She's too far gone...
too corrupted.
If we're not careful, she could
throw an ultra-tantrum
and whang the castle apart.
I'll have to disassemble her
and try again.
No, Princess.
This is my castle now.
Don't worry, Princess.
We'll stop her.
No, Finn.
Here's the plan.
I'm going to build another
candy sphinx in my lab.
It's the only thing that could
possibly match her.
Just keep her busy
'til I return,
and don't think about
the plan!
She can read your minds!
Ohhh!
Whoa!
Ugh, that eyeball.
Just tuck that eyeball back
in its hole.
Goliad, no!
Ugh.
Jake! Don't swallow!
Uh, you're in Finn's bubble.
Don't think about
the plan.
Think of something else.
Don't worry, Princess,
we'll stop her.
No, no!
No, Finn.
She's ohhh...
Anyway, like I was saying,
she's far too powerful-I-I-I...
Ugh! Unhhh!
Aah!
Finn, she's far too powerful.
Here's the pl...
Argh.
♪ I'm a buff baby that
can dance like a man ♪
♪ I can shake-a my fanny, I can
shake-a my... waahhh!
Here's the plan.
- No!
- I'm going to...
Goliad, no!
Wait, brother.
Why must we fight?
Rule with me!
No, brother.
Don't you see?
They're turning us against...
So be it.
Finn, are you
okay?
Yeah.
That dude saved me.
That's Stormo,
Goliad's new brother.
Well, what are they
doing now?
They're about to
have a psychic showdown.
Whoa, man!
So, like, I guess they're so
evenly matched
that it's a stale...
blaghhh!
It's a stale...
flughhhh!
Ughh, blah!
They're so evenly
matched that it's a stalemate.
Yes.
Stormo sacrificed himself
to keep Goliad in check
for all eternity.
Well, that's pretty cool,
but I don't understand.
If Goliad and Stormo
are the same,
how come Stormo is
a good guy?
Oh, that's simple.
I used some of your heroic DNA
in Stormo's recipe
and not Goliad's.
Oh. Whoa.
So, that means Stormo is,
like, my son?
Well, yeah,
in a way.
Happy birthday, Stormo.