♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ we'll go to very distant
lands ♪
♪ with Jake the dog
and finn the human ♪
♪ the fun will never end ♪
♪ it's adventure time ♪
- Whatcha think?
- I can make that driz,
- no problem.
- It's crazy far, man.
Nah, that's just a
perspecto illusion.
It looks far 'cause the cliff's
lower.
- Eh, go for it.
- Whoo!
- Shoot!
- Almost.
- Not really.
What?!
Watch me, fool.
Hup!
Whoo!
I did it!
Sike!
Hey, you know what?
This is cool just having bro
- time for once.
- What, like no ladies?
Or dudes or whatevs.
It's just a chore sometimes.
Yeah, two people is mad
efficient.
- Whoa!
- It's a beach brawl!
Looks like they're
trying to drown a barn.
That's not a barn.
That's a dude!
Holy fizzle.
What's going on here, tough boy?
What is that huge dude?
He's the farm, the legendary
fighter of the shiney isles.
I came here to participate in
his open challenge, but this
mother can't be beat!
Give up, worms!
My fight power is supreme!
I'm too freaking legendary for
you!
Train!
Train! Train!
Whoa!
Train! Train! Train! Train!
I love you, the train!
You're almost as legendary as
the farm, the train!
The train is gonna smack you
down on his tracks!
Whoo!
Your caboose is mine!
Choo-choo!
- Oh, my glob.
Choo!
Ow!
My legs are backwards!
Why?
Ohh! You're mean!
Did you just die?
No.
The train will chug on.
My friend makes bionic legs.
I'll be better than before.
I want bionic legs!
Who's your friend?
Yeah, right.
It's secret!
Don't follow me!
- Train can do this.
- You don't want bionic
legs.
It ain't natchy.
I don't care about
natchy.
Let's discuss this
later.
You guys want to fight me?
You think we can
beat him?
Yeah way, we can't.
He's the ultimate!
But if we beat him,
we'll be crazy legends.
Man, I already am a
legend in other aspects of life.
Third highest score in
"kompy's kastle," brah.
- Third. In the candy kingdom.
- Jake, that's your
legend.
This could be our legend!
- Brogend!
- Okay, how are we gonna
- beat him, then?
- Train!
- He can't even walk.
- No, man.
"Train up," like "get ripped!"
Yeah, I was just
kidding.
Let's destroy that guy!
We're coming back for
you, the farm!
After we train!
- Yeah, that's cool.
- We're gonna annihilate
you, the farm!
Mm-kay.
I'm gonna do a
finishing move on you!!
All right! Yeah!
- Come on, Jake!
- Ugh.
- Huh! Hyah!
- Let's see your chokey
brokey style.
- Nice one.
- Yes.
Now watch my...
Something style.
- Hyah!
- Huh?
Jake?
- You're playing "kompy's kastle"?
- Huh?
Whoo!
Uh...Yes.
Winning this battle
could take our reputation to a
- whole new level!
- Look, I'm a full-grown
dog of my own, and I need to
play "kompy's kastle" every day
- so I can maintain my rank.
- So...You don't care
- about fighting the farm?
- I never really take
anything seriously.
Except "kompy's kastle."
Hy-ah!
Komp-y-y-y!!
I'm gonna break every bone in
your body, then heal you later
with that magical goo we got
from the cyclops's eye.
Aah!
- Ouch.
- Apologize!
Never!
I'm gonna turn up the
- juice!
- And I'm gonna drink it!
My little face!
Ow!
Where are you? Huh?
- Huh?
- Apologize for not
taking training seriously!
Come out, you chicken
nug!
Ow.
Apologize to
- "kompy's kastle"!
- No.
You apologize for not taking
training...Seriously.
Ugh, gross!
Ow!
Aah! My eyes!
Cheap move, you butt rag!
You...
You're the cheap move!
Huh?
Pants!
I'm really gonna wipe you now.
- Bring it on, bro!
Ou-u-ch!
Ow! Ow!!
No biteys!
I'm gonna down the farm
- without you!
- I'm gonna knock down
the farm just so you'll never
know the taste of downing the
farm!
Yo, guess
what?
Guess what, homey?
I put in the time.
I'm-a make you mine.
Yeah, that's right.
Come and get this.
So, what -- both at the same
time?
I'm cool.
You're gonna fight this, the
farm?
Okay.
Just me.
I don't need this clown town.
The only way you're
gonna win is if you use your
- cheap moves.
Hey, come on.
You got to fight the dude.
I can't see!
- Walk me to the light!
- Yeah, that's what you
get.
Cloud looks like a car.
Awaken to your dream, finn
- and Jake.
- Whoa!
Who are you?
I am the dream warrior.
I've summoned you here to hang
with me in your together dream.
Are you gonna show us a
move to beat the farm?
First, listen.
Then wake up.
All right.
I have cheap cars.
- My cars are che-e-e-ap.
- My cars are cheap.
But they drive bad when I
turn out the lights!
Turn out the lights.
These sweatpants have another
- name.
- Another name.
Yeah, don't you always
call sweatpants "give up on
- life" pants, Jake?
- I do, because peeps
need to respect themselves when
they leave the house, even if
it's just for ice cream or t.P.
Or whatevs.
Two shiny golden apples, ripe
enough to bite!
Bite!
That's all I got to say for now.
Get lost!
What is going on here,
dream warrior?
Yeah, what's this all
about?
Nap's over! Sorry!
Whoa.
That was a good nap.
Hey, did you dream
about dream warrior?
Yeah.
What was he trying to tell us
- exactly?
- I don't know.
I didn't get it.
But listen, man.
I'm sorry I got mad at you.
Who cares about my high score in
"kompy"?
It ain't important.
No, man.
It is important.
Being the third best at
something is math and deserves
respect, not like I did to
"kompy."
Anyway, I think we both got
cranky after all that training.
Well, good thing we're
rested, 'cause now we can beat
- this beast.
- Yeah!
Oh, hey! Look!
The dudes came back to
watch us fight!
A'ight. This is it.
Let's use what we learned in
- training.
- Uh...
All we did was fight dirty with
cheap -- wait.
My cars are che-e-ap.
Che-e-ap.
Dream warrior was
telling us which cheap moves to
use on the farm!
Headlights mean eyes!
- Mud in the eyes!
- Give up on life pants!
Pull down his pants
like you did to moi!
- Two golden apples!
- Mm...
- I think I know what that means.
- Well, sure, I can make
- a wild guess.
- You ready, man?
Yeah, dude!
Put your pants on.
Okay.
Ready?
Yes.