Oh
What?
Where are we?
I don't know.
What did we do last night?
Mayhaps we drank juice
of the elder toad.
Nah, I doubt it.
Yo, do you see this?
We're in a cage.
DO you think we,
like, did something wrong?
Yeah, right.
When did we ever
did wrong actions?
Get real.
Who you calling?
I'm calling Beemo --
see if he knows what happened.
You know, with us being here and junk.
My new camera phone.
Wait. Come here.
What?
I guess I vid-taped a
buttload of stuff on here.
Play it for the
clues within.
Okay , play.
Did you take it yet?
Recording.
Okay, get a shot of the portal.
Gonna go through this biz.
All right, let's do --
Oh, no! What?!
Battery crunked out.
Dude, do you remember
any of that mess?
No.
But I guess we're
here on purpose?
So, we opened a portal
to somewhere, but where?
The Nightosphere.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah...
You're in the Nightosphere.
Are you sure?
Uh, yes.
You got thrown in jail.
Look.
Look!
Marceline's dad!
We really are
in the Nightosphere!
Up and at 'em, people.
Everyone out of your cages.
My shift is over,
and no one's shown up, so...
Whoa, wait.
You're letting us go?
I mean... yeah,
but not really.
You're in the Nightosphere,
so...
So... what?
Is there an outlet
somewhere for this?
Hey, come on!
Just tell us how we
can get back to our world.
You can't leave
the Nightosphere --
not unless he lets you.
Marceline's dad.
Yeah, that's Hunson Abadeer.
He runs this place.
Hunson Abadeer?
All right.
Well, dude,
how do we talk to him?
You can't just
talk to the boss.
You got to make
an appointment.
Yeah, but we don't
even know why we're here.
And what's up with this?
Ugh. Ah. Oh, Oh, sick!
You touch that stuff'?
Later, fools.
Hey! Hey, is there an
outlet anywhere?
You guys!
Maybe this is where they
put all the dummy demons.
Right, big guy?
You're not so smart, right?
Yea-a-a-h.
Let's go out that hole, man.
Okay, get on.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Pretty neat.
Whoa! Look!
Charlic, don't socialize
with the smaller demons!
They're dirty and stupid!
Whoa!
Daddy!
What is that?
I think it's, like,
sentient blood mist.
Cool.
Come on.
Let's see if anyone knows
where Hunson Abadeer is.
All right.
Well, how about that dude?
Okay.
Yo, bros! How do we talk
to Hunson Abadeer?
The teller can help you.
Get in my flipping belly,
and I will transport you.
My insides are habitable.
You will not be digested.
Bye, mister!
Who's the teller?
That guy?
Okay, bozos, make room.
Make room. Make room.
Ouch! Come on!
Scooch over, fatty.
I can't, dude.
This outbox is packed tighter
than my tummy tunnel when
I can't make brown on the camping
trips because of my anxieties.
And I have I.B.S., also.
Ow!
Hey, guy!
Are you the teller?
No. No, no, this is the
line to meet the teller.
No, man!
Are you for real?
How long's the wait?
I don't know.
I just like to row around
on top of their heads.
Bunk that!
Hey, do you know about this?
I, uh -- ohh. No.
Sick.
Why do we need to
see the teller anyway?
We just want to
see Hunson Abadeer
and find out what
happened to us.
The teller will get you
in touch with Hunson Abadeer.
We got systems down here.
You got to swim the proper
channels, you know?
Youse ain't special!
Youse got to wait
like the rest of youse!
Us.
Where's the line start?
Oh I don't know.
The thing sort
of governs itself.
Tight!
Ow!
That guy stinks.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Big man? Over here!
Huh? What, me?
Uh, yeah. How long have
you been in line for?
How...long?
Oh, butt traps.
Jake, stretch us to the front.
No cutting!
I will kill you with
all my hopes and regrets!
All right, dudes, chill!
We'll wait.
I can't feel my legs.
Say something!
Say something to me!
I... can't.
I got nothing to say anymore.
Just make up words, then!
Bloo-be-de bloo bloo
bloo-blee-blee blah!
Shree shrah ha--
Hey, check it out.
We're at the front
of the line.
Whoo-hoo!
Yo, yo!
We want to talk
to Abadeer!
What? Oh.
When your thingy comes up,
Hunson Abadeer will
see you through the door.
42 million?!
What's the number on the door?
41 million...zabba, dabba...
We're next! Whew!
Man, I thought I
was gonna throw up.
That's us!
Yay!
Noooooooooo!
I'm gonna lose it!
Hey, do you know if
there's an outlet anywhere?
No.
Do you know what
this is all about?
No.
Gross.
What's going on, buddy?
You giving up?
I guess.
You don't want to just
stick it out a little more'?
I don't know if my little-boy
heart can take it.
Listen, Finn.
Are you listening?
Mm-hmm.
Your heart may be small, but
it's strong as a bull donk!
And I know you can wait through
this line so we can meet
Hunson Abadeer and
find out why we're here
and why we're in
a pile of Banyanles.
'Cause you're a champ!
Okay?!
Okay.
Jozu des gamate ne.
Well, at least I can see
the end of the line ...l think.
Let's wait the heck
out of this line!
That's it, champ!
Pretty pumped up.
I'm super pumped!
Does anyone need
to go pee-pees?!
Go ahead.
Okay.
Who's here with a
question for Mr. Abadeer?
Oh, yeah.
We've got questions.
Put your hand down, Finn!
No way, dude!
I've got questions!
What the hey, Jake?!
It's not answering questions,
man.
That thing's gonna
bake our beans!
Hey, blood-mist cloud!
What happened to us?!
Why can't we remember anyth--
Oh. It's gone.
Look.
Ride me, partner.
Hup!
Hey, cloud!
Where's Abadeer?!
Whoa.
Look at all these paintings.
I think this is
Hunson Abadeer's house.
Hey!
Hunson Abadeer!
How dare you chumps
trespass here?
We just want to
go home, man.
Yeah. Why'd you lock us up,
Abadeer?
When Marceline finds
out about this,
it's gonna stir up some heavy
daddy-daughter issues!
No one leaves
the Nightosphere!
Aw, come on, man!
No one!
No one leaves
the Nightosphere!
Come with me, you juicy,
little, mortal soul.
Finn!
Oh, my log, Jake.
You found the portal!
Huh?
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Huh?!
We don't want to hurt you,
Abadeer.
Just let us go!
Ugh!
- Hyah!
- Ow!
Rrragh!
What the--?
Marceline?!
I'm gonna close
this portal!
You're forbidden to come
back to the Nightosphere!
But, Marcy!
Let us help you!
It's too late!
Stay away from me!
Foreve-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-r!
Marceline's in trouble.
We got to go back and save her!
All right, but I'm
gonna take a shower first.