♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Don't ever mess
with me again.
Who was that?
The Princess of the Fire Kingdom.
Dude.
I think I have a crush.
What do you know
about her, Jake?
I was trying to help you get
over your Princess Bubblegum
sad times by
hooking you two up.
But she's evil, man.
You shut your
dirty mouth!
Dirty?!
Huh.
No, really, man!
Her dad said she was evil!
Nah, man.
I peeped beyond
her burning gaze
and noshed hot
lunch with her soul.
She ain't evil.
She's passionate.
Help me track her down.
Mmmmm...
Come on, man.
I really like her.
Help me out.
Jake.
Jake, help me out.
Help me out.
Jake.
Jake, help me!
Jake!
Jake, help me!!
Ye-e-e-e-a-ah, okay.
Whoo! All right!
You sure you're not into
any other Princesses?
What about Wildberry Princess?
She's small and plump.
You could sleep on
her like a pillow.
Could be nice.
Is that bird...
smoking?
Hey!
Don't you judge me!
It was that fire chick down
there that done this to me!
Oh!
Oh, Jake.
Look at her.
She's innocent...
like the steam off a puppy's nose
searching for
ham in the snow.
Guy drops one piece of ham in
the snow and he never hears
the end of it!
Snap out of it!
She's burning cute
little flowers!
Yeah.
She is like a cute,
little flower.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
I-I was just
worried about you.
Huh?
Look, I-I'm sorry
about before.
I-I don't know what happened,
but I just...
I had to see
you again.
And I don't know, really...
I don't know anything
about you, but I just...
I really like you.
You know, you're...
you're so...
beautiful.
Aaah!
Aah!
Ow!
Oh, glob!
Am I hurting you?
Yes!
That's all you've done!
Are you trying to hurt me?
Is that why you're
following me?!
I'm not following...
Well, I guess technically
I am following you...
Hey! No! Wait!
I guess now I'm
technically chasing you.
Finn!
Hold on!
Ow!
Toasty buns!
Where are you?!
I want to chat it up with you!
Oh, we lost her!
Whoa.
I am ambushing you!
Rrah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
Whoa!
Hey, I like your fireballs.
Huh?
Why do you torment me?!
I'm not trying to!
I just like you.
I think I...
I think I like like you.
Listen, when I look at you,
my brain goes all stupid,
and I just want to hug you
and sit on the couch and...
and play Beemo with you.
I can't explain why, but...
I've never felt this way,
and I think we should be together.
I...
Yeah!
Ugh! Enough!
You should not toy with the
emotions of a fire elemental.
Wait! Wait!
I really didn't...
You told me you liked me, and
you made my flame grow brighter.
But then you put me out...
Which hurt!
Gyah!
You're trying to impede me.
That must be your purpose.
But fire's purpose is to burn.
So I'm going to turn this
land into my fire kingdom!
No!
Ooh! Ow! Hot! Hot!
She's headed for the
Goblin Kingdom!
We need to defeat
this fiery she-beast!
I can't fight her, man.
I'm still into her.
Finn!
What's more important...
your love for that
screwball dame
or being a hero and saving the
lives of innocent goblin folk?
Being a hero.
All right! Come on!
Let's go build fireproof suits!
I got to get back to her!
Dude, slow down, or your
fire suit will be junk.
Ooh!
Is bags of old
bread fireproof?
Jake!
You found Neptr!
I am the ultimate
hide-and-seek champion.
15 months, 4 days, 9 hours,
and you guys did not find me.
Oh, plops.
We forgot about the game.
Shhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
I missed you, creator.
And we missed you, too,
but, Neptr, right now, we need you to...
To count to 100
while you hide?
One, two, three, four, five...
Neptr.
Will you help us
build fireproof suits?
You cannot tell,
but I am giving a thumbs-up.
♪ Working for the master ♪
♪ Preventing a disaster ♪
♪ Building giant robots from
aluminum and plaster ♪
♪ Faster, a cast to
build the blaster ♪
♪ Yes, for foam and water ♪
♪ Yes, for when it's hotter ♪
♪ I've got it,
it's no bother ♪
♪ 'Cause I live to please you,
father ♪
I am finished.
I sure hope Flame
Princess is okay.
Ha ha!
We are as one, creator.
Jake, you think
Flame Princess is okay?
Du-u-u-u-de!
I feel like I could
touch the heavens...
and sock angels!
We're coming up on
the Goblin Kingdom!
There she is.
She seems okay.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Wood for sale!
Wood on fire for sale!
It's really starting
to come together.
Needs more...
fire.
Hmmmm.
- Flame Princess!
- Huh?
Listen, you got to stop
burning the Goblin Kingdom.
But I don't want to fight you...
or hurt you.
I swear!
I've heard this all before.
You meanie!
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
My cart!
I was born in that cart!
I'll put it out!
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
- Aah!
Aaaah!
Jake didn't mean that!
Ook!
I need your help, Finn!
This one's too big!
Aah!
Why-y-y-y-y-y-y-y-y-y-y?!
No, Jake, stop!
You're hurting her!
I will solve this, creator.
I will extinguish her using
our suit's foam blaster.
Hold still, burning lady.
Wha...?
Locked on target.
No, Neptr!
Yes, creator.
N-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
I'm sorry!
Whoa!
That is the last
time you hurt me.
Rrrrrrrrrrrraaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
My bad, Jake!
Turn it off, Neptr!
Oh, my.
N-o-o-o-o!
Rrrrrrrrrraaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
No more! No more!!
Flame Princess!
I can't fight her.
But... but I can't let
her destroy the city.
I've failed everyone.
Not true, creator.
You haven't failed Neptr.
Even if everyone burns,
you'll still have me, creator.
Mmm!
No.
Why can't I just like a girl?
Ow!
Huh?
Oh!
Did I... do something... cool
while I was knocked out?
I understand now.
You're a water elemental.
What?!
You're my opposite.
You create water.
What? Cry?
No, I ju...
Yeah.
You cry and cry all the time.
N-no! No!
I-I-I don't
usually do that.
That's your power.
No! No-no-no-no-no-no!
Finn, even if we
like each other,
we're going to
hurt each other.
No!
W-we don't have to!
I can take it.
I-I mean, can't we try?
You would defy nature for me?
Uh... yeah.
Whatevs.
Aah.
Bye, Finn.
Goodbye, Lady.
Finn! Oh, my glob, man!
Everyone's dead, man!
They're all burned!
There's barbecued
bods everywhere!
Wha-a-a-t?!
I'm just kidding.
I saved them.
Everyone's fine.
See?
Yeah, we're alive.
So, how'd everything
go with Flame Princess?
She hugged me,
then left.
Whoa!
How did it feel?
It hurt.