Credits and bs
I remember you.
Okay, Gunther.
You ready for the show to begin?
One, two, three...
Gunther, why did you Gunt my fries?
I gunted them, and they were mine.
What kind of Gunt Gunts
his Gunther's fries?
And doesn't even Gunt him in the eyes.
Gunther there were tears there.
If you Gunted them would you even care?
Gunther, do you even love me?
It's rethorical, Gunther.
Marceline's songs are so good.
Maybe I can get Marceline to
write a song with me.
Man, if she helped me
write a song like that,
I'd be crushing it non stop
with the princesses.
Oh, yeah!
Gunther, you cute little dummie.
You know, Gunther?
My song is gonna need some
dope lyrics to lure the honeys in.
Jay T. Dawgzone always says
ladies are drawn to bros
with tortured pasts.
And I got a way tortured past.
I think.
I don't really... re...
Quickly, Gunther.
To the "the past room".
Oh, yes.
Lot of emotionally powerful
stuff in here.
It's still wet with tears.
I'll take some of this for
lyrical inspiration.
So, where's Marceline living this days?
A cave?
Well, well, well.
Looks like Ice king is up to bad biscuits brother.
Bad biscuits make the baker broke, bro.
Ice king, you make our job too easy.
You ready to roll on this fool?
Do the roll!
Hello? Anybody home?
No.
What are you doing here?
I told you not to come around me.
Yeah, I know. But I was hoping you
could help me write a song.
One that could help me get
some princess action.
I'm not gonna help you
pick up on chicks!
Come on!
We can be a prog rock duo!
I'll even split the fans with you.
I get the princesses and you get...
whatever it is you're into.
Sounds good, yeah, I think it does.
Hey, get out of here!
Wait, just let me play you
what I've written so far.
Oh, dang it, tangles in the cord.
Sometimes this happens
when you fly with it.
Tangles are hard.
Oh geez, no.
Oh, no.
Ice kings' in trouble.
Hey you know what?
I'll just hum it for you.
Is that good?
Ice king!
Whaaa?
Oh, you got him.
Nice job, Marceline.
Your constant harrasement of the
female gender makes me sick.
No, he can stay.
What?
Yeah, what?
It's all right, we're working
on a song together.
You don't want us to...
for you?
No, it's okay, you guys can go.
Okay...
Well I guess we'll see you, then.
- Bye.
You know? I kind of like being
tied up in this cords.
Kind of fruity.
So, what kind of song are we playing?
Oh, I brought these for some inspiration.
I'll just use this to work off a,
you know, a template.
Okay.
Yeah, that's good, keep doing that.
# Slime princess, you're all right. #
# Flame princess, you're okay. #
# Wild berry princess could be better. #
# All of the princesses are
pretty all right, but, #
# oh, Bubblegum, you look
like a lot of fun. #
# I write outside, and that
is how I know. #
# Hey, princess did you get my text #
# with the picture of my
awesome gun show? #
# I'm also working on my pecs. #
# If you'd like I'll send you
a picture of that too. #
# Oh, Bubblegum, I really need someone. #
# Or anyone. #
# Pretty much anyone. #
# I'm so alone. #
# Won't somebody tell me
what's wrong with me? #
# Anybody? #
Grob in the sky, please tell me why!
Stop acting like this!
No! It's just starting to get good!
Anybody!
Princesses, I command you! Love me!
Love me!
Love me. Love me.
Stop acting crazy.
I just wanna be loved!
I'm sorry I pushed you.
I'll just stay out of your way.
Again, I'm sorry I pushed you.
What you got? An apple?
# You're so annoying,
you pitiful old man. #
# I'd like to help you, but
I don't know if I can. #
# I thought you were nuts. #
# But you're really really
really nuts. #
# Everytime I move, eventually you find
me and start hanging around. #
# Just another lame excuse to see me,
man, it's getting me down. #
# You know? I'm actually
glad to see you. #
# Maybe I'm the one who's... #
nuts.
Hold on.
Do you... like me?
Of course I do, you old jerk!
Really?
How about one of this?
Not like that!
You don't remember anything,
do you, Simon?
What-mon?
Why do you even come see me
when you don't remember me?
You don't even know who you are.
Yes I do. I am a lyricist.
It's all here, on the page.
The page in song, baby.
On this receipt, on this take out menu,
on this newspapers.
Look, this clipping...
this was you, Simon,
before the war.
This! You took this picture.
You scribbled all over it.
Oh, oh, are they good lyrics?
I'll get the keyboard.
What? Wait, listen!
Yeah, let's go! What does it say?
Sing out, sister.
# Marceline, is it just you and me
in the wreckage of the world? #
# That must be so confusing
for a little girl. #
# And I know you're going to
need me here with you, #
# but I'm losing myself and I'm affraid
you're gonna lose me too. #
Ooh, yeah! Keep it going!
# This magic keeps me alive, #
# but it's making me crazy, #
# and I need to save you, #
# but who's going to save me? #
# Please forgive me for whatever I do #
# when I don't remember you. #
Wow, I love that. Hot stuff.
What? You don't remember what it means?
Look!
# Marceline, #
# I can feel myself sliping away. #
# I can't remember what
it made me say, #
# but I remember that I saw you frown. #
# I swear it wasn't me,
it was the crown. #
# This magic keeps me alive,
but it's making me crazy. #
# And I need to save you, #
# but who's going to save me? #
# Please, forgive me for... #
What is going on in there?
I have no idea.
# Please forgive me for whatever I do, #
# when I don't remember you. #