Okay. I'm going to lower the screen.
Tell me what you see.
Crunchy, you look like
a rainbow.
It's beautiful.
Can you guys see that?
Nope, only you can see it because
you're hooked up
to the aura visualizer.
But actually, I'm lying.
We can see everything you see
on this screen.
Now I'm gonna send that image
into Crunchy.
Whoa!
The aura's gone.
- Except...
- Whoa!
...Crunchy's true essence manifested
in the material plane.
I want to see
Peppermint Butler's aura!
You don't want to see that.
Yeah, we do!
Right, Princess?
Sure, Finn. Just let me
recalibrate the device.
No! Bunk that.
I'm tired. Come on, Finn.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, me and Jake,
we got to peace out.
Goodnight.
Hey, what's going on
in here?
- Yo, guys!
- Hey, Finn.
Whoa, what's that?
Security cams?
Yeah, man. You gotta see
some crazy stu--
Yo, shut up!
- Oh, shoot.
- What?
Nothing.
- What is it?
- Nothing!
Show us now!
Show you what?
What you said!
We didn't say nothing!
It's too late for take backs!
We practically
know everything already!
Now show us!
Okay, but you can't tell anyone.
Yeah, this is our weird secret.
Of course, dude.
All right.
Now look at monitor three.
Can you see it?
Oh, yeah. That's uh...
Who is that?
That's Chocoberry.
Why you guys spying on Chocoberry?
No, man.
Look there, in the corner.
- Who's that?
- Zoom in, dude.
Plus, plus, plus, plus, plus,
plus, plus, plus --
Lemongrab! What the...?!
This is our weird secret, okay?
Remember that.
How long has this been
going on?
He's shown up every night for
the past two weeks.
He goes to different rooms
and just stands there.
And you didn't tell me?!
If we told you, then we knew
you'd mess up
our weird TV show.
Banana guarding is boring.
I'm gonna talk to him.
Oh, no. You see?
Sorry, guys.
Lemongrab!
Nyah!
Why are you stalking my peeps?!
I am within my rights!
Yeah, but what are you doing?
It's creeping me out.
Uh, I am the Earl...
- Yeah?
- The Earl...
of nothing!
Wait!
What do you mean, "nothing"?
Castle Lemongrab has no citizens!
You have excess candies!
You must donate.
Dona-a-a-te!
In your dreams, you freak.
But you don't get
along with others.
I don't understand you, Lemongrab.
No one --
no one understands!
I am alone, and you made me
like this.
You made me!
You're... my... glob!
You're my gob!
What are we gonna do?
Something totally bum slops.
No, no! We won't go!
Please! Please!
All I need is three healthy
volunteers
to move in with Lemongrab.
He's all by himself
with no one to govern.
No, no! We won't go!
Come on, Mr. Cupcake.
Just for a little while?
I can't, Princess.
My arm is broken.
Dude, you didn't have
to do that.
All right, what's
it gonna take, people?
Two things, Princess.
Yeah, that's right.
Back up, fools.
You got nerve
showing your faces here,
Notorious Pup Gang.
Bunch of bad apples.
Back up, Finn.
I'll take you out!
We came out of hiding
'cause all y'all is scared
of a Lemon man.
And we ain't afraid,
so we gots demands.
And what is that?
One -- total amnesty
for past crimes
committed by the Pup Gang.
Hmm... granted.
Wait. They threw a basketball
at my head one time.
You gonna let that slide?
We only did that 'cause
you're old.
You sacks!
I'll rip your cups!
Jake, please.
What is your second demand?
We want the big
cash-money wad --
enough to provide for our
delinquent mothers
so that, hopefully,
they'll show us the love
we always dreamed about
in our sad, young lives.
Huh.
I grant you
the big cash-money wad!
Now off with you
to Castle Lemongrab!
Yo, Lemongrease.
We're gonna live here at
Lemongrabs now.
Yes.
I'm Jamaica, and this is
Toughy and Blombo.
Blombo, what is that?
- What?
- On Blombo's ears?
That's his headphones.
Blombo, take them off!
Blombo!
You must heed my instructions!
Take off your things!
Whoa, settle down, Lemongrease.
I am not grease!
This is unacceptable!
What? What's going on?
All unfit citizens of
Lemongrab must be reconditioned!
Man, are you crazy?
Yo-u-u-u-u-u-u-u-u!
M-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e!
I have to use
my sound sword now!
You guys.
What -- where are we?
You are in my reconditioning chamber.
You will receive four to three
units of juice now.
Ooh-ah!
♪ Crunchy. Wake up, Crunchy ♪
Eh? Glob, is that you?
No sign of Lemongrab for three days.
I think it worked.
Maybe.
Let's keep looking.
Aw, geez.
Hey!
- Huh?
What happened to
your new citizens?
They didn't understand
my Lemonstylz.
I like this way better.
Hmm... I wonder if
maybe you don't understand
their Candy stylz.
Come on!
Let me show you something.
You see, Earl, candy people
are mad special.
They need constant stroking
and snuggling.
Here, you try.
Ha-ha, ha!
Ha-ha, ha-ha, ha!
Goo-goo, uh, g-goo!
Put you in my oven!
Nyah! It's gross!
And who says
your Way's right, anyway?
I look in the Lemonheart
you gave me
and see my Lemonway to act,
and that must be right!
Man, that guy's a real d-list.
Oh, dear. His candy citizens!
Let's crush this mess all accordingly!
Crazy light-bulb freestyle!
Yeah!
No. He's my responsibility.
I have to try to help him.
- Okay, that's cool, too.
- Hop on.
Hup!
Lemongrab?
No Lemongrab.
Come on.
Let's find the Pup Gang quick.
Wait. I have a plan.
You guys go on ahead.
Okay, cool.
Hmm.
What do you got, Jake?
Just an empty room with a Catcher's mitt.
Weird.
Oh. Oh, no!
Oh! Ah!
Goonie-goo-goo-foofie!
Kooky-kooky-kooky!
This is serious!
Pup Gang got four units.
Maybe... maybe 10 units for trespassers!
You got tricks, huh?
Got to fall down sometime,
and when you do...
12 units!
Lemongrab, stop!
Huh?
Please, Earl.
I can help you.
No! No!
No more helping!
You're the one
who made me this way!
How can you help?!
You unload your punkest
boys on me?
You try to change my ways.
You poison!
You need reconditioning!
Reconditio-o-o-o-n!
Whoa, whoa! Whoa!
Yo-u-u-u-u!
N-o-o-o!
Whoa, whoa. What the hey?
Wait, Lemongrab.
Look!
Hello?
Am I in the right room?
Huh? What?
Who's this rigmarole?
- I'm Lemongrab.
- Oh.
I made him for you
in your pantry,
for you to be with.
Two L-Lemongrabs?
Hmm?
Hmm.
Yeah, okay!
Yeah!
All in favor of pardoning
the prisoners?
Aye!
Pardons for all!
Goodbye, Lemongrabs! Goodbye!
Take care, boys!
Yes. Yes, indeed.
Ha ha!
A lemon gives by taking.
And cares by yelling.
- Hmm!
Well, okay!
Stop by anytime!
But call first!
Yes, goodbye!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪