Well, looks like
your new house is done.
Jake, you want to check out
the new house?
Nah, don't let me
interrupt you.
You two have fun.
I wanna see inside.
I love it!
Great!
Huh. This doesn't hurt
as bad as it used to.
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Oh, gob! Oh, gob! Oh, gob!
Finn!
I'm okay!
Hmm.
Oh!
Do the thing that I like.
Now do the thing that I like.
Classic.
All right, Finn,
that's enough.
Thank you for building
my new home, Finn.
I'm so happy.
You want a hug?
Yes.
Whoa. Hold on, mama.
Okay, bro, tinfoil's on.
You can hug now.
Bye.
Bye, Finn.
Looks like your date
went pretty good, buddy.
Ah, I don't know.
Was the hug okay?
Give me some tips, mang.
Bro, you gotta let things
take their natural path.
Look. Look, let me explain some
junk about dating.
Right now you're at tier 1,
which is hugging.
But pretty soon,
you'll be at tier 2,
which is smooching.
Then down the road,
you'll make it to tier 5,
where she'll let you
discover all 15 feet
of her long,
beautiful stomach.
And after a while,
you'll make it to tier 8,
where you touch her horn
for the very first time.
Very special.
What about tier 15?
You stay away
from that!
Do not do tier 15!
Dude, I got no idea
what you're talking about.
Don't worry about it,
dude.
Just let things naturally move
to tier 2.
Oh, and, um...
you need a shower, dude.
What?!
Oh, gross!
Do you think Flame Princess
could smell me?
- Probably.
- Crup.
'Sup, guys?
Princess Bubblegum?!
What are you doing here?
Collecting taxes.
You guys weren't home,
so I let myself in.
- Oh.
- I'm gonna take a shower.
Princess, do not inhale!
- What? Why?
- Just don't!
What's that all
about?
Ah, he's just smelly
from a day of running around
with his lady friend.
Ooh! A lady friend.
Do tell.
Uh, I shouldn't say.
It's his business.
Oh, come on.
You can tell me.
That's his personal biz.
You gotta respect
a man's p-biz.
Okay, you're right.
I'll respect it.
Flame Princess! He was hanging out
with Flame Princess.
What?!
And I don't mean to be
telling stories out of school,
but pretty soon, they're gonna
be taking it to tier 2.
No.
This isn't possible.
Oh, it's possible.
I just never thought...
Flame Princess.
I --
I have to go.
Morrow!
Hmm. Weird.
Guess who's late for their
video chat?
President Porpoise!
No. No.
Oh, gob.
I thought I'd be
ready for this.
Yowwwwwwwwn!
Jake, I'm going to see
Flame Princess.
Be back later.
Finn!
Aaaah!
Okay, Princess, you need
to stop breaking in here.
I have something
important to tell you
about relationships.
Uh, that's okay,
Princess.
I just hope
you'll understand.
Relationships are like layers
of sedimentary rock.
Jake, Flame Princess is
waiting for me.
I'm gonna bounce out.
Okay. Tier 2, baby.
Word.
If too much frustration builds,
the magma will erupt,
causing a catastrophic
superstratum of
igneous rock to form.
What? Where am I?
Jake, you're president now.
Oh, my gosh!
Jake!
Wake up!
- Jake, where's Finn?
- He stepped out.
Will you tell him why he can't
see Flame Princess anymore?
Oh.
Ohhh!
I see what's going on here.
Great. I cannot stress
how important it is
that they not see each other.
Oh, man.
PB is totally jealous of
Flame Princess!
Jump. Punch. Kick. Kick.
- 'Sup, man?
- Yo, dude.
So, what did PB want?
She doesn't want you to
see Flame Princess anymore.
She's crazy jealous.
So, you at tier 2 yet?
I got about five hugs.
Does that count?
Nope!
Well, still at tier 1.
I know exactly what'll
get you to tier 2 --
a sappy poem.
Say something about her
spectrum.
Ew!
Let's see...
she's bright.
She's beautiful.
She makes me feel...
confused.
Like something's
filling up my chest.
Like I can't breathe.
Is it because she's so
dangerous?
Glob, Jake,
I-I can't stand it!
Inspiratio.
- Finn!
- Aaaah!
Whatcha doin'?
Oh. Uh, hi, Princess.
I'm, uh, writing
something for Jake.
Oh.
Well, speaking of Jake, did he
explain everything to you?
Yeah.
- And you understand?
- Yeah, I understand.
Finn, sometimes
you want someone
and you want to kiss them
and be with them,
but you can't because
responsibility demands sacrifice.
What are you trying
to say?!
I'm trying to say
that you're a hero, Finn.
You're my hero.
So, I'm glad you understand
why you can't be with
Flame Princess.
Bubblegum, I can't do this
anymore!
- What?
- Now you like me?!
Finn, what are you
talking about?
What am I talking about?!
PB, I was --
I was in love
with you, okay?!
And you didn't love me back.
Now I'm ready to move on,
and it's like...
...you're gonna build me up
all over again.
Well, I'm done!
I'm done.
Oh, no.
♪ Bacon pancakes,
making bacon pancakes ♪
♪ Take some bacon,
and I'll put it in a pancake ♪
♪ Bacon pancakes, that's what
it's gonna make ♪
♪ Bacon panca-a-a-a-ke ♪
Finn?!
Jake, where's Finn?
Is he with Flame Princess?
Back off, Bubblegum.
That's his man's biz.
Is he with her
or not?!
You heartless monster.
Do you have any idea
how much
he's cried over you?!
Finn deserves to be happy!
Even if his bloopin' face
gets burned off!
You should be ashamed!
- You're sick!
- What are you --
This isn't about some
petty love triangle!
Flame Princess is
physically unstable!
Her elemental matrix can't
handle extreme romance.
Glob, if Finn tries
to kiss her,
she'll burn so hot,
she'll melt right through the
planet's crust,
down through the molten
core.
Then she'll be thrown back
and forth by gravity
until she burns out the world
from the inside!
Why do you think I had her father
keep her locked up?!
Will you take me
to them?
Faster!
Your wavelengths are my weakness.
Your emissions are what
I've been missing.
No.
Aaah!
Flame Princess?!
Flame Princess!
Finn!
Finn, there's no time!
You have to --
Are you all right?
Finn!
Flame Princess!
It's hot!
Wait. Wait!
Don't move.
This is good.
If you stay
on the hole for 24.8 seconds,
the reaction will be
deprived of oxygen.
She'll go out.
What about Finn?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Please -- say something.
Please, I need you...
to be okay.
Huh?
Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
She's stabilized.
We're safe...
for now.
Oh, Finn.
What?
Jealous?
Shut up.