My King.
My King?
Wake up, husband.
What?
Long live the King!
What is going on?
Mm. Not much.
Long live the King!
Huh?!
Wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah...
Hey. Do I know you?
...wuah-wuah-wuah --
Hey.
I-I know that guy.
He doesn't know
he's dreaming.
Huh?
Huh?!
Come on, honey.
Eat your soup.
Huh?
Wait. Wait, wait.
Eat it now!
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm!
What kind of --
Aah!
How...did we get here?
Uh...
I'm good on the soup.
Huh?
You!
You haven't much time, sir.
What?!
You are trapped in a dream,
and you are in danger.
You need to find this
worm and break it.
Find the worm?
But...you've got
him right there.
Satori!
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Come on.
Jake?
Ohh!
Pfllllll!
Hold down the tape
until it fully sticks to the paper.
Like this?
Yes. But now try
holding it higher.
Like this?
You need more tape.
Use this.
Now tape the bottom.
Who's it for?
It's for, um...
Pfllllll!
It's for me!
Play this.
Um...okay.
The worm!
Wo-o-o-o-rm!
Worm!
Woiiiim!
Finn!
Aw, man!
Is it really you?
Jake?
Yeah.
I think so.
Yup.
I'm trapped in this dream,
and I can't wake up.
Me too.
I was just in some other
part of the dream with
Princess Bubblegum and
Flame Princess.
Make-out dreams?
Nice!
What?!
No, it wasn't like that.
Hey, I won't judge.
Uueeeggghhhhh!
Lady's got two mouths.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think she's real.
Weird.
Ouch!
What was that for?!
Just wanted to make
sure you were real.
Our dreams must be linked,
for some reason.
Whoa!
Well, Pep But told me we got
to find that worm that crawled
through that hole
and break it.
In my dream --
In my dream, suddenly,
an unimaginably amazing sword
appeared in front of me,
able to blast
the hole open.
Rad!
I usually dream of
messed-up stuff,
like a shark trying
to bite off my face.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Oh! Oh!
Careful!
If you grunk up the dreamscape
with your subconscious fears,
the whole thing
will blow apart.
Ohhhh.
Just shrink down,
like me.
And then, I shrunk down,
like Jake.
How come you know so much
about dreams and stuff?
'Cause I sleep a lot.
Oh, yeah.
Fionna! Cake!
I need your help!
What?!
What did you say?
I really did
it this time.
They're loose,
and they're coming for us!
Who?
Aaaah!
Aah!
Dad?
Help us!
Maybe he's not really...
real.
Dad? Are you okay?
That scarf
looks familiar.
Yeah.
Man!
The worm is fast!
Yeah, it's nuts --
fast as nuts.
Well, let's catch
it with...
Some big ol' legs!
Well, that's kind of boring
for me 'cause that's my
normal power, you know?
Then you get...
birds!
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi!
Remember --
this is just a dream.
Keep climbing.
Now what?
Break it.
Pshhh!
Gah!
Jake!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you?
I'm okay.
We did it!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Hmm.
Was that -- was that
mirror always like that?
I'm pretty sure
this is not normal.
Nah. It's fine.
Aah!
Jake?
I think we're
still dreaming.
Nah, it's just dream residue.
Forget about it.
You sure know a
lot about dream stuff.
Hmm.
You pinched me earlier,
but I never pinched you.
Everything's normal.
It's still a dream.
Hmm.
Huh?!
Hey, guys.
Hyah!
Ha ha.
Why are you janking
up my dreamscape?!
Listen,
don't worry about it.
What?!
You can't defeat me.
I'm the King Worm.
I'm going to keep you in this
dreamscape until I've consumed
all your life energy.
My life energy?!
I use that!
Huuaahhh...
Wait.
Something's wrong.
I'm missing something.
Wait. Something's wrong.
- Worm!
...something's wrong.
I'm missing something.
- Worm!
Oh, man.
I'm gonna be stuck here --
forever.
Ouch!
Hey, guys.
Knock it off.
Huh?
Psst!
If you grunk up the dreamscape
with your subconscious fears,
the whole thing
will blow apart.
Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks, dream Jake!
Get ready to eat it!
Wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah
wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah...
Okay, Finn.
Concentrate.
Deepest gut fears!
Oh, gross!
The ocean.
Aah!
Yah!
Aaah!
Yaah!
Yaaaaaaaaaaah!
Okay.
Okay, that wasn't so bad.
Aah!
Oh, grob!
The Lich! Aah!
Hey, why don't you sit down or
pass out or something?
Never!
Bubblegum!
Waa-hooo!
Finn! Shush!
I'm having coffee
with the Lich.
You wouldn't understand.
You're too young!
Bleahh!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aah!
So much screaming!
Yaah! Aaah! Aaaah!
Had...enough...
destabilization?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm a clown-ning-ning-ning.
Eep!
Well, that's that.
Wuah-wuah-wuah-wuah...
I don't feel so good.
Get out of our house, King Worm!
Is it really
you this time?
Yeah, mans --
actual Jake.
Cool...
Pinch.
Ow! Man, come on!
I'm just checking.
Just checking.