Reign of Gunthers
Where the turd is my
demonic wishing eye?
I've looked everywhere.
What is it girl?
Do you know where it is?
Lead the way!
Oh, boy. This is just wonderful.
You just want me to brush you.
You know this brush is
for princesses only?
Ah! Princesses only.
No Gunthers.
What are my options here?
Gunther! What is your damage today?
Wizard market!
W, I, Z...
Hey!
You're really peebing me off, Gunther.
Go stand in the corner.
I said stand in the corner.
You make me sick.
Try not to break anything
while I'm gone.
Gunther?
Jake, we gots penguins.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Come on, you guys. Get off me now.
Jake?
Now, shoo, you little creeps.
This is unusual.
Glob drag all.
What's with these super penguins?
I don't know, I'm guessing
it's the Ice king.
- Well where is he then?
- Ice king!
Wizards rule.
Uh, let's see.
That's the symbol for
magic items, right?
Hey, this is the magic
items shop, right?
What does it look like, you dunk?
I know that, I know.
Why can't they write it
on the sign, though?
Why is it all gotta be secret?
Let's just put it all out there, uh?
Equal distribution of
magic to the people.
No more symbols.
No more initiations.
You feelin' me huntress wizard?
You tryin' to get killed, Ice king?
I was just steppin' to you, girl,
with my intellectual wizard politics.
No, don't go.
Well, swing at every ball,
that's what Jay T. Dangzone says.
Hello.
So then he was telling me to beef
in the eye of glob and stuff.
Whoa, did you do it?
Yes, I did.
- Yo, I wouldn't do that.
- Get over it, man.
Don't you wanna reach the highest
initiation of the secret schools?
Of course, man.
In shadow we find the light.
Safely sealed in darkest night.
So make sure y'all keep it tight.
Wizards only, fools.
Keep what tight?
A secret you never should
have heard, Ice king.
Yo, guys, chill. I lost my
demonic wishing eye.
Just give me a new one and I'll jet.
I didn't hear nothing about no
weird secret wizard club
that I wanna be a part of.
Loose lips sink the ships, Ice king.
Sorry, man. Nothing personal.
Oh, sleds.
You, guys!
Okay, I give up.
Gunther?
Nice eyes.
What's going on here, man.
Cold your super-bros.
Well, that's great.
Where's the Ice king, Gunther?
Gunther?
What? All right.
Is this happening everywhere?
I don't know, let me see.
'Kay.
- What do you see?
- Hold on.
Oh, no. No!
- What dude?
- Hold on, man. Wait.
Oh, glob, this can't be happening.
Tell me!
It's over, we've been conquered.
- Who's been conquered?
- Everyone.
- By the Ice king?
- No, dude. By Gunther.
Holy schnab.
Give me that!
Gunther's heading for the candy kingdom.
We've gotta save them.
Whoa, okay.
Hurry, Jake!
Wait, I'm still in my p-jayjays.
Yo, Finn, are you seeing these penguins?
Yeah, It's Gunther. He's taking
over the whole thing.
Well, he'll have to beat
my banana guards
and my gumball guardians.
That's not gonna work.
What did he say?
- He says your plan is bunk.
- Well, what's your plan?
- I got a plan.
- You do?
When we get there, I'll do my plan
in adittion to your plan.
Two plans. Laters.
All right.
- So you're not gonna tell me y...?
- I'm outies.
You're not gonna tell her the plan?
No, I've gotta be mysterious.
What? I thought you weren't
into Bubblegum anymore.
I'm not, but this is how I act now
with all the ladies, you see?
I keep them in a state of confusion.
That way, I've always got options
in case Flame princess doesn't work out.
Oh my gosh!
Where is that coming from?
It's called "future farming".
I read it in that book you have
by Jay T. Dangzone.
Jay T. Da...! Oh, dude!
Don't read that book!
It's gonna mess up your brain.
I keep that book around for laughs.
It's all really bad advice.
Oh, okay, I'll stop it then.
No, well. You can still be
mysterious, that's fine.
What? Now I'm confused.
Nevermind, I didn't say nothing.
Hey, P-Bubs, are you ready?
Yes. The cavalry is standing by.
Cool, I'm gonna rally some citizens
and do this other plan.
- Okay but what...?
- Good luck!
Jake, what's with all the mystery.
Oh, snap! Look out!
Banana guards, defend!
Oh, geez.
Evil presence detected.
Must defend...
candy kingd...
You'll never get past
these walls, I think.
This is my plan.
I got the candy kingdom
underground to help me collect
all the bottles in the land.
Breaking news, that mystery plan
of yours is a smash hit.
Because, uh... of the glass.
I guess all they care about is bottles.
So, what will happen when
they run out of bottles?
I won't let that happen, probs.
Stay back!
Wait a minute!
Put away your weapons and
we'll get you more bottles.
Peeb, there aren't any bottles left.
I have a third plan.
So, we make them new bottles,
then the Gunthers break the bottles,
then we pick up the glass and
make new bottles again?
Yup.
What, like forever?
Yes.
Bub, your plan bunks.
Yeah.
I like it. I got a rythm going.
What, what do you want? I don't...
He wants to smash the
Gumball guardian's head.
We're going to make more
bottles, just wait, okay?
No!
Goodbye, princess.
Hey, what's going on here?
Why is this place all crazy?
I was just flying by and...
Gunther! You took my stuff!
That's bad! You know what you get now?
That's right. You get
the squirty squirts.
Bad, bad.
Now take off my demonic wishing eye.
All right, Gunther. Now go home.
That's right, walk.
While you're walking home
you think about what you did.
It's getting worse and worse
with him, he just...
he hates it when I leave the castle.
I'm sorry guys.
Uh, dude, where have you been?
Yeah, and why are you all jacked up?
Well, I got into some crazy
wiz biz over a wizard city.
Honestly, I don't even
know how I survived.
Basically, it was the craziest
showdown ever, I...
I wish I could tell you
all about it, but you know,
wizards only, fools.
Keep it tight.