Man, let's go home.
Nuts to that.
I want to find
a mystery cave.
But, Finn, I'm getting all
cranky around my joke-hole.
Oof!
Ow!
Ooh la-la!
What's that?
Mystery cave!
Come on, Jake!
Oh, my glory.
Dude, no!
Don't touch that thing.
It's probably got some kind
of sacred significance.
Yeah, I want it for
my sacred bathroom.
Finn?
Oh, my jah!
Finn's become one
with the lamb!
Huh?
Jake!
You see this crazy jazz?
We'll get through this,
my bro.
I swear I'm gonna get
you out of that lamb.
Jake!
Come on.
Quit messing with me.
Whoa!
Ow. Ow.
Ow.
Wish I knew how
to free you, bro.
Me too, bro.
Pbbbbbt!
Thbbt!
Thbbbt!
Pbbbbbt!
Beemo,
stop fake-farting!
But Finn always
loved Beemo farting.
Thbbt!
Hmm.
That's it!
We'll do all Finn's favorite
stuff till he comes out!
Beemo,
play Finn's favorite song!
Okay!
♪ three baby spiders... ♪
What?! No!
No! Not this song!
♪ The rain came down,
and it was no fun ♪
Are you hearing this, buddy?
Guys, I haven't liked
this song since I was 2!
Aggggh!
Cut it out!
Leaf princess!
Come to me,
my arboreal beauty!
Gotcha!
It's just a dumb, old leaf,
you dumb, old Ice King.
I know,
but it's mine.
Wait! What?
Ice King,
you can hear me?
Yes.
Why? Are you making fun of me
or something?
No, it's just no one else
can see me or hear me talk.
Ohh. Yeah.
You're trapped in
the spirit realm.
I can see all things spirit
with my "Wizard eyes"!
Man, never thought I'd be happy
to talk to you, Ice King.
Can you help
me get free?
Oh, yeah. I know all
the ins and outs.
And I'd do anything
for a friend like you.
Quiet, Gunther. Can't you see
I'm hanging with Finn?
I know I say that a lot,
but this time, it's true.
Anyways, where do all
these spirits come from?
Oh, there are portals
all over the universe.
I have one in my basement.
Every once in a while,
a real cutie pie drifts through.
Oh!
Gosh, there she is.
Mmm. Oh, yeah.
Sick.
What?
I swear I never touch 'em.
I can't!
Can't touch this!
Can't touch this, either!
Yep, I can't
kill any of them.
I hate them.
Okay, all right.
Enough messing around.
Let's get you free
from the spirit plane.
Cool.
So, the only way to get out
of the spirit world is to
stick all these lousy things
in the spirit hole down there,
then plug up the
hole with that.
And doing that will
send me back to normal?
Mm-hmm! Trust me!
We are tur-bros!
Turbo bros.
Tur...bros.
Turbo...bros.
So be it.
All right, Finn.
This ought to free you
from your body prison.
Couple of rounds of Kompy's
Kastle will jog your
psychic Schnapps.
That's what I think.
Co-op mode,
like we always do.
Oh, yeah!
Come on, Finn.
Drop the drawbridge.
Kompy's bloodlust
meter's going down.
Let me help you there.
Wazza!
You love Kompy.
I...did it!
Whew! I did it.
I'm ready, Ice King.
Make me normal now.
Ohh, that's not
all of them.
There's this other
guy that watches me.
He's...super-creepy.
Do you see it?
Oh, it sees you.
Catch it and put it
in the spirit hole!
In the spirit hole,
where it can't see me anymore --
so you can be free!
Huh?
Get it! Get it!
Ugh! Aah!
Get it in the hole!
Ew! Ew! Ew!
Ew!
Yes!
It's gone!
So...now I can go
back to normal?
Uh...wait, though.
What?
There's this last
guy you got to get.
He's pretty much the worst.
He usually leaves
these gross heads around,
but I'm not seeing
them anywhe--
Aah! Ew!
There it is! There it is!
Wan wan!
Wan wan wan!
Noooooo!
No!
Don't come near me!
What is that?
It's from the dead one.
He leaves these
heads around everywhere.
I can't even touch them,
but it still creeps me out.
Wan wan!
Please get rid of him!
What do I do?
Follow the heads?
Yes, the heads!
Oh, snow, please!
All right, man. I'll get it.
Wan wan.
Where's your daddy, huh?
Is he hiding in there?
Wan wan.
Ugh!
Better get back in
the spirit hole, dead one.
Blagh.
Okay.
Hyah!
Ugh!
Agh!
Wan wan wan!
Hyup! Oof!
Oh, bolts!
Whoo! Yeah, get him!
Boosh!
Oh, my --
what?!
The cave?
How the...?
Weird.
That's weird,
but whatevs, though.
Whatevs.
Ice King?!
Ice Ki-i-i-ng?!
Where'd you go, Simon?
Ice King?
♪ Oh, me, oh, moy,
oh, fa-la-loy ♪
♪ Everyone sing
my song of joy ♪
♪ The child of man
who touched the lamb ♪
♪ Is soon to be my
new best friend ♪
♪ All to me,
can't you see? ♪
♪ For I will never
set him free! ♪
♪ I had no bro
in all of Ooo ♪
♪ But now I've got one,
Finn the hu-- ♪
Dude, come on! What?
Ha ha, Finn!
You fell right into for my
brilliant plan that I formed
out of the thin air
like a true magi!
Not only did I get you to remove
those horrible creatures from my
castle, but now you're trapped,
and only I can see you.
So, if you want friends,
this is it, pal.
I'm gonna
re-open the hole.
No, wait!
My plan fell apart!
My new plan is that you don't
open the hole and I destroy the
porcelain lamb,
which will bring you
back to the material plane.
Jake.
Ugh! Blah!
Give me that lamb!
No!
Finn's trapped in here!
That's why I
have to smash it!
You donk!
I will smash you!
Blaaaaaaaah!
Escape!
Aah! My winter body!
I was gonna start up on the
elliptical again,
but I got depressed, okay?
Don't look at me!
Ow!
Ooooh!
Aaah! They're touching
me for real!
Ew!
Great. Now we're both
stuck in here.
Aaah!
Finn,
give me your clothes!
Stop!
I need a buffer!
Gah!
Oh, geez! Come on!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
They were just touching
me on the body.
I'm sorry.
Whoa.
Do that again.
I'm sorry.
They were touching my body.
Your hand is
affecting the TV!
We must have some kind of subtle
effect on the material plane.
Cool.
What do you think,
Finn?
Can we pull back the veil of
static and reach into the source
of all being?
Behind this curtain of patterns,
this random pattern generator.
So clever.
Right here, in every home,
watching us from a one-sided mirror.
Whoops!
Just wizard-talking to myself.
It's okay, but let's use
our subtle influence to
break the lamb.
Yeah, a'ight.
You mean like this?
Whoooosh.
Yeah, man! Whoo!
It's working, man!
Combine the swirls!
Okay.
Wazza!
Whoa!
Finn, is that you?
Yes!
Finn! Finn! Finn!
Whoa!
That was beautiful.
Let's go flush this in
the sacred bathroom.