The Lich
Dark times are coming.
You talk like justice, Billy,
but you can't kick a plane.
Are you alright buddy?
Another nightmare?
Yeah, that dang snail again, man,
monkeying it up again.
But, there were other
guys this time too.
The bear was there, and some dogs,
and Billy's lady, and Billy.
And Billy was really scared
of something fierce, man.
Something real fierce.
And the cosmic owl was
there too, kind of,
screeching it up.
Whoa, the cosmic owl?
What if that was a
premonition dream, Finn?
Do you think?
Could be.
We better go tell Billy
about it, just in case.
He'll know what to do.
Dang. Whoa.
I dreamt I was in kindergarten again,
but I had really big feet,
and was also the teacher.
Come on. We better hurry.
Hello?
Billy?
Billy, wake up!
What the heck are you
guys doing in my crack?
It's three o'clock in the morning!
Oh, you know, just
dropped by to say hello.
See what you've been uh...
up to, what uh...
How are these days?
We came to see if you're dead.
What? Why would I be dead?
Yeah, stupid...
I had a dream about a bear,
and an old lady, and a snail,
and you were there, and the snail
killed you or something.
Was the cosmic owl there?
Yeah, on tv. Does that count?
Your dreams are omen
of grave significance.
- Finn?
- Yeah?
Are you ready to come with me on a
mission to save all life from The Lich?
Yes.
Wait. So, we have to snatch the gems
out of all the crowns of power?
- That's right.
- Cool.
Why do we have to snatch 'em?
Can't we just ask 'em for 'em?
No time. The faith of the
world hangs in the balance.
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
"I suck hamburgers"
- Are you sure that's a gem?
- I think so.
It's so deep.
Gross.
Man, we got so many gems. This is crazy.
Hey, Billy, how many gems
we still need to get?
Two? One?
Wait, two or one?
I want candy.
You got anything in the saddle bag?
Get out of there!
The Enchiridion? How did you get this?
I found it in the mouth of a bear.
A bear?
This book is really important.
It has magical powers.
Turn the little sword sideways.
Cool!
What is this stuff?
Hold on.
Hello, my name is Booko.
What you see here is
the map of the multiverse.
It shows all the known dimensions
and the links between each of them.
This is the dimension that contains the
universe in which we currently reside.
Enhance!
Make it stop!
Anyway, at the center of the
multiverse there's a dimension
called the time room, believed to be
the quasi-corporeal dwelling place
of the almighty Prismo.
The time room is a single dimension
that exists outside of time.
The time room produces the time waves
that are experienced by the dimensions.
Some dimensions have permanent
links that allow travel to and fro,
others become linked temporarily
by naturally forming wormholes,
and others can become linked
artificially by magical portals
torn open by items of great power.
Once the last gem is inserted into
the Enchiridion it will have the power
to create a portal to any
dimension in the multiverse.
An activated portal creates a
time dilation in which either end
of the portal experiences a temporal
synchronization allowing for the
safe passing of particles through a
non local region of space-time.
I'm gonna push the Lich in there.
Oh, cool!
Let's go get that gem!
Yeah!
Hi!
Who's there?
Princess! Princess!
I need the gem from your crown.
What the junk? No!
Get off!
Get off of me!
That was an accident.
Finn , stop!
Hurry!
Finn, stop!
That's not Billy! It's the Lich!
Lich alert! Lich alert!
Billy!
Billy?
The book, Finn. Give me the book.
Quickly, child, we're
running out of time!
Lich! You... you messed Billy up!
You just wanna mess me all up.
Mess everyone up.
You tricked me!
No, child, it's all true.
The book has great power.
I can make you live forever.
Anything you want.
Just give me that book!
No, no, no!
No more tricks!
You'll never get this book!
No!
Oh, no! Finn! What did you do?
What?
Thanks, Finn.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Jake, stop him!
Don't let him through that portal!
Hang on, Jake!
What now, princess?
Hold on, Jake!
Finn!
Finn, would you come in here please?
Hurry! It's very important!
Coming, mom!
Man, she sounds steamed.
Guess I done dung
something up yet again.
Come on, Jake.