Welcome to Top Gear, with our
all-new, improved audience.
- Tonight, I get chased.
- Right behind us.
Matt gets chased.
See if I can shake 'em in these twisties.
And then, in a bizarre
twist, I chase Matt.
Come on, Great Britain!
And Matt chases me.
We're going to get smashed.
This is brilliant!
Marvellous, amazing, beautiful.
All right, before we go any
further, would you like to meet
the first ever non-UK host of Top Gear?
Yes!
Brilliant, please welcome Matt LeBlanc.
Matt LeBlanc, everybody!
All right, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Oh, you're too kind, too kind.
All right, and with
that, back to you, Chris.
Thank you very much, Matt.
OK, right, well, if it isn't
all the guys and girls
from my local Indian restaurant.
- Hi, guys. - Hi, Chris. - Hi, guys.
- Good evening.
- Boss man. - And, firstly, thank
you for your continued custom.
Well, you're very welcome,
you're very welcome.
Now, anybody got any idea
why these guys are here?
- New caterers.
- What?
By the way, by the way...
we don't talk about catering
on this show any more.
In fact, to be honest,
maybe questions from the
floor was a bad idea.
Actually, Muno, you tell
everybody why you're here.
What are you here to represent?
We represent the equivalent of
one metric ton of downforce.
That's what they are, one metric ton
of downforce, ladies and gentlemen,
which apparently is enough to
turn an old-time US muscle car
into a lap-time destroyer.
This is Fallon US Naval Air
Station, deep in the Nevada Desert...
.. home to the US military's
finest array of warplanes,
and something called
the Naval Aviation Warfighting
Development Center,
better known as...
Top Gun.
♪ Highway to the danger zone
♪ Highway to... ♪
This is where the best of
the best get even better
in the most fearsome
aircraft on the planet.
The perfect place, then, to test
America's latest killer wing,
which happens to be attached to...
.. the brand-new Dodge Viper ACR.
Now, you might take a look at the ACR
and think, "With its giant long
body and front splitter and scoops
"and rear diffuser, my goodness me,
"that's going to be a handful to drive."
Thing is...
you'd be absolutely right!
0-60? Just over 3 seconds.
Top speed? 177mph.
Noise? Tooth-shattering.
Listen to that.
Basically, it's a road car,
but it's got to be said,
it's as close as you can come to
a race car without having to wear
fireproof knickers and a wristband
with your blood group on it.
All highly exciting, but the
Viper formula has barely changed
since God was a boy, and you can tell.
We all love a manual gearbox, but
this one's a little bit tight.
It's offset at a weird
angle, which means that third
can often become fifth if
you're not fully concentrating.
And then there's the Viper's
prehistoric power output.
An 8.4-litre V10 chucks
out 645 horsepower.
But, at its heart, it's a
quarter of a century old.
Modern supercars produce far more
power from engines half the size.
It's about as cutting
edge as a rusty crowbar.
But Dodge have at least
polished their crowbar up a bit.
The ACR has bespoke sticky tyres,
brakes as big as dinner plates,
race car suspension and,
most importantly, the wing.
This piece of carbon, like the
inverted wing on a fighter plane,
actually jams the Viper into the
tarmac with phenomenal power.
On the straights, it
actually slows the car down,
but going into the bends at
top speed, over a tonne of air
presses the Viper into the floor.
A tonne!
And it really works.
The Viper ACR holds 13 track records,
more than any other car
in production right now.
So, after all these years,
it seems Dodge has finally
perfected their Viper.
Good for them.
Or at least it would be
if the competition hadn't
been busy making this.
The Corvette Z06...
or, as the Americans have it, the Zee 06.
It's more powerful, it's quicker to 60,
its top speed is higher,
it's cheaper to buy
and it looks better.
But which one, then, is
the king of muscle cars?
Viper or Vet?
It was time for a dogfight.
Our cars have been equipped
with guns -- laser guns.
Manning those guns will
be Top Gun instructors
call signs JoJo and Syphin.
And at the wheel of the Vet,
Top Gear's top girl, Sabine Schmitz.
I feel the need, the need for speed.
The rules are simple. First
to get missile lock wins.
Ginger, I don't like you
because you are dangerous.
We've got a rule here at Top Gun --
it's a 10 fine every
time you quote the movie.
JoJo, I think Sabine's ego is
writing cheques her body can't cash.
This is going to be an expensive day.
Whoa, rock and roll, JoJo.
She's right behind us,
she's right behind us.
- Get behind him.
- I'll get closer.
Time for a little... evasive action.
I'm going to hit the brakes
and watch her fly by, OK?
Have you got him?
Three, two, one.
Fire!
Brakes.
Whoa!
There she goes!
Go, go, go.
Son of a...
The hunter has now become the hunted.
He's on our tail!
- Get closer, get closer.
- I'm going to reel her in.
Woo!
Don't let her get away from you.
The Viper's wing is doing its thing, baby.
Until I found out there's a limit
to how much "thing" it can do.
Oh, he spun! He spun off.
You can be any time my wingman.
- Wait, what is wingman?
Not wingman? - Yeah.
Whilst I was recovering from
my aerodynamic overconfidence...
.. Schmitz disappeared.
Where would the enemy
most likely come from?
- Probably where you're
not looking. - Really?
Have you ever had an angry
German on your tail before?
I've never had that.
She so wants to win.
Go, go.
I follow you, buddy.
- Eyes left.
- Oh, oh.
We're on his tail, we're on his tail!
The smiling assassins were all over us.
Get closer.
Or at least, that's what they thought.
Shoot!
Missed him.
That's when she can't keep up with us --
round the corners, the Vet is killed.
She's all over the place.
The suspension's awful... like a Ferrari.
There's so much more grip
than this piece of sh...
Jeez, this car's good!
She will not be able to make this corner.
We missed it!
- Where is he?
- I don't see him.
Yeah!
She's dead, man, she's dead.
Boom, she's dead.
Oh, holy moley.
I might need a break, Sabine.
- Huh? - I might need a
break. - You need a break?!
- I might need a break. - What? - Yeah.
Oh, sh...
Sorry, I... My Top Gun pilot
is a little bit, er, in trouble.
Oh, did he throw up?
Is it time for a new call sign?
- Er, yeah.
- Upchuck.
Yeah. Pukes on Top Gear.
Oh, no!
And so it's the Viper
that is officially Top Gun.
Fast, agile, and once you know how
to use it, absolutely devastating.
Top Gun, clear to take off...
Whoa-oa-oa!
Fly safe, my friend.
Fly safe.
- That was good. - That was
good fun, wasn't it? - Great.
Thank you, thank you.
And thanks to the US
Navy, and Sabine Schmitz,
now undoubtedly the
queen of the Vomit Comet.
OK, now, just... hang on a second.
Do you seriously expect all
these people to believe
that she made a guy who
flies fast jets in wars
throw up after just, like, a
half an hour in a Corvette?
Yes, because that's what happened.
Are you sure that it wasn't
just a ruse that you came up with
to cover up the fact that she
made you throw up in an Audi?
No.
OK, just chicken... checking!
- Did you say "chicken"?
- No. - All right, anyway...
Here is the Viper ACR
in the flesh, everybody.
- And now...
- Woo!
.. we need to see how fast
it can go around our lap,
which means only one thing.
Yes! It's time to bring
on our tame racing driver.
We got custody! We got custody!
Some say the day he was born,
he drove himself home from the hospital,
and that he's being investigated
for irregular emissions.
All we know is, he's called...
.. the Stig.
OK, here we go, he's off.
The Stig back in the saddle and
armed with 8.4 litres of engine.
That's 15 pints of displacement.
Into the first corner and the first
test of the ACR's massive wing.
Stig keeping it tidy there.
Let's see how happy he is
to be back in the groove.
Oh, look at him beaming! He's ecstatic.
Right, very clean through
Chicago, heading into Hammerhead...
on those massive brakes.
Can the Viper keep it tidy?
Very neat. Little skid there.
Little slip on the exit.
Into the fastest part of the lap.
Stig and Viper in perfect harmony.
Follow Through, that wing
shoving the ACR into the tarmac.
Serious speed past the
tyre wall. Look at that.
No expense spared on the white paint.
Second-to-last. Very stable under braking.
Stig can smell the finish now. Come on!
And over the line. There you go!
So...
Here we have the time.
OK, we're holding out
a lot of hope for this.
It if goes 1:16.8 or less,
it's up there with the
Bugatti Veyron Super Sport.
Can it beat the Lamborghini
Huracan -- 1:15.8?
I can tell you the Dodge Viper...
1:15...
. 1 -- there it is with the Ariel Atom.
Rock and roll!
So I join Top Gear. They
say, "How about a road trip
"and a UK/USA challenge?"
I say, "Sure." They say,
"Head-to-head with Chris."
I say, "Bring it on." They say,
"Blackpool." I say, "Where?"
They say, "In fibreglass
three-wheelers." I say, "What?"
We'd be driving to Blackpool in these...
.. stunning Reliant Rialtos.
Oh, wow, look at that.
OK.
Successor to the Reliant Robin and
equally as terrible in every way.
Worse still, the producers
had kindly chosen
to chop off their roofs.
Nice wheels, Matt.
Great paint job.
They've told me that one of
these costs double the price
of the other one, so I suppose
we could try and guess which one.
I mean, mine looks nicer, to be honest.
- Don't you think?
- Yours is nicer, yeah.
I think this was the more expensive
one. I'm sorry, but... I don't know.
- I don't know, I'm just guessing.
- Yeah. Looks like it.
- OK, and you know where we're going?
- Yeah. We're going...
- The route? - Yeah, we're
going to Blackpool, so we'll...
We'll come out of central
London here and we'll turn left
at Regent's Park, look out for Birmingham.
- If they start talking in a Braveheart
accent, we've gone too far. - That's too far.
- Yeah. - That's too far north, OK.
- Yeah. But it's about 250 miles.
All right, let's roll.
With zero idea what challenges
awaited us in Blackpool,
we set off on our very
first Top Gear road trip.
This is perfect. You wrap up warm, you've
got blue skies, it's nice and fresh.
It's not that bad, this little car.
You know what, honestly,
gearbox, nice and smooth.
OK to give you a little love tap?
Erm, OK!
Despite our first impressions,
we were loving our three-wheelers.
Listen to that.
Hey, there's fourth gear now.
Oh, I haven't tried fourth
gear. Tell me about it.
Very luxurious.
Buddy!
Thing is about Matt, is
because he's such a superstar,
he actually looks cool in his
Stars and Stripes Reliant.
He-hey!
I just look like a dick!
And with London traffic behind us,
things were actually looking good.
At least, so I thought.
Chris, what's that smell?
Ooh.
'Just 26 miles into our journey,
my Reliant gave another hint
'that it might be the cheaper car.'
The temperature gauge just
started going up, up, up.
It's just water, coolant, it's
overheating. It's not oil smoke.
- That'll be it. - That's
the problem. - That's it.
- That's the problem.
- Be fine now.
Problem solved. Soon we
were back on the road.
- Hey, Matt, how's the car?
- Running like a top now! Runs great.
Blackpool, here we come!
I just saw a sign for Oxford.
- Does that mean we're near Blackpool?
- Not really, to be honest.
- Um, no. We're sort of half
the country away still. - Right.
'And then...'
The temperature gauge has pinged.
It's all the way high again.
If you don't want to go
to Blackpool, just say.
'Frankly, this was
getting a little suspect.
'A UK versus US challenge in British
three-wheelers on a British TV show
'and the car they'd given to the American
'decided to roll over and die... again.'
You know, you watch Top
Gear on TV and you see them
driving Bentleys and
Porsches, and they invite you
to be on the show, you say,
"Sure, that sounds great."
And they make you drive
this... from here to eternity.
And his runs fine.
You all right?
- Honestly...
- Does it look like I'm all right?
- It's nothing to do with
me. - I'm happy. - Are you?
Don't I look happy? That's my happy face.
It's a good face. You're a great actor.
It goes up on the corners, like this.
Still 200 miles from Blackpool,
we put our heads together
and got Matt's car back in the groove.
Drives itself, this thing, really.
But as we pushed north, the
chilly winter air started to bite.
Fortunately, though, the producers
had kindly packed some extra clothing.
It's now raining, it's much
darker, it's much colder.
I'm dressed like Captain Birdseye.
Matt is dressed like a bear.
When this piece is over, I'm
going to have a good long talk
with the wardrobe department.
Got to be firm. Behind closed doors.
With a stick.
- A big stick.
- But ever the professional,
LeBlanc soon got stuck into his
first ever Top Gear car review.
Let's talk about this gem
of an automobile here.
Acceleration -- can't tell.
Handling -- can't tell.
The clock works, apparently.
It's midnight.
The fabric on the seats is disgusting.
I wonder when they finished
the first prototype,
did they shine it all up,
step back, look at it and say,
"Oh, yeah, nailed it"?
Do you think that was the conversation?
'Delirium was beginning to take hold...'
'.. of both of us.'
My windscreen wiper is
now imitating the sound
of a seagull at the seaside.
'But the great British public
were still doing their bit
'to cheer us on our way.'
How you doin'?
'And by the time we got north
of a place called Birmingham...'
Do we have to pay for the
one that's on the truck?
'.. morale had hit rock bottom.'
Oh, it's really raining now.
Hey, listen, you know what?
Between the cold weather and
these flashing yellow lights,
I'm going to lose my mind, man.
'Time for decisive action.
'I figured my Reliant had
about ten miles left in it,
'and while I hadn't been
able to drive to Blackpool,
'I could at least drive into Blackpool.'
So this is what we're going to
do -- we're going to pull over,
get the car off the truck and,
hopefully, she lasts into Blackpool.
You're going to last,
aren't you? Honey? Come on.
'Despite being lumbered with
the worst car in the world,
'Matt was determined to get
there under his own steam.
'Or, as it turned out, his own
smoke. Lots of his own smoke.'
That's more smoke than I've ever seen
coming out of a car that isn't on fire.
I'm not stopping again.
I'm going to go until it blows up.
- If I see an actual flame, I
will tell you. - Thanks, bro.
Matt, we are so close to
Blackpool. Please make it.
Come on, baby.
We're going to do it.
Oh, it just died!
Come on, we're there, Matt!
We're there! You can't stop!
It won't restart.
'There was only one thing for it.'
'The love tap.'
- It's running! It's running! Go!
- Come on, Matt's car!
Purring like a kitten. Woo!
Thanks, Chris. Thanks for the start.
Come on, Matthew! We're going to make it.
OK, come on, baby. Hold it
together. It's about 500 metres.
Blackpool, here we come!
- Yes! - All right! We
made it! Woo! - Woo!
LeBlancpool! Genius.
- Yeah-heh!
- Yee-haw!
Matt LeBlancpool. It doesn't get
any better than that, does it?
No, it doesn't. No, it
doesn't. No, it doesn't.
- But as you and I both know...
- Oh, yes.
.. it did get wetter, windier,
wilder and weirder. That's right.
More Top Gear presenter torture I
really did not sign up for coming up.
- Yeah, sorry about that. See
you later. - Yeah, OK. - OK.
All right, how about we now meet tonight's
Star in a Reasonably Priced Car?
Well, we can't.
How about we meet tonight's Two
Stars in a Reasonably Priced Car?
Well...
.. that's not going to
happen either, I'm afraid.
But how about we meet tonight's two stars
in a brand-new rally cross car?
We can do that! Please welcome
Gordon Ramsay and Jesse Eisenberg!
Jesse, how are you? Gordon, how
are you? Come and sit down.
- Thank you. - Come on,
guys. - Thank you very much.
- Jesse Eisenberg, Gordon Ramsay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Gentlemen, welcome. - Thank
you so much. - Good to see you.
- Welcome to the programme.
So first of all, Jesse. - Yes.
Can you tell us, please, what
Gordon's up to at the moment?
Yes, of course. I've been rehearsing this.
Yes, Gordon Ramsay, who is
currently seated to my right,
is preparing to compete in an
ironman in June to raise money
for the Gordon and Tana Ramsay
Foundation, as well as which
he will be making a record
sixth appearance in Soccer Aid,
where he'll once again be risking
actual bodily harm, like this.
- Painful.
- Ow!
And, Gordon, how long were you
affected by that injury for?
Cos you were stretchered off, weren't you?
I was ill for about five weeks after that
because I just didn't expect it.
It's not as if you can prepare yourself
and get sort of tense to take the
hit. So, yeah, naughty Teddy.
- And have you seen Sheringham since?
- Funnily enough, no.
Now, can you do me a favour?
Can you tell us what Jesse's
up to at the moment, please?
- Yes, I would, but I can't - BLEEP
- see that. It's so, so small.
Can't really see. That's better.
It is tiny. It is. It is...
Jesus, that... that is
super small. Thank you.
So, Jesse Eisenberg,
currently seated to my left,
is performing in the incredible
satirical comedy play The Spoils,
written by Jesse himself.
It's playing now at Trafalgar Studios.
Sadly, obviously, there's no video
available, but here's another clip
of me getting clattered again,
this time in slow motion.
Oh! Oh!
And watch this -- just
have a look at this.
Any sympathy? I don't think so.
That's...
- All right, cars. Are you
ready, boys? - Sure. - Yes.
OK, audience, you are going
to decide who lays claim to,
first of all, as far as these two
are concerned, best first car.
Let's go with Gordon
first. Gordon's first car?
A Fiat Strada.
That's shocking. Can I just
apologise about the hair as well?
- Sorry. Jesus. - Well, it may have to
become best first car and hair, this feature.
So we have the Strada.
OK, best first car. Your first car, Jesse?
Yes, my first car was,
like, a Honda Accord.
- Honda Accord! Here we go.
- Yeah!
- Yes, yes, yes. - Once again, I'm feeling
this is best first car and hair competition.
Yeah, yeah, I... See, I
had a haircut at the time
cos I couldn't fit in
that car with that haircut.
And... yes. No, that car, by the
time I got it, it had probably been
through, like, 35 owners,
including, like, Henry Ford.
And it was so broken down
that the engine would overheat
every time I drove it, so I had
to drive with the heat fully on
in order to extract the heat from it.
I don't even know if that's true. My dad
said I had to drive with the heat fully on,
which now, in retrospect,
seems like a practical joke
he was playing on me, but
then seemed totally logical.
OK, so audience, you
decide. Best first car.
Let's have a look at them
both again, here we go.
It is a cheer for Gordon's Fiat Strada...
.. and hair.
Or Jesse's Honda Accord and hair.
Ooh, Jesse just gets that
one, don't you think so?
- He just gets it. - One-nil,
Jesse, congratulations. - One-nil.
Are you ready for best car ever
now? Gordon's best car ever.
- Oh!
The LaFerrari.
Yes, an absolute beast.
How long have you owned yours for?
I got delivery... yeah,
about nine months ago.
- Right. - I told Tana I
was buying an electric car.
Well, it is a little bit
electric, isn't it, I suppose?
- Isn't it?
- A little bit electric.
Can you recall the first ever
drive you had in your LaFerrari?
Yes. Meg asked if I'd go
and pick her up from school,
so she had, like, a netball
tournament up in Ascot.
So I took a little spin out
there, literally from the showroom
- and drew up in the school
and Meg went - BLEEP - crazy.
She said, "Dad, how can you
embarrass me like this?
"The noise of the car,
we had to stop playing,
"everybody's staring at me."
And I said, "But you've got
no idea, this car's..."
She said, "Yeah, but you look
like a grandad in a Batman's car."
So this is your best ever car now.
But you may have a sort
of future best car.
There's one on the way. There's
another little thing proving...
- What's this? What's this?
- So this is from Ferrari.
And I got it sent about three months ago.
And they're doing a limited
edition of the LaFerrari.
- So what are we talking about?
- The LaFerrari Spider.
They made 499 of these beauties.
These, I think, they're making 100.
- 150. - OK. - There's the key. - Wow.
This is the first proof on TV, radio
or in a magazine that this car exists,
cos anybody you ask about this car to do
with Ferrari, they go, maybe, maybe not.
But you have actually ordered one,
and this is what they've sent you?
- Yes. - So you've parted with a lot
of money, and they've sent you a box?
Yes.
Well, you're a very lucky boy, well done.
And if this is ever going to
be attached to anything else,
- then good luck with that, too.
- It's great.
- So, Jesse, you are up for best car ever
against LaFerrari. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What are we thinking about
Jesse's chances here, everybody?
Yeah. I need some kind of
spaceship to compete with it.
- Remember, it's your vote that counts.
- I think I might win the sympathy vote.
The nicest car I've ever had was that
Honda Accord from the previous image.
- No, come on, it's not. Come on.
- Yes, it is, it is. It is, it is.
No. I moved to... I moved to
New York City, I ride a bicycle.
Didn't you have a Nissan once?
No, no, I learned to drive on, like, I
think maybe an Altima, a Nissan Altima.
But it was also not a
good car. I mean, not...
- At the time it was really... you know, had
been used by several generations. - All right.
So far, the LaFerrari or the
Nissan Altima, what are we thinking?
Wait, wait, before they vote, can I just
say, mine has an air freshener in there.
We need something better
than a Nissan Altima.
Do you have any experience
of another car that might be
- a bit better that we can represent you with?
- Yes, I was in a Porsche one time. - A Porsche!
Shall we take the Porsche?
Let's take the Porsche.
- What kind of Porsche was it? Why
were you in it? - I've no idea on
either of those. I don't know.
No, I wound up in it for maybe
30 seconds -- does that count?
Yes, of course. It's going to have to,
cos we can't put this against LaFerrari.
Did it look a bit like this one,
perhaps? 356, was it like that?
- Oh, that's nice. - It looked nothing
like that. - Gorgeous car, by the way.
- Beautiful. - Nothing like that? - Nothing
like that. - OK, was it more like this one?
- 2.7 RS? - No, no, it was much
more modern. - Really? - Yeah.
- OK. Was it like this
one? Carrera GT? - Oh.
It was somewhere between the
yellow one and this one, yeah.
OK, was it like this one?
- Just use your acting
skill. Say yes... - Got it.
- Was it like that? - Yeah, it was
exactly that one. - OK, perfect! Perfect.
OK, so once... Once
again, you're in charge.
- OK, remember, Gordon's one down
here, everybody, OK? - Yes. Come on.
Best car ever between Gordon
Ramsay and Jesse Eisenberg.
Is it Gordon's LaFerrari,
or is it Jesse's 918?
Let's hear it for Gordon's LaFerrari.
Let's hear it for Jesse's 918!
- Oh, no! - Nothing. Not even
one person. - Gordon wins.
I should have brought my mother
here, she would have voted for me.
It's one-all. It couldn't
be more exciting.
Shall we have the decider as the lap?
- Yes!
- Yes.
OK, let's go with Gordon first.
Here we go. Our muddy Mini Cooper, then.
136 horsepower of prime British beef.
- Come on. - Can he handle it? - Let's
go, baby. - BLEEP - nail this one.
First corner. Here it is.
All change, sharp right-hander now.
And straight onto our first
dirt section, everybody.
And the water splash, brand-new.
Look at that, woohoo!
Oh, very nice, Gordon.
Into Hammerhead.
Oh, come on! Round of
applause, ladies and gentlemen.
Excellent control. Right,
our second off-road section.
- Heading towards the hairpin.
- Come on.
Apparently, the fastest way around
this is with a handbrake turn.
Does he go for it? Yes, yes, he
does go for it with a handbrake turn.
- Used the handbrake?
- Up.
Coming up, our jump. Our brand-new jump.
And... all right! Big air
there from Gordon Ramsay.
More big air from Gordon Ramsay.
Right, back onto terra firma
and approaching the tyre wall.
- Oh.
- Left, left, left, left.
- Get out of the - BLEEP
- way, bird. Before I eat you.
His next-to-last corner. This
often catches lots of people out.
Very tidy. Bit of counter-steering there.
And finally round Gambon,
and he's across the line.
There you go.
- How did that look? - Loved
that. - Yeah? - Great.
- First-ever lap time. - I know,
thank you. - OK. - Thank you.
- OK. Right. Jesse.
- Yeah.
How did that look to you, compared
to how you think yours turned out?
Well, that's how I pictured myself,
but I'm sure I look a lot different.
- Shall we have a look?
- If you need to.
Jesse's lap. Here we
go, come on, everybody!
This is the one.
Into the first corner. Looking smooth.
No tyre squeal there. Slow and
steady... could win the race.
OK, fight all instincts to go too
fast, this is really slippery.
Towards the water splash,
let's have a look.
Yay!
OK. Bit of trail-braking there.
Call it what you like, I'm not quite sure,
never seen it before, to be honest.
All right, now. There he
is through Hammerhead.
Enjoying the scenery as he goes.
Will he ever get to the
second off-road section?
And, yes, he's on the
second off-road section.
Now the thing with the handbrake.
Can we see the Scandinavian flick?
Actually, that wasn't bad, I
don't think. That was all right.
Hey, thank you very much for your pity.
And air. There's some air!
Nice through the tyres there.
Next-to-last corner, hard left.
Tight, good line.
And round Gambon, and
Jesse is over the line.
OK, so...
What do you think, guys?
I have an idea.
The thing about the conditions
today was they were near perfect.
And so one of you could end
up top of our leaderboard.
Right, right.
Well, Gordon, this is
automatically the fastest lap ever
until we have Jesse's, because
it's the first lap ever.
Gordon Ramsay, you did our
brand-new rallycross circuit
in our rallycross car...
.. in 1:56.3, everybody!
- Yeah. I'll take that.
- Well done. - I'll take that.
- There for now. - All right. - Yes.
- OK. - Yeah. - Jesse, looking
at 1:56.3 and seeing the film...
- Yeah.
- .. what would you like to be?
I think you could just move that
colon over one... one number.
OK. 15 minutes, 63 seconds.
Would you like to be under two minutes?
- Would you like...? What do you think?
- I'm just happy I'm alive.
So, yeah, whatever you want
to put me on. I don't care.
OK, well, I can tell you,
Jesse Eisenberg went round
our course in one...
- Yes!
- Oh!
- I'm joking. - Oh! - 2:10.9 seconds.
There you go, Jesse Eisenberg!
Hey!
Going to be close together,
closer together. Thank you, Jesse.
- You know what, that's not bad.
- Thank you, Gordon. - Thank you so much.
Come on, guys!
I don't know about you, but I
often lie awake in bed thinking,
"When they approach Top Gear
to remake Lawrence of Arabia --
"which they will --
"what car are we going to
replace the camel with?"
Well, those crazy Brits
who came up with this,
the bonkers Ariel Atom, think
they might have the answer.
Check this out.
It's called the Nomad.
And it's some sort of off-roader.
Look, I don't really want
to start by picking apart
your strange British cars,
but as an off-roader,
the Nomad does suffer a few tiny flaws.
'First of all, getting in.'
No.
A door would have been nice.
'And where most off-roaders
have four-wheel drive,
'the Nomad makes do with just two.'
So if you get stuck, you're
probably not going to get unstuck.
'Worse still, as you can clearly
see, the Nomad is full of holes.'
Yeah, getting wet here. Getting
really quite wet. Yeah.
'So, as a conventional off-roader,
the Nomad is completely useless.
'But conventional can be so... boring.'
Woo!
On a surface like this, you simply
shouldn't be able to go this fast.
Behind my head is the latest 2.4
litre four-cylinder Honda engine.
Makes 235 horsepower.
In an age of 600 horsepower family sedans,
that doesn't seem like a lot.
'And it's not a lot.
'But because the Nomad weighs as
much as your mother's G-string...'
.. this thing hauls ass!
0-60 takes just 3.4 seconds.
And unless your other car is a superbike,
or a cheetah with a saddle on
it, that ought to be enough.
'And so should its top speed.
Sure, it's only 125mph...'
.. but it feels like
more. Much, much more!
This is not off-roading.
This is low-level flight.
Because this car is from the same
people who brought you the Atom,
the time they've saved on styling
has been spent on the important stuff.
The suspension is the same kind of
stuff they use in World Rally cars,
so the Nomad can absorb bumps that'd
split most cars clean in half.
Look at all that suspensioning.
Suspend! Suspend!
Oh! Oh, yes! Smooth, like a Cadillac!
And there's more cleverness.
This bodywork, if you can call it that,
is made of the same
material as traffic cones,
so it'll bend instead of dent
if you were to accidentally bump
into, say, a medium-sized mountain.
And look -- unlike the Atom, there's
a windshield. For obvious reasons.
Such as the wind.
But maybe the Nomad's
neatest trick is that
it isn't just brilliant off-road.
Most of your hardcore lightweights
-- your Atoms, your Caterhams,
your Radicals -- yeah,
they're great on a race track,
but they can be pretty hard
work on real world roads.
But the Nomad is more approachable.
You can really feel the
suspension doing its thing.
You feel the limits of the tyres.
A really flickable chassis. I love it.
You really feel part of the action.
You feel, I don't know, plugged in.
'And, OK, £33,000 is quite
a lot of money for a car
'with no luggage space or doors...'
.. but honestly, it's the
most fun you can have in a car.
Whoa!
Well, the most fun you can
have with your clothes on.
I remember one time, I
was with this, er...
Well, there was two of them actually...
Oh, they were supposed to cut that out.
So it's quick both on and off-road,
which in no way begs the question,
does this make the Nomad the world's
best all-terrain getaway car?
As we all know, one of the
hazards of modern Britain is being
pursued by bloodthirsty evil villains.
'Or to give them their
Latin name, paparazzi.
'But can the Nomad outrun them?'
To find out we've assembled
three of the most vicious,
cold-blooded villains on the planet.
Scum.
This is Barry. Pure evil.
He's going to be chasing me
with this kid's toy. Good luck.
This is Dave. Ruthless,
heartless, homeless, probably.
He'll be on a dirt bike.
Meet Pete. Basically a
lizard with opposable thumbs.
He'll be on...
.. whatever that is. Put that down!
'The challenge is, can these
villains get a clean photo
'of me in the Nomad?'
Let's find out.
On my mark, get...
Nah, just go!
'We'd agreed I'd get a
one-minute head start,'
'but the villains, being
villains, didn't play fair.
'Dave's bike took off like a shot.
'Barry's camera drone took
off like a... camera drone,
'and Pete took off like
a... drunk puppet.'
So, how to escape the villains.
Tip one -- weaving.
Ha-ha!
Tip two -- keep them guessing.
Bike's gone, bike's gone!
It's an all-aerial battle now.
Aerial Nomad versus aerial assholes.
Ha-ha!
Tip three -- create a smokescreen.
That ought to do it.
'And drones, it seems,
not great with dust.'
Drone down, drone down!
'So long, Barry.'
Then the drunk puppet man met his
worst enemy -- a moderate breeze.
Where's he going? I'm pretty
sure that's Algeria over there.
That's unlucky.
'But just as I was busy
basking in my own smugness...
'.. biker Dave was back.'
Sneaky. So sneaky.
'With the dirt bike hot on my tail,
it was time to change the play.
'On tarmac the Nomad's extra
grip would, in theory,
'give me the upper hand, especially here.'
See if I can shake him in these twisties.
I think I should be able to get
a bit of a gap on him here.
'Sure enough, the Nomad's
agility through the corners
'gave me some breathing space.'
So there you go. No match for the Nomad.
'Unless, that is, you hit traffic.'
Ah, man.
♪ Truckin' got my chips cashed in
♪ Keep truckin'... ♪
- Stig!
- ♪ .. Just keep truckin' on... ♪
Stig! A little help!
Oh, yeah.
My man.
Thanks, Stig.
It's dark in here. Whoa, whoa!
Something just licked me.
That was brilliant.
- That was fun, that was all fun.
- That was brilliant.
- That was a lot of fun. - It was like
a movie. - Yes, it was. - Wasn't it?
How great was that?
The Italian Job lives, starring LeBlanc,
LeStig and LeAriel Nomad.
And what you've got to
love about the Nomad,
like the Viper, is that they are
just built for pleasure alone.
Yeah, that's right. But
now back to the pain...
.. as we re-join our
USA versus UK challenge.
♪ With my little stick of Blackpool rock
♪ Along the promenade I stroll... ♪
We woke to vintage British weather,
excited at our first challenge.
But what would we be driving?
Representing the US of A, the Willys Jeep.
Born in the Second World War,
the daddy of all off-roaders,
the American definition of tough.
Representing the UK, the
Series One Land Rover,
a reliable workhorse so indestructible
it lasted seven decades.
- Oh. - Now we're talking.
- Yeah, now we're talking.
- Two legends, yeah.
- Two legends.
This is now proper USA
against the UK. This is good.
I know, I know, this is it.
This has got -- what's
this? A 2.2 litre motor
- and you have a one point...
- Six. - .. six litre motor.
Should, on paper,
absolutely spank this thing.
I know, but the bloke who invented
this had one of those and then,
sort of in his own mind,
improved it and came up with
- the Series One, so technically this
is a later evolution of that. - OK.
I think we should wait for the
weather to get a little more
challenging before we actually begin.
- Yeah, this is a little
too balmy. - Yeah.
Soon and, I have to say, a little
weirdly, a man in robes appeared.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as Mayor, it gives me
great pleasure to welcome our
two intrepid challengers.
Your first challenge today will be
a simple race -- the speed test.
1km of run-up. Fastest
through the timing gate wins.
Gentlemen, to your vehicles.
- OK.
- OK, is it all right?
This may take a while.
Since we seem to have some time to
kill, here's an interesting fact.
On this very stretch of
promenade in 1906, a lady called
Dorothy Levitt set a women's
land speed record of 91mph.
Come on, you beauty! For Britain.
Come on! Come on!
Oh, I tried, I tried, I tried, I tried.
Abysmal at best.
- All right? - It was...
It was terrible, wasn't it?
Well... I mean... wasn't that bad, Granny.
- What do you think?
- I think...
Please, over 50mph. Maybe 49... 48, 49mph.
Your guesses seem to be dropping.
All right, let's see it, come on.
- Oh!
- No!
Fine, not that quick.
But the signs weren't looking
great for cocky Matt either.
Piece of cake, piece of cake.
Yeah, feel that American power, baby.
- Here we go. Yeah!
- Click it there!
Oh, that looked quick, didn't it?
Look at that face.
You know you've beaten
us, don't you? Yeah?
- That felt... That felt pretty quick.
- OK, erm, 43.81 to beat, OK? - 43.81.
For America's honour.
Oh! Oh-ho-ho-ho!
This is what happens when
you mess with the Big Dog.
So that's one-nil to the States
and it was back to robes guy
to find out what was next.
'I love this guy.'
It's time for our second challenge.
A British classic, the tug-of-war,
here on Blackpool Beach.
On your marks, get set, tug.
With a rope tied between us,
the winner would be the
first to spear their balloon
and this time, we'd each be
backed by some home-grown muscle.
Helping me were local rugby
superheroes, the Fylde Vandals.
And helping me was an
American football team
from somewhere called... Blackburn?
The Lancashire Wolverines.
'Then it turned out
robes guy had a friend.'
On your marks, get set, GO!
Come on, boys!
- Come on! Come on!
- Pull! Come on, pull!
'Never before on Top
Gear had so much effort
'produced so little movement.'
'Soon it became clear that
neither of us was going anywhere.'
Oh, no, no, no.
'And as Chris threw the
rule book out the window,
'the tug-of-war was
declared a no-score draw.'
So it remained one-nil to the USA
with just one challenge left.
USA, USA, USA!
And so back by popular demand...
Today's final challenge will be a
traditional automobile drag race.
But this is Blackpool, so we're
doing it bigger, better, brighter.
Welcome to the Top Gear
triple-drag challenge.
- Can I go?
- No.
We would have to race across the
beach, tow a stranded ice cream van
to safety and escort these
lovely ladies to the finish line.
So it was drag, drag and drag.
- Three... - Two... - One...
Go!
Oh, no! The American's got the lead!
I can beat him on the reverse.
'As we hitched up to our ice cream vans,
'it was pretty much neck and neck.'
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on! Oh, no!
'Until Matt's superior torque
started to give him the edge.'
Come on! He's got it absolutely nailed.
'And with just the ladies left to collect,
'I unleashed all 2.2
litres of my Jeep's power.'
See you later. Ha-ha-ha!
'With Chris flailing behind...'
He's already at the drag queens. No!
'.. I picked up Miss UK and
made a sprint for the finish.'
Oof!
Jump in, jump in, jump in! Come on!
Quick, quick, quick! Jump in!
- How's it going?
- Oh, lovely.
Ha-ha!
- Ooh!
- Careful.
Here we go. Yeah!
We've lost the battle but
we can still win the war.
'Yep, another defeat for the Brits.'
Two-nil to Team USA.
Victory, or so I thought.
"Congratulations, you have
completed the qualifying stage
"of Top Gear's UK versus USA challenge."
- Qualifying?
- That's what it says here.
"Tomorrow, you and your
respective cars will race
"to the top of a mountain.
"Matt, you have gained a
one-second head start tomorrow."
You're kidding me. All that effort
for a one-second head start?
I don't make the rules.
Our deciding challenge brought us
to the magnificent Lake District,
and a race to plant our national
flags at the top of Muncaster Fell.
Off-road hell awaited us.
And so did two old friends.
- Hey-hey! - Oh. - The
Reliants are back, yes!
Yay(!)
'Good thing I had my
one-second head start.
'Still, at least I had backup, in
the shape of professional strong man
'and world champion
powerlifter Nick Best.'
- Hey, Nick.
- Matt, what's going on?
Good, good, good. Thanks for helping out.
- How much do you lift?
- Everything.
And helping Chris out
would be some thin guy.
- Hiya. - Alistair Brownlee,
how are you doing?
- Good, thank you. How are you?
- Great, thanks.
I can lift a Jeep. I don't think he can.
Oh, I've been studying the
old Ordnance Survey maps
and I've been looking at the
tracks that we've got to go up
and hopefully I'll find the
smoothest and quickest way up there.
Let's quit the small talk
and get going. Come on.
Can we just have a little bit of respect
for my Olympic gold medallist?
I'll have Nick pick him up and throw
him off the hill if you don't. Let's go.
'And so, for the honour of our nations,
'and with one more British
thing I'm yet to figure out...'
Matt, you will go on my first cannon.
Chris, you will go on my second cannon.
Three, two, one.
- All right, Nick. Here we go, buddy.
- Let's do it.
Al, can you keep checking the
Reliant's still there, yeah?
'With the summit looming way above us,
'we each took our own view on
the fastest way to the top.'
Ah, there's nothing like a Willys Jeep.
- Whoa! - Think we're still
on the right route here.
- Yeah?
- We're doing all right, yeah.
Alistair's route was longer,
but undoubtedly more achievable.
Meanwhile, Team USA's more direct approach
was throwing up some obstacles.
- Oh, we've got some crap in the
way up here for sure, Nick. - Yeah.
Clearly he doesn't need my help.
That is a big dude.
It's good to have strong friends.
'Hang on, a friend that reads
maps isn't exactly a disadvantage.'
200 yards straight and a gate coming up.
- Disengage the brain and just
engage the power. - Got it.
Here we go! Whoa!
Surely he's not going this
fast in the Jeep. No way.
- Got to be, come on! - No
way. - Come on, Britain!
'And he was right. Back on the short
route, Nick and I were in trouble.'
We've missed the turn.
Why didn't you tell me we were
supposed to turn back there?
It's not my fault, you're
the one that's driving.
I didn't say it was your fault,
clearly it's my fault. Clearly.
Do you think you could pick
that up and spin it around?
Yeah, yeah, I can pick it up.
- Uh-oh.
- That's not a good sound.
- We're going to have to get it up.
- Yeah, I'm sorry I yelled at you.
- It's all right, man.
- OK. - It's all good.
Just go up and over, that'll
get it past the tree.
'So after an incredibly hands-on U-turn...
'.. America was back in business.'
And as we climbed higher,
we closed in on the Brits.
- Where is he now? Is he close?
- About 20 yards off us.
'Then things got a little... competitive.'
- We're going to get smashed.
- Yeah.
I might have tapped you
a little bit. Sorry.
- It's more than a tap.
- Slightly more than a tap, yeah.
I'm not sure that's within the rules.
- Come on, we'll find another
way. - All right. - Whoa!
We can cut that out.
'Matt and Nick had muscled
their way into the lead,
'but Britain never gives up.'
We are never more dangerous
than when we're behind, Al.
Underdogs, that's where
we like to be, isn't it?
Behind us, the Brits were
gaining confidence and ground.
Then our route planning
let us down. Again.
- Give me a push, Nick.
- Go on. Hit it.
Come on, baby, come on. Come on!
- Argh!
- Come ON!
Team GB were also closing in
on the summit, and also stuck.
No, we're not going
anywhere, I don't think.
- We're really struggling.
- Or at least they were,
until another skinny triathlete
appeared from nowhere.
Look at him go!
- Jonny! - Thought you lads could use
some help. - I think this is allowed.
Two Brownlees equal one
American strongman.
- I think that's fair.
- And then Chris cheated. Again.
As long as we take a bit of the Reliant
with us to the top of the hill, that's fine.
- Technically we've
done all right. - Yeah.
'So taking what I prefer to call a
liberal interpretation of the rules...'
- Yeah, he's got it!
- Yes!
'.. we grabbed a bit of
flag, ditched the Reliant,
'and pushed for the top.'
- Great.
- Come on!
Straight up. Straight up.
- Come on! - Come on. - Straight up.
- Come on! - Come on! We can do this.
I can't see, boys. Where am
I going? I can't actually...
Right, go, go, go.
With the cheating Brits
making a break for it,
Team Fair Play weren't far behind.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Get on it, get on it,
get on it. Get on it.
'But our Reliant Reluctant
had dropped anchor.'
- Give me a push, Nick. - All right.
- Come on, we're almost there.
- This is it. This is it!
- All right. Keep going! Keep going!
- We can do it! - Come on! - Stop!
- Ye-e-ey!
- All right, come on.
Put the flag up, put the flag up!
YEAH! USA, where are you?
'We were close, so close.
'But even with the might of one
of the world's strongest men,
'we weren't going to make it to
the top without a little help.'
Come on, boys.
- ♪ Let the sunshine in
- Let it shine
♪ Let the sunshine in
♪ Open up your heart
and let it shine on in
♪ Let the sunshine in... ♪
Yeah! Woo!
You didn't bring a whole car.
- We brought... we brought enough of a car.
- No, no, no, no.
- That's our first-ever film together.
- That's our first one.
The end of the first film.
OK, well, now, thank you, Blackpool,
thank you, the Lake District.
- Thank you very much. - Yeah.
- That was a lot of fun, yeah.
OK, I know what you
might be thinking here.
You might be thinking
from the video evidence
it's patently clear
that I may have cheated.
What do you mean you "may"
have cheated? You cheated.
Yeah, all right, OK. I did cheat.
But after I cheated, I helped you to win.
- Well, yeah, that's true. Thank
you. - Oh. - Thank you very much.
- You're very welcome.
- And on that bomb...
- No, no, no! We're not...
- I didn't... - No, no, no, no!
- We're not doing that, no.
- I was just testing you.
- Just testing you.
- Phew!
Next week -- the Jaguar
F-PACE, the Porsche Macan,
the Mercedes GLC and the McLaren 675.
Cue the TV walk. Plus Eddie Jordan,
Jenson Button, Tinie Tempah,
Sharleen Spiteri and Seasick Steve.
Goodnight, everyone! Goodnight!