- We can move in here, we
can make some money, baby.
- We might make it work,
but them kids gonna die.
- I think they're
thinking of moving here.
- Stay calm until we know
what they're thinking.
- We can't think that old!
- We can move in here,
we could redo the place.
- Dad lost his job.
- We can make this thing work.
- They're gonna move
us out of school.
- They can go to school.
- And have local friends.
- Hell, they'll
make new friends.
- What am I gonna do
without civilization?
- This cannot happen.
- Go tell the kids.
- You go tell the kids.
- We can't let them do this.
- I can't take the disappointed
look on their faces.
- [whimpering]
- ♪
- Uh, kids?
Kids, come here, uh, me and
your mom wanna talk to you.
- LEAH: Come on.
Come sit down.
- Where?
- On the couch.
- You first.
- Come stand up! [laughs]
- Oh no, here it comes.
- Oh, please God, no.
- Do what she says.
- No, no, you know what?
I'm not.
- Baby, you're not what?
- I'm not coming to stand up.
- Why won't you just
stand here and talk to us?
- Because you have on
your "come stand up" face.
- It is the face.
- Mm-hmm.
And that means you got bad news.
- [in sing-song voice] I
don't have any bad news.
- Okay, first of all, please
don't do that ever again.
- She is judging me.
- And second of
all, yes, you do.
- Your daddy has something
he wanna tell you.
- Really?
- What?
I thought this was your idea.
[laughs]
- Uh, I thought we were supposed
to be doing this together.
- [whispers] Not when it comes
to disappointing my babies.
- Stop acting like
you like these kids.
- [whispers] Ssssh.
They right there.
- Go on, break it to us.
- Why you say that like
I'm about to tell you
your transmission went out?
- You're gonna tell us
that we have to stay here.
- No! No!
That is not what he's gonna say.
- He is about to tell us...
- Would you, please?
- Go on, Dad, tell her.
- We are not...
- No, no, no, no, no, that's
not what you're gonna say.
See, see, I will go
to the gas station.
I will grab the gas for the car.
We have to get out of here.
- Honey...
we are staying here.
- No!
- Ow!
- This is terrible,
I can't do this.
I just can't!
- Sandra, would you
stop being so dramatic?
- I can't make it here!
- Hey!
- No!
You are not listening to me.
- Oh, I'm listening.
- There is no reception here.
And there is no Wi-Fi here.
My generation...
we don't live like this.
And you and Dad need
to get it together!
I'm going.
- Baby, you better hold me.
You better hold me. - No, no.
- You better hold me! Whoo!
Whoa! Ooh, oooh! - Calm down.
- Who she think
you're talking to?
- That's... that's your daughter.
That's your daughter.
- That's his daughter!
- Be strong.
- [groans]
- Be strong, baby.
- Am I y'all favorite now?
- Get out of here boy, go!
Go with your sister.
- [laughs]
Boy, if you had talked to me
like that
when you was a little boy,
I'da hooked you to death.
[laughs] I'm gonna
check on my weed.
- ♪
♪ No matter what
you do, I love you ♪
♪ No matter where you go
♪ I'm behind you for sure
♪ Always remember
♪ No matter where you are, we'll
make it if we stay together ♪♪
- ♪
- Oh, my God, I can't believe
you let her
talk to you like that. [laughs]
- Grandpa, she upset, man.
- Hell, I know that.
- She... she just
needs some time, okay?
- Look, boy, upset is one thing,
being disrespectful is another.
- Okay, alright. Well, what do
you want me to do?
We don't hit our kids.
- [laughs]
That is bullshit.
Where is the black man
that don't hit his kid?
There he is, I'm looking at him.
Let me point at him with
my good hook finger.
- And we don't use that kind
of language around our kids.
- Boy, that is more bullshit.
You have been cussing
ever since you been here.
- Well, you rubbing off on me.
- Oh, I'm sorry, was
I being disrespectful?
- Yes, you were.
- Well, that's what the
hell you should be used to,
because she just did it.
And she's a child.
I'm a grown-ass man.
I'm disrespecting your ass.
- Grandpa?
- What?
- You know, baby,
I'm gonna go talk to her.
- No, no, no.
Let me talk to her. - No.
- She won't ever talk to
you like that ever again.
She won't have a tongue.
Or teeth.
- Grandpa Vinny, no.
- I wish... ooh.
Whoo, uh.
[groans]
I wish to hell
one of my grandchildren
would talk to me like that.
- Yeah, well, you know,
I never did, Grandpa.
- Oh, yes, you did.
- Grandpa?
- Well, you know what?
Let me tell you something.
Come here, boy, let me
tell you something.
There was this one time, right?
Your daddy looked at me.
- Mm.
- You told me to look at you.
- He looked at me...
and I slapped the
snot out of his nose.
- That's so violent.
- No, oh, that... that...
That was a good thing.
See, uh, your daddy had a cold.
And then when I slapped him...
- Whoa!
- I'm... he... he, uh...
He got over it.
I actually healed his ass.
- Come on, Grandpa,
that did not happen.
- Do you have a cold?
- No, stuff... [sniffs]... the dust.
- 'Cause I can
show your ass, too.
- No, I'm... I'm good, thank you.
- Get out my face.
- I can do that.
- Do it, good.
- Grandpa?
- What?
- I need to give
her some space, man.
- Whooo! You need to give her
some space?
Does she have a mortgage?
Does she have a condo?
When she get any of
them damn things,
she can have all the
damn space she need.
That is some more bullshit,
bullshit, bullshit.
- Grandpa, the language.
-... don't say nothin' to me.
- Oh my... baby, I'm gonna
go talk to her, okay?
- Yeah, look, I'm sorry you
gotta deal with this, alright?
- No, baby, no, no.
- Nah, nah, nah, this is... this
is really all my fault.
If I had kept my job...
- Listen, it is not your fault
that those stupid people
laid you off.
- Yeah, I know that.
- Well, it's kinda his fault.
- Grandpa!
- If he had been more
productive, showed his value,
they wouldn't have
laid his ass off.
- Baby, she is
being a selfish teenager.
And it is wrong for her
to make you feel bad.
- Baby, you know how I... look,
I just hate to upset her.
That's my princess.
- Uh, he don't like to have
his daughter upset at him.
- Look, I just hate
disappointing her.
- Oooh!
That's why she like that.
- Grandpa!
- No, no, no.
She like that 'cause you all
give her every damn thing.
I had nothing!
- Here we go.
- When I came to this
country, on a banana boat...
- Grandpa.
- What?
- Ain't no banana boats
coming from Mississippi.
- [laughs] Boy,
I'm from Jamaica.
- Wah!
Grandpa, I did not
know you were Jamaican.
- Yea, mon.
- No, no.
- LEAH AND VINNY:
[indistinct singing]
- Hello? Hello?
Your kid is in the room.
That's nasty.
- Forgot about you.
Um... - [laughs]
- Grandpa, so
you... you speak Jamaican?
- [in Jamaican accent] No, well,
see, me left as a little boy
before
me learn to speak the language.
- Ooh, listen... [laughs]
- [laughs]
- Hey, hey, hey... uh,
am I missing something,
or don't they speak
English in Jamaica?
- VINNY: Ooh.
- You right.
- Is he still in the room?
- Yeah, I'm right here.
- Then be gone.
- [laughs] Yeh, mon.
- Alright, now, mon.
Anyway, where was I?
- Uh, on a banana boat from...
- From the Bahamas!
[laughs]
- Wait, what?
- Look...
- And I remember so well, mon.
Me had nothing.
Me had no shoes.
Me had no clothes.
Me was butt naked.
Get off the boat butt naked.
Everything was
swinging in the wind.
Swinging.
People were saying, "You
must be from Jamaica."
I say, "Yah, man.
That's where I'm from."
- [laughs]
- She said, "Not cold today."
I says, "Speak for
yourself, I'm freezing."
I appreciate everything I got.
Everything.
And I'm so grateful.
♪ So grateful to be
here, right here ♪
♪ I am so grateful
- ♪ And you're so high
- [laughs]
- Well, me not high, we
just kinda in the middle.
- [laughs] Okay.
- You know what? That's what
I was going to do.
Go get high before that
girl rudely interrupted me.
- Alright, well, yeah.
Go ahead, you go do that.
- Okay, okay, fine.
♪ So grateful
♪ So grateful - Baby?
You are not encouraging
him to do that.
- I'm encouraging
him to be gone.
- You know what?
I am going to go talk to
our wonderful daughter.
- Okay.
- You should go talk
to our wonderful son.
- I'm on it.
- Now if I can just find her.
- Just follow that loud perfume.
- LEAH: Mm.
- [sighs]
So, son...
- Oh, boy, I got to see this.
- Grandpa?
- VINNY: [laughs]
Go ahead, go ahead.
- You think we can
get some privacy?
- Privacy my ass.
Boy, this is my place.
- Please.
- Okay, okay.
Alright, I'll give
you some privacy.
Okay.
- Grandpa!
- Alright, man.
- Hey, hey! Stop being silly.
- Okay, alright, I'm leaving.
I'm leaving.
But I need you to speak loud
so I can hear you, alright?
- Alright.
Is he really gonna
sit right there?
- I sure in the hell am.
- What is it, Dad?
- So, Son...
- No, no, look.
I know you're
having a hard time.
- How you know that?
- You wanna work, I get it.
- Son...
- No, Dad.
If we have to move
here, I'm all for it.
- [crying]
Son...
man, you just so
much like me, man.
You just... [crying]
- Is his... ass crying?
- No!
- [laughs]
- Yes!
- [crying]
Look, man,
you just so much like me.
You just... you know, you
just go with the flow.
You know, unlike your mama.
- Who's right there.
- Oh damn.
- ♪
- So what did you say?
- You're on your own.
- No, no, no, no.
No, no, don't leave me,
don't leave me, don't leave me.
- Look, look, in this situation,
every man for himself.
- Will you stop it?
- I'm serious.
- No, stop it, man, for real.
- Look, if she tells me to
leave, you're on your own.
- She... she's not
even that upset.
- Honey, can you leave us?
- Sorry, playa.
- Ah!
- Ooh, your ass is busted!
[laughs]
And speak up so I can hear you!
- So, uh, what did you say?
- Hey, baby.
- So, I don't go with the flow?
- No, no, I was just...
- No, go on and say
what you were saying.
- Whoo! I gotta sit up
and watch this...
He fittin' to lie. [laughs]
- You just, you know... you just
so beautiful and wonderful and...
- Oh, and I don't
go with the flow.
- Baby, he just
so easy to talk to.
- No, Jeremy, I do not want
him with that in his head,
thinking that women
are difficult.
- I know, look...
- Okay...
- ...that's... that's
not what I'm doing.
- Because I'm not.
- You're... no, you're not.
- And women are not difficult.
- Bull...!
But it's true.
I mean, what woman wants to be
cool with everything a man says?
- Women are not supposed to be
cool with everything
that a man says, Grandpa.
- You see, that's some
difficult -
you're doing right there.
Now you acting like
you ain't difficult.
That's difficult.
And anyway, the Bible said...
- Don't...
- Hmm-mm, no, no, no.
- Don't what?
- Tell me. Tell me
what the Bible says,
Grandpa, tell me.
- Okay, the Bible says...
- You don't know the Bible.
- Boy, I know the Bible.
The Bible says
in... second Geronimo...
- Geronimo?
-... Alexander 19, 47, 38 verse.
If you grow it... they will come.
- Right.
You should leave, Grandpa.
- Grandpa, don't leave me.
- VINNY: [laughs]
See, your problem, boy,
is you can't handle
the little woman.
- What did you say?
- Don't, uh... don't repeat it.
- No, you just called
me a little woman.
- I thought women liked
to be called little.
- It's Me Too, Grandpa.
- Watch... watch me fix this...
Watch me.
I called you little.
You wouldn't want me to
call you a big woman.
You see, I called you a
little woman as in small.
As in you've lost weight.
As in I've noticed
you're smaller.
You lost weight.
- You recognize it?
- VINNY: Yes.
- Honey, this snatch works?
- Yes, yes, I'm seeing it.
- Stop it. [laughs] WW.
- [laughs]
You see me fix that -?
- How the hell did you do that?
- Boy, with a quickness.
- Baby, I'm sorry, okay?
- Mm.
Mmphm.
Go on, I'm listening.
- No, you know, look.
It's just easy to talk to...
- I just don't want
him to think women are...
- That women are difficult.
- Yes.
- I get it. 'Cause you're not.
- I'm... am I?
- Nothing can divide us.
- A comment like that can.
- Baby.
Come on. - Hmm?
- Leah, I'm sorry. Alright?
- Mm-hmm.
- Did you talk to Sandra?
- No, I can't find
that little girl.
- Where did she go?
- I don't know. She gotta be
around here somewhere.
- Okay, alright, come on.
Look, I'ma help you find her.
Let's go. - Uh, no.
I should do this by myself.
You know, women are
so... difficult, you know?
- You stop.
Look, you gotta get
over this, alright?
Look, stop playing.
- Oh, I gotta get over it?
It's gonna be difficult for
you to get into bed tonight.
[laughs]
- ♪
- Can you believe they
want to keep me here?
Hello? Can...
Can... can... can you hear me?
What is this wretched
place with no cell service?
- Sandra?
- [sighs] No.
- You know we need to talk.
- Are we really staying here?
- Yes.
- Well, that's just wrong.
- What's so wrong about that?
- I mean, to take
me out of school...
- Okay.
- ...away from all of my friends.
- Honey...
- No, I have a whole
life back in Chicago.
- Okay, I need you
to listen to me, okay?
- I just...
- Listen.
Your father lost his job.
- I know.
- You do?
- Yes.
- And you still
acting like this?
- Like what?
- Honey, we try very hard to do
what's in the best interest
of this family.
- Well, I don't like it.
- Look, I need you to hear...
- No, I don't!
- Listen.
Your father feels really bad
that he can't provide for us
right now.
This could be a
second chance for him.
Okay, and I need you to
stop being so selfish.
- Selfish?
- Yes.
- I'm being selfish?
- Yes, Ma'am, very selfish.
- Mom.
- No, listen to me.
Your father and I have made all
kind of sacrifices
for you and your brother
because we love you.
Now, this is the least you
can do for your family.
Okay?
- But this is so unfair.
- Them laying your
father off was...
- Unfair.
- He's been there 20 years.
Twenty years.
- I just...
- Listen, okay?
I love you, baby, okay?
You are going to... to
meet new friends.
I promise you your
life will go on.
We're gonna get back to Chicago
as much as we can, okay?
And you know what?
Your friends can come down
and visit you sometimes.
- Even Sammy?
- [whispers] Sammy?
Sammy?
- Sammy.
- You know what?
If you are still, uh, interested
in ol' Sammy boy...
by next summer...
he can come down and visit.
- Okay.
- But we might have to convince
your daddy of all of that,
you know? - [laughs]
- We might have to bring Rhonda
up here
and blame it all on Philip.
- Ooh, I like the way you think.
See, that's... you're my girl!
- ♪
- Fine.
I'll stay here.
- Thank you.
You know, that was
very adult of you.
- But I have a condition.
- A condition?
You know that's not how this
works, that's not how
any of this works. - Mom!
- What is it?
- We have to have
high-speed internet.
- I'm with you, girlfriend.
- Mm-hmm.
So I can video chat
with all of my friends.
- We can fix that in the budget.
- [laughs] Okay.
- Okay, now you know you gonna
be paying for that though?
- With what money?
- Well, see, you know,
we gonna be living here,
and we gonna be working here.
We got a lot of work to do.
- You know, I'm sure there's
some kind of
child labor laws against that.
- [whispers] That don't
work in this house.
- We can get Philip to do it.
- And your dad.
- They can do it.
- Again, my girl!
Yeah!
Subtitles >>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
♪♪
- ♪