(male narrator)
Previously on Battlestar Galactica.
If you go back to Caprica
and bring me the arrow...
that will show us
the way to Earth.
What do you want from me,
Helo? She's a Cylon.
[Gun fires]
I'm not gonna let you kill her! Okay?
She's carrying my child!
Bitch took my ride.
(Tigh) I am placing you under arrest,
Madam President.
This is mutiny.
You know that.
(Adama) I'm terminating your
presidency, as of this moment.
I recommend we execute jump to
emergency standby coordinates.
What about our people
on the surface of Kobol?
If they're still alive,
they'll have to wait.
He's not gonna make it.
Tarn, you forgot the med kit, so
you're gonna have to go back and get it.
You can't send him alone.
You questioning my orders, Chief?
[Gun firing]
I don't want a command. I never did.
Don't you dare die on me now.
The Cylons are hacking
our network.
Attempting to access
our mainframe.
(Hotdog)
What is that thing?
(Apollo) I don't know, but whatever it
is, it's bearing on Galactica.
We've got to take it out!
(woman on P.A.) Attention,
Damage Control Team to Deck 12.
Hey.
Attention, Damage Control Team
to Deck 12.
Quite a day, huh?
Yeah.
Wow, I haven't seen you
in person since...
Two weeks ago.
I've really been thinking about you.
That's nice. I gotta go.
Hey, Dee.
Dee, hey. Hey.
Listen...
I know that I haven't really
made an effort, or it must seem...
like I really haven't
made an effort...
to make this, whatever this is,
a priority.
But...
But?
But you were too busy helping the
President spark a mutiny on my ship.
Or, but you wanted to wait
until you were desperate...
and needed
a shoulder to cry on...
before making your move?
I think that was
a little uncalled for.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
You're right.
I gotta go.
What the hell?
(Ishay) Grab the
emergency flashlights.
(Kim) Copy that.
Check the ventilator.
(Kelly) We have DMA interrupted.
Report status.
I'm checking.
(Gaeta) Let's check subsystems! Let's
get emergency power back on!
(Hotdog)
Flyboy!
(Flyboy)
Hotdog!
[Kat whooping]
XO, sitrep?
It's the virus, sir.
I think it must have spawned copies of
itself in some of the computer systems.
It's knocked out main power
and auxiliary units.
(Gaeta) Emergency power
just kicked back in.
Hey, Captain,
nice work out there!
I'm not sure what you guys are kissing
and hugging about. We screwed up.
We let one through.
(Kat) What's going on
with the lights?
(Apollo)
I'm not sure.
We still have no idea
if we can reach most of the ship.
[Thudding]
What the hell was that?
I'm not sure, sir. Checking.
Power's out, sir.
I think it's ship-wide.
Sound-powered phones
is the only thing working.
Been trying to get to
Damage Control, but the lines are jammed.
Okay. Get the birds tied down
and make the ordnance safe.
I'll head up to Combat
and see what the hell's going on.
Yes, sir.
Say again.
Cylons reported
in the starboard flight pod.
We've been boarded.
(Apollo) Okay, nuggets. Keep moving.
Yeah...
but when I came up on his six,
all right, he rotated, so I had to bug out.
It was plain, clean, simple.
(Kat)
Hey, did you see...
when I turned on that pair
chasing me on the port beam?
Yeah.
(Hotdog) I saw that. That was sweet.
I rotate, pull back,
hit the brakes, and there, bang!
Left one's lined up
dead-center ring.
I chatter him, turn back to get
his wingman...
[Kat screaming]
Jesus!
(Apollo) Cylons! Come on! Move! Come
on! Let's get out of here!
Come on! Come on!
Go! Go!
My gods! It's coming!
(Kat)
Go! Go! Go!
Get the hell out!
Go!
Get up! Get out!
Go now, now!
Frak!
[Gun firing]
You all right, Captain?
I'm still breathing.
I guess that's all right.
Kat!
Hotdog, you all right?
(Hotdog) Think so.
Can I get back to you on that?
Sitrep?
We've been boarded, sir.
We don't know how many,
where they are, where they're headed.
Our standard ammo
doesn't even make a dent.
The explosive rounds
are the only way to take them down.
How many rounds you got?
That was our last one.
All right.
Hotdog?
Take this to CIC.
Give it to Col. Tigh
or the officer in charge.
(Hotdog)
Yes, sir.
Marines, let's go toaster shopping.
All clear, sir.
Kat, on me.
Yes, sir.
(Gaeta)
Galactica to all ships:
We have been boarded
by a Cylon raiding party.
Do not approach
or attempt to dock with Galactica.
Keep a safe distance
until we have secured the ship.
I say again, we have been boarded
by a Cylon raiding...
[static buzzing]
What the hell was that?
The Cylons jammed the signal.
Great.
[Gunshots]
Are those gunshots?
Yeah.
We can't stay in here.
(Roslin) Open the door.
You know I can't do that,
Madam President.
Cpl. Venner, I have no intention of
being locked in this cell...
and shot like a rat in a cage.
Open the door!
Thank you.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
(Apollo)
Cpl. Venner, don't shoot!
It's Capt. Adama!
I have a fire team with me!
Come on in, Captain.
Watch the companionway.
We're clear, sir.
We've been boarded.
This deck is crawling with Cylons.
They're trying to get to the magazines.
How can we help?
Stay alive and don't get shot.
Leave the Cylons to us.
Okay, sickbay is the safest spot.
It's farthest away from any potential targets
and it's designed to function as a...
disaster shelter in case the ship
were lost. Right.
Bonnington, sidearm.
Sir.
Okay, Billy.
You ever handled a weapon before?
A pellet gun from my uncle
when I was, like, 10.
The principle's the same,
the real ones just make a bigger noise.
Madam President.
No, thank you. I can't.
Corporal.
Yes, sir.
You're in charge of getting her down
to sickbay. Take Bonnington as escort.
Remember, just head away
from the sound of gunfire.
(Venner)
All right.
What about you?
Well, we're heading towards the gunfire.
Okay, listen up.
There's a small arms locker
on causeway Bravo, two decks down.
We're gonna go get
some explosive rounds...
and then we're heading
towards the magazines.
Twinam?
(Twinam) Sir.
You take point.
Yes, sir.
Good luck, Captain.
May the lords protect you.
And you, too.
(Twinam) Clear.
Okay, let's go!
Move.
(Helo) We should probably
head out of the city...
try to scout one of
the outlying air bases...
see if we can find a Raptor.
It's not exactly
what I expected.
I thought I'd be stepping over decaying
corpses in the streets.
Yeah, we saw a few bodies
here and there.
Not much though.
Sharon said...
Cylon Sharon said they had
troops picking up the bodies...
transporting them
to mass incinerators.
Your girlfriend's
from a lovely family.
Good people, great values.
Enough, all right?
Okay, I was fooled by her.
She fooled me. You happy now?
It's not about making me happy.
Then what's it about?
What do you want here? You want
me to say I'm a frakking idiot? Okay.
I'm a frakking idiot.
That make you feel better?
I don't care anymore.
I've been here for months, by myself...
on the run,
one step ahead of the Cylons.
With the Cylons,
I guess, actually.
She seemed so real.
Like Sharon, you know?
Same grin, same laugh,
all the little things.
I fell in love with a machine.
It's stupid, so just call me an idiot,
and let's be done with it.
You're an idiot.
All right? You're an idiot.
But the Cylons have a way
of making all of us look like idiots.
Kara, what are you doing?
Making a pit stop.
I've got something
I gotta pick up.
Hey, we gotta keep going.
I got a place here, Helo.
The Cylon virus spawned itself in our
subsystems before we broke the network.
I had teams cleaning
each subsystem...
but it'll be at least an hour
before we restore main power.
Captain?
What few Marines we have...
are assembling at their checkpoint,
but comm. Is spotty.
Where are the Cylons?
It looks like they split into two forces.
One moving forward...
Forward, one moving aft.
Yes, sir.
I've seen this before.
These are their objectives:
Secondary Damage Control
and Auxiliary Fire Control, sir.
If they're successful, they will
override our decompression safeties...
and vent us all into space.
Once we're all dead, they'll turn the
ship's guns on the fleet and wipe it out...
once and for all.
[Wind blowing]
Dr. Baltar.
How, in God's name,
did you find us?
What do you have there?
It's a child, obviously.
A child?
Can I hold it?
Please.
Is this the shape
of things to come?
That's my understanding.
Only one thing for it, then.
Commander?
Please! Commander, where are you going?
Come back!
Commander!
Commander.
Commander, please.
No!
[Shushing]
He killed our baby.
Our baby?
Adama,
I saw him drown the baby.
Why would anyone want to drown a baby?
Gaius, the answer is all around us.
What happened here?
Human sacrifice.
Not the fairytales
your scriptures would have you believe.
I thought Kobol was supposed
to be a paradise, or something.
Some place where...
gods lived with the humans
in harmony, or...
For a time, perhaps.
Then your true nature asserted itself.
Your brutality.
Your depravity. Your barbarism.
So the scriptures
are all a lie.
It's all just a lie, just a cover-up
for all this savagery.
Exactly.
All of this has happened before,
Gaius, and all of it will happen again.
Adama.
Mankind's true nature
will always assert itself.
So he will try
and kill our baby.
Only if you let him, Gaius.
Only if you let him.
Keep your eyes up ahead.
Come on.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Is it clear?
(Twinam) Yeah.
All decks, sir.
(Apollo)
The keypad's dead.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I'm human! (Kat) Jammer?
Yes, sir, it's me. It's me, Jammer.
Jammer. Don't shoot. Please. It's Jammer.
(Apollo)
Collishaw!
(Collishaw) Sir!
Watch the hatch!
Kat, Twinam, find those explosive rounds.
(Twinam) Sir.
What the hell happened here? I don't
know, sir. I wasn't here in this fight.
I just came in here to hide.
The Cylons are everywhere.
All right, settle down.
You're gonna be just fine.
(Kat)
Apollo?
You're kidding me. That's it?
Didn't have much to begin with, sir.
The other fire teams must've come
and cleaned the locker out before us.
Six rounds,
there are five of us.
Okay, well, each of you guys take one.
I'll take the reload.
You're not counting me, are you, sir?
I mean, I'm just...
I'm just a knuckle dragger here.
I don't know to fight Centurions.
I don't know the first thing
about fighting Centurions.
Come on, let's go.
(Helo)
Let's do it.
[Gun firing]
Never have your house keys
when you need them.
These yours? You paint these, Kara?
Yeah.
¤[music playing]
How the hell did you get power?
Batteries.
Kept turning off the power.
Something about not paying the bill.
That is definitely not you.
It's my dad.
Well, we've got one package of noodles.
You don't believe in groceries?
You know, I never really
liked this place, anyway.
[Cigar cutter clicks]
Air conditioning
doesn't work in the summer.
Heater doesn't work in the winter.
The rent's a crime.
[Exclaims]
After the attack, I never...
never pined over
any of my old crap.
Never missed it.
The stupid view of the parking lot,
broken toilet in the bathroom.
You know, everyone I know
is fighting to get back what they had.
I'm fighting 'cause I don't know
how to do anything else.
(Roslin)
How far to sickbay?
(Venner)
Sixty meters.
(Dualla) She stopped breathing
a while ago.
(Billy)
Dee?
Oh, my gods, it's Dee.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah. I was going
to the head...
Oh, my gods, you're bleeding.
Went back to my rack.
Are you shot?
I forgot something.
Hey.
Dee, look at me. Dee, look at me. Dee?
Try using her rank.
Petty Officer Dualla,
look at me.
Hey.
I'm glad to see you.
I've been here in the dark a long time.
It's probably a concussion.
Cpl. Venner, we need
an alternate route to sickbay.
Open your eyes.
Look at me.
We don't want to walk into gunfire.
We want to go away from the Cylons.
Now clear your head.
Come on.
We can go only... All the way on
the starboard side. It's a lot farther.
Good. Starboard, let's go.
Lt. Wallace reports his unit destroyed
two Centurions at this junction.
They've trapped a third
in the ship's laundry.
It can't walk,
but it's still shooting.
At least we've contained
the threat to Auxiliary Fire Control.
Trust me, they're still heading
for the Aft Damage Control.
Lt. Gaeta?
Sgt. Hadrian reports
her unit's had to halt...
their advance
on Deck 10 at frame 69.
(Gaeta) Cylons cut through
the hull ahead of her...
and the compartments
are open to space.
Smart move.
Keeps us from chasing them.
There's nothing between the last two
Cylons and the decompression safeties.
If you know any prayers,
now's the time.
[Chirping]
What do you say we take five?
How much further do you think?
Tarn getting shot, it wasn't your fault.
You know that, right?
Chief?
Talk to me,
you motherfrakker!
Motherfrakker.
[Coughs]
Socinus
better appreciate this.
He's probably lying in the sun
like some godsdamn emperor.
He's an idiot.
I hope he's okay.
He'll be fine.
He's a tough kid. We just...
gotta get him the med kit.
Yeah. Get ready to go, Cally.
[Leaves rustling]
Where the hell have you been?
Where have you been?
- L... - Doc, where have you been?
Answer me.
I got lost in the...
Answer me!
Doc, you never
run off like that, all right?
You're under my command. This is
military operations, you understand me?
What I want to hear from you is,
"Yes, sir!" Yes, sir.
Look, Crashdown, I...
I'm getting a really bad feeling
about this place...
Yeah, you and me both, Doc.
(Tyrol) Flash. Flash!
Thunder.
Go, go.
Here.
Where's Tarn?
What happened?
The Cylons.
Were you followed?
No.
How's he doing?
He's not gonna make it.
What?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
We got the med kit.
Give him a shot! Give him another shot!
It's too late.
What do you mean it's too late?
I got you the med kit.
What else do you want?
So we go get
the medicine you asked for.
Tarn... For what?
For this.
Come on,
you gotta do something.
You have to do something.
I can't change that he's gonna die, Chief.
It's going to be slow and painful,
and we can spare him that.
We can spare him that
if we give him the morpha from my kit...
and the one
that you brought back.
What?
No.
El-tee?
El-tee, come on.
He's your man, Chief.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Hey, buddy.
It's Chief. How you doing?
What's going on, Chief?
Well, you know,
listening to the birds.
I got a little something
for the pain.
Good news, buddy.
We got a rescue party here.
Raptor just landed.
We're gonna put you on it
and take you back to Galactica. Okay?
We're going home?
Yeah. We're going home.
How're you coming, Jammer?
That should do it, Captain.
Hey, nice job. You guys, check
the deck, check the lockers.
There's gotta be more rounds in here.
Yes, sir.
Combat, 12-8642,
Arms Locker.
Apollo here.
Colonel, it's Apollo.
He's on Deck 12, aft frame 86, between
the Cylons and Aft Damage Control.
Apollo, XO, sitrep.
Five armed effectives.
We haven't seen anything but bodies
between here and the hangar deck.
(Bonnington)
Clear.
(Venner) Okay, from what
I can remember...
the sickbay is about 20 meters
through that hatch.
How you feeling?
Like I'm walking underwater.
Any Marines with you?
(Apollo) Privates Collishaw, Twinam.
Take your men and proceed without delay
to Aft Damage Control.
Is that yours?
Yeah, I guess it is now.
Okay. If you're gonna keep it
in your trousers like that...
you might want to
turn the safety on.
Great.
(Venner)
Is it stuck?
No, frak!
The hatch won't open.
The other side's
been depressurized.
All right, Cpl. Venner, this is your ship.
I'm just a tourist.
Find us another way to sickbay.
Okay.
Okay, we have to head toward
Aft Damage Control.
(Apollo) Aft Damage Control?
That's what they're after.
(Tigh) Let's not waste any more time.
You get to Aft Damage Control.
And get there
right frakking now, mister.
Get there before the Cylons or we
lose the ship. Is that clear?
Aft Damage Control. RFN.
On our way. Apollo out.
(Apollo)
Okay. Hold on.
Okay, we made it.
Twinam, Jammer, you take this side.
Yes, sir.
Kat, Collishaw, you take that side.
We're gonna need some cover.
(Collishaw)
All right, let's move.
Let's get this stuff out.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
[Guns firing]
That's not so...
Okay, everybody, get down. Stay down.
Hold your fire
till I give the signal.
Remember, you only have one round, so
it's gotta be a headshot to make a kill.
You understand? Understood?
Yes, sir.
Kat, kill the flashlight.
Take cover. Take cover.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Steady up there, Jammer.
Yes, sir.
Not really cut out for this, sir.
Me, neither.
But sometimes you gotta roll the hard six.
What does that mean, sir?
I don't know.
It's something my dad says.
Just don't shoot till I tell you to,
all right?
Okay, we're in good shape.
They're coming.
But we're in good shape.
[Thudding]
Headshot. Reload. Headshot.
Reload. Headshot.
Okay, they're coming.
Everybody down!
You want to shoot that,
you have to take the safety off.
[Footsteps thudding]
[Gun firing]
[Screaming]
[Guns firing]
Fire!
[Screams]
(Venner)
Hey.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
We did it. We got them all!
They don't look so big now,
do they?
(Apollo)
They look big enough.
(Kat)
Oh, gods.
(Dualla) I'll take that.
Yeah.
(Venner) Have you been shot?
No, I don't think so.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm fine.
The gods must be
watching over you.
Tired of walking?
Okay.
[Engine starts]
Thanks.
[Sighing]
Hey.
How you feel?
Better.
I thought you said...
Forget what I said...
and listen to what I'm saying.
Are you listening?
[Grunts]
I'm sorry.
I didn't hear that.
Could you...
Could you do that one more time?
Come here. Let me be clear.
Get the curtain.
(Tigh) Doc Cottle's on his way.
He'll be here any minute.
He's gonna be all right.
You know that.
Yeah. Yeah, I know that.
Colonel, I assume there's still
a cell out there waiting for me?
That's right.
Cpl. Venner, I'm ready.
I can't believe you sided
with that woman against the old man.
I wouldn't do that
if you put a gun to my head, and you did.
As far as I'm concerned,
you're not fit to wear a uniform.
You're right about that part.
I am not fit to wear the uniform.
And maybe I never was.
Then again,
neither were you.
But this isn't my ship, and
it sure as hell isn't yours. It's his.
And when he wakes up, he'll decide
what to do with the both of us.
Thank the gods
I didn't have kids.
[Metallic rolling]