(female narrator) Previously
on Battlestar Galactica.
Congratulations, Doctor. You've
just uncovered your very first Cylon.
I'm not a Cylon.
(Boomer)
This isn't happening.
[Gun fires]
I've been here for months, by myself,
on the run, one step ahead of the Cylons.
You're going out there or I'm gonna blow
your brains out right here, right now.
[Grunts]
(Apollo)
How did Crashdown die?
He gave his life in the finest
tradition of the service.
You have my parole.
When I'm on duty...
I'll make no attempt to free her
or sow insurrection among the crew.
And when I'm not on duty, I'll
report directly back to this cell.
I have
a few months to live.
And in that time, I will
lead the people to salvation.
It is my sole purpose.
As it appears obvious that...
the Government cannot function
under the current circumstances...
I have decided to dissolve
the Quorum of Twelve.
[Reporters chattering]
And as of this moment...
I have declared martial law.
(Tigh)
You're sweating.
It's hot in here.
How long have you known...
Lt. Valerii was planning to
assassinate Commander Adama?
I had no idea she was
planning anything of the kind.
You were frakking her.
I ended that weeks ago on your orders.
You covered for her, you lied for her.
I admit I used bad judgment.
You protected her
at every turn.
Colonel, I had no idea
she was a Cylon.
I would like to exercise my
Article 21 rights at this time.
[Scoffing]
I'm sure you would.
I guess you haven't heard,
Cylons don't have rights.
Cylon? Wait a minute... You know
what we do with Cylons, Chief?
I am not a Cylon. Roslin came
up with the execution method.
I'm Galen Tyrol.
She put a Cylon
out of the airlock.
My father was a priest.
My mother was an oracle.
I've served on Battlestar
since I was 18 years old.
The Pegasus, Columbia,
Atlantia, Galactica...
[groans]
Don't talk to me
like you're a soldier!
You are not a soldier!
[Groaning]
The old man always had a soft spot for
you. Let him decide what to do with you.
Colonel, you gotta believe me.
I am not a Cylon.
I'd never do anything
to hurt Adama.
I love the old man.
That's what your girlfriend said.
Get him the hell out of here!
[Man chattering
on PA system]
[Gate clanking]
[Chains jangling]
Chief.
[Sobbing]
I thought you were on Kobol.
[Gate closing]
Don't you talk to me.
Don't come near me.
Don't touch me. If you do...
I swear, I will kill you.
[Boomer sobbing]
[Leaves rustling]
No sign of Centurions on the
perimeter. I don't like it.
Human toasters
don't go anywhere alone.
Think they're bait?
No.
A pair of Cylons don't just
drive up here in broad daylight...
not after we hit
that convoy last week.
Frakking A.
[Panting]
All right, screw it.
Pass the word
for everybody to sight in.
I want to blow these Cylons away
before they ever knew what hit them.
Good.
We got to figure out
where the hell we are.
Why? You don't know?
You're the navigator.
You were driving.
(Starbuck) All right, we
can head toward Cobb's Point.
There's an emergency
airstrip there.
No, I've been...
I was thinking we could
head southwest towards...
[gun cocking]
Do you hear that?
Drive through a lot of bad
neighborhoods? Better safe than sorry.
I hear that.
[Gun firing]
We're sitting ducks down here!
You go, I'll cover.
Why me?
Don't start.
Fine!
Ready?
Yeah!
Go!
[Panting]
Five of them, spread out
between nine and one! 50 meters.
Ready?
Go!
I didn't see
any shiny silver out there.
I think we're dealing
with the human variety.
Hope so. They're not
as tough as mechanicals.
Yeah.
They do bleed good, though.
You gotta like that.
[Panting]
(Helo) Let's get out of here. Come on.
They locked the Chief up with
Boomer. Tigh thinks he's a Cylon.
I know. I'm going
to see the Colonel now.
I think he wants me to find
a way to clear the Chief or...
Or what? Throw him out the
airlock like a piece of garbage?
If Commander Adama were in
charge this would never happen.
Yes, but he's not
in charge, is he?
But I've known the Chief
for years. He's no toaster.
He was involved with Lieutenant
Valerii, who most certainly is a toaster.
That word is racist.
I don't like it.
(Cally)
Sure...
he's shown some bad judgment
getting involved with her.
But that doesn't mean he's a
toaster. You've got to help him.
Say something, Gaius.
Tell me you won't have racial
epithets used in your presence.
I'm very sorry.
I was going to tell the Colonel
there's nothing I can do.
The Cylon detector I developed
doesn't work. Clearly.
No.
You've got to help him.
Your child's gonna be half toaster.
How does that make you feel?
Nothing could
make me happier.
I just don't know what I'd
possibly say. Excuse me.
(Cally)
He helped you.
He didn't tell anyone
what you did on Kobol.
What you did
to Crashdown.
[Gasping]
What I did to Crashdown
saved your life.
Are you blackmailing me?
Help the Chief,
help yourself, Doctor.
Yes, Doctor. That's what
you're best at, isn't it?
Deck log.
What the hell's the matter with
your Cylon detector, Doctor?
You gave the assassin a pass.
Yes, but that was a beta test.
A preliminary.
Clearly, I haven't perfected my
methodology and she slipped through.
(Dualla)
Fuel report.
(Tigh) What the hell are
you telling me here...
that we are
back to square one?
That no one's results
are definitive? No, I...
That we have no way of knowing
who are the Cylons among us?
(Baltar)
I'm not saying that.
I'm saying since
Valerii's test...
Since the assassin's test, I've
developed a new set of protocols...
which should eliminate any errors,
anomalies, that cropped up earlier.
If you let me test
the Chief's blood...
I might be able
to tell once and for all...
No if. I want a definitive answer,
no more of your weasly techno-babble.
He's a Cylon
or he's not...
so get down there and do
something right for a change.
I am the Vice President.
Legally speaking, if the
president is incapacitated...
shouldn't I take over
her duties?
Legally speaking, I have declared
martial law and that makes you nobody.
[Machines beeping]
So, unless you want to join
Roslin in the brig...
I suggest you get to work.
It's good to see you,
Colonel.
Aren't you getting tired of
the continual humiliation?
The disrespect from mechanics
and colonels alike?
What do you think?
Maybe it's time
to do something about it?
(Gaeta) Sir? What's this?
The fleet captains are reporting
protests among civilians...
demonstrations, petitions,
even some civil disobedience...
all over the declaration
of martial law.
Sir, there's more.
The Tauranian refining vessel
has stopped refining tylium.
They say if they don't have
a voice in the government...
What?
Their captain says
they'll send fuel...
once a civilian government
has been restored...
and, three other ships are also
refusing to re-supply Galactica...
until the President's
reinstated.
And I got a note from Combat, warning
about problems with tylium re-supply...
so watch your fuel burn
until further notice.
Questions?
When you coming back
to the card game?
I'm afraid when I'm off duty, I'll be enjoying
the intimate surroundings of the brig...
until... well,
until further notice.
Come on back.
We miss you, Captain.
We could bring
the game to you.
Somehow I doubt
Col. Tigh would approve.
There's one going on tomorrow
night! Hey, all right. All right.
Hey, knock it off!
Morning, sir.
Sergeant. Shall we?
[People chattering]
Morning, sir.
Morning, Dee.
Fancy meeting you here.
I was just on my way, sir.
Hey, guys.
How's it going, Dee?
Good, thanks.
How's my father today?
Commander Adama's the same,
Captain. He's sedated.
Resting comfortably
since the surgery.
Trouble brewing in the fleet,
though. Oh, I'm shocked.
What kind of trouble? Martial
law isn't going down too well.
Protests, demonstrations...
some ships are even refusing
to re-supply Galactica.
And this is the honeymoon
period. What's a dictator to do?
[Chuckles]
Yeah, I wish...
[sighing]
I wish you were
in command, sir.
Dee...
He's hitting
the bottle. A lot.
Thank you for the company,
Petty Officer Dualla.
You're welcome, sir.
[Gate opening]
[Woman chattering
on PA system]
[Ellen sighing]
You okay, baby?
No, I'm not okay. My head feels like
it's gonna roll off my shoulders.
What are you working on?
I'm trying to figure out how to
solve our re-supply problem...
now that half the fleet
has gone out on strike.
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
I should probably call a summit. Sit
down with all the ship captains...
and explain the situation and tell
them why I had to declare martial law.
Screw them. Like you have
to explain yourself to them.
It wouldn't hurt. Might
cool things down a little.
What?
Nothing.
No, No, No, it's...
You're the boss.
Far be it for me to tell you
how to do your job.
I know that's one of
your issues. Just say it.
I don't know, it just
feels kind of touchy-feely.
You know, "Let's all sit down and talk
about how we feel about martial law."
Bill would
never do that.
But you gotta do
what you gotta do...
I mean, Bill may never
get on his feet again.
Honey.
Honey, you handle this
the way you want.
They'll respect that...
eventually.
This is the XO.
Mr. Gaeta, send the following
to all ships captains.
Message begins:
"Re-supply operations of this
ship are not, repeat, not optional.
"All ships to recommence
scheduled supply runs immediately.
"Failure to comply will result
in stern measures."
Message ends.
You happy now?
(Starbuck) I'll flank! I'll draw fire!
[Panting]
[Gun cocking]
No, no.
Hi.
[Guns cocking]
We're not Cylons.
Right. You're human.
You have a soul. You swim in the
stream. We heard it all before.
Hey, Colonial Fleet.
Notice the uniforms?
Yeah, right. We've seen
Cylons in uniform before.
We're human.
Yeah, right.
(Starbuck) Everyone on
Caprica is dead. You're not.
I just got here.
I want to hear some names.
I'm Anders.
Samuel T. Anders?
Yeah, that's right.
That's Jo-Man, Rally, Ten Point,
Sue-shaun, Crip-key, Morris Fink.
Kara, these are
the Caprica Buccaneers.
[Scoffs]
I don't think so.
Give me a ball, little girl.
I'll shove it up your ass.
Please. Try.
Okay, since we're all
getting along so well...
can people stop
pointing their guns at us?
How does a professional pyramid
team survive a nuclear holocaust?
We were in the mountains
when the Cylons attacked.
High altitude training.
We've been on the run
ever since.
Doing what?
Raiding military stores for
ammo, anti-radiation meds...
and plugging toasters
whenever they show up.
Same as us.
Okay.
How many foul breaks did you have
in the play-off against Aerilon?
You're kidding, right?
You either have the answer
or you have a bullet.
Three.
Wrong. Four.
Three. Last one was
called back on instant replay.
(Helo)
He's right, Starbuck.
I lost 20 cubits
on that game.
Fine, for now.
On three.
One.
Two.
Three.
[Anders sighs]
You know
you guys suck, right?
You can't shoot, you can't pass, and
you sure as hell can't take a point.
Everyone's a critic.
Here's your medication,
Madam President.
And a little something
from the galley.
Thank you, Cpl. Venner.
Chamalla and licorice.
Would you like some?
I hate licorice.
Me, too.
It's interesting he still
calls you, "Madam President."
You still have
a lot of supporters out there.
Something ugly is coming.
I can feel it.
Sir, the refinery captain's
still not cooperating.
And now seven
other container ships...
are refusing to release their
supplies, food, medicine, even coffee.
Coffee?
This is getting ridiculous.
Frak this. It's time to get their
attention. I'm sending in the Marines.
I want a Raptor and an armed
Marine boarding party...
for every ship
refusing the re-supply order.
Sir, we're stretched
pretty thin on manpower.
I'm not sure we have
enough Marine non-coms...
to command
that many boarding parties.
Pull pilots
and deck officers...
to command the boarding
parties if you have to.
Tell them to get over there
and bring back the supplies.
Whatever it takes.
Make it happen, Lieutenant.
Yes, sir.
People, step back.
All right.
We're just here
for the supplies!
Stay out of our way
and no one gets hurt!
(Palladino) For the last
time! Step back, all right!
Get back!
[People clamoring]
[Gun fires]
[Woman screams]
[Groans]
[Screaming]
Cease fire!
[Machines beeping]
(Tigh) Four civilian dead. How
the frak could this have happened?
What did you expect, genius? You put
a pilot in charge of crowd control.
[People chattering]
Palladino!
Did you give the order
to shoot on that crowd?
No, sir. Of course not.
The crowd surrounded us.
Were they armed?
No, sir, but...
you had to be there. They were
yelling and screaming at us...
and then it got violent. They
started throwing things, canisters...
coffee, I think.
Coffee?
You shot people
for throwing coffee?
The crowd was out of control,
they were pressing in on us.
My men were getting hurt.
Somebody took a shot...
I don't know who it was.
Then all hell broke loose.
If ever we needed you, Bill,
it's right now.
Troops shooting unarmed
civilians. This is a travesty.
He has truly stepped over the line.
It'll cause an explosion in the fleet.
The press will have
a field day.
The ships will
begin to splinter.
The Cylons will be able to
eliminate us a few ships at a time.
I've got to
get out of here now.
Corporal.
I'm right with you.
I'm so glad you said that. I wanna
take Billy and Elosha with me.
Of course you do.
I've worked out a way of
getting us in the hangar deck...
and I can get us a Raptor.
But we're still gonna need
clearance to get off the ship.
I know how to get that.
You do?
Mmm-hmm. The question is, where
do we go once we get off this ship?
We'll have to find some place
to hide in the fleet...
while we rally support
among the people.
(Apollo)
I've got an idea about that.
You're not gonna like it.
I'm not cut out for this.
I never was.
Don't talk like that, Saul.
This is your moment.
Me and Bill, side by side,
that was the deal.
It was never
supposed to be me alone.
Well, like it or not, you're in
command. So you better deal with it.
I don't want to "deal with it." I do
not want a command, don't you get it?
Jeez, why do I
listen to you?
What are you talking... I never told
you to send troops out to that ship.
No, no. You didn't tell
me to send troops anywhere.
You just manipulate. You always do.
You put the knife in and you twist it.
Oh, right. You're gonna blame
me for your own inadequacies?
I'm not blaming you, Ellen.
You are so frakking passive...
that if I didn't push you...
Well, forget it.
...you'd never get your head out of
that frakking bottle and do anything!
[Bottle shattering]
I'm warning you, I'm telling...
Get your...
[grunting]
[Moaning]
Oh, yeah.
I love you so much.
Shut up, Ellen.
I guess
you really must hate me.
I don't know if it makes
any difference right now...
but I'm really sorry
you got pulled into this.
You know, what we had...
Was nothing. Nothing.
You're a machine. I'm not.
Well, whatever I am,
I know how I felt.
Software doesn't have
feelings. (Baltar) Open cell.
I never meant to hurt you.
[Gate opening]
I'd like
some privacy, please.
I'll be fine,
thank you.
And how are we this
evening? What do you want?
I'm here to determine
whether you're a Cylon or not.
Your arm, please.
His test doesn't work too well. I
mean, he gave me the green light.
The test works...
just fine.
Chief? Chief?
(Baltar)
I lied to you, Sharon.
I covered up your true nature from the
rest of the fleet for my own purposes.
What did you do to him?
He's not breathing!
No, he's dying right now,
Sharon.
I can save him, if you tell me how
many Cylons there are left in the fleet.
I don't know,
but I'm not getting a pulse!
Yes, you do.
Now, buried, deep down in that thing
you call a subconscious, you know.
How many?
I don't know!
He doesn't have time for this,
Sharon. His organs are shutting down.
In 10 seconds time, he'll
experience complete brain stem death.
Now, how many?
[Boomer sobbing]
Do you love him, Sharon?
Only you can save him.
Ten, nine...
Do you love him?
Do you love him, Sharon?
Eight! There are eight!
[Gasping]
[Groaning]
All right, let's get these
weapons unloaded! Let's go!
We raided an armory earlier
today, about 18 klicks north.
Brought home a lot of toys.
What is this place?
Delphi Union High School.
Toasters don't patrol this area.
It's a good place to get
some shut-eye, a bite to eat.
How many people you have here?
53.
We had almost a 100 before the
toasters ambushed us last week.
Let's go!
More pyramid teams?
No. Just us C-Bucs. The rest
are survivalists, hikers, mostly.
How's your stock
of anti-radiation meds?
(Anders) We raided a couple of
hospitals down in Pilgrim Bay.
I figure we've got enough
for about three months.
Let's get you some bunk space.
Come on.
Fifty-three, huh?
Not exactly an army.
A hell of a lot better than the two of
us if we're going to assault an airbase...
steal a Heavy Raider and
get the frak off this planet.
I'll just be a moment.
[Machines beeping]
Doctor...
I need your help.
But it's illegal, dangerous, and in
violation of your oath as an officer.
You're a lousy salesman.
Corporal.
Cpl. Venner.
I just want to tell you how
much the President appreciates...
all the little things
you do for her.
Hey, anything I can do
to make things easier for her.
Great.
She has a special request.
If I could
just get your signature, sir.
[Sighing]
Why are we closing down
Causeway B?
Integrity testing, sir.
It got chewed up pretty bad
when the toasters boarded us...
and we've been getting
some pressure drops in there.
Tell them to get it fixed.
[Man chattering
on PA system]
[Exclaims]
Sorry.
Lieutenant.
Things are pretty frakked up
these days.
most days.
If people are upset they should
go through proper channels, so...
I'm not sure I understand what you...
I was running some maintenance checks...
and detected a series of scrambled
calls going out over the past few hours.
You wouldn't happen to know
anything about that, would you?
No, sir. Off-log calls
are against regs.
That's right.
[Door closing]
[Cardiograph beeping]
I'm sure you won't approve.
But I guess
that's nothing new.
I just want you to know that
this... This isn't about you and me.
[Footsteps approaching]
Goodbye, Dad.
[People chattering]
You gonna help out here
or what?
They're putting the Chief
in there, you know.
I don't care if they put
a giant parakeet in here.
The Colonel says we build
a cell, we build a cell.
This isn't right.
He's one of us.
No. He's one of them. He always
was. We just never saw it.
No, he's innocent.
She tricked him.
Such loyalty.
Were you frakking him, too?
[Both grunting]
You want to get pissed at
someone, you get pissed at Boomer.
She's the one who put the
Chief in this cell here, not us.
A truce?
[Panting]
Evening, sir.
Evening, Dee.
Fancy meeting you here.
Everything set?
Roger that.
Sorry, Captain.
Can't chit-chat today.
Captain.
I'm having trouble with the
ordinance tracking on my Raptor, sir.
I can't get it to cycle.
Oh, change of plans, boys. Instead
of getting some rack time...
I'm gonna take a minute to do
the Lieutenant's job for her.
(man) Yes, sir. After you.
Thank you.
Okay, make it look good,
but not too good.
[Gasping]
Hold it!
Private, do you know
who I am?
Good. You and I
have something in common.
We each took an oath to protect and
defend the Articles of Colonization.
Those Articles
are under attack...
as is our entire
democratic way of life.
Now, my duty won't let me stand
here and allow that to happen.
So I intend to go through that
hatch and get off this ship.
Damn it. They should
be here by now.
You can either stand aside
or you can shoot me.
You'll have to decide
where your duty lies.
Madam President...
Madam President,
this way.
Oh, Billy...
Madam President...
I'm not getting
on that ship with you.
What?
I understand
what you're trying to do.
But it's gonna
divide the fleet.
At the very best, it'll create an insurgency
against Adama and at the worst, a civil war.
Taking part in that
is a line that I won't cross.
(Apollo)
We do not have a lot of time.
I wish you well.
Dustoff two-seven,
Checkers green...
ready for launch
on medical mission.
Request clearance.
Good to see you. You okay?
I think so. My feet barely
touched the ground getting here.
I know what you mean.
(man on radio) Dustoff two-seven,
Standard port three departure approved.
Cleared for launch.
Standard port three, wilco.
Sir, Cpl. Venner reports the
former President's missing.
Missing?
Two men down. Cell's empty.
Damn it.
Alert security. Set Condition
Two. No one on or off the ship.
[Alarm blaring]
Attention. Set Condition
Two throughout the ship.
Repeat. Set Condition
Sir, flight log records a Raptor
departed ship two minutes ago...
with Doc Cottle
on a medical emergency.
Medical? Confirm that.
Dradis has their transponder
bearing 2-8-7 carom 0-0-3.
Range 2-7.
Get the CAP on the horn
and have them intercept.
And get Captain Adama
out of the brig.
Sir, Doctor Cottle
is still onboard.
He says he was forced to request
the Raptor at gunpoint by Apollo.
Son-of-a-bitch.
Dee, put me through
to that Raptor.
(Gaeta)
CAP has visual on the target.
Turn that ship around, Apollo, or
I'll order the CAP to shoot you down.
(Apollo)
We're not turning back.
I'll do it.
And don't think I won't just
because you're the old man's son.
Then do what you have to do,
Galactica.
Apollo out.
Fire across their bow.
Hotdog, Galactica. Fire
across their bow. Acknowledge.
Wilco, Galactica.
Hotdog reports they're
not turning around, sir.
Where are they now?
Dradis shows them
approaching Cloud Nine.
(Gaeta) Sir, if they
dock, we may lose them.
Cloud Nine is one of the busiest
transport hubs in the fleet.
Shuttles are coming
and going constantly.
If they board one and take off, it'll
be before we can shut down air traffic.
Galactica, Hotdog.
Request instructions.
I need further instructions.
Do I fire or not?
Dee, tell Hotdog
to hold his fire.
Repeat, weapons hold.
Do not fire.
Hotdog, Galactica. Weapons
hold. Repeat, do not fire.
[People murmuring]
They couldn't have done it
on their own.
Anybody notice off-log calls?
Scrambled communications?
No, sir. Nothing.
Well, we're home free
for now.
(Zarek) Good to see
you, Madam President.
Captain Apollo...
what is Mr. Zarek
doing here?
Once Tigh gets over his initial shock,
he'll send troops out to search for us.
If we're going to make it
we have to keep on the move.
I figured Mr. Zarek here is
the only one in the fleet...
with enough shady friends around
who could possibly hide us.
I love the way
he puts that.
Well, Mr. Zarek. It would seem
the enemy of my enemy is my friend.
Call me Tom.
A shuttle's waiting, ma'am.
We have to hurry.
[Sighing]
Wow, is that the best
you can do?
Nice to know installing a
regulation pyramid court...
was one of the priorities
of the Resistance.
Well, there are some things
one cannot live without.
Let's go.
(Anders) Are you kidding me?
I'd wipe the court with you.
We'll see about that.
I was up for the pros.
Bum knee took me
out of contention.
I see.
Is that gonna be your excuse
when I kick your ass?
"My poor knee hurts."
At least I have an excuse. I can't
imagine what yours is gonna be.
[Both grunting]
[Yells]
Nice shot.
Thanks.
Thanks, Doc.
I appreciate it.
Don't thank me. Thank her.
(Tyrol) Why? What did
she have to do with it?
(Baltar)
Everything.
Nothing.
Love is a strange
and wonderful thing, Chief.
You'd be happy
you experienced it at all.
Even if it was
with a machine.
(Tyrol) What're they going to do to her?
They're setting up
a new holding facility.
There will be tests,
mental, physical.
Like she's... Like she's
some kind of lab rat?
That's the idea.
This is just great.
Bill Adama's little baby boy
pulls the wool over your eyes...
and you let him
get away scot free.
You're a laughingstock.
You didn't want
this command.
Well, don't worry about it. You
won't have it for much longer.
All because when push came
to shove, you got shoved.
It was his son.
(Adama)
Saul.
What's happening on my ship?
Wait in the corridor.
Ellen, can I speak to my XO?
Of course.
[Grunting]
Slow.
[Panting]
What's happened?
I've frakked things up
and good.
How?
I made some bad calls.
[Chuckles]
I've done that.
Not like these.
You gonna pour us one
of those or what? Yeah.
I never had much use for people
who second-guessed my decisions...
especially if they've never
held a command.
They don't understand
the pressure.
You make a call...
that affects
the lives of thousands...
and you have no one
to turn to for backup.
(Tigh)
You make it look easy.
You know that's a lie now.
A lot of pieces to pick up.
Then we'll pick them up
together. Where's my son?
(man) Bitch! (woman) Traitor!
[People yelling]
[Gun fires]
[Mumbling]
No, no, no, no.
[Gasping]
I love you, Chief.