(female narrator) Previously
on Battlestar Galactica.
I have a few months to live.
And in that time, I will lead
the people to salvation.
It is my sole purpose.
Praise be to the Gods.
Here is our salvation.
Laura Roslin's actions in
suborning mutiny and sedition...
among the military
could not be tolerated.
Therefore, Cdr. Adama
was left with no choice...
other than to remove her
from office.
We've got to
get out of here now.
I'm right with you.
I think these guys might
really be human.
Everyone on Caprica's dead.
You're not.
I just got here.
Not exactly an army.
A hell of a lot better
than the two of us...
if we're gonna assault
an airbase...
steal a Heavy Raider, and
get the frak off this planet.
Nice to know installing
a regulation Pyramid court...
was one of the priorities
of the Resistance.
[Groans]
Nice shot.
Thanks.
[Panting]
Stand aside
or you can shoot me.
I intend to go through that
hatch and get off this ship.
The former president's missing. Missing?
Two men down. Cell's empty.
Damn it.
(Apollo) Well, we're home free for now.
Glad to see you,
Madam President.
Zarek here
is the only one...
with enough shady friends
around who can possibly hide us.
(all)
Traitor!
(man)
Cally shot Boomer!
(Tyrol)
No, no. No.
[Gasping]
I love you, Chief.
What's happening on my ship?
I frakked things up
and good.
I made some bad calls.
A lot of pieces to pick up.
Then we'll pick them up
together.
Go through.
[Truck engine droning]
You've been awake
for an hour?
[Sighs]
So what are you gonna do if you
can't make it back to your ship?
I'm getting back.
Well, I know we were able to
take your sorry ass by surprise.
Frak you.
Nice. But the truth is...
we really don't know
what the hell we're doin'.
A lot of our tactics are stuff
we just saw in the movies.
We could use
some professional advice.
You want some advice? You're
on the losing end of this fight.
Give it up
before you all die.
Head further up
in the mountains...
above the ambient radiation,
and just hole up.
And what? Wait to die?
As soon as I get back to
Galactica, I'll send a rescue party.
Yeah, right.
If I say I'm gonna
do something, I do it.
You always such a bitch
in the morning?
Count on it.
My kind of woman.
[Grunting]
Hey. We have a mission to accomplish.
So what?
Mission.
[Grunts]
Fine. Whatever.
[Sighs]
I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't mean to...
[laughs]
Got you.
So weak.
So, so very weak.
Lighten up a little bit. It's
only the end of the world.
[Laughs]
Sue-Shaun, I want you to watch our
perimeter, especially on the flank.
Okay.
The Cylons have a refueling airstrip
just on the other side of that ridge.
There's a Heavy Raider makes
a regular refueling stop...
every afternoon,
like clockwork.
(Helo) Machines like routine. Yeah.
It's usually guarded by less than
three of the mechanical varieties.
We've left it alone
up until now.
(Helo)
So what's the plan?
Go through this gully, approach
the airstrip from the south side...
sprinkle our men
through the tree line...
wait for the Cylons
to land the Raider...
hook up the refueling hoses. Once
they hook up the tylium hoses...
we take out the guards and
blow their refueling station.
I thought you wanted
the Raider intact?
They build them tough.
Believe me.
Blowing the fuel will barely
put a scratch on the hull...
but it might give us enough
time to board the Raider.
Once I'm inside...
I'll blow the brain, and I'll
start working on trying to get it...
[gun firing]
(man #1)
Stay back! Over there!
(man #2)
Open fire!
[Guns firing]
[People shouting]
(Anders)
Kara, take cover!
Get back!
Everybody fall back!
Fall back! Kara, let's go!
[Guns continue firing]
[All chanting]
Adama! Adama! Adama!
[All applauding]
[People whistling]
[Inaudible]
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to be back.
There are things
we don't say often enough...
things like what we mean
to one another.
All of you
mean a lot to me.
I just want you
to know that.
Let's get back to work.
I feel strange. Like...
Closer to the ground.
You should check in
with the doctor.
Mr. Gaeta? Where do
we think they are now?
The stolen Raptor
with Capt. Adama...
and the former president.
The fugitives.
The fugitives docked
at Cloud 9 last week.
We effectively lost them
at that point...
due to the large volume of inter-fleet
traffic going to and from Cloud 9.
By now, they could be holed up
anywhere in the fleet.
I want them found.
She was dangerous enough
as a symbol of Resistance...
but now with Lee helping...
I wanna search
every ship in the fleet.
Quarantine procedures.
Isolate the ship
out of the main body.
If it's clean, we keep it quarantined
away from the rest of the fleet.
She can hide,
but she can't run.
Dee, start
quarantine procedures.
Start with Cloud 9.
(Roslin)
How much longer...
are we meant to stay hidden
in this meat locker?
(Elosha)
I don't know.
I communicated your latest
message to the Quorum of Twelve...
and they've decided that the question
of openly supporting you needs more...
deliberation.
I need to make
an appeal to the people.
Make a strong enough
argument...
and the Astral Queen will be
the first ship in line.
[Apollo scoffs]
Like they knew anything but roll
over and take orders from you.
One more bit of news
I should convey.
[Sighs]
Zeus has returned to Olympus.
Adama's back in command.
[Stuttering]
My father? He's back?
(Zarek) Word just came
in over the wireless.
He is a tough
old bird.
[Sighs]
(Zarek) What we really need
is something heartfelt...
something human and personal
that will galvanize the people.
Like a son
denouncing his father.
(Apollo)
My name is Lee Adama.
Until recently, I was the commander
of Galactica's air group...
but when Cdr. Adama,
my father...
decided to stage a military
coup against the President...
I could no longer support him
or his actions.
I love my father.
I respect him.
But in this...
he is wrong.
He must be opposed.
I call on all free-thinking
people in the fleet. I...
I can't do this. Sorry, everyone.
I thought I could, but I can't.
I'm playing
the religious card.
I know exactly
what I have to do.
How does this thing work?
(Simon)
You're okay.
You're in an aid hospital.
They brought you in
yesterday morning.
You got shot in the abdomen.
I'm Simon.
Can you tell me your name?
Kara.
[Clears throat]
Kara Thrace.
[Inaudible]
(Simon) You were in
surgery for about two hours.
I removed the bullet.
I didn't think you were gonna
make it there for a while.
Take it easy.
[Coughs]
I know that hurts.
Who brought me in?
(Simon)
This big guy named Anders.
Used to be a pro Pyramid
player, if you can believe that.
Yeah, I know him.
[Water running]
Where is he?
He died.
On the table.
I thought he was
only slightly wounded.
It turns out a piece of
shrapnel had nicked his aorta.
Massive internal bleeding.
I'm sorry. We did everything
we could do.
[Door closes]
[Crying]
[Door opens]
(Simon)
Good morning.
I see you're sucking down fluids
at a rapid pace. That's good.
Are you a Cylon?
What do you think?
I think you didn't
answer the question.
[Chuckling] I am most
definitely not a cylon.
Of course, I don't know
what you'd expect me to say.
If I was a Cylon,
I certainly wouldn't admit it.
Can I leave?
There's the door.
[Sighing]
Frakking doctors.
So I am a doctor,
not a Cylon?
The jury's still out.
I would expect the Cylons to have
better digs than this, though.
Where is this rattrap?
We're about 20 clicks north of Delphi.
Used to be a mental institution.
It's not much, but it's one of the few
places the Cylons haven't found yet.
[Groans]
Okay.
So, what, I'm supposed to believe
there really is a Resistance out there?
Shh. Don't tell anybody.
We're trying
to keep that quiet.
Time for your pain meds.
[Groans]
(Tyrol) If I may speak on
behalf of Specialist Cally?
She was distraught through
the experience on Kobol.
Being on the surface,
fighting the Cylons...
it's shattering
for all of us.
I don't believe she was in her
right mind when she shot Boomer.
[Sighs]
Did you love her, Chief?
Excuse me?
Boomer. Did you love her?
I thought I did.
When you think you love
somebody, you love them.
That's what love is:
Thoughts.
She was a Cylon,
a machine.
Is that what Boomer was?
A machine?
A thing?
That's what
she turned out to be.
She was more than that
to us.
She was more than that to me.
She was a vital,
living person...
aboard my ship
for almost two years.
She couldn't have been
just a machine.
Could you love a machine?
No, sir.
I guess I couldn't.
Cally discharged a firearm
without permission...
endangering the lives
of her shipmates.
Thirty days in the brig.
Dismissed.
Thank you, sir.
You'll see her again, Chief.
Excuse me?
There are many copies.
You'll see her again.
[Clears throat]
How many patients
do you have here?
Am I being
interrogated again?
I just think it's odd...
that I've been here for two days,
and I haven't seen anybody else.
Just you.
We have 223 patients
at the moment...
two doctors, and five teachers
masquerading as nurses.
I know a teacher
masquerading as president.
What's that?
It's awfully quiet.
No screams, no moans, no...
"Doctor! Doctor!
Please help me! It hurts."
Most of our patients are succumbing
to acute radiation poisoning.
Symptoms include powerful
fatigue and immediate nausea.
This is followed by several
days of comparable well-being.
After that, cell death in the gastric
and intestinal tissue causes...
massive diarrhea, intestinal
bleeding, and loss of water.
It's not pretty.
But it is quiet.
The biggest killer
in this place is infection.
That's why we have you
under quarantine.
We don't know what you
brought in with you yet.
Your test results
will be back this afternoon.
Okay, almost done.
I think there may be a cyst
on one of your ovaries.
Is it serious?
No, it should be fine.
We'll keep an eye on it.
Gotta keep that reproductive
system in great shape.
That's your most
valuable asset these days.
Right.
I'm serious.
Finding healthy,
child-bearing women your age...
is a top priority
for the Resistance...
and you'll be happy to know that you
are a very precious commodity to us.
[Laughs]
I am not a commodity.
I'm a Viper pilot.
You see any Vipers
around here?
[Gasping]
I mean, you do realize...
that you're one of a handful
of women left on this planet...
actually capable
of having children, right?
I mean, that is your most
valuable skill right now.
Well, I don't want a child,
so just drop it, okay?
Well, no one's forcing you.
Just take a moment
and think about...
where you are
and what's going on.
The human race
is on the verge of extinction.
And, to be quite frank
with you, potential mothers...
are a lot more valuable right now
than a whole squadron of Viper pilots.
I shouldn't have mentioned it. I
should've known you'd be sensitive.
A lot of women with your history
forego bearing children of their own.
My history?
I saw the fractures
on your X-rays.
A lot of old fractures
from childhood.
It's interesting how you managed
to break every finger on both hands.
Every break in the exact same place,
between the first and the second knuckle.
Did someone
break your fingers, Kara?
Get out.
Children
of abusive parents...
often fear passing along that
abuse to their own children.
Get out!
All right.
[Door opening]
[Sobbing]
[People chattering]
Is she kidding with this?
I know it's hard to believe, but that
message has cropped up all over the fleet.
It's religious crap.
"It seems I have been chosen to help
lead you to the promised land of Earth.
"I will not question
this choice.
"I will simply try
to play my part in the plan.
"Therefore,
at the appointed hour...
"I will give a signal
to the fleet.
"All those wishing to honor the
gods and walk the path of destiny...
"will follow me back to Kobol.
"It is there that we will meet the
gods' servant with the Arrow of Apollo."
We've got five Raptors with
marine fire-teams standing by...
to board the Astral Queen.
No one's gonna follow her.
No one's gonna believe
this crap.
No one's this stupid.
And anyone that is, that wants
to make a suicide run to Kobol...
please let them.
(Roslin)
How long till we jump?
Two minutes.
Any other ships
declared themselves for us?
Not yet.
[People mumbling]
No, that... No, please,
this isn't necessary.
Give them your blessing.
[Whispering]
Oh, no. It's not right.
It isn't who I am.
Laura, this is your path...
the one the gods
picked for you...
the one you picked
for yourself.
Sue-Shaun!
(Helo) Anders, we must have been
over this line 10 times already.
She must have taken a bullet. She
was right here by the vehicles.
She would have got up and
crawled the frak out of here.
Hey, we have to search
the entire area again.
I told you we shouldn't have
pulled back so fast.
I thought she was with us.
Anders, we got ambushed, okay?
We all got separated. There's
nothing we could have done about it.
Kara, of all people, would
understand. Let's just find her.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
(Boomer)
I know where Starbuck is.
Sharon?
Where have you been?
Tracking you.
Who is she?
She's with us.
You're the father
of my child, Helo.
I'm not gonna lose you.
Where is she?
(Zarek)
We're ready.
Send the signal and jump.
Astral Queen has jumped away.
Now we'll see
how many follow.
To sit around and wait for Starbuck
to show up with that stupid arrow?
Two, three at the most.
[Groans]
[Door opens]
Good morning.
[Panting]
You look better.
What's this new scar?
You had to go back in last
night while you were asleep.
Some internal bleeding to tie
up. Nothing to worry about.
Everything's gonna be fine.
We're just about
done with you, Starbuck.
Nice way of puttin' it.
Just a couple more tests,
and...
I almost said, "We'll be
sending you back home."
I guess we'll be sending you
back into the fight.
That sounds good to me.
Hey, I just woke up.
And now you're
going back to sleep.
You're the doc.
[Door closes]
[Groans]
(Simon) Pending lab-test
results on sample ovaries...
complete removal
will proceed tomorrow.
If lab tests are positive,
then subject will be removed...
to processing facility
for final disposition.
(No. 6) Is that regret I
hear in your voice, Simon?
If it is, it certainly
is none of your concern.
[Sobbing] Lords of
Kobol, please help me.
Good morning.
[Chuckles]
Are you sure
you're feeling okay?
You know, something actually
has been bothering me lately.
[Screams]
I never told you
my call sign was Starbuck.
[Rasping]
You can't kill me.
Just die!
[Gasping]
[Choking]
[Panting]
[Gasps]
Sue-Shaun. Sue-Shaun,
it's me, Kara.
Hold on, okay? I'm gonna
get you out of here.
[Gasping]
No, no time.
Cut the power.
That'll kill you.
Can't live like this.
The baby machines.
Please.
[Machines beeping]
[Sighing]
Please.
[Whispering]
[Grunts]
[Sobbing]
[Grunting]
[Buzzing]
[Crying]
[Groaning]
[Starbuck grunts]
Hello, Starbuck.
[Gun firing]
[Screaming]
Kara, come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
Go! Go!
[Groaning]
Get down!
Kara, get down!
[Guns firing]
[Groaning]
Come on! Let's go!
Gotta go!
Hey.
[Men shouting]
Come on! Move like you have
a purpose, people! Go! Go! Go!
[People chattering]
Twenty-four ships, sir.
That's almost a third
of the fleet.
Why?
[Crying]
(Boomer) They were
conducting research...
into Human-Cylon
breeding programs.
(Starbuck) Human-Cylon?
They call them farms.
[Groans]
Your gunshot wound
looks fine.
So, farms, that's great.
What were they gonna do? Knock
me up with some Cylon kid?
They were gonna try to.
We haven't been
very successful so far.
Supposedly,
they can't reproduce...
you know, biologically...
so they've been trying every
which way to produce offspring.
Why?
Procreation, that's one
of God's commandments.
"Be fruitful."
We can't fulfill it.
We've tried. So we decided...
To rape human women.
You know, if you agreed to bear
children, it'd be voluntary.
Maybe even set you up
with someone you like.
Like you two kids?
We're different.
What the frak is that
supposed to mean?
They have this theory.
Maybe the one thing
they were missing was love.
So Sharon and I...
[sighs]
We're set up...
To fall in love?
[Sobbing]
They didn't ask Sue-Shaun...
if she wanted to
fall in love, all right?
They put a tube in her, and
they hooked her up to a machine!
They know who you are, Kara.
You're special.
Leoben told you that.
You have a destiny.
Starbuck, what's this
second scar?
I don't know. I don't think
I wanna know now.
You know?
No.
[Scoffs]
All right, how many women
do they have at these farms?
Hundreds.
Maybe thousands.
I don't know. I haven't
accessed that data.
Here's what we do.
Take the Heavy Raider, cram
it full of ground troops...
find out where the next farm
is, liberate it, then the next...
and the next, and the next. No. No,
that's not why you came to Caprica.
[People chattering]
Go find Earth.
What about you?
You said you needed
professional advice.
We'll muddle through.
We've managed so far.
They'll kill you.
You'll die here.
You know that.
A lot of people died here...
but I'll tell you this:
If I'm gonna die here...
I'm gonna take out every last one
of those frakking farms before I do.
I'm not gonna leave you here.
You said you were gonna
come back, remember?
I'm gonna hold you to it.
I'm coming back.
I said it.
I meant it.
Yeah, okay.
Hey.
Be safe.
Let's go home.