NARRATOR:
Previously on Battlestar Galactica.
We lost her.
We did the best we could, but she's dead.
And that's all there is to it.
It's you and me from now on, no matter what.
Just like we agreed.
I just can't get her out of my head,
our little girl.
She's so beautiful.
You understand, Maya, that this adoption
requires absolute secrecy.
You have my word.
I'm leaving Galactica, not you.
I don't know how we can.
I don't either, but I know I'm gonna try
if you will.
I'm Brother Cavil.
I understand you asked
for religious counselling.
Let's talk about what happened.
Chief?
Ah!
TYROL: I don't understand
how I could do that to Cally.
BROTHER CAVIL: You think you're a Cylon.
I am not a Cylon.
Well, of course you're not.
But that's what you're afraid of, isn't it?
CAIN: We have our own Cylon prisoner.
NO. 6: She's obviously
been abused, tortured.
I know a place where you can stay,
where you will be safe.
Where I can look after you...
Vice President Baltar offered the contents
of this case as proof of his sincerity.
GINA: A nuclear bomb?
I'm afraid that that I have no alternative
but to announce that I am,
as of now, a candidate for the presidency.
What should be important to you, personally,
is that Roslin's up three points in the polls.
SKULLS: Hey, I am picking
up a large planetary body.
Hey, you know what this is?
It's habitable.
We may have just found
a world that can support human life.
ZAREK: We needed an issue,
something to set us apart from Roslin.
This is it.
Permanent settlement on this planet.
What took you so long?
We got Marines and Raptors.
We're gonna get you and your people
out of here, okay?
Incoming!
MARINE: Go! Go! Go!
MAN: There's no way out!
Go! Move!
WOMAN: Get up and get going.
They've got us zeroed in.
If we stay here, they're gonna chew us up!
All right, we've got to fall back.
Position up this hill. Let's go!
- Let's move, people!
- MARINE 1: Let's go! Let's go!
MARINE 2: Let's go! Let's go!
(SCREAMING)
The jaw's set nicely. You're done here.
I'm kicking you out of here
and sending you back to work.
Work? Like this?
You gotta love a woman who can complain
even with her jaw wired shut.
You got a visitor.
I'm sorry.
What I did was
unforgivable,
inexcusable.
I didn't come here to...
I forgive you.
No, Cally, no.
It wasn't you. I know that.
It wasn't you.
It was me.
I may have been out of my mind
and not know where I was...
Doing or anything, but it was me.
You're in pain.
I know you've been in pain
for a really long time.
Don't feel sorry for me.
I care about you. I always have.
I always will.
BOOMER: Move! Come on!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- MARINE: Come on, get up!
Get them up! Get them up!
This way!
HELO: Let's go! Get in there! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
STARBUCK: Come on, get in here!
HELO: Get him up there!
Get him up there, now!
Sharon, take the gun!
Ammo!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
STARBUCK: They've got us
boxed in here really good!
Frak!
Can't reach the Raptors.
The Cylons have jammed the freqs.
MARINE: Frak!
Are they still out there?
Watch yourself.
STARBUCK: Yeah, they're holding back now.
Yeah, but why?
They're holding position,
sending for non-lethal weapons.
They want some prisoners for interrogation.
The rest they're gonna send to the farm.
STARBUCK: I'm not going back
to one of those farms.
Yeah, well, you don't have any choice.
None of us will.
They're gonna lob some gas in here
and then we'll all wake up somewhere else.
Damn.
So what you want to do here?
Sit it out. Wait and see if she's right.
If she is, then you and me,
we've gotta have an agreement.
An agreement?
I'm not going back to
one of those farms, Sam. I'm not.
So if she's right
and they throw gas in here,
you do me, I do you.
What are you talking about?
This is what I'm talking about, okay?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Down two more points, and this after
hearing his notions of social policy.
Not to mention his wishful thinking
that he's calling security policy.
Are people really gonna be that stupid?
Are they really gonna be that shortsighted?
TORY: He's got the only
issue people care about.
Oh, I know. The planet.
That's all anybody wants to talk about
is a frakking planet.
Excuse my...
My language, Tory. I'm sorry.
I know in my gut that settling on
this planet's gonna mean disaster
for humanity, and I will not say otherwise
just to win an election.
As you wish, Madam President.
So, I guess I should
start packing up my office
unless you have some super-secret back-up
plan for victory in your pocket.
There's always a back-up plan for victory.
Just in time for the priest.
Oh, good. Send him in.
18 hours.
They're taking their good,
sweet time out there.
They could've overrun us
at any point during the night.
They're up to something.
What are we up to?
Got any brilliant ideas
in that military brain of yours?
We do the same thing, we always do,
fight them till we can't.
HELO: What do you think?
Let's get a recon crew together.
Scout the area.
Figure out what's going on out there.
Clear.
They're gone.
They just left.
Thank the Gods.
It's a miracle.
Let us pray.
Lords of Kobol, we trust in your benevolence
and praise your righteousness.
Give the people of this fleet the wisdom
to see the goodness
and the strength of your servant,
Laura Roslin.
Amen.
Admiral?
Madam President...
The Admiral's not here.
This is my meeting.
I wanted us to talk privately,
without the press getting wind of it.
Please have a seat.
Well, you must have something
very interesting to say to resort to such
pedestrian methods of deception.
The question of permanent settlement
may well be the most important issue
we face since the attack.
- I agree.
- Good.
The question should be carefully studied
before making the final decision.
And the middle of an election campaign
is hardly the time for careful study.
Therefore, I propose a truce.
You and I will issue a joint statement
declaring that the question be tabled
till after this election.
We will both pledge that regardless
of who is elected,
the decision will be made only
after careful deliberation
involving all elements of the public,
and after consultation with the military
and the Quorum of Twelve.
Doctor,
I know we've had our disagreements,
but this issue transcends
personal disagreement
as well as politics.
I am appealing here
to your sense of patriotism.
Let me tell you, my sense of patriotism
is doing just fine.
Thank you very much for asking.
I see it as my patriotic duty
to lead this fleet to a new world.
That new world is
unquestionably New Caprica.
But thank you, Madam President,
for demonstrating to me
just how desperate your campaign
for reelection has become.
Were you with a blonde woman
on Caprica just prior to the attack?
What?
She knows.
Were you
with a tall, blonde woman
in the Riverwalk section of Caprica City,
just prior to the attack?
She can see right through you.
Get out of here now.
You'll resort to anything
at this stage, won't you?
I'm afraid my affairs on Caprica,
and who I chose to consort with,
are none of your business.
You know, I saved your life.
I won't save your political career.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
We are not moving down to that planet.
If Baltar wins the election...
Baltar won't win the goddamn election...
If he does, then what?
We're gonna just sit on this ship and rot
while everyone else gets to start a new life?
Ellen, my job is to protect the fleet
from the Cylons,
and that's exactly what I'll be doing.
If you want to move down there,
go ahead, be my guest.
Go down and cat around with all the men,
have yourself a good old time.
Saul, I want you.
(INTERCOM BUZZING)
XO.
You got to be kidding me.
I'll be right down.
Starbuck's back.
I gotta get down there.
WOMAN: Put him in here!
Hey, hey, guys, take it easy with it.
Come on.
Am I good or what?
There's gonna be no living with her now.
It's good to see you. Welcome back.
Thank you, sir.
I brought some friends with me.
I see.
Right, right. Um...
This is, um...
Wow. This is Samuel T. Anders of...
I know who he is.
Damn good to meet you, sir.
- Caprica Buccaneers.
- That's right.
A hell of a player.
Picon Panther fan myself.
Well, we enjoy beating them, too.
- It's good to have you aboard.
- Thank you.
I have news. Good news, actually.
The Cylon occupation is over.
They left. They're gone.
What are you talking about?
BROTHER CAVIL 2: It's true.
The Cylons have left the Colonies.
They're headed for greener pastures.
Security!
What the hell?
Code Blue!
He's a Cylon.
Back off, Chief. We've got him.
Well, this is an awkward moment.
Yes, he's right. I'm a Cylon.
And I have a message.
So, take me to your leader.
Take him to the brig.
Take that to the brig, too.
HELO: What? Admiral, she didn't know...
Don't even start.
Of course she knew.
Welcome to Galactica.
Why the frak didn't you say anything?
I don't know. Maybe I didn't want to.
Or maybe I wanted him to come here
and blow up the whole ship.
Is that what you're looking for?
Hmm?
You don't mean that.
Sharon, we'd finally got
the Admiral to start trusting us.
Finally.
And what?
They killed my baby.
You think I care about you or us
or whether the Admiral trusts me anymore?
Hey!
Sharon, I love you!
And I'm not giving up this frakking easy!
Not after everything!
Are you ready? All right.
Aah!
No, no, no, no, no.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Hey, hey, hey, listen,
you don't have to get me drunk.
I will sleep with you, okay?
I figure I owed you one,
what with you saving me and all.
- Little slut.
- Shut up.
- Now you're gonna play hard to get.
- Yeah.
My hero.
Gods, I guess they'll let
anybody in here these days.
Hey.
Hi.
Welcome back.
Do you want to meet my man?
- Your man?
- Hmm.
My personal property.
Right, Sammy?
Don't call me Sammy.
Oh!
How does it feel to be my personal property?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And before you answer.
He loves it.
I bet he does. I'm Lee, by the way.
Hey, Samuel. I'm sorry.
I've heard a lot about you.
Pleasure. A shot?
Sure, why not.
Lee, when are you gonna get yourself a girl?
I'm doing fine, thank you.
You're not still frakking Dualla, are you?
Thanks a lot.
I'm not one to like, you know,
lecture or anything
'cause I'll do just about
anything to get into the pants
of some hot, little young thing.
Hey!
Is that all I am to you?
Yes, but you love it.
That's right. I don't mind doing charity work.
You are a hot, little thing, but you know that.
Thank you.
Where did he go?
(EXCLAIMS)
I'm here to deliver a message.
After that, you can do
whatever you want with me. I don't care.
Would you mind telling me what's going on?
I'm not a frakking Cylon. I'm not...
Oh. Well.
Okay, then.
Sorry to bust up your day, Brother,
but there's been a change of plans.
It's been decided that the occupation
of the Colonies was an error.
I could have told them that.
Bad thinking, faulty logic.
Our first major error of judgement.
Well, live and learn. But the war heroes
have managed to swing opinion
over to their side.
What heroes?
A Six and an Eight. One of the Eights
you know as Sharon Valerii.
Their voices carry a lot of weight,
so when they started talking
about our mistakes and our corruption
and our need for a new beginning,
the rest of us listened to them.
You see, we're not like you.
We can admit our mistakes,
and we're not afraid of change.
So you abandoned the Colonies,
leaving behind a devastated,
nuclear wasteland.
And we're supposed to be grateful?
Our pursuit of this fleet of yours
was another error.
That's two, for anyone who's keeping score.
Both errors led to the same result.
We became what we beheld.
We became you.
Amen.
People should be true
to who and what they are.
We're machines.
We should be true to that.
Be the best machines
the universe has ever seen.
But we got it into our heads
that we were the children of humanity.
So, instead of pursuing our own destiny
of trying to find
our own path to enlightenment,
we hijacked yours.
You said it, Brother.
My mission here is simple.
I'm to tell you that you've been given
a reprieve.
Cylon and man will now go
their separate ways.
No harm done.
No harm?
You completely annihilated our race
and destroyed our civilization.
Now, if you're gonna start pointing fingers...
Where did the Cylons go?
Back to their home world?
Well, I'd rather not say just now.
Let's just say we have other plans.
New marching orders by your one true god?
There is no god.
Supernatural divinities
are the primitive's answer
for why the sun goes down at night.
At least that's what we've been telling
the others for years.
We can't really prove it
one way or the other, of course.
You know a way to prove it?
Throw them both out the airlock.
Let them see if there really is a Cylon god.
Ballots from the Adriatic. D?
Right. This way.
MCMANUS: (ON RADIO)
It has been an exciting day.
The election has been
a real rollercoaster ride.
The polls now have been closed
for about five hours,
results have come in,
and it's been a see-saw battle,
back and forth between
the presidential candidates.
So, all night long,
as we suspected it would be.
We're still waiting for a few more numbers
to come in now,
from the counting room of Galactica,
which, I must tell you,
as some of you may know,
was the source of a bit
of a controversy yesterday.
Councilman Zarek
had filed a formal complaint
against the use of military...
The military involvement
in the election process.
Now, it's just reached...
A compromise was just reached
late yesterday, allowing Galactica
to provide security for the balloting,
as well as civilians to oversee
and then to monitor the situation.
Yes, okay. Now we have some more
votes coming in here.
Still not done, but what we have so far is
6,282 more votes for Baltar,
which puts his total now to
21,569.
Is that... Is that correct?
And we also have Roslin.
Her total now is at 17,754.
We've had 2,981 more votes
come in for Roslin at this time.
So that is how things
are looking at this point.
We'll continue to bring you up-to-the-minute
coverage as the count progresses.
Yeah, it's me.
Is this a secure line?
Okay.
There are only five ships left to report in.
We need to move now.
I'll take care of it.
Lieutenant.
I'll be right back.
Are those the ballots from the Zephyr?
Yes, sir.
All right, we'll take it from here.
We were told to take it to the ballot room, sir.
Counting has already begun.
We'll take it from here.
GAETA: Right there, please.
Last one.
We have some more results that
have come in here now.
And, uh...
Wow, okay. 8,593 for Roslin,
now, which puts her over the top.
That's 24,265 for Laura Roslin.
Is that correct?
And 22,266 for Gaius Baltar.
We're gonna check these again
because that has put her over the top.
She... She has done it.
She has retained the Presidency
in an improbable comeback
in the final hours of the campaign.
Again we will, of course,
like to check those numbers if we could,
but it appears that Laura Roslin has
retained the Presidency
in defiance of the polls, the pundits
and the purveyors of gloom and doom.
But I've never seen a political race
end like this,
but it has just happened.
I'm James McManus.
We'll check those numbers
and we'll get back to you very shortly.
Thank you.
I've seen a lot of elections, Gaius.
Most honest, a few fixed.
And you can always tell the fixed ones
because they don't make sense.
And this doesn't make sense.
Laura Roslin is many things,
but she's not corrupt.
And she's not dishonest.
It's over.
Congratulations, Madam President.
Well, thank you.
I hope you don't take this the wrong way,
but are you as shocked as I am?
I'm relieved.
Well, you don't sound it.
I'm just tired.
It's been a long campaign.
Colonel?
May I speak to you for a moment?
What's up?
Sir, I'm afraid these ballots
from the Zephyr are wrong.
What the hell are you talking about?
Dr Baltar's name is spelled correctly
on these ballots.
But this morning the Zephyr called me
and told me their ballots had a misprint.
They misspelled Baltar's first name.
We didn't have time to print new ballots,
so I told them on my authority to go ahead,
use them anyway.
Baltar's name is spelled correctly here.
So they couldn't have come from the Zephyr.
They're frauds.
Now, there's a complete chain of custody
from the Zephyr, all the way into this room.
So someone in the chain
is either the perpetrator
or at least, a willing ally in...
Thanks for bringing this to my attention.
I'll take care of it from here.
Yes, sir.
We should at least notify
the civilian observers
and the press that these ballots will...
I said I'll take care of it from here.
Yes, sir.
Madam President, you should celebrate.
It's a great victory and you've earned it.
(INTERCOM BUZZING)
Excuse me.
Admiral, we'll talk later. Thank you.
Adama.
Yes, sir, this is Lieutenant Gaeta.
Sir,
I don't know how to say this...
Fast and straight, I'd advise.
Yes, sir.
Admiral, I believe that Colonel Tigh is
involved in a conspiracy
to rig the election for President Roslin.
When I confronted the Colonel,
he admitted his guilt.
He said he acted in collusion
with your campaign manager,
Tory Foster.
Saul said Tory had contacted him
a few days ago.
He did it because he felt that Baltar
as president would be a disaster.
I said I agree,
but that what he had done was illegal.
A judicial tribunal may have to be convened.
Stop.
I gave Tory the go ahead.
I didn't know exactly what she was planning.
I certainly didn't know about Colonel Tigh.
Oh, my Gods.
But I did know that she was planning
to fix the vote.
You tried to steal an election?
Yes, I did.
And I got caught.
But Gaius Baltar
cannot become President
of the Colonies, Bill.
It cannot happen.
Laura,
I don't want him as President either, but...
He's working with the Cylons.
I saw him just before the attack on Caprica
with a copy of the tall, blonde Cylon woman.
The same model who accused Baltar
of treason
before disappearing from Galactica.
What the hell are you saying?
Why didn't you say something before this?
Because I didn't remember
seeing him with that woman
until I remembered it when I was dying.
I know how that sounds, but it's real.
The same way Kobol is real
and the Tomb of Athena is real.
And the map to Earth is real.
Baltar is working with the Cylons.
Even if that's true, you have no proof.
No, I don't.
Do we steal the results
of a democratic election or not?
That's the decision.
Because if we do this, we're criminals.
Unindicted, maybe,
but criminals just the same.
Yes, we are.
You won't do it.
We've gone this far, but that's it.
Excuse me?
You try to steal this election,
you'll die inside.
Likely move your cancer
right to your heart.
People made their choice.
We're gonna have to live with it.
It's the wrong choice.
Yes, it is.
All right, all right, all right.
(SIGHING)
So, that's it.
We just give it up, just like that.
The battle perhaps,
but not the war.
Well, the important thing is the error
was discovered and corrected.
You've been elected President.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much, Admiral.
Now about this error.
Exactly what kind of a tabulating error
could have occurred on your ship
that could have swung several
thousand votes away from me
in favour of your preferred candidate,
Admiral?
As soon as I have the time,
there will be an investigation.
I suggest that you take your victory
and you leave it at that, Doctor.
I think you'll find I can be magnanimous
in victory, Admiral.
And I believe the correct honourific
at this time is
Mr President Elect.
Set a course for New Caprica.
Jump completed.
We are in orbit around New Caprica.
We have all ships present
and accounted for, sir.
Send word to the Pegasus to launch
their initial ground team onto the surface.
ADAMA: Let's get a good look
at our new home.
Gods help us all.
Well...
I think my ability to see you will no doubt be
constrained by the responsibilities,
the requirements of my new position.
Listen to me.
My new position.
But obviously, we...
We will have the chance to connect,
to get together again
on New Caprica, once...
I'm not going to New Caprica.
What?
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to New Caprica.
We're all going to New Caprica.
All of us.
Every last, single one of us.
It's our chance to be together.
To be together again.
No.
I can't do this anymore.
Stay.
(UNZIPPING)
If you'll raise your right hand
and repeat after me.
"I, Gaius Baltar, do now avow and affirm."
"That I take the office of the President
"of the 12 Colonies of Kobol
"without any moral reservation
or mental evasion."
"That I take the office of President
"of the 12 Colonies of Kobol
"without any moral reservation
or mental evasion."
"That I will protect and defend the articles
of colonization."
"With every fibre of my being."
Congratulations, Mr President.
WOMAN: Congratulations, Mr President.
MAN: Congratulations.
(PEOPLE APPLAUDING ON RADIO)
BALTAR: I accept the role
offered to me by the Colonies
with humility and gratitude.
Thank you.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
No, no, no, wait.
And now,
because it was the first will of the people,
I am going to sign my first executive order,
requiring to immediately
establish settlements
on the planet we have come to know
as New Caprica.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
You have your orders.
(BEEPING INCREASES)
We suspect the warhead
was stolen from your lab,
then smuggled aboard
Cloud Nine by a Cylon agent.
I don't suppose I could interest you
in a cup of tea, Admiral?
A glass of ambrosia, biscuit...
Mr President,
this may be the first step
in a coordinated Cylon attack.
I suggest our first priority
be to focus in on internal security.
No.
No, I don't think so.
Our first priority is to the people.
See that they are safely established
on New Caprica.
Once that's accomplished,
we can put this tragedy behind us.
You're not listening.
I don't have to listen.
I'm the President.
The settlement begins and it begins now.
(SIGHING)
GAETA: Mr President?
President Baltar, good morning, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Oh.
Mr President, the union needs their answer.
(GROANING)
The union.
If it's not the union, it's the Quorum.
If it's not the Quorum,
it's the people's council.
(SIGHING)
We survived a nuclear holocaust, Mr Gaeta,
and the people complain about the weather.
Well, sir, it's hardly the weather...
Well, whatever it is.
How many Cylon attacks have there been
since I took office?
How many?
None, sir.
None. Precisely.
So why do the people complain?
Tell the union to get off their fat asses
and do some frakking work for a change
or I'll start rounding up their leaders
and holding them in detention.
I doubt they'll like that very much.
I'll tell them, Mr President.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Where's my... Where's my pills?
ADAMA: I'm telling you to go, okay?
TIGH: No, it's not okay.
I feel like I'm abandoning my post.
It's time to pack it in, Saul. You know it.
More than half the crew is down there
on the ground already.
We can barely put a squadron
in the air to train,
much less fly a decent cap.
We're not really doing
too much up here anymore.
Well, you're staying.
Yeah, well, someone has to
take care of the lighthouse.
Then I'll stay and take care of it with you.
I appreciate that.
But you know there's only
one person per lighthouse.
We both know the Cylons
could still show up.
Anything's possible.
But we've been orbiting New Caprica
longer than we ran after the attack.
I don't think they're coming back anymore.
Colonel,
good luck.
If she gives you too much trouble,
find yourself a younger one.
(CHUCKLING)
WOMAN: (OVER SPEAKER)
Attention. Attention.
Please donate any available
clothing remnants,
to HTV's New Caprica LOK outlet.
Any and all sizes are needed,
and your contribution
will help our children and elderly.
(MAN CHATTERING ON SPEAKER)
Hey, have you seen Sam?
I think he's over there playing pyramid.
Thanks.
(COUGHING)
Set her up.
Sam, you idiot!
I have been looking for you everywhere!
What the hell are you thinking?
Looks like I'm in trouble.
Doc Cottle is here. You're sick.
You are supposed to be in bed.
I would rather work this out of my system
right here than lie in bed all day.
Sam, come on.
Come on.
Duty calls.
PLAYER 1: Hey, you gotta be tough.
PLAYER 2: Where you going, Anders?
Tomorrow, man. Same time, same score.
PLAYER 2: Send us another player then.
I can't believe I married a moron.
Are you okay?
(COUGHING) I'm fine.
I'm fine.
PLAYER 3: Let's go! Let's go!
Ah.
STARBUCK: I'll be right back, okay?
Hey, Doc, wait.
So?
There's fluid in the lungs.
It's probably pneumonia.
So give him something.
I'd love to.
I've been out of antibiotics for months.
So what, that's it?
I have a lot of patients to see,
but he's young and he's strong.
So, make him rest, keep him warm
and with a little luck, he'll make it.
Son of a bitch.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
TYROL: Please, just calm down.
Everybody listen, just for a second.
Please. Please. Be quiet!
Hey! Shut the frak up!
When you elected me union President,
I promised I would keep us working.
Keep benefits flowing, but most of all,
- keep this city alive...
- Colonel!
Hey!
TYROL: I promised we would stay on the job.
TIGH: Wow, look at you.
Hi.
Oh, I'm so glad you guys are here.
Me, too.
It's pretty, pretty exciting.
Yeah, that wears off.
So what's going on here?
President Baltar.
TYROL: Men, women and children
are dependent on our...
Sir, Anders is really sick.
Doc Cottle's giving me the runaround.
Says there's no antibiotics.
It's a load of crap.
Anything you can do to help me cut through
the red tape?
You should give Apollo a call.
Pegasus is sitting on the backup meds.
He'd spring some for you.
Yeah, I doubt that.
That was a long time ago.
People change.
TYROL: Health benefits,
rations and fair compensation.
Yes, we have a vital responsibility.
Okay.
There comes a time when you realise
that the engine you've built
with your blood and your sweat
and your tears is being used
for something so foul,
so perverted
that it makes you sick in your heart.
And it's then that you must throw
your body on the gears
and on the levers and on the machine itself
and make it stop.
And we have to show the people who run it,
the people who control it,
that unless we're free,
that machine will be prevented
from working at all!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Strike! Strike! Strike! Strike!
ROSLIN: Okay, everybody have that so far?
CHILDREN: Yeah.
Good, you're listening.
Think the President has a bit of a problem
on his hands.
I also want you to look at Chapter 10,
it's the history of the 12 Colonies.
It's really interesting.
The President's problems
are not our problems, right?
MAYA: That's right.
Our problems are homework
for everyone tonight.
(CHILDREN GROANING)
Now some of you are
going to stay and help me
with the art project for the presentation.
Everyone else, your parents are here.
Get your stuff, let's go!
Go on, get out of here!
MAYA: Bye, bye.
ROSLIN: Good job!
Yeah, okay. Bye, honey, thanks.
Good job. Good job.
CHILD: I finished again...
WOMAN: That's wonderful.
ROSLIN: Thank you, parents!
You know what?
Why don't you take the baby
and go on, okay? I'll finish up here.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Yes, go ahead.
A bubblehead. I love this. Are you staying?
Okay, everybody with an art project,
bring it up here!
Hello, Isis. Oh...
WOMAN: (OVER SPEAKER)
Section 7 power grid
is temporarily shut down for repairs.
Hey, what's going on?
It's for you.
Who is it?
Right.
APOLLO: What do you want?
I need a favour.
Is that right?
I hear that you're hoarding
a bunch of antibiotics for the pilots.
Where did you hear that?
Anders is sick. He has pneumonia, Lee.
I think that he might die.
Commander?
Wait one...
Yeah, Lieutenant. What is it?
I'm not sure.
I'm picking up something on dradis.
Dradis? How can you see anything
in that soup? I mean...
- There it is.
- What is it?
Wait, what is that?
Oh, my Gods!
It's a Cylon fleet.
They found us.
APOLLO: We have to get out of here, sir.
We can't just leave
all those people behind.
There's nothing we can do.
It's taking us forever just to get
to action stations over here.
We're in no shape for a fight, sir.
They'll be wiped out.
We don't have a choice.
We need to get out of here, right now!
All decks finally report condition one, sir.
Should we launch the alert fighters?
No.
Begin jump prep. We're leaving.
But we'll be back.
Start your prep.
Mr President! Mr President!
- Don't you knock?
- GAETA: Gaius!
- Gaius!
- Yeah, what is it?
The Cylons just jumped into orbit
and the Fleet's jumped away.
Judgement day.
I'm looking for Kara Thrace.
I am Gaius Baltar,
President of the Colonies.
I know who you are, Gaius.
I know very well.
As long as you offer no resistance,
you won't be harmed.
How do I know that?
You don't.
You also don't have any choice.
How did you find us?
Oh, it was quite by accident, actually.
We were over a light year away from here
when we detected the radiation signature
of a nuclear detonation.
Very well.
On behalf of the people of the 12 Colonies,
I surrender.
What do you want to do now, Captain?
The same thing we always do.
Fight them until we can't.