(male narrator) Previously
on Battlestar Galactica.
This will be Adama's command
until the day he dies.
And we are not going
to let him die.
(Gaeta) Sir, what about our
people on the surface of Kobol?
(Tigh) If they're still
alive, they'll have to wait.
El-tee, I think we should double-check
the supplies before we bug out.
We don't have the time,
Chief.
I could give you a shot, but you
wouldn't like the side effects.
Just do it.
The time is going to come when
you're not going to be able to hide...
what you're going through.
His lungs are filling up with fluid,
if he doesn't get more Serisone soon...
he's not gonna make it.
Tarn, you forgot the med kit, so
you've got to go back and get it.
Take a rifle, two clips
of ammo and a canteen.
[Guns firing]
(Seelix) It's too late.
He's not gonna make it.
(Crashdown)
I'm sorry, Chief.
Lords of Kobol...
take these brave men
into your arms.
Take up... Take...
the spirits
of our fallen friends...
so that they may share
in the everlasting life...
that awaits us all
beyond the vale of tears.
So say we all. (all) So say we all.
Nothing awaits them. No
eternal life. No damnation.
Only oblivion.
Because they haven't seen
the face of God, I take it?
Because they died here,
on Kobol.
I see.
(Tyrol)
Doc, let's go.
We're moving out.
Doc, you hear me?
No, I did hear you, Chief.
I just don't respond
to the title "Doc."
A "dock" is a platform for
loading and unloading material.
My title is Doctor or Mr. Vice
President, if you don't mind.
You are loading,
are you not?
(Tyrol)
El-tee?
El-tee? Crash!
Yeah, Chief,
I'll be right there.
No Cylons. (Crashdown) You sure?
[Groans]
Wait a minute.
Tree line, 2:00.
Got them.
What're they doing?
(Tyrol) Looks like they're
dismantling the ship.
(Crashdown)
Why?
Why not use it to fly the
hell out of here? I don't know.
I can't tell.
They're dragging it
into the tree line.
Oh, wait a minute.
They're building something.
Chief, is that a...
A missile.
They're building
a missile battery.
Well, at least we know
why they're not chasing us.
Why?
Why aren't they chasing us?
Because they don't have to.
[Sighing] They can just sit
back, launch a missile barrage...
that'll wipe out every
living thing in this valley.
[People chattering]
Next time I say I'm in a hurry,
cycle the damn airlock faster.
Is this your first day?
Dr. Cottle,
thank the gods you're here.
The President needs your help. Move!
Doctor. Doctor!
Okay.
Let's have some vitals.
Like now.
(Kim)
Two bullets, 9 mm.
This one lacerated the spleen,
the other nicked the aorta.
Now, we've removed the spleen
and felt we repaired the aorta...
Over the past few hours,
his B.P.'s dropped down again.
It's only 80I40, and his heart
rate's creeping back into the 130s.
Well, you missed something. He's
still hemorrhaging somewhere.
We're gonna lose him unless
we can stop that bleeding.
Get me an ABG, CBC and coags and get
set up for a rapid sequence intubation.
Is he gonna make it? How should
I know? I'm not a psychic.
Now get the hell
out of here.
(Cottle)
It's a mess in here.
Looks like the mesenteric
artery may have been damaged.
3.7 Mac.
Gods damn it, Kim, learn the
instruments! I said a 3.7 Mac!
(Kim)
Sorry.
Clamp it. Clamp!
(Ishay) Dr. Cottle,
his pressure's dropping.
It's 60I30.
Heart rate's starting to fall.
I don't think he can last
much longer. Just stay focused.
Get some more suction in here
so I can see what I'm doing.
[Grunts]
Colonel,
how's the Commander?
What?
How's the Commander?
He's still in surgery.
What's on your mind?
I need some medication
for the President.
She's not the President anymore.
Cottle's a little busy right now.
Sir, she's very ill...
Why aren't you in the brig?
Because no one
put me in there.
What the hell's all this?
Why aren't you in the brig?
I'm on duty, sir. Planning
the search and rescue mission.
Search and rescue?
For who?
We lose a plane
and nobody tells me?
For our Raptor crew down
on the surface of Kobol, sir.
Simes is senior pilot now.
He can plan the SAR.
You asked me to command the air group
when I'm on duty, and I'm on duty...
so am I in command or not?
What's the status
of the SAR, Captain?
(Apollo) Well, we don't know
in what area Raptor 3 went down.
So the only realistic chance
we have of finding her...
is the hope that her transponder or
disaster beacon is still functioning.
I intend to take
two Raptors...
one with medical personnel, and make
five low-level orbits of the planet.
What about that Cylon base ship that
Lt. Valerii supposedly destroyed?
What if she was lying?
Racetrack confirmed the
destruction of the base ship...
and I checked the gun-camera footage
from the Raptors, which verifies it.
Lt. Gaeta,
why are you hovering about?
It's the press.
The press?
They're demanding to know how much
longer we plan on holding them...
and when they can contact
their home-ships.
They demand? They're in no
position to demand anything.
You tell them to shut their yaps.
We'll get to them in due time.
(Dualla)
Excuse me, Colonel.
Shuttle from the Zephyr has just requested
permission to enter the landing pattern.
The Zephyr?
Yes, sir.
Evidently the Quorum of Twelve is
aboard. They're demanding to see you.
They demand?
Demanding job,
commanding a battlestar.
Clear them to land.
Put them in the Ward Room and hold them
there until I have time to see them.
Stop!
Madam President? What's wrong with her?
I don't know, but she's clearly
sick. You can see that, can't you?
But there's nothing I can do.
Madam President?
Yes.
Can I get you anything
while you're in the brig?
[Exhaling]
Billy.
No, thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm finding it...
hard to think.
It's withdrawal.
The chamalla.
Yes.
I'm trying to get you more.
Go fast.
[Chirping]
I count six missiles being carried
into the forest site so far.
It's all so pointless.
We kill them,
and they kill us.
So we kill more of them and...
so they kill more of us.
What's the point anymore?
You,
your race invented murder.
Invented killing for sport,
greed, envy...
It's man's one true art form.
You've done some
killing of your own, I think.
Yes, well, we're your
children. You taught us well.
Why does God want to bring a child
into this kind of world, anyway?
Because despite everything, despite all of
it, he still wants to offer you salvation.
Our child will bring that salvation,
but only if you accept your role...
as her father
and her guardian.
I'm not ready for that,
all right?
I'm not a father,
I'm not a guardian.
I'm not a moral leader capable of
leading anyone, let alone a baby.
Be a man, Gaius.
What?
Be a man. Whatever else
you are, you are that.
The time is coming when
you'll have to act like one.
(Tyrol) Wait a minute, wait a
minute. El-tee, check this out.
(Crashdown)
What do you got, Chief?
45 degrees east of the launcher,
you see that tree stump?
What the hell is that? It
looks like a dradis dish...
or at least a Cylon version
of a dradis dish.
It's probably salvaged
from the nose cone of a ship.
They are building
an anti-aircraft battery.
Anti-aircraft? For what? There
are no other aircraft around here.
The Galactica's gonna send
a search and rescue team.
When they do, that's at least two Raptors
doing a low pass over the crash site.
When those Raptors come looking for
us, risking their lives to rescue us...
The Cylons will
shoot them down.
Seven birds down for repairs. Three
out on picket duty with the CAP.
Com traffic, sir.
Priority messages are on top.
Cut to the chase, Captain.
How long before you launch the SAR? Come
on, Dee, these are all marked priority.
Sorry, sir.
That's how they came in.
I'm cannibalizing
305 for parts.
Should be up in the air in,
I don't know, 90 minutes.
90 minutes? We got men down
on that frakking planet!
Get your head in the game. You do
your job or go back to the brig.
Are all the members of
the Quorum in the Ward Room?
All 12, sir.
Don't suppose you want
to do this for me?
Never was much
at public speaking, sir.
So why are we here?
That's what I want to know.
What exactly is going on?
We have been cooped up in...
Laura Roslin suborned mutiny
and sedition aboard this ship.
She caused a key military asset
to be lost at a critical moment.
The Commander felt he had no
choice but to remove her from power.
You've said that.
Several times.
Well, I... You don't seem
to be listening, Colonel.
It does not matter what Adama felt,
he had absolutely no authority...
Adama knew exactly
what he was doing.
He was paving the way
to declare martial law...
and usher in a military dictatorship.
Isn't that right, Colonel?
(Tigh) I can't speak for the Commander.
He's still in surgery.
Well, you seem to be giving
the orders around here...
so what exactly
are you planning to do?
Are you declaring martial
law? Absolutely not.
I know for a fact that the old man
hated the very idea of martial law.
He believed in freedom and
democracy, and all that good stuff.
Well, since this is still a
democracy and "all that good stuff"...
I move that the Quorum demand
immediate access to President Roslin.
Excellent. I second it.
(Porter)
All those in favor?
(all)
Aye.
(Zarek)
Motion carries.
Colonel, we demand immediate
access to the President.
I will take your "demand"
under advisement.
(Ellen)
Madam President.
...anything that impedes
that understanding...
Madam President?
I have to consider...
Laura?
Hello.
Hi.
Are you all right?
I just came down to see if there
was anything I could do for you.
Anything I can get you?
I would like to have a conversation
with my attorney. Could you arrange that?
Yeah, sure, right.
Laura,
do you know where you are?
I'm in jail.
What's my name?
Have we met?
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
It's just the ringing.
Excuse me.
The ringing?
Right.
Okay, then. Take care.
[Groaning]
[Metal clangs]
Oh, my gods.
Ellen Tigh.
Ellen?
Ellen.
Lords of Kobol...
(Crashdown) The launcher looks
like a simple point and shoot...
no built-in guidance.
(Tyrol) Ordnance appear to be
standard ship-to-ship missiles.
They're modifying it
for atmospheric flight.
(Cally) One Cylon Centurion
walks the perimeter...
stopping at
regular intervals.
(Baltar) The dradis dish
that controls the missiles...
is on a 4.5 kG wavelength,
judging by the diameter.
It's guarded by
two Centurions, I think.
Sorry, Doc, did you say it
was guarded by two Centurions?
Yes, I did.
Okay. Is the dradis guarded
continuously or intermittently?
I saw two Centurions, through the field
glasses, continuously for five minutes.
In that time
they didn't leave their post.
So there's three toasters near the
launcher, two more out by the dish.
That's a lot of Cylons.
You ever handle a weapon?
Who, me? No.
I'm not a soldier, Crashdown.
I'll try to give you
the most simple assignment...
but I'm going to
need every man.
(Tyrol) You're not suggesting
we attack the Cylons?
We owe it to Socinus and Tarn to take those
frakkers out before they kill anyone else.
We have equal numbers. We
have the element of surprise.
Therefore we have
the initiative.
We can attack at a time
and place of our choosing.
El-tee, a word in private.
He's crazy. I'm not trained
for this kind of thing.
I've never fired
a gun in my life.
I haven't fired one
since Basic.
You? I just joined to
pay for dental school.
Basic Ground Assault was a
long time ago for all of us.
Those aren't training
officers out there...
they're programmed killing
machines. We don't have any choice.
Galactica will definitely be
sending a search and rescue party.
It's just a matter of time. If
we don't take out that launcher...
We can't go up against an armed
and defended position like that.
They'll wipe us out in the
first two minutes. That's enough!
Chief, look, under the circumstances,
it's important that you keep your cool.
I don't believe I've
lost my cool. I disagree.
Look, I don't want to attack the
launcher, either, but it's our duty.
We owe it to the rescue party,
and we owe it to Socinus and Tarn.
I fail to see what this has
to do with Socinus and Tarn.
Maybe that's why I'm an
officer and you're not.
Dismissed.
(Crashdown) This briefing will outline
a plan of attack in five graphs.
Graph 1: Situation.
Our situation is that we are stranded
on Kobol with a group of five Cylons...
who are planning to use an AAU to
destroy any SAR aircraft sent to find us.
There are no other
friendly forces present.
What's all this "graph"
business? Graph 2: Mission.
It's a five paragraph order.
... to destroy the AAU...
It's a Basic command tool. It's
taught at officer candidate school.
It's just not usually used
this literally in the field.
Graph 4: Execution.
We will assault the Cylon launch
site from the northwest, using...
Oh, come on!
This is absurd.
What, we're taking on the Cylon
Army, are we? Us? Look at us.
What, with two rifles
and a canteen?
Have you lost your mind...
That's enough, Doctor.
Is it? Look, no disrespect, but
why are we always going uphill?
Does anyone else think that
his plan is frakking nuts?
I'll tell you what's fair, this is
fair. We'll have a show of hands.
No! Absolutely not! Now everybody
who thinks it's unfair...
This is not a democracy.
Well, it's not...
The El-tee's in charge.
No ifs, no ands, no buts.
He say we go, we go!
There's no questions. We've
already lost two men, Chief!
How many more people
are we gonna lose?
You need to sit down
and shut up right now.
Nobody tells me to shut up.
I am the Vice President...
You need to sit down
and shut up, right now.
Your briefing, El-tee.
Thank you, Chief.
Graph 4: We will approach the Cylon
launch site from the northwest...
using natural ground cover
to mask our approach.
Our objective is the command
and control console.
Once we reach this position...
Cally, you're gonna
flank out to the left...
making a feint on
the Cylon position...
hopefully drawing their fire
long enough for me and Seelix...
to flank out to the right
and get a shot at the console.
Tyrol, you and the Vice President
will stay at position one...
provide covering fire
for both flanking maneuvers.
I have been given the opportunity
to perceive from the scriptures...
In peace I believe...
This is ridiculous.
Look.
She obviously needs her medication. I keep
trying to tell anyone that'll listen...
It sounds like she's talking about
the scrolls of the Prophet Pythia.
I suppose.
Pythia foretold
the rise of a leader.
A leader who would lead
all humanity to salvation.
So say the gods.
You seem to know
a lot about the scriptures.
I'm from Gemenon.
We believe in the literal
truth of the scriptures.
Cpl. Venner, there's...
a drug that priests sometimes
use. It's called chamalla extract.
I guess it's happy hour.
What's happy about it?
Yeah. The old man's
still in surgery.
[Sighing]
I got a boatload of politicians and
press demanding to see Laura Roslin.
Let them.
Yeah, right.
She's crazy.
I know.
No, no, really, Saul.
She's lost it. I just went
down to the brig to see her.
You did?
She's completely nuts.
She doesn't even know
where she is anymore.
You're kidding.
You should let them see her.
The press, the Quorum,
all of them.
I mean, the little school teacher's
mind has gone bye-bye and the...
Vice President is
either missing or dead.
That leaves you in unchallenged
command of this ship and this fleet.
Just until the old man
gets back on his feet.
Well, of course.
(Apollo) Galactica, Apollo. We
are preparing to jump to Kobol.
Roger that, Apollo. You are
cleared to jump. Good hunting.
Thank you, Galactica.
Let's go find our people.
Okay, cock the rifle, click
the safety, open the scope.
Cock the rifle, click the
safety, open the scope.
Cock the rifle...
(No. 6) One of you will
turn against the others.
During the mission?
Yes.
One of us will betray the others? Yes.
During the attack?
Yes.
But if the attack fails?
You'll die.
Not me. I am God's instrument.
God turned his back on Kobol.
Turned his back on man and
the false gods he worshipped.
What happens on Kobol
is not his will.
(Crashdown)
Saddle up.
It's time to junk
some toasters.
[Phone ringing]
XO. (Dualla) Combat. Dualla here, sir.
The Quorum is demanding
to see the former President.
They're being pretty adamant, and
they're giving the sentries a hard time.
Well, maybe we should tell them to shove
their demand up their collective asses.
How about that?
Yes, sir. I need
instructions for the sentries.
They're asking
how to respond.
Tell them that they are
going to get to see...
what has become of their precious
President. You tell them that.
I got a transponder signal.
Definitely Colonial.
Trying to establish a lock.
Got it.
Northern hemisphere. Looks
like mountainous terrain.
There's a valley.
Take us out of orbit.
Signal Raptor 2
to form up on us.
There they are, all three of them,
right where they're supposed to be.
All right, people.
This is it. We're going in.
Cally, you move up
the tree line to point alpha.
Whoa, El-tee. There's five
Cylons at the launcher.
What?
Something's wrong, isn't it?
Something's wrong with the plan?
Quiet down,
there's nothing wrong.
There's just a couple Cylons
that we didn't account for.
That makes for seven Cylons,
five here and two up at the dish.
Are you absolutely certain
about the two guards at the dish?
I know what I saw.
Maybe there are only five Cylons.
They just changed their deployment.
They brought the two that were
guarding the dish down here.
Now the dish
is unprotected.
God, Chief, that dish is,
like, almost a klick away.
So what? It's unprotected.
We can go take it out.
We don't have to take on
the whole Cylon army.
[Rumbling]
What the hell was that?
Sonic booms.
Spacecraft entering
the upper atmosphere.
It's the SAR mission. They're
here. They're right up there, Chief.
We got to go. There's
no time for discussion.
All right, everyone up,
move out. It's game time.
We're taking out these toasters
before they kill any more of us.
[Breathing heavily]
Cally, I said move.
I can't.
What? That's an order.
She doesn't have to. We could
just go take out the dish!
Cally, you have to move.
Cally, this is not a joke. Go!
This is not a game, Cally, go!
We have people counting on us.
They're up there, Cally.
Move!
Listen to me, we still have time to
double back and take out the dish.
Shut up for a second, Cally. Cally.
Specialist, you have your orders.
I need you to go up there
and create a distraction, now!
Move! Move!
El-tee.
There were only supposed to be
three Cylons and now there are five.
How are we supposed
to take on five Cylons?
Frak orders,
frak court martial!
Our people are up there,
we have to save them.
We don't have any time.
Move! I can't do it.
Cally! Move!
No!
Chief!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
Put it down. Put it down.
You are going out there,
Cally.
You're going out there, or I'm going to
blow your brains out. Right here, right now.
Put it down. Hey, El-tee,
easy. Take it easy.
I'm gonna count to three.
This is crazy, this is crazy!
One.
Put it down. Right now.
(Seelix)
Oh, my gods!
Listen to me!
Drop your weapon!
Two.
[Cally sobbing]
Three.
[Gun firing]
[Cally panting]
[Cally sobs]
[Guns firing]
(Tyrol)
Fall back! Fall back!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on, Doc! Let's go!
Now you're a man.
ETA?
Five minutes.
[Groaning]
(Seelix)
Cally! Oh, Cally!
[Guns firing]
[Sobbing]
[Guns continue firing]
[Screaming]
Doc! Give me the launcher! Give
me the launcher, Doc! Come on!
(Tyrol)
Cover me!
[Beeping]
Missiles!
There's a battery down there!
Evasive! Break!
Break! Break!
(Racetrack)
Break formation.
No lock! No lock!
They're not locking on us!
[Airplanes rumbling]
[Guns firing]
[Screaming]
(Cally)
Chief!
[Firing]
Stay there! Stay there!
Chief! Chief!
[Tyrol screaming]
You're welcome.
[People chattering]
Viewing time at the zoo.
Glad to see you hold the
President in such high esteem.
Your day's gonna come,
laughing boy. Let's go.
(Porter)
What is she saying?
(Bagot) I don't know.
She's not saying anything.
I don't know what to do.
I feel like she's...
All right, the show's over.
Let's give her some privacy.
Everybody out. Let's go
back to the Ward Room...
and we'll talk about the business
of how we proceed from here.
Thank you all for coming. I have
a statement I'd like to make.
The attempted military coup against
the lawful government of the Colonies...
is illegal, ill-advised,
and clearly doomed to failure.
I have not resigned the presidency,
and I will fight this action...
with everything
at my command.
She's crazy.
She's nuts.
She thinks she's a prophet
or some such nonsense.
Go ahead and ask her.
Ask her, she'll tell you.
Just listen to her. What was
it? The Arrow of Apollo...
will open the tomb of Artemis,
or some such nonsense.
Everything I have done
is consistent, logical.
We have found Kobol. We have
found the city of the gods.
And when we retrieve the Arrow,
we will open the tomb of Athena...
and we will find
the road to Earth.
Madam President, have you
read the scrolls of Pythia?
Carefully and many times,
and I humbly believe that...
I am fulfilling
the role of the leader.
Okay, enough of this nonsense.
Everybody out.
I don't think so.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute!
Sarah, you represent Gemenon,
you know more about the scrolls...
and the scriptures than anybody
else here. Why don't you speak up?
The scrolls tell us that a dying
leader will lead us to salvation.
She's not dying,
she's crazy.
I am dying.
I have terminal breast cancer. Dr.
Cottle will verify the diagnosis.
I have a few months to live.
And in that time, I will
lead the people to salvation.
It is my sole purpose.
Praise be to the gods.
Here is our salvation.
Sergeant of the Guard!
(Sergeant) Yes, sir.
Remove these people from the brig
and escort them back to their shuttle.
[All chattering]
Thank you, Corporal.
Thank the gods.
[Sighing]
It's a hell
of a butcher's bill, Chief.
How did Crashdown die?
Leading the charge.
He gave his life in the finest
tradition of the service.
Yeah.
He was a hero to the end.
[Sighing]
I'm so proud of you, Gaius.
Why?
Because I've taken a life?
It makes you human.
Is it...
not conscious thought...
not poetry, or art,
or music, literature.
Murder.
Murder is my heritage.
Is that the lesson I'm supposed
to pass on to our child?
Lt'll be all right, Gaius.
Hey, Doctor, let's go!
Doctor, come on! We got to go!
I'll be your conscience.
(Apollo) Come on, Doctor!
We got to get out of here!
He'll live.
When will he wake up?
Knowing him, when he damn
well wants to, probably.
I really frakked things
up for you, Bill.
The events which took place aboard
Colonial One are unfortunate.
Laura Roslin's actions in
suborning mutiny and sedition...
among the military
could not be tolerated.
Therefore, Commander Adama
was left with no choice...
other than to
remove her from office.
Miss Roslin is now resting
comfortably aboard this ship...
where she will remain until such
time as the Commander deems otherwise.
[All chattering]
As it appears obvious
that the government...
cannot function under
the current circumstances...
I have decided to dissolve
the Quorum of Twelve...
and as of this moment,
I have declared martial law.
[Reporters clamoring]
- Get those people the hell
off my ship.  -Yes, sir.