(male narrator) Previously
on Battlestar Galactica.
The refinery captain
is still not cooperating.
And now, seven other container ships
are refusing to release their supplies.
Frak this!
I'm sending in the marines.
Tell them to get over there
and bring back the supplies.
People, step back, all right?
We're just here
for the supplies. All right?
Stay out of our way,
and no one gets hurt.
[Gun firing]
[Grunts]
Cease fire! Cease fire!
You shot people
for throwing coffee.
The crowd was out of control.
Somebody took a shot.
I don't know who it was.
Then all hell broke loose.
It was an accident.
What do you want from me,
Helo? She's a Cylon.
[Gun firing]
I'm not going to let you
kill her. Okay?
She's carrying my child.
I'm okay, really.
Yeah.
It's just, I don't want
a baby born in a cell.
People, just step back. Stay back,
all right? We just need some supplies.
Get them back.
[Gun firing]
Cease fire! Cease fire!
[People clamoring]
Medic.
We need a medic in here, now.
Dad!
Oh, my gods! Oh, my gods!
(D'Anna) This recently
discovered footage...
from what's become known
as the Gideon Massacre...
appears to show Galactica's
marines firing indiscriminately...
into a crowd of
unarmed civilians.
Four dead, 12 wounded.
And yet, as of today, not a
single charge has been filed...
against any of the marines involved,
nor their commanding officers.
This is D'Anna Biers,
reporting.
(D'Anna) That's gonna
blow this thing wide open.
We need some stock footage
of raging marines.
We can intercut that with
the eyewitness statements.
[Door opening]
You've no right
to come in here like this.
Ma'am,
you're to come with us.
What, am I under arrest?
No, ma'am.
And what if I refuse to go?
Hello, Miss Biers.
It's nice to see you.
Welcome to Colonial One.
Madam President,
it's an honor.
Cmdr. Adama. Where did you get the tape?
From an anonymous patriot.
So, is this a social call or are
we on the verge of another coup?
Funny.
Just something
to break the ice.
I take it I'm here because you are unhappy
with my story on the Gideon Massacre?
What happened aboard
the Gideon was a tragedy.
But it was not a massacre.
But the tape shows your men firing
into a crowd of defenseless civilians.
My marines tell
a different story.
Not to me.
I've submitted a dozen
interview requests, all denied.
Well,
that's about to change.
You've been lobbying to do a
story on the Galactica for months.
Cmdr. Adama has agreed to give you
unlimited access to his crew and his ship.
That's right.
Unlimited access.
All access won't buy you
a propaganda piece.
We don't want one.
Miss Biers,
this tape of yours...
has put fuel on a fire
that was about to die.
People are angry, they are
distrustful of the military.
Yeah, with good reason,
ma'am.
In some cases,
with good reason.
But I want to show the people what life
aboard the Galactica is really like.
I want to put a human face on
the officers and the crew...
who protect us against Cylons
and guard our freedoms every day.
You might not like that face
when you see it.
What would that be?
All we really want
is a balanced story.
Show us what the men and women
of Galactica are really like.
That's it?
That's it.
And I need you to do it now
before we tear each other apart.
The CAG had better start
cracking some heads.
Half our supply runs
are behind schedule.
[Phone ringing]
Combat, Dualla.
Colonel, it's your wife.
Something's wrong.
Colonel.
Ellen, are you okay?
Oh, Saul, gods.
Oh, I'm so scared.
(Tigh) "From the
darkness, you must fall."
What does it mean?
Racetrack,
where did you get these?
Sorry, sir, they were
left over from a civilian run.
I've been meaning
to throw them out.
No.
(Adama) Put them in a safe
place. Hold on to them.
Yes, sir.
You filming this?
(D'Anna) We've been
rolling since Colonial One.
The President did say, "Total
access." You'll have that.
But you start shooting anything that
compromises the safety of the ship...
and it will be cut.
(Dualla) That hiss you hear
is an oxygen recirc unit.
We have about a dozen CO2
scrubbers aboard Galactica.
They all work
24 hours a day.
Get a close-up of that,
would you, Bill? Yeah, sure.
We just finished
a 15-hour rotation.
Yeah, well,
you better get used to it.
We may be short on pilots till the
rest of the fleet pulls the stick...
out of its collective fat ass.
[Laughing]
More fall-out from
Tigh's moment of glory?
You heard about
his death threat?
Couldn't have happened
to a nicer guy.
[Sighs]
I just can't believe that I haven't
been called in for questioning yet.
Oh, you were top of the list.
But don't worry. I told Tigh that
you wouldn't know Caprican poetry...
if it was hot-soldered
across your helmet.
"From the darkness,
you must fall...
"failed and weak,
to darkness all."
Kataris. Not one of his best.
Can I be a suspect again?
Please.
(Dualla) Ship's galley
is next on the itinerary.
Our vegetable stores and canned
goods are kept in titanium lockers...
to ensure maximum freshness.
I didn't come all this way to
interview the soup of the day.
[Both laughing]
(Dualla)
Ma'am.
There comes
Tweedledum and Tweedledee.
Guys,
people are sleeping.
(man #1) Keep it down. (Kat) Sorry.
(man #2)
Lighten up, Palladino.
Hey, is that on?
Are you recording?
Hi, Mom! Miss you, Mommy.
This is for my buddies
on Freighter 2-12!
Yeah, that's for you!
Kat!
Kat, you want to tell me what
the hell you think you're doing?
I was just saying hi to some
of my buddies on the fleet, sir.
Right.
So you were literally
talking out of your ass.
Kind of.
Go on, get dressed.
Yes, sir.
Castanza, get the hell
out of here.
It's the last time you come into
senior officers' quarters. Go. Move.
So, you must be the reporter
we were expecting.
Well, you didn't have to
dress for me.
D'Anna Biers,
Fleet News Service.
Capt. Lee Adama, Commander of the
Air Group, that's pronounced "CAG."
And I suggest you find yourselves
an exit as soon as possible...
and that's pronounced, "ASAP."
I think we've seen
all we need to see here.
Whose brilliant idea was that?
How did your family respond?
My Dad went crazy
when I enlisted.
He thought the military
was a joke.
A refuge for emotional
cripples and patriotic fools.
But you signed up anyway.
I guess I just wanted to
believe in something.
You think it'll give it
more memory?
Yeah, it seems pretty simple.
Maybe just a basic adjustment.
It's a pretty good piece.
Yeah, it's kind of old.
(D'Anna)
Maybe I need a new one.
What the hell is going on?
I don't know.
You don't know.
I'm the Vice President.
She's supposed to be
interviewing me, isn't she?
Well, of course she should. Your
title alone commands respect.
Of course it does. It's a
rare commodity around here.
I mean,
I'm the Vice President.
I'm not going beg.
I'll tell you that much.
(Dualla)
Miss Biers, our next stop...
Now, Gaius,
you may have to beg.
You'll do whatever's necessary
to protect our child.
Politics may not be your strong
suit, but it serves us in the moment.
Trust me.
This one can help us.
Mr. Vice President?
Hello.
Hi. D'Anna Biers,
Fleet News Service.
Oh, you're the reporter.
That's right. Cmdr. Adama said the
News Service might be joining us.
I suppose you're...
well, very busy doing a lot
of interviews, I would imagine.
Well, I would love
to speak to you.
If you've got a second,
we can do it now.
No. I'm afraid not.
I am very busy.
Really, really busy, at
the moment. Snowed under.
But if you get in touch with one of my
aides, there might be a small window tomorrow.
I'm not promising anything,
honestly.
But, I might be able to
give you an interview then...
if that's what
you would like.
Good. Good. Well, you just... carry on.
What a strange little man.
(D'Anna)
Capt. Adama...
I hardly recognized you
with your clothes on.
Look, I'm sure you thought
it was clever...
busting into the pilot's duty locker,
but the area's off-limits for a reason.
It's the one place where my
people can unwind, be themselves.
You seem to think that your pilots
deserve special consideration.
Actually, I do.
Like everyone else...
my pilots have lost their
families, their friends...
everyone they ever
cared about.
But on top of that, they are asked
to put their lives on the line...
every single day...
for a fleet that seems more
interested in what they do wrong...
than in what they do right.
They're not asking for your pity, but
they damn well deserve your respect.
[Men chattering]
Gods, Chief, we've already
run this up twice.
Yeah, something doesn't
feel right. What?
Something doesn't feel right.
Well, hurry up.
[Grunts]
That's it.
Great.
Oh, that's fantastic.
That's just great.
I knew it.
How did I miss that?
Maybe if your knuckledraggers
spent more time on maintenance...
and less time
frakking around...
This knuckledragger
just saved your ass, sir.
Why don't you say that
a little louder, Chief?
I don't think
the camera heard you.
You know what? Frak the
camera. You've been riding my...
Don't even try defending...
... for no frakking reason!
Knock it off!
Chief, fix the ship.
Yeah, fix the...
Hey!
What?
Hey, enough!
Chief, fix your ship. You
get the hell out of here, now.
Get the camera out of my face.
[Thudding]
She has been pissing me off all
week. What the hell's going on?
I'm taking her off rotation until
she gets her head rewired. I mean...
Can't do it.
We need the pilots.
Besides, if I scratched everyone
who popped off at the Chief...
the cooks would be flying
the missions. Son of a bitch.
Did you get all that?
You happy? Come on.
Walk away.
We were never trained
for crowd control.
First order of business when under
attack is defend yourself and your squad.
But these were civilians.
I have 10 stitches that say
we were under attack.
Truth is, it was a command frak-up the
moment Tigh put us on that supply ship.
I'm not surprised someone's trying
to take out that drunk son of a bitch.
All right. Private. Belay that.
Col. Tigh's been threatened?
No. This interview's over.
Shut that off.
Commander.
Watch your step, please.
Okay, come on.
Sitrep.
Fleet's quiet, no enemy
contact for the last 10 days.
No Cylon contact, anyway.
Well, they have their
job to do. We have ours.
Did you hear about
the meeting on Cloud Nine?
Reps flying in from every
vessel in the fleet...
for a king-size bitch session?
Yeah, I've heard.
Well, they sent us an
invitation to send a delegation.
You're it.
Do you mind? (D'Anna) No, no. Go ahead.
We're in.
I'm not exactly the most popular
guy in the fleet right now.
Well, it'll be good then, to let your
cutters know that you're not afraid of them.
That what you think?
I've been hiding?
What the hell is
going on here, Bill?
You've been doing this too long. We
were worried about ulterior motives.
You're going because you're not
afraid and people should see that.
Plus, it'll also give people a
chance to vent their feelings...
instead of seething
in private.
And finally,
I think you need a little R&R.
So consider this
mandatory shore leave.
Take a swim. Get some sleep.
Sir.
And...
stay away from the bar.
Three. There's three.
So, you got lots.
(Starbuck) Good luck, Colonel.
Have fun on Cloud Nine.
You bet.
[Hissing]
Initiating pre-flight.
What's going on? Abort
launch! Everybody out, now!
[Alarm blaring]
Everybody back.
Get back, now.
What's going on?
The main bus is totaled. Looks
like somebody took a hammer to it.
If this had blown in transit, the
cabin would have vented to space.
Someone's trying to kill you,
Saul. Comes with the stripes.
It's because of
that damned Gideon incident.
Ellen, we don't know that.
Of course we do.
D'Anna Biers left
two messages already.
She's giving you the chance
to tell your side.
I don't have to explain
myself, especially to her.
Roslin wants to
placate the fleet...
put the great Bill Adama
back on his pedestal.
The fastest way to do that
is by hanging you out to dry.
Why do you think Adama wanted
to send you to Cloud Nine?
The Gideon happened
on my watch.
Yes.
But you didn't order
those jar-heads to open fire.
[Sighing]
This is so like you, Saul.
Always the proud soldier, taking
the heat because it's honorable.
When are you going to realize
we're all alone out here?
[Sighing]
(D'Anna) Are you afraid
when you go into combat?
First thing they tell you is
to assume you're already dead.
Well,
that sounds ghoulish.
Yeah, maybe.
But dead men don't get scared
or freeze up under fire.
Me, I'm just worried that hell's
going to be a lonely place...
and I'm gonna fill it up with
every toaster son of a bitch I find.
What's been
the hardest for you?
They try to turn off the human part of
you because that's what'll get you killed.
But when you're out in the
field, it's not that easy.
Nothing's that easy.
(guard)
You got five minutes.
Sharon? It's me.
Sharon!
Give me your light. What the
hell are you talking about?
Give me your light, now.
Something's wrong.
Oh, gods. Call Dr. Cottle.
(Helo)
Now!
[Crying]
(D'Anna) Does that help
you cope with the stress?
Not really.
Look, all that I ever wanted was
to be an officer on a Battlestar.
Okay, I trained my whole life, trained
harder than anyone in my unit...
basically, I put my life on hold
until I was assigned to Galactica.
Then the Cylons hit and I realized
that this is all that I know.
Tech manuals, commands,
and tactics.
You know, I'm not saying
that I'm unhappy.
Just wondering if
there's something more.
And what have you
discovered?
I hate cigarettes.
[Coughs]
Ambrosia's good with a chaser.
And if you have
enough ambrosia...
they don't really
hurt that much.
There you go. We'll make
this as painless as possible.
Drink?
Is this an interview
or a cocktail party?
Are you kidding? This is
how we keep it painless.
Just like to keep it casual,
that's all.
Please.
Cheers, Colonel.
Cheers.
Before we begin...
I had heard rumors that,
that you had death threats...
leveled against you.
Is that right?
This is a military vessel. We
have rumors for every occasion.
Was it hard for you to take over your
friend's command when he was shot?
I didn't take anything. Command
fell to me and I did my duty.
But you were in full command of
Galactica for more than a week...
and in that time there were a number
of controversial actions taken.
You're talking about
the Gideon.
I made a military decision.
Given the same circumstances,
I'd do it again.
So you have no regrets,
whatsoever?
You're trying to set me up!
Colonel, why do you think there
was no official investigation...
into the Gideon Massacre?
Please come.
Get out of my face!
Did you get that?
Got it.
Someone's a mean drunk.
Great. I could use
a sparring partner.
Sorry. I didn't bring
my gloves. Too bad.
Capt. Adama said that I could
ask you about the new pilots.
Yeah, well, Capt. Adama
likes to push my buttons.
[Panting]
So, what do you look
for in a new recruit?
[Panting]
Coordination.
Good reflexes.
Total commitment.
[Grunts]
Most of all, someone crazy
enough to follow me into combat.
(D'Anna)
Colonel, why do you think...
there was no
official investigation...
into the Gideon massacre?
Please come.
Get out of my face.
I want to apologize for Col. Tigh's
behavior. It was uncalled for.
Seems like a lot of people
have been...
apologizing for him
over the years, Commander.
So level with me.
Why is Col. Tigh not being
charged in the Gideon incident?
We're at war
against an enemy...
with a vastly superior force.
I will not sacrifice the few people we
have left on the altar of public outrage.
So four civilians are dead...
and Tigh and the shooters
take a walk.
Nobody takes a walk.
We all gotta live with it.
(Kelly) Viper
five-niner-one Galactica...
you are cleared
into the break.
Portside landing bay
hands-on approach.
Checkers are green.
Call the ball.
(Kat)
Roger ball.
Wait a second, guys. Damn it!
Speed two-zero-five.
Keep your power up, Kat, you're
dropping below glideslope.
Controls are messed up.
Come on, come on, come on.
[Panting]
Still too low. Wave off, Kat.
Wave off!
What the hell is going on?
That is her third wave-off.
When we make a contact...
the squadron's got seconds
to put it all together.
Pre-flight, weapons check,
communications...
one mistake,
we're a smear in the cockpit.
I don't understand,
is she trying to...
Shut the frak up. Kat.
We're gonna do this, okay?
Leave the throttle alone down the middle,
then chop it at the come-on in close...
and feel for the deck. (Kat)
The controls are messed up.
I can't feel it.
I can't do it.
Kat, we did this all through training, okay?
You're gonna stick this, just like before.
No.
Viper five-niner-one Galactica, you are
cleared into the break. Call the ball.
Too low, five-niner-one.
Wave off!
No, she's putting down!
Kat, full throttle now.
I can't feel it.
When you came back
after a successful run...
Let me tell you, it is better
than a great meal.
Better than hitting a jackpot.
It's better than sex.
(Kat)
I can't do it.
[Alarm blaring]
She missed the trap.
Damage control, medics,
report to portside hangar bay.
(woman on PA system)
Medics to portside hangar bay.
What the hell happened?
Kat's made the trap 100 times.
Yeah, I guess 101
was a real bitch, huh?
(Kat)
Let go of me. Let me go.
Hey.
Kat!
It's Starbuck.
You're okay. You're home!
Home? Home is dead. We gotta get
out of here, they're gonna kill us!
What are these, stims?
Please don't do this.
[Kat screaming]
(Kat)
Let go.
No! Let go!
Let go off me!
We're gonna die!
(Starbuck) Get my pilot to sick bay now.
Stims. By the look of it, she's
been taking them by the handful.
Hey.
(Sharon) Don't you dare touch
me. (Cottle) Listen to me.
What are you doing? Listen to
me. I'm trying to save your baby.
Hold her still! (guard)
This is a restricted area.
(guard)
Commander, she's over here.
Cmdr. Adama, that woman looks
just like the late Lt. Valerii.
The tape, please.
Why would Galactica be
harboring a Cylon? The tape.
Did the baby survive?
You understand that even a hint
of this could be devastating...
to the morale in the fleet. You
are the master of understatement.
You know, after the Gideon, this could
turn the entire fleet against you.
Then the real question is,
whether or not it matters to you.
You know, I am sick to death of people
like you questioning my patriotism.
We all want
this fleet to survive.
I think you're
doing very well.
Very well,
under the circumstances.
I understand this has been
a difficult job for you.
I mean, I hear that your
reports haven't exactly...
ingratiated you with
the Commander, have they?
[Scoffs] Or the rest of
the crew, for that matter.
Still, luckily, as a member
of the civilian government...
I'm here to assure you that
I have no such reservations.
I think most of the crew
understands I'm just doing my job.
As are we all. All just
doing our jobs, aren't we?
I'm just doing my job.
You're just doing your job.
Okay.
Cut to the chase, Gaius.
Tell her why you deserve
to lead this fleet.
As I myself discovered,
when I was stranded...
stranded on Kobol...
I found that the stress
of survival revealed...
leadership qualities that previously
I didn't even know that I possessed.
Really.
Yeah?
I understand your party
took several casualties.
Yes.
That was very unfortunate.
They were heroes,
every one...
You know what, I'm ready.
Shall we shoot this one?
[Alarm blaring]
Oh, it's probably just a false
alarm. Ignore it. You're okay.
Bill, you take the hangar deck.
I'm gonna take the CIC. Go.
Please. You're as safe
as houses down here. Really.
(man on PA system) Incoming Cylon
Raiders. This is not a drill. Repeat.
That's showbiz.
What have we got?
Two Raiders, closing fast.
[Alarm blaring]
Sir, the Cylon Raiders
are on CBDR with Galactica.
Speed
two-two-point-seven-niner.
Dualla, what's CBDR?
Constant bearing, decreasing
range. A collision course.
(Tigh)
Where the hell's the CAP?
(Dualla)
Other side of the fleet, sir.
Scramble the alert fighters. Set
Condition 1 throughout the entire fleet.
Have them spool up their FTLs,
just in case.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Move. Move.
(Hotdog) Clear this deck.
Get this out of here.
What's the sitrep?
Two bandits, coming hard.
Just keep your eyes open
and follow us.
All right, let's go. Let's get the birds
in the hole. Let's go move them out.
Get this flyer out of here.
Let's go.
Move them fools out of here.
First team in the tubes.
Dee.
Pilots on speaker.
(D'Anna) Did you ever come
to terms with your dad?
I wouldn't let him. The last
time we talked, it got...
heated.
I told him I never
wanted to see him again.
Three weeks later,
the Cylons attacked.
Okay, so I'm new at this.
Should I be scared?
I am.
All right, people, that's it. Last
bird's away, let's clear the nest.
Get this deck ready
for recovery.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Move. Move.
Sir, Alert Vipers are away.
Gun Control reports
weapons manned and ready.
(Apollo)
Apollo, wireless check.
(Starbuck)
Starbuck, I'm hearing you.
(Hotdog) Hotdog
one-four-one, loud and clear.
(Grayshirt)
Grayshirt, loud and clear.
(Kingston)
Kingston, you're good.
Apollo. Tally two Cylon
Raiders, close formation.
This is Starbuck. Roger that.
Roger formation.
(Apollo)
Prepare engage. Weapons hot.
Targets in view. Repeat. Targets
in view. Locked six-four-two-one.
Copy that.
Engaging Cylon Raiders.
(Starbuck) They're breaking
formation. Hotdog, stick with me.
(Hotdog) Roger that. Come on, you...
(Hotdog) I've got no joy, I lost visual!
They're throwing me
right on my stick.
Come on, Starbuck.
Hotdog, Raider's on your left
eight. I'm on him. I got him.
Yeah! Splash one!
Targeting second Raider.
(Kingston) Kingston,
Bandit's taking off.
Take evasive action.
(Apollo) I've got him,
Kingston, come on. Come to papa.
Damn it, take the shot.
(Apollo) That's a kill. Yes.
Outstanding.
Dradis shows clear, Commander.
This is the Commander.
Cylon Raiders have been intercepted
and destroyed. Good work, people.
(Starbuck)
Roger that, Galactica.
Let's head back
to the bird farm.
Secure from Action Stations.
Set Condition 3.
Mr. Gaeta, you have the deck.
Yes, sir.
Set Condition 3
throughout the ship.
Repeat. Set Condition 3.
Does this ever get
any easier? No, ma'am.
It gets harder.
Thank you.
Was 15 degrees?
Sixteen.
So, how'd it go out there?
Well, we didn't lose anyone.
That's a good day.
Ellen?
I'm not sure I've found
a story in all this yet.
Go back a bit.
Yeah. There.
I know that book.
That's by Kataris.
What's wrong, Colonel?
Need a drink?
[Ellen gagging]
[Gags]
You can go to hell.
I've been there.
It was called Gideon.
I can't eat. I can't sleep.
I see their faces.
Those weren't Cylons we
attacked, those were real people.
They looked like my dad.
They looked like
my little brother.
This isn't gonna
change anything.
At least the people on the
Gideon will have their justice.
If that's what this is about,
then do it. I will. I'll do it.
Somebody has to pay for
what happened on that ship.
I was in command, I sent
you there, it's my fault.
Come on, son.
Do it.
Gideon was an accident.
This is a choice.
Colonel.
We're all right here.
Let's go, Lieutenant.
[Ellen crying]
Would you get out
of my face?
What made you do it, Kat?
I was tired.
[Sighs]
Haven't gotten any sleep.
I felt like I was losing my edge.
I don't know what else to do.
Couldn't you
talk to someone?
Who am I gonna talk to?
We're all in the same hole.
Okay, there are no
replacements coming up.
There's no down time.
This is it.
So I started taking stims.
(D'Anna) You made a mistake. It happens.
(Kat) Yeah, except now
my flight's a pilot short.
Those guys,
they're just as tired...
and they're just as messed up as I was,
but they're still laying it on the line.
I've worked my ass off
defending this fleet.
I've been frustrated.
I've been angry.
I've been everything that
you can possibly think of.
But this is the first time
that I've felt ashamed.
[Sighing]
I've seen enough.
Kill it.
Look. I understand this might
be hard for you to watch...
It's a hatchet job. The
fleet already thinks we're...
a bunch of trigger-happy
assassins, this just confirms it.
You show us with our pants
down and our asses hanging out.
Don't you have
anything to say?
I think it's great.
I think she did exactly
what we asked her to do.
She put a human face on the
guardians of the fleet. Warts and all.
I'm proud of it.
You can show it
to the entire fleet.
Doesn't get better
than that.
I'd like to see
the end.
So would I.
Go ahead. Yeah.
(D'Anna) I came to
Galactica to tell a story.
In all honesty, I thought I knew what that
story was, before I ever set foot there.
How an arrogant military let their
egos get in the way of doing their jobs.
Safeguarding the lives
of the civilian population.
But I found out that the truth
was more complex than that.
These people aren't Cylons.
They're not robots blindly following
orders and polishing their boots.
They're people.
Deeply flawed, yes.
But deeply human, too.
And maybe that's saying
the same thing.
What struck me most
is that, despite it all...
the hardships, the stress, the
ever-present danger of being killed.
Despite all that,
they never give up.
They never lie down on the road
and let the truck run them over.
They wake up in the morning, put
on their uniforms and do their jobs.
Everyday. No pay. No rest.
No hope of ever laying down the burden
and letting someone else do the job.
There are no
relief troops coming.
No Colonial fleet training
new recruits every day.
The people
on Galactica are it.
They are the thin line of blue
that separates us from the Cylons.
Lt. Gaeta told me
a remarkable statistic.
Not a single member of Galactica's
crew has asked to resign. Not one.
Think about that.
If you wore the uniform,
wouldn't you want to quit?
To step aside and say, "Enough. Let
someone else protect the fleet. "
I know I would.
But then,
I don't wear a uniform.
Most of us don't,
and most of us never will.
The story of Galactica isn't that
people make bad decisions under pressure.
It's that those mistakes
are the exception.
Most of the time,
the men and women...
serving under Cmdr. Adama
get it right.
The proof is that
our fleet survives.
And with Galactica
at our side, we will endure.
This is D' Anna Biers.
Fleet News Service.
That was shown across
their entire fleet.
Their resilience
is remarkable.
Play the footage
that was cut.
(Sharon) What are you doing? Stop it.
(Cottle) I'm trying to save your baby.
(guard)
This is a restricted area!
(Sharon)
Get off of me.
I'm still alive.
She's still alive!
I told you.
That's incredible.
And the baby?
(D'Anna)
It was saved.
We lost two Raiders relaying
the images back to the fleet...
but, I think
the sacrifice was worth it.
(Doral) We must proceed with caution.
The child's life must be
protected at all costs.
Yeah.
It truly is a miracle
from God.