(male narrator) Previously
on Battlestar Galactica.
(Elosha)
This planet is Kobol.
The birthplace of mankind.
Organize a ground survey team.
Three Raptors.
(Karma) They're everywhere!
Get us out of here!
(Tyrol)
Pull it up!
(Crashdown)
Get down!
(Apollo) Galactica. Apollo.
Starbuck just jumped away.
(Roslin)
If you go back to Caprica...
and bring me the arrow, it
will show us the way to Earth.
[Groaning]
Starbuck?
(Adama) I'm terminating
your presidency...
as of this moment.
(Tigh) I am placing you
under arrest, Madam President.
This is mutiny. You know that.
(No. 6)
Come.
See the face of the shape
of things to come.
Isn't she beautiful, Gaius?
I'm not a Cylon.
This isn't happening.
(Cylon Boomer) You can't
fight destiny, Sharon.
It catches up with you.
No matter what you do.
[Inaudible]
[Crew chattering]
(man)
Make a hole!
(Apollo) Where are the
medics? Where's Doc Cottle?
(Ishay) Off-ship, on
rounds in the fleet, sir.
Stand clear!
(Fischer) Pressure. Sgt.
Fischer reporting, sir.
(man) You got it?
(Fischer) Pressure! Yeah.
It's lodged too far.
I'm calling for him.
(Fischer) He's gotta be drugged.
(man) He's gotta be aggressive.
What's the status on the
bleeding? (Fischer) Let's go.
(man) Are we supposed
to do that here, though?
(Fischer) No, we're gonna
get him into med bay...
as soon as possible.
I'm your new shipmate.
Bill Adama.
Saul Tigh.
We've got tension pneumo. I'm gonna
stick him and release the pressure.
(Fischer)
He's gonna be okay.
What's going on?
What happened?
Sergeant of the Guards,
secure that thing in the brig.
Aye, sir. Hollis, Wenzler,
let's go! Let's go!
[Grunting]
No!
(Boomer)
No! Wait!
(Ishay)
Okay, he's breathing.
(Boomer)
I didn't do anything!
Let's get him down
to sickbay, RFN.
(Boomer)
No!
Valerii shot the old man. (Kelly) What?
(Boomer)
Three-one...
(Gaeta)
She must be a Cylon.
The Colonel's in command.
You're second.
(Ishay)
Make a hole!
(Boomer)
No!
(Fischer) Sergeant, secure Capt. Adama.
Put him in the brig!
Colonel! Col. Tigh!
(guard) Let's go!
(Apollo) I didn't do it!
He's my father!
Colonel! Colonel! (Kelly) Colonel.
Could this be a prelude
to a Cylon attack?
How would they know
where we are?
(Racetrack) Valerii
could have told them, sir.
What? How? When we were
aboard the Base Star...
she left the Raptor for a few minutes
and came back without her helmet.
She might have told the Cylons
everything, our position, defenses...
(Kelly) Colonel, the toasters
have knocked out our CO.
This has gotta be part
of a bigger plan.
I recommend we execute jump to
emergency standby coordinates.
Colonel, I've located Doc Cottle.
He's aboard the Rising Star.
[Computer beeping] (Gaeta) Dradis.
Single contact! Cylon Base
Star, bearing 487-carom-015!
Sir, we can't stay here.
[Alarm blaring]
Sir!
(Adama)
So what's your plan here?
Personally, I tend to go with
what you know...
till something
better turns up.
(Kelly)
Sir!
Dee, alert the fleet.
We are making an immediate jump
to the emergency coordinates.
Go!
Sir, Doc Cottle is still
15 minutes away.
He'll have to rejoin us
on the other side of the jump.
Sir, what about our people
on the surface of Kobol?
[Alarm continues blaring]
If they're still alive,
they'll have to wait.
(Gaeta)
FTL!
(Dualla)
Go.
NavCon?
Galactica to all vessels.
Prepare to make immediate FTL
jump to escape coordinates Alpha.
I say again,
escape coordinates Alpha.
Clock will start on my mark.
Mark!
[Panting]
Captain, what have they
done to you? What's going on?
My father's been shot.
What?
Someone get this frakking
thing off me, please?
I'm not authorized
to do that yet.
I'm behind the frakking bars!
Captain...
how bad is your father?
Bad.
Two bullets in the chest.
Is Dr. Cottle with him?
No. Doc Cottle's not on board.
(Dualla) Attention,
Galactica. Fleet is away.
Stand by to jump
in five, four...
three, two, one...
jump!
(Gaeta)
Jump completed.
Report.
Report!
Dradis is empty. No contacts.
No contacts?
Where's the fleet?
Dee!
Checking all channels.
No Colonial signals.
They're gone, sir.
(No. 6)
Isn't she beautiful, Gaius?
I don't think I've ever been
touched so deeply in my entire life.
You're going to make
a wonderful father.
Speaking metaphorically,
of course.
And literally.
She's our child, Gaius.
Our little girl.
What?
Do you want to hold her?
[Quavering]
Yes. Yes, of course I do.
But she's not real...
any more than...
any of this is...
real.
She's real.
She is?
She may not be with you yet,
but she will be.
Soon.
I'm having
a little difficulty.
I'm trying to understand.
I want to understand. I...
You're the mother.
And you're the father.
Am I the father?
Excuse me?
Dream.
I'm clearly having a dream.
We're moving out, sir.
Get up.
[Panting]
And if you wouldn't mind carrying
something this time, that would be great.
[Wheezing]
This is Serisone. It should
help you breathe a little easier.
[Coughing]
[Crewman Specialist Socinus
continues wheezing]
(Tyrol)
Take it easy.
You'll be up, feeling better,
in a few minutes.
Excuse me, sir.
We've got to get you up.
(Crewman Specialist
Socinus) It hurts. I know.
If you don't mind me asking,
where are we going, Crashdown?
Tree line.
We can hide...
but still see the crash site, in
case Galactica sends a rescue party.
Galactica will be sending
a rescue party.
[Rumbling]
(Crashdown)
Everybody down!
(Cally) What was that? That Cylons?
Seelix, grab the ammo. Staggered
formation, I'll take point.
Chief, you're bringing
up the rear.
Be ready to double-time
it, people! One, two, three!
El-tee, I think we should double-check
the supplies before we bug out.
Sorry, Chief,
we don't have the time.
If that's an aircraft turbine,
they're gonna be on us any moment!
El-tee, we've gotta make sure
we have everything!
We don't have the time, Chief!
Damn it.
Gods damn it.
What's going on, Saul?
Where's the fleet?
We don't know. They
jumped to another location.
You've got blood on your
pants. Why would they do that?
Every watch, we update our
emergency jump calculations...
with new star fixes...
to compensate
for inertial drift.
And then we transmit them
to the rest of the fleet.
This time, ours were updated,
but theirs weren't.
Gaeta was supposed to transmit
them to the rest of the fleet.
So it's Gaeta's fault.
The kid was overwhelmed.
He had his hands full.
If you say so. It sounds like
a pretty big screw-up to me.
I should have checked before
I gave the order to jump!
This doesn't sound like you,
Saul. You don't let people slide.
You bust their ass.
Now if Bill doesn't make it...
He'll make it.
If he doesn't, this will
be your ship. Your command.
All I'm saying is you need to
be... This is Bill Adama's ship.
This is his command.
His orders are still the
word of the gods on this ship.
Just so we're clear.
This will be Adama's command
until the day he dies.
And we are not
going to let him die.
So say we all.
(all)
As you were.
So how do we find the fleet?
If we jump back
to our original coordinates...
our Nav computers can use those star
fixes to generate a best-fit solution...
giving the fleet's
current position.
The Cylons are waiting
for us back there.
How long will it take to
calculate once we get back there?
If we shut down
all other functions...
12 hours.
There's no way we can hold off
a Cylon Base Star for 12 hours.
We have got to jump back.
We can't stay here.
Lt. Thrace won't be able to find us once
she retrieves the arrow from Caprica.
If she retrieves the arrow.
She'll retrieve the arrow.
Captain, you've got to get reinstated.
You've got to get back to CIC.
You've got to denounce me, disavow
me, do whatever you need to do.
Col. Tigh cannot relocate this
fleet on his own without your father.
Tigh's not letting me
out of here.
I put a gun to his head. He
won't forget that anytime soon.
I am so sorry that I got you
into this, Captain.
No, don't apologize.
I knew what I was doing. I...
And I didn't do it for you.
I did it for...
Well, actually, I did it
for nothing, turns out.
That's not true.
You took a stand.
And now look at us.
[Birds chirping]
(Tyrol) Watch your foot. (Seelix) Okay.
Everyone take five.
Give me the med kit.
Where's the med kit?
How you doing?
Hey, how you doing, buddy?
Good.
Just listening
to the birds.
[Birds chirping]
I'll be damned. I don't remember
the last time I heard birds.
[Coughing]
Take it easy, okay?
Damn it.
We're out of Serisone.
Tarn, get the other med kit.
What other med kit?
Don't frakking tell me. We
pulled two med kits from the ship.
I told you to keep an eye
on both of them.
I only saw the one, sir.
There were two!
I'm sorry, sir, but I don't
remember you telling me...
Well, I did!
Sir, his lungs
are filling up with fluid.
If he doesn't get more Serisone
soon, he's not gonna make it.
Okay. All right, Tarn.
You forgot the med kit, so you're
gonna have to go back and get it.
Take a rifle, three clips
of ammo, and a canteen.
What?
Move.
Cally, come here.
Watch the rear.
El-tee,
you can't send him alone.
You questioning my orders,
Chief?
No, I'm just pointing out
a flaw in your plan.
It doesn't need to be anything bigger
than that. Cally and I can go with him.
All right, fine. But would
you look out for Cally?
Cally, give me the rifle.
We three go. Leave that,
leave your backpack.
Sidearms out. Tarn,
you're bringing up the rear.
In the middle, eyes and ears.
Her consciousness is being downloaded
into another body right now.
And when she wakes up, she'll
tell them exactly where we are.
She's right.
We can't stay here.
[Sniffs]
She's right, huh?
Sharon the Cylon is right.
Let's all just listen
to Sharon the Cylon...
do whatever she says,
'cause that's a good idea.
Hey, Kara,
she helped me get this far.
Okay, I get it.
I get it, Helo.
You and I go way back,
so I get it.
All right, I remember
how you felt about her.
But that is not
the real Sharon.
That is some cheap
knock-off copy.
I'm not a copy. I'm Sharon.
I remember the first day
I met you, Starbuck.
You were puking
your guts out in the head...
because you'd eaten
bad oysters on...
Don't do that.
Hey!
I don't like it,
and I don't like you.
So the best thing you can do is
just keep your damn mouth shut.
Starbuck, put it down,
for gods' sakes.
What do you want from me,
Helo? She's a Cylon.
You've been had.
We've been had.
So what, I'm just supposed to be nice
to her because she says she's pregnant?
[Gun clicking]
Get out of the way.
No.
Karl, do not think
that I will not shoot...
I'm not gonna
let you kill her!
Okay? She's carrying my child!
My gods, men are so painfully stupid
sometimes! How do you know that?
I know, all right?
She's not lying.
They lie about everything,
Helo.
Their entire existence
is a lie.
[Both panting]
They're not human, Helo.
They're machines.
You can't have a baby
with a machine!
I don't know what to tell
you, okay? But I believe her.
It's hard to describe. We've
been together a long time.
I mean, I know what she is,
but she is not like the others.
She is not.
[Spacecraft engine starting]
No, no, no, no, no!
Bitch took my ride.
[Panting]
(crew member)
Yeah, go ahead.
How's he doing?
Well, the bullets
tore up his spleen.
His blood pressure
is way down.
Somebody needs to get in there and
stop the bleeding or we'll lose him.
[ECG machine beeping]
(Adama)
So what's your plan?
(Tigh)
Don't really have one.
I'm getting back
in the cockpit.
into my fleet.
(Adama) I want you
to come with me, Saul.
You really believe that
we can get back in the fleet?
Yeah, I do.
(Adama)
How long until
Doc Cottle's aboard?
I don't know.
It's gonna be a while.
He doesn't have
much time, sir.
You're gonna have
to go in yourself.
Me? I'm just a medic.
Today, you're a doctor.
[Knocking on door]
Colonel.
(Tigh)
Open the cell.
[Cell door opening]
How's the Commander?
You've bungled the job,
if that's what you're asking.
Then he's alive.
Thank the gods.
[Groaning]
How many of our pilots
were Cylons?
I don't know.
Who gave the order
to shoot the old man?
No one.
Just get it over with,
you frakking coward!
[Boomer grunting]
Give me your sidearm!
Give me your gun!
Yes, sir.
Just shoot me.
Get it over with.
[Crying]
(Tyrol)
Hey, Tarn. Go up, take a look.
If it's not there,
it's at the Raptor.
We'll have to move up more.
I got it, Chief.
(Tyrol) All right, let's
get the hell out of here.
Tarn on point.
Let's go! Go, go, go, go, go.
(Cally)
This makes no sense.
Why am I carrying the med kit
when you forgot it?
First of all, that's the El-tee's
kit. Secondly, I'm on point.
Whatever.
All right, children, that's
enough. Tell you what, Cally.
If it makes you
feel any better...
I'll put him on hangar deck mop-up
duty with you for the next week.
(Cally) Now you're
talking. (Tarn) For what?
If anybody should have
mop duty, it's the El-tee.
[Gun firing]
(Tyrol)
Go! Go! Get down!
[Grunts]
Top of the ridge!
Cally! Take the rifle
and cover me!
Drastic fire!
[Gun firing continues]
Okay, okay. Wait for me.
Wait for me, all right?
Go! Go! Go!
Stay there! Don't move!
I'm coming for you.
Don't move!
[Groaning]
Chief!
(Tyrol) Cally! Help me out here, Cally!
Give me fire! Cally, go! Go!
There's no need, Chief!
I can't see them!
Cover me! Tarn, stay down!
Stay down!
(Cally)
Chief!
Come on, Chief!
You're okay. You're okay. It's
okay. It's okay. Get on my back.
Get on my back.
Get on me, get on me!
[Tarn groaning]
(Cally)
Chief!
[Screaming]
(Cally) Chief, stop. They're
not following us anymore.
Cally, there...
Chief...
I know you're hit, buddy. It's
okay. I'm gonna check you right now.
I'm gonna put him here, Cal.
Here. Lay down. You're
gonna stay right here, okay?
I'm gonna check you right now.
Let's just try...
It's not that bad. It's not
that bad. Cally, check the ridge.
I wanna go home.
I know. I know. We're going home.
We're going home, okay? Okay.
(Tarn)
Take me with you.
[Shushing]
[Gasping] It's okay. It's
okay. It's okay. Stay with me.
Look at me. Look at me.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Here, be with me. Be with me,
come on. Come on. Hey. Hey.
Hey. Hey.
(Cally)
Chief?
Chief, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
Chief?
Gods damn this stupid
frakked-up crap!
[Breathing heavily]
Chief, Socinus needs us now.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
[People chattering]
Not your fault, Lieutenant.
Not from where I was standing.
I was the OOD.
It was crazy in there, sir.
You can't blame yourself.
So, we jump back
to the last coordinates...
but we network the FTL computer with
the Nav, DC, and fire control computers.
Once they're linked, we'll only need
10 minutes to complete the calculations.
You can't be serious.
The old man would
never do this, Colonel.
(Kelly) No computer
networks on his ship.
I acknowledge that, sir.
But I can devise a software
firewall that will buy us more time.
Really? You're going to out-think
the Cylons at computer software?
Sir, if we don't do this, we're
never gonna find the fleet.
Certainly not before
the Commander dies.
This is still
the old man's command.
We can't do something
he'd oppose...
especially when it puts
the entire ship at risk.
[People chattering]
[PA system beeping]
This is the XO.
Begin jump prep.
Those are my orders.
The kid is back in the fleet!
Bill, let's have the truth.
So how did you do it? How'd you
get off this frakking freighter?
Connections. Anne's father has a
friend on the Defense Subcommittee.
So the new wife comes through.
I wish I had in-laws
with pull.
Give me a couple of years.
I'll have some pull.
You watch me.
I'll have my own
Battlestar one day.
[Guard]
Open up, please.
All right.
You have my parole.
When I'm on duty, I'll make
no attempt to free her...
or sow insurrection
among the crew.
When I'm not on duty, I'll
report directly back to this cell.
Pre-flight brief is underway
in the Ready Room.
Right.
(Roslin)
Good hunting, Captain.
Thank you, Madam President.
Colonel, once you find the fleet,
I'd like to have a word with you.
There's nothing to talk about. You went
up against the old man and you lost.
[Door slams shut]
We jump in,
we hold off the Cylons...
we crunch the numbers,
and we jump out.
That's it. Simple plan.
Not so simple to do.
Computers have been networked.
The board is green, sir. All
stations report ready to jump.
(crew member)
FTL go!
That software firewall ready?
Best I can make it, sir.
I wish Dr. Baltar was here.
To hell with that.
I'll take your work over...
that shifty son of a bitch
any day.
(Dualla) Speeding up
FTL drive. Stand by!
In five, four, three, two...
jump!
Jump completed.
Report.
Multiple dradis contacts.
Cylon Base Star,
and multiple Cylon Raiders...
bearing 487-carom-221.
[Alarm blaring]
[Beeping]
Lieutenant!
Computations underway.
We'll be able to plot the
fleet's position in seven minutes.
[Flyboy whooping]
Let's get these suckers!
Hey, Flyboy, you know we
got a pool going, right?
To see who gets the most kills
now that's Starbuck's AWOL.
We know I'm gonna clean up.
Flyboy, shut up and focus.
This is not a simulation.
Roger that.
[ECG machine flatlining]
(Kim)
His heart stopped.
Defib now!
Power's unstable. The battery
units are at the aid stations.
Well, then get me a knife.
[ECG machine beeping]
Weapons free.
And open racks and engage!
(pilot) Viper two-one,
I'm right behind your tail.
Here it comes.
[Alarm blaring]
The Cylons are hacking
our network.
They're attempting
to access our gateway.
Now it's a race.
(pilot)
We've got three more.
Spike that, spike that.
We have four more.
(Gaeta)
First firewall penetrated.
(Apollo) Sierra-Alpha.
We got a new bogey.
(Hotdog)
What is that thing?
I don't know, but whatever it
is, it's bearing on Galactica.
We've got to take it out!
Apollo, Hotdog, defensive.
Three right, five at two.
Tally, Hotdog! Kat, on me!
(Kat) Roger that. I'm with you, leader.
Will you pray with me?
Help us, Lords of Kobol.
Help your prophet, Laura, guide
us to the path of righteousness...
that we might...
[Venner breathing heavily]
That we might destroy
our enemies.
Let us walk the path
of righteousness...
[sighing] And lift our
faces unto your goodness.
Help us turn away from
the calls of the wicked...
and show us the knowledge
of your certain salvation.
We offer this prayer...
[ECG machine beeping]
(Gaeta)
Calculations at 56%.
Second firewall's
been breached!
(Apollo)
Damn it!
(Gaeta) Frak, they're
fast. Third firewall down!
(Kat) Apollo, approaching
Galactica's flack barrier.
Cylon target within gun range.
(Apollo)
Wind it!
Apollo, we're straying into
Galactica's engagement zone!
I'm almost there. I'm almost
there. I'm almost there. Come on!
Frak! Frak!
(Apollo)
Damn it!
Had it!
(Apollo) Plan in position
for a strafing run!
Apollo reports impact
on the starboard flight pod.
We've got a decompression in the
flight pod. No explosion, no fire.
Repeat, no fire.
No fire!
(Gaeta)
80%! Almost there.
They're through
the fourth firewall.
One left till they've
accessed our mainframe.
Frakker.
That's mine. That was mine.
[Beeping]
We have a solution
for the fleet's position!
(Tigh)
Break the network!
(pilot)
Hang tight.
Sure can, gentleman. Sure can.
Network is broken! Computers
restored to local control!
Tell the Vipers
to get back aboard.
We're getting
awful lucky today.
Prepare to jump!
(Dualla)
Vipers aboard, sir.
Stand by in five, four,
three, two...
jump.
Jump completed.
Report.
[Beeping]
Multiple contacts,
round the board.
Colonial transponders,
Sir. We found them!
[Crew cheering]
[Crew applauding]
Capt. Kelly.
Lt. Gaeta.
Sir.
Dee, contact the Rising Star.
Tell Cottle to get his ass
over here, ASAP.
Hell of a job.
From now on,
no more heart massages for me.
I'm sticking to pills
and enemas.
Sir.
Let's hear it.
Well, I managed to stop the
bleeding, but he's still critical.
Doc's on his way.
Can you hear me, Bill?
[Sighing]
[Sniffs]
[Knocking on door]
Go away!
(Watkins) Capt. Tigh?
This is Shore Patrol.
Sgt. Watkins, sir.
Open up, please.
Maj. Adama's compliments.
He wishes me to inform you, you've
been reinstated in the Colonial Fleet...
with the rank of Captain.
Maj. Adama?
Welcome back
to the Fleet, sir.
I'll be right with you,
Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
You never should've brought
me back in the service.
If you'd just let me be,
I'd have died back there...
on Caprica along
with everyone else...
and been happier for it.
I don't want a command.
I never did.
Don't you dare die on me now.
[Clanking]