NARRATOR: Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
ADAMA: Colonel Fisk
is the new Pegasus Commander.
The Cylon's foetus contains no antigens.
It makes it a universal donor.
ADAMA: Are you saying you've found a cure
for the President's cancer?
BALTAR: Yes.
ROSLIN: I've got ships on half-rations.
When will some of these supplies
start getting out to the Fleet?
The target's FTL is history. She's all yours.
(PANTING)
RACETRACK: He's all right!
I say again, Apollo is all right.
Let's just be glad that we both
came back alive, all right?
That's just it, Kara.
I didn't want to make it back alive.
You're not gonna shoot.
You're not like me.
APOLLO: Hey, hey. Hey, don't go.
Sorry. I thought you were still asleep.
You should have kicked me out of bed
an hour ago.
If I hold up Galactica's Raptor,
Tigh'll have my ass.
(CHUCKLES)
Which, we both know,
currently belongs to me.
All right, let's move on to the next item.
Oh, no, gentlemen, please, don't get up.
After the last few weeks,
it just feels good to be on my feet.
Thank you, though.
You've made a remarkable recovery,
Madam President.
Remarkable indeed.
But now I'm playing catch-up.
I'm afraid during my illness I lost focus.
I let some things slide.
Well, that's behind us now.
Yes, it is. To the point.
Supplies are running low
and the people are worried.
FISK: Well, they wouldn't be civilians
if they didn't have something to bitch about.
ROSLIN: Well, I think that in this case,
they're entitled.
Our inventory levels are tight,
but they're not critical.
But all the way across the Fleet,
people are reporting shortages
of essential goods,
and what they do get comes at a high price.
They're turning to the black market.
Last week, one of my aides
came down with pneumonia.
Billy had to trade liquor
to get the antibiotics.
It's the nature of the beast.
People want what they want.
A few trades would be one thing,
Commander Fisk. That's reality.
But I'm talking about criminals
making outrageous demands on the people.
So, bottom line is, I'm implementing a new,
Fleet-wide trade policy.
We need to be in control of our supply chain,
not black market thugs.
I am hoping that I can have
the military's support on this.
Admiral, if you want Pegasus to run
these dogs down, you just give us the word.
Our people will do whatever it takes
to get this under control.
And it's good to have you back,
Madam President.
It's good to be back. Thank you, Admiral.
Gentlemen, thank you.
(DOOR CLOSING)
FISK: Is Madam President
always so right-in-your-face?
Her last-minute resurrection
seems to have invigorated her somewhat.
Yeah, well, maybe too much.
She doesn't really think
her made-up plans and regulations
are gonna change anything, does she?
As if we don't have enough to do.
No, Madam President sets a great prestige
by her office
and Adama supports her,
at least for the moment.
Well, then, so do I, just for the moment.
By the way, did you get the cigars
I had sent over?
I not only got them, I enjoyed them as well.
Well, my pleasure, Mr Vice President.
Well, I've got a ship to run.
I look forward to our next visit.
As do I.
SHEVON: I got them from a friend.
(DOOR OPENING)
APOLLO: Paya.
SHEVON: Hey, sweetie.
Wow. You seem to get an inch taller
every time I see you.
What, I don't get my handshake?
Well, that's okay, Paya.
I have a special surprise for you,
and it's in here.
APOLLO: You wanna come see?
SHEVON: What's he got? Go on.
(BAG UNZIPPING)
APOLLO: What have we got?
(GASPS)
Oh, Paya.
I've never been great with kids.
Maybe next time I'll get one with two eyes.
I'll see if I can trade it for something else.
No, it's okay. You just surprised her.
Well...
Well, look, I'm not sure
when I'll be able to make it back.
I know.
I'm gonna have to ask for an extra hundred
since you spent the night.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(LIGHTER CLINKING)
Well, I wondered when
you were gonna show up.
(FISK GAGGING)
LANDING OFFICER: (ON RADIO)
Raptor one-two-niner,
you are cleared into the break.
(PANTING)
RACETRACK: Galactica,
Raptor one-two-niner has the ball.
Inbound speed 220.
Admiral, Colonel, I'm just getting started,
but from the looks of him,
I'd say he was garrotted.
Gods. This is the last thing we needed.
Admiral, you might want
to take a look at this.
Looks like our friend Fisk hit the jackpot.
Cubit?
If you find anything else,
let me know right away.
If I find anything else, I may retire early.
ADAMA: Someone's sending us a message.
Or running us in circles.
Maybe there's another Cylon in the Fleet.
I'd almost prefer that to the alternative:
We start killing our own.
All they have to do is sit back and watch.
Fisk?
Do we have any idea who did it?
No.
But we will do a full investigation
and I want you to lead it.
Don't you think it would be better
if someone from Pegasus dealt with this?
Even though Cain's gone,
her influence lingers.
I need someone I can trust.
You know, there were times
when that was in short supply between us.
We've both been through an awful lot, Son.
And I hope that we've grown stronger for it.
I need your help.
I'll call up a flight to Pegasus right away.
Anyone else been inside?
Just the medical team, sir.
BALTAR: Do you know who I am?
I am the Vice President of the Colonies.
Let me in.
Captain Adama.
Commander Fisk didn't tell me
you were invited.
Let him in.
They were going to let me in.
BALTAR: Oh, my Gods.
What's going on in here?
Where's Fisk?
On a slab in Galactica's morgue.
What, he's dead?
Isn't this your brand?
NO. 6: Careful, Gaius.
You bought yourself some goodwill
by saving Roslin,
but it's fading.
Their old suspicions are re-emerging.
What are you doing here?
Captain?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
Wait a minute, I...
Are you interrogating me?
I'm not sure I appreciate your tone.
This isn't a diplomatic exercise.
A man was butchered.
APOLLO: His head was practically severed
from his body with piano wire.
NO. 6: You're Vice President of the Fleet.
Why are you acting like a child
with your hand in the cookie jar, hmm?
Wonder what she would say
if she saw you like this.
You know, I can't believe it's even necessary
for me to explain myself to you,
but obviously, no, I had nothing to do
with Commander Fisk's death.
For the record, I just came here to discuss
President Roslin's new trade policy.
Well, I thought that was settled.
No, Commander Fisk had some reservations.
I'll bet.
And as the Vice President,
I decided to assuage his doubts
of my own free will.
Is that sufficient?
Or would you like me
to provide you with an alibi?
I'm sure I can rustle one up.
Enjoy the cigars.
APOLLO: Escort the Vice President
to his ship.
(MACHINES HUMMING)
The wireless is going crazy.
Word of Fisk's murder
has spread out through the entire Fleet.
When we lose a command officer
aboard a warship,
people are gonna be concerned
about their security.
TIGH: A crew can fall apart
when their commander's killed.
Pegasus lost two in a matter of weeks.
Maybe this time they were lucky.
His personal log shows
that he was rerouting supply runs,
on and offloading freighters
without command authorisation.
APOLLO: He raided the MacConnel,
and at least a dozen other ships
in the last week.
I also found a small warehouse
of high-value merchandise in his quarters.
He was working the black market.
Half the Fleet's working it.
Fisk was getting greedy.
If he crossed one of his suppliers on a deal,
that would explain the cubits
that Cottle found.
It still doesn't tell us who did it.
Well, he's gonna need trading partners.
And they wouldn't be hard to find,
even on Galactica.
WORKER 1: All right, let's open it up here.
WORKER 2: Move around back.
(PAYA COUGHING)
Lee, I'm scared.
Paya's cough keeps getting worse.
I'll bring her something on my next trip.
Which could be weeks
if there's another Cylon attack.
I keep hearing about shortages
on the other ships,
people trading anything they can
for food, and for medicine.
Really?
Have you seen
all the new working girls outside?
Lee, when your baby's crying
because it's hungry,
you'll do anything to make it stop.
Hey.
Come here.
PAYA: Mommy.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Captain.
What do you want?
APOLLO: Is your wife around, Colonel?
No. Why?
Is this hers?
Yeah. She lost it a couple weeks ago.
Where the hell did you find it?
On Pegasus.
In Commander Fisk's quarters.
(COUGHING)
She's burning up.
APOLLO: What did they say
at the infirmary?
Antibiotics have all been rationed out.
They said they might have something
by the end of the week.
(PAYA COUGHING)
We got shortages across the Fleet,
people begging for scraps,
but somehow you and Mrs Tigh
have fresh fruit, real liquor...
All right. What the hell is this about?
You must have known
she was trading with Fisk.
Well, maybe I'll talk to her.
She didn't give it to Fisk.
I did. I traded it for a few necessities,
a couple of things to help her get by.
Big frakking deal.
There's nothing illegal about that.
Not yet.
Don't you play holier-than-thou with me.
I haven't done anything
that most people on this ship haven't done.
Including you.
Doesn't make us right, Colonel,
just a whole lot of people wrong.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
You didn't make it to class today.
(PANTING)
Yeah, I've been pretty jammed up.
Anyway, I'm not sure
you need me holding your hand anymore.
Was that what you were doing?
Holding my hand?
(CHUCKLES)
I meant it as a compliment.
Permission to speak frankly, sir?
You don't need my permission
and you don't need the "sir".
Maybe that's the problem.
I don't really know what to think anymore.
So I'll just ask. Is this going somewhere?
Dee...
Please don't pretend like you don't know
what I'm talking about.
You know, our...
Our time together, our workouts.
Something's changed between us.
I'm just not sure what you want me to say.
Then don't say anything.
WOMAN: (ON PA SYSTEM)
Communications paging Captain Adama.
You have a priority ship-to-ship call
from Cloud 9.
Captain Adama here.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
APOLLO: Shevon. Shevon, it's me!
Shevon?
Oh, my Gods. What did they do?
They said they knew about you and me.
They wanted to know
what we've been talking about.
Lee, I don't understand why they'd care.
All right, get what you need.
I'm taking you and Paya back to Galactica.
(BAG RUSTLING)
Lee, wait.
It's the only place I can keep you safe.
What are you gonna tell them about us?
I'm not fooling myself. I know what this is.
SHEVON: Lee!
(MAN GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(SHEVON SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
Get away from us!
(CHOKING)
You listening?
I hear any more talk about Fisk,
I'm going to send your whore
back to you piece by piece.
And then I'm gonna start on the little girl.
I know who you are,
I know whose son you are.
And I don't care.
You tell Adama to let it go.
Is that when you knew that you loved her?
I thought so.
SHEVON: But you hurt her.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
This is Captain Adama.
I need a medic
and a security team on L Deck ASAP.
You wanted to see me, Madam President?
Yes.
Thank you for coming, Doctor.
Have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
I'd love one.
You know, I'm never quite sure
where we stand with each other, Doctor.
Why do you think that is?
I can't imagine why.
I've never had anything but the utmost
respect for you and your office.
I understand that you and Commander Fisk
planned to meet
just prior to his death.
As I have already explained
to Captain Adama,
Commander Fisk had several lingering
concerns about your new trade policy.
What can I say?
And that's it?
NO. 6: Gaius, she's afraid of you.
Why
are you asking me this?
You saved my life and I'm grateful.
But I sense that there is some unease in you
about assuming the presidency
and I'd like to offer you an out.
You what?
Resign.
Return to your scientific work on Galactica.
No one will question your motives,
and you can consider it a second chance
like the one you gave me.
Charming.
Doctor,
this is a one-time offer.
I suggest you reconsider.
You know, Madam President, I've never been
particularly interested in politics
and I never wanted
any lofty position of power.
I never wanted to be the Vice President.
That is, until this very moment.
Because right now,
I can't think of anything I want more.
One to the head. You didn't do this?
I was attacked.
I found him there when I woke up.
Security bulletin said
Commander Fisk was garrotted with a wire.
Whatever happened,
looks like you found your guy.
What about Shevon, and her daughter?
Cloud 9's an open port.
Chances are they're already off-ship.
I'll get a team down here.
Councilman Zarek.
Lee. I just heard. Are you all right?
What are you doing here?
Attending a Quorum meeting.
Nothing as exciting as all this, I assure you.
I know these places are legal, but still,
the son of the almighty Adama?
Talk to me about the black market.
(ZAREK CHUCKLES)
Not much to say. It's widespread, inevitable,
and according to President Roslin, illegal.
So it's no surprise that you and Fisk
were in it up to your necks.
Fisk, maybe, but not me.
I represent Astral Queen.
Have to be careful about the company I keep.
This is Fisk's log.
He says he made three runs
to Astral Queen in the last 10 days
and I doubt it was to discuss prison reform.
What do you want from me, Captain?
Names of ships. Contacts.
I can't help you.
Why do you think Fisk approached me?
To get a piece of your black market scam.
To offer you protection.
You and your father are both
so blinded by the past.
Fisk's black market was up and running
when he approached me.
He knew Adama would pick up
on his unauthorised shuttles,
so he tried to force me
into taking over the deliveries,
creating a firewall between Pegasus
and the illegal shipments.
So you're trying to tell me
that you turned him down?
At great cost.
Check the fleet logs,
see how many supply ships made stops
at the Astral Queen after Fisk's last trip.
The answer is none.
So if Fisk was trying to starve you out,
why didn't you bring it to the Quorum?
Roslin's acting like the black market's
some sort of aberration,
but I thought you were smarter than that.
Did you really expect
some utopian fantasy to rise from the ashes?
ZAREK: I heard the security officer.
They gave you Fisk's killer for a reason.
They're offering you a way out.
You know something, don't you?
Just rumours.
There's a freighter, Prometheus.
Some people say it's gone off the grid.
But if you want something bad enough,
that's where you go.
The deals are brokered
by an ex-military mercenary named Phelan.
Lee.
I hope she's worth it.
(ZAREK SIGHS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Hey, man, biotics. Here.
(PAYA COUGHING)
(CHILDREN SOBBING)
Paya?
Paya! Paya! Hey, Paya.
Hey, it's okay.
It's Lee, do you remember? It's Lee.
You're gonna be fine, I promise you.
Okay, you just hang tight.
I'll be right back. I'll be right back.
(SIGHING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
You may find this hard to believe,
but my father was in the service, too.
Strict as hell,
probably the same as your old man.
But when the Cylons attacked, all his duty
and honour didn't add up to squat.
Is she dead?
I can see why you want her back.
She's one of my best.
One of yours?
A good escort understands
it's about a lot more than sex.
PHELAN: She knows when to listen,
and when to call for help.
Lee, I had to.
PHELAN: Don't blame her.
The only reason you're alive
is because I was able to see you
through Shevon's eyes.
And what I saw seemed reasonable.
Like Fisk?
Fisk was a pig.
He tried to force us to renegotiate.
So you killed him.
No. I gave you the killer,
the murder weapon, the prints,
everything you needed
to close the case legitimately.
Despite the President's objections,
the Fleet needs us.
Rationing's too tight, ship comes in too late,
we're the pressure valve.
We provide.
PHELAN: When Shevon needed antibiotics,
she knew where to go.
Without us, people would have
nowhere to turn.
The Fleet would tear itself apart.
And what about those children outside?
How are they
helping the Fleet?
Everyone has needs.
Some settle for cigars and liquor.
You wanted Shevon.
Others are more demanding.
It's hard to find the moral high ground
when we're all standing in the mud.
I'm not like my old man, Captain.
And you are not like yours.
I came alone,
but Galactica tracked me on dradis.
All they'll need to vent this ship into space
is an excuse.
So let's make a deal.
I want Shevon, the girl,
I walk out of here
and you shut down this operation.
And all of you will live.
Sorry, the little girl's been paid for.
No refunds.
Oh, Gods. No!
- PHELAN: Wait.
- Lee, don't.
Come on. Do it. Do it.
I made you a fair offer.
(MAN CHOKING)
So did I.
APOLLO: Yeah, you're probably right
about everything.
You, me, Fisk.
Nobody can stop it.
And maybe nobody should.
But it needs limits.
There's lines you can't cross
and you've crossed them.
You're not gonna shoot.
You're not like me.
You're not gonna...
(MUMBLING)
(GASPING)
APOLLO: All right, it's done.
The Fleet relies on the black market.
Much as we'd like, we can't wish that away.
So you're still in business.
For now.
But if there are any more killings,
if you hold back essential medicines,
if you ever touch a child...
Shevon...
No, I don't want...
Hey, hey, it's over. It's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay...
- Lee, Lee, no.
- Hey. Shevon, it's over.
Stop.
I can't be what you want me to be.
I don't want you to be anything.
You want me to be her.
(SNIFFLING)
That's what this is about.
That's what this has always been about.
No. That's not what
this has ever been about.
Come on, Lee. I know my job.
I'm a replacement.
For a lot of things.
Things that men can't get anywhere else.
SHEVON: Things they've lost.
She wanted to give you a child.
But you were afraid,
so you pushed her away and then you ran,
and you didn't stop running
until it was too late.
Well, I'm not her.
And Paya is not,
and will never be, your child.
APOLLO: Commander Fisk's murder
has been resolved
and Pegasus' crew appears
to have accepted Galactica's conclusions.
That's all, Madam President.
Not quite. What about this ship Prometheus?
I understand it's the hub
of the Fleet's black market.
We will keep an eye on them.
Keep an eye on them.
That's not exactly the solution I had in mind.
Whether or not we allow
a criminal enterprise to thrive in this Fleet
is not a matter of choice, Captain.
Admiral?
I've given Lee full authority on this issue.
The decision is his.
I support your trade policies wholeheartedly,
Madam President,
but we are never gonna have
a perfect system.
There will always be
some kind of black market.
At least this way I know names, I know faces,
I know where they are
and we will monitor the situation.
Thank you, gentlemen, I'm busy.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
BILLY: Eighteen. I'm starting to sweat here.
Nineteen...
- You should be sweating.
- Twenty...
Why aren't you doing any of these?
No talking, no talking, please.
No cheating. Hold it up, a little higher.
(CHUCKLING)
- Sneaky.
- Eight, nine...
- Start again.
- You aren't serious.
Zero...
Well? No?
President wasn't very happy today.
No.
Ever since you ejected from the Blackbird,
you've been different.
Harder to reach.
I'm just trying to understand.
Well, like you said, Dad,
we've all been through a lot.
Fair enough.
But you should have told me
about the woman.