(female narrator) Previously
on Battlestar Galactica.
We networked the FTL computer with
a nav DC and fire control computers.
Once they're linked, we'll only need
10 minutes to complete the calculations.
Really? You're going to outthink
the Cylons at computer software?
Cylons are hacking our network.
Attempting to access our mainframe.
[Electricity buzzes]
What the hell was that?
It's the virus, sir.
I think it must have spawned copies of
itself in some other computer systems.
It's knocked out main power
and auxiliary units.
[People screaming]
I love you, Chief.
What do you want from me,
Helo? She's a Cylon.
I'm not going to let you
kill her.
She's carrying my child.
I have terminal breast cancer. Dr.
Cottle will verify the diagnosis.
I have a few months to live.
Five-four-two-eight-niner.
So, how are we feeling today?
[Thudding]
Great!
[Men laughing]
(Helo)
Thought I'd find you here.
[Coins rattling]
Karl Agathon.
[Men chattering]
You wanna sit in?
Maybe next time.
So, he's the Cylon lover?
You know what? I don't
care who or what he fraks.
He saved my ass down there,
all right?
[Sighing]
How could anyone fall in love
with a toaster, though?
Same way I hear everyone
was high-fiving our Sharon...
right before she put two
in Adama's chest.
The bastards frak
with your head.
Yeah. Just ask the Chief.
[Dripping]
I knew it.
I need a drink.
Tanned, rested and ready! Look at you.
Rested, anyway. Nothing to do
but eat and sleep in the can.
"Unauthorized discharge of a
firearm." What a bogus charge.
They should have given you a
medal for popping that toaster.
[People chattering]
Chief, I heard that
you went to bat for me.
Forget it.
I just want you to know...
I need all the knuckle
draggers I can get.
(Tyrol) Sharon flew 47
missions in this thing...
and still couldn't trap
a landing worth a damn.
Had to bend her undercarriage back
into place after every landing.
Approaches made her nervous.
She was afraid you'd be watching.
I usually was.
Screw it.
[Men chattering]
You're folding with three up?
Are you crazy?
Not when you've got me beat.
Prince high red, right?
Been playing with these cards
for so long, I know every fold.
So, life's a bitch. What do
you want to do, cry about it?
No, I just want it to end,
okay?
The bad food,
the endless rotations...
pretending that a card game
is the high point of our day!
It's not going to last forever,
all right. Earth is out there.
[Smirking]
Right.
We could all be chasing our tails
over some half-assed planetarium show.
You guys can all go to hell.
[Coins rattling]
I'm gonna go find Helo.
Good idea. Maybe that Cylon
whore taught him a few tricks.
[Groaning]
Look, Chief. I never intended
for Sharon to know that.
You know,
it just kind of evolved.
Just a couple
of lovesick kids, huh?
I know how she felt about you.
She loved you.
Did she fill you in
on the rest of the plan?
She and I were going to muster
out at the end of our service.
You know?
That we would get married...
maybe we would have children.
[Sighing]
I guess I'm just a big
frakking idiot, though, huh?
Probably that godsdamn
toaster's plan all along.
Don't call her that.
To sucker some moron...
into giving her a kid.
But you know what? I should
probably be grateful to you.
Probably be grateful.
You know why?
Because that freak in her
belly could've been mine.
[Groaning]
Hey. You okay? Sorry.
Son of a bitch!
[Gasping]
[Both grunting]
That's enough, Chief.
You don't get to call it.
Enough!
[Grunting]
[Both grunting]
Come on,
you damn toaster lover!
[Panting]
[Spanner clanking]
[Both panting]
I don't even know
why I'm mad at you.
My Sharon's dead.
That thing in the brig...
that isn't Sharon.
Roger, Blue leader.
Say fuel state.
[Screaming]
[Radio feedback]
What the hell is that?
It was us, sir. But I can't find
the source of the transmission.
Something's triggering our comm system
to broadcast an automatic signal.
Which the Cylons could trace
to get a fix on our position.
Let's assume that for now.
Update and distribute
emergency jump sites...
just in case
they show up again.
Dee, get me a...
[gasping]
[Men chattering]
[Sighing]
I'm okay, sir.
No. No, stay down.
We'll get you to Doc Cottle
to make sure everything's okay.
Mr. Gaeta,
find out what happened.
[Dualla exhaling]
I'm okay.
Mr. Gaeta?
A power surge
energized the board.
System's been twitchy ever since
the Cylons infiltrated our network.
Mr. Gaeta,
this is more than a twitch.
The commander's right.
I don't care if you have to go through
this program line by line. Fix it.
Excuse me?
You heard me. Sir, I'm running
every diagnostic we've got.
Checking each line of code
could take days.
I am not interested
in excuses. Fix it.
It's not an excuse, sir.
It's a frakking fact!
[Sighing]
Mr. Gaeta.
Yes, sir.
Pull yourself together.
I'm sorry, sir.
[Men chattering]
What the hell
is his problem?
Months on the run and what
do we have to show for it?
Casualties.
Deteriorating conditions.
This crew needs a rest. It's
finally hitting them, Saul.
Our old lives are gone.
The only thing we have
to look forward to is this.
Chief, where's 2-8-niner?
I need her for drills today.
She was grounded, sir.
What? For how long?
Permanently.
We're salvaging what we can,
but it's gone.
Damn it,
I need that ship on line.
What can I tell you, Captain? Engine
mounts are shot, cockpit seals are cracked.
If it was a horse, they'd
shoot it. Got something, Chief.
(Apollo)
Chief, come on.
Work with me here.
I need your help.
What do you want me to do?
Work my crew to death?
No. Just do your best.
Nobody's expecting any miracles.
[People chattering]
Maybe that's the problem.
(Tyrol)
Frak it, why not?
What's going on, Chief?
All right, here's the deal. We
are going to build a new fighter.
[Snickers]
What about
the rest of the ships?
I'm three days backlogged
on repairs as is.
This is strictly
an off-duty project.
Nobody takes one minute away from regular
maintenance and repairs. You got it?
You don't think
we can do this?
I wouldn't even know
how to begin.
What else is new?
Screw you.
Okay. He's talking about fabricating
a frame, avionics, life support.
It's frakking impossible.
You know what, then?
Forget you. I don't need you.
Chief, wait.
It's not like that.
I said forget it.
Get back to work.
That's an order.
[Clears throat]
How much time do I have?
Weeks. A month at the outside.
Will I be able to work?
Unless the cancer goes to
your brain. If that happens...
[gun firing]
Someone's a tad aggressive.
Just shut up and shoot.
My gods, between you
and Racetrack, it's like...
Having a conversation is like
walking through a minefield.
And you're the last person who
should be lecturing me about manners.
From what I hear, you've also been
riding Chief Tyrol pretty good.
Press it.
[Machine buzzing]
I just reminded him that I
expect Viper maintenance...
to take precedence
over his hobby project.
(Starbuck)
Nice.
I'm surprised he didn't take
a swing at you.
Come on, Starbuck.
You don't actually think that piece
of junk's gonna actually fly, do you?
[Guns firing]
Fifty cubits says
he gets it in the air.
Yeah? And who's gonna fly it?
It's not gonna be me.
Don't look at me! (Apollo)
I wasn't looking at you.
What?
I'll fly it.
You?
Me.
Why?
Because while everyone else
is standing around whining...
(Apollo)
We're whining?
...the Chief
is doing something positive.
I'm deeply moved.
Really?
Honestly, I am.
[Starbuck laughing]
[Apollo laughing]
His lips are blue!
[Whispering]
You look like a blueberry.
There's no oxygen in here.
No oxygen.
[Starbuck laughing]
[Gasping]
[Starbuck wheezing]
I'm out.
[Both gasping]
Nice shot.
[Alarm sounding]
The environmental computer decided that
the firing range was over pressurized...
and started bleeding out air
to compensate.
Two more minutes,
we may have been dead.
Power fluctuations.
Equipment failures.
Sir, I think I've found
what's causing it.
What is that? (Baltar)
A Cylon logic bomb.
A heuristic computer virus.
It's capable of learning,
evolving.
It's probably running
in parallel...
with every computer
in the ship, right now...
just waiting to be activated.
No doubt left behind...
when the Cylons infiltrated
the network Col. Tigh set up...
the day you were shot, sir.
That was weeks ago.
Why now?
Most likely, sir, it took
that long for it to crack...
our encrypted pass-codes.
And once that happened, it started
testing its ability to control our systems.
Electrical, environmental.
How do you kill it?
Well, that's the tricky part.
If it's a Cylon virus, it is
extremely difficult to eradicate.
Well, I guess
I'm pretty lucky then.
Because I have
an expert onboard.
Tell Helo to run this past
our prisoner.
[Grunting]
[Men chattering]
Come on. Come on.
For frak's sakes.
Son of a bitch!
Gods damn it!
[Machine humming]
I got it. Go back to work.
It's a two-man job, Chief.
You want this wing up or not?
On three.
One, two, three.
(Tyrol) Great. Great, hold
it there. Pull it that way.
Sir, we're continuing
to experience power spikes...
and equipment failures
across the ship. Thank you.
We'd better up
our alert status...
and put our damage control
teams on standby.
Not yet.
Have you seen the ship
that the Chief is building?
His imaginary fighter? I don't need
to see it. I know it's a waste of time.
The deck crew doesn't seem
to think so.
We need to focus on the fleet
we've got left...
not get bogged down
in some pipe dream.
You should shut it down.
It may come to that.
This project,
it's giving them something.
I'm not going to take
that away until I have to.
[Men chattering]
Doc Cottle cleared me. And I
feel like hitting something.
Okay. Don't square up.
Don't square up.
Rotate,
and just drop the knee.
[Man chattering]
That's nice.
Now,
if you want to throw them...
I'll be you.
Head in a lock, grab the
wrist, secure the arm...
and I'm just gonna drop
the knee, rotate 45. Okay.
[Exhaling]
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Just like we did in basic.
Let's bring a live opponent
into the mix.
[Man chattering]
(man) Nice. And strip the knife.
[Knocking on door]
(Dualla)
Billy.
Hey.
How long have you been
onboard? I just arrived.
Do you have actual memories of being
with the Chief before the Cylon attack?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. You asked.
Do you still love him?
Helo...
you're the father
of my child.
You're the first in my heart and
nothing is ever going to change that.
All right.
We have to get to this.
Dr. Baltar says it's some
sort of Cylon logic bomb.
Do you see anything?
Can you flip?
Sharon?
Sharon.
I need to talk to Cmdr.
Adama. Right now. Why?
It's a Cylon virus,
all right.
It's been learning your systems.
Testing, adapting, finding weak spots.
For what?
So they can turn Galactica's
systems against you.
Crash you into other ships,
detonate your weapons stores...
suffocate the crew.
What about you? The baby?
I'm a liability to them...
a mistake.
Helo, this logic bomb will run
its course in a matter of hours.
Once it does, the Cylons
will be on top of us.
They're going to kill us all.
Cmdr. Adama...
Whatever it is you have
to say, make it quick.
[Machines humming]
Well, I hate to say it, but you've
got the cockpit too far back.
You're gonna run into CG
problems when you maneuver.
We're not going for maneuverability,
Captain. We're going for speed.
Besides, you didn't think
this thing would fly anyway.
Well, it sure as hell won't
with the cockpit rammed up its...
Dee?
Hey.
(Apollo) What are you doing
here? Communications, I think.
She's great with hydraulics,
but this comm system is a mess.
Ten-hut.
I had to see this
with my own eyes.
Won't be long before we
have the whole CIC down here.
You working on this
class project, too, Apollo?
No. It's good to see
someone has a little sense.
Where's the Chief?
Tool room?
Aye, getting some
rack time, sir.
[Door opening]
(Tigh)
What's this, Chief?
[Door closing]
Making solvent, sir.
To clean engine parts.
Solvent, my ass.
I know a still when I smell
it, what the hell are you up to?
[Liquid dripping]
I need booze
to trade for parts.
I'm scrounging most of
what I can from the fleet.
But I need engines.
I know I need
Cmdr. Adama's permission...
to cannibalize
one of the wrecks.
Engines or not, we both know that piece
of crap out there is never going to fly.
I gotta try, Colonel.
What's the point?
Because that ship, the work,
that's all I've got left.
I don't have that, I...
[tap squeaking]
I almost forgot. I promised the XO
of the Baah Pakal I'd help him out.
Sir? He's got some
obsolete DDG-62 engines...
that's taking up space
on his flight deck.
They're probably crap but I told him
that I would have a crew in there...
to haul them out
as soon as possible.
Glad to be of help, sir.
Good.
Madam President, your
shuttle's ready. Of course.
Thank you again for letting
me use your quarters.
Please.
I wanted to return this.
This was a gift.
"Never lend a book," I know.
But I've had it far too long.
It belongs in your collection.
I'm late for a quorum meeting.
Is there a problem?
Our computers have been
infected by a Cylon virus...
corrupting systems
throughout the entire ship.
I've just been notified
that this is a prelude...
to an all-out attack
by the Cylons.
I assume you've tried
to disable it.
Mr. Gaeta and the Vice President
are handling that right now.
I'm not hopeful.
Commander, I'm not sure what I can
offer you here besides my moral support.
Actually, Madam President...
I could use your advice.
You want to what?
Completely erase
our computer drives...
cold restart
the entire ship's system...
and then restore them
using our prewar backups.
Leaving us with our pants down
until we're back online.
The Commander
will never go for this.
I've already spoken to him,
sir.
What did he say?
He's considering it.
It's the only way
to destroy the virus.
I thought the Commander
told you to stay out of this.
I'm sorry, do you want to
survive this one or not?
All right, so we calculate a jump and get
some distance on these Cylon bastards...
No, sir,
we can't risk a jump.
All of our systems are
compromised, including navigation.
The virus could drop us
in the middle of a sun.
We're running out of time.
Our signal's gonna catch up
with the Cylon fleet.
If we haven't come up
with anything before then...
They'll take control
of all of our systems...
and then they'll have
a hundred ways to kill us.
I've just come from
seeing our Cylon prisoner.
She's offering a possible
solution to the problem.
And you're wondering
if you can trust her.
It took everything I have...
not to put my hands
around her throat.
I can't believe
I'm contemplating this.
We both know the Cylons
are experts at manipulation.
They will do anything
to confuse you.
This is not the one
who shot me.
Can they really be that
different from one another?
Commander,
if you're asking me...
if it's possible that your
judgment's been clouded...
by your history with this
particular Cylon model...
I'd have to say yes.
But...
we created them.
There's always a chance
we might find common ground.
[Man chattering on radio]
We need to work quickly.
We're on borrowed time.
Let her go. (guard) Yes, sir.
Dee, do you still carry
your father's pocketknife?
Give it to her.
Mr. Gaeta, can you set me up
with a fiber-optic comm link?
I need broadcast
to all frequencies...
and direct contact
to the mainframe.
(Adama)
Do it.
(Gaeta)
Sir.
Right here, Sharon.
Thanks.
(Gaeta) Dradis. Here they
come. Multiple targets.
[Alarm sounding]
Bearing 371 carom 552.
Cylon raiders.
Bastards tracked us,
all right.
Launch Vipers.
[Alarm blaring]
[People shouting]
(man on radio) Apollo,
the raiders are holding.
(Apollo) Galactica, Apollo.
Raiders are holding formation.
Repeat,
raiders are holding formation.
What the hell?
(Sharon) Okay, this is
how it's going to work.
The raiders are going to send
a signal to activate the virus.
It could take a few seconds.
On my mark,
initiate the computer wipe.
Miss the window...
The virus takes over
every system in the ship.
Sometimes you gotta roll the
hard six. Right, Commander?
[Sharon groaning]
What the hell is she doing?
[Sharon moaning]
(Dualla)
They've made contact, sir.
(Gaeta) It's moving too
fast, I can't follow it.
We gotta stop this.
Stand by to execute
computer wipe on my command.
System is ready, sir.
Wipe the hard drives now.
Do it.
(Starbuck)
My gods, what are they doing?
[Alarm blaring]
Weapons are still offline.
No dradis. Systems down.
We're looking at a godsdamn
bloodbath. We're defenseless.
(Hotdog) Apollo, Hotdog. Here they come!
All right, copy, Hotdog.
Gods, there must be
hundreds of them.
Cylons are still moving in.
She set us up!
[Electricity buzzing]
Give me your sidearm. (guard) Yes, sir.
If they're coming for you,
they're gonna be very disappointed.
Do it.
(Tigh)
What are you waiting for?
This.
[Engines shutting down]
[Groaning]
What the hell?
We just transmitted a signal.
Galactica?
They seem to have lost power.
They're drifting
out of control!
What the hell?
Cylons sent a computer virus.
But we just sent one back.
Apollo, this is Galactica.
Kill the bastards.
(Starbuck)
Yeah! Come on, baby.
Roger that.
Vipers, weapons free.
Engage.
This is payback.
[Apollo whooping]
Yeah! How do you like that?
You seeing this?
(Apollo)
Got this toaster padlocked.
Come on!
[Apollo laughing]
I got another
where that one came from!
(Starbuck) Guys, clean
them up. Come on, let's go.
Officers. (guard) Yes, sir.
Take this thing
back to its cell.
[Men chattering]
[Machines whirring]
There you go, Chief.
Nice to be small, huh?
Ship's got more than
one engine. Get to it.
(Starbuck)
We are so damn close.
There has got to be some
extra metal lying around...
that we can use
to skin this thing.
Floorboards, extra bulkheads, something.
Most of it's ticketed
for Viper repair.
Who says you need metal?
Carbon composite.
(Starbuck) Good call, Helo.
It's gonna be hard as hell
to see on dradis...
but the question is,
will it fly?
Just watch me.
(Starbuck)
Instruments: In the green.
Fuel pressure: Nominal.
Apollo, Starbuck. Blackbird
flight is cleared for launch.
Run-up.
(man on radio) Maglock secure,
initiate launch sequence.
Don't blow up on me,
you bastard.
Clear for launch.
(Dualla)
Blackbird is away.
Will you take it easy?
Start slow.
You're testing the ship. It's
not about the pilot showing off.
(Starbuck)
Who's showing off?
(Apollo) Gods damn it, what is
this? What are you trying to prove?
I'm not trying to prove anything.
You've got to be kidding me.
[Whooping]
Oh, lords.
Okay. Let's see
what this baby can do.
[Panting]
[Starbuck whooping]
(Apollo)
Starbuck, where are you?
Starbuck, do you hear me?
Starbuck!
(man) I'm not... She's gone!
Galactica, Apollo.
I've lost her.
(Dualla)
No dradis contact.
(Apollo)
Starbuck, where are you?
Starbuck, come in.
Starbuck, do you read?
Kara, are you okay?
Of course, you lost contact. It's
a damn stealth ship, remember?
Oh, you...
[Starbuck and Apollo laughing]
[All clapping]
(officer)
Commander on deck.
As you were.
Chief Tyrol?
This is the Blackbird?
Yes, ma'am. Madam
President, this is an honor.
No, the honor's mine.
It's remarkable.
Just a ship, ma'am.
(Laura)
You're much too modest.
After what
we've been through...
it would be very easy
to give up, to lose hope.
But not here. Not today.
This is more than a ship,
Chief. This is an act of faith.
It is proof that despite
all we've lost...
we keep trying.
And we will get through this,
all of us, together.
I promise.
Commander.
Ahem,
Madam President...
this was supposed to be
a surprise...
but, well.
Thank you.
If you'll do us the honors,
Madam President.
Of Course.
Okay.
[Gasping]
[People laughing]
Kidding.
Hell of an idea,
using carbon composites.
(man)
It was a good job.
Nice work.
That was lovely.
They wanted to do that
for you. Thank you.
None of this would have been possible
if you hadn't trusted the Cylon.
I took your advice,
met on common ground.
What was that?
We both wanted to live.