NARRATOR: Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
STARBUCK: There are survivors on Caprica.
A resistance movement.
ANDERS: We've been fighting the Cylons,
hitting them where we can.
Now it looks like they're here to stay.
They're rebuilding Caprica.
ADAMA: The first Sharon
was a sleeper agent.
Didn't realise she was a Cylon
until her programming kicked in.
I'm Sharon, but I'm a different Sharon.
And I'm here to help.
No, I've decided you are an expression
of my subconscious mind playing itself out
during my waking states.
So, I'm only in your head?
BOOMER: I'm pregnant, Helo.
We're gonna have a child.
Sharon is going to bear our child?
An honour for which she is hardly deserving,
but one doesn't question God's will.
The Cylons reincarnate.
It makes sense, doesn't it?
All our memories are downloaded
to a brand-new body.
We're as good as new.
Death becomes a learning experience.
Wait, there has to be
another way out of here.
I mean... I mean, you must have
an escape plan.
You're not about to be destroyed
by your own bombs, are you, huh?
How are you leaving?
(SCREAMS)
Gaius, I can't die.
When this body's destroyed, my memory,
my consciousness
will be transmitted to a new one.
I'll just wake up somewhere else
in an identical body.
You mean, there's more out there like you?
There are 12 models. I'm number six.
I don't want to die.
Get down.
Do you love me?
(GASPING)
Where? Where?
I was in a house.
D'ANNA: But you're not in a house
any longer.
You're back with us.
You've been reborn.
I died?
That's right.
You were in a house. It was destroyed.
A nuclear blast.
But that is all over now.
You have been downloaded into a new body.
Gaius.
Gaius was in the house.
Gaius Baltar?
He's... Is he alive?
Is he?
(SHUSHING)
BALTAR: I'm not really here.
No one can see me but you.
Don't let them know.
Six, would it trouble you
if Dr Baltar were dead?
If they know how you feel about me,
it'll be a problem.
It would be unfortunate
if he died.
He was so helpful.
Very helpful.
Your mission was a resounding success.
We completely disabled
the Colonial defences.
The attack succeeded
beyond our most optimistic projections,
thanks to you.
(PEOPLE CLAMOURING)
(GUN FIRING)
You're a machine. I'm not.
I know there's pain, but breathe.
Ride through it.
You're going to be okay.
Trust me.
D'ANNA: You're in God's hands.
We're all here with you.
(COUGHING)
D'ANNA: That's it.
(GASPING)
(COUGHING)
D'ANNA: This will pass. Trust me.
Everything's gonna be all right.
NO. 6: Welcome home, little sister.
We're here.
We're going to take care of you.
DORAL: We're proud of you, Sharon.
And we love you.
No!
NO. 6: I was thinking it symbolised rebirth.
A new beginning.
BALTAR: It's a memorial.
Do you know how many people died
in this park during the attack?
How many people in this park alone?
It's gonna be lovely, isn't it?
This park.
You know, a place to relax,
collect your thoughts.
How you doing?
I'm a little stiff.
I'm still trying to get used to this body.
I mean, I know it's identical,
but even after all this time,
I still feel awkward.
I was a klutz, too.
I used to knock things over.
I was forever tripping over things and...
You know what, you get over it.
And you know what,
this is a great chance to cleanse.
You've got a new body, a new life.
And anything that you've built up,
like anxieties
or remorse or guilt,
just let it wash away.
I can't tell you how thankful I am.
You've been a really big help to me.
No, it's me who's thankful.
We all are. You are a war hero.
We could not have won without you.
Excuse me.
I just wanted to say, it's an honour
to have you here on Caprica with us.
What you did...
Well, that's inspiring.
Thank you.
(BEEPING)
Hey. How you doing?
I'm freezing.
I can't feel my legs.
That's the epidural.
What happened?
You passed out and started bleeding again,
but everything's gonna be all right.
Like hell it is.
I find it absolutely amazing.
You people went to all the trouble
to appear human
and didn't upgrade the plumbing.
You have a detached placenta.
Baby has to come out now,
or we could lose you both.
Okay, sir, I'm gonna have to ask you
to step back, please.
She's tachycardic
and her blood pressure's dropping.
Yeah, she's haemorrhaging again.
We're gonna have to make the cut, now.
HELO: Sharon, can you hear me?
BOOMER: Helo.
(SIGHING)
I still can't get used to this.
Well, you're a hero of the Cylon now.
You're our first celebrity.
No, I'm just another Six.
You're too modest. I'm just another Three,
and they're Fives and, oh, Eights.
But you? Everyone calls you Caprica Six,
like you're the only Six on the planet.
And what you did was incredibly difficult.
To seduce a man
so emotionally and physically,
so that he grants you access
to all the most closely
guarded secrets of his people.
I mean, that mission could be
profoundly disturbing.
Disturbing?
She mean sleeping with me
or killing billions of people?
Because I rather thought
you enjoyed sleeping with me.
It was difficult at times.
See, nobody here can possibly understand
what you've been through,
which is why we need your help.
There's another Cylon
who's been having trouble reintegrating
after a download.
Another hero, actually.
An Eight still insists
on calling herself Sharon.
And you thought I could help?
I'm still having...
I'm having problems of my own.
Caprica, you don't understand.
She really needs your help.
If we don't turn her around soon,
there's talk of boxing her.
Putting her memories in cold storage?
You can't be serious!
Well, that's a charming way to deal
with emotional problems.
One might almost call it inhuman.
Oh, that's right, you are.
All right, look, it is a last resort.
But she's been regressing.
Please.
She's living up there in that apartment.
It's the one she had
when she thought she was human.
Security's minimal.
Two Centurions patrol out front.
The third bullet-head walks the perimeter.
The bullet-head walking perimeter makes
random changes to his patrol.
Be tough to get past him.
All right, so we go under them.
The storm drain leads directly to the garage
underneath the cafe.
There'll be dozens of skin jobs inside.
HELO: She's not breathing!
COTTLE: Suction it.
ISHAY: Right away, doctor.
What's going on? Where are you taking her?
Her lungs aren't fully developed.
She needs oxygen support.
But she's alive, right? Right?
(BABY CRYING)
There's your answer.
Now, you get the hell out of here.
We've got to stop the mother bleeding,
or she's not going to make it.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
You here to kick me out?
No.
If you're here to help me
with my adjustment problems,
I can save you some time.
(GRUNTS)
This is home.
I'm not leaving.
I lived on Caprica for two years.
I knew what I was.
Pretended to be human, but I knew.
If you knew what you were and you lived
on Caprica, you know what that makes you?
A really good liar.
Start with the elephants.
These are beautiful.
Ithacan?
Hand carved.
My mother gave them to me the day I left
for the Fleet Academy.
Is this her?
Supposed to be.
Of course, none of it's real.
All fabricated for my mission.
It's all a lie.
Following God's path is never easy.
Oh, don't go religious with this one.
What are you thinking?
Do you think I care about your God?
Look, God loves you.
This is love.
These people love me. I love them.
I didn't pretend to feel something
so I could screw people over.
I loved them. And then I betrayed them.
I shot a man I love.
Frakked over another man,
ruined his life. And why?
Because I'm a lying machine!
I'm a frakking Cylon!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
I've got bandages in the head.
Nicely done. You timed it perfectly.
BALTAR: Scratch your face
with the side of your fingernail
the moment the glass hits the wall.
(DOOR OPENING)
Never saw a Cylon show fear before,
especially the Sixes.
They're usually so hardcore.
Feign fear and emotional vulnerability.
You're very good, you know.
But I'm better. Let me help you.
I'm different.
I'm more like you.
I had someone I met here. A man.
I loved him and I think he could've
loved me eventually.
Half a cigarette should give us two
or three minutes to get the frak out of there.
Any longer and we risk
them finding the charges before they go off.
Is it two minutes or three?
About to find out.
This is a risky operation
just to nail a couple of dozen skin jobs.
You know, we can't kill them.
They'll just download into a new body, and...
I mean, what's the point?
That skin job with Starbuck,
Sharon, they called her,
she said that when they download,
they remember everything,
right up until the end.
These skin jobs are gonna remember
being blown into tiny little pieces.
That's gotta hurt.
Yeah. I hope it hurts a lot.
Because sooner or later
the message sinks in. There is no safe place,
not even a cafe.
So if you want to quit living through hell
and dying over and over again,
then get the frak off our planet.
Three minutes, 10 seconds.
Boom.
NO. 6: His house was on a bluff over a lake.
I always loved the view.
The sunlight on the water.
It's my favourite spot in the universe.
Yes, magical.
Too bad you nuked it.
After I downloaded,
I went back to the ruins of his house.
Why?
Like you, I was looking for some sort
of connection to him.
Found a few of his things,
even held on to them for a while,
but I realised they were keeping me
from truly embracing my new life.
BOOMER: So, what did you do with them?
I burned them.
But I felt liberated.
Yeah, it's a beautiful story, isn't it?
A shame it's all a pack of lies.
So, who was he? This man you loved?
Maybe you've heard of him.
Gaius Baltar.
Doctor Baltar?
Yeah.
He gave you access
to the Colonial defence grid?
He was the one who betrayed us?
"Us." Oh, I love it.
This one thinks
she's more human than Cylon.
Just like someone else I know.
Does he still work for the Cylons?
What?
On Galactica?
He's...
He's alive?
He's the Vice President of the Colonies.
You didn't know that?
If the baby does survive, the question is,
what do we do with it?
Do?
What are you suggesting?
That we throw it out of an airlock?
I don't make suggestions, Mr Baltar.
If I want to toss a baby
out an airlock, I'd say so.
Well, it's really gratifying
to know that infanticide is not on the table.
Do I have to point out
that this is not a baby?
It's a machine.
No, it's half machine, half human.
I suggest we all keep that half in mind.
The Cylons went through
a great deal of trouble to create this thing.
It should go without saying that if it's good
for them, it's gonna be bad for us.
I completely agree.
And I take it as a given,
we can't turn it over to Sharon to raise.
That would be disastrous.
ADAMA: There's still another factor
to consider here.
There are Cylons aboard this fleet.
If they find out this thing's been born,
they're gonna make a play for it.
You can see where this is headed, Gaius.
We're gonna have to take our child.
BOOMER: Hello, Hera.
(BOOMER EXCLAIMING)
She's got quite a grip on her.
You don't like it in there, do you, Hera?
You gotta stay until your lungs get stronger.
BOOMER: Oh, she's our little girl.
We made her.
Almost makes you
want to believe in the Cylon God.
Almost.
I love you so completely.
It's clear.
Here, take these.
Let's move!
Here you go.
Why do you think they kept it from you?
Is the wrong question.
The right question is,
why did she get me to work with you,
knowing that you'd tell me the truth?
She knew I had feelings for Gaius.
Knew that I had trouble letting go of him.
She must've known
it would trigger those feelings,
and those memories.
She's frakking with you, can't you see that?
But why?
Oh, it's so perfectly obvious.
You know,
for self-aware cybernetic life forms,
sometimes you can be unbearably obtuse.
- Oh, for God's sake!
- BALTAR: Careful.
Everything okay?
Fine.
Just talking with Sharon here.
Yeah, what about?
She asked me to move out.
Ah, you know what?
Which is what
we've been asking her for weeks.
I was kind of hoping that you'd see the light
after talking to our friend here.
She is lying, unfortunately.
She has no wish to see Sharon cured.
They're just gonna do it.
They're going to box her.
ANDERS: How many Cylons up in the cafe?
Full house. At least 40.
Three minutes, 10 seconds.
We've just made a breakthrough.
She's agreed to move out of her apartment.
Didn't you, Sharon?
Yeah.
I'm moving out of the apartment.
When?
Whenever.
What about now?
I'll help. The apartments are right upstairs.
Sure.
Let me... Let me just get some things.
Good work, Six.
Must have been some chat, huh?
Yes. We had a lot to talk about.
She's right behind you.
I know.
(TIMER BEEPING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(METALLIC FOOTSTEPS)
This is not a debate.
This child will not be raised by the Cylon,
and I cannot risk Cylon agents getting
their hands on it. I've made my decision.
What I need from you, Doctor, is your help.
Fine. I don't like it, but have it your way.
I need it immediately.
We'll have to find somebody suitable.
I have to work up a list of names.
Each of them is capable, each of them
is anonymous, and each can be trusted.
Thought of everything, haven't you?
I hope so.
Are you all right, Sharon?
(COUGHING) What happened?
Explosion.
Building came down on us.
Looks like the stairwell saved us.
Where's Six?
Her body's dead.
(GASPING) No, not yet.
Help me out here.
Would've been better
if the explosion had killed her.
There's nothing we can do about the pain
until we get out of here.
Hey, Six, I can get a crossbeam
and put you out of your misery.
I'm not gonna give up on life again.
It's your choice.
(GROANING)
(SCREAMS)
D'ANNA: Where the heck are we, anyway?
Must be in the garage.
The north entrance might be that way.
Then I'm gonna start digging.
(GRUNTING)
Hang in there.
(NO. 6 PANTING)
(GROANING)
BOOMER: You're gonna be okay.
Another survivor.
Yeah.
Hang on, buddy.
We'll get you out.
Fresh air coming from down there.
(ANDERS COUGHING)
Thanks. I thought I was a goner.
Frakking human.
You know, he probably set that explosion.
What, from the Resistance? Why?
No military value to the cafe.
Humans don't respect life the way we do.
No!
I won't let you kill him.
She's right.
Don't kill him.
Why not?
Hmm.
Why not kill him?
You've already killed billions of people.
Do you honestly believe
one more body's gonna weigh any heavier
on your conscience?
Which is something that you don't have.
Do you?
We should interrogate him.
Find his accomplices.
Okay.
You can let go now, Sharon.
What's this?
BOOMER: Looks like Colonial Fleet ID.
"Thrace, Kara."
Starbuck?
She was on Caprica a couple of weeks ago.
She escaped with the help
of another Sharon.
If she gave him this,
he meant something to her.
Well, ain't it sweet?
BALTAR: You have it in your hand.
Hard, physical proof
of one person's love for another.
If only you felt this deeply about us.
I did.
I do.
I love you, Gaius.
Where's the tangible proof?
HELO: I don't understand.
She was doing so well.
COTTLE: Oh, no, she wasn't.
I tried to tell you that.
Her lungs were never fully developed.
She finally went into respiratory distress.
We couldn't get her intubated
in time and we lost her.
I'm sorry.
(SOBBING) I should have been here.
(BOOMER CRYING)
HELO: Sharon, you need sleep, okay?
You've lost a lot of blood.
You murdered her.
Sharon, come on.
Who ordered it?
Adama? The President? Who?
I don't kill patients.
We did the best we could.
But she's dead.
And that's all there is to it.
I should be able to release the ashes
to you in a few hours.
Murderer.
- HELO: Sharon! Sharon.
- Die!
(BOOMER SCREAMING)
BOOMER: You're all murderers!
- MAN: Stay back!
- You're all murderers!
Get her out of here!
Easy! Easy! Easy!
(BOOMER SCREAMING)
You let them murder our child.
I am so sorry.
I tried. I tried my best.
God's will was that our child should survive.
His will was that she would
lead the next generation of God's children.
His will was that you would protect her.
Yes.
Listen, you have committed a monstrous
and unforgivable sin.
And now you and your entire wretched race
are gonna suffer God's vengeance.
She's so beautiful.
(BABY GURGLING)
I don't know how to thank you.
When I lost my baby,
I didn't know how I could go on.
Well, I'm glad things worked out for you
and this little girl.
I can't believe somebody would give up
this little angel.
You understand, Maya,
that this adoption requires absolute secrecy.
The mother is a Pegasus officer
and must remain anonymous
for political and religious reasons.
You have my word.
Maya, you won't mind
if I drop in occasionally?
Oh, of course not.
Good.
Go.
Thank you.
I know how awful this was for you,
but trust me, it was imperative.
As far as the Cylons know,
this child no longer exists.
That is a good, good thing.
(GROANING)
Is this what you're looking for?
You can have it.
Here.
What're you doing?
Just making it easy for him
to get what he wants.
Come on. I'll give you a head start.
I'm fine where I am.
(CRASHING)
Hey, they're coming for us and you.
They'll be very interested in you.
Leave him alone.
Sharon,
you're a hero of the Cylon.
Now you're just a broken machine
who thinks she's a human.
But you're not a human, Sharon,
and you never will be.
Yeah, well, at least I'm not a murderer.
I have a conscience.
And I know the difference
between right and wrong.
A murderer is exactly what you are.
Life is short, but the next one's not.
Let your heart adrift
and your soul will get caught.
I love you, Gaius.
My heart and soul are yours.
(CRASHING)
They're nearly here.
You know why they wanted you
to work with Sharon?
So you'd lose your mind.
They're gonna box you, darling.
Just like they're gonna box Sharon.
We're dangerous.
What?
Sharon and I.
We're celebrities in a culture based on unity.
No.
Our voices count. More than hers.
More than others'.
We're two heroes of the Cylon, right?
Two heroes with different perspectives
on the war.
Perspectives based on our love
of two human beings.
(SNIFFLING)
That's why she wanted me to work with you,
so that you'd tell me
that Gaius was still alive.
And she wanted me to lose my mind.
No, you're corrupted by your experiences.
D'ANNA: You're a waste.
Believe the lies,
ignore the truth.
Listen to me, I will show you the proof.
Speak from your heart.
Say the things that you know to be true.
Genocide,
murder, vengeance,
they're all sins in the eyes of God.
That's what you and I know.
That's what they don't wanna hear.
Because then they'd have
to rethink what they're doing.
They'd have to consider that maybe
the slaughter of mankind was a mistake!
(CRASHING)
God loves me.
We'll see you again soon!
Here.
Looks like they're almost here.
You should get out of here while you can.
The fresh air coming in might lead you out.
Is this some kind of trick?
You can stay and be tortured if you want.
Your call.
(JACKHAMMERING)
Who are you? What kind of people are you?
I don't know.
BOOMER: Hey, wait.
How long till she downloads
and tells them what happened?
We had a lot of people in the cafe.
At least 36 hours till they get to her.
Long enough.
Long enough for what?
To change things for the better.
What are you talking about?
I have never loved anyone more in my life
than I love you now.
(JACKHAMMERING)
Our people need a new beginning.
A new way to live in God's love.
Without hate.
Without all the lies.
All they need is
for someone to show them the way.
Someone like two heroes of the Cylons.
(JACKHAMMERING)
I'm with you.
(RUMBLING)
DORAL: We found them!
They're alive!
Yes, we are!
We're alive.