-♪ He's Orange,
he has a lot of friends ♪
♪ They live together
on a fruit stand ♪
♪ They have adventures
all across the land ♪
♪ And even play in a
rock and roll band ♪
♪ He's Orange ♪
♪ Annoying Orange ♪
[Orange laughs]
-Captain's log of
the USS Fruiterprise,
a fruit cart on a peaceful
and weird mission
to sell fruit
throughout the galaxy.
[sparks flying]
[lasers spewing]
Officers, report.
-Weapon systems are down.
-We can't outrun them.
-Maybe not, but we can do this:
nya-nya-nya-nya,
nya-nya-nya-nya-nya-nya.
[crash!]
Huh. I thought that would help.
-We've lost another thruster!
-Engine room, what's going on?
-[coughing hysterically]
Everything's fine down here!
There's a little bit of smoke,
but besides that...
everything's fine.
-Captain, we're getting
a transmission-type thingy
on the picture-maker.
-This is Commander Broccoli
of the Starship Cruciferous.
You cannot escape. Surrender!
And I shall be merciful.
-Merciful?
I thought you said
your name was Broccoli. [laughs]
-That's so stupid.
I'm rescinding.
You hear me? Rescinding!
-Can I call you Rescindy
for short? [laughs]
-Give up. You have
until the count of ten.
One... two...
-19. 7. 86.
-87... 88... no, wait.
Aah! Stop doing that.
I lost count.
-Hey! Hey, Commander Rescindy!
-That's not my name, but what?
-Light speed!
[laughs]
I said, "light speed"!
Guys, take us to light speed.
-We don't have that.
-Warp speed?
-We don't have that either.
-Fruit speed! Fruit speed!
-What's "fruit speed"?
-It's what I just did.
[laughs rather nervously]
-Right. I'll destroy you now.
Bye-bye.
Veggies rule! Et cetera.
[laser blasts]
[ship zooming]
-(Midget Apple)
Aah! Whoa!!
-Ensign Marshmallow,
what's your outlook?
-Sunny and mild with 100% chance
of rainbows and happiness!
Whee!
[fruit screaming]
[crash!!!]
[ship creaks]
-Whoa!
Looks like we landed in some
weird little girl's imagination.
[rustling]
-I don't like the looks of this.
-(Pear) Just remember:
we come in peace.
[boing! boing! boing!]
-Aah! Alien monster!
Set blasters to "destroy."
-Orange, no! It's just a bunny.
-Oh.
So no blasters?
-Only if it has rabies.
Intergalactic rules.
-Aw, drat.
Once again,
our federation's laws
vex our innate desire to
commit random acts of violence.
-Why do you sound so smart?
-I'm a starship captain!
Can't you tell by these
goofy uniforms? [laughs]
-Hey! Look, guys! A unicorn!
[sparkling]
-(Marshmallow)
Pink bunnies?
[unicorn whinnies]
Unicorns?
A caramel lake
and candy forest?!
This is no alien planet;
this is my home!
-Huh?
I thought you were from Detroit.
-Yep. The city of Detroit
on the planet Marshmalia. Yay!
-[coughs hysterically]
I did it!
-You fixed the engine?
-No!
I made this sweet lanyard
out of the mainframe wiring.
-How does that help anything?
-Uh... dang it, Orange. I'm a
fruit seller, not a doctor.
-What?
-I inhaled a lot
of engine smoke.
-That explains it.
Now get back in there
and make her space-worthy.
-The lanyard?
Oh, right! The ship! Right!
[monstrous growl]
-[whimpers]
What's that?
-It's the
Big Rock Candy Monster.
He's been trying to destroy
Marshmalia for centuries.
-Who could possibly
want to do anything
but hug this magical place?
-The Big Rock Candy Monster's
jealous.
See, a long time ago,
the main ingredient in s'mores
was rock candy.
-[crunches, screams]
-(Marshmallow) People thought
campfire desserts were ruined.
Then marshmallow stepped in
and saved the day!
-[squishes]
Mm-mm-mm! [wink!]
-The market for rock candy
was decimated.
The Big Rock Candy Monster
blamed my people
and vowed revenge,
but he's yet to succeed.
-Maybe he's just too sweet,
'cause he's candy. [laughs]
-[groans deeply]
-He can't destroy Marshmalia
because marshmallows
have the gooey power
of love on our sides,
and love always wins! Yay!
-See, Apple? Be more like that
and people might like you.
-[blandly]:
Yeah, okay, I'll do that.
-[chomps]
-Give it back, jerk!
-[baritone voice]:
Be prepared for anything.
I saw the alien ship
land right around here.
Winky?
-Father!
-My child has returned.
It's a miracle, a sign from the
great marshmallow in the sky.
-Actually, it's on account of
some evil space vegetables,
but close.
-So,
think you can hang for a minute?
-At least till our
ship is repaired.
-Peabo, Freundlich, Hector,
alert the others.
To celebrate by child's
highly coincidental
return to his homeland
and to welcome his friends,
we shall hold a three-day
feast in their honor!
[marshmallows and Orange cheer]
-Good, 'cause that's exactly
how long it's gonna take for me
to stitch these lanyards
back into the mainframe.
Oh hey, can you get me some
buffet while you're out there?
Thanks.
-♪ All the shorties in the
club, let me see you just ♪
♪ Back it up, drop it down,
let me see you just ♪
-Word up, Marshmalia.
We gonna funk it up tonight
and then tomorrow
and also the next day,
'cause a three-day festival
is how we do!
-♪ Let me see you just
wobble baby ♪
♪ Wobble baby, wobble baby,
wobble, yeah ♪
wobble baby, wobble, yeah ♪
[marshmallows cheer]
-I'm warning you guys,
cut it out.
-You guys really do it up right.
-This is amazing,
King Marshmallow.
-We do like to get our party on.
-Hey Marshmallow, why'd you ever
leave this magical place?
-Oh, I had to go.
-Because... you killed a man?
-Hehehe, no.
I had to follow my dream
of becoming an actor
on a web-based
Internet comedy series.
-[laughs]
Good luck with that.
[record scratches]
-Aah! It tickles! It tickles!
[laughs]
-What the? What joker brought
fire to a marshmallow party?
-This joker.
[stomp! stomp!]
[rocks rattle]
-(Marshmallow) It's the
Big Rock Candy Monster! Yay!
-Not yay. Boo! Boo!!!
I'm mean.
[flames whoosh,
marshmallows cheer and bounce]
I love the smell of burning
gelatin in the morning.
[grumbling laugh]
-Okay, first of all,
it's not morning.
And second, for a candy monster,
you're not sweet at all.
-He's awful.
-[laughing]
Our heads are hot!
-Stop enjoying your own demise!
-That's how we dooo.
Marshmallows,
to your battle stations.
[marshmallows cheering]
-Jelly cannons?
-We're a peaceful people. Yay!
-[grunts]
-[chuckles]
-Yeah!
-[firing]
-(marshmallows)
Yay!
[stomp!]
-[chuckles evilly]
-Guys, we should help!
Set blasters to "candy."
-Yeah, let's light up
that dream killer!
-Captain, we can't. We're on a
peaceful mission, remember?
-She's right. Intergalactic law
doesn't allow us
to interfere
with regional conflicts.
-Dang it! Oh, well.
I guess we'll just sit back
and enjoy the show.
[marshmallows cheering,
unicorn whinnies]
-(burning marshmallow)
It tickles! [laughs]
-Father, we're taking
heavy casualties.
Shall we send in reinforcements?
Yay!
-There aren't any, Winky. Things
have changes since you left.
The Candy Monster has destroyed
most of our villages,
townships, suburbs, and even
that sad little trailer park
out by Caramel Lake.
[banjo plays]
We can't hold him off
much longer.
Soon all of Marshmalia
will be gone, I fear.
But we're going to party until
the end 'cause that's how we do.
-It's how we do!
-DJ Princess Buttercup, kick out
the end-of-the-world jams!
-Don't mind if I do!
-[laughs sinisterly]
Soon I shall destroy
the last of you,
and then rock candy will become
the main ingredient in s'mores
and other
marshmallow-based desserts,
like marshmallow cookie pies
and... some other things.
-[singsong]: Thanks for
laying out your entire plan!
-I said that out loud? Shoot!
It's a terrible affectation.
-Maybe we can help you guys.
-We can't.
Intergalactic law says...
-Apple,
you're past your sell-by date.
Pear, Passion,
check the intergalactic bylaws
for a workaround.
-The only way we can
interfere in regional affairs
is if one of crew
was harmed in the conflict.
[boom!]
-(Apple) Ow!
-(Orange)
Well, that's good enough for me.
Now fire!
[blasters whirring]
-[chuckles]
-Captain, our weapons are useless.
They're bouncin' off his skin.
It's like a reflective surface.
-[laughs evilly] Your pathetic
laser weapons can't defeat me,
unless they can heat my body
to a consistent temperature
and boil me down to liquid
sugar, which they can't.
[grumbles]
Oh, said it out loud again!
-Guys, I've got a crazy plan.
Marshmallow, what's
the boiling point of caramel?
-Really hot.
-Midget Apple, can you swim?
-LITTLE Apple can bob.
-[chuckles]
-Okay, Bob, get swimmin'.
[laughs]
[Nerville grunts,
Midget Apple screams]
-Hey, Candy Man!
Here's a little peace offering!
Come and get it!
-[grunting]
-(Midget Apple) Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa! Pull!
-Now!
[Nerville grunts,
Midget Apple screams]
-What the? I'm stuck.
Did I say that out loud?
-Yeah. You kinda did.
[lasers whirring]
-Boiling caramel? Oh, that will
melt me to a sugary morass!
Gah! There I go!
Giving away my secrets again.
-Hey!
Hey, Big Rock Candy Monster!
You're cooked!
[laughs]
-[burbling]
[marshmallows cheering]
-(marshmallow) Yay!
All hail Orange! We're saved!
-I can't thank you fruits enough
for saving our world
from that horrible monster.
-No problem, Your Kingship.
Glad to help "sweeten"
things up. [laughs]
-So long, Father!
See you next time we happen
to crash-land here! Yay!
-Will do, Winky! Yay!
-Nerville, we good to go?
-[Jamaican accent]:
Yeah, mon. We be ready, mon.
-Thanks, Captain Orange.
-(marshmallow)
Good-bye! We'll miss you!
[ship blasts off]
-Unicorn Princess DJ Buttercup,
play these fruit heroes out
with some crunchy beats! Yes.
-That is how I dooo!
[marshmallows cheering]
Captioned by StreamCaptions.com
-♪ Ooh, oh! Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, oh! Ooh ♪
♪ Wobble baby, wobble baby ♪
♪ Wobble baby, wobble, yeah ♪
♪ Get in there! ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah! ♪
♪ Yeah! Yeah! ♪
♪ Get in there! ♪