1x01: Downsizing
All right Jim your quarterlies look very good.
How are things going at the library?
Oh I told you couldn't close it.
So you've come to the master for guidance?
Is this what you'e saying "grasshopper"?
Actually you called me in here, but yeah.
All right, well let me show you how it's done.
Yes, I'd like to speak to your office manager please?
Yes hello this is Michael Scott, I am the regional manager
of Dundler Mifflin paper products.
Just wanted to talk to you manager on manager.
All right done deal, thank you very much sir.
You're a gentleman and a scholar.
Oh I'm sorry, ok, sorry, my mistake.
That was a woman I was talking to...
she had a very low voice.
Probably a smoker.
So that's the way it's done.
I've been in Dundler Mifflin for twelve years,
the last four as regional manager..
If you want to come through here..
We have the entire floor.
So this is my kingdom, as far as the eye can see.
Ah, this is our receptionist Pam.
Pam, Pam Pam! Pam Beesly.
Pam has been with us for?
Forever, right Pam?
Well, I don't know..
If you think she's cute now
you should have seen her a couple of years ago!
What?
Any messages?
Yeah, just a fax
Pam this is from Corporate.
How many times have I told you that there's
a special filing cabinet for things from Corporate.
You haven't told me!
It's called the wastepaper basket.
Look at that !
Look at that face!
People say I'm the best boss.
They go, "God we've never worked in a place like this before,
you're hilarious, and you get the best out of us."
I think that pretty much sums it up.
I found it at Spencer Gifts.
My job is to speak to clients
on the phone about quantities
and type of copier paper.
You know, whether we can supply to them
whether they can pay for it and...
I'm boring myself just talking about this.
He still loves that after seven years!
What?
Nothing
Ok, all right. See you later
All right, take care.
Back to work.
Corporate really doesn't interfere with me at all, Jan Levinson-Gould
Jan, hello!
I call her Hillary Rodham Clinton, right?
Not to her face because,
not because I'm scared of her, because I'm not
but...
yeah.
All right, was it anything you wanted to add to the agenda?
Me no get an agenda.
I'm sorry, what?
I didn't get any agenda.
Well I faxed one over to you this morning.
Really? Cause I didn't.. Uh, did we get a fax this morning?
Yeah, the one?
Why isn't it in my hand?
Because a company runs on efficiency of communication, right?
So what's the problem Pam, why I didn't I get it?
You put it in the garbage can that was a special filing cabinet.
Yeah, that was a joke, that was actually my brother's,
it was supposed to be with bills and doesn't work great with faxes.
Do you want to look at mine?
Yeah. Thank you.
Ok since the last meeting, Alan and the board have decided
that we can't justify Scranton branch and the Stafford branch
Oh ok?
No, Michael don't panic
No no no no this is good, this is fine
Michael listen, don't panic
We haven't made any decisions yet,
I've spoken to Joshua in Stanford, I've told him the same as you
and it's up to either you or him to convince me that your branch can incorporate the other
Ok no problem
This does however mean that there is going to be downsizing
Me no wanna hear that Jan,
because downsizing is a bitch,
it is a real bitch,
and I wouldn't wish that on Joshua's men,
I certainly wouldn't wish it on my men,
or women. Present company excluded...sorry.
is Josh concerned about downsizing himself?
Not downsizing himself but is he concerned about downsizing?
Question: how long do we have to ?
Oh, Todd Packer, terrific rep, do you mind if I take it?
No, go ahead.
Pac man!
Hey, you big queen.
Oh, that's not appropriate..
Hey, coming in today?
I don't know what you mean
Look, I've been meaning to ask you one question
Does the curtain match the drapes?
Oh my god!
That's so horrifying! Horrible
Horrible person!
So do you think we can keep a lid on this for now I don't want to worry people unnecessarily.
No, absolutely. Under this regime, it will not leave this office.
So what does downsizing actually mean?
Well
You guys gotta update your resume, just like I'm doing.
I bet it's gonna be me, probably.
Yeah, it'll be you
I have an important question for you.
Yes
Are you going to Angela's keg party on Sunday?
Yeah, stop. That's ridiculous.
Am I gonna tell them? No I'm not going to tell them, I don't see the point of that.
As a doctor you would not tell a patient if they had cancer.
This is Mister Scott.
Ryan Howard from the temp agency.
Ted Nickels sent me down to start today
Howard, like Moe Howard, Three Stooges?
Right here, my vibe. Oh Pam, that's a guy thing Pam.
I'm sort of a student of comedy
I'm Hitler, Adolph Hitler
I don't think it would be the worst thing if they let me go.
Because then I might
It's just, I don't think it's many little girls' dream to be a receptionist.
I like to do illustrations,
mostly water color, a few oil pencil.
Jim thinks they're good.
Dundler Mifflin this is Pam.
Sure, Mr. Davis, let me call you right back.
Yeah, some just came up, two minutes. Thank you very much.
Dwight, what are you doing?
- What?
- What are you doing?
Just clearing my desk, I can’t concentrate
- It's not on your desk.
- It's overlapping.
It's all coming over the edge.
One word, two syllables : demarcation.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
Safety violation, I could fall and pierce, and organ.
We'll see
This is why the whole downsizing thing just doesn't bother me.
Downsizing?
I have no problem with that. I have been recommending downsizing since Halpert got here
even brought it up on my interview.
I say, bring it on!
You just still have messages for yesterday. Relax everything is under control
Yeah, yeah, yeah oh that's important, right.
Oh, this is so important, I should run to answer it.
What?
Come on. Six million dollars man, Steve Austin,
actually that would be a good salary for me don't you think? Six million dollars?
Memo to Jan: I deserve a raise
Don't we all?
I'm sorry?
There's nothing!
If you are unhappy with your compensation, maybe you should take it up with HR,
ok? Not today, ok? Pam just, be professional.
I think I'm a role model here, I think I garner other people's respect.
Attention on Dundler Mifflin employees, please we have a meeting in the conference room ASAP
People I respect, heros of mine, would be Bob Hope,
Abraham Lincoln, definitely,
Bono,
and probably God be the fourth one.
And I just think all those people really helped the world, in so many ways,
that it's, it's really beyond words.
It's really uncalculable.
Now, I know there's some rumors out there, and
I just kind want to see?
I'm the assistant regional manager, I should know first.
Assistant to the regional manager.
Ok. Can you just tell me please?
Just a whisper in my ear.
I’m about to tell everybody.
I'm just about to tell exeryone
Please, ok.
Do you want me to tell them?
You don't know what it is!
Can you tell them, with my permission?
I don't need your...
Permission granted. Go ahead
Corporate has deemed it appropriate to enforce an ultimatum upon me,
and Jan is thinking about downsizing either the Stanford branch or this branch.
I heard they might be closing this branch down,
That's just...
That's just the rumor going around
this is my first day I don't really know.
Yeah, but Michael what if they downsize here?
Not gonna happen
It could be out of your hands, Michael
It won't be out of my hands, Stanley, ok?
I promise you that.
Can you promise that?
On his mother's grave.
Well yeah it is a promise, and frankly I'm a little bit insulted that you have to keep asking about it.
It's just that we need to know
Hold on a second, I think Pam wanted to say something, Pam?
You had a look that you wanted to ask a question, just then?
I was in the meeting with Jan and she did said that it could be this branch that gets the axe.
Are you sure about that?
Pam? Maybe you should stick to the ongoing confidentiality agreement of meetings.
Pam, information is power.
So you can't say for sure whether it's gotta to be us or them.
No no, no Stanley, no you did not see me in there with her.
I said, if corporate wants to come in here, and interfere
then they're gonna have to go through me, right?
You know, you can go a mess with Josh's people,
but I'm the head of this family,
and you ain't gonna be messing with my children.
If I left, what would I do with all this useless information in my head?
You know, tonnage price of minal folders?
Pam's favorite flavor of yogurt, which is mix berry.
Jim said mix berries?
Yeah he's under me
Watch out for this guy Dwight Schrute in the building!
This is Ryan, the new temp.
Nice to meet you.
Introduce yourself, be polite
Dwight Schrute, Assistant Regional Manager.
Assistant to the Regional Manager.
So Dwight tell him about the kung fu, and the car and everything.
Yeah, I got a '78 28Z, I bought her for 1200, fixed it up, now worth three grand.
That is his profit!
New engine, suspension.. I've got some photos
Damn it!
Ok, hold on,
Judge is in cession. What is the problem here?
He put my stuff in jello again.
That's rough professional, thanks
That's the third time and it wasn't funny the first time.
It's ok here, but people somehow are taking advantage because it's so relaxed.
I'm a volunteer sheriff's deputy on the weekends,
and you cannot screw around there.
It's one of the rules.
What is that?
That's my stapler.
No no no, do not take it out!
You have to eat it out there,
because there are starving people in the world,
and which I hate, and it is a waste of that kind of food.
Ok, you know what? You can be a witness.
Can you reprimand him please?
- How do you know it was me?
- It's always you.
- Are you gonna discipline him or not?
Ooh discipline, kinky!
All right, here's the deal you guys
the thing about practical jokes, is that you have to know when to start, as well as when to stop!
And yeah, Jim, now is the time to stop putting Dwight's personal effects into jello.
Ok, Dwight I'm sorry because, I've always been your biggest "flan"
Nice, that's the way it is around here
You should have put him in custard-y!
Yes, new guy!
He scores !
Ok that's great, I guess,
what I'm most concerned with is...
damage to company property.
That's all.
Pudding?
I’m trying to think, another desert to do.
Do you like to going out at the end of a week for a drink?
Yeah!
Oh, that's why we all going out, so we can have an end of the week drink!
well then when are we going out?
I don’t know, tonight, hopefully.
Ok, yeah.
Hey man!
Hey!
What's going on?
Hey baby!
Roy is my fianc? we’ve been engaged about...
about 3 years, and we were supposed to get married in September,
but I think we’ll gonna get married in next spring
Do you mind if I go out for a drink with these guys?
No, come on. Let's get out of here and go home.
Ok, I will be out in a few minutes so it’s lame
twenty past five I’ve still to do my faxes.
You know you should come with us,
because you know we are going out and it could be a good chance for you to
see what people are like outside the office, I think it could be fun
No, it sounds good but seriously we gotta get going
Yeah
What's in the bag?
Just tell her i'll talk to her then
No definitely all right dude awesome, we’ll do
Do I think I'll be invited to the wedding?
So, have you felt the vibe yet?
We work hard, we play hard.
Sometimes we play hard when we should be working hard, right?
I guess the atmosphere that I've created here is that I am a friend first,
and a boss second.
Probably an entertainer third.
Just a second
Right?
Oh, hey, do you like the Jamie Kennedy Experiment?
Yeah.
"Punk'd", and all that kind of stuff?
You are going to be my accomplice, just go along with that ok?
All right
Just follow my lead, don't pimp me all right?
Come in!
So corporate just said that I don want to..
You got a fax
Oh, thank you Pam.
Pam? Can you come in here for a sec?
Just have a seat, I was gonna call
you in anyway, you know Ryan?
As you know, there is going to be downsizing
and you have made my life so much easier,
in that I'm going to have to let you go first
What? Why?
Why? Well, theft, and stealing
Stealing?
What am I suppose to have stolen?
Post-It notes.
Post-It notes...?
What are those worth, like 50 cents?
You steal a thousand Post-It notes at 50 cents a piece,
then you know you’ve made a profit margin.
Gonna run us out of business, Pam.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
I can't believe this, I mean,
I have never even stolen as much as a paper clip and you're firing me.
And the best thing about it is that
we are not gonna have to give you any severance pay,
because that is gross misconduct, and..
just clean out your desk. I'm sorry.
You're been just "Punk'd"!
Surprise it's a joke, we were joking around, you see?
Ok, he was in on he was my accomplice and
it was just kind of a morale booster thing, and
we were showing the new guy around kind of, to give him the feel for the place, so?..
God, you were.. we totally got you?
You're a jerk!
Well, I don't  know about that
What is the most important thing for a company?
Is it the cash flow? Is it the inventory?
No it's the people.
The "people".
My proudest moment here was not when I increased profits by 17%,
or when I cut expenses without losing a single employee.
No, no, no, no.
It was a young Guatemalan guy,
First job in the country, barely spoke English
came to me and said
"Mr Scott,
would you be the Godfather to my child?"
Didn't work out in the end. We had to let him go. He sucked.
Hey
Hey how are you?
Good I thought you were going out for a drink with?
Oh no
How's your headache?
Better, thanks.
Good
Are you
Walking out?
Yes
Yes do you wanna?
Yeah
Great, let me just
Oh Roy
Yeah, listen have a nice week-end!
Yeah definitely you too! Enjoy it
Come here
The World's Best Boss