In the far north,
after three dark months of winter...
a world is waiting...
for a trigger.
The sunshine of spring.
Starfish are the first to respond.
They race for the highest point...
and sensing changes in the water,
with the tips of their tube feet...
they spawn.
Sea cucumbers,
with only their mouths exposed,
now emerge.
They collect as many
starfish eggs as they can.
Which is quite a lot,
when you've got ten arms.
Now sea pens rise up
to claim a share.
The creatures here must grab what
they can of this annual banquet.
For the light has also set in motion
the greatest transformation of all.
Fronds of kelp, a marine alga,
rise towards the surface,
lifted by their gas-filled bladders.
Soon, a marine forest
has materialised...
teeming with life of all kinds.
These green seas
are some of the most productive,
but fiercely competitive, waters
in all the oceans.
The southern tip of Africa.
Here, two great oceans collide.
In the shallows,
fed by rich currents,
are bountiful forests of kelp.
Barely visible except
for the pulsating siphon
through which it breathes,
a common octopus,
waiting for prey to pass by.
A crab will do.
The octopus sets off in pursuit.
And then lurks...
with the patience
of an ambush hunter.
But the octopus
shares the Cape waters
with a great concentration
of other predators.
Fur seals...
and sharks.
They all eat octopus...
if they can find one.
And pyjama sharks are experts...
at hunting in the undergrowth.
Time to disappear.
But these tough-skinned
little sharks
are small enough
to reach deep into crevices.
But the octopus
is far from finished.
She slips her tentacles
into the shark's gills.
That prevents the shark
from breathing.
So, the shark has to let go.
When caught out in the open,
and vulnerable,
this octopus does something
truly extraordinary...
and never recorded before.
She disguises herself...
with a protective armour
of shells.
She's hiding... in plain sight.
The shark can sense its prey...
but the shells confuse it.
In a forest full of hungry mouths,
superior wits
allow this octopus to stay alive.
Forests of kelp flourish in
seasonal waters around the globe...
particularly along the
Pacific Coast of North America.
Here, the biggest kelps of all
grow in vast forests,
stretching for hundreds of miles.
In some places, the giant fronds
rise up to 60 metres tall.
The thickets they create
are crowded with life.
Competition here,
for space and food, is intense.
A challenging problem
for the Garibaldi fish.
He tends to his patch of seaweed,
filled with tiny creatures
that he eats.
As with most farmers,
his work never ends.
He removes snails
and any other grazers
that come to eat his algae...
no matter how big they are.
He has to deal
with pests of all kinds.
This can be the worst of them -
sea urchins that can scrape off
every vestige of algae from a rock.
Its spines are needle-sharp.
Somehow, the Garibaldi
must remove it.
But the problem with sea urchins...
is that they just keep coming.
When evening arrives
and the light fades, he has to stop.
He not only needs a rest,
he needs to hide.
Because at night, predators prowl
through these forests.
A torpedo ray,
capable of stunning its victim
with 45 volts of electricity.
While the Garibaldi hides...
the urchins
can feed without interruption.
The light returns...
and he finds his farm is
once again under attack.
Urchins, like locusts,
have the ability to swarm.
And this can be disastrous,
not just for the Garibaldi,
but for the kelp forest itself.
All the vegetation
is now under attack.
The urchins move through the forest,
cutting through the kelp fronds
and leaving behind vast barrens.
These urchin armies
have felled many kelp forests
along the Pacific Coast
of North America.
But help is at hand.
Sea otters.
All other kinds of otters
spend much of their lives on land,
but sea otters
rarely leave the water.
At first, a newly-born pup
is not a very good swimmer,
so its mother spends hours
grooming its fur to make it buoyant.
But to provide her youngster
with milk and keep herself warm,
she must eat up to 30%
of her body weight every day.
She does that by eating shellfish.
And urchins are among a sea otter's
favourite delicacies.
In the past, sea otters were hunted
so intensively for their fur
that they came close to extinction.
With them gone, many kelp forests
were replaced with urchin barrens.
Today, sea otters are protected...
and as their numbers
slowly return,
many of the kelp forests
are recovering, too.
Now, in some remote places,
sea otters are so numerous
they assemble in huge rafts...
something that hasn't been
seen for over a century.
In the sun-drenched shallows
off Australia...
kelp is replaced by
the sea's only flowering plants,
sea grass.
The most extensive of these
marine grasslands
can stretch
for over 3,000 square miles.
All across the tropics,
they're patrolled by tiger sharks.
They can grow up
to five metres in length...
and have powerful crushing jaws.
Green turtles are their prey.
The turtles feed almost
entirely on sea grass.
A single one can consume
up to two kilos of it in a day.
But they can never rest easy.
Healthy turtles will keep well away
from an approaching shark.
And just by keeping
the turtles on the move,
the sharks prevent any one patch
of sea grass from being overgrazed.
And that has benefits for us all.
A patch of sea grass
can absorb and store
35 times as much carbon dioxide
as the same area of a rainforest.
So, the prairies and their sharks
are surprising allies
in the fight against
a warming climate.
The struggle to survive
in our green seas
can have far-reaching consequences.
Once a year, one particular meadow
in Australia is transformed.
Around the first full moon
of winter,
an army materialises.
Spider crabs.
For the past year, they've
been feeding in deeper waters.
Now they march
across the sea-grass plains.
Hundreds of thousands of them.
They clamber over one another...
creating great mounds...
nearly 100 metres long...
They're not seeking mates,
neither are they laying eggs.
They have come here in order...
to grow.
Like all crabs,
their bodies are enclosed
in a hard, un-expandable shell.
So, to grow,
they have to break out of it...
and that allows the soft one that
has developed beneath to expand.
It will take days
for the new shell to harden.
Its legs are so limp
that they won't work properly.
The crab is unprotected
and in great danger.
A smooth stingray.
It's huge - about four metres long.
It wants a soft,
freshly-moulted crab
that will be easier to eat.
The crabs try to stick together.
But now, disturbed by the ray,
they're scattering.
A newly-moulted crab
is too weak to keep up
with the crowd.
The safest place is right
in the middle of the pile.
That is why they have
all assembled here.
There is safety in numbers.
The vast majority
of the crabs escape...
and within the next few days,
they will be ready to return
to the depths
and resume their lonely wanderings
in search of food.
This is no graveyard...
but the triumph of a 100,000 crabs
successfully moulted.
The green seas of Southern Australia
are particularly rich
in such spectacular assemblies...
but most of the creatures
come together
for a very different reason.
To breed.
The giant cuttlefish,
the largest of all cuttlefish.
They live for just one or two years.
Now, as the Australian summer draws
to an end,
they have one last act to complete.
To find a mate.
But there are over 100,000 males,
competing for the arriving females
in this one bay.
Among them a giant - a true Goliath.
He probably weighs about ten kilos.
Bands of colour
sweep across his skin.
That's how cuttlefish communicate.
This smaller male
couldn't possibly take him on.
Beside Goliath,
and under his protection,
a female who has just
mated with him.
But other rivals
are still interested.
It seems a small male
wouldn't stand a chance.
The female is now displaying
a white stripe
along her side nearest Goliath.
It's a clear signal that she no
longer wants to mate with him.
It's all the encouragement
that the little male needs.
He's going to have to use trickery.
He tones down his colours
and tucks in his arms.
He's just the right size
to mimic a female.
Goliath is deceived.
The small male
now displays a white stripe,
just like the real female,
to deter his advances.
He slips beside her...
and they mate.
By mating with multiple partners...
the female ensures the greatest
genetic diversity for her young.
The sneaky male leaves,
his final act complete.
So, even among giant cuttlefish,
it seems...
it's not all about size.
Other males in these
Australian green pastures,
take greater responsibility
for their young.
A weedy sea dragon.
This is a male and he's carrying
a precious cargo.
While mating with the female,
he collected the eggs
and attached them to his underside.
Now, he's leaving these
seaweed thickets...
and travelling
into more open waters
where elaborate camouflage
is less effective.
And there are many
predators out here.
And this is what the fathers
risk their lives for.
Dense clouds of minute shrimp.
Mysids, one of a sea dragon's
favourite foods.
They're drawing other
sea dragons out here, too.
Finally, it's time
for the young to break free.
But algae has grown over
these developing eggs...
and it risks smothering them.
Nonetheless,
the babies are emerging.
They've hatched successfully.
The fathers return
to the tangle of kelp,
where they're virtually invisible...
while the young remain out here.
But they will grow quickly,
surrounded as they are
by their ideal food.
Vast numbers
of the oceans' young fish
start their lives in the green seas.
One of the richest nurseries
of all are the mangrove forests.
Fringing the coastline
of the tropics,
they form a natural protective
barrier between land and sea...
and are some of the world's
most productive forests.
Below the water,
their arching aerial roots
give them a firm footing.
Here, there's abundant food
for baby fish.
While the tangled roots protect
them from bigger fish
and other predators
that haunt the channels.
But in Northern Australia,
with the receding tide...
the little fish are forced
to leave their shelter.
And now, they are vulnerable.
It's the most deadly assassin
in the green seas.
The zebra mantis shrimp -
a male, almost 40 centimetres long.
But he's not hunting
just for himself.
He's collecting food for his mate.
She may have been his partner
for 20 years.
She relies on him
to bring her food...
and puts her energy
into her eggs instead.
In a world so full of food,
this would seem a sensible strategy.
But it's also a risky one.
Were her male to disappear,
she could starve.
Something has caught
this male's attention.
Perhaps an irresistible odour...
or a distant call.
Whatever the reason,
a male will leave his burrow
and his lifelong mate.
An even larger hole.
Females who have lost their mates
appear to send out distress signals
to call in a new male.
A larger female
will produce more eggs.
So by mating with her,
he will father more offspring.
But infidelity comes at a price.
A larger partner demands more food.
The richer a sea,
the greater the competition..
And there is one green sea
that supports more life
than all the rest combined.
Unlike the mangrove forests
and the sea-grass prairies,
its location is in the open seas
and only temporary
and unpredictable.
This greenness comes
not from rooted plants...
but from clouds of floating ones.
Billions of microscopic
phytoplankton are proliferating.
And in such numbers that they fuel
one of the greatest feasts of all.
Off America's Pacific Coast,
hundreds of common dolphins
are rushing to a banquet.
They're not the only ones homing in.
So are sea lions.
They're heading
for Monterey Bay, California,
where algal blooms have caused
an explosion
in plankton feeders.
Anchovies - millions of them.
The dolphins herd the anchovies
towards the surface.
Sea birds and sea lions take
advantage of the shoal's appearance.
It's a race to grab a share
before others arrive.
Humpback whales,
hundreds of them.
With every upward lunge,
they sieve out up to 100 kilos
of fish.
They're claiming the biggest share
of one of the biggest feasts
on Earth.
So crucial are these tiny plankton,
that almost all marine life
ultimately depends upon them.
It's the green seas, not the blue...
that are the basis of almost
all life in the world's oceans.
To capture the magnificence
of the undersea forests
and the surprising creatures living
here, the Blue Planet II team
have developed a series
of specialist camera rigs.
From the mega-dome
recording half-in-half-out shots
at the top of the towering canopy...
to state-of-the-art
time-lapse equipment
that speeds up time to reveal
the secret life of the forest floor.
But, of all the creatures
living in these forests,
filming one in the waters
off the Cape of South Africa
was to prove
the greatest challenge of all.
Naturalist Craig Foster
has developed a fascination
for its most secretive resident,
a common octopus.
There are almost 100 species
of shark in these waters,
but that doesn't deter Craig,
who's swum here every morning
for the past six years.
When you find that really small,
tiny, little oval hole,
then you know it's
been killed by an octopus.
And then if you look very,
very carefully,
they're often
in the vicinity of that.
Craig has witnessed
the antics of these octopuses
and wants to share
his remarkable discoveries
with Blue Planet cameraman
Roger Horrocks.
Roger is immediately charmed by
the strength of their personalities.
It's really been astounding to see
how individual these characters are.
The common octopus all display
different behaviours.
Some were extremely timid,
some were very, very bold,
they have variety
and it's really endeared me to them.
After weeks of filming
different individuals,
they finally meet one octopus
that's not only seemingly
unafraid of the camera,
but willing to perform for it.
She just came right up - whoop!
And then came right through
underneath the tripod
in between my legs.
Yeah, that's cool, amazing.
She very quickly just completely
accepted both of us.
So, we've actually been getting
these really intimate behaviours.
It's amazing.
I've watched this octopus
for many months,
it's just trusting us in the water,
carrying on with normal activity
which is just so fantastic.
Months later, the team finally film
their star octopus on the hunt.
But then discover the grave
consequences of sharing the forest
with so many other predators -
pyjama sharks.
Pound for pound,
these sharks are far more brazen
and aggressive than a Great White.
They're like guided missiles.
The slightest smell that octopus
gives off, that shark will find it.
The pyjama shark
actually got hold of the octopus
and, I mean,
I just assumed that was it.
After spending
so much time with this animal,
it was just so difficult
watching her get attacked.
Then, to their amazement,
she fights back!
She put her tentacles down,
you can see them coming through
the gill, basically,
closed the mouth.
The shark couldn't breathe,
and that's what enabled
her to escape.
And just witnessing
that whole thing was,
you know, it was an
incredibly intense moment.
The team are relieved by her escape.
But when caught out in the open,
her next trick astonishes them
even more.
It lifted its arms and legs
over its head,
and, at the same time,
pulled the shell material with it
and created
this extraordinary armoury.
Octopus had armoured up
and then, when that guy came
through from the back,
he could kind of smell something.
He's not seeing an octopus shape,
he's seeing that strange armoury.
Then he was bumping the octopus,
and it was just incredible
to see how that octopus
outwitted that shark
using the armour,
using all his, his knowledge,
it's just... absolutely phenomenal.
She's a rock star, man.
A proper little rock star.
Thanks to Craig's and
Roger's dedication,
the octopuses' astonishing
behaviours are now known to science.
What else might we find
as we continue to explore
these fascinating undersea forests?
Next time on Blue Planet II...
we meet the creatures that live
where two worlds collide...
and discover how they cope with
the demands
of the ever-changing coasts.