Resync by XhmikosR - www.addic7ed.com
Resync by TEDI for HDTV.x264-PLUTONiUM
Antarctica.
The coldest, the harshest and the
most remote continent on Earth.
No human being has ever descended
into the depths that surround it...
...until now.
The deep ocean is as challenging to
explore as space.
We know more about the surface of
Mars than we do about the
deepest parts of our seas.
Now we can dive these uncharted
depths to discover
what secrets lie beneath.
Sinking down beside the submerged
wall of an iceberg,
we enter an unforgiving world.
These waters are
the coldest on Earth.
As we descend into the deep, the
pressure increases relentlessly.
And the light from above
all but disappears.
Yet, incredibly...
...there is life here.
We might have expected that, deep
beneath the surface of
the polar seas, the waters would be
truly barren.
But in fact we find life here in
unimaginable abundance.
Nor is such great abundance confined
to Antarctic waters.
Currents carry this richness into
the depths of almost every ocean
around the world.
Astonishingly, in the deep sea,
there is more life than anywhere
else on Earth.
The sunlight fades
and the seas darken.
Here in the Pacific,
200 metres down,
we enter an alien world.
The Twilight Zone -
a sea of eternal gloom.
There are strange creatures here.
A pyrosome.
A tube of jelly two metres long that
dwarfs a visitor from above -
an oceanic whitetip shark.
Only a tiny amount of light filters
down this far.
Survival here means making the most
of every last glimmer.
A swordfish.
Its eyes are as big as tennis balls,
to help it see
in the perpetual dusk.
A squid,
but this is one
that lives only here.
Its right eye looks
permanently downwards.
But its left eye is much bigger and
trained upwards to detect the
silhouettes of prey
swimming nearer the surface.
No wonder it's nicknamed
"the cockeyed squid".
And even stranger.
This is barreleye...
...a fish with a transparent head
filled with jelly so that it can
look up through its skull.
We now know that the Twilight Zone
is a refuge for an incredible
90% of all fish in the ocean.
Only at night do vast shoals of
lanternfish migrate to the surface
to feed on tiny plankton.
By day, they retreat back down here.
Humboldt squid.
Two metres long
and 50 kilos in weight.
Like most squid,
they're voracious hunters.
There are hundreds of them.
They've found a shoal
of lanternfish,
hiding 800 metres down,
off the coast of South America.
Their tentacles are armed with
powerful suckers
with which they grab their prey.
And when there are no more
lanternfish to be found...
...they turn on each other.
This squid has caught a smaller one
in its tentacles.
To hide its capture from the rest,
it releases a smokescreen
of black ink.
But then an even bigger one
challenges it...
...and steals its catch.
The Twilight Zone is the Humboldt
squid's favoured hunting ground.
They seldom go deeper...
...into the world of perpetual
blackness below...
...The Midnight Zone.
Two thirds of a mile from the
surface, beyond the reach the sun.
A giant black void,
larger than all the rest of the
world's habitats combined.
There's life here...
...but not as we know it.
Alien-like creatures produce
dazzling displays of light.
Nearly all animals need to attract
mates and repel predators.
This language of light is so
widespread here that these signals
are probably the commonest
form of communication
on the entire planet.
And yet we still know
little about them.
Hunters illuminate themselves,
and by doing so
attract inquisitive prey.
This is fangtooth.
It has the largest teeth for its
size of any fish.
There are pressure sensors all over
its head and body which can detect
anything moving
in the surrounding water.
It's the Midnight Zone's
most voracious fish.
But prey use light as a distraction.
A decoy of luminous ink.
Down here, in this blackness...
...creatures live beyond
the normal rules of time.
Siphonophores are virtually eternal.
They repeatedly clone themselves...
...some eventually growing longer
than a blue whale.
Down here it snows.
Continuous clouds of organic debris
drift slowly down from above.
This is food, and a whole variety
of filter feeders depend on it.
Jellyfish...
...and delicate sea cucumbers.
The 1% of marine snow they miss
eventually settles on the sea floor.
Over millions of years
it forms a layer of mud
up to a mile thick.
It's an empty plain that covers
half the surface of our planet.
The deep sea bed
may at first appear lifeless...
...but it's home to
a unique cast of mud-dwellers.
The sea toad.
It is an ambush predator
with an enormous mouth...
...and infinite patience.
This fish has been living
for so long here
that its fins have changed
into something more useful.
Feet.
They help it shuffle about
on the sea floor.
The flapjack octopus.
It hovers just above the surface of
the mud as it delicately sifts
through it, searching for worms.
But it can jet away at
the first sign of danger.
A sixgill shark
as big as a great white.
It may not have eaten
for an entire year.
It patrols the mud plains
using a minimum amount of energy.
High above, the carcass of a huge
sperm whale is slowly decaying.
This will be a bonanza for the
creatures of the deep.
Food, 30 tonnes of it.
Finally, it settles
on the ocean floor...
...and its presence is soon detected.
Sixgill sharks have an
exceptionally acute sense of smell.
Just 25 minutes after the whale's
carcass arrives...
...a sixgill finds it.
Each bite releases blood
into the current.
The news that food is here
spreads quickly.
Two more ravenous sixgills arrive.
Within 12 hours,
there are seven enormous sharks
jostling with one another as they
compete to tear off mouthfuls.
No-one is prepared to back off.
24 hours later and a third of the
carcass has gone.
The first arrival has gorged until
it's completely full.
This single meal may be enough to
sustain it for a whole year.
Now the clean-up team arrives.
Spider crabs carrying coral
in their hind legs,
presumably as makeshift body armour.
There are rock crabs here, too.
They probably detected the carcass
almost as soon as the sharks...
...but they can't move as fast.
A month on, and over 30 species of
scavenger are clearing away the last
edible fragments.
But now the scavengers are
attracting their own predators.
Scabbardfish,
habitually swimming upright,
are picking them off one by one.
Some of the whale's teeth have been
dislodged as the skeleton starts to
fall apart.
Four months later, there is nothing
left but a few bones.
But even they are food...
...for something.
Zombie worms.
They tunnel into the bones by
injecting acid...
...and so reach the tiny amounts of
fat that still remain there.
It may take decades, but eventually
the last of the bones will crumble
and the whole 30-tonne carcass
will have been recycled.
A whale fall is a temporary oasis
in the desert of the sea floor.
But there are permanent
oases here, too.
Rocks projecting above the mud
provide anchorage
for deep-sea corals.
As far down as 3.5 miles,
there are more species of coral
in the deep
than on shallow tropical reefs.
Without sunlight,
they rely solely
on food drifting in the current.
And they grow just
a hair's breadth a year.
But some of them can live
for 4,000 years.
They, like their shallow water
relatives,
provide homes for
all kinds of other creatures.
Growing among the corals is one of
the most beautiful of sponges.
This is Venus' flower basket.
These sponges have lodgers.
Shrimps.
There are plenty of predators
on the reef,
so the shrimps are fortunate.
Both this male and female were swept
into this sponge
when they were tiny larvae,
along with the minute particles of
food on which the sponge feeds.
They found each other and have been
here ever since.
Now they're full-grown
and the female is carrying eggs.
Once hatched, the larvae will swim
out through the sponge's walls.
But the shrimps will never leave.
They can't.
They are now far too big to go out
the way they came in,
and no doubt they will live longer
here than they would
if they were wandering about on the
reef unprotected.
But how one of the simplest of all
animals, a sponge,
is able to build
such a complex structure,
to the great benefit of the
shrimps...
...is a mystery...
...and surely a marvel.
But today their timeless world is
being reduced to rubble.
As overfishing empties the
surface waters of the seas,
trawlers have started
to ransack the deep.
Now countless numbers of the reefs
that have flourished here
for millennia
lie in ruins.
Over time, organic matter on the sea
floor slowly decays...
...producing methane.
In the Gulf of Mexico
these eruptions also release
a super-salty liquid.
Brine.
Five times heavier than seawater,
it accumulates in great pools
on the sea floor.
It's difficult to make sense
of the sight.
A lake of concentrated saltwater,
15 metres deep
at the bottom of the sea.
Around its margin,
perhaps even more strangely,
there is a profusion of life.
Giant mussels, that can live and
grow for a century or more,
pack tightly together,
dwarfing the shrimps and squat
lobsters that feed around them.
Cutthroat eels, scavengers,
come to the shores of the brine lake
in search of something edible.
Some even venture into the brine.
Spending too long in it
can send an eel into toxic shock.
Its only hope is to rise above it.
It manages to escape.
Others are not so lucky.
The brine embalms their bodies...
...and the casualties of decades
accumulate around the margins.
But parts of the deep are
even more hostile.
In places, gigantic cracks stretch
for many miles
across the ocean floor...
...canyons that plunge towards the
centre of the Earth.
Scans from survey vessels make it
possible to graphically reconstruct
an image of this
vast submarine landscape.
The deepest of all,
at almost seven miles,
is the Mariana Trench
in the Pacific Ocean.
Even Mount Everest
could disappear inside it.
Down here, in these deep ravines,
it was once thought that nothing
whatever could possibly survive.
But there is life even here...
...a kind of sea slug.
A so-called "sea pig".
They, and other simple creatures,
manage to survive on the
minuscule amount of food
that drifts down here.
Like this starfish,
they can withstand pressure
equivalent of 50 jumbo jets
stacked on top of one another.
A remote camera probe reveals
the most extraordinary
discovery of all...
...the ethereal snailfish.
At five miles down,
this is the deepest living fish
so far discovered.
No-one imagined that an animal as
complex as a fish could exist
in such extreme pressures.
From the greatest depths to the
uppermost limit of
the Twilight Zone, it seems that
there is nowhere in the deep sea
where life of some kind
can't survive.
And we now think that the deep sea
may well be
where life on Earth began.
Here, in a world hidden within
the greatest geological
feature on Earth...
...running right down the middle of
the world's oceans,
an underwater mountain range,
spanning the entire globe.
The Mid-Ocean Ridge.
In the South Pacific,
the ocean floor is being torn apart.
Over three quarters of the planet's
volcanic activity
occurs in the deep...
...almost all of it along the
Mid-Ocean Ridge.
But from this titanic violence
come great riches.
Gases and scalding water gush up
through the crevices.
Minerals condensing from these jets
build up great chimneys...
hydrothermal vents.
This one, 30 metres tall,
has been named Godzilla.
Astonishingly, we now know
that they hold as much life
as tropical rainforests.
In places, half a million
individual animals
are crammed into
a single square metre.
They depend entirely for
their food on bacteria.
And THEY feed on chemicals dissolved
in the searingly hot fluid.
Crabs consume the bacterial mats
that coat their shells.
Others maintain bacterial cultures
actually within their bodies.
Shrimps carry such cultures
in their mouthparts,
but that is a strategy
fraught with danger.
To provide sustenance
for these microbes
the shrimps must dash
into the hot vents...
...and that risks being boiled alive.
In the last decade
the number of hydrothermal vents
discovered has doubled.
Every one has its own unique
character and community.
But perhaps the most important one
of all is in the Atlantic.
It has been named "The Lost City".
Within its 60-metre towers,
something truly extraordinary
is taking place.
Under extremes of pressure and
temperature, hydrocarbons -
the molecules that are the basic
component of all living things -
are being created spontaneously.
Indeed, many scientists now believe
that life on Earth may have begun
around a vent like this,
four billion years ago.
We now know that there are deep seas
on the moons of Jupiter and Saturn.
If life can exist under such
extreme conditions down here,
then surely it could exist
somewhere out there.
The team spent more than 1,000 hours
filming in the deep ocean,
mostly from the research vessel
Alucia and her twin submersibles,
Deep Rover and Nadir.
Their most ambitious mission
was to Antarctica,
hoping to film life
two thirds of a mile down,
something never attempted before.
We honestly do not know what we're
going to find down there.
We're going to a place that has
never been explored.
There could be nothing,
there could be a carpet of life,
there could be anything in between.
Who knows?
It's a huge technical challenge.
The water temperature here can reach
minus 1.8 Centigrade.
No-one knows for sure
how the subs will cope
with this extreme environment.
OK. Right, I'm going to soak it up.
OK.
Just half an hour into the very
first dive,
a puddle is forming
on the floor of the sub.
Orla confirms it's seawater.
Yeah, Roger. I'm just try to soak up
this puddle of water,
and then see if any more comes.
They must find the leak
and repair it fast.
Are you going to knock that over
my...? Yeah.
You're at 450 metres in a small
bubble and water's coming in.
That's a half an hour straight shot
back up to the surface.
You're kind of thinking about,
"Are we going to fill up with water?
And if we are, there's no way out!"
Yeah.
The sub pilots are well drilled for
emergencies.
Just pass them over. Yeah.
Ralph quickly finds the flood
and fixes it.
He made it all seem absolutely
ordinary and normal and,
"I've got this covered,
don't you worry,"
and within 20 minutes, he did.
The waters of the Antarctic Sound
are potentially rich
but also treacherous.
The Sound is ominously known as
"Iceberg Alley".
We've got to find a place where we
can get the submarines down and up
safely without any icebergs coming
along and bowling them over.
I've got a feeling it's going to be
a bit like a game of Space Invaders.
A metre cube of ice weighs a tonne.
You start sort of grinding that
around the sphere, it's delicate.
It's like a big Faberge egg.
One dive brings them right up to the
underside face of an iceberg.
There are icebergs up there that are
the size of a small car, and
then there are icebergs up there
that are the size of Hyde Park.
Enormous.
Conditions here
can change in an instant.
The captain radios down to the subs.
Yeah, Roger that.
We've currently got a couple of big
icebergs coming down
the channel, and it looks like
they're on a collision course.
The impact of two icebergs colliding
overhead is clearly heard.
That is ice.
With icebergs colliding above and
the weather turning fast,
the subs are quickly recalled.
Once again
their efforts are thwarted.
Finally, after two weeks,
conditions are just right.
Once again the team attempt their
1,000-metre dive in Iceberg Alley.
An hour after leaving the surface
they close in on their goal.
999.
Control, control.
This is Nadir
on bottom, depth -
one-zero-zero-zero metres.
Roger. Depth - 1,000 metres.
Control out. New record!
First manned sub dive
to 1,000 metres in Antarctica!
At the bottom of the ocean, at the
end of the world,
the amount of life they find is
astonishing.
But they are equally astonished
to find that,
two thirds of a mile from the
surface,
icebergs are still a danger.
Rocks can drop from them
as they melt,
and one lands
right in front of the sub.
I don't think many people who are
diving subs
ever consider big lumps of rock
landing on them.
It's, it's not your normal risk.
If it had hit the sphere,
there's a good chance it would have
put a nice scratch down it.
If something of ten, 15, 20 tonnes
had hit the sub,
it would completely destroy it.
But over the following dives
the team learns it's these
very drop stones
that enrich the Antarctic
deep sea bed,
creating firm anchor points
for life to thrive.
Proof that the only way to fully
appreciate the complexity and
abundance of life in the deep
is to go there ourselves.
Next time, we travel to bustling
coral reefs.
Here, animals must go to
extraordinary lengths
to get ahead of the competition in
these crowded cities.
Resync by XhmikosR - www.addic7ed.com
Resync by TEDI for HDTV.x264-PLUTONiUM
To find out more about our oceans
with this free poster, call...
Or go to...
...and follow the links to
the Open University.