Resync by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com
The oceans seemingly limitless,
invoke in us a sense of awe and
wonder and also sometimes fear.
They cover 70% of the surface
of our planet,
and yet they are still
the least explored.
Hidden beneath the waves
right beneath my feet,
there are creatures
beyond our imagination.
With revolutionary technology,
we can enter new worlds...
...and shine the light on behaviours
in ways that were impossible
just a generation ago.
We've also recognized
an uncomfortable fact.
The health of our ocean
is under threat.
They're changing at a faster rate
than ever before in human history.
Never has there been
a more crucial time
to reveal what is going on
beneath the surface of the seas.
In this first episode,
we will journey across the globe
from the warm waters of the tropics
to the coldest around the poles.
To bring us a new understanding
of live beneath the waves.
This is Blue Planet II.
The surface of the ocean conceals
the many creatures that live beneath
but not all.
Bottlenose dolphins.
They're extremely intelligent.
And with this intelligence
comes playfulness.
They surf.
And as far as we can tell,
they do so for the sheer joy of it.
But to properly appreciate
their true character,
you have to travel with them
into their world.
A pod of bottlenose dolphins is
visiting a coral reef in the Red Sea.
For the youngsters,
there are things to be learned here.
The adults lead a calf
to a particular bush-like coral
called a Gorgonian.
And here, the adults behave
rather strangely.
They deliberately rub themselves
through the fronds.
Their calf seems reluctant to do so.
By watching his elders,
he may be realizing that this
is something he ought to do.
Gorgonia fronds, in fact,
are covered with a mucous
that can have anti-inflammatory
and antimicrobial properties.
So maybe the adult dolphins
are doing this
to protect themselves from infection.
The dolphins' intimate knowledge
of the reef
is spurring us to search
for new medicines here, too.
Tropical coral reefs
occupy only a tenth of one percent
of the ocean floor.
But their shallow warm waters
and stable year round conditions,
support some of the most crowded
and varied communities
to be found anywhere in the oceans.
And there are new discoveries to
be made on every one of them.
One creature
on Australia's Great Barrier Reef
is challenging our understanding
of fish intelligence.
A tusk fish.
And you can see why it gets its name.
He does something few would
have believed a fish could do.
Every morning,
he travels to the edge of the reef.
He's searching
for something special to eat
amongst the coral and sand.
Here's one.
A small clam.
But how to crack it open
and get to the meat?
He takes it all the way back
to his special kitchen.
A bowl-shaped coral
that has a particular bump on
the inside that he always uses.
It's not easy if you have no hands.
Whoops.
There he goes again.
But he's got great determination
and surprising accuracy.
At last.
So here is a fish that uses tools.
Some fish are much cleverer
than you might suppose.
The density of the animals
on tropical reefs
makes competition
inevitable and extreme.
Not only for those that lived
within the reef,
but for the birds
that fly above them.
During the dry season,
over half a million terns
crowd onto this remote atoll
in the Indian Ocean.
Their chicks are still
in their dark, juvenile plumage.
They vary in age.
Whilst the more advanced chicks
take to the air,
others aren't quite ready yet.
Those just starting to learn to fly
use the shallow lagoon
that occupies the centre of the atoll
as their training ground.
It's difficult for some of them
to stay aloft for long.
Giant trevallies.
Usually, they're solitary hunters,
but about 50 of them have come here
from neighbouring reefs
attracted by this abundance
of potential prey.
The fledglings stay out of the water
if they can,
they even drink on the wing.
If the trevally are to catch one now,
they have to up their game.
So there is a fish
here that amazingly
has a brain capable of calculating
the airspeed,
altitude and trajectory of a bird.
The time comes when every fledgling
has to take to the air
and collect food for itself.
Their parents lead them
to the training grounds.
If they're to survive,
they must learn quickly.
After a month of practising
over the lagoon,
the youngsters start to leave
and take their chances
out over the open sea.
The oceans hold 97% of all the water
in the world.
As the sun warms their surface,
water evaporates.
The vapour rises into the sky
until it cools and condenses
into towering clouds.
And they generate huge storms.
The spin of the earth
deflects these storms
north and south into
cooler latitudes.
As they travel across the sea,
storm-driven winds
create huge swells.
When the swells reach
shallower waters,
they rise into gigantic waves.
In its lifetime,
a large storm can release energy
that is the equivalent
of 10,000 nuclear bombs.
These are the seasonal seas.
And when they warm in spring,
they can suddenly explode with life.
Mobula rays have gathered
in Mexico's Sea of Cortez
in vast numbers.
Why do they leap?
Is it to tell others
that they're here?
No one knows.
They feed mostly at night
for that is when vast swarms
of plankton rise from the depths.
The disturbance in the water...
stimulates many of the planktonic
creatures to luminesce.
Only now do we have the technology
to record their faint glow.
The feasting rays swim through them
creating an extraordinary ballet
of life and death.
The richness of these waters
is based on microscopic plants,
phytoplankton,
which bloom on such a massive scale
they benefit us all.
They, together with seaweeds
and seagrasses,
produce as much oxygen
as all the forests
and grassy plains on land.
Every spring off New Zealand,
the seasonal bounty
draws in rare visitors.
False killer whales.
They're relatives of the orca,
six metres long
and weighing over a tonne.
They appear to be searching
for dolphins.
And there are many
in these coastal waters.
Here, bottlenose
dolphins stick together
constantly chattering
with whistles and clicks.
Such a din carries for
miles underwater.
The false killers have detected them.
Travelling at ten knots,
the killers quickly close in on them.
But then, something truly
extraordinary happens.
The dolphins turn
as if to greet their pursuers.
They seem to change their course.
Could it be that they're attempting
to communicate?
Scientists studying
this annual encounter,
now think that individuals
may recognize one another.
Almost unbelievably,
it seems that these different species
appear to be old friends.
Together they're gathering
as one unified army
up to a thousand strong.
This formidable hunting party
now harvests the riches
that come with New Zealand's summer.
All across the higher latitudes,
seasonal seas flourish
under the summer sun.
Here in Alaska,
sea otters lounge in the canopy
of great submarine forests.
Giant kelp, the biggest seaweed of
all is home to all kinds of life.
On the forest floor, spiny
sea urchins munch through the kelp.
Elsewhere there are continuously
hungry sea cucumbers
And in the tangled undergrowth,
wonderfully camouflaged sea dragons.
In the underwater forests
of northern Japan,
the residents of this sunken wreck
are waiting for the summer temperatures
to reach 16 degrees Celsius.
That for some is the time for mating.
A kind of giant wrasse
called a Kobudai.
This is a male.
And in female terms,
he's particularly handsome.
He's a metre long and
weighs 15 kilos.
Much larger than the
diminutive female,
and he is ready to breed.
He attempts to mate with her
and with any of the dozen or so
females that live in his territory,
whenever he gets the chance.
But females from around ten years old
take little notice of his advances.
This is because when any large female
reaches a critical body size,
she can begin a dramatic
transformation.
Over just a few months,
particular enzymes inside her body
cease to work,
and male hormones start to circulate.
As time passes,
her head expands
and her chin gets longer.
A she has changed into a he.
And with this comes a change
in temperament.
The old male who rules
all the females here
is challenged to a face off.
The more bulbous the head,
the more it intimidates an opponent.
The territory has a new ruler.
Only the largest females transform
themselves in this way.
But the change enables them
to have more mates,
so they will have many more offspring
carrying their genes.
But a new male can't afford
to be complacent.
Inside the body of
every Kobudai female,
there is a new male in waiting.
The closer we travel towards the
poles, the colder the seas become.
Icebergs appear.
Huge slabs that have broken away
from glaciers that are sliding
into the sea.
And then the surface
starts to freeze.
While the lights of the aurora
play above,
even in the depths of midwinter,
there are a few places
well north of the Arctic circle
that are still open.
The fjords of northern Norway
remain ice free
because a giant current,
the Gulf Stream,
flows up here from the south
bringing warmth all the way
from the Caribbean.
And every winter,
billions of herring
come here for shelter.
And following them...
...Orca.
There are up to a thousand of them.
It's possibly the greatest gathering
of orca on the planet.
The herring maybe plentiful
but in these winding fjords
they're not always
easy to track down.
These particular orca, however,
are fish hunting specialists.
They work as a team,
coordinating their approach
by calling loudly to one another.
They herd the herring
into tighter and tighter shoals.
They swim below them,
trapping them against
the surface of the sea.
And now the orca deploy
their special weapon.
They beat their tails
with such force,
that the shock waves
stun the herring.
And then the senseless victims
are easily collected.
But all this underwater noise
attracts others.
Humpback whales.
They move in on the action.
They approach the shoal from beneath
and then lunge upwards,
gathering up to a hundred kilos
of herring in a single mouthful.
The humpbacks are
comparative newcomers.
They only started coming here
within the last decade.
But these polars seas are so rich
that there appears to be enough food
for everyone.
Nonetheless, few if
any of these riches
would be here were it not
for the Gulf Stream.
Ocean currents, in fact, are crucial
to the well being of our planet.
They distribute the sun's heat
towards the poles
all the way from the equator,
maintaining a climate favourable
for life almost everywhere.
From creating the weather
to producing oxygen,
the seas keep our world healthy.
But there are now worrying signs
that conditions in the oceans
that have remained relatively stable
for millennia
are changing radically.
Nowhere is this more evident
than in the Arctic.
Here in the past 30 years,
the extent of the ice in summer
has been reduced by 40%.
This sudden warming,
most likely a consequence
of human activity,
is having a profound impact
on its wildlife.
Walruses are among those
that are seriously affected.
Every adult female
needs to find a safe place
where her 80-kilo pup can rest.
The sea ice is retreating
from much
of the walrus' traditional range,
so they now have
to haul out on dry land.
But a herd of hundreds
of quarrelsome mothers,
some weighing almost a tonne,
is not an ideal nursery.
Walruses on land stick together
for good reason.
Polar bears.
A full grown male walrus is gigantic,
too big for even a
polar bear to tackle.
So the bear is looking
for a walrus baby.
The scent of the bear
spreads alarm through the colony.
The walruses retreat into the sea.
The bear knows it won't be able
to catch them there.
But she too has young ones to feed.
What is a mother to do?
A mother walrus still needs
to find a place
where her young can rest.
A melting iceberg might do,
but she is not the first
to find this one.
Suitable places are already taken.
Other mothers don't want to share.
They, too, need a patch of ice
where they can protect their young.
A desperate mother has no choice
but to barge her way in.
So this time everyone loses.
Finding the right place
on these melting shores
gets harder and harder.
Solving these problems together
helps create a bond so strong
that the mother will stay in contact
with her young for the rest of her life.
But who knows now
what their future will be.
As we understand more
about the complexity
of the lives of sea creatures,
so we begin to appreciate
the fragility of their home.
Our blue planet.
Blue Planet II has been
four years in the making.
The teams have explored every ocean,
seeking extraordinary untold stories,
many new to science.
Bringing a new understanding
of life beneath the waves.
The latest diving technology
producing no bubbles or noise
has allowed our teams
longer and closer encounters.
To explore our final frontier,
the deep,
we have spent a thousand hours
in submersibles
over half a mile below the surface.
Innovative new camera technology
makes it possible to film moments
never seen before.
Low-light cameras capture magical events
almost invisible to the naked eye.
Probe cameras
give a completely fresh perspective
into the lives of tiny creatures.
Here he comes, here he comes.
While suction cameras take us
on a giant's eye view of the ocean.
But the sea is an unpredictable
and dangerous place to work.
Nowhere more so than the so called
wild coast of South Africa.
Home to surfing dolphins.
The team's mission here
is to ride alongside the dolphins
and record their surfing behaviour
in closer detail than ever before.
These are treacherous seas,
so the film crew enlists local
professional surfers to guide them.
But this year, the waves are bigger
than anyone had anticipated.
A daunting prospect for surf
cameraman, Chris Bryan.
Yeah, I'm feeling pretty nervous,
the, uh...
It's a big swell out there.
Really big swell.
Like there's 20-foot waves out there,
and, um, yeah this will probably be the
biggest seas I've ever been out in.
No risks, no reward, I guess.
Chris has a high-speed camera
to shoot super slow motion action
in the waves.
The challenge is to get as close to
the wave-riding dolphins as possible.
The good news is that the dolphins
have been spotted on the horizon.
Um, they said this was gonna be
the biggest swell of the year and...
Hey, I've never seen
anything like this.
This is much bigger
that I'd possibly imagined.
In these waves,
the only way to get out to the
dolphins is with a jet ski.
It's gonna be enough
of a challenge for them
to just kind of weave their way out.
At last,
the driver's detailed knowledge
gets them safely
through the massive breakers,
but the dolphins are
nowhere to be seen.
Leaving the crew to face
the hair-raising task
of getting back to shore.
Keep going, keep going!
Whoa!
MAN</fo
That was pretty wild, yeah.
The wave actually hit
the back of the sled,
and I was like, "Go, go. Get out
of here, guys. Get out of here."
Heard a big bump and
almost bounced off
trying to hold the camera
and, um, just rode out of there,
but, yeah, it was hectic.
Just another day at the office.
The next day brings
a sudden change in conditions.
Plenty of dolphins...
but a calmer sea.
We've got a complete lack
of any wave at all.
Look out, look out, look out.
As so often in the ocean,
if you know you're
in the right place,
you just need the patience
to wait for the perfect moment.
A week later and a storm
is once again brewing
off the wild coast and
surf is building.
Feel like a nervous excitement.
The conditions are absolutely perfect.
It's what we've been waiting for.
And the dolphins seem to know it.
But Chris is struggling
to get a steady shot.
Look at that.
Hello, gentleman. Uh, this is tricky.
Little tricky no the jet ski, uh,
just trying to get the right angle.
So, I'm gonna have a go on the zodiac
and hopefully have better luck
on that one.
The inflatable boat
gives Chris a larger,
more stable filming platform.
At last, he's in exactly the right
place at exactly the right time.
And the results are spectacular.
That's amazing!
Mission accomplished.
And this intimate footage
is now available
as part of wider scientific studies.
Supporting evidence
that dolphins surf
to strengthen friendships,
develop social skills
and for the sheer exhilaration of it.
Next time.
The deep.
A world richer
than we ever though possible,
where creatures thrive,
in the most extreme
conditions on earth.
Resync by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com