Hello once again.
As usual, I must warn you all
that this year's Halloween show
is very, very scary,
and those of you
with young children
may want to send them
off to bed--
Oh, my. It seems
the show is so scary
that congress
won't even let us show it.
Instead, they've suggested
the 1947 classic
Glenn Ford movie
"200 Miles to Oregon."
♪♪
BART: There's nothing wrong
with your television set.
Do not attempt
to adjust your picture.
We are controlling
the transmission.
HOMER: What's that, boy?
We're in control?
Hey, look--
I can see my voice. (laughs)
(sputtering)
(vocalizing)
Blub, blub, blub,
blub, blub.
This... is my voice...
on TV.
BART: Dad! You're ruining
the mood.
HOMER: Sorry.
BART:
For the next half hour,
we will control
what you see and hear.
You are about to experience
the terror and foul horror
of The Simpsons'
Halloween Special.
(wolf howling)
(distant scream)
(evil laughter)
(distant wolf howling)
(moaning)
Well, it was a long trip,
but we're almost there.
Homer, did you
remember to lock
the front door
of the house?
D'oh!
Well, it's been two long trips
but we're finally
almost there again.
When you locked
the front door,
did you remember to lock
the back door?
D'oh! D'oh!
(gasps) Oh, no!
We left Grampa
back at the gas station.
What about Grampa?
-Hi. We're here.
-We made it.
Oh, goody. The sea monkeys
I ordered have arrived.
Look at them
cavort and caper.
Sir, they're the new
winter caretakers for the lodge.
Yes, they work hard
and they play hard.
This house has quite a long
and colorful history.
It was built on an ancient
Indian burial ground
and was the setting of
satanic rituals, witch-burnings
and five John Denver
Christmas specials.
Oh... John Denver.
Hmm... that's odd.
Usually the blood
gets off at
the second floor.
(chain saw buzzing)
Hey, I found a shortcut
through your hedge maze.
Why, you little--
No, go easy on
the wee one.
His father's gonna go crazy
and chop them all
into haggis.
What's haggis?
Boy, you read my thoughts.
You've got the shinning.
You mean "shining."
Shh! You want to get sued?
Now look, boy,
if your Dad goes gaga,
you just use that shin
of yours to call me
and I'll come a-running.
But don't be reading my mind
between 4:00 and 5:00.
That's Willie's time.
Yes, by cutting off cable TV
and the beer supply,
I can ensure an honest winter's
work out of those lowlifes.
Sir, did you ever stop to think
that maybe it was doing this
that caused the previous
caretakers to go insane
and murder their families?
Hmm. Perhaps.
Tell you what:
we come back and everyone's
slaughtered,
I owe you a Coke.
Hmm... cable's out.
Think I'll have a beer.
Hmm...
not a drop in the house.
What do you know?
Homer, I'm impressed.
You're taking this quite well.
I'll kill you!
I'll kill all of you!
-Homer!
-Sorry, sorry.
Don't worry.
There's plenty I can do
to keep myself occupied.
Maybe I'll check out
that ax collection.
See you later.
Mom, is Dad going to kill us?
We're just gonna have
to wait and see.
So, what will it be, Homer?
Moe! Give me a beer.
No, not unless you
kill your family.
Why should I
kill my family?
Uh... they'd be much
happier as ghosts.
You don't look so happy.
Oh I'm happy!
I'm very happy.
La-la-la-la-la. See?
Now waste your family.
I'll give you a beer.
Homer?
Homey?
Hmm... what he's typed will be
a window into his madness.
"Feelin' fine."
Wow, that's a relief.
Oooooh...
Hmm... this is
less encouraging.
Hello!
(screaming)
So, what do you think, Marge?
All I need is a title.
I was thinking along the lines
of "no TV and no beer make
Homer something something."
Go crazy?
Don't mind if I do.
(raving)
(Marge screaming)
Stay away from me, Homer.
Give me the bat, Marge.
Give me the bat.
Come on, give me the bat.
Give me the bat-bat-boo!
(babbling)
(laughing)
Scaredy-cat.
(groans)
(screams)
(grunting)
You stay here
till you're no longer insane.
Hmm, chili
would be good tonight.
(knocking)
Homer, it's Moe.
Look, some of the ghouls and I
are a little concerned
the project isn't
moving forward.
Can't murder now-- eating.
Aw, for crying out loud,
come on.
No!
Here's Johnny!
D'oh!
David Letterman!
Hi, David.
I'm Grampa.
D'oh!
I'm Mike Wallace,
I'm Morley Safer
and I'm Ed Bradley.
All this and Andy Rooney
tonight on "60 Minutes."
(all screaming)
Hello, police?
This is Marge Simpson.
My husband is on
a murderous rampage. Over.
Oh. Well,
thank God that's over.
I was worried
there for a second.
No answer.
Don't worry, Mom.
I can use my... shinning
to call Willie.
And that was the first time
she'd ever flown a plane.
Uh-oh. The little fat boy
and his family are in trouble.
I'm coming to rescue
the lot of you.
All right, loony,
show me what you got.
Is that the best
you can do?
Oh, my, I hope that rug
was Scotchgarded.
Must kill family.
(moaning)
(panting)
The troops
had been given rifles
but no ammunition.
Dad, look!
Television!
Teacher, mother, secret lover.
Urge to kill fading...
fading... fading.
Rising. Fading.
Fading.
Gone.
(all sighing)
Come, family.
Sit in the snow with Daddy
and let us all bask
in television's warm,
glowing, warming glow.
MAN:
Live from Broadway
it's the Tony Awards
with your hosts
Tyne Daly and Hal Linden.
Homer, change channel.
Can't... frozen.
-♪ One... ♪
-ALL: Ah!
♪ Chorus line of people ♪
Urge to kill rising.
You know, Marge,
I've had my share of troubles,
but sitting here now with you
and the kids in our cozy home
in this beautiful,
free country,
it just makes me feel
that I'm really a lucky guy.
Dad! Your hand is jammed
in the toaster!
(all yelling)
(Homer screaming)
Get it off!
Get this off of me!
Ooh!
Whew-hoo!
Dad! It's in there again!
(screaming)
(yelling)
This shouldn't be
too hard to fix
with the right tools.
There.
Better than new.
Now to take her
for a test toast.
What the--
(screaming)
Look at that. I'm the first
non-Brazilian person
to travel backwards
through time.
Correction, Homer.
You're the second.
That's right,
Mr. Peabody.
Quiet, you.
(gasps)
I've gone back to the time
when dinosaurs weren't
just confined to zoos.
(screeching)
Okay, don't panic.
Remember the advice your father
gave you on your wedding day.
If you ever travel back in time,
don't step on anything
because even the tiniest change
can alter the future
in ways you can't imagine.
Fine. As long as I
stand perfectly still
and don't touch anything,
I won't destroy the future.
Stupid bug!
You go squish now.
But that was just one little
insignificant mosquito.
That can't change
the future, right?
Right?
(grunts "I don't know")
Phew! I'm back.
Aw, my loving family.
Nothing's changed.
Hidely-ho, slaverinos.
ALL: Okely-dokely.
Hey, what the hell is that
geek Flanders doing on TV?
(alarm sounding)
Oh, I see by the big board
we got a negative Nellie
in sector two.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to
ask the whole family
to kinda freeze and
prepare for re-neducation.
Don't you remember, Dad?
Flanders is the unquestioned
lord and master of the world.
D'oh!
Okay, everybody,
let's see some big smiles.
Just relax and let
the hooks do their work.
What the hell
are you smiling at?
Oh...
Now, in case all that smiling
didn't cheer you up
there's one thing
that never fails--
A nice glass of warm milk,
a little nap and
a total frontal lobotomy.
It's not so bad, Homer.
They go in through your nose
and they let you keep
the piece of brain
they cut out.
Look. Whoo, hello.
Hello there.
Who's that big man there?
Who's that?
BOTH:
Join us, Father.
It's bliss.
No!
(alarm sounding)
(frantic panting)
(dogs barking)
Oh, no, they're gaining on me.
Wait! I have an idea.
These wieners will give me
the quick energy
I need to escape.
I got to go back.
Fix future.
This time I'm not gonna
touch a thing.
(roaring)
Ah!
Ooh! Ooh! Mustn't crush,
mustn't kill.
Made it.
Oh, I wish, I wish
I hadn't killed that fish.
Hey, where is everybody?
Hey, there's a bug
that looks like Dad.
Let's kill it.
Okay.
(screaming)
(panting)
Oh... oh...
-(roaring)
-Ah-choo!
(sneezes)
(sneezing)
This is gonna cost me.
HOMER: D'oh!
I mean, hey...
Good morning, Father dear.
Hope you're well.
Are we taking the new Lexus
to Aunt Patty and Selma's
funeral today?
Hmm, fabulous house,
well-behaved kids
Sisters-in-law dead,
luxury sedan...
Whoo-hoo! I hit the jackpot!
Marge dear, would you
kindly pass me a doughnut?
Doughnut? What's a doughnut?
(screaming)
Hmm, it's raining again.
You're still not
in your own world, Homer.
I can get you home,
but you have to do exactly as--
Ah!
(deep male voice)
This is indeed
a disturbing universe.
Don't touch anything?!
I'll touch whatever I feel like!
(roaring)
Foolish Earthling.
Totally unprepared
for the effects
of time travel.
(laughing)
What happened to us,
Kodos?
Quiet, you.
(panting)
Good morning, dear.
What's my name?
What color is the sky?
What of doughnuts? What?!
For the love
of God, tell me!
Homer, the sky is blue.
Doughnuts are plentiful.
Friday is
T.G.I.F. night on ABC.
What's gotten into you?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Let's just eat.
(slurping)
Ah, close enough.
(clamoring)
(whistles)
Hey, everybody.
Let's all turn
our desks backwards
before Mrs. Krabappel shows up.
-Yeah!
-Great idea.
(laughing)
Huh?
All right, backwards boy
back your butt
down to detention.
Over here, Simpson.
The detention room
is dangerously overcrowded,
so you'll be serving your time
in the cafeteria.
Oxygen running out.
Yes, you should have
thought of that
before you made
that paper airplane.
This overcrowding
in detention
is becoming critical.
It's a powder keg
waiting to go off
in an explosion of
unacceptable behavior.
Don't bitch to me,
boss man.
Thanks to the latest
budget cuts,
I'm down to using
grade "F" meat.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
if there was a common solution
to both our problems?
That would be great.
Hey, Bart, watch this.
-Oh, drats!
-Oh, no!
My favorite outfit.
Jimbo, this is by far
the worst... mmm.
Mmm...
Jimbo, why don't you assist
lunch lady Doris in the kitchen?
-Bite me, Skinner.
-Well, might we.
JIMBO: It's hard for me
to clean this giant pot
when you keep spilling
meat tenderizer all over me.
(clank)
Oh great. Now I got to work
in the dark.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
This sandwich tastes
so young and impudent.
Seymour, what's
with the good grub?
Well, perhaps I ought to
let you folks in on a secret.
You remember me
telling Jimbo Jones
that I'd make something of him
one day?
(gasps) Are you saying
you killed Jimbo,
processed his carcass
and served him for lunch?
Ha!
Hmm... I wonder
where Jimbo is today.
He should have
beaten us up
for our lunch money
an hour ago.
Frau lunch lady.
Please to have
another sloppy Jimbo.
Das ist gut, nein?
That's your third helping,
young man.
It's making you fat
and soft...
and tender.
Mmm... you just cut
in line, didn't you?
-Report to detention, Uter.
-For how long?
Oh, about seven minutes
a pound should do it.
Okay, I got your
German grub right here.
Bart, does it strike you as odd
that Uter disappeared
and suddenly they're serving us
this mysterious food
called "Uterbraten"?
Oh, relax, kids.
I've got a gut feeling
Uter's around here somewhere.
(chuckling)
After all, isn't there
a little Uter in all of us?
(laughing)
In fact, you might even say
we just ate Uter
and he's in our stomachs
right now.
(laughing)
Wait. Scratch that one.
Mom! You've got to help.
They're cooking kids
in the school cafeteria.
Listen kids. You're eight
and ten years old now.
I can't be fighting all
your battles for you.
-But, Mom--
-No "buts."
You march right back
to that school
look them in the eye
and say, "don't eat me."
BOTH: Okay.
Since so many students have been
put on permanent detention--
(burps)
We've merged everyone
into a single class.
I trust there are no objections.
(shuddering)
Detention.
(Milhouse gasps)
Psst! Hey, you guys.
I was just thinking
that any of us could be next.
So what do you say
we make a break for it?
(gasping)
♪♪ (harmonica)
Easy there, young man.
You'll only make yourself
tired and stringy.
Now to check on
the free-range children.
(all scream)
Hold on, kids!
I'm coming to rescue
the lot of you.
I'll-- Ow!
Ah... I'm bad at this.
I'm going to enjoy
devouring you, Bart Simpson.
Yes, I believe I'll start,
as you've so often suggested
by eating your shorts.
(all whimpering)
(yells)
(whirring)
(kids moaning)
Don't worry, guys.
Something always
comes along to save us.
(screaming)
Nevertheless,
I remain confident
that something
will come along
and save the two
Simpson children.
(screaming)
Ah!
Relax, honey.
You were just having
a crazy nightmare.
You're back with
your family now
where there's nothing
to be afraid of,
except that fog
that turns people inside out.
-Huh?
-Uh-oh.
It's seeping in.
Stupid, cheap
weather stripping.
(screaming)
♪♪
♪ One ♪
♪ Chorus line of people ♪
♪ Dancing till
they make us stop ♪
♪ Too ♪
♪ Many dancing people ♪
♪ Covered with blood,
gore and glop ♪
♪ Just one sniff
of that fog ♪
♪ And you're inside out ♪
♪ It's worse than that
flesh-eating virus ♪
♪ You've read about ♪
♪ Vital organs, they are
what we're dressed in ♪
♪ The family dog is eyeing
Bart's intestine ♪
♪ Happy Halloween ♪
♪♪
Get off!
(screaming)
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.