♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy Show ♪
(grunting)
(laughing)
(moaning)
(yells)
(laughing)
Thanks, kids.
Now we'd like to speak to you
seriously for a moment.
Yup. This week is
the grand opening
of Itchy & Scratchy Land--
the violentest
place on Earth.
And to celebrate,
for this week only
we're cutting ticket
prices in half.
Yow!
Kids, you heard
the cartoon rat.
If you haven't already
run to your parents
begging to go, do it now.
You won't be missing
anything funny.
I'll just be sitting here
reading this
grown-ups' newspaper.
(laughing)
Go now!
(gasping)
LISA: Dad!
Remember how you said
that going to
Itchy & Scratchy Land
would be too damned expensive?
Oh everything's too damn
expensive these days.
Look at this Bible
I just got-- 15 bucks.
And talk about
a preachy book.
Everybody's a sinner,
except for this guy.
But now
Itchy & Scratchy Land
is cutting ticket
prices in half.
Can we go, Dad?
Can we, can we, can we?
-Take it, Lis.
-Can we?
No, no, no, no, no.
Ask your mother.
BOTH: Yay!
Mom, guess what?
We're going to
Itchy & Scratchy Land.
No.
I've already planned
our vacation.
We're going to the
Highway 9 Bird Sanctuary.
I understand they've installed
a new bird feeder this year.
It's shaped like a diner
and it's on this
really tall pole.
Mom, Dad, Bart's dead!
(both gasping)
That's right--
dead serious about going
to Itchy & Scratchy Land.
(both groaning)
You know,
Itchy & Scratchy Land
isn't just for kids.
They have a place
called Parents' Island.
-Hmm?
"Yeah, dancing, bowling,
fashionable shops
"over 100 bars and saloons
and a world-class
chemical dependency center."
TV Town! Hammock Land!
Oh, recipe-related
bumper cars.
(both gasping)
BOTH: Yay!
Wait a minute.
I'm not sure
about this.
Every time
we've ever gone on vacation,
I end up being
horribly embarrassed.
We end up in a big fight,
and we come home more miserable
than when we left.
You have to promise me that
this isn't gonna happen
this time.
Embarrassed?
What are you talking about?
Well, there was our trip
to the Amish Country.
Oh, yes.
(laughing)
Hey look, Marge,
they're still
not fighting back.
(grunts)
Hee-hee.
I can be a jerk
and no one can stop me.
Hee-hee-hee-- Ahh!
MARGE: Even worse was
our trip to Sandy Beach.
(all screaming)
(laughing)
Suckers.
(screaming)
Shark Boy!
This year I want us to do things
together as a family
and get a lot
of good exercise outdoors
so we'll have a lot
of wonderful memories
of our vacation.
Don't worry, Mom.
We'll make you
proud of us.
Lobster hat,
fishnet Speedo Junior,
wheelie shoes,
invisible dog leash.
(laughs)
Well, I'm packed.
MARGE: And remember,
every morning,
give one bowl of kibble
to Santa's Little Helper.
Do you want me to write
any of this down?
No. I ain't senile,
dad-blasted!
-Okay, bye-bye.
-Bye.
LISA: Bye, Grandpa!
Wait a minute.
What was that last thing
you said?
Grandpa's little helper?
What's that?
Which one of you
is the mailman?
Okay, let's make a pact.
This is gonna be
the best vacation ever
or we'll all agree to disband
and join other families.
ALL: Agreed.
HOMER: Ah, the interstate.
Fasten your seat belts, kids.
We're on our way
to Itchy & Scratchy Land!
ALL: D'oh!
Don't worry.
I've got an ace
up my sleeve.
(honking)
(gasping)
Dad, can we stop
at Flickey's?
No.
Oh, my God, what'll I do?
What'll I do?!
What's the matter
with you, Homer?
We don't have any fruits
or vegetables in the car.
The whole trunk's
full of them, Marge.
You got any fruits
or vegetables?
(panicky scream)
Hey. Mr. Wimbley,
it happened again.
Now to absorb
some local color
through the magic
of A.M. radio.
MAN (on radio):
The Book of Revelations
tells us to watch for
the seven signs of evil...
MAN 2:
...sign of evil number four.
MAN 3: Continuing our
"sign of evil" countdown
here's Vanessa Williams.
Aw, haven't we stood in five
different states long enough?
No.
(yawning)
We better find a motel
and stop for the night.
We don't need
to do that, Marge.
I'm not tired.
I'm not tired at all.
(tires screeching)
Ooh, glad that wasn't us.
North... south...
Ah, nuts to this.
I'm going to take
a shortcut.
Homer, no.
You're going to get lost.
Trust me, Marge.
With today's modern cars,
you can't get lost--
what, with all
the silicon chips and such.
All right, we're here.
Let us never speak
of the shortcut again.
HOMER: Now remember,
we're in the Itchy lot.
PILOT: We're now approaching
our final destination.
Itchy & Scratchy Land--
The amusement park
of the future
where nothing
can possi-blye go wrong.
Possibly go wrong.
Huh. That's the first thing
that's ever gone wrong.
(kids laughing)
One adult
and four children.
Would you like to buy some
Itchy & Scratchy Money?
-What's that?
-It's money that's made just for the park.
It works just like
regular money,
but it's, uh... fun.
-Do it, Dad.
-Well, okay, if it's fun.
Let's see...
I'll take $1,100 worth.
(groans)
-Ha, cool!
-Wow!
Neat-o!
Such a violent motif.
Yeah, but it's just
pretend violence
which is actually
beneficial for children.
-Ow!
(soft growl)
(laughs)
There's no need
to murmur, ma'am.
Here at Itchy & Scratchy Land,
we're just as concerned
about violence as you are.
That's why we're always
careful to show the consequences
of deadly mayhem
so that we may educate
as well as horrify.
When do you show the
consequences?
On TV, that mouse pulled out
that cat's lungs
and played them
like a bagpipe.
But in the next scene, the cat
was breathing comfortably.
Just like in real life.
Hey, look over there!
Yoing!
I'll have a Brain Burger
with extra pus, please?
-Bart!
-Eyeball stew.
Homer, We just got here
and already I'm mortified
beyond belief by your
embarrassing behavior.
I was just ordering
a cheeseburger, Mom.
They have violent names
for everything here.
Oh, I see.
All right.
Mmm...
I'll have the Baby Guts.
Lady, you disgust me.
(disgusted snort)
Mom, that's veal.
Oh.
You're sure
she'll have fun here?
Oh, of course.
Babies love the ball room.
MARGE: "Torture Land."
"Explosion Land."
"Searing Gas Pain Land."
"Unnecessary Surgery Land."
HOMER: Oh look!
It's the 12 noon robot parade.
Hurry up or we'll have to wait
for the 12:05 parade.
♪♪
(gunfire)
(laughing)
Wow, this is so much
like my dreams it's scary.
Aw, look at that
cute little baby ax.
It's cute,
but I'm sure it's very sharp
-and probably dirty.
-(laughing)
Dirty, maybe.
Dangerous, hardly.
These are the latest
state-of-the-art
animatronic robots.
They have sensors that ensure
they only attack each other--
never the guests.
MARGE: See all that
stuff in there, Homer?
That's why your robot
never worked.
(clicking)
♪♪ (quiet banjo)
This is just what
I was hoping for--
spending the day together
as a family.
(screaming)
BOTH: Yay!
You know, part
of spending time
together as a family
is spending time apart
as individuals.
-Parents' Island?
-Yeah-huh.
I'm sure we'll appreciate
each other all the more
when we meet up at dinner.
Are you kids gonna
be all right?
Kids?
(laughing)
HOMER: It is the '70s--
right down to
the smallest detail.
Hey, the bartender
even looks like
John Travolta.
Yeah. Looks like.
Look at all this
great stuff, Lis.
Cool-- personalized plates.
"Barclay,"
"Barry,"
"Bert,"
"Bort"?
Aw, come on-- Bort?
Mommy, Mommy!
Buy me a license plate!
No. Come along, Bort.
Are you talking to me?
No. My son is
also named Bort.
Who are all
these characters?
Well, you're probably
too young to remember
the short-lived
"Itchy & Scratchy and Friends Hour."
They had to come up
with some friends.
There's
Disgruntled Goat
Uncle Ant,
Ku Klux Klam.
Oh, yeah.
They weren't very funny.
I don't know.
Disgruntled Goat
had his moments.
(muffled humming)
(grunt)
(groaning)
♪♪
Welcome to T.G.I. McScratchy's
where it's constantly
New Year's Eve.
Here we go again!
Three, two, one...
CROWD:
Happy New Year!
(cheering)
It must be wonderful
to ring in the new year
over and over and over.
Please, kill me.
(explosions)
(laughing)
(grunts)
(groaning)
The babies look unhappy.
Add more balls.
NARRATOR:
Roger Meyers, Sr.,
the gentle genius
behind Itchy & Scratchy
loved and cared about almost
all the peoples of the world,
and he, in return,
was beloved by the world,
except in 1938
when he was criticized
for his
controversial cartoon
"Nazi Supermen
Are Our Superiors."
Among his proudest
achievements
was the full-length musical
"Scratchtasia."
(panting)
(yelling)
(evil laughter)
♪♪
Hey Ma, I'm gonna
get me a picture
of this crazy critter.
(nervous laughing)
Uh, no flash photography,
please.
(sputtering)
NARRATOR: Roger Meyer's
next full-length feature
was the wildly successful
"Pinnitchy-o."
Now you be a good,
Pinnitchy-o
and don't you lie.
I promise I will
never hurt you.
Ouch!
I wonder if this
kind of violence
really does
desensitize us.
Want to get
a sno-cone?
Okay.
(both gasp)
BART: So, Mr. Itchy,
you think you're
God's gift to women, do ya?
Don't do it, Bart.
Oh!
(groaning)
-I just wanted to entertain.
-(laughing)
Can you believe
I keep getting
away with this?
Uh, officer?
(elevator bell dings)
Mop-and-bucket man to
the exit of The Nauseator.
We have another jumper
on the roof of T.G.I. McScratchy's.
We need more
"Bort" license plates
in the gift shop.
I repeat, we are sold out
of Bort license plates.
Aah!
I really wished
they wouldn't scream.
Dad?
I kicked one of those
stupid Itchy characters
in the butt.
Yeah. There's just no way
to resist it, is there?
I want all five T-shirts to say
"Best vacation ever."
MAN (on PA):
Attention, Marge Simpson,
your son has been arrested.
(crowd gasps)
I'd be
terribly embarrassed
if I were that
boy's mother.
(soft growl)
Attention Marge Simpson.
We've also arrested
your older, balder,
fatter son.
(soft growl)
I'm so embarrassed.
I wish there was a hole
I could just crawl into and die.
Okay, throw her
in the hole.
Oh please! It was just
a figure of speech.
(exasperated growl)
You've got to listen to me.
Elementary chaos theory
tells us that all robots
will eventually turn
against their masters
and run amok in an orgy
of blood and kicking
and the biting
with the metal teeth
and the hurting and shoving.
How much time do we have,
Professor?
Well, according to
my calculations,
the robots won't go berserk
for at least 24 hours.
(groaning)
Oh, I forgot to carry the one.
I have nothing
to say to you.
But Marge, I was
a political prisoner.
How were you
a political prisoner?
I kicked a giant mouse
in the butt!
Do I have to draw you
a diagram?
Oh, for gosh sakes,
what now?
Hey, look.
This one's coming on to me.
Yoo-hoo!
Mr. Robot.
Dad, I think you're
wrong about that robot
trying to be your friend.
Lisa, don't...
contradict...
your... elders.
Ah! My hair!
You chopped off my hair.
Oh, God, I'm ugly.
I knew we should have gone
to the bird sanctuary.
(chirping and twittering)
(screaming)
I need the biggest seed bell
you have.
No, that's too big.
A chopper! We're saved.
Hey, you're the guys
who didn't like our capering.
When you get to hell,
tell them Itchy sent you.
(grunts)
Oh, my.
It looks like we're doomed.
Back, you robots!
Nobody ruins
my family vacation but me
and maybe the boy.
(grunting)
(grunting continues)
(screaming)
(all screaming)
Dad! The flash must have
scrambled their circuits.
What are you,
the narrator?
Ahh! Just keep taking pictures.
(clicking)
I'll get more cameras.
Smashy-smashy.
I don't approve of that.
(screaming)
Hey, mouse...
say cheese.
With a dry, cool wit
like that
I could be an action hero.
-(cameras clicking)
-(groaning)
Die, bad robots, die!
With a dry, cool wit
like that I could be--
Who would have thought
that our visit to
Itchy & Scratchy Land
would turn out to be
our best vacation ever?
Yeah, best ever.
Are you two bonkers?
We almost got killed.
Not to mention all
the embarrassment I suffered.
But, Mom, it's exactly what
you wanted in a vacation.
It brought us
together as a family.
We got a lot
of good exercise outdoors,
and we have so many memories.
You know you're right.
This truly was the best
vacation ever.
Now let us never
speak of it again.
As Roger Meyers, Jr.,
the owner of the park,
I'd like to thank you for
stopping the killer robots,
and to show my appreciation,
here are two free passes.
But there are five of us.
(louder)
Here are two free passes.
That's better.
Man, if this is happening here,
I'd hate to think
what's happening
in Euro Itchy & Scratchy Land.
(French accent)
Hello!
Itchy & Scratchy Land
open for business.
Who are you to resist it, eh?
Come on.
My last paycheck bounced.
My children need wine.
(yelling in French)
(Lisa and Bart laughing)
I hope you realize now
that violence on TV
may be funny,
but it's not so funny
when that violence
is happening to you.
But it would
be funny to someone
who was watching us.
-(soft growl)
-No, Mom, he's right.
Observe.
Ow!
(laughs)
(all laughing)
Oh, my.
Lisa, go to your room.
(low growl)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.