♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screeching)
Oh, damn F.D.A.
Why can't it all be marshmallow?
Ew, Bart, don't put
the non-marshmallow pieces
back in the box,
they go in the trash.
Ooh, you like sweets,
kids?
I know a place that's sweeter
than sweetness itself.
In this sweet place,
earthly doughnuts
are sour as poison.
You'd spit them out,
you would.
I'm talking about
the candy industry trade show.
How did you get tickets?
They hid them in every millionth
Krusty Klump Bar
and Krusty
Klump Bar with almonds.
Hey, Hey, Hey!
I have asked you nicely
not to mangle my merchandise.
You leave me no choice
but to ask you nicely again.
Can I come
to the candy show?
-No! Me! Me!
-Huh? Can I?
Sorry kids, but this
is the one event
I want my darling wife
by my side.
Oh, well, thank you, Homer,
but take one of the kids.
Marge, they can't carry
enough candy.
They have
puny little muscles.
Not big, ropy ones
like you.
(groans)
You go, Mom,
for the greater good.
For the greater good.
Homer, are all
these pockets necessary?
They wouldn't be if you were willing
to sit in a hollowed-out wheelchair.
(doorbell rings)
That's the baby-sitter.
No one in town will
sit for you two anymore.
I had to choose between
a grad student at the university
and a scary-looking hobo.
Please the hobo,
please the hobo, please the hobo.
Hi. I'm Ashley Grant.
-(Bart groans)
-(gasps) Ashley Grant!
You gave a talk on women's
issues at my school
on how we don't have
to be second-class citizens.
Mom, how can you leave us
with this maniac?
Hurry, Marge! If we get there early,
we can get our pictures taken
with the two surviving
musketeers.
There's also a baby
somewhere upstairs.
-(door slams)
-So, you're one of those
"don't call me a chick"
chicks, huh?
Sorry about
my unenlightened brother.
He will make the next few hours
a living hell.
Oh, I don't know.
See this, Bart?
Disemboweler IV.
The game where condemned
criminals
dig at each other
with rusty hooks.
Mm-hmm...
Do a little housework,
and you can
play for five minutes.
No way.
Yes'm.
See, Lisa?
Males aren't hard to tame.
They all follow their
video cartridges.
Ow.
MAN (on P.A.):
Mr. Goodbar to the front desk.
The front desk is looking
for Mr. Goodbar.
(gasps) I feel like a kid
in some kind of a store.
Yeah! Ooh!
Great.
Exquisite.
Oh, you'll do well.
Give me those.
As you can see, I have created
a lemon ball so sour
it can only be safely contained
in a magnetic field.
The candy,
known as 77-X-42...
Where the hell
is the candy?
(muffled)
I don't know.
Hey, sir, try our wax lips.
It's the candy
of 1,000 uses.
Like what?
One, a humorous substitute
for your own lips.
-Keep going.
-Two, uh...
Ooh, I'm needed in the basement.
Hmm.
You're going to have
to put some sugar
-on that celery or get out, ma'am.
-(Marge groans)
(overlapping chatter)
Ooh, Gummi Bears,
Gummi Calves' Heads,
Gummi Jaw Breakers.
(Homer gasps)
What's that?
That is the rarest
Gummi of them all.
The Gummi Venus de Milo.
Carved by Gummi artisans
who work exclusively
in the medium of Gummi.
Will you two stop
saying Gummi so much?
Must have rare Gummi.
Distract the salesman.
No, I won't make a spectacle
out of myself any further.
Oh! Whoa! Oh!
How'd they get there?
(laughs nervously)
Now, this is going to take
all my skill.
(chuckles)
(alarm wailing)
Halt, halt!
Run, Marge!
Save the booty!
After him!
He has the Gummi!
(all shouting)
See you in hell, candy boys!
Ahhhh!
(giggling)
Hey, Lise, I found
a big caramel deposit
at the small of her back.
I'm coming.
(giggling)
(laughing)
-Whoo!
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Where's my Gummi de Milo?
Okay, don't panic.
She can't have gotten far.
She has no arms.
I'm sure it'll turn up.
Take the baby-sitter home now.
She's been sitting
in the car for 20 minutes.
Relax Marge, there's plenty
for her to do in there.
(horn honking)
See? She's having
the time of her life.
So, a graduate student, huh?
How come you guys
can go to the moon
but you can't make
my shoes smell good?
-I'm sorry.
-Ah, nobody's blaming you.
Hey, would you take
the wheel for a second,
I have to scratch myself
in two places at once.
Just drop me off here.
(gasps)
Precious Venus.
-(gasps)
-(groaning)
-(screams)
-(door slams)
Thank you.
(sighs)
(groaning)
Hey, kids, lots of candy
left for breakfast.
(both groaning)
Why don't we give it
to some needy children then?
BOTH:
No.
(crowd clamoring)
Oh no, the candy conventioneers
tracked us down.
There he is-- there's the man
that sexually harassed me.
Oh, for a minute there,
I thought I was in big trouble.
It's just a-- D'oh!
(crowd chanting) 2-4-6-8,
Homer's crime was very great.
Great meaning large or immense.
We use it
in the pejorative sense.
Marge, I swear
I didn't touch her.
You know how bashful I am.
I can't even say
the word "titmouse"
without giggling
like a school girl.
(giggling)
At any rate,
I believe you.
And I think you should go outside
and straighten this out.
Some of their chants are
very catchy and memorable.
You grabbed me
in the car!
Oh that... no. I was just
grabbing a Gummi Venus de Milo
that got stuck
to your pants.
Yeah, right.
That's the oldest
excuse in the book.
(booing)
Come on, I'm a decent guy.
(gasping)
(booing and hissing)
Why would anybody want
to touch a girl's butt?
That's where
cooties come from.
Dad, I don't understand.
What is she saying you did?
Well Lisa, remember that postcard
Grampa sent us from Florida
of that alligator
biting that woman's bottom?
Oh, yeah!
That was brilliant!
That's right.
We all thought it was hilarious,
but it turns out
we were wrong.
That alligator was
sexually harassing that woman.
And the dog in the Coppertone ads?
Same deal, Dad?
That's kind of a gray area.
We know you're innocent, Dad.
Thanks, kids.
They seem to be building
some sort of a shanty town.
(clamoring)
Do your worst, protesters.
You can't stop me
from living my life.
No respect for women,
no peace.
Just try to push
the right buttons now.
We aren't crazy about
nuclear power either!
You people aren't
allowed in here.
It's okay.
They're with me.
(booing and yelling)
They're ruining
my whole life.
Marge, please, this is where
I need you the most.
I'm counting on you
to do something
or say something
to make it all better.
Okay... go.
-Homer...
-Uh-huh?
I already talked to the indignation
coordinator out on the lawn today.
I told her you were a decent man,
but she wouldn't listen.
Besides standing by you
and supporting you,
there isn't anything
more I can do.
You mean I'm on my own?
I've never been on my own.
Oh, no, on own... on own...
I need help.
Oh, God, help me.
Help me, God!
(phone ringing)
Ye-llo?
Hello, Homer.
This is God... frey Jones
from the TV magazine
show Rock Bottom.
We're aware of your problems,
and, Mr. Simpson,
we want to help.
Mmm. I saw that report
you did on Sasquatch.
It was fair and even-handed.
I'll do it!
Somebody had to take
the baby-sitter home.
Then I noticed she was sitting
on the Gummi Venus,
so I grabbed it off her.
Oh, just thinking
about that sweet, sweet candy...
(gurgling)
I just wish
I had another one right now.
But the most
important thing is...
That was really
great, Mr. Simpson.
We got everything we need.
Okay. Say, can you introduce
me to the Sasquatch?
I like his style.
He-he!
Here comes the bouncing
ball of justice!
Tonight on Rock Bottom,
we go undercover at a sex farm
for sex hookers.
I keep telling you,
I just grow sorghum here.
Uh-huh, and where are
the hookers?
Round back. Oops.
But first...
She was a university
honors student
who devoted her life to kids
until the night
a grossly overweight pervert
named Homer Simpson gave her
a crash course in depravity.
"Baby-sitter and the Beast."
Aw, crap!
Somebody had to take
the baby-sitter home.
Then I noticed she was
sitting on her sweet can...
so I grabbed her sweet can.
Oh, just thinking
about her can...
I just wish I had her sweet,
sweet, s-s-sweet can.
So, Mr. Simpson, you admit
you grabbed her can?
What do you have to say
in your defense?
Mr. Simpson, your silence will
only incriminate you further.
No, Mr. Simpson.
Don't take your anger out on me!
Get back! Get back!
Mr. Simpson, no!
ANNOUNCER: Dramatization--
May not have happened.
Marge, kids, everything's
going to be just fine.
Now go upstairs
and pack your bags.
We're going
to start a new life...
under the sea.
(calypso music playing)
♪ Under the sea ♪
♪ There'll be no accusations ♪
♪ Just friendly crustaceans ♪
♪ Under the sea ♪
Homer, that's your solution to everything.
To move under the sea.
It's not going to happen!
Not with that attitude.
Look, maybe this whole
thing will blow over.
(helicopters approaching)
It didn't blow over, Marge.
Nothing ever blows over for me.
(humming)
(screams)
Simpson Scandal update: Homer
sleeps nude in an oxygen tent
which he believes
gives him sexual powers.
Hey, that's a half-truth!
I don't know Homer Simpson.
I never met
Homer Simpson
or had any contact
with him, but...
I'm sorry.
I-I can't go on.
That's okay.
Your tears say more
than real evidence ever could.
Today on Ben--
Mothers and runaway daughters
reunited by their hatred
of Homer Simpson.
And here's your host,
Gentle Ben.
(applause)
(growling)
I just have
one thing to say--
Let's have less
Homer Simpsons
and more money
for public schools.
(growling)
Ben, I have
a question...
(growling)
No, Ben. No!
(all screaming)
(tone sounds)
♪♪
ANNOUNCER:
And now we return
to Fox Night at the Movies--
Homer S.: Portrait of
an Ass-Grabber.
starring Dennis Franz.
Ooh! Portrait!
Sounds classy.
Doesn't it?
(tires screeching)
(maniacal laughter)
(yowls)
No, Mr. Simpson!
A cat is a living creature.
I don't care.
-(tires screech)
-(cat yowls)
Now, I'm gonna
grab me somethin' sweet!
No, Mr. Simpson!
That's sexual harassment.
If you keep it up, I'll yell so
loud the whole country'll hear.
(laughing)
With a man
in the White House?
Not likely.
(cackling)
This is hour 57 of our live,
round-the-clock coverage
outside the Simpson Estate.
Remember, by the way,
to tune in tonight at 8:00
for highlights of today's vigil
including when
the garbage man came
and when Marge Simpson
put the cat out...
possibly because
it was harassed.
We don't know.
Of course, there's no way to see
into the Simpson home
without some kind of
infrared heat-sensitive camera.
So, let's turn it on.
Now, this technology is new
to me, but I'm pretty sure
that's Homer Simpson
in the oven rotating slowly.
His body temperature has
risen to over 400 degrees.
He's literally stewing
in his own juices.
Now, here are some results
from our phone-in poll.
95% of the people believe
Homer Simpson is guilty.
Of course, this is just
a television poll
which is not legally binding,
unless Proposition 304 passes,
and we all pray it will.
Aw, I don't have
a friend in the world.
(clamoring)
BARNEY:
We're Homer's true friends!
Oh, really?
Come on. Let us through,
you vultures.
Oh, Marge, it's a miracle.
How can you judge this man
without talking to the people
who know him best?
We got the real dirt
on Homer Simpson
and the bidding starts at 10 Gs!
-I bid 10 Gs!
-10-5 Gs!
-Fifteen!
-Fifteen-five!
Oh...
I need a hug.
(murmuring)
How come
you guys hesitated?
Sorry, Dad. We do believe
in you. We really do.
It's just hard not
to listen to TV.
It's spent so
much more time
raising us
than you have.
Oh... maybe TV is right.
TV's always right.
HOMER:
Are you hugging the TV?
-BOTH: No.
-(kisses TV loudly)
(audience cheering)
And the number one reference
that I am running into the ground
is Homer Simpson!
(audience cheering)
Ay-yi-yi!
Es Homer Simpson!
Me ha molestado! Oh!
Ohh. I like it better
when they're making fun
of people who aren't me.
I know!
Evening at the Improv.
They never talk about anything
beyond the 1980s.
See, I think about weird stuff.
Like, what would happen
if E.T. and Mr. T. had a baby.
Well, you'd get
Mr. E.T., wouldn't you?
And you know, I think he'd
sound a little something like this.
(as Mr. T.):
I pity the fool who doesn't
phone home.
(chuckles) Ooh, I wouldn't
want to be Mr. T. right now.
Homer, the kids
have a great idea
how you can clear
your name!
The media is making
a monster out of you
because they don't care
about the truth.
All they care about
is entertainment.
Well, you need a forum
where they don't even know
the meaning of the word
entertainment.
Public Access television.
Aw, but those shows
all look so crummy.
Well, we can
dress it up a bit.
We can bring a fern,
and a folding chair from the garage
and the most decorative thing
of all-- the truth.
There are only 49 stars
on that flag.
I'll be deep in the cold,
cold ground
before I recognize Missouri.
Now it's time for the
Innocence Report, with Homer Simpson.
Hello. I am Homer Simpson,
or as some of you wags
have dubbed me, "Father Goose."
You know, everybody believed
the worst about me right away.
Nobody cares that
I didn't do it.
But I didn't.
Okay, look, I've done
some bad things in my life,
but harassing women
is not one of them.
Like one time
we were having this race
with this stupid old-timey
bicycle with the big wheel in front.
So I figure,
"We'll see about that."
so I get this big chunk
of cinder block, and I--
-(groaning)
-Oh, got to go.
Innocent.
Dad, you did it.
I am so proud of you.
The switchboards
are lighting up!
ALL:
Yay!
Two calls.
That's our best ever!
Hello? No, Janice
doesn't live here.
Hello?
Yes, I am interested
in long-distance savings.
Very interested.
(all groaning)
Marge, this is
so depressing.
My only hope is this
homemade Prozac.
Mmm... needs
more ice cream.
(doorbell rings)
So, uh, you don't like
the old-time bikes, huh?
(groans)
(doorbell rings)
Homer, I love amateur video.
And your show is the most
amateur video I ever saw.
My hobby is secretly
videotaping couples and gals.
I dare not come forward,
because in this country
it makes you look
like a pervert!
But every single Scottish person
does it!
Oh, baby.
Oh, yeah. Oh, baby.
Oh, no. That's Mayor Quimby.
Ah. Here we go.
Precious Venus.
(gasps)
(gurgling)
(screams)
Thank you.
(chomping)
(sighing)
Dad, this clears
you completely!
You know the courts
might not work anymore,
but as long as everybody
is videotaping everyone else,
justice will be done.
See?
Hmm. Homer,
I thought you were an animal,
but your daughter said
you were a decent man.
I guess she was right.
You're both right.
In our mad pursuit
of the scoop,
we members of the press
sometimes make mistakes.
Rock Bottom would like to make
the following corrections.
Wow! V-8 juice isn't
one-eighth gasoline.
And Ted Koppel is a robot.
There's you, Dad!
ALL:
Yay!
Tomorrow, on Rock Bottom...
He's a foreigner who takes
perverted videos of you
when you least suspect it.
He's Rowdy Roddy Peeper.
That man is sick!
Groundskeeper Willie
saved you, Homer.
But listen to the music.
He's evil.
Hasn't this experience
taught you
you can't believe
everything you hear?
Marge, my friend,
I haven't learned a thing.
(all grumbling)
Let's never fight again. Aw...
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.