♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Well, you're certainly doing
your job today, Mr. Sun.
Oh, rats.
And here we have
the world-famous Beatles,
exactly as they looked
performing on
"The Ed Sullivan Show."
I hardly think it's fair
to be charged full price.
I'm up to my knees in the
original cast of "M.A.S.H."
♪ Sunshine on my shoulders
makes me happy... ♪
Homer, my hat goes off
to you.
It's cool in here, boy.
For the rest of the summer,
we can live inside
the refrigerator.
Homer, the fridge wasn't
meant to be used this way.
Although I must say,
it's certainly refreshing.
I got the idea
when I noticed
the refrigerator was cold.
MARGE:
Won't this overload the motor?
(motor sputtering)
Marge, can you set
the oven to cold?
(moans)
MAN:
Ice cream! Ice cream!
(both gasping)
I'm all out of ice cream!
It's true, you know.
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Fresh out of ice cream!
(both groan)
(truck music plays)
Chili! Red hot
Texas-style chili.
And we got ginger ale.
Boilin' hot Texas style ginger-ale...
Texas!
Ugh!
Aw, face it, Bart.
Our salvation isn't
just going to roll by
on the back
of some stupid truck.
Whoa!
I got to replace that window.
BOTH:
Pool-mobile?!
Look, Lisa, I snatched
five bathing suits.
All Martin's.
Take your best shot.
I'm wearing 17 layers.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ooh!
I brought this on myself.
Okay, little dudes, time's up.
Everybody out!
(kids groaning)
-Time's up?!
-So long, Lis.
I'm gonna stowaway underwater,
and go where the pool goes.
Have a good life.
Sorry, Bart dude.
We got to fill this
with epsom salts
and jam it on over
to the old folks' home.
Oh, well. Same time
tomorrow, Otto?
Ha ha ha!
No way, man.
One day of summer is
all we're budgeted for.
I guess it is
kind of a tease.
(police sirens blaring
from TV)
Dad.
Dad!
Yes, Lisa.
Dad, as you know,
we've been swimming,
and we've developed
a taste for it.
We both agree that
getting our own pool
is the only way to go.
Now before you respond,
you must understand
that your refusal would result
in months and months of...
BOTH: Can we have a pool, Dad?!
Can we have a pool, Dad?!
Can we--
I understand.
Let us celebrate
our new arrangement
with the adding
of chocolate to milk.
Over here we have
"The Hick Tub"
The "Insta-rust."
That's "The Lightning Magnet."
-That's "The Tinkler."
-Whoo! "The Tinkler."
I like the sound of that.
We'll take it.
Is it true should we wait at least
an hour after eating before we go in?
Look, question lady, this job
is not what I really do, okay?
I play keyboards.
HOMER:
All right.
Everybody in the pool!
'Tis a fine barn, but sure
'tis no pool, English.
D'oh-eth!
-Is it a pool yet?
-Yes, Dad.
Whoo-hoo!
(doorbell ringing)
Who could that be?
Uh, hello, uh,
Mrs., uh, Bart.
Is your pool ready yet?
-(groans)
-(children cheer)
Bart, are all these children
friends of yours?
Friends
and well-wishers, yes.
-Hey, Bart.
-Hiya, Bart.
-My buddy Bart.
-Hey, Bart.
Hello, Mrs. Cumberdale.
Mmm.
People! People!
It's time we all discussed
the pool safety rules.
ALL:
Jump, Bart, jump!
You got it.
Hey, Bart,
your epidermis is showing!
It is?
Oh... Ooh.
Whoa...
See, epidermis
means your hair.
(Bart screaming)
(thuds)
So, technically it's true.
That's what makes it
so funny.
Pardon me a moment.
Ha-ha.
Hey, Nelson,
he's really hurt.
I think he
broke his leg.
I said, "Ha-ha!"
Get this kid a magazine.
Stat.
I'm sorry, that leg's
gonna have to come off.
-(both gasp)
-(chuckles)
Did I say leg?
I meant that wet bathing suit.
I'm afraid you'll need a cast
on that broken bone.
Oh, I'm going to miss
the whole summer.
Don't worry, boy.
When you get a job like me,
you'll miss every summer.
Isn't it amazing the same day
you got a pool
is the same day we realized
we liked you?
The timing worked out great,
don't you think?
-Hi.
Hey, guys, sign my cast?
Sign my cast?
Guys?
(laughing)
Milhouse.
Uh... Hi, Bart.
Faithful Milhouse.
You'll spend the long,
hot days by my side,
won't you?
Oh, I think I lost
my glasses in your pool.
I better go in
and find them.
But you're wearing
your glasses.
No, I'm not.
Oh, look,
Bart's all alone.
Maybe I should
keep him company,
at least
for a little while.
-BOY: Lisa! Hey, look!
-Boy 2: Watch this!
Uh...
Heh heh. Coming.
(groans)
Well, it looks like it's
just you and me, Barty boy.
Oh, great, I get to spend
the summer with my brain.
What fun can you have
in a pool anyway
that you can't have
in a bathtub
with a garbage bag
taped around your cast?
(kids laughing)
(Busby Berkeley style
musical extravaganza)
Traitors.
Go on and have your pool.
I'm fine by myself right here.
Ah-ha-ha!
(shuddering)
(brains pulsating)
Oh.
(screaming)
(laughing)
You know, this isn't so bad.
I'll just spend the summer
getting better acquainted
with an old friend
called television.
(cheering)
(goofy laugh)
Hope you enjoyed that, kids
'cause Krusty's out of here
for the summer.
In the meantime,
we'll be running...
(groans)
Classic Krusty.
Enjoy.
(chuckling)
Good evening.
Tonight my guest is AFL-CIO
chairman, George Meany,
who will be discussing
collective bargaining
agreements.
It's a pleasure
to be here, Krusty.
Let me be blunt.
Is there a labor crisis
in America today?
Well, that depends what
you mean by crisis.
(groans)
Ah, there's nothing like
rising with the sun
for a quiet, peaceful dip
in your very own pool.
(whooping)
Whoo!
(shrieking)
Eww...
Lisa, the blob has got me.
Don't touch me,
or he'll get you too.
Dad, you have to put chlorine
in the water every day
to keep it clean.
Chlorine, eh?
(all bawling)
Oh, my face is on fire.
(groans)
Oh, look.
There's Bart.
Wave to him.
Hmm, maybe we should spend
more time with Bart.
He's becoming
isolated and weird.
I swear I don't know
where the bombs are.
Only the miners know that.
(evil voice)
Maybe this will loosen your tongue.
Wha! No! Ah!
Uh, Bart?
Don't turn on
that light!
Sorry, I just came to see
-how you were feeling.
-I'm fine. Just fine.
What are you writing here?
A play?
Uh... No.
Yuh-huh. "Cast of characters:
Viceroy Fizzlebottom
a hearty cherub
of a man..."
Give me that.
It's a work in progress.
So, how do
you like being
Miss Popularity?
Oh, well, you know,
it ain't so great.
Bart, it's the best thing
that ever happened to me
in my whole life!
Well, anyway I brought
you a present.
Look, it's the telescope
I won at the optics festival.
There was an optics festival,
and I wasn't informed?
-You go now.
-But...
Go!
What have we here?
"The Lighter Side of Hippies."
Ha ha! They don't care
whose toes they step on.
(chuckles)
(Marge and Homer laughing)
MARGE:
This was a lovely idea, Homie.
Come here and kiss me.
Mmm...
(screaming)
CHIEF WIGGUM:
Do not be alarmed.
Continue swimming naked.
(munching)
Aw, come on. Continue.
Come on. Aw...
All right, Lou. Open fire.
BART:
Wow.
The universe is so boring.
I know.
I'll use this to peer into
Springfield's seamy underbelly.
(Bart groans)
It turned out it was
his evil twin.
(chuckling)
(Bart groans)
(Jimmy Stewart voice)
Grace, come here.
There's a sinister-looking kid
I want you to see.
(Bart groans)
I'm never ever going to see
anything interesting
with this stupid piece of junk.
(high-pitched scream)
That came from Flanders' house.
Oh...
(high-pitched scream)
Oh, my God.
What have I done?
I've killed her.
Can't be what it looks like.
This is Flanders
we're talking about.
Nah, I'll just watch some TV.
Now, what you've been
waiting for.
Another long raga
by Ravi Shanker.
Shan-kar.
Shankar. Groovy, man.
(groans)
(snoring)
(noise outside)
Huh?
BART:
Huh? Whoa!
This can't be what
it looks like.
There's got to be
some other explanation.
I wish there was
some other explanation for this.
But there isn't.
I'm a murderer.
Then that's not
the real Ned Flanders.
I'm a murdiddly-erdler!
If that's not Flanders,
he's done his homework.
Daddy, where's Mommy?
We miss her.
Mommy... had to go away.
She's with God now.
BOTH:
Yay! Can we go there too?
Soon enough.
BOTH:
Yay!
(gasping)
He's going to kill
Rod and Todd too.
That's horrible...
in principle.
Look, Lisa.
I found this change
on the bottom
of the pool.
You can have it.
Thanks, Nelson.
Somebody took
my juice money!
Lisa, please join my family
for a weekend in the country.
There'll be hunting, charades,
and ever so many delightful
romantic misunderstandings.
(clamoring for attention)
They're only using you
for your pool, you know.
Shut up, brain!
I got friends now.
I don't need you anymore.
Duh... Yeah, I'd love
to go to your house.
(chortling)
Ah, my plan
has come to fruition.
Soon I'll be queen
of summertime.
Uh, king. King!
(whispering)
Dude, Buzz has it
an even wussier kid
has an even better pool
than this.
Huh?
Hello?
Hey, I'm stuck in here.
I got to think
of a way to get out.
Well, well, well.
Look who's come crawling back.
Listen, Ned Flanders
murdered his wife.
But why?
She's such a fox.
I mean, what's
on Fox tonight?
Something ribald,
no doubt.
I wish you'd stop spreading
bad rumors about people.
Remember how you got Grampa
tarred and feathered?
Sure. That was
20 minutes ago.
Gonna be in the tub
for a while.
Bart, I'm really sorry I've
been ignoring you lately.
I got carried away
with being popular,
but now that I'm
unpopular again,
I want you to know
I'm here for you.
You can start making it up
to me right now.
Flanders is leaving
the house.
I want you to sneak in there
and bring me back
some evidence.
And something
sweet for later.
Bart, I'm here for you,
but I'm not gonna
break into
somebody's house.
All right.
You're right, you're right.
Let's just forget about that.
Here.
Let me read to you
from my play.
Ahem. (Cockney accent)
"'Kippers for breakfast, Aunt Helga?
Is it St. Swithen's
day already?'"
"'Tis,' replied
Aunt Helga..."
I'm going, I'm going!
(gasps)
A human head!
Phew!
Oh. Of course.
Oh, no. He's back.
Flanders is back.
Lisa, get out of there.
No, Lisa, don't go upstairs.
You'll be trapped!
An axe!
He's got an axe.
I'll save you, Lisa.
Ow!
Uh, I'll save you
by calling the police.
MOVIEFONE VOICE:
Hello, and welcome to the Springfield
Police Department resc-u-fone.
If you know the name of
the felony being committed,
press 1.
To choose from a list
of felonies, press 2.
If you are being murdered
or are calling
from a rotary phone,
please stay on the line.
(frustrated growl)
You have selected "Regicide."
If you know the name
of the king or queen
being murdered, press 1.
(yelling)
I'll save you, cast or no cast.
(grunting)
Got to save Lisa,
trash can or no trash can.
(straining)
D'oh!
Oh!
Oh, no.
That sinister-looking kid
is coming to kill me.
Help! Help! Aah!
FLANDERS:
♪ Mary had a little lamb ♪
♪ Little lamb,
little lamb ...♪
(gasps)
Oh, no. Oh, no...
(panting and grunting)
Oh!
Aah! Aah!
Unh!
(footsteps)
(grunting)
(growling)
It's time to put you away.
-(gasps)
Put you away for good.
(screaming)
No!
Ho... what the gumdrops
is going on here?
I came to stop you
from murdering Lisa
like you murdered your wife.
Murdered?
Ohhh...
Oh no, I've just been
in the country for a week.
But I distinctly
heard you say
that Maude was with God.
That's right.
I was at Bible camp.
I was learning
how to be more judgmental.
But I saw the murder,
and then I saw you bury the corpse
in the backyard.
All right, it's true.
I am a murderer.
(gasping)
I over-watered Maude's
favorite ficus plant,
I panicked and then
I buried the remains.
-(gasps)
-I was hoping to replace it
-before you got home.
-Oh.
But I heard a woman scream.
Huh? Well, now,
that I can't explain.
Found it, chief.
(high-pitched scream)
Oh. Well, I guess that
explains everything.
Not everything.
There's still
the little matter
of the whereabouts
of your wife.
Um, I'm right here.
Oh, I see.
Then everything is wrapped up
in a neat little package.
Really, I mean that.
Sorry if it sounded sarcastic.
(laughing and clamoring)
More friends! More allies!
More, I say!
Hang those who talk of less!
There's a few inches
over here! Ho!
(screaming)
My precious pool
and its lifestyle
accoutrements. No!
(all grumbling)
Out of here.
Ha-ha.
Oh.
The gentle caress
of a summer breeze.
(pop ballad musical intro)
♪ The summer wind ♪
♪ Came blowing in ♪
♪ From across the sea... ♪
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.