♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Remember, Bart--
I mean,
Dances in Underwear--
We take
the white man alive.
All right,
Thinks Too Much.
It shall be so.
Keep your eyes peeled
for injuns.
I mean Native Americans.
They're after us
because we gave them
those blankets infected
with cooties.
-I ate all my caps. Ooh!
-(explosion)
Throw down your weapons
and kiss the prairie,
cow dorks.
Aah!
Oh, why do we have to play
this corny old game anyway?
I brought my jacks.
(gasps)
I got twosies.
NELSON: Eh!
-Hey!
-Ow!
That's not fair, Nelson.
They didn't have
the Killmatic-3000 back then.
Hey, records from that era
are spotty at best.
(groans)
(bell ringing)
MARGE:
Bart, Lisa, time for church.
MRS. VAN HOUTEN:
Milhouse, time for church.
MAN: Shlomo, time for
your violin lesson.
(all screaming)
(grumbling)
Why the crap do we have
to go to church anyway?
You just answered
your own question
with that commode mouth.
Besides, you kids
need to learn
morals and decency
and how to love your fellow man.
And with flaming swords,
the Aromites did pierce
the eyes of their fellow men,
and did feast
on what flowed forth.
Among whom also we all
once conducted ourselves
in the lusts of our flesh...
♪ I'm a troll man ♪
♪ Doo-doo, doo-doo,
doo-doo, doo ♪
♪ I'm a troll man ♪
MARGE: I don't want you
playing with something
that has such bizarre hair.
Awful, awful hair.
Mmm!
And now, my daughter Jessica,
who has just returned
from boarding school,
will read the same passage
I just read.
I noticed a few of you
weren't paying attention.
(groans)
(gasps)
Wow!
There is a God.
I'm telling you,
the light would work better
if it pointed out to sea.
Dar, shut up.
I know what I'm doing.
Yar, I hate the sea
and everything in it.
Bye. Bye-bye,
bye-bye.
Thank you for choosing
our church. Bye-bye.
Oh. I've never felt
this way about a girl before.
My long search
is finally over.
(clearing throat)
Hi, I'm Bart Simpson.
I was incredibly moved
by your reading.
I don't think God's words
have ever sounded so plausible.
Thanks, Art.
Um, I have to go
over here now.
Oh!
(moaning)
Don't be so hard
on yourself, Bart.
It's not your fault
Jessica doesn't like you.
Is it my hair, my overbite?
The fact I've worn
the same clothes
day in, day out
for the last four years?
No, Bart. I just think
you and Jessica are too different
from each other to get along.
She's a sweet, kind
reverend's daughter,
and you're the devil's
cabana boy.
Hmm.
Good.
Very good.
Ralph, Jesus did
not have wheels.
(gasping)
Bart Simpson?
Yes, ma'am.
I'd like to return
to your wonderful
Sunday school, please.
But, Bart, we banned you
from Sunday school.
You were happy, we were happy,
everybody was happy.
Particularly the hamster.
I've changed my ways.
Please give me
another chance, ma'am.
All right, Bart.
The Bible does teach
forgiveness.
Class, I want you to welcome back
our prodigal son.
What's
prodigal mean?
Oh, dear.
You know, the great thing
about Sunday school
is we're finally learning
something we can use.
Yeah, so true.
I have to turn my chair
this way now.
Somehow I got to convince her
I'm a good person.
All right. I have to sit here
and behave no matter what.
Okay, class, we have
a special treat today
for pass-around:
A replica of the slingshot
David used to slay Goliath.
While you kids are
looking at that,
I'll busy myself
in this file cabinet.
Must... fight... Satan.
Make it... up to him...
...later.
(sighs)
You know, I was considering
staying after school
and helping
teacher clean up.
(yawns)
Do you ever think anything
you don't say?
(shouting and cheering)
There is just no pleasing
a girl like that.
All that unnecessary behaving.
I'm all tense through
the chestal area.
I need relief.
(bagpipe playing)
Though the kilt was only
for day-to-day wear,
in battle,
we donned a full-length
ball gown covered in sequins.
The idea was to blind
your opponent with luxury.
(gasping)
Ah, 'tis no more
than what God gave me,
you puritan pukes.
(laughing)
That'll hold me.
At least till I get my hands
on some kind of explosives.
(gasps)
Congratulations, Simpson.
You just fell for our sting,
and won yourself
three months' detention.
There's no such thing
as Scotchtoberfest.
There's not?
You used me, Skinner!
You used me!
Three months? (groans)
Hi, Bart.
I saw the way
they set you up.
That was really unfair.
(groans)
Want to have dinner
at my house tonight?
Really?
Uh... sure.
Great.
We eat at 7:00.
There's only one thing to do
at a moment like this...
strut.
("Stayin' Alive" playing)
I can't believe
my little boy
is already going
on his first date.
♪ Sunrise, sunset ♪
♪ Sunrise, sunset... ♪
♪ Cats in the cradle
and the silver spoon... ♪
♪ Yes, we have no bananas ♪
(sobbing)
Oh, that's sweet, homer.
Our son is growing up,
isn't he?
No, it's not that.
Didn't you hear?
They have no bananas.
They have no bananas today!
So, Bart,
how's school going?
Jessica always gets
straight A's.
Well, in my family, grades
aren't that important.
It's what you learn
that counts.
6 x 5-- What is it?
Um, actually, numbers
don't have much use
in my future career:
Olympic gold medal
rocket sled champ.
Hmm. I didn't know the rocket sled
was an Olympic event.
Well, no offense, lady, but what
you don't know could fill a warehouse.
(gasping)
Young man,
explain yourself.
Sorry. I have kind
of a short fuse,
which some
find charming.
Speaking of charming,
watching Fox last night,
I heard a rather amusing story.
This character named Martin
was feeling rather randy,
and he was heard to remark...
(grunts)
And don't you ever come near
my daughter again.
Never have I heard such
gratuitous use of the word "butt".
-But, but, but...
-Make him stop.
-Make him stop!
You're bad,
Bart Simpson.
No, I'm not.
I'm really--
Yes, you are.
You're bad.
And I like it.
I'm bad to the bone, honey.
Let's go find some fun.
But your father said--
I told the rev
I was going to my room
to say my prayers.
Smart, beautiful and a liar.
So much better than
that Sarah, plain and tall.
♪♪
Woo!
Right there.
Put it right there.
(both laughing)
Oh, excellent.
You're incredible, Jessica.
Your throws, your catches,
your spirals, your loops.
It's like the toilet paper
is an extension of your body.
Wee!
No way would
a minister's daughter
go out with you.
Oh, yeah? I'll prove it.
Hey, Jessica.
Yes, am I supposed
to know you?
Jessica, we just-- Oof!
That's for besmirching
an innocent girl's name.
Why?
I'm sorry, Bart.
You know my parents
can't find out about us.
And besides, if it's secret,
it's even more exciting.
I guess.
Hey, you want to
go skateboarding?
Um, actually,
I was hoping I could
sit down for just a second.
Come on. It'll be fun.
Wow!
Now I have the energy
to do anything.
Oh!
Just give me two minutes.
BART: Jessica, I think
this is too steep.
Bart, you can't trust your
perception at this altitude.
(grunts)
(screaming)
(laughing)
Actually, if the road surface
maintains its integrity,
I just might be able to hold on.
(Bart shouting)
(sighs)
(screams)
Oh, the glue will slow me down.
Any glue leaking?
No, that glue
ain't going nowhere.
Oh, nothing's ever
gonna stop me.
(grunting)
MAN: Oh, no.
There goes the glue after all.
No!
(gasps)
Fun, huh?
(gurgling)
(meowing)
Have you noticed
any change in Bart?
New glasses?
No. He looks like something
might be disturbing him.
Probably misses
his old glasses.
I guess we could get more
involved in Bart's activities,
but then I'd be afraid
of smothering him.
Yeah, and then
we'd get the chair.
That's not what I meant.
It was, Marge. Admit it.
(bell ringing)
-Hi.
-Uh, we should get to class.
-What's the hurry?
-We could get in trouble for being late.
Oh, you worry too much.
Come on.
If you stay here a while,
I'll let you hold my hand.
(Bart gasps)
-(alarm ringing)
-(Jessica laughs)
Teamwork.
Come on, Bart.
(siren wailing)
If I don't save the
wee turtles, who will?
Aah!
Save me from the wee turtles.
They were too quick for me.
Aah!
I can't believe it, Bart.
I'd always thought
Jessica was so sweet.
She's like a milk dud, Lis.
Sweet on the outside,
poison on the inside.
You gotta give her up.
No, no, wait. Hear my plan.
Put up with her
for seven more years.
Then we'll get married.
Once the first
baby comes along,
she's bound to settle down
and start treating me right.
After all, I deserve it.
Bart, it's naive to think
you can change a person...
Except maybe that boy
who works in the library.
Do you have
"Go, Dog, Go"?
(scoffs)
That's in juvenile.
This is young adult.
Well-read, and just
a little wild.
Ooh, if only someone
could tame him.
You're right, Lisa.
Love isn't about
fixing someone.
I'm just gonna
give her up cold turkey.
I'm not going to talk to her
or see her. It's over.
Thanks for the advice, sis.
(sighing)
There.
If I can just get through
this many days
without seeing her,
she should be completely
out of my system.
Okay, day one.
Time for church, Bart.
I bet your little friend
Jessica will be there.
D'oh!
-(soprano singing)
-Jessica.
Bart, be strong.
You don't need
that little hellcat.
Oh, Lis, she's already
drawing me to her
with her beautiful siren song.
(singing in falsetto)
Oh, that's very disturbing. Hnh!
Hey, Bart.
What?
What's wrong?
Well, Jessica,
I don't think we should
hang out together anymore.
You're turning me
into a criminal,
when all I want to be
is a petty thug.
Oh, good. Here comes
the collection plate.
Homer!
We can spare it, Marge.
We've been blessed.
You're right
about everything, Bart.
I have been too reckless.
From now on,
I am going to settle down.
(gasps)
Jessica, what are you doing?
Well, it takes money
to start a new life.
Stealing from the collection
basket is really wrong.
Even I know that.
Ah, fine.
You just lost your cut.
I'll just take that.
(gasps)
Everyone turn around
and look at this.
(gasping)
What is it, a unitarian?
(clamoring)
Just relax. For once,
you didn't do anything wrong.
Just explain yourself,
and everyone will understand.
I...
Took the money?
Yes, we know.
He confessed.
Okay.
HOMER: Stop him,
he's headed for the window!
Son, if you can look me
in the eye
and say you didn't take
the collection money,
that's all I need.
I didn't take it.
Why, you little...
How can you
look me in the eye
and lie like that?
MARGE:
Homer, stop that.
I believe him.
Tell me, if he didn't
take the money,
why is he wearing
those fancy clothes?
That's what he
wore to church.
Ooh, how convenient.
Bart, honey, do you know
who did take the money?
No.
See, son? Telling
the truth isn't so bad.
(booing)
-Crook!
-Thief!
Stealer of money from
the church collection plate!
We've got to talk.
Listen, thanks for
not turning me in.
That was sweet.
Well, it seems like if you
really care for me,
you should come forward.
Oh, don't you see, it's
because I care for you
that I can't come forward.
That doesn't make any sense.
Alright, then I just don't
feel like it, okay?
Jessica,
you're really beautiful,
but you are
not very nice.
(scoffs) Duh.
You know, with the way
you're treating me,
why should I protect you?
Because if you tell,
no one will believe you.
Remember, I'm the sweet,
perfect minister's daughter,
and you're just
yellow trash.
Huh?
So here's where you're hiding.
Yeah, this is my
only refuge
from the taunts
and accusations
of the townspeople.
Thief.
Bart, we can't just let her
get away with this!
Give it up, Lis.
She's a criminal mastermind.
She's got 108 I.Q.
She reads at
a fifth grade level,
and... (sighs)
her hair smells
like red Froot Loops.
Yeah? Well, I eat
Froot Loops for breakfast.
Because of
last week's problems,
we'll be taking
certain precautions
with this week's collection.
We really shouldn't have
let them do this.
It can't be helping
his self-esteem.
Now for our offertory reading,
Lisa Simpson,
who we'll all be
keeping an eye on.
I know most of you have already
judged my brother guilty
without any proof,
but doesn't
the Bible teach us
"Judge not, lest ye
be judged", Reverend?
I think it may be
somewhere towards the back.
There is someone among us
with a guilty conscience.
After much soul searching
I decided it would be wrong
of me to name names,
but I urge that guilty person,
here, under the eyes of God,
to come forward,
to confess and save yourself
from the torment
of your own personal hell!
Aah! I smelled some
marijuana smoke in Vietnam!
I was the one that
canceled "Star Trek"!
I left my Porsche keys
inside Mrs. Glick.
I am talking
to the collection money thief.
Only you can come forward
and end this injustice.
Oh, what the heck.
It was Jessica Lovejoy!
(all gasping)
If you search her room,
I am certain you
will find the money.
To the little girl's room.
That's the
collection money.
Oh, yeah.
Smells like church.
I guess it's obvious
what's happened here.
Bart Simpson
has somehow managed
to sneak his bedroom
into my house.
Well, come on,
use your imaginations.
No, Dad.
I did it.
It's your classic cry
for attention.
Well, young lady,
I suppose
we brought you home
from boarding school
a little prematurely.
I was expelled, Dad.
Remember the pipe bomb,
the glee club brawl?
Remember the school chapel
collection plate?
-♪ Bringing in the sheaves ♪
-Exploding toilets ring a ball?
-Come on, Dad! Pay attention to me!
♪ Sheep will all
be marching... ♪
Uh, I think you all owe
my son an apology.
-Very sorry.
-That's okay.
Appreciate it.
Mm-hmm.
BART:
Hi, Jessica.
Hi, Bart.
Come to watch me suffer?
I just wanted
to let you know
that even though this was
a difficult experience,
I really learned a lot.
I'm a little wiser
and a little less naive.
Well, I learned that
I can make men do
whatever I want.
Well, don't you see,
Jessica?
Then you really
haven't learned--
Um, would you finish
scrubbing these steps for me?
Will I?
Hey, Jessica.
Coming.
Poor sucker.
It's amazing what some guys
will do for a pretty face.
Not me, though.
Wait till she sees
the second-rate job
I do on these stairs.
(Bart laughing)
(laughing continues)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.