Guys, we're here.
We're here.
I missed you, buddy.
No, you didn't. You didn't.
Don't be a phony.
- Oh, man...
- The last episode.
- The last episode, guys.
- It's not the last.
Let's be quick this time
because I can barely breathe.
Bring something here.
Can you scooch over just a little bit?
You look like those Spartan heroes.
- Shut up, Felipe.
- It's just...
I think you should look that way.
Don't do this. Don't bully me.
Is it showing? Bullshit.
- Fuck.
- Girl, I also... The skirt...
- What now?
- Beautiful girl.
We're here together to watch
the last episode of Wild and Free.
Remember that in the the last episode,
it almost ended in a rumble.
- That's true.
- In short,
Ramon broke up with Nath again.
That's something new.
He found out she gave someone a peck,
right, baby? Gossip, right?
This series tells the story
of eight friends on vacation,
and there's no script.
Everything is real.
Let's watch this?
- Press play.
- I'm delighted, sweetheart.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
Jeez, you were rude to those guys.
That's why Mu got pissed.
I was pissed because... I was sleeping.
- Let's go to bed.
- Why are you up here?
Taynara, let's go to bed, okay?
Who? I'm fine... Who let you come up here?
Get a grip, Taynara. It's cool...
Leave me here.
I hate being woken up. I hate it.
Murilo saw me,
I was in the bathroom, furious.
Bastard, he had to get beaten.
Even I wanted to beat him.
He didn't have to come upstairs.
And I asked, "Why are you up here?"
Then I said, "But you can't come up here.
This is our bedroom. You can't be here."
That's fucked up, Tay, man.
Jeez, that's way fucked up.
I think it's the manager.
- Jeez.
- Hey, guys, how are you?
I will need you one more time at the bar.
Tonight I'm counting on the boys, okay?
See you later.
Tell him I won't come.
I'm calling in sick.
I don't want to work anymore.
Hey, Jão.
It's here.
Let's go?
Good evening, guys. Get in here.
Let's have fun tonight.
Did you like the drink?
- What? It's wonderful.
- Good?
It was prepared with love and affection.
I even put a little action figure in it.
You put a pretty little one, right?
For you can say,
"This is me."
What's your name?
- João Vitor, you?
- My name is Isadora.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Is the carioca's order still on?
It's not allowed?
- What's not allowed?
- To kiss you.
It's allowed.
I don't want to work anymore.
I'll be cool in a while.
- I have work to do.
- Aren't you working?
Didn't I tell you I had...
- I'm going back right now.
- I guess you already made her order?
Yes.
- Do it tomorrow?
- Tomorrow...
There's nothing right now.
Man, tomorrow we're having
a boat party here.
There's going to be a lot of babes,
just the local girls.
It's going to be great. Wanna go?
Yeah, man.
Invite the guys and let's go.
No problem. Cool.
All you guys need is a boat
to come along with the gang.
- Okay.
- No boat, no party.
- Deal?
- Deal.
- If you have a boat...
You have a party.
- With whisky.
- That's it.
Hey, guys. Listen up,
I've just gotten an invitation.
There's going to be a party tomorrow,
with a bunch of boats.
We were invited and we're coming.
- Where?
- It's here.
The guys who have big yachts
are going to take us for a ride.
He's at the last table there.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I saw when he invited you.
This is it, bro. You're nuts.
Remember I told you about yacht parties?
Yeah! He said there's going
to be a lot of beautiful girls.
Yeah?
Yes, the morning is mine.
Get to work, carioca.
He's working hard tonight.
This guy is a slacker.
After my shift, I want to talk to you...
You've always said good things...
After you're done, we'll talk, along with
the people who are working, okay?
You'd better say it now.
Here's the thing.
I've just gotten invited with all the guys
to take a boat ride tomorrow.
There's going to be a party.
There's going to be a lot of boats...
A ride on the high seas.
But we don't have a boat, you do.
And I'd like to propose some way
of paying you back, working for you...
The nerve of you guys!
- For us to enjoy our...
- You want my boat again?
- If you want to come along, that's okay.
- You can take the boat.
I have an appointment at the end
of the day, not the whole day.
I need the boat by evening.
- Cool?
- We'll return it in the afternoon.
You're the best boss in the world.
I'm not lending it to you, but to João.
Oh, fuck! You're fucked up!
But you can go along with him.
- If we want.
- Get to work.
Don't touch me.
Get to work. Take off.
I want to see it. Dance.
- I'll come along.
- Will you?
I have to wear this for 15 minutes.
Fuck.
There's going to be a party
called The Roof.
What kind of music?
It's deep house.
Wow, that's cool.
I hope it's not country again.
It would be cool.
It's the best, right?
Low ceiling, right?
Is there room for everybody in here?
Is there room?
Hey, brother...
Look at this place.
One for all, all for one!
Do you have any idea?
Are you coming back from Rosa?
- We've just arrived.
- From Rosa?
No, we just arrived in Floripa, at 7:00.
You're back. How did it go there?
- I'm back, guys.
- Do you remember Rosa?
Oh, jeez...
- You're very hot, man.
- Thanks.
Really, I missed you.
All she thinks about is you.
She said, "I'll get there, and he'll be
with some girl, what am I gonna do?"
You didn't know I was going to be here.
No, I didn't.
Bro...
Really, are you here?
Hey, hey...
Come here.
One more troublemaker from yesterday.
- One more...
- He didn't do anything.
Don't even talk to me.
He didn't do anything.
- It wasn't him?
- It wasn't him, baby.
Do they want a mess?
That's what they're going to have.
We did start yesterday, and they saw it.
Luan said,
"We met six chicks outside.
We invited them to the afterparty."
I said,
"Okay, let's invite six guys, too."
That's how things are going to be, get it?
I'm done being a fool.
'Cause they bring girls every time,
and we don't do anything.
We're polite, we're friendly.
And so on...
I'll bring somebody.
He's got to know how to control himself.
The boys were very stressed...
Tay said that one of the boys teased her.
So, Murilo was already
kind of, you know...
I apologize for whatever I did, okay?
I didn't think I was going
to meet you here, really.
Nath kissed him...
What is this guy doing here? I told you...
I asked him to dance.
The box is yours and mine, too.
She's crazy...
You're right, you know?
I'm right. I have the same right...
But the respect... Lower your finger.
You invited women I didn't like
and had to put up with.
Whoever I want
is getting in the house.
Okay. You're right.
What are you going to do?
Am I a jerk? I kiss whoever I want.
From now on, that's how it's going to be.
Are you happy?
Hey...
Broo, don't fight with me.
"Bro" my ass. I'm not your "bro."
- Murilo.
- I'm not your bro.
That's wrong, this guy threatened
me yesterday. If he stays, I leave.
- What guy?
- This Vitor guy.
You're inviting guys, that's okay.
But this guy won't stay.
I'm warning you.
Tell him to leave,
or else there's going to be a mess.
Can I tell you something?
You're all my brothers.
I defend you if you want it.
But, bro, I have to put up
with every girl. Every girl.
- Come to the bathroom.
- Just a sec.
I have to put up with every girl.
He did no harm, it's quite the opposite.
He was good to me because he's a partner.
Now I tell
the guy I like to leave?
- Weren't you with another one?
- Bro, regardless.
Bro, he won't stay.
This is wrong.
He better behave
or I'm kicking his ass.
Hey... Let's go home.
- Look at the snipers...
- Look over here.
No, I'm going to...
- Press pause.
- It was Nath who did the inviting. Damn.
She's a troublemaker. He asked,
"What is this guy doing here?"
The box was theirs... She said,
"I invited him. The box is mine, too."
She put that guy from the mess in the box,
together with the guy who...
And she even kissed him.
This chick is doing it on purpose...
Let's say I don't like Boca Rosa...
I prefer girls with red lipstick,
or whatever.
I almost fought with her, I called her
names. Are you gonna put her beside me?
- On purpose?
- There's going to be trouble.
You have to avoid that, man.
It's common sense.
Common sense.
Nath is hooking up with the guy
wearing the white shirt.
- I want Nath to fuck off.
- Oh, no.
Stop it now.
You don't listen to me.
That chick is a jerk.
Let me tell you something...
You're hooking up with some guy,
the friend of...
Pull yourself together...
You're hooking up with some guy...
Are you on her side?
You can't be with him...
But she broke up with Ramon?
But that's not the problem.
If she's hooking up or not...
Nathália celebrated, did you feel that?
The fire in her eyes...
She already knew...
Fight in the house, the house isn't mine,
I'm leaving.
But fighting at the party
is so wrong, man.
Guys, fighting anywhere
is wrong, anywhere.
I guess some people
go looking for trouble.
If the guy is jealous...
He says,
"I'll have my girl wearing a skirt...
Wait...
Back in the day,
we had funk party for this.
- Really?
- No, we had side A, side B...
Wait a sec.
You go to a party...
You dress up with your girlfriend.
You go to pick a fight?
Me?
I don't even get out of the house...
If I go out, I'll go to a restaurant...
There are jerks who go out to fight.
I'd pay my bill and leave.
But they want to fight.
The dudes are there...
They're waiting for something bad.
They want to fight.
It's make it or break it, honey.
She thinks she owns him.
It's not just about him,
it's about everybody.
Literally, she doesn't make up her mind.
She says one thing and does another.
She's batshit crazy.
If you were in love with her...
- Girl, I don't fall in love.
- Never?
The last time I fell in love I was 17.
I was cheated on, wrote a song,
been out there since then.
- Which song?
- Open bar.
He betrayed me with a boy who went
to school with me. He came to me and said,
"I have to tell you something
because I'm your friend.
I'm hooking up with your boyfriend."
- And then...
- Just like that?
And it's a song.
DJ, hit it
I can see your panties.
Darling, it's just panties.
I'm all shaking here, for Christ's sake.
But, girl, you hook up with everybody.
Are you talking to me or to Bia?
- Both of you.
- You allow yourself meeting people.
I allow myself... I'm an allowable person.
I don't know if this word exists.
No, she does it, too.
Girl, we're here to live, right?
I think... His feelings are over.
We're talking too much. Press play.
If you spit on me again...
It's the last episode. If he spits
on me again, I'm going to... Fuck, man.
Gosh.
At last, home.
It's going to start, me and Bia.
Nathália!
Everything is a mess.
Me and you.
Let's play. Nath, pay them back.
We have to make him lose.
It was my turn, right?
High five. I'm here to work hard.
Just don't smell my neck.
We're coming.
Ouch, fuck, let's go, let's go.
Look, be gentle at the party.
- I like charm.
- Hey, sweetheart?
She dumped the guy
and is now with the old one?
Is the revenge tonight?
- Yeah...
- I'm terrified.
She dumped the cute one and chose him.
She chose the annoying one?
She's a real fool.
I'm terrified, girl.
That she dumped the other one
and chose the...
Girl, she's a fool.
Girl, why?
I gave a lot of advice.
Look at the cute one, so pretty,
so nice and quiet,
then she comes back to the annoying one.
She comes back to...
I told Nath...
I'm going to get it for you.
Man, you're wasted.
- I'm going to go.
- Already?
- I'm beat.
- Okay...
- Let's have drinks, okay?
- Sure, man...
It was cool. It was cool seeing you.
Take care. Go for it.
No problem, that's it.
- Are you leaving together?
- Yes, because...
You're leaving together.
I have to talk to Nath.
- You guys talk later.
- No, not later.
If you had enough time...
You came together,
you leave together.
Chill out, yesterday...
You're leaving together.
I want to talk to Nath.
We don't even live together.
- No.
- Nath, I'm leaving.
Bia, I'm winning.
I came to say goodbye.
It was good to see you.
Enjoy the last few days.
Girl, you were a total fucking loser.
- She was, yesterday.
- What? Why?
You have to make up your mind.
You brought the dude
to be with you, and abandoned him.
- He left.
- You abandoned him
- to stalk Ramon.
- You ignored him.
I was playing.
No. You were stalking Ramon.
You abandoned...
And you said, "I don't want anything."
Come on, bro, fuck this.
I won't say anything anymore.
Don't ask for my opinion anymore.
You two work things out.
I won't say anything.
But they ask for an opinion,
and what I think about...
Who asked for your opinion?
Did I ask for your opinion?
There it is.
Blondie is fighting for her.
Blondie.
Fuck, bro. I love you both
and I'll defend both of you.
You have to make up your mind.
- I did.
- It's an on-off relationship...
They broke up today
because she said she wasn't sure.
But then there's a party,
and he chases her.
Did I chase her tonight?
It's not about tonight.
He didn't care about her tonight.
- It's not about tonight.
- She was after him.
- Me?
- Yes, girl.
You were after him here, girl.
Your boy left
because you said you were after Ramon.
Girl, we all saw it.
My boy, my ass. I don't have anyone.
You hooked up with him
and brought him.
So what?
He left because you were after
another guy.
Girl, it's...
I do whatever I want.
Yes, you're single.
You said you wanted to bring him over.
I do whatever I want.
If I want to hook up with Ramon,
- I'll do it. If I want to hook up with...
- Not with Ramon, not anymore.
I warned her many times.
Then she got jealous,
and the gang got blamed.
She didn't hook up with me.
She dumped him for you.
I didn't even understand.
I won't treat her badly,
but I didn't hook up with her.
She made a scene, man.
Let her do it.
It's over, bro.
I won't kick the chick out of bed,
but I won't do anything with her.
I don't have any more feelings, you know?
It's over, bro.
Yeah... I've already moved on...
She brought the dude, then...
Poor guy. He bounced, didn't he?
He bounced, obviously.
He must've felt real bad again.
I feel like picking up this lamp
and throwing it in your face.
But I was acting unconsciously.
I was drunk, like,
- I can't control my feelings.
- I know we can't control...
Girl, what Tay said was very real.
We have to stop saying...
Don't say what you're doing,
just do it.
Didn't I do it?
Didn't I? I held his hand
and said, "Come to my box."
No, you said,
"I'm going to bring him over.
I'm going to hook up with him.
Fuck Ramon, I want Ramon
to fuck off." You got here,
"Ramon, let's play together!"
I didn't say I was playing with him.
He asked me. I remember.
You should've said,
"No, I don't want it. I want to play
- with Júlio."
- I know, right? Why didn't I say it?
He was going to be embarrassed.
He was going to be pissed off.
He'd say, "No, she didn't."
Can I say this?
He thinks... You do whatever he wants.
It's kind of true.
You have to prove him wrong.
You don't have to say yes.
Yeah, you're learning. Little by little.
Yeah.
- It's bad.
- It is.
Let's get in before the mosquitoes...
- I'm already being attacked.
- Now they're attacking my vag.
Let's go!
Everybody's happy.
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Today I'm going to party with my friends
- Fuck!
- Fuck, man!
Let's drink!
Let's get drunker than a bunch of...
It's ending.
This is a fucking friendship. Thanks for
everything, for your friendship.
You're happy, right?
Of course, bro. That's peace.
To me, this is awesome.
- To me, too.
- And life, bro...
We rule, man! We rule.
Where's your...
Headset? I'm asking, please.
What's your name, boy?
- Pedro, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Look.
Fuck, kiss him.
Take her home, I'll pick her up there.
I'm waiting for you guys.
Guys, I have a message for you.
Ricardo sent a message.
Time's up. We have to return the boat.
- We have to leave now.
- Now?
I'd die if I had to work now.
Look at the sun!
Thanks, guys. Time's up.
Ricardo was real nice to lend us his boat.
Hey, guys, thanks!
You're fucking awesome!
That's it.
Wonderful people.
That's it!
Is this our house, bro?
I'm wasted, bro! Fuck!
I know you lived this intensely.
Enjoy it. This is the party.
It's for you, guys.
Let's go!
Fuck!
You're crazy!
Come on, fuck you!
How are you?
What's up?
You were right.
Relax, relax. Let's enjoy it.
I'm more free.
This is a toast to you guys,
the brothers I made.
I love you guys. I love you, my man.
I love you, stylish man.
I love you, huge heart.
You're all my brothers.
That's it. To us!
Call everybody.
Hey!
Jão!
There's somebody you met on day one.
I want to tell you she's here.
Do you know who she is?
Joyce is over there!
Joyce, João. João, Joyce.
Hey, you became a caricature.
And it's identical.
Wow, what a beautiful girl...
I didn't know...
I can't believe it!
May I have a minute of your attention,
towards the blue curtain, to welcome
tonight's great number...
Hello, everybody!
Throw your hands in the air!
I think you know how to sing
this one, huh?
My friend, Cantini. Go.
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with you by my side
I hope our love never turns into routine
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with you by my side
I hope our love never turns into routine
This is what life is all about...
What's up, Cantini, you go.
She wants to date
And I know where this is going
Maybe it's a good kiss
Maybe get goosebumps
There's nobody home
I'm going to turn the stereo on
For her to dance
She'll look at me
She'll tease me, all horny
Looks like a mirage
But it's a dirty thing
This chick will live in my bedroom
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with you by my side
I hope our love never turns into routine
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with you by my side
I hope our love never turns into routine
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with you by my side
I hope our love never turns into routine
Thanks, guys. Thanks, thanks!
Everybody, may love always prevail.
- This could be better.
- But it's what we've got now...
If you sleep with me tonight,
you're going to get more.
- Now I'm going to enjoy it.
- Oh, yeah?
Hey!
Hey, no jealousy, my baby.
No jealousy, okay?
Tonight I'm going to go wild.
He told me she came over and hit on him.
Fuck it.
I'm beating him up tonight.
I'm going to throw this glass in his face.
While production was cleaning up,
Beatriz caught Luan with two women
on the lawn.
The scenes we're going to exhibit
are part of what happened afterwards.
Excuse me. Man...
Easy, girl.
Easy, easy.
I want to talk to this chick.
- This girl.
- Come with me, young lady.
Wait...
Let's get inside.
If this chick goes inside,
I'll kill her!
Don't go, don't get mad... She's there.
- Can I go in with them?
- No.
No. Luan, it will get ugly.
I'm going to take both of them.
They're with me.
They're laughing,
but they don't know what happened.
No, it's not that...
Fuck you!
Once again, you're a clown! Piece of shit!
Piece of shit!
Bastard.
How could this be?
- You're here to teach a lot of people.
- I can't take it.
You're good.
I can't take it, man. God, help me.
Help me, help me.
We're here by your side.
A lot of people are by your side.
Everybody is learning from you.
Easy, go on. Let it out.
Let her breathe. Relax.
Easy, we're here with you.
You're not alone.
Breathe.
Inhale and exhale.
Easy.
Everybody quiet.
Easy, easy. Breathe.
Inhale and exhale.
Get my pants up.
Let's take her to the Tiger Room.
Because it's warm there.
Let's get in the pool?
- Yes, skinny dipping.
- Okay, let's go.
If they step inside my house,
I'll kick their asses.
Hey, it wasn't Manu...
Fuck it. They won't come in.
No woman will step foot in the house.
If they come in...
- Shut up, Taynara!
- Shut up!
You sexist!
- You sexist!
Damn.
Hey, bro. The two of them
have nothing to do with this.
Nothing to do with it.
If you bring them over, I'll cut them!
If you do it, I'll cut them!
What a crazy woman, bro.
Relax.
Crazy bitch.
Shut up, Nathália. Shut up!
Respect her.
Don't you talk
to my friend this way.
Crazy.
Are you crazy?
- I won't let you!
- Fuck off!
You were the guy I liked the most
in this house.
Learn to fuck.
You're nothing but a puppet.
Manu and her friend
don't have anything...
But they're not supposed to come in.
They won't come in.
- Only Keila.
- Good.
We don't need more problems.
Doesn't he have any common sense?
Bia's passed out...
If you guys don't control
yourselves, I will.
No more sexists, not anymore.
The whole season, I put up with him
insulting women. Not today!
Listen to me.
"It's better you don't bring them over
because things are
getting ugly over there."
- It's his character.
- He doesn't have one!
It's okay.
Warn them, because I'll pull
their hair out if they come in.
- Manu has nothing to do with it.
- Tell them to leave.
She knows the situation.
If she comes to my house...
She's aware of all of this.
If she comes to my house,
I'm going to pull her hair out.
- Keila can come.
- Okay.
I've already asked them to leave.
I was polite.
If she comes in, she'll be beaten.
Her and him.
I'm going to put her on our bed.
You're going to be okay...
Good. Good.
You're okay.
Yes, leave her.
Jeez...
Jeez, I was such a fool.
How can I be that stupid?
Don't say that.
He's two-faced, girl. He's two-faced.
But how could I do that?
You didn't know.
It just took too long to figure out.
Oh, man...
It's normal.
Anybody could've gone through this.
He really is a psycho
who pretends to be another person...
He's insane. That's it, like...
Anybody could've been in your position.
We just found out
who he really is, when he drinks.
We've seen who he really is.
Hey, guys.
I'm going to need help this summer.
Who wants to come back?
- Fuck...
- Did you see João's face?
He didn't know where...
"I need help this summer."
"Who wants to come back?"
There's going to be a recap.
They're going to stay at that house again.
Invite me...
Did you see João's face when he woke up?
I wonder if can handle it.
Another 30 days of booze?
He woke up and said, "Wow!
"Am I at Carol's place?
-"What happened?
- Fuck!
-"Am I going to play video games?"
The dude woke up in...
Would you come back?
- Of course I would.
- What about you...
Seeing that not only is there a house
where eight people
fight all the time, but they get along...
They fight and sort things out.
It's like a family.
Do you know what I think the key is?
It's the fact that there's no prize.
- Nobody is competing.
- Yeah.
Nobody is competing.
That's the catch about this show.
- It's about enjoying. Nobody's competing.
- That's true.
That's another thing, too.
One fucking awesome thing is...
It's much bigger than a show because...
When you watch a series,
you learn a lesson.
They also learned something.
We learned a lesson, but they also did.
They showed all kinds of feeling...
I like this.
Acknowledged their mistakes, gratitude,
love, hate, too, anger...
Everything was all mixed up.
It ended up like this.
Didn't you hear the boss,
"I'll need help this summer.
- Who's coming back?"
- Every good show ends up like this.
They go home,
think about it and come back...
There's going to be a lot of seasons.
- I'm shocked.
- Fix me, Carol, I'm shocked.
- I'm looking forward to the summer.
Beautiful!
I want a cup of chocolate milk, fuck!