- We're here.
- Hello?
I hope we see a lot of hot sex scenes.
Excuse me.
You're totally being Blanca.
Blanca Evangelista.
Guys, we've been invited
by Amazon Prime Video
to watch the first episode
of Wild and Free: Florianópolis.
Basically, eight friends go to Floripa
to spend their vacations in a dream house
and enjoy the best parties.
Who has already been to Floripa?
My gosh, that's everybody.
"Who's been to Floripa?"
is not the right question.
It's "Who got lucky in Floripa?"
I can't think of anybody not getting lucky there.
That's true.
I'll rephrase my question.
Who's had a hot date in Floripa?
No.
Who has hooked up with anyone in Floripa?
Who's been happy in Floripa?
I have to go to Floripa.
Let's go to Floripa?
Amazon will pay for our tickets.
Amazon...
Anyway, I have been to Floripa
in the summer.
And when I went there,
it all felt very...
Everyone's free, you know, no rules...
...everybody is enjoying themselves,
no worries, no stress.
When I went there, I was ugly,
and people there are pretty.
Where do they come from?
Yes, they are. It's true.
Their fathers have paint brushes,
not dicks, honest to God.
Women are like paintings!
Pretend my mouth is a canvas, go ahead.
I'm scared to see...
My mouth is a canvas, do your thing.
Go ahead, Picasso. I'm ready.
Guys, all we know is they're not actors
and there's no script, it's all for real.
We'll have to watch to know more.
- Get it started.
- Let's go ahead.
It's on. Shush.
Get the popcorn, Titto.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
Shit, look at this house, bro!
Awesome, bro!
It's gonna be crazy, brother!
Oh, my God!
Yeah, bro. Welcome! Fuck!
Fuck! Wow!
Man, I knew you were coming too, boy!
Guys, let's get noisy!
Fuck, this is crazy!
I can't believe it, man.
What's up, bro?
Guys, look at the moon.
Tonight's gonna be wild!
Check this out, bro.
Gorgeous!
Hello?
Hey!
Oh, yeah!
Hi! Thank God you came.
We're lucky, man. Amazing, man.
We're freaking lucky.
Everything is great! Hi!
- Of course it is!
- I'm fine, and you?
You're the first ones here?
Check it out. Check out the house.
Is everybody all right?
We're all good, and you guys?
- Great, man.
- Even better now.
Better now, for sure.
Damn, man, so cool, bro! Insane!
It's awesome. Look, many shots.
Is this the crazy place
where we're going to be?
Welcome, my darlings. Long Live Life, see?
We're the best!
Someone's coming!
Hello.
I need a man
to help with the luggage.
Yo! You can leave it there, I'll get it.
- Hi! So, how are you doing?
- Hello!
This is insane, man!
So many beautiful women, look!
Look who's here! Look who's here!
The most beautiful and gorgeous girls.
Everything all right? I can't believe it!
She's hitting me.
Already hitting me, what the fuck?
You good? It's been so long!
- Yeah, this is so cool.
- Say it, girl.
Hi, guys!
For heaven's sake,
I can't take this right now.
What the hell?
You all know the house,
it's my turn now.
So, this is the small area...
Check this out!
The small area, right?
- This is gonna be wild.
- Yes.
Thank God!
Let's go party tonight?
Wow!
I wanna go dance.
Look!
Look at his face!
Are you kidding me, Blondie?
When you come talk to me,
I'll tease you.
Like, "What's up, Blondie?"
We're the best.
Boy, what a gang!
A hell of a gang!
I remember seeing you earlier.
That girl went crazy.
I was worried. Like, already? Jeez!
Guys, I got something to say.
Only the best, huh?
You're such a Don Juan!
We have a couple in the house.
The first couple!
Fuck! Floripa's family!
It's all good, my man.
Hey, brother!
Damn!
Hi! How are you?
That's the last one of the girls.
You're looking good.
Damn, you're looking good!
Guys. Let's sit over there.
Great to see you, kid!
Does this camera work?
Let's take a selfie.
Look at that nose, man,
that's a big nose.
The size of that nose!
It's like a 40-inch TV screen
on my face.
Our first picture, yay!
Put it on the board.
- Where's the board?
- Is it that one?
Boy! Now it's for real. We're all here!
Blondie! Open your mouth.
First, I'll go around kissing everybody.
Little kisses. Okay?
It's one guy, one girl.
Little kisses.
Let's go to a club tonight?
I have good news...
Good?
...and I have excellent news.
Booze is excellent.
I got us a VIP box at the Green Valley.
Let's have a warm-up party?
Here we go!
Somebody's hot, right?
I think you should show us
your body.
I think so too.
Catwalk!
- Can't you see?
- No.
- You should...
- Stand up...
I'd take it all off, but I'm fat.
Stand up!
No, look.
Turn around.
Hold on, let's get a better picture.
- He turned around.
- That's exactly what I want.
Exactly what I want!
I haven't hooked up
with him yet, so...
But you can kiss now.
It's never too late to change that.
Truth or dare?
It's time for the first
little smooch to get it started.
First little kiss in the house.
It's red lipstick!
Shit, man. It shouldn't be
a movie kiss, ok?
We should do the same.
That's crazy.
Stop, we were just kidding.
Murilo!
Crap, little smooch?
That lipstick is not waterproof.
- No, it's not.
- Look at him!
Someone, help me!
I'm going to kiss someone too.
Who wants one?
My God!
Come to the ladies room, girl.
Let's go freshen up.
I'm going to wipe it off.
Yes, exactly. Wipe it off.
Such a nice kiss!
Wait, there'll be more.
It's still early.
- Let's go get dressed up?
- Okay.
We'll be right back.
- Brother...
- No.
There...
Yes, it's on the four lower teeth.
Here, on the tip of your teeth.
Still there.
- Man, I'm so naughty.
- And he's very handsome, too.
I couldn't help it.
Fuck, man.
She's beautiful, right?
Yes. As well as the other ones.
I can't resist red lipstick.
It's too good.
She stands out. Hot brunette.
I couldn't help it.
I was just waiting for that moment.
She threw the ball and you had to score.
Crazy, man. Well done.
You know it's going to be insane.
Yeah, it'll be awesome.
And I don't want a boyfriend, no way.
Me neither.
You know why? I'm not going to lie.
I'm like,
"I don't like to get too attached."
But I'm not like that. I get jealous.
So am I. So, like,
if I hook up with someone in the house,
I'm going to get super jealous
if I hook up.
That's why I think I screwed up.
Hey, Luan. Did you bring this?
- I did.
- And how does it work?
One person pours and the other one...
- Awesome.
- Cool!
Really, just straight vodka?
No, add an energy drink.
Let's do it. Put it in your mouth.
- Let's break it in...
- I can't see what I'm doing.
Go.
That's going to be a big hit,
my beautiful flamingo!
That's exactly what I want!
Don't you know me?
You're so bad, you pervert.
I'm bad?
Holy crap, her jacket!
- Pour it. Put it all in.
- Everything?
I got a surprise for you guys.
Just stay here, real quick.
Give me one sec.
Come on, bus!
NATH AND RAMON
THAIS AND JOAO
- Let's stay here.
- You're single, right?
If you don't want to go over there,
we can have fun right here.
I can't believe this.
This is the gang!
If you wanna leave with me,
that's okay too.
She was pretty.
Write down my name or something.
Can I have your number?
Go hook up with her.
Tell Joyce to go away!
- I already did.
- Blondie is here.
- I want Blondie!
- I don't give a fuck.
Do you think I screwed up?
Because that girl...
She was hot, you know?
Of course she was,
but you should hook up with Thais.
Thais is better.
Then I kissed João.
He then kissed another girl
and then wanted to kiss me again.
I didn't want to kiss him again.
- I don't know why I'm crying,
- Don't cry.
I think it's because I'm drunk.
I'm crying because I'm drunk.
I don't care about him.
Okay, stop crying.
I don't care about him. He's full of crap.
Why did you do that to me?
It took you hours to kiss me!
You are full of crap.
I kissed the girl I took to the VIP box.
And she got pissed at me.
She saw me kissing someone else,
then she came back and kissed me.
I was kissing one after the other.
Daddy is great with the ladies!
He's a jackass.
Afterparty at the house!
That's great!
Gosh, that was a crazy party!
First, the boys are all single.
- Second...
- So are the girls.
They're all wrong,
hooking up right away.
It's the first day!
- They're single!
- It's not wrong!
You just can't get attached. Let it go!
It's not complicated.
If João...
You hook up. Then you say,
"I can't fall in love on the first day."
Can't do that.
The guys should go to that club first,
they all knew they were going to a party,
and then see if they can score there.
- Yes.
- Right. Right.
Score, sure.
Score? That won't work.
They're not all so rational.
People have feelings.
He started kissing immediately.
The guys are rational,
but after a few drinks, they're fucked up.
That's when it gets nasty.
- Better order some food.
- It was like this...
Let me tell you.
I was at home, in the pool,
making out with a friend of mine.
Making out, for you,
could be a type of flirting.
Very cool!
You were humping the guy,
making him hump you.
Yeah, humping him.
Then his cousin came over at night,
and a friend said to me,
"I'll give you 50 bucks
if you hook up with him."
Hook up with the cousin...
I said, "I'll win, man!"
Fifty bucks buys you a good meal.
- So, what I did was...
- Man, 50 bucks.
My friend went to get a glass of water,
and I told the guy,
"Come here,
I wanna show you something."
So I went to my bedroom and said,
"Shit, is he going to follow me?
I wondered..."
So you were already in bed.
"Will he fall for it?"
Then he came in and said,
"What's up, Carol?"
I said, "Come in."
My God!
So we got it going
and I got my 50 bucks.
And what did you do with it?
Buy a sandwich, man.
On the first day,
would I flirt with everyone?
Yes, but I'd rather wait
and check out things.
I think they should make out
with everyone.
But if that happened to me,
I would kick his ass.
What?
I wouldn't make up with him again
until I got over it.
Write some lyrics
spilling out my feelings and all.
Way to go. A sad country song!
I'm a songwriter too.
Get a country duet to play it.
And only after that,
I'd go back to him again.
The problem is that a man can get
50 girls and it's all good.
- No.
- Yes, real nice guy. Super cool.
I mean, for society.
For all that matters, he's the man!
But if we do it people judge us.
Some women can't deal with that.
Guys can get a lot of chicks and...
He's a total jerk,
like those guys over there.
No, just like the boy is saying...
He's the Daddy or something.
Here's what they think.
Some women don't want that.
- They don't want that.
- I understand what you're saying.
She won't hook up with several men
or she'll be judged.
That's how it is.
Patriarchy sucks, guys.
Girls, you can have whoever you want.
Girls, go crazy! You can screw
as many guys as you want.
Who cares what people say?
You have to...
No, get them all if you want.
It's all good!
I want to see
what that horny chick will do!
Hit play.
Let's go.
We're here!
Fuck, man, that was crazy!
- Yeah.
- Nice!
Nobody's sleeping tonight.
Hey, guys,
the party is by the pool, all right?
The outdoor pool is for the ones fighting.
The indoor pool is for those who aren't.
What's that?
Am I seeing that?
You see?
You're wasting time.
She'll start laughing.
She has already raised her head.
You look like a meerkat.
Is that a tennis match?
My God!
He screws all day?
Blondie, come here.
Just the two of you.
Let's talk, seriously.
- Serious talk?
- Yes.
Only if it's serious.
I'm not going to get mad.
Just a normal talk.
Only if it's serious...
- Go talk to her. Go.
- I just want a...
Wasn't I supposed to go over there?
No, I'm just a little shy.
He's a gentleman. Let him come to you.
Go to a private place to talk.
Go where? But they are busy out there.
We're going to bother them.
He's a cockblocker!
Cockblocker, my ass.
There are 200 bedrooms.
Why don't want to pick one?
Never mind. Forget about it.
Do you want to stay here?
- You can go to sleep.
- Fine, I will
No!
Guys...
Come here. Lie down here.
Fuck you all!
Blondie, he's going to
bring someone here tomorrow.
If you cry, I'll kick your ass.
I'm not going to cry, I'm over it.
- Right?
- If you guys start making out...
If you start kissing him,
that's not cool, okay?
Yes.
Will you stop being so loud over there?
Murilo. João is already cockblocking
them upstairs.
Do you think it's easy?
I wanna fuck that ass real bad,
but I can't.
Then you say,
"Look, João cried at the party!"
Fuck you! Son of a bitch.
You think it's easy for me?
Chill, kid.
An eleven-inch cock and I don't...
No, go to hell, Luan.
Cover up that dick, motherfucker.
Girl, I'm pissed off.
I warned him. You know what's worse?
I warned him. I told him
"Go kiss other girls,
but I won't hook up with you."
I warned him and he said "No."
I'm furious.
That party was insane, man.
Let's turn the lights down,
so it gets dark!
Son of a bitch! I told you.
No shit. Really?
Crap, it's really cold, bro.
I'll make some stroganoff.
What time is it?
Let's have coffee.
No way, really?
- 5:00.
- Whatever, bro.
- 5:00pm.
- Maybe the clock is broken.
What's up, brother?
I'm good, all cool.
Shit!
Did you get some rest?
I got some rest.
Have you been awake long?
- I just woke up.
What are you doing?
Get some water.
No.
- You okay?
- Yep.
I feel humiliated.
"The humiliated will be exalted."
I wasn't crying because of him.
I was drunk.
"I didn't know you'd be so sad."
Let me know next time.
That girl got jealous last night?
The one I was kissing was.
Man, that was funny.
Both of them got...
What?
Both of them got jealous.
Both? Man...
You guys kissed at the party
and made her cry on the bus, man.
No, poor thing, man.
Shit, she cried a lot.
Because she got jealous.
But I think it was more like...
I think it was a mix of...
- Of different feelings.
- That's right.
I hope we get this everyday.
You cooked, so you sit
at the head of the table.
- Come over.
- Perfect!
- Is this right?
- Where are the ladles?
Where are you sitting, girl?
Someone sit next to me.
For heaven's sake.
Go, go, Thais.
Aren't you going to
pull out the chair for me?
It starts at "Suck it up!"
Just to warm up!
No reason.
Did you wake up and remember
it's a beautiful day?
Shit. Good morning.
Good morning.
I slept all by myself last night.
Did you sleep well?
They're starting already.
Let's eat, guys. Feeling grateful.
Go ahead.
My gosh!
Help yourself, leave the pan for me.
When I was...
How about we talk
about the party last night?
- That party wore us out.
- Cut it out, I'm tired. Aren't you?
I'm still tired.
I'm in good shape, ready to party again.
- Brother, I'm good to go!
- Me too!
Man, my calves are all achy.
You danced a lot. I danced a lot.
I was totally wasted! Jeez!
Yes! Gosh! You and I...
I danced a lot.
Now, the elephant in the room. Tell us.
You cried, but not because of him.
Explain it to us.
- I was fighting with her.
- Did you cry?
Because I was drunk.
I wasn't crying because of him.
He was like, "I can't believe
you're crying because of me.
"I didn't want to hurt you."
Shit, man, blah, blah, blah...
I don't remember bursting out in tears.
I remember I was hurt.
But not like crying and sobbing.
But Ramon... Now, tell us what happened.
One minute, you're kissing Nath,
and five seconds later
you're kissing this other girl?
- It's my lust for life.
- It's life!
And where did she come from?
I saw that girl.
You did? You did not!
Sometimes Nath,
she has her limits.
I don't go around telling stuff, so...
She flipped out on him,
and he went looking for another girl.
That's not what happened.
What about this other girl,
Joyce or something?
- João.
- Congratulations on that one.
That one was hot.
I have to admit, that girl was pretty.
Very pretty.
It was just a kiss.
At least, he didn't bring her home.
We wouldn't let him, right?
He didn't bring her home.
She wouldn't be allowed in.
Do you need me to buy anything?
I could go out.
Let's decide what we want to cook.
Get stuff for a barbecue.
Cheese, garlic bread...
- Garlic bread!
Let's get some garlic bread.
Can you guys help me?
The girls can help me.
Get chocolate too.
Guys, wine.
Wine is super important, man.
- We're screwed.
- Guys, let's...
Tay, if Tay could come...
You can drive, right?
I'll drive you.
You coming? I'd like to chat.
- Okay?
- Okay.
That's settled, then.
How about pizza?
Let's get some chicken pizza.
Four-cheese pizza.
Portuguese pizza.
- Pepperoni.
- Chicken, creamy cheese and mozzarella.
Get it. No, get more. Like, four.
So we have appetizers for later.
Did you hear Blondie
and João fighting last night?
He was chewing her out non-stop.
Blondie, don't you want...
When we're drunk, we have feelings
we don't know about.
Man, he makes me laugh so hard!
He looks at me, like,
"So, Murilo, look..."
Let's do something.
I'll get a broomstick,
put something on her head...
We'll be creative, Joyce.
Funny, we keep talking about her.
Her ears are ringing.
Every day, we're talking about Joyce.
Write it down, "Joyce."
He'll laugh so hard,
he'll pee his pants.
He'll get attached to this.
- You need to write...
- Joyce Kelly.
- Hold it up like this.
-"Joysse."
Now, "Kelly."
Tonight, he won't kiss Blondie anymore.
Before we get to the house,
just between us...
You won't hook up with Thais anymore?
Not even at the party?
- No, it's...
- It's not going to happen?
- Will you go for it or not?
I'm not going for it. I gave up.
For real.
I don't want the commitment.
I don't want a commitment.
And neither does she.
I told Murilo,
"Wow, a bunch of hot babes."
He said, "Yeah, but they're not my type."
"What is your type?"
And he looked at me.
You!
She's totally in love!
- Girl, you're in love!
- You're totally in love.
I honestly thought that Carioca was
going to hook up with Blondie.
And that I would hook up with you.
Are you serious?
Honest to God, because...
If you cheated on me, I'd get really mad.
I don't know. Maybe.
What if I had hit on you first?
What if João had hit on you first?
Go ahead, be honest.
No need to say a thing.
I got it, João.
You lost your chance, João!
Son of a bitch!
I got to the house and Murilo kissed me
right away, like, "That's it.
"I'm kissing this mouth."
You could have been the one.
But now, you're moving to Rio.
- Not me. I'm single.
- If you want...
I'll save you a place in my bed.
You clown.
I won't do that, Blondie is my friend.
Blondie wouldn't mind.
What if we do just the opposite?
For real, I think that if that happens,
Blondie wouldn't be upset.
The only one who would mind,
that would be Bia and Luan.
If someone hooks up with Luan,
things would get nasty.
- Sure.
- Bia would get mad.
Yes, she would.
I said to Luan,
"Look, I'm not going to hook up
with anyone else."
He said, "If you hook up with anyone
during the whole vacation,
"will you kiss me?"
I said, "Okay."
Last night, before everything, he said,
"You mean it, right?
Because, if you hook up with someone else,
"you'll have to do as you promised."
I said, "No way, I'm not a grass cutter."
If you break the promise...
Did Luan say that to you?
...Bia will pull your hair out.
Who's hungry?
- I am!
You have no idea who came to visit you.
Where?
She's waiting for you upstairs.
- Joyce.
- Can... Let's...
Go, João!
João's best friend.
Is my love here?
She's waiting for you in the bedroom.
She can't leave.
She can't get out.
- Ask if you can come in.
- Excuse me?
- You can't come in.
- So, I can't come in?
Fuck you!
Kiss!
- I'm going to start the barbecue now.
- Go.
This is so neat!
You're not going to starve.
He'll bring you breakfast in bed everyday.
- Just like a princess.
- Like a princess.
Did you see that? Learn how to be
a prince, a gentleman, very polite.
Girlfriend, Ramon is a prince, my friend.
A super prince.
- That was just last night.
- He's not João.
You'll see the prince tonight.
Boy...
Hey, Nath?
- Yes?
- Are you ready, love?
- No.
- I can't believe I'm so hot.
Take this heat out of me!
Before, it was "love," "Nath,"
"Nath," "love."
Now, it's "love," "baby."
- Nathalia! Are you ready?
-"Nathalia."
Thanks. Let's go!
Shit, man.
Check this place out, Murilo.
It has broadened my horizons.
Tonight I'm getting wasted.
You'll have to carry me out.
I'll get so wasted...
Check the girls out. Look!
Girls, I wanted to meet a hot boy,
but it's hard.
Chill, I've got a good feeling about it.
If not tonight, some other time. Relax.
- Where are you from?
- From Rio.
Really? I'm from Rio.
Look me in the eye.
I'm not mature enough.
I'll be mature for us both.
I'm not done talking.
If I steal a kiss, would you get mad?
- No.
- No?
- Not at all.
- Really?
No?
- Can I nibble on your ear?
- No.
No?
My heart is broken. Ridiculous!
You got cheated on.
I got cheated on
In your face!
The guy is such an asshole.
He makes me sick. I'm furious.
Don't feel this way.
This is exactly what we came here for.
No, that's not what I came here for.
It would be the same thing
if I wanted to control Murilo.
How could I control him?
But you don't like it. There's no way...
- You don't like it, obviously.
- Well, yeah, I don't like it.
But karma is a bitch!
You reacted just like I did.
I didn't like that.
- What can you do?.
- And he kissed her.
I'm going to fall over.
- Man, you fucking suck.
- Why?
You got cheated on before,
and now you're cheating on him? Payback?
Girlfriend.
- Girlfriend, don't fall over.
- Sit down.
We'll get you some water.
Wanna use the restroom?
You know I was with him, right?
He told you that.
I got cheated on.
I asked him about that.
So sorry.
No, relax, he's all yours.
Because I don't...
About that...
I don't think that's the point.
You... Fuck you!
- Princess, you...
- Fuck you, Ramon.
What's with you? You're falling down
like crazy.
- Your girlfriend is here.
- Fuck you, Ramon.
Go on, then. I was serious.
Stop falling down.
Shit, what the hell?
For heaven's sake!
No!
No somersaults, Nath! For heaven's sake!
No somersaults, my friend,
for the love of God!
You're such a sweetheart, you know?
Thank you!
Putting up with me is not easy.
And putting up with me and my friends...
Attention, everyone!
Good morning, João!
Whoever wants to go to the afterparty,
stick with Daddy!
It's time!
Follow Daddy.
Feeling bad, is one thing.
Being a loser it's another.
- No.
- But what happened?
Shit, you're my friend, ok?
He is talking and you...
Do you think she'd be happy
if I talked to you like this?
No, look at me.
Would she like it
if I talked to you like this?
- No, she wouldn't.
- So, there.
- Okay, fine. I get it.
- That's all.
Bia, come here.
Look, you're a grown woman.
Don't lose your mind, okay?
That one there is going crazy.
Don't you tell me
not to lose my mind,
we haven't even talked yet.
I'm talking to them, not to you.
No, my hearing is very good.
My hearing is very good.
Then talk to me
before you start talking bullshit.
Talking bullshit?
You're saying
"Stop saying bullshit."
Then you start...
Leave it alone, man.
Leave it alone.
We're home!
Make yourselves at home!
Go!
Make yourselves comfortable!
Girlfriend! Check out this view!
Check out this view!
What do you want? Beer? Vodka with ice?
- Cigarette.
- Where can I sleep? Here's fine.
Put a mattress here.
No, come here.
Here.
No, not here.
Not this bed. Oh, my God!
Jesus!
Well, then sit on this bed here.
Can I have a cigarette?
I should go upstairs, to see if...
You think they're hooking up?
No! They're not.
He's just protecting her.
She's going to hug and cuddle
with anyone who goes up there.
Just like she was with her, with her,
with her and her...
So, yeah. Exactly. That's exactly it.
That's what I'm saying.
It was his fault, not hers.
I think she's naughty.
Here.
Iced tea.
That tastes horrible.
I don't think she's thinking right, now.
She's drunk. She can't tell...
If one comes to me, then the other...
Please! Get don't let me
and drown me in the pool.
But don't let me,
or shit will hit the fan.
I'll smack one or the other.
That's how I am. Fuck it.
Tomorrow, when you're sober,
you go talk to him.
Just don't let it happen, that's all.
I'm serious. We're family.
She wasn't being a friend.
I was acting like a friend.
But she didn't.
We are all family.
Let's all talk when we sober up.
Should hook up with someone else?
You should do whatever you want.
If you feel like it, do it.
- I don't want it anymore.
- Then don't.
If you want to shout, do it.
Fight, if you want to.
You think I'm here with you,
because I want to kiss you?
Because I like you.
I don't want you
to make a fool of yourself.
More?
I didn't let you
make a fool of yourself.
And helped you get on the bus, before.
Let's tease them.
- Are you crazy?
- Let's do it.
I'm going to tie your smart-ass tongue
to that thing there.
I'm not going downstairs.
Let's go downstairs.
Bia is mad. Don't get near her,
or she'll chew you up.
- Talk to her tomorrow.
- But didn't hook up with Luan.
I know you didn't.
She's still getting over it,
don't try to reason with her.
She's mad at this situation.
If you talk to her,
you two will get in a fight.
Hey, pretty thing!
For the record, you're gorgeous!
Crap, I fell down.
Quiet, quiet, quiet!
Let me get that.
- Hello?
- What the heck?
Good evening.
How are you, Ricardo? You good?
What time? Tomorrow?
Okay, I'll let them know.
Guys, come on over.
Come here, please, Ramon.
You want to hear the good news
or the bad news first?
- The good news.
- We have to work tomorrow.
- Cool!
- All right?
So we're all going to work.
I just wanted everyone to know.
I'll let you know the time tomorrow, okay?
You just need to know
that we're working tomorrow, all right?
And the good news?
Is that we're here in this house.
What time?
Is there a time frame, Murilo?
Listen up.
You should go home.
We're going to have to say goodbye.
I knew it.
Because we gotta work tomorrow.
We appreciate you all coming here.
You made our night! It was awesome.
Okay?
Sleep well.
Be true to yourself, always.
I will. Always.
- Always.
Let's be true to ourselves.
- Right.
- Always be true to yourself.
Character is everything.
Take it easy.
I changed my mind.
You should have talked to me
instead of talking behind my back.
Don't talk to me.
Don't talk shit to me.
I'm right here. I'm a man!
And I'm a fucking woman!
- Then say it to my face.
- I think that now,
because I'm a mature person...
- You're drunk, right?
- You, mature?
I'm wasted.
If we talk now, things will get ugly.
- Crystal clear.
- Things will get ugly.
- Really? Why?
- Yes, it will.
- Cause you're selfish.
- I'd rather not talk...
You can't even face your own shit.
I'd rather not talk.
- Then why you slept with me?
- I was just chilling.
So we slept together for no reason?
You're pointing a finger at me.
Because I don't want to talk today?
Be yourself. You are being fake.
I am being myself!
That's great, so be yourself.
That's it! I don't want to talk to you
or to her because I am drunk and I...
So go upstairs, it's our house.
So, it's our house?
That's right,
and I can sit here if I want.
He's the one in a relationship with you,
not me, darling.
Okay. But then...
- I'm cool.
- I didn't hook up
with him because I didn't want to...
I don't want to know!
- ...because of you!
- I didn't ask.
I didn't ask him anything.
We're done talking.
You can't even have a conversation.
- Go to bed!
- Enough.
We're done talking.
This conversation is fucking over!
Shit!
He and I are on edge, me and Luan.
I can see that, so awkward.
For two reasons, right?
You know what sucks?
It's all for no reason.
It pisses me off, you know?
But in the end,
we all have our own feelings.
it sucks.
Come talk to me outside.
Come on.
Nath must be...
Things are going to get nasty.
- Right?
- No, for heaven's sake.
Let me hear your version now.
I was with everybody, just like you,
and we were all...
And Nath's guy hooked up
with someone else.
Do you think
I was going to leave her alone?
If I were you, I would have never done
what you did!
Really? You'd leave her on the floor.
No, I wouldn't.
- So typical of you.
- But I would talk respectfully.
In my opinion, you didn't.
If you're fucking me,
you're not going to talk like this
to a friend of mine. Do you understand?
If you think this is respectful, fine.
For me, it's not.
- For me, it's not.
- You have a loose screw.
- No, no, no.
- Loose screw.
If I wanted to screw her,
- I would have.
- Wrong. Watch how to talk to me.
You're saying I have a loose screw.
- You do.
- Have I offended you?
Have I, by any chance,
said that you're weak?
That, for me, is disrespect.
Learn how to talk to me.
You asked me to come talk to you.
- Learn how to talk to me properly.
- I am.
- Got it?
- Stop being a bitch.
Shove that loose screw up your ass.
I guess we're done talking.
Because, if that's how you feel about me,
we're not on the same vibe anymore.
We haven't been on the same vibe
for a while.
Your head is full of shit.
They're not even married
and he's sleeping on the couch.
See that?
What I think is,
if the shoe fits, wear it.
If you're sleeping on the couch,
in your head, you're in trouble,
"Man, that was wrong."
No. If you're upset,
go somewhere else.
He's upset. He stayed away.
I bet she's going to go
talk to him on the couch.
No. She's going to wake up
the next morning, all pretty,
they're going to have a chat
and kiss again,
because nobody has a partner.
I believe it'll all happen
in the same episode.
You can't win
an argument with a woman.
I like that. She is Bianca.
I'll say! He better behave.
You know what I'd do?
But this is all for fun.
Those guys are there just to...
- You know what I would do?
- What?
I'd do just like I did once...
Another one of her stories.
Just like us, right?
I'd do just like I did once...
I'd leave the bedroom door open.
- I would...
- And I'd sleep with the door open.
I'd do just like I did once,
when I was singing at a party.
I saw something I didn't like
and said, "Give me a hug."
- During the show?
- No.
No, the show was over by then.
It was dark.
- Was that your steady boy?
- Yes, he was.
I said, "Give me a hug."
And he goes, "What happened?"
"Give me a hug."
When he hugged me,
I reached for his rib and pow!
A punch?
Did he smack your face
with his elbow?
If someone punches me like that,
that's what I'd do.
You're fast. Carol, girl!
A punch on my rib?
But girlfriend, she's super emotional,
he's super emotional,
they are both drunk...
It's a recipe for disaster.
Man, I love her.
But if I'm with a boy
and he talks to my friend like that,
come on!
What would you do?
I'd say, "Look, honey, it's over."
Girlfriend, it's the same old story again.
- They're all single.
- Right.
I would tell my friend,
"Go get him, knock yourself out.
"But be ready, he'll do the same
with another girl."
If you're at a party,
everybody is on their own.
But it's different
if I'm friends with Titto,
I am with you,
you go and...
We're not stupid. He didn't go take care
of the drunk girl
and fight with the other for no reason.
He said that to her, right?
He did. No, he said,
"Why am I looking after you?
'Cause I want to kiss you?
-"I'm doing this because I like you."
- Of course not.
- No, no, no.
- But he said it.
- No.
It's one thing saying it...
- But he said it.
- When the guy...
I can't judge a guy I've known
for 12 hours.
- Let me say something.
- He said it.
"I like you and I don't want you
to make a fool of yourself."
- Do you think if...
- Okay.
...she encourages him,
he won't go for it?
Drunk? I think...
Let's go back to the metaphor.
I don't think so.
I think he meant well.
I think he meant well. Seriously.
I really do.
He meant well.
You've never looked after woman
you didn't want to fuck?
Wait, wait, wait...
No. You've never looked after a woman
you didn't want to fuck?
You've never looked after a woman
In those conditions?
Both wasted? No, I don't think so.
He was less drunk.
Less drunk, my ass!
He was talking like a drunk.
It's just that guys
can hold their liquor better.
You can't be more drunk or less drunk.
- Imagine you're in Luan's shoes.
- Okay.
"Luan is not here, it's Titto, super-hot,
tattoos and all."
Would you go for it or not?
- Not at all.
- You're lying.
He was not wrong for taking her upstairs,
that was cute.
And then he made a scene
in the middle of the party.
Not cool, love.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
João?
Don't talk about
what you don't know. No, just shut up.
I'm your brother, man, I'm your brother.
She's a total sucker.
Listen. We're not living a simple life,
we're living big!
Things will get nasty!
What's the next episode going to be like?
There will be blood!
What's the name of the girl who
was crying? I felt bad for her...
- It's Taynara.
Jeez, João is pissed off!
I wonder what happened.
João is pissed off.
Taynara was making a scene...
- Things are going to get real now.
- A guy came in a motorboat.
I want to see how this escalates.
We'll have to wait till next week.
Oh, my God!