We're here!
Wow, here comes Pabllo,
look how she comes.
This is a Victoria's Secret
fucking mother fucker!
- This is an angel.
- What's up?
She's a Hell angel.
Where is John?
We can't pretend he's not here.
- Yeah.
- Look at this.
- My God!
You say that you love me when you drink
But your mouth prefers me
Dear Lord, bro!
And what
What is it, man?
- Get up, girl.
- Oh, my gosh.
That's great, man.
Imagine what he would do at school...
Look at the heels!
With high heels?
I thought there was...
These are phantom heels, girl!
- And he tiptoes!
- What the fuck?
Fuck, I thought there were heels.
Me too.
We're here together
to watch Episode 3 of Floripa Beach House.
Tay and João had an argument,
she was dumped by Murilo,
bad vibe in the house.
And I don't know
what is going to happen.
What do you think, MC Carol from Niterói?
- It's real.
- It's real!
Man, I think...
I feel bad for João, you know?
Because João...
He doesn't even know what's happening.
Anything could happen.
When I think one thing will happen...
There was a bet...
João, I started falling in love,
then I was disgusted,
now I feel I'm in love with him
because he's... the fun one.
Tonight he's gonna get laid. He is!
I used to love Tay,
now I think she's too attached.
I thought Tay wasn't like that,
but now she's crying.
João ate the egg...
I only remember that.
Tonight João is gonna get laid.
He ate an egg...
To fuck someone, but he didn't...
Let's pray for him tonight...
João cried in order to fuck somebody,
but he didn't fuck anybody until now.
Let's press play real good?
- Let's go! I'm very anxious.
- Go, Titto. Kill it.
- What's up?
- What's up, ma?
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
Every day, something happens...
Are you seeing this?
Yeah... I've had my share.
Enough.
One day, something happens,
next day, nothing.
- Thank God.
- It's the dynamite couple.
Look, girl.
It's better than crying in front
of the cameras saying you're heartbroken.
Look into my eyes
and say you feel nothing.
Come on, that hurts.
At least, it's an eye for an eye.
Crying over a broken heart,
that's a shame. Shame!
- This ruined my life.
- Yeah.
Your fault, Blondie.
The fight is on you.
You don't know what it's like...
Being sober. It looked like a zoo.
I didn't know what was going on.
I didn't even know who was involved.
I knew nothing until I got home.
But we didn't fight there.
Not even on the bus.
- Just in the bathroom.
- You got mad at João at the bar.
You talked a lot with Bia.
At the bar...
I don't remember what you said...
That's because João came to tell...
João was full of shit...
Then I said,
"I can't believe he did that..."
He told me a lot of bullshit.
I asked Bia,
"So, why didn't you tell me?"
I really don't know.
You said I wasn't being judged.
That pissed me off.
Why did you tell me that
if it was supposed to come from Murilo?
- You didn't let me talk.
- That's it...
You didn't have to mention it there.
You got drunk, wasted,
you were drinking, ready to...
What am I gonna do?
You didn't have to mention it there.
...talk about something
that would make things worse?
We definitely would've had
a serious fight.
- Yeah... Sure.
- A very serious fight.
It was a misunderstanding, okay?
Yes. A misunderstanding.
- People are thinking...
- You got it all wrong.
That's why I asked you!
You got mad 'cause I asked you a question.
- It was an affirmation.
- It was just a question.
That's okay. I told you
what had to be said. It's over.
But you told me a lot of things...
Then you said to me...
We didn't achieve anything.
Anything out of love.
Not even out of friendship?
- Was everything in vain?
- No, that's right.
- Not everything was in vain.
- It was your question.
- The problem was the tone.
I answered what I understood, you know?
It looked like everything was in vain.
And that hurt. I said,
"Wow, am I being played?"
- I don't judge what you did.
- Me neither.
- Work cell phone.
- Cell phone.
Where's the phone?
How do I answer it?
- Hello?
- Who is this?
Hold on. That's hard.
It's Amanda!
Is it for you?
It's for me!
- Hi, girl!
- Are you all right?
- I am, what about you?
- I'm fine.
I bought a ticket to Floripa.
I don't...
I got invitations for a nightclub party.
It's called Art's...
We're gonna go to this party.
I have nowhere to stay.
Stay here.
It's crazy, girl...
When do you get here? Already?
I'm boarding, yes. I'm boarding...
- Okay.
- I'm gonna get there real soon.
Okay.
I'm gonna stay there.
- Can I stay there?
- Of course.
Tell the guys I'm arriving.
But I gotta rush, I gotta catch a flight.
- Okay.
- All right?
I love you so much!
- I love you. Bye.
- Bye.
Bye.
Guys, she's coming.
What did she say?
That she's catching a flight...
She's catching a flight?
She has nowhere to go...
- Did you offer her to stay here?
- She's staying here.
- Man!
- Fuck! She's staying here?
She said there's a top party
for us to go dancing.
May the night be unforgettable!
It's gonna be!
May it be better than yesterday
and worse than tomorrow!
May theirs be ours, may ours be ours...
We own it!
Just in time, man!
A toast for Amanda, guys!
This is yours.
Cheers! Go!
We own it!
Tonight special guest!
God, that's crazy!
Do you like the same things Tay does?
Dancing on the table?
Falling off all the time?
I love a stage...
I love being the star... Please?
Take me as I am.
Do you fall to the ground?
Girl!
We are going by bus.
It's a party bus, got it?
I wanna know everything!
...sure I was gonna cry?
I did because the boy doesn't like me.
- I cried because I was in love.
- What boy?
- He went to have a smoke.
Remember I said
I kissed a boy in São Paulo?
At São Paulo's party?
- What?
- It's him. He's here.
It's the cute one with... Yeah...
I get it.
Who do you think I hook up with
in this house?
Now I get it.
Used to hook up or still do?
- Everything makes sense.
- You used to.
It's in the past.
You know, guys are like that.
First, he won't want it,
then he'll fall at your feet.
You'll see. It's always like that.
It's not that he doesn't want it.
We're hooking up since day one.
I think you've got to set yourself free.
I'm not in the mood.
Our relationship is going great.
It's like...
There has been no boy like this...
So you're the house couple...
No, everybody has someone.
João is the only one...
Everybody has someone?
I'm going to hook up with the boys.
From this house?
You're gonna get in trouble.
- What?
- Not from this house, right?
- What do you mean?
- Everybody is committed.
You want to hook up
with all the boys here?
Aren't you my friend?
Girl, don't start!
Don't start what, Taynara?
I'll be here for two days.
Do you think I care about those girls?
Girl!
Hey! Go downstairs, fuck?
- Who are you?
- She's getting ready.
- This is Ramon.
- Ramon.
- Nice to meet you. Welcome.
- Thank you.
Let's go downstairs?
- This is pinkish...
- Are you doing the makeup?
No, I'm going to...
I'm trying to find a lipstick...
I'm going downstairs...
Do you wanna use lipstick too?
Do you wanna...
take my lipstick off?
Stop it.
And don't get close to Murilo,
or I'm gonna beat you.
Let's go, Blondie. Let's go, Bia.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Let's go.
You smell nice.
Fuck! Each one... Let's thank...
You got to enjoy it!
Fuck, you got to enjoy it!
That's it! Let's enjoy it, come!
What's wrong?
- Nothing. I'm fucked here.
- Speak, now!
She wanted to fuck.
That girl?
Go fuck yourself, okay?
I was just being nice.
I was dancing.
Don't start with this. For Christ's sake.
I'm gonna kiss you.
Girl, how do I enjoy it?
Don't hook up with my boy.
Right? You won't hook up with...
If you do it with my boy...
Are you hooking up with my boy?
Easy, girl. It's not like that.
We're best friends forever.
This boy is yours.
But, man, think about it...
I'm a little interested
in hooking up with your boy.
But nevermind, this boy is not yours.
This boy is... He gets to...
I said, "It's great being here.
"Man, just enjoy it.
"Just don't hook up with my boy."
Then she said, "No, but..."
I said, "If you do it..."
Girl, I'm sorry, but she's clueless.
I said this to her.
What?
What were you talking about?
We were getting along.
Good, because you've made a little mess.
- What did I come here for?
- Not this way.
Girl, you know me, right? I'm a Leo, baby.
But you're not respecting
the couples, girl.
That's it, girl.
We've just gotten along.
Good, but it was close.
- It wasn't. Girl...
- It was. She told me.
If it were you, being jealous
like you are of a boy and a chick...
I'm not jealous, man.
If a pretty chick said,
"I wanna kiss your boy,"
you'd say,
"Feel free to kiss him"?
You are all too committed.
You can't judge others, girl.
This has got to stop, just a little.
You don't know what they're going through.
Now I'm enjoying it. We'll talk later.
Let me see you standing.
Awesome.
Give me this.
She's going to the after party.
You must be five foot eight-point-five.
I'm wearing heels.
Five feet three inches.
Five feet six.
I can't get it right tonight.
You got it wrong.
She's very hot. Didn't I tell you, bro?
Kiss her.
I kissed her.
- Can you get me a cigarette?
- Yes.
And a kiss?
I can, too.
Are we allowed to kiss?
I'm wearing red lipstick,
it's gonna get all smudged.
Your red lipstick stained me...
Did you get me smudged?
I did.
Is it too bad? I already kissed.
- Serious?
- Jesus.
God is good.
Let's bounce.
Do we have a deal?
Rad!
This was the real deal.
I wanna know when I am having a good day.
I don't want anything to do with Nath.
You didn't do anything tonight, right?
Exactly.
I told her. She's imagining stuff.
I didn't do anything to...
You didn't. I saw you were very quiet.
You just danced with me.
I danced with...
With my friends. Just friendship.
No bad intentions.
I just danced.
If she took it badly, she's got to know
we're all free, you know?
The thing is... Exactly, you can't stop
dancing with people because she's jealous.
She's got to control it.
I'm all right,
but she ruined the fucking party.
I went there to have a good time,
then she just sits,
- cries, then...
- Hey, mister.
Girl, come here.
I don't wanna talk, Nathalia.
- You have to apologize to him.
- Why?
You were wrong.
You are judging him, he did nothing.
I'm not judging anybody, bro.
I don't believe you.
Why were you crying?
- Why did you cry?
- You said the woman was a whore.
Didn't you say it?
You said it, I heard you.
You said her friend wanted
to hook up with me.
Girl, he just danced with friends.
Stop acting crazy.
He respected you all the time.
As long as he just kisses you, it's okay.
Go away, Nathalia.
I'm serious. We'll talk later.
- But I wanna talk.
- Go away.
I don't wanna talk now.
I'm mad, I don't wanna talk right now.
- Mad at what?
- Will you leave me alone?
Will you leave me alone?
So, go, we'll talk later.
I'm asking you, get up.
You kissed a lot of people, didn't you?
- You kissed seven people.
- Seven?
- I counted. It was seven.
I said I'm a kisser.
Not a fucker, a kisser.
...I think it was too much.
- You kissed seven people.
- I bang a few, but I do it real good.
- They were all together, right?
- Right.
- One at a time, right?
- How many people did you kiss?
That's none of your business.
So many...
You're being rude to me?
I don't even wanna talk to you.
Respect my brother here.
But the chicks that were here left?
Did you kiss one of them?
I just kissed one person.
- No, you kissed the ginger.
- Just a peck.
- No real kissing.
- It was a French kiss.
It was a peck.
In front of me.
She bit my lip and I left. I said, "No."
No, you used your tongue.
No, I just kissed one person.
One mouth.
Come on, bro. I saw it.
- Liar. Such a fucking liar.
- You're mistaken.
You kissed in front of me.
Who is a liar? Me?
No, she's... No, girl... No...
People... It wasn't like that.
That was it, you know?
He just said I'm a liar.
Let me have a smoke.
You know what's worse?
I kissed one person,
I'm not gonna expose the chick.
I told you. I told you he kissed.
Fuck off. I respected you.
- And I didn't respect you?
- You know shit.
- Didn't I?
- You don't know the half of it.
- Didn't I respect you?
You're a fake. I'm disgusted.
Please. I'm gonna go...
...you got to impose respect.
Want to be respected?
If you can't handle it,
don't get involved. Don't bother me.
Don't bother me.
Hey, people, for Christ's sake.
I think both of them are right, guys.
When you wanna affect someone,
you can't do it to the person.
You got to do it with their best friend.
Hook up with someone
in front of their friend.
They will think you don't give a shit.
Carol, you got it right, you know?
- I'm in shock...
- I'm a strategist.
Her only mistake was crying.
I think she should have done this,
"You don't want me anymore?
Cool, let's be friends."
- Tay, right?
-"I'm cool."
Then she would hook up with some guy
in front of João... She's damn right.
- Make him mad.
- He's... Yeah.
Way to go.
Let me tell you...
- Now, he's gonna want her more.
- I don't know.
He is.
Not now, in a while.
This anger is out of desire, honey.
He wants to fuck her again.
This is João, who cries.
It's a risky game
because it's gonna get bad...
She won't take it.
We'll see if she's gonna take it or not.
Maybe she just wants to...
She wants him.
Because she meant to hook up
in front of João, she meant to show off.
...in front of her?
No. Let's see if he's gonna do the same.
If he does,
it's because he's pissed,
he also has feelings.
But we got to see
if she can take it, right?
An expert, Carol is an expert.
- That's because he can do it.
- She's a bitch!
He could have used a strategy, too,
because he likes her.
He pretended not to like her anymore
to see what she was gonna do about it,
to make her like him even more, you know?
Where was this monster hidden?
Where? It was asleep,
the giant has woken up!
This is too complicated, guys.
Nobody is really committed,
there are no deals.
He said he didn't like her that much.
He told her he doesn't want her...
He doesn't want her anymore,
he has no feelings...
I wonder if this is about ego, too.
Only if he's playing like Carol said...
But it's about ego, too.
Nobody likes to be switched, right?
It's not even about love...
- Ego, yeah.
- I'd rather switch than being switched.
Do you know what I think?
The show is gonna end and they're
gonna be together forever.
I think the same way.
I think they're not.
They're gonna fight again,
because... Holy shit, right?
One of them kissed
in front of the other...
I hope they sleep together.
I, Kimberly, think they're gonna...
- Who are you?
- Kimberly.
I think they're not gonna have sex...
But it's not gonna be a good relationship.
Do you think they're gonna do it tonight?
I think they're still mad at each other.
- But, clearly, they like each other.
- They like each other.
Both of them are in a bad situation.
- I love his opinions.
- Man, it's ugly.
It gets bad, but they get hornier.
What do you say we go for a ride?
Drive Amanda to the airport?
I'm gonna have to do this.
- Come with me?
- Yes.
Do you? Just the girls today.
We need this.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Let's go for a ride, just the guys.
Let's go to the beach.
No, just stay here... In peace, bro.
In peace.
- You can relax.
- Don't take too long.
If you take too long, we'll be late.
Welcome to my spaceship.
Where everything happens.
I used to say men are fragile.
But I didn't know it was like that.
- No, guys...
- Fucking sensitive.
No... It's all wrong.
- I swear.
- It's all wrong.
It's all wrong.
Again, girls proved they're badasses.
And men are useless.
Yesterday, what happened to Murilo
was beautiful.
One day I cried,
the other day he was pissed.
Everything that goes around
comes around, honey.
Grandma used to say,
"Men are only good for sex,
then you walk away."
I already said, "Use their body
and toss them away."
It's time.
It's time, girl.
Time to say goodbye.
That's it.
Thanks for having me.
Thanks for us. That's so us.
- Good luck to you, guys.
- Thank you.
- Be yourselves... It was good to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Take care, girl, right?
Don't let that boy fuck with you.
Be yourself and put him in his place.
- All right?
- I already did.
- Love you, girl. Bye!
- Bye!
- Bye.
Come on...
I don't wanna tease you,
but where are my brothers?
What's the deal with you?
- I'm around...
- You saw yesterday...
I'm coming back.
It's over. You could be like him, right?
Not fucking... You had to be
like this, too, right?
- I was alone there.
- Yeah.
I'm not in the mood to talk to Ramon.
It should stay the way it is.
Nothing's gonna change anyway.
I think you should talk, girl.
How do I talk to Murilo?
I think... You should make this clear,
you know?
It's impossible
to understand you and Murilo.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Murilo is impossible to understand.
No way we can talk.
Yeah... But if he keeps...
Treating me badly...
Then you... If this is bothering you,
you go and, I don't know.
Until now, it's not.
I'd rather he doesn't look me in the face.
What do you wanna do today?
Bro... It's a fucking beautiful day...
Beach, please, let's go to Praia do Rosa.
Do you remember the place we saw?
There are dunes nearby, bro.
There are... Jesus...
There are some wild dunes,
we can go sandboarding there.
We can go for a ride, you know?
Jesus, that's my dream, bro!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Let's go.
Do you wanna talk?
We talk at the dunes, kiddo!
- Let's go!
- Damn!
Look at those flip-flops!
Wonderful!
Who's gonna fall on the sand today?
Me!
Let's give it up for this TV show!
Fuck, Universe! Thanks!
Where's my hug, family?
It's the beginning...
Thanks!
Tonight, the party is gonna be huge.
300 is one of the best parties in Floripa.
You're gonna get wasted.
Get ready, bro, this party is crazy.
It's crazy.
- Are you going in the kitchen?
- What do you want?
I wanted you to warm up
the food in the microwave.
- And take it out.
- I'll do it. Sure.
Thanks.
She hasn't eaten yet?
She hasn't, bro.
I love your dress, Blondie.
- Do you?
- It fits you perfectly.
- Like a whore.
- Color of skin.
No.
Get the tableware.
My coccyx hurts a lot
because of that dune.
What is it, Blondie?
You're eating because tonight
you're gonna get it.
Tonight I'm gonna get it, João.
Now we're talking.
I like the mess.
Tonight you're playing at home.
What?
Tonight you're playing in your habitat.
Big party?
Big party.
- Cheers, Blondie.
- Cheers.
You're looking good.
Say it to me, Blondie.
- I can't take it this way.
- You're looking good, João!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Hello, kid!
I'm coming!
Hold our baby here, baby.
A toast!
To this night.
Wonderful!
Let's go fucking crazy!
You're very beautiful.
Really... You're a wonderful woman.
- Do you think?
- No, I'm sure, bro.
You gotta think you're the best woman
in the universe.
Don't exaggerate...
I swear to you...
If you don't think you're hot,
who's gonna think so?
- That's true.
- Nobody, you know?
You're here. That's it.
Fuck the rest.
Excuse me...
Now it's our moment.
We're walking.
We're gonna go out for a ride.
Let me ask you something...
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
Where do you live in Sampa?
Vila Ipiranga, what about you?
I'm from Porto Alegre,
but I've been to Sampa a lot...
I spent a lot of time
at Chácara Santo Antônio... A lot.
Do you want him, girl?
Do you wanna come to the box
where we're staying?
I wanna go with you!
- Let's go?
- Let's go.
I wanna go with you.
- Follow me, then.
- I am.
Look at Blondie.
Hey, mister...
Why do you have a girlfriend?
I'm dying to kiss you.
- Really?
- I swear.
I have a girlfriend...
I respect that.
Not even a little kiss?
I wanna kiss you pretty bad.
I can't believe it.
That is brutal.
They hired one for her...
They hired him.
They hired someone
to the one wearing lurex.
The good thing is that
they wear the same size.
Let me take off my earrings for you.
No... What the...
Finish your meal, I'll pass.
Okay.
Now I need to clean up.
For Christ's sake!
- What is your name?
- Keila, and yours?
- João, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet...
- Are you from here?
- Porto Alegre.
- Here.
- A fellow citizen.
Everybody is going crazy.
Kiss him, kiss him, kiss him.
He's wonderful.
You're allowed to kiss him.
Wow!
- You're very hot, bro.
- Thank you.
Let's go to the after party, then?
Is it gonna be nice?
That's on us.
Because we are starving...
Let me tell you...
Is there a private room
for me and her to get some sleep?
You can sleep there...
It's okay.
Let's go. Write down his number.
Make yourselves at home.
Let's go.
Bia?
Show her my closet.
She wants some shorts, man.
Please.
- What is your name?
- Evelin.
- Right. I remember.
- What about yours?
- Beatriz.
- Right.
We'll come to this room later...
It's the makeup room.
Make-up room?
Wow.
- What is this room?
- The Tiger Room.
This one is the Tiger Room...
I find it very ugly...
Jeez, man...
- Did you get it?
- It looks like...
Oh, my God, it looks like...
Somebody who's never seen clothes...
Somebody tell them
they're not gonna spend the night?
Go to bed, girl... Leave them...
Jesus, guys, cut it out.
I wanna sleep here forever.
If you stay here with me,
you'd bring the whole house,
and we're sleeping here every day.
Every day.
I don't know...
It has begun.
Is it cold?
I found my flip-flops.
No kidding.
Will you do me a favor?
Can you take those flipflops off?
Sure, honey!
- Sure!
- You are wearing socks.
Sure, honey.
Sure, baby.
No. Will you eat this much, little one?
It looks like...
If she was phonier,
she'd be awarded a prize.
- What?
- You said that.
- It was Maria.
- Phony what? I didn't get it.
I didn't say... I said...
No, she was the one who said,
"If she was phonier,
she'd be awarded a prize."
- Why did you say that?
- Because she said, "Bye..."
What did you say?
It sounds phony when I'm called "honey".
I think it sounds phony
when I'm called "honey."
It was a... A joke, got it?
It's better this way.
Easy, girls. Easy.
This house is ours.
You're guests, okay?
First of all, be polite.
Guys, relax.
Man, we're at the table, please.
That's why I was joking, got it?
Peacefully.
She's mine, too.
So, a little more respect, please.
Easy, easy, easy...
Let's eat, okay. The food is delicious!
I don't think she meant to call you...
Got it?
No, I was saying to Maria that...
I think it's phony
when somebody calls me "honey."
No, it's over.
I said specifically to her.
There is a lot of screaming upstairs.
It's hard, thank God, Lord.
He is relieved.
It's been a week, he was in need.
The boy earned it.
He came back
from Amazonas and came straight here.
And back in Amazonas, he did nothing.
He was there for a month.
Shit, there are wild women in Amazonas.
Put some clothes on.
You were the one who took them off.
Roll up.
Will you do me a favor? Here, this way?
Stop it, let me see if it worked.
Let me see.
Yes!
Hey, Ramon, come here.
Come here.
Let's talk, now.
Girls are teasing your girls...
I'm gonna send the girls away, man.
I'm gonna send them away.
I'm gonna do it, do you know why?
I don't want trouble, you know?
Girls from here
are talking shit about them.
What did you tell them?
- Go fuck yourself. That's it.
- What?
- Bro, way too lame.
- Look...
Here's what I think...
If we hook up with someone...
Your girl is gonna stay,
but the other two are leaving.
I made a mistake...
I wouldn't do it if I were you.
I'm gonna do it. Do you know why?
I can't take it. Or I'm gonna say
"fuck you" to somebody.
I almost said it to Nath.
I don't wanna stop being friends
with anyone.
Let me talk to you, guys.
Where's the milk, honey?
Bro, here's the thing.
You know the girls are not agreeing...
Really?
We're gonna call a cab for you guys
because we...
I don't want trouble, I don't wanna tell
the girls to fuck off, you know?
I'm really leaving,
or else I'm gonna kick somebody's ass.
Did you have enough?
Fucking slut, I'm pissed.
Ramon?
- He's naked.
- You're a sensible person...
He didn't see this demon.
Don't come in here.
I'm not going there,
I'm gonna stay here.
You're a sensible person...
- Talk to me.
- She's cheeky?
Not Murilo's girl, the other one.
The other one is quiet.
Murilo's girl is quiet.
Now, the other one...
Too cheeky, that Shakira girl.
I swear to God, she threw them and said,
"Take it, honey."
Those flip-flops are mine.
- It's complicated.
- Jeez...
"'Honey' sounds phony to me."
She said that out of the blue!
Bye. Good night. God bless you.
Sorry about everything.
No problem.
- See you tomorrow, right?
- See you.
Let's stay in touch.
Bro, that's something. Here's the thing.
The chick made a joke with her friend...
Why? Because she wanted to tease her, bro.
Or else,
she wouldn't have said anything.
If that happened to anyone else...
- You're losers.
- No, I'm not.
No, I didn't talk about you. Not you.
Are you talking about me?
This is not about you.
Nevertheless, I didn't like it.
You gotta respect above all.
Do you think they respected us?
What did they do? Tell me.
They're our guests.
The house is ours, not theirs.
Tell me. What did they do?
What did they do?
Called us losers.
Said, "That's disgusting."
She was talking to her friend.
End of discussion.
There's nobody here anymore.
I don't even know their names,
because nobody said, "Hi, I am..."
End of discussion. It's cool.
Man, now that they bounced,
let's talk about...
I don't wanna talk...
What am I gonna say?
Wait, guys, let's give it up for João,
come on.
I'd only believe it
if the comforter was removed.
- My God!
- João had sex.
I wanted to be that girl!
He left the room celebrating
in front of her, man.
That's fucked up!
Guys, I had sex, look!
Yeah! That's a dickhead, bro, really.
Would you ask for the flip-flops back?
- I wouldn't!
- I'd say, "Bitch, come here."
I'd tell her,
"He's just hooking up with you,
"because he loves me."
Would you tell her that?
...that would be
lowering myself to their level.
That would mean I care about him.
Mariano, what would you do?
Man, I would bounce.
Would you give her your flip-flops?
If you were Taynara, you'd say,
"Keep my flip-flops?"
But I'd say to her, "Look, sis,
let's stay together
"because he's messing you guys..."
"He's bringing you down here,
because we had a fight.
"What do we do now? Let's be a team
and leave him jerking off."
Leave him alone.
This should happen.
If men did something like that,
it'd be a mess.
Those chicks faced the other ones
because they worked as a team.
They made him jealous.
Usually women are like... "Fuck it."
I love it. Women are like that.
"Yo, are you hooking up
with my friend's boy?
"She's hurt because of that..."
This situation was too awkward.
This is friendship.
I can talk shit about my friend,
but nobody else can.
When you get emotional, you get stupid
and you don't rationalize
like we're doing here.
When you're angry, you don't behave
like when you are here watching the TV.
But, at least, I won the bet,
because João had sex.
João had sex!
Way to go, João!
Do you remember who bet...
I don't. I bet he wouldn't,
I lost the bet.
I know, you have to
pay me forfeit, Pabllo.
- What forfeit?
- Come here.
What?
She said, "What?"
Because I was here, look!
- Forget it...
- What?
Let me say it,
I think João is gonna date that girl.
- No way, girl.
- He is.
She already noticed she was his first...
She was the first girl he hooked up with.
And she's gonna take off.
I think João is gonna show
who he really is from now on.
Now that he's made a start,
he's gonna begin, I think...
No way. I know his type.
Okay, then. You'll see.
I'm going by what he said. He said,
-"I'm not a fucker, I'm a kisser." So...
- I'm a kisser.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Look at this beautiful place.
- Why are you looking at her like this?
- Come on...
Ramon and Luan are not getting along, boy.
That sign in the background is the best:
"Keep going."
- João is in the middle of it.
- Keep going.
What do you think
they're fighting about?
Because of those women there,
or is it a problem they have?
I think... Luan is very close to Tay,
he wants to protect her.
Murilo is mad at this and...
No, I think Murilo messed up,
and he's protecting a friend.
But Murilo is not arguing,
it's Ramon.
- Ramon and...
- And Luan. I didn't get it.
Is it because of women?
It's the liquor talking.
...with the other's girl?
It's because of booze.
Booze. There's no girl...
- I think it's because of food.
- Food?
I don't know, I'm hungry.
It's already noon. Titto...
Booze
That's gotta be booze...
And women, bro.
Men only fight because of those things.
Booze
Men also fight over cars...
You hit my car, yo.
...spent more money at some party.
I don't know.
There could be several reasons.
I know I'm not gonna be able to sleep
till next week, I wanna watch this now.
I'm anxious.
I'm very anxious about
the next episode. Bia, are you anxious?
I think they're gonna get married.
I think Tay is gonna marry Murilo.
Whose house is gonna be the next episode?
We're interested in trouble.
It's gonna be here, in your house.
Do you like a fight?
I love it.
Are you anxious, Carol?
I love a fight. I love when the fight
is about to happen. I love it, man.
Bro, did you eat six sticks at once?
Man, were you starving?
It's delicious.
Damn! Where were you locked up?