Let's go, guys!
Don't you feel like getting another one?
Really, Titto?
Look at this motherfucker.
Look at this package, you fag.
Look, Carol, you're screwed...
This is called a camel toe.
Stop seducing me. Enough.
Get out of here. Jesus.
Sniff my stinky feet.
Guys, we're back.
Guys, we're using the same colors.
I'm not, Bia.
It's true. Forest green.
The jaguar. The snake. And the forest.
Hey, I'm a plant.
The snake...
I'm a... tree, and he's a plant.
And you are yourself.
Hey, I know this. It's called "holt-holt"?
You mean hot roll.
"Holt-holt..."
Could you take one and spoon-feed me?
Sure, milady. What else do you want?
Spoon-feed me...
- I'll give you...
- Yummy.
What do you want?
I want you to spoon-feed me.
To spoon-feed you? Wait.
Careful, I'm wearing lipstick.
He has to see it. He must be jealous.
- Me? Baby, Titto is nothing to me.
- Open your mouth.
You want everything?
Just a piece of it.
Girl, Titto is nothing to me.
- Poor thing.
- Put it all. Put it all.
Stop it!
Stop being jealous, crazy girl.
Stop it.
- All right, I'm sorry.
- Carol choked.
Are you okay, Carol?
Guys, Carol has to be awarded...
the series' icon prize.
Episode five, cheers. Cheers. Cheers.
Let's toast to what's going
to happen today.
Go... Everybody is anxious.
I don't want to drink a toast to John.
He doesn't deserve it.
Me neither. I thought about João
last week, you know?
Thinking about how he was an icon.
Guys, João surprised me because he had
more sex than anybody in one day.
That's true. And Ramon, too.
Because Ramon is a prince.
Guys, seriously, I want to know
how João's life is.
- Because he's...
- Man, João is a mystery to me.
He started being something...
We call it a "virgin" in Salvador.
Same here?
Virgin, big time.
He started as a virgin,
then he said, "I only date."
After a while, baby... I swear...
I'm going to take my shoes off...
I didn't understand why he said he wasn't
a fucker. I'm confused.
Girl, he must be mineiro.
He does things quietly.
Nice to meet you, do me quietly.
- I don't know anything.
- I want to watch it. Shall we?
I press play, Miss Bianca?
You can, honey.
It's her snack!
She's at her house... That's rude.
I remember there was trouble.
Luan and Ramon are going to do
that again.
I'm shocked...
Press play. Use your heel to do it, go.
What a heel, girl.
You killed it, I love it.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
- Hello?
- Hello? Ricardo?
- Hi, Ramon, how's it going?
- How are you, all good?
I'm okay.
I need your help.
Trust me. Stay in touch.
Thanks, boss.
- Bye.
- Take care.
Bye.
Murilo.
Murilo, remember that Sunday when we were
at Acqua talking about the beach,
that you hadn't been
on a beach in ten years?
Do you want to go on a boat ride?
Bullshit!
Really? Really?
Really?
Man! Fuck, let's do this.
Fuck, I'm grateful for this wonderful day.
Thank you for this moment, universe.
Holy shit.
Let's do it all over again. We're here.
That's it.
One for all! All for one! One for all!
And all for one!
Man, look at this island.
It's awesome, man.
I'm very grateful.
Look at this, man, look at this water.
Wonderful.
Cool. There's only one house.
There's nothing to complain about, just
be grateful for. Cool place.
Go, baby.
Go, go. Go, Ramon.
Go, Mauro!
Fuck!
That's supposed to restore energy.
The ocean took the bad energy
from me, man.
Fuck, man. I've never seen this, man.
I'm very happy, man.
- You're crazy.
- I've never seen this, man.
You've seen the ocean, ten years later.
Look at this.
You deserve it. You deserve it.
Fuck, you deserve it. You deserve it, bro.
I'm very happy, man.
- Have we arrived yet?
- Yes.
- I'm okay, baby.
- Hey, be careful.
We got the right amount of sunlight.
It was beautiful.
- We didn't get caught in the rain.
- What about the view?
The view was awesome.
Now, I just want to take a warm bath,
warm up my balls
because my dick has shrunk.
It's all wet.
- You have to sit down to piss.
- Poor him.
It's in the cave.
Let me tell you something...
I was talking to a friend who surfs,
and he said there's
a cool bar we can go to...
Let's check this bar out tonight.
Let's go to this bar
and have some craft beer, man.
Tonight, we're going to this bar.
Let's go, let's go.
Look, guys, thanks a lot
for sharing one more night...
Do you think I'm going to drop it?
...for sharing these wonderful moments
with all of you.
Do you know why?
Because the day today was awesome,
and the night is just getting started.
Do you know what I want?
I want more!
Let's do this,
because you only live if you fuck.
- Ouch.
- It's the Tiger Room.
Who do you like?
That blond girl or this...
I prefer the brunette.
Me, too, I swear.
But let's call both of them over.
That blond girl is too hot, man.
She's not my type.
Forget about the blond... Get
the brunette, what's left over is mine.
Maybe we hook up with both
of them together, think about it.
Let's go, brother. It's time to let it go
and fuck all the girls, bro.
I want you to do this for me.
If you hook up with Nath again,
I'll slap you in the face.
I'll punch you in the face.
That's it. Cheers.
Let the naughty ones out, man.
I didn't sleep like this, you know?
No? You acted like a saint.
The others didn't...
If you sleep with somebody like this...
You can't do it with that
naughty girl I slept with.
- What's your name?
- Ramon, what about yours?
- Ramon?
- Susan.
Stop it.
Really? Are you jealous of Ramon?
I have nothing with him.
If I did, I'd tell you.
Okay... What I want to know
makes no sense.
I'm going to sleep with you, baby.
- Not today.
- Yes, today.
- I'm leaving.
- Don't.
Yo, kids!
Listen up.
Let's go to the afterparty.
The bus is here.
Let's go. Come on, come on.
Everybody!
Chill out. You're with me.
Let's go, let's go.
You're invited. You can come.
Let it go! Home! Finally.
What's this place, man?
We just need ice.
Look at this, man.
- Is this ours?
- Yes.
Really...
- Why are you like this?
- What do you want to hear?
I want to know the truth.
- The truth.
Really? Do you want to hear it?
Really? I won't tell you.
Yes. Say it...
So I don't look bad to you?
Look bad to me? Like that...
No, that crazy man almost...
Who? What?
- What is it, guys?
- What is it?
Mauro is mad at me because of you.
I did nothing to you.
- I know.
- Okay.
- Is he mad at me? No...
He's mad at me.
Okay, but you have to fix this with him...
Look, you started hooking up... We settled
everything that had to be settled.
I'd never disrespect either of you.
- Really?
- Yes.
I won't get involved because
you have to settle this.
- That's enough.
- That's it.
Mauro, grow up.
Grow up, me? I've already grown up a lot.
For Christ's sake. Ramon, did we hook up?
- No.
- Man, when did I say this?
What the fuck are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
I didn't hook up with him.
I've just said it, I'll say it again.
Do I want to hook up with him? Yes.
Am I jealous of him? Yes.
That's the guy I...
Why am I talking to you?
I did nothing.
Why are you suspicious of me?
Do you want to curse me out? Curse me out.
You should charge for this show
you're putting on.
No, bro.
What? You owe me? I have nothing
to forgive for. Chill out.
Pound it, pound it.
You want to give me a high five
'cause you're pissed.
I wanted to know why.
Because you know, man. Come on.
No... Damn...
I don't want...
you to get mad at me.
- Do you want me to leave with you?
- You're crazy.
So, you want to do this? I'll do it.
I won't allow it.
There it is. Talk to me, bro.
I'm talking, wait.
I'm going to cause trouble.
Fuck. You're crazy.
You know what?
I did nothing, man. What did I do?
I must've done something.
I'm dying, help.
Fat scrambled eggs by Ramon.
I want you to join us to eat.
Yesterday Nath said,
"I'm leaving with you. You'll see.
I'm going upstairs to pack my bags now."
She went upstairs and fell asleep.
No way, Murilão, really?
She didn't even say goodbye to him.
Didn't you see what
she did on the table?
- No.
- I heard it.
She was here annoying him,
"I don't know, man."
What? She put him and Ramon down
and went upstairs saying,
"I want him!" Then pointed to Ramon.
She said she likes you.
Shut up.
- I'm really sorry.
- About what?
About saying things to Mauro.
Because of what you said, right?
I'm very upset.
I wouldn't care if it was another person.
Dude didn't deserve it.
- But I did nothing, like...
- Yeah, right.
Nothing happened,
he just got jealous...
You think?
...of us dancing.
Sure thing.
Then he said, "You know what?
They're made for each other."
I was daydreaming.
I was wasted and said,
"What are you talking about?"
Then...
The problem is that
I want to settle things
- immediately.
- Sometimes, you don't get to do that.
When I'm drunk, I want to settle things
and... I ended up saying too much.
Do you remember that party
we were invited to, at that DJ's place?
Let's get ready.
Drink for free? Let's go!
Bro, like, dude wants...
Take it, take it, take it,
Take it, take it, hot girl
Let's go!
Wonderful!
Summer here is crazy. Like...
I play in the band besides working.
Man, there's three parties every day.
Every day.
I've been here.
I've already been here before.
I saw you talking to the blond guy.
Stop it, you're going down.
Did it work?
- He's a good person.
- He's hot.
- Very hot.
I hope Murilo doesn't
hear me saying this, but he's hot.
Ramonzinho is out of the picture?
Have you seen the phoenix?
Rising from ashes.
That's what he did...
If you want to kiss somebody,
don't let Ramon stand in your way.
You're beautiful! You know it.
Inside and out.
I tried not to say that I love you.
Ramon was talking to me.
We were dancing and...
He said, "You're beautiful,
you know it, inside and out..." and stuff.
Then he said,
"I'm trying not to say that I love you."
Man, you're out of your mind.
You're out of your mind, as usual.
Was he tricking me?
- No, you're out of your mind, as usual.
- Why?
You're ruining everything.
Why don't you hook up with that guy?
Fuck, cut it out.
Is she going to talk to him?
Come on, baby.
- I don't get it.
- Things are not like this.
I don't think it's a problem.
Things are not like this.
If I was in his shoes, you'd be hurting.
- Can I be honest?
- So, he's not talking to anyone?
No. That woman hat he hooked up with,
that he took home.
She came here...
I saw it, in front of me.
That woman came here wanting him,
he said, " I don't want you."
But both situations are different.
- That's okay.
- It's totally different.
No, don't get involved.
I don't want you to, but you know what?
People will start saying,
"Ramon this, Ramon that. Move on."
And when I see him talking
to some other girl, I get pissed and say,
"Bro, I wonder if people are right."
I get like this...
I don't know. Why?
But did you see who started tonight?
- What?
- Talking to other people.
- It was you.
- But... Let me speak.
Ramon was cool.
After we fought,
I admired Ramon
because he knew how to move on.
He treated Mauro so fucking well.
He showed that he's not a child.
I told him, "Man, you're not a man..."
I noticed that's not the case,
but it happens, that's chance.
I'm here for the party.
You can keep on talking.
It's a good thing to let her boy know.
Not boy, it's a casual date.
That's fair.
- That's what I told you.
- You told me.
You see? I told him.
Right, but... What are you telling them?
That she wants to hook up with him,
but he's afraid of what happened and all.
I think that's not it.
Do you think he's lying?
I think she has to think straight,
you know?
Because he made a mistake,
but you screwed up, girl.
Get it? You said you loved Mauro and him.
Fuck!
- Make up your mind, got it?
- Not love.
If you want to hook up with the dude...
If you want to, do whatever you want.
Right? You're free.
- That's the way out. You're free.
- Don't be a phony and say,
"I wanted Ramon."
Yeah, that's enough of that.
Got it?
Don't do this. It's looking bad, really.
I'm saying this as your friend.
I don't know what's going on,
but cut it out.
You know everything.
You know?
Guys, this party was something, huh?
Beatriz, I love you!
Beatriz took her to task.
She left upset.
Now she's going to take Beatriz down.
No, girl...
When you don't want
to hear the truth, you act like this...
Ramon looks like he's from Goiânia.
I think Ramon is doing that
so she doesn't hook up with the blond guy.
They're saying in the house
that she's a screwup.
She's hurting because of Ramon.
She acted like crazy,
said the guy was a piece of shit, a child,
that she regretted meeting him.
She hooked up with that boy she ordered,
things are not going her way.
Guys, let's be honest.
It failed. She's trying to force
a relationship that doesn't exist.
I think Ramon is feeling worse 'cause
of the situation, not 'cause he likes her.
I think...
she doesn't like him.
She was playing with him.
It backfired.
He doesn't care about her anymore.
Do you think he's not into her?
- I agree with you.
- No...
I think Ramon's attitude was great,
because he moved on,
he was hooking up with a girl.
And that other one...
I think he didn't move on.
After that talk they had,
I think he wants to say, "I told you so."
- That's it.
- But I think he's behaving in a good way.
- I think he's the most consistent...
- Sensible.
I think he doesn't want her anymore.
Do you know why?
Because when you're seeing somebody...
Hear my wise words.
When you're...
When you're seeing somebody,
you analyze the behavior...
to see if it's possible to have
a future relationship with that person.
He's already seen it, he's like...
I'm sure he thinks, "I'm seeing this girl,
and she does that.
Imagine if I had a real relationship...
What else would she do?"
Guys, she wants Ramon pretty bad.
She called Mauro because of Ramon.
If you were Ramon,
would you give her a chance?
- I wouldn't!
- I'd call the cops.
She plays dirty, right?
She's low, girl.
No, she's mean.
She said she was going to leave, right?
She said she was going to pack.
- I'm going... to bed.
- Baby, who's Amanda?
Everybody judged Amanda.
Who's Amanda compared to her?
- Amanda was nice in the house.
- Amanda's honest.
She doesn't play dirty.
Amanda, friends with Tay.
The vegan friend...
At least she said what she wanted.
- Shame.
- Look at the fight.
- You and Nath didn't hook up yesterday?
- No.
Not even a kiss?
It's not going to happen again,
I'm telling you.
It's not going to happen.
- It's not going to happen?
- No...
What you're gonna do? Party with me?
I am.
I'm going to party, my way. Yesterday
I danced when I wanted, I partied...
Last night was cool.
No pressure, nothing.
You danced a lot, right, baby?
You two put on a show on the dance floor.
- Tay's situation...
- You were born to funk dance.
Are we going to cook more potato
so as not to leave this here?
I think it's worth it.
I'm going to remove...
The potato?
Just a little is enough.
- I have the oil here.
- Give it to me.
Take it.
Oh, fuck.
The son of a gun is calling.
- There he goes.
- Hey, my friend!
- What's up, Ricardo?
- We jinxed it.
- Ricardo?
- Go to the porch.
Hey, my man.
It's Murilo, how are you?
Do you recognize my voice? Tell the truth.
How was the boat ride?
Man, it was rad. Thanks, you know?
For the boat...
If it wasn't for you,
we wouldn't have taken a ride.
Thanks a lot.
Today, the four boys are coming over
to help me.
Cool.
I'm waiting for you guys.
Cool. Take care. Later.
Take care.
Things just got better.
The four boys.
The four of us?
Good.
- Again?
- Let's get to work, right?
Madness inside the bus
That beautiful moment we had
What do you think about going
funk dancing tonight?
- What?
- That's fair.
- Funk dancing is never bad.
- Girls only.
What?
Guys, the bus is here.
- Let's go.
Should we take a picture beforehand?
Let's put the picture on the fridge
with a note for the boys.
- Let's do it.
- Good.
This one goes a little more
in the back, right?
We went to the funk party
Let's go.
- Let's go?
- Let's go.
Tonight is the night.
Let's go party!
We're going to shake our asses.
To shake the big ass...
The big ass God gave us.
Mine is not that big.
Mine is a little flat.
But you have it.
Wow, the flashing drink.
Pour some for me again.
One for all.
All for one!
One for all, all for one!
I hope we have a magical night.
Us for us. Always!
Always!
For those who've never been a waiter...
Tell me,
is it the coolest beer?
The best we have.
Come on, it was at the end.
There should be tequila.
I wanted it, too.
You have to talk to our manager, Ricardo.
There should be tequila for you.
- For you.
- If we drink tequila, baby...
Yeah?
I'm scared, I'm scared of you.
Tequila for everybody here, fuck.
Now I want to see... the four of you.
I'm going to leave for a while.
I have some serious business to deal with.
- You're responsible for the bar.
- Deal.
- I trust you.
Thanks for trusting me.
- You got it?
- Sure.
Do I need to do anything?
- Ramon, you already know the job.
- Deal.
So... Teach them.
I trust you. Don't let me down.
I got it. Be cool.
- It's okay. Deal.
- Thanks.
Good evening.
Listen to this.
The boss had to leave
and left me in charge while he's away.
Here's the thing, you're going to work,
and I'll enjoy a little while he's out.
- Okay? Deal?
- Deal. You're such a carioca.
It had to be you, right, punk?
If you're not doing anything,
let me take over this...
I'm going to enjoy.
Just a minute.
The boss had to leave
and left me in charge.
Luanzinho, what did you ask me
just a while ago?
- We want shots!
- Do you want shots?
I want to hear it, who wants shots?
I can't hear you.
Raise your hands, everybody up.
Shot! Shot!
Then, shots for fucking everybody.
Luan, bring shots for everybody.
I'm fucking in charge.
Let's go!
Come, come. Didn't you want shots?
At last, you did something right, carioca.
Come, we have shots for everybody.
Not too much.
You're going to drink it too...
I'm going to get in line again.
Can't I drink just one more?
Next!
This is the Brazil I want, huh?
Hold it, don't swallow it.
Hold it in your mouth.
Swallow it!
Now, here, look!
It should've been on the mouth.
Give me a tequila kiss.
Nobody told you to drink tequila.
Tequila ruins people's lives.
You're going to be shot.
Don't you want it? Here.
- Bring me a drink?
- What do you want?
- You can bring me an Aperol.
- Okay.
Okay. I'm going to get you one.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, what?
I don't want it. I'm cool.
Let me tell you something.
Come here, in the corner.
If you gave shots to everybody in the bar,
we're so fucked.
Good, man.
Give this cap to him later.
You can celebrate,
but tonight, we're screwed.
Now we're fucked.
I have some notes for you.
First, I want to thank you for the effort.
The bar got happier, great.
I'm gonna let you go earlier
so you can enjoy.
Okay?
That's not all.
There are two things. One,
the boat ride is expensive, I told you.
You're not only paying for this tonight.
- Okay?
- Sure.
I'm having a party at the bar...
Are you seeing this crowd?
I want to double it.
You're going to promote
- this party I'm throwing here.
- Great.
- We got it.
- Ask the girls for some help.
I'll invite the whole island here.
- Deal, deal.
- Cool?
When is it?
- I'll let you know.
- Okay, deal.
- Cool?
- Cool.
We can tell people now.
Is this going to be wild?
The wildest... Now you can go enjoy
the place because you cheered up the bar.
Thanks.
At the end, we'll cash out
and see how the situation is.
Sure.
But, for now, I trust you guys.
That's it, gang. Thanks.
Thanks, Ricardo.
Thanks, brother.
Sex on the Beach.
I'll finish it.
This is the gin.
I thought I was going to be scolded.
Punk... You're a punk.
Let's go.
Thanks.
I'm João Vitor.
You said you were going to kiss her.
Whoa.
You didn't give me tequila anymore.
You didn't give it to me.
If it isn't like this, it ain't happening.
Not sure if I'll show Rio to you.
I'd rather stay and fuck you.
No.
Then find time to know Rio and fuck me.
I want to know Rio, too.
- Yeah? You want to know it?
- Sure.
I'll show you around.
My room is great.
It's time, huh?
Who's coming?
Let's go! Let's go!
Good evening for those who date.
We're waiting for you at our party, huh?
Let's go home.
Come on, Blondie.
Jesus.
MOMMIES
ARE HERE
Girl, what do you think
the boys are doing back home?
I think they're not giving
a fuck about us, and we're doing the same.
We came here to party.
Nobody needs men to be happy.
That's it. No, girl...
Seriously, we party...
That's the best party I've ever been to,
with the four of us.
I don't want to worry about anybody.
I don't want to worry about
what you're going to do.
I like to see you like this.
Beautiful and drunk,
falling on the ground.
Not so much.
But... I'm very drunk.
Fuck.
Rain!
Man, don't fall.
Luan, I have terrible news for you.
There's no food.
There is always food. Champagne?
I want to give... this to Luan.
"We went to the funk party."
Ouch!
They went to the funk party.
No one's here.
Do you know if they have more than us?
I'm going to raise a toast
with this champagne. This goes for you...
And for Murilão.
You're the first one to have a sip.
Welcome! You, too, come.
Is all of it those girls' fault?
Not coming home?
They'll be really wasted.
I wonder what's happening there.
No...
Bro, they went to a funk party, VIP area,
with a bunch of men dancing all over them.
Look at this, bro.
We'll see.
Look,
if I were you,
I wouldn't get ahead of myself.
I'm cool, bro. Are you insane?
There's nothing to say.
Luan is the one who's mad.
Not at them.
Because we didn't go, man.
Bruna?
She doesn't care...
Kiss him, baby!
What time are you leaving?
Are you going to spend the night?
Girl, are you leaving?
See you later...
One step at a time.
- Don't.
- I'm with someone here.
Do you want help?
Look how she's doing the dishes.
Girl, it's my heel.
- Forget the shoes.
- What?
Did you go to a party?
Have some champagne...
Jeez, this heel... There.
And I'm deluding myself...
She's the best...
Wonderful, guys. Girls...
- I'm in, too.
- We already visited the lions' room...
How was the night?
And I'm deluding...
And I'm deluding myself...
I want a kiss from my baby.
And I'm deluding...
Milu
Girl,
Ramon is with somebody, easy.
Murilo isn't with somebody, right?
Damn, I would be crying a lot right now.
Good.
You really love me.
Look.
Do you...
Put your hand on my chest.
I think I'm feeling bad.
Are you sleeping on my bed?
Oh, no!
That's messed up.
At least let me see your face.
You're sleeping on my bed.
Beatriz.
Get out of here... Out.
You're sleeping on my bed!
You're imagining things, Nathalia.
You're imagining things.
I'm not imagining things.
Slap your own face.
I can't believe...
Jeez, man.
Jeez, that chick is clueless, man.
I'm shocked with Nathalia's attitude.
Nathalia is totally insane.
Seeing what she's done,
I understand that she has a feeling
and doesn't know how to deal with it.
Since the beginning.
It would be one thing if she was crazy.
She has no feelings at all.
You think?
He was playing because he said
he loved her one day
and the other day he did that.
- But...
- This is worse.
She was thinking she was
- full of herself.
- Do you think he's playing, too?
He doesn't have
any feelings for her.
Do men play hard to get with you?
Many men do it with me.
Jeez, I say, "Look, baby,
I'm not gonna play this game."
I don't like it.
Don't do this to me, I'll go crazy.
Nice to meet you, I like games.
The other day I was out with my friends...
Then you felt like fucking.
Everybody was talking, a woman
showed up and said, "I want to fuck."
Stop it. Where were you...
What is this place?
- I mean it.
- Some place.
I mean it. 3:00 a.m.
"I'm doing nothing here,
anybody want to fuck me?"
Are you out at 3:00 a.m.?
I'm still waking up at 3:00 a.m.
That woman showed up at the taxi stand
and said, "I want to fuck."
This way, anybody does it, right.
She showed up, there were 20 people,
and said, "I want to fuck."
- So, the first to get up fucked her?
- No, three got up.
I'm going to the streets saying,
"Who wants to pay my bills?"
I think it's much more difficult for men.
It's already difficult for men to kiss,
but to fuck...
"Today I'm going to fuck."
It's more complicated.
It requires a lot of talk.
You have to do this...
I'm going to show up on your street
and say, "Who wants to pay my bill?
Who wants to pay my credit card?"
Who do you think is enjoying
that house the most?
- João, man.
- Blondie.
- It's Blondie.
- Do you think it's João?
Blondie doesn't fight.
She doesn't care about anything.
Blondie is wonderful.
It's Blondie and João.
After João had sex, he went nuts, guys.
He enjoys the parties the most.
He hooks up with more girls.
He's the one enjoying the most.
He has no reason to fight.
I'd be like João, but not...
I wouldn't be friends with anybody.
I'd hook up with one boy,
hook up with another.
I'd wake up, have breakfast,
hook up with another boy.
Man, João is like this, right?
He's not hooking up with anybody
from the house.
But if you hook up with a boy
who was somebody else's,
the chicks would fight you.
They'd follow me.
Everybody would hook up with each other.
- Who would you be in the house?
- João.
I'd be Tay. What about you?
Tay?
I think I'd be... Taynara and Murilo.
Man, Murilo is awesome. I'd be into him.
I like relationships with fights.
No, I wouldn't be into him.
Who would you be?
I wouldn't be.
Choose one. Everybody did.
- Blondie.
- Blondie? She doesn't hook up with anyone.
She does whatever she wants, she's cool.
Would you kiss someone there?
- On the mouth.
- Which one did you like the most?
Man, in the beginning I liked João,
but I don't like men like that...
What he showed himself to be.
I like discreet men.
That's true.
I think Murilo seems to be more...
The manager?
The manager is so serious.
That's true, the manager is super serious.
Where would you hook up with him
in that house?
- In the bathroom.
- I would do it in the pool.
I'd only do it in the bathroom, too.
Press play, for Christ's sake.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
I'll put Tay against the wall
and shake on her ass.
I respected your girl a lot, you prick.
Do you want to show off?
- Easy, man.
- Who do you think you are, brother?
They'll kill him.
What happened, bro? Go.
You don't need this.
I'm going to have to kill you.
Guys, this show is crazy.
- I'm shocked.
- Man...
Looks like somebody rubbed up against Bia.
I think Carol taught them how to rub up.
People did it and it caused trouble.
I'm shocked
because there was a real fight.
Guys, one episode ends well,
the next one...
Girl, I told you that bus is something.
That bus is something.
Amazon Prime Video,
please, bless that bus.
That's true.
Now,
Luan, after that fight,
you can come out. We're waiting.
I'm shocked... Let me tell you something.
Set the alarm
because I want to see everybody here.
I'm shocked with those fights, you know?
I need to take a rosemary
and honey bath to...
How can we wait one week?
How can we wait one week to watch this?
- Let's make a group on the app?
- Guys, I'm shocked.
One group on WhatsApp
to talk about Wild and Free...
I'm very anxious.
What happened?
- Guys, that's crazy.
- But we'll find out
on the next episode, right?
Take care, it was great being with you.
- Bye, see you.
- My car from the app.
Can we take this cake home?