WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
THE REVIEW
Guys, João surprised me because he had
more sex than everybody in one day.
That's true.
Guys, seriously, I want to know
how João's life is.
Because he's...
- João is a mystery to me.
- He started being something...
We call it a "virgin" in Salvador.
Is it the same here?
- It's called a virgin.
- Sure. Virgin.
He started as a virgin,
then he said, "I only date."
In a while, baby...
I thought about that sex the whole week.
Why did he say he wasn't
a fucker and did that?
Girl, he must be from Minas Gerais.
He does things quietly.
That's true.
Nice to meet you, do me quietly.
I want to watch it. Shall we?
Can I press play, Bianca?
You can, honey.
She's at her home.
But episode five ended like that.
I remember some trouble.
I'm shocked you're doing this to me.
Press play. Use your heel
to do it, I know you like it.
What a heel. You killed it.
- Bring it on, man.
- Floripa!
- Do you want to sit down?
- I didn't sleep like this, you know?
No? You acted like a saint.
But you didn't...
If you sleep with somebody...
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
I very much believe it.
Because she was tempted to do that.
She said she wanted to...
The worst is that dishonesty from her.
Using a person...
Both of them, man.
As much as the person knows everything,
like her crush,
but she's using him
and manipulating the situation.
It's a lack of character.
She keeps playing these kind of games.
No, it makes me bored.
I was hooking up with...
You criticize her, but you...
But I'm here to criticize,
not to stay quiet.
Doesn't mean...
I already hooked up with a guy at a club,
then I saw him with another guy,
I hooked up in front of him.
I talked to a lot of people...
I see.
...just to annoy him.
In the end, I screwed up.
The same happened to her.
I ended up being the loser,
making a fool of myself.
So, I think that's not right.
I started seeing a guy,
and he was not very much into it...
I realized he was kind of distant,
and I said,
"Cool, his brother is hot."
I hooked up with his brother.
Then he got hornier, and I ended up
hooking up with both of them.
- Did they know?
- They saw everything.
Same house, same room.
Let's go. You're invited. You can come.
- Look at Ramon...
- Look at Ramon's face.
- Look at his face.
Did he want her to go, guys?
The same look a young man has
when he goes into my place.
Did you hear that?
"Am I going?" He said, "Sure."
I loved...
"You're invited."
Look at his face. No... I liked it a lot.
He thought, "Today's the day."
Checked his underwear, "Today's the day."
- Why are you like this?
- What do you wanna hear?
I want to know the truth.
- The truth.
Really? Do you want to hear it?
Really? I won't tell you.
Yes. Say it...
When she drinks, she loses it.
Man, she's kind of a villain.
- She messes up a lot.
- I can't understand her.
Is she going to come at Ramon's chick?
Mauro... Mauro, grow up.
Grow up, me? I've already grown up a lot.
For Christ's sake. Ramon, did we hook up?
- No.
- Man, when did I say this?
Did you hit on me?
What the fuck are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
We didn't do anything.
I've said it, I'll say it again.
I want to hook up with him? Yes.
Am I jealous of him? Yes.
That's the guy I...
Why am I talking to you?
I did nothing.
Why are you suspicious of me?
Do you want to curse me out?
You should charge for this show
you're putting on.
No, bro.
Guys, I wonder
if she's a desperate, needy person.
I think she's like Rubi.
Rubi, right? She's like Regina George.
I think she's very delusional about it.
She's not acting normal
because of all of that.
Far away from loved ones.
What would you do with someone
who's suffocating like her?
- We feel suffocated, man.
- I think sometimes we need cleansing.
We need to clean our chakras.
She needs a cleansing,
a healing touch, I don't know.
She does that to every guy, man.
She's desperate for Ramon.
She called Mauro because of Ramon.
If you were Ramon,
would you give her a chance?
- I wouldn't.
- I'd call the cops.
He's so upset, he thought, "I'm leaving.
I won't wait until tomorrow."
Jeez, guys, I feel so bad for that boy.
That's unfair, he was called...
- He's cute.
- Poor guy, he was kicked down the steps.
Hey, cutie, don't be sad,
Nathalia doesn't deserve you.
- I'm really sorry.
- About what?
About saying shit to Mauro.
- Because of what you said?
- I'm very upset.
Is it Nathalia? She went to Ramon
to talk about the guy.
What is that bowl for, guys?
- She's eating...
- What is it?
- It's cake. It's a birthday cake bowl.
- What?
It's Tupperware.
- Then you said that...
- I ended up saying too much.
- What advice would you give her?
- I'd tell her to be cool, enjoy the party
and not hook up with any boy
for no reason.
It's better for her to wait...
- I'd tell her to take antidepressants.
- Or a coach.
What if she's in love and is
doing that 'cause she's out of control...
This is a kind of love...
Passion is something much...
Passion is something much better
than love at some points.
Passion has a fire that love doesn't have.
You have to enjoy it while you still can.
When you touch someone,
you get a shock.
Love is something that takes time,
intimacy, respect and a lot of things.
Do you remember that party
we were invited to, at that DJ's place?
- The DJ.
- Let's get ready?
Drink for free? Let's go!
Bro, like, dude wants...
She's suffering for one,
and going out to see another.
This is the meme Nathalia.
If she has to suffer,
may she do it being pretty.
Jeez, the soundtrack is really cool.
I like this one.
What he...
It raises the bar for Brazil. Right?
What are you talking about?
Guys, who's that rich sugar daddy?
Two cars in the garage.
Look at the size of the door.
- Stop doing this.
- Three.
- Oh, my God.
- That's not new to you.
I love it.
Wonderful.
Summer here is crazy.
I play in the band besides working.
Man, there's three parties every day.
Must be awesome.
Every day.
I've already been here before.
It was winter, though.
- I forgot she wants him.
- Yeah.
- There's that boy Tay set her up with.
- Look at Ramon, man.
Ramon is a clumsy dancer, right?
But he's cute.
- Who's that girl? Is it Taynara?
- It's Tay.
- With her man, she doesn't want trouble.
- Baby, she feels at peace.
Ramon is out of the picture?
Have you seen the phoenix?
Rising from ashes.
That's what he did...
Stop, Ramon.
Wanna kiss somebody?
Don't let Ramon get in your way.
But Ramon couldn't care less.
Guys, that's it...
Maybe she's fantasizing
this whole romance.
Girl, I don't know why.
She went there looking for trouble.
She's really an attention whore.
I don't know what to say.
I don't want them together.
Oh, no, they're kissing.
No, Ramon! Don't you do this to yourself.
- I told you.
- Holy shit.
Look at the blond DJ.
I've been trying
not to say "I love you".
- What did he say?
-"I love you."
"Trying not to say 'I love you'."
I've been trying
not to say "I love you".
He didn't say that, John...
I told you, Brazil,
he would come back to her.
- No, that guy should be spanked...
- Dear Lord.
When someone says, "I love you,"
that's a whole different story.
That doesn't change anything.
If a guy told you,
"Pabllo, I love you," what would you do?
You know what...
I wonder if he's...
...she didn't hear and say, "Huh?"
I'd see that things were getting serious
and I'd bounce, sis.
- That's a lie.
- Especially in two days.
Dude... If you want to,
do whatever you want.
Right? You're free.
Don't be a phony and say,
"I wanted Ramon."
That's enough of that, okay?
If you want Ramon,
you go there and kiss him.
Don't do this. It's looking bad.
I'm saying this as your friend.
Nath, cut it out.
Beatriz, I love you!
- Bia was very sensible.
- Bia is a fool.
Beatriz took her to task.
Now she's going to
take Beatriz down, I bet.
No, girl... It's like this...
Why is Bia a fool?
Bia is a fool for wasting her time
with Nathalia.
Look at him dancing, this is awful.
He's like a worm.
Guys...
Teach him how to
rub against someone.
Does he dance like that in Niterói?
He's from Niterói.
I ship that couple.
Take it.
Girl, morning has broken.
They didn't show the house, nothing.
- I want that house.
- Do you? I'll sell it to you.
But...
- She wants to buy it legally.
- Take me there, Titto.
Amazon rented it from my daddy
for $300 a day.
You and Nath didn't hook up yesterday?
- No.
- Nothing? Not even a kiss?
It won't happen again.
I'm telling you this.
It's not going to happen.
It's not?
What did he say?
Paraphernalia.
I love you, Ramon, keep being like this.
- Don't let me down.
- He won't. He'll hook up with her.
He won't. He's realized she's kind of...
Guys, have you found out
who had sex or not yet?
Blondie hasn't had sex, right?
Man, you know what's worse?
- She's not upset about that.
- She's wonderful.
João got upset when he didn't have sex.
No, we got upset.
Sometimes I'm like her,
and I don't hook up with anyone.
She's hooking up with everyone.
- I'd rather have fun with my friends.
- Sometimes I'm like her.
I'd rather both options
if it's possible.
If not, that's okay.
But it has already happened, and don't...
Everything is wonderful.
Sometimes, don't you just want to
go out and have fun?
I'm like this a lot.
I say, "Tonight I'm having fun,
but if I meet someone,
that's okay, I'm not dead."
I'm not shutting my door
for a boy either.
If he gets in, he gets in.
It's like Carol,
she sleeps with the door open.
Carol is a mafia woman.
Do you ever go to a party
and don't hook up?
Kissing someone at a party, man?
No, I just say, "Give me your number."
Then I set a date for another day.
And on the streets?
- Do you do this on the streets?
- I stop the car, "Let me talk to you."
What if you hear a no?
What if you get rejected?
Have you ever been rejected?
I've got a thing, I don't know.
I have something, you know?
She's the best.
No, you know what?
I think you're empowered.
You have confidence.
She's not!
She's more unbreakable than a rock.
For love...
What? Hi.
Pabllo, have you ever been rejected?
You hit on anyone,
and the person said no?
- I have.
- Bullshit! Recently?
Not recently because
I don't even go out...
After being famous or before?
I've been rejected.
Just because we're recognized?
I didn't reject you, I just said
I couldn't do it, you know? I'm sorry.
These days,
I was talking to an açaí street vendor.
I said, "Hi, how are you?
"Do you deliver açaí...
Would you deliver to me?"
It was midnight, you know?
Fuck!
"Would you deliver to my place?"
He said, "Well, I don't know..."
"Do you have a girlfriend?"
He said, "I'm seeing someone."
This is a... You know?
It's just reality.
- Guys, the bus is here.
- Let's go. Here we go!
- Let's take a picture before?
- Yes.
Let's put it on the fridge
with a note for the boys.
- Let's do it.
- Good.
Put all of them together.
This one goes a little more
in the back, right?
We went to the funk party
I wonder if that is going
to cause trouble.
Oops. Definitely that is
going to cause trouble.
I want to know who they'll meet
at the funk party.
Let's go to the funk party.
We're going to shake our asses.
To shake the big ass...
The big ass God gave us.
Guys, how I wish I was
doing that with my friends...
Going out with a drink. I love that vibe.
I love it, too.
- Get in the van already drunk.
- A warm-up at home.
Fuck, I love it.
Play it, shake it, shake it
- Is it you? Who?
- No.
Tati?
This is very old.
All of her songs are great.
The big drum stopped
Go, go. What the fuck?
Can Mariano dance funk?
You're dancing with me.
I really dance.
I want to see both of you dancing.
Dance funk rubbing yourself against her...
He knows it... He's dancing.
- What's going on?
- Take it easy. Not here, fellow.
Damn. He knows the moves... Fellow.
- Keep going, Mariano.
- Go for it!
Move your hips! Move your hips, Mariano!
Yeah.
Respect, respect. Respect MS, dude.
- Now you go.
- No, I can't. I can't.
Now you. You do know it. Stop it, go!
I don't know, man. I swear to God, fuck.
I don't know how to dance.
Titto, you did the move.
Raise your shirt and do it, please.
I've seen you wasted at a funk party.
Shirt off, showing your tush...
Go, you go. Carol!
Can I dance for Carol?
Go, dance for Carol.
She's gonna love it.
I don't want it to be a funk song.
- Go!
- Then go.
Look at her face, just because I'm close.
Go!
Sit straight, Carol, I'll dance for you.
Come, Carol!
Oh, my God!
What's this, Carol? Are you shy?
Take down your hand.
What's this, Titto?
Guys, heavens, that's delicious!
I sensed a smell of ass all of a sudden.
She almost had a heart attack with that...
We sensed a smell of ass all of a sudden.
It's Carol's. Mine? It's not.
Who? Hey little John, what about you?
Bianca farted, she has diarrhea.
It wasn't me.
- I know... I dance very well, wait.
- Go, dance!
Wait.
Is it for me?
Don't stop...
No, no, no! No, no, no!
Come, my woman!
Dude...
Some ass. If you fart in a confetti bag,
Carnival lasts three years, man.
Look at the size of his ass.
I can say goodbye with my ass.
How is it?
This is a water tank.
Talk to me, Pabllo.
Hi, girl. Bye, girl. Bye.
Oh, my God.
If you put a cell phone in the pocket
and you switch sides,
the area code changes, dude.
If you put a cell phone in the pocket...
You nailed it, guys.
But I know Bianca can dance.
I'll dance if Pabllo dances.
- Go, Bianca.
- Now the girls, go!
I'm going to dance for Pabllo.
Fuck, fuck, very good fucker
Bianca is a very good fucker
Fuck, fuck
If I see Titto at a funk party,
I go like this, "Let me talk to you."
Stay here. Hey, Titto.
Titto, stay there. Carol, stand here.
Titto there and Carol here.
- Let's go.
- Holy shit.
Look at Carol's flirt, pay attention.
Learn it.
I play it like this, look...
- Titto was looking at it.
- Charming.
I'll look this way in a while.
Then I pretend I don't want it.
You gotta pretend... You have to value me.
How do you pretend?
- I look like this...
- It's a game.
- Pay attention.
- Talk to me.
Then he comes, and I say,
"Give me your number."
What if he steals your cell phone?
You won't steal, right?
He's going away with your cell phone.
Then the man gives his number,
no one saw it, no one knows.
You hook up with him the next day?
Yeah.
You're very patient...
When I'm leaving...
You hook up with him in the end?
You don't hook up
with anyone at a party?
In front of everyone?
At the funk party...
Has anyone given you a wrong number?
"And the flash?"
- No.
- Girl, come here, you make...
You make funk parties...
They're at a funk party...
they have more chances
of hooking up with someone there?
Women hook up with men more than...
Than men hook up with women, dude.
Let's test it, Titto.
Absolutely.
Go to the gate,
let's see who's the first to get laid?
Me or you?
I want to see it.
If I say, "Dude, I want to fuck."
He's going to fuck you.
I'll go to the gate now,
look at a woman passing by and say,
"Hey, I need to have sex urgently..."
She'll say you're a perv
and call the police.
He'll say, "I need
someone to pay my credit card."
Guys, the bank slips are past due. Who...
- Where's the remote, man?
- Go on, guys!
One for all.
All for one! One for all, all for one!
I love it,
that's a girls' night out.
A girls' night out.
Bring that sparkling drink!
"Bring that sparkling drink!"
Haven't I told you?
Sparkles!
Bring that sparkling drink
Look, the sparkling drink.
Play it, shake it
I love sparkling drinks at a party.
Don't you?
I love it, sparkling glass.
We have to go to a funk party
with Carol, man.
Jeez, it's my princess dream.
I'll go, wearing mini shorts.
I barely went to funk parties.
We have to take Carol
to a Jurerê funk party...
I knew...
I've already written a funk song.
Let's see these girls at a funk party.
I've never imagined Mariano doing this.
It's fun. Stop it. You're very fun.
They are really serious at work now.
They have to pay for the boat.
Ramon promised.
For those who've never been a waiter...
Tell me, did you bring the coolest beer?
The best we have.
Come on, it was at the end.
This place had to serve tequila.
I wanted it, too.
You have to talk to our manager, Ricardo.
There should be tequila for you.
I'm talking about you.
If we drink tequila...
I'm taking notes
of every tip about parties...
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- That's for sure.
Four.
Listen to me.
I'm going to leave for a while.
I have some serious business to deal with.
- You're responsible for the bar.
- Deal.
I trust you.
Ramon is hardworking. Even the owner
of the bar gave him that responsibility.
- I don't think so, okay?
- Don't you?
I think it's a test.
I think he's coming back at half.
Here's the thing,
you're going to work,
and I'll enjoy a little while he's out.
That's it. We have a deal.
What? Is this real?
"I'll enjoy a little while you work."
You'd do the same if you were him.
Are you nuts?
Everyone has to work together.
I would do it. I would tell him...
What he said was, "Well, I got the boat.
I was a good guy at the ride.
Now you work,
I'm going to enjoy a little."
It's part of the game.
Really, would you do this? What he did?
Enjoy and leave your friends working?
Then I'd say to everyone, "Take five."
I thought it was wonderful when he said,
"You work, I'm going..."
I'm going to say it.
First, he called to...
Who would call the boss
and ask to borrow his boat?
He had guts,
called and set the whole thing up.
He did the PR...
Is he not enjoying now? Obviously.
Beside, he's...
Things got complicated with Nathalia.
He deserves to have fun.
Just a minute, just a minute.
The boss had to leave
and left me in charge.
Haven't I told...
What did you ask me
just a while ago?
We want shots!
Anybody else wants shots?
- I love Ramon.
- I told you...
I don't know. Really, man?
It's not possible.
Man, I guessed right. He raised hell, man.
Shot, shot!
What?
Shots for everyone for free.
Look how he's cheering,
he's cheering them all.
No, he's giving shots
for everyone for free, man.
For free?
Who's going to pay for this?
It's cool those chicks are getting in line
to drink straight from the bottle.
Awesome, I used to do that at clubs.
Jeez, bro! Look...
Look at João, he's clueless, man.
That's cute.
Bro, he's hooking up
with all the clients, man.
Murilo!
- No...
- Ramon.
Ramon? He deserves it. He should do it.
- He deserves it.
- At work? That's what you're not getting.
He said he loved the other girl
and is taking another one home.
Now we're fucked.
First, I want to thank you for the effort.
The bar got happier.
Great. I'm gonna let you go earlier
so you can enjoy yourselves.
Okay? That's not all.
There are two things.
The boat ride is expensive, I told you.
You're not only paying
for this tonight. Okay?
Sure.
I'm having a party at the bar...
Are you seeing this crowd?
I want to double it.
You're going to promote
this party I'm throwing.
- I love PR.
- It's a promoter.
I'm asking the girls for help.
I'll invite the whole island.
- Cool?
- Deal, deal.
When is it?
- I'll decide and let you know.
- Okay.
Take it.
Is this going to be wild?
The wildest... Now you can go...
You're free to go
enjoy the place
because you cheered up the bar.
He gave everyone tequila for free.
He'll see it on the surveillance cameras.
Bro, how I wanted to see him cashing out.
"Man... Something's wrong."
Guys, he nailed it.
That guy didn't notice.
He cheered that bar up
but finished a tequila bottle.
- He cheered... But that tequila...
- Nonsense.
Murilo was sensible to say,
"You're giving shots for free."
Yeah, yeah.
I'm João Vitor.
You said you were going to kiss her.
What now?
João's rejected a lot, man.
You didn't give me tequila anymore.
What? You're hot.
I say no, and a little after, yes.
Guys, what's going on with João?
What?
- What is that?
- Holy fuck!
Guys!
Her girlfriends looked and said,
"Girl, you crazy!"
I'll introduce you to the good things.
My room is very top.
Do you really like those things?
I love it, girl.
Where would you rather be?
At the funk party with your friends
or hooking up at the bar?
At the funk party, certainly.
That depends on the moment.
If I'm in a hooking-up phase, I go for it.
- What about you?
- Funk party with friends, always.
New cast, João took it home...
Twelve women went to the house.
The committed people got screwed.
I have terrible news.
They went to the funk party.
There's no food.
There is always food. Champagne?
I want to give... this to Luan.
"We went to the funk party."
He was going to say something and stopped.
They went to the funk party.
He's such a troublemaker. Champagne.
- He's very cool.
- He's very cool, awesome.
I wonder if Luan will blow it.
I wonder if Luan will fuck things up.
Murilo won't.
You're the first one to have a sip.
Welcome! You, too, come.
We went to the funk party
Is all of it those girls' fault?
Not coming home?
They'll be really wasted.
I wonder what's happening there. No...
Bro, they went to a funk party,
they stayed in their VIP,
with a bunch of men dancing all over them.
Look at this, bro.
Let's see it.
The boys left those chicks there...
Girls go eat and show up at that house.
- I wouldn't get ahead of myself.
- Are you insane?
Is Murilo pissed?
When you say you're cool, you're not.
Exactly.
If you have to explain that you're cool...
Yeah.
Murilo went to bed.
He left the hook-ups.
I love Murilo.
- Oh, my God, what?
- He also...
The committed people went to bed.
- Oh, my God... Dear Lord.
- The other chick is going to be pissed.
The other chick is going to be pissed.
João and Ramão.
What move would you use? Would you hook up
with someone from the house or outside...
I'd hook up with anyone
who wanted me. I don't care.
Who would you be there?
I'd be like João, but not...
I wouldn't be friends with anybody.
I'd hook up with one boy,
hook up with another.
I'd wake up, have breakfast,
hook up with another boy.
- You'd be João.
- João is like this, right?
He's not hooking up
with anybody from the house.
- Who would you be in the house?
- João.
I'd be Tay. What about you?
Tay? I'd be Murilo or Taynara...
What about you, Titto?
I have no idea...
I think I wouldn't be.
- You have to choose one.
- Me?
Say it.
I can... I'd be Thais, got it? Blondie.
Blondie? She doesn't hook up with anyone.
- But she's enjoying.
- Bro...
Zoom in on his face.
Will you give me a nail file
so I can file my nail?
Would you kiss somebody from the house?
Not from the house.
Would you kiss anyone there?
Who?
I would kiss on the mouth.
Which one did you like the most?
Man, in the beginning I liked João,
but I don't like men like that...
What he showed himself to be.
I like discreet men.
That's true.
I think Murilo seems to be more...
The manager?
The manager is super serious.
Would you kiss the manager?
That's true.
Where would you
hook up with him in that house?
- In the bathroom, no camera.
- I would do it in the pool.
I'd only do it in the bathroom, too.
One step at a time.
Jeez, the high heels...
The deck made the high heels get stuck.
Thais is like me.
"Forget it.
We'll deal with this tomorrow."
"It's my Schutz shoes, girl."
- Will she catch him in bed?
- She will.
Have some champagne...
This heel... There.
I don't know where I'm going.
And I'm deluding myself...
Hi, buddy!
She's the best...
Wonderful, guys. Girls...
I'm in, too.
We already visited the lions' room...
How was the night?
Ouch, she's drunk, she's going to...
- Jeez, everyone is wasted, man.
- Those people are wasted. Poor girl.
I wish I was like this
with my friends I love.
I want a kiss from my baby.
"My baby." She's perfect.
And I'm deluding...
Everyone is wasted.
She's going to catch him, right?
They're hunting those chicks.
Ramon is with somebody, easy.
"Easy." "Easy."
Easy...
Murilo isn't with somebody.
I wish she'd arrived
when they were having sex.
Damn, I would be crying a lot right now.
Good. You really love me.
- I'm not going to look.
- Look. Do you...
Look. It was an accident...
I want to talk to Murilo...
Yes... Are you sleeping on my bed?
- I can't believe she did that...
- No... I'm telling you, no.
- Jeez, man, that chick is clueless, man.
- I'm shocked with Nathalia's attitude.
- I didn't find it nice.
- Nathalia is totally insane.
She has something that doesn't
exist anymore, she needs good sense.
- Yeah, it doesn't. Fuck, she hurt the boy.
- She's ungraceful.
It's like, she may be upset because
he said he loved her yesterday,
but she did something way worse.
- Would you do it?
- Sitting on him? Are you nuts?
Carol and I sitting on a boy...
Would you do it?
I'd say,
"Buddy, put your clothes on, please."
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Imagine this, I'll put Tay against
the wall and shake on her ass?
That's why I'm single.
- I like discreet men.
- House husband who goes to church.
I don't like those men
who dance and stuff.
Do you dance?
More or less.
"But this is me. Real life."
But you're old stuff.
- I'm one of a kind.
- So, you can do it, he can't?