Good morning, friends.
- Good morning.
Today is the day.
Son of a bitch.
Look how close they are now, guys.
Consider the first day and today.
Hello, people. How are you? Look...
We're here together to watch Episode 6
of Floripa Beach House.
I want to remind you
that the previous episode
ended with Nathalia
catching Ramon red-handed.
"Catching him red-handed?"
That was a good one. Great.
What? Did you know about this?
To catch red-handed is a soap opera
back in Cuiabá, got it? That's it.
Remember, Floripa Beach House
has no rules, no limits, okay?
No script, it's real life. Absolutely.
Do you remember that...
That's nice...
On the teaser, Luan was fighting again?
What?
On last week's teaser.
- So, let's watch it?
- Let's do it.
Press play. Bye, thanks.
Yeah, that's true.
That's real.
Get out.
You're sassy...
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
No, it's not.
Bro, I don't remember this.
Ever.
Taking pictures at parties...
Good morning.
- Good morning.
You're so...
What is it?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm the one who gets to be embarrassed.
Give me a kiss. Take care, all right?
You got it, I will.
Thanks, I loved meeting you.
Me, too.
Bye. Be careful, don't fall over there.
You're going to fall.
- Let's see what's inside this box.
- Open it.
CRUSH'S PARTY
- It's the party thing.
- That's rad.
Look at this flyer.
The party flyers.
- Here.
- Look.
Whose party?
The party Ricardo told me about.
We're the promoters.
That's awesome.
Crush's party.
Conceição Lagoon. Choose your look
in the right color and meet your match.
Wait. Let's see.
Did you hear it?
- Is it a message?
- Ricardo, João. Hey, João.
- Damn, that's cool.
- Come here, João.
What's up, guys? How are you?
You got the party flyer.
I want all of you to focus on this, right?
You have to promote this party.
We need to crowd that bar.
We have to bring a lot of
beautiful people, rock that party.
I wonder if I could ask my brother
to show up at this party.
I don't know. What do you think...
When is it?
But, João, we could take the car...
- It's complicated.
- Be my guest...
...me, you, Murilo and Luan. We promote it
today, take the car, four of us,
then, tomorrow, the girls promote it.
- We could do it...
- I'm in.
Bye, guys. Bye.
Bye, bye.
Let's rock this party.
Let's take the back seat.
Stay together.
Man, in my opinion,
we should go to the beaches...
Fuck your opinion.
No, but I'm giving my opinion
so that you consider it.
I agree with the beaches.
- See? You talk too much...
- There's no big deal here.
The car is too high.
Bro... You got big, kid.
A party, at Kai...
It's going to have lots of colors...
I'm inviting you guys...
The sponsorship is...
I want to invite you to a party
we're having tomorrow.
We're promoting here. It's right there,
at Kai's bar.
Have you been there?
Not yet.
If you want to invite your friends...
What beautiful eyes!
Thanks.
I hope to see them tomorrow.
João, let's go.
Let's go, I still have to work.
It's at 7:00 p.m.,
you pay for what you order.
It's gonna be crazy. Let's do it,
couples welcome, invite the gang. Okay?
If you want to invite
anybody to the party,
you're welcome. Admission is free.
Okay... Cool. Where is it?
If you need it,
there's a phone number here.
Okay?
Admission is free.
Hey, girl, we're having
a party here tomorrow night.
If you're interested,
it starts at 7:00, okay?
I found the perfect chick, man.
Do you want to come to the party tomorrow?
I'm organizing it with the boys.
Look over here, the first kiss.
This is really you.
Let me see it.
I'm going to take her...
First Joyce, now her. What's her name?
Go, go.
- Go.
Why don't you invite somebody,
a friend or your boy, to tomorrow's party?
I wanted to invite my friend.
Call her, then call me.
To have some fun...
I don't know...
We're going to mess with...
Girls...
Fuck... We're starving, man.
- Didn't you eat?
- No.
We thought you'd eaten.
Jeez, we were sure...
No, we worked a lot.
Fuck... We invited everybody.
Hello?
What's up, Tô?
What's up, man? It's crazy, right, bro?
- That's weird.
- Holy shit, man.
Bro... I miss you, man.
Fuck, man. How are you, man?
- Bro...
- Is it cool? Really?
It's hard to explain.
It's crazy here, man...
I'm shaking, talking to you, man.
I even farted.
- Really?
- Yeah. It's crazy, man. Look...
That's crazy...
There's a room here called Tiger Room.
My brother, I'm staying in this room.
I had an idea...
What are you doing tomorrow, man?
I'm going to work, right?
Kid, come here tomorrow. Come have fun...
- Tomorrow?
- Come party with me tomorrow.
Come tomorrow, kid...
Tomorrow's the day. All I'm saying.
Easy, kid... Easy, man.
I have to organize things, right, man?
It's not like, "I'm going."
Brother, that's the only chance you'll
have to party with me. It's tomorrow.
I have to see this. I'm going to decide.
Tomorrow? Do I have to go tomorrow?
The party is tomorrow. Tomorrow night.
Come, spend the day tomorrow.
You can stay here.
Take two, three days off, find a way.
Fuck, man. I'll decide on this.
See if I can make it, okay?
Okay, brother. God bless you.
You have to come.
Awesome.
What are you doing tonight?
Bro, there's a place called Lontra...
The bus is here.
Let's go.
- Thanks.
What do you think I am?
I don't give a fuck about those guys.
What did you want me to do? Look.
No, kid. Look... Luan,
I don't want to argue with you, okay?
I respect you, you respect me.
I respect you... Go fuck him if you want.
Kiss him if you want. Fuck.
If you think like that,
that's your problem.
Bê is dancing on the counter,
and he's after Bê.
What's the deal with Murilo?
I think Murilo has no ulterior motives.
No, of course... It's not that vibe.
I don't know, it's not that vibe.
No, I think you can trust
Murilo blindly, man.
He made a mistake.
I didn't see it.
Imagine him breaking up with Tay,
and I lean Tay against the wall and twerk
on her ass. Yeah, right, totally fine.
- I didn't see it.
- No, then it's okay, right?
I didn't see it, bro.
That's it.
Sort things out with him.
I wasn't nervous for nothing.
I won't sort things out with him.
I won't sort things out with him, man.
For me, it's bullshit. Fuck it.
It's over... Let's go.
The car is here, look.
Get in, get in.
I'm cool.
You're a screw-up.
We ruled. We ruled, baby.
This one wanted things to get ugly...
Fuck him. Fuck him, idiot.
I'm going to pretend
I'm not listening to you, Luan.
- Be quiet.
- No, you be quiet.
- Be quiet. You mess things up.
- You be quiet.
That's who you are, Beatriz.
What did I say to you? Be free.
Baby, shut up, you know shit about me.
This is you. This is you...
- That's right.
- Don't pretend to be a good person.
- This is me.
- Twerking on people's faces.
- You, go fuck yourself.
- Fuck you!
Man...
- we danced a lot.
- Man, what?
I danced with Bia a lot. Fuck it.
I saw it. What if it was me and Tay?
Now you're upset, right?
You do whatever you want, Luan.
You do whatever you want, you know?
Respect me, boy. Respect me, boy.
Know your place, boy.
Get your hands off me.
No, she likes it, she means it.
I danced with Bia. Like I danced with Tay,
like I danced with Blondie.
Do you wanna fight? Let's fight.
What do you want?
You know, I'm not going to ignore this!
I want to fight you!
I'm not going to ignore this.
Stop it!
I know how to kick ass...
Are you fucking with me?
Murilo...
Are you making fun of me?
Murilo! Murilo!
I've always respected you. Always.
Me, too. So what?
I'm going to tell you something.
I never treated you like this, you know?
Easy...
You're imagining things, buddy.
Who do you think you are?
Stop it, guys. Please, stop it, man.
Do you think you have five balls?
I have six, buddy.
- Do you have six? Come here, then.
- Stop it!
I'm not going to ignore you, you know?
I've always respected you.
No, brothers, brothers...
For Christ's sake...
- Stop it!
- You fucking piece of shit.
You piece of shit?
Come here, then, you piece of shit!
He's a dick! Hey!
You think you're a man?
Easy. No... Stop this.
What do you think you are?
- They're going to kill him.
- Easy, Murilo.
I respected your girl a lot.
- No, I saw it.
Because yesterday when you were wasted,
I took care of her, you fucker.
That's because I care about you, buddy.
Easy, Murilo. Don't do this.
I don't give a fuck, you know?
You're better than this, Murilo.
Come and get some.
See this, bro? I did nothing.
Do you know where I come from?
You come here, bro. Let me pass!
- I did nothing.
- No, you don't need it.
- He attacked me, you know?
- We know it. We saw it. Everybody did.
Let's take care of her.
You can't face me. Look...
Stop it, Murilo.
Don't you want to talk?
Come here, then.
Come on. Fuck you!
Murilo...
You wanna talk to everybody.
You're a showoff.
Put yourself in your place.
I have to make you pass out.
Fuck, what a mess. My God.
- Good morning, my brother.
- Good morning, brother.
Did you sleep well? Good?
No, bro. No.
I'm going to throw this out.
Fuck, Luan, bro...
What are you doing to yourself, man?
How cute are they...
What?
How cute are they... Bro, what a day!
- Did you get to sleep?
- Just a little. I took a nap.
Good...
Has Luan come out of his room?
What?
- No...
- No sign of him.
Do you remember everything?
Yes. Nath, I got really jealous.
I pictured Beatriz dancing,
leaning against the wall, twerking...
And Murilão behind her,
thinking he was the man.
It's not like that.
I think that wasn't necessary,
not all over again.
I know...
Do you understand? Is this going to happen
whenever you get jealous?
That was the first time
because of jealousy.
But I'm talking about the future...
No, I'm wrong, Nath. I'm wrong, Nath.
But Beatriz did it... She did it...
But I don't think like that.
In my opinion...
Murilo wanted to talk to you respectfully.
Even I danced with Murilo, I hug Murilo,
and there's nothing going on.
I'm not defending you. You were wrong.
I won't leave you alone.
- It's cool.
- That's it.
Thanks.
Weren't you the one who said,
"Are you going to support me? I am."
That's it. I'm all right.
- Have you already eaten?
- No...
Do you want something?
No, I'm going downstairs.
Can I sit here?
Yeah, bro. Go ahead.
Just let me smoke this cigarette.
No problem.
Tobacco is there. I left half of it there.
You're going to smoke. Yeah.
I wanted to explain what I thought, okay?
I know I'm wrong, okay?
I apologize before starting
this conversation.
No problem...
I'm a little aggressive. People know me.
I got really jealous of Bia.
When I came back from the smoking lounge,
Bia and Nath were dancing
with you behind them.
Man, that could be anybody.
Unfortunately, it was you.
And the way she was dancing, man...
It was fucked up, you know?
Leaning against the wall, twerking
her ass, and it was you, bro, sadly.
For me that's very serious, you know?
But I'm truly sorry, bro.
I didn't even sleep, you know?
Relax...
By the look on my face...
When I took some medicine,
I fell asleep, but I said,
"Man, I have to talk to Murilo first."
First of all...
I know I can trust few people here,
and you're one of them.
I should've never suspected you
and involved you in that situation,
you know? Really.
Relax. We're good.
I apologize from the bottom of my heart.
From the bottom of my heart, bro.
That's I why called you, bro.
Relax... We're here to grow, man.
You know? We're good. Relax...
Bê... Can you go to the Tiger Room
so that we can talk? Five minutes.
Okay, it's quick. I'm just going
to shower. Okay? Just a second.
Damn, it's cold in here.
The way I like it, right.
Can I give you a hug first?
I was going to ask you.
Man, I'm sorry, you know?
I talked to Murilo...
I'm here to apologize to you
for the things I said.
You're a very important woman to me.
You became very important
in a very short time.
I know I want you in my life forever,
no matter what.
I understand your motives. I don't know...
Do you want to know the truth?
What?
The truth is that I love you. Truly.
It's a very pure and real feeling.
Forgive me, my love.
That's all I need.
Yes, sure.
The most important is that
you realized what you had to
and apologized, you know?
You were humble enough to see
that nobody's perfect...
- Can you hug me again?
- Yes.
I miss you.
- Where's Bia?
- Me?
- We have to leave in 15 minutes, okay?
- Oh, my.
- Bye.
- Take care.
Man, the guy is exaggerating, dude.
I believe him...
Bia, what would you do?
I already...
I would listen to him.
I've already been in love at first sight.
Have you been in love at first sight?
- That's called passion.
- It's passion, exactly.
But there's love at first sight.
Me, too.
Did you look at some guy and said,
"Fuck, I love this guy"
- The first day.
- Did it work out?
- We got married.
- You got married?
"But, boy... I'm one of a kind."
- But I'm one of...
- You can't...
No, but, man... What happened?
I saw this and said, "Fuck, already?"
Then I remembered,
"I already felt this way."
Don't you think he said that
because of the mistake he made and...
I think he's analyzing... Sometimes
things happen so we think about the past.
Guys, stop it. She didn't do anything.
She was dancing like this. She was
with her friend like this. Right, Carol?
Like this. Then she said,
"I didn't like the way you were dancing."
"Blah, blah, blah, fuck off."
- She was with her friend.
- But I think Murilo wanted something, too.
He didn't, he was by their side.
And João got him and said,
"I'm going to have to make you pass out."
- Did he pass out, guys?
- João's funny.
He applied a rear naked choke hold.
João didn't love anybody.
- That's true.
- He doesn't do anything.
In a fight, do you break it up
or help with the beating?
Depends on the situation.
Depends a lot on the situation.
If they're friends, I break it up.
Depends on where, depends on what.
I always leave.
Are you the one who does a beat-down?
I'm not hitting anybody.
Look at the size of this little hand.
That's true, that little hand of yours.
If you hit someone, you decapitate them.
Titto, press play... You decapitate...
I leave, I sit in the corner. No.
Don't you get involved?
What if they're fighting over you?
She doesn't get involved at all.
- She's like this...
- Then sorry.
Then sorry, right, baby?
"Easy, boys. Easy."
In the last episode, Titto is going
to have to hook up with Carol.
- Because there's sexual tension.
- I'd let you play video games.
Right.
I don't cook, but I have "assalpão".
I know how to make "assalpão".
- What is "assalpão"?
- To bake bread?
- Isn't it "alçapão"?
- No, it's "assalpão."
What's that?
I cook pasta with cheese...
Then I present it to the person,
"Carol Bandida? No.
Carol Bandida is super talented."
Old school.
The person has
a different opinion about me.
What's this all about?
The person has a different opinion
about me. Then I do, out of the blue...
I turn the stereo on, they'd be playing
video games. I play a romantic song...
What's the romantic song?
- We have to learn from her.
- I'm a strategist.
But would you hook up
with everybody?
No. I would say to the DJ,
"Hi, baby, let me talk to you..."
Do you know what I like to do
when I want to hook up with the DJ?
I dance near his booth.
And every time
he plays a song I really, really like,
I dance looking at him...
Seducing.
And the three second rule.
You look three seconds and look away.
I don't flirt. I say,
"Do you want it or not?"
- What do you say?
-"Do you want it or not?"
I don't flirt either, you know?
I don't seduce, you know?
Bro, what did I get myself into?
I love it. I love it.
I'm addicted to seducing.
I even seduce my friends.
I tried seducing a guy.
He called the cops.
He thought it was a robbery.
Imagine him wearing a cap and a hood...
Once I was seducing some guy
at the airport,
he called the guard,
thought it was a robbery.
Oh, my God.
Everybody was looking like this.
Were you wearing a hood?
Give me the cell phone, asshole.
How is this seduction...
I was looking at his package,
he thought I was looking at his cell
phone. He said, "Take it." I said, "Easy."
Carol, do you do it in a good mood
or in a serious way?
No, I'm serious. I don't...
Yeah, I can see. Really.
But when I want somebody,
I'm very serious. I pretend that
I don't want them.
No, I show the person I want them.
I like discreet men.
- House husband who goes to church.
- Really.
I don't like those men
who dance and stuff.
Do you dance?
More or less.
-"But that's just me."
- But I'm old school.
I'm one of a kind.
So, you can do it, he can't?
But I'm nervous, I have this reputation.
Nobody does it, got it?
Since the beginning,
Luan considers himself special. Then...
- The special one.
- He always does something like this.
When things get serious, he runs away.
You know?
- Oh, my God, I'm shocked.
- He's all talk.
So you're tough. Go.
It wasn't Bia's fault.
Bia did nothing. Murilo did nothing...
Luan, since the beginning, wants to be
a hero, a thug... a wise man, a thug.
He just talks and does nothing.
He's all talk.
I think he was honest with Murilo.
I don't think he's a phony.
It was from the heart.
Bianca, would you accept his apology?
I would, I would.
I would, but I'd say,
"Look, baby, you have to change,
because like this,
we're not going to last..." I don't know.
Bia, she forgave him,
but she's still hurt. I don't think...
Yes, that's it.
You don't accept the apology
and that's it, right?
But she's cool, you know?
Everybody has a counselor friend.
- Let's watch this.
- Press play.
Let's go, girls. Who's going to drive?
Bye, boys. Take care.
Don't bring women over.
- You got it.
- Bye.
Think about me, baby. Think about me...
We're not going to starve.
Yeah.
Girl, let me ask you... Luan's fight.
I had no idea what was going on.
How did it all get started?
Nobody got that either.
Girl, I only remember...
He got jealous of me with Murilo.
- With Murilo.
- But jealous of what?
Of us dancing, according to him,
my ass was on Murilo's face.
And you were next to us,
I saw everything.
But they started to argue on the bus,
and Murilo got angry?
No. Luan got angry,
said he would kick Murilo's ass.
Yeah, Luan...
And Murilo faced it, girl.
Yeah, Luan started to say
a lot of things. "Fucker..."
"Whore..." Pretty bad things.
Yeah, it was horrible, girl.
Did he ask to get back together?
He did,
he wants to be with me and stuff...
I talked to him. He apologized.
I don't know what to believe, you know.
I think that's the right spot,
right? I think it fits.
- Yeah...
- It fits.
Let's invite these guys.
Let's invite these people.
Let's get started.
Good afternoon.
Here's an invitation for you guys.
This party is tonight, at the lagoon,
downtown, at 7:00 p.m.
Hi, boys. Are you all right?
I know you can't take these flyers,
but I wanted to invite you, okay?
It's just... We're surfing, right?
Yeah, it's difficult, it's okay.
Where are they keeping the flyers?
But he could listen to it, at least.
We could drop this over there, real close.
There are cool people. There's cheap food.
It's worth it, watching the sunset.
And touch the ocean.
And touch...
Let's go, 14, just to make sure.
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
- Hello, I'm home...
- Are you Blondie's friend?
No way...
- What's up?
- Hi...
- Welcome.
- Are the girls out?
What is going on, man?
How are you? Nice to meet you.
- Oh, man...
- You can leave...
- I'm going to mess things up.
- No, over there. I won't...
- She's here, bro.
- Are you okay?
- I'm great.
- What's your name?
- Ramon. You?
- I'm Victoria.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you...
- How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
- Are you the famous Vic?
- Blondie said good things about you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Is she Blondie's friend?
- How are you, buddy?
I smell like garlic.
How are you? You're cooking? That's great.
Let's do something here, right?
That's what I needed. Ocean and sunset.
Washed feet...
Washed feet, washed soul.
How are you feeling about Luan?
I don't know, I'm okay, I think.
You are, right?
I forgave him, but...
I need to breathe. I'm hurt, you know?
Yes. You're right...
He can't make things go away
with apologies. Time will do this.
Yeah. Even though I want to be with him,
I love myself more.
Yes... Yes.
Yesterday, I was saying,
"People may forget what you said.
People may forget what you did.
But they'll never forget how you
made them feel." Like, you made them feel.
That's it. Really, you might forget.
Words are forgettable, but...
It's just, I'm really confused.
I don't know what's true...
I don't know who is
and who isn't...
Things got to a point...
They're here...
We're here!
What's up?
- Hey...
- How are you?
I want to know how you did.
We invited a lot of people.
- Yes...
- There's food.
Wonderful.
João is feeling sick.
- Why?
- What happened?
Seems like food poisoning. I don't know.
Baby... I got you a gift, a shirt.
Good night, good morning.
Poor thing, he's calling you.
What? It's the Tiger Room,
he's with Joyce.
What is it?
Is he with someone?
This is Joãozinho.
Girl, I missed you!
Girl...
Blondie's arm.
Girl!
Boss sent an audio message.
- Look, time to work.
- Let's listen to it.
- Is everybody paying attention?
- Everybody.
Hi, what's up?
Today's the big day.
Our party is tonight.
I wanted to thank all of you
for your hard work with promotion.
And the work is not done yet. I need
four of you to help me out at the bar.
Nathalia, Taynara, Luan and Ramon
are going to work.
The rest of you can come over
and have fun.
- Fuck it.
- Motherfucker.
- Do you have those black torn jeans?
- Yeah.
So I'm going to borrow them.
Okay? Gorgeous.
Hit it!
Go for it, bro!
- Yes, man!
- Fuck!
Just in time, man.
Fuck, brother. Fuck, man.
- My brother.
- Man...
Damn.
That's it, man. I fucking love you, man.
How are you, my man?
- Nice to meet you. I'm Murilo.
- I'm Tomás.
Welcome. Fuck!
- Fuck!
- That's it!
- This shit is good.
- What the fuck?
No, man, I did the shit
and it worked, man.
Man...
It worked, man.
- Damn, man...
- Damn!
He's identical. He's very similar.
Is she your girl? Nice to meet you,
I'm Tomás. Everything's great.
Man... Fuck you, dude.
Easy, let me get things straight.
What? What is it...
Fuck, you're identical, man.
Let me see what's going on.
I'm drinking a lot. Let's see.
You're tense...
You guys are drunk...
- Come here.
- Let's go there.
Are you going together?
I'm going with you.
- Blondie, let me introduce you.
- Hi...
- Are you João's brother?
- Yes, I am. I'm Tomás, how are you?
He's talked a lot about you.
- Vic got here today, too.
- How are you?
- Did you get here today?
- She's my best friend.
- How are you?
- Great. Nice to meet you.
- Blondie!
- Go take a picture of you guys. Go.
Let's go, everybody. Come...
Go there...
Yeah...
Let's go, let's go. That's it.
Yes, man. João's happy, did you see it?
That's great.
- They're here.
We're here. You can't, man.
Are you excited?
We're very excited... to start drinking.
I'm drinking for you, girl.
- Yeah, drink for me.
- You come here with us.
What's your name?
- Yeah...
- Renata.
Renata? Tomás... And you?
- Luará.
- Luará?
- That's it...
- I'm still learning.
You toasted, you drink it...
You can use the straw. You could also...
This way, look, let's do it.
Yeah!
Jeez, what a wonderful kiss.
- Cheers to us.
- Thanks for giving me...
Just the beginning.
Take it easy, the best part comes later.
Hey, hey, hey. Wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
I wonder if there's anybody thirsty...
Does anybody want to begin with shots?
Shot! Shot! Shot! Shot!
I want to hear it... Who wants shots?
Do you want a shot?
Pour me one. Who wants shots?
Who wants shots?
Come here, Blondie.
Ouch...
Stick your tongue out.
Guys, guys. Listen up, the work is done.
Fuck! We're coming!
Let's go. Let's get this thing started...
Ramon, Ramon.
Do you know what I wanted to do to you?
I wanted to fuck the hell out of you.
Do you think I didn't want that, too?
Where there's a will, there's a way.
- There's not.
- Why, guys? I'm just saying.
Blondie, kiss him.
Hey...
Go, Blondie...
Kiss him, Blondie. Go, Blondie.
I know that, for you,
that's the only way that works...
I'm going to lick you.
That's beautiful. You pervert.
Hey, guys! Guys! Where are the boys?
Let's go to the afterparty.
Hey, but then...
Tonight you're going to make
both of them smile.
Let me borrow a jacket.
Take a look here... We're here, let's go.
Go...
- Come on, Tomás.
- Go, Tomás.
We're home, guys,
beautiful people... I even fell.
- Here's the toast.
- Look there.
That's crazy, man.
I'm never getting out of here.
Hey, Luanzinho...
Gossip, man...
Let's eat, for Christ's sake.
Hey, boozer.
What is it? I even got shy.
My girl is nervous.
Let me see one thing here...
I even got shy. Are you crazy?
Come, come, come...
Bro...
I know, I trust your potential.
Turn a little bit. Go...
Let me see it. Girl, I can't.
- I'll hold you.
- Did I tell you to stay?
Come.
Jeez, what a shame, Blondie.
You're fucking both of them.
Hold on to that string, girl.
I turned too much.
Go, go.
Do you want to take these heels off?
Do you want to take a shower?
No? So, let's go to bed.
Girl, I'm sad.
- Why are you sad?
- Because I'm wasted.
Do you have PJs or not? Do you have PJs?
Sit over there. Come on.
What are you doing here, DJ?
- What are you doing here?
- Wasn't it the opposite?
You see? I take care.
I don't see it, girl.
You see it... If I see it, I stop you.
I don't see it.
- Hey, Luan.
- Ramon...
Luan, tell your brother to go there, man.
I can't even leave the kitchen because...
This guard is worse than SWAT.
"Against the wall. You punk!"
Against the wall.
I can't even pass, girl.
I'm clean, I'm clean.
Go ahead.
- What's up?
- You're crazy. Why am I wrong?
Don't take the bait...
Because he takes the bait, you don't.
- Why am I wrong?
- I'm fucking cool.
Girl, where are you?
No... I don't know.
But, Bia, go have fun, relax. Easy.
- Bia. Go there...
- What is it?
What's going on? Why did you call me?
I called you to eat.
No, Nath called me, "Bia, go downstairs,
something's going on."
What's going on?
Come here and see.
I'm with Ramon in the kitchen.
I made us two burgers.
Okay. Let's see what's going on.
He's making a burger for you.
- Then why did you call me?
- For you to...
- Why did you say, "Go downstairs"?
- To eat.
Baby, what is it? Look, look.
Stop freaking out, baby.
- Man, I'm out of patience.
- Look. Hey, stop freaking out.
I'm out of patience, man.
Tell Nath to drop
the bullshit 'cause something's wrong.
Baby, there's nothing.
Stop it, look at me.
- You're crazy.
- I'm not crazy.
- If there's one thing I'm not is crazy.
- Then stop it.
I'm going to see what happened.
Talk to her, go.
Do you see what she's doing?
He said,
"Look at the watchdog here, the SWAT."
- Go...
- What?
Why did you tell me
to go downstairs?
Luan didn't do anything.
Girl, I told you. For the second time,
I won't say it a third time,
don't mess with me.
I'm not messing.
Why did you tell me, "Bia, go downstairs.
Bia, go downstairs."? Why then?
Blondie's friend is in the pool.
Then João's brother said, "Go over there."
I held him and said, "Where are you going?
You're going nowhere."
Then I said, "Brother,
you're going to stay with me."
He said, "Girl, I won't do a thing."
He doesn't want to do anything, but...
Girl, you're wrong. Again, you're wrong.
Do you understand my point of view?
Girl, pay attention.
You're drunk, I get it.
But the way you said,
"Bia, go downstairs, go downstairs.
Bia, go downstairs,"
I imagined a lot of bad things.
Okay...
Why didn't you tell me the truth?
"Bia..." Got it? Now I understand.
The way you spoke to me,
I wasn't getting anything.
That is not the way to talk to somebody,
especially me.
Don't you know me? Do you get it?
Because... I mean,
you've created an unnecessary situation.
Oh, no, man...
I thought about a lot of bad things,
the way you spoke to me.
Know how to talk to me. Got it? That's it.
- Oh, no... I'm out of here.
- I'm not arguing with you, girl.
I'm just trying to explain
that you already know me.
You don't have to talk to me that way.
Don't talk to me that way either.
Exactly. But then... You...
The same way you didn't like the way
I spoke to you.
You talk like something's
going on here.
Wait, Bia, shut up.
Bro, I see what's going on.
You'll see... Then you'll see.
I did what a friend should do,
so don't talk shit to me...
You said, "Go downstairs."
What did I do?
You didn't do anything.
You told me.
You said, "Go downstairs, Bia."
Exactly. Not because of him.
Was it because of you?
Then, what?
The chick checked me out,
I didn't see it.
People were annoying Luan,
saying he wanted to hook up
with somebody. He didn't.
I held him... Am I lying?
I held him and said,
"He's not going to hook up with anybody."
"She's with the SWAT.
She's a cop."
"Yes, 'cause Bia is my friend."
Am I lying?
Why didn't you explain
this to me upstairs?
When you went upstairs,
why didn't you tell me?
I'd rather the attitude of a woman,
of a friend.
Stop it, you pointed your finger at me.
You pointed your finger at me.
- Fuck you.
- You don't get to say that.
You don't get to say "fuck you."
You have to learn to talk...
You have to learn to keep your voice down.
To respect people 'cause you're like this.
It's very different.
Nath, to the living room.
Go away! And you have to respect...
Learn to be polite, and talk...
Let's go. Bia...
Fuck it. She has to learn
how to deal with people.
Stop cursing, please.
I'm like this. I respect her,
she has to learn how to respect me.
She doesn't know how to talk to me.
It was awful.
Again, that was unnecessary.
It's the second time that this happened.
There's no third time.
You said... Luan, get out of my way.
Fuck you!
Stop it, Nath... Hey...
Being a friend doesn't involve hooking up
with my man...
Now the shit is going to hit the fan.
There's going to be a fight.
I want to see this fight.
We've been talking about this for a while,
and Bia was suspicious.
Not something only people
outside the house notice.
If she wanted to steal her man...
Girl, but why is she trying
to make all this trouble?
Did you see what she's just done?
That's what I'm talking about.
I understand.
We're not the only people talking about
this thing since the beginning.
Bia and Luan...
Since the beginning we've noticed
something between Luan and Nathalia.
She noticed the same thing?
There's something going on.
If she did that thing downstairs,
she didn't have to go upstairs
to make that other chick
fight Victoria because of Luan.
She'd already sorted it out.
Bro, she likes to cause trouble.
So, I think she didn't intend
that fight between Luan and her.
She explained later,
even Luan agreed with her,
separate Luan from those girls...
That chick was in the pool.
"I'm going to tell my friend
to grab her man
'cause they're hitting on him."
- No, it's not that. I'm...
- It was wrong.
Don't talk to me like that.
Don't point your finger at me.
- Wake up.
- Get your finger out of my face.
What a mess.
- Wake up.
- What a mess.
Everything happened at that afterparty.
Who do you think is right and wrong
in this whole story?
I think Luan, this time,
as hard as it looks, didn't do anything.
But it's Luan's girlfriend
with his friend.
Was Luan in favor of his friend?
He defended his friend.
What?
Girl... No, he held her. He held her.
Who was wrong? It wasn't Bia.
Why would he hold Bia?
Bia was telling what happened.
She was telling the truth, got it?
No, he wasn't by her side. Facts.
Bia is the most sensible, man.
She is.
She's drunk, the mess begins.
"Not now. Later. I'm already drunk."
Did you see who was holding Bia?
It was Ramon.
Ramon.
Ramon held Bia.
The one who held Nathalia was Luan.
Swinging.
Girl, I didn't see any of that.
The way I saw it,
"I'm going to hold this chick.
She's more drunk than Bia."
I'm going to tell you this...
- And Bia said a lot of things...
- I...
Bia...
Give it up to Victoria, who barely said
a thing and got a lot of attention.
It's my fancy applause.
She was expecting
to be defended by Luan.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Welcome to our humble home.
Is this your boyfriend?
My man. Yes, he's a very good person.
You have to meet him.
Fuck you, man.
You know? Get out, bro.
Come on, easy.
I want to watch it now.
There are a lot of men...
That wasn't a fight. That was messy.
I'm afraid of Murilo
when he gets angry...
Me, too... I think it's beautiful.
I was sure this was going
to cause trouble.
I was sure, man.
Do you know the good thing
about group fighting?
- The boys from the house stick together.
- Of course.
The girls from the house
always stick together.
It's a mess...
I can say bad things about my friend,
you can't.
Everybody sticks together.
- Let's go... What now?
- What a mess.
How are we going to spend the whole week?
Guys, I won't be able to sleep.
To watch this mess.
- Guys.
- Guys...
I love that I came here to watch this with
you, but I have to pick up my daughters.
Who's doing the dishes?
I'm not, honey.
I don't have to do it.
Imagine her showing up
like this at day care...