WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
THE REVIEW
- The last episode, guys.
- The last episode.
It's not the last.
I'm sorry, success...
Amazon, invite me for the next season.
I'm in mourning.
Remember that there was a mess
in the last episode.
It almost ended in a rumble.
Yes, gossip.
In short, Ramon broke up with Nath again.
That's something new.
Because he found out she gave someone
a peck in the afterparty.
Gossip, right?
It's time, boys.
We're very anxious.
It's the last episode.
Has everyone memorized this yet?
Ramon!
I can't wave my hand, girl.
I'm going to stay here.
Cool, calm and collected.
I loved the earrings.
Has anybody kept score on the sex deals?
- João is the winner. Certainly.
- João.
I've grown to like them.
I want to be their friend.
Did you like the drink?
It's wonderful.
It was made with love and affection.
- Yeah? Really?
- I swear.
Holy shit!
I wish I were that girl.
I'd answer João...
What would you say, Pabllo?
Come and ask about my drink.
Pabllo, did you like this drink?
It's your job to do it, baby.
- Do it tomorrow?
- Tomorrow, brother, no...
There's nothing right now.
Man, tomorrow we're having
a boat party here.
There's going to be a lot of babes,
just the local girls.
It's going to be great. Wanna go?
Yeah, man.
There's a party invitation going on, look.
A boat party.
I'm scared.
That's good, right?
They were invited to a boat party,
but he doesn't have a boat.
We were invited and we're coming.
- Are you nuts...
- What boat?
They'll go in someone else's boat?
Because they don't have one.
It's about having a friend who has a boat.
Yeah...
- It's good being friends with a boat guy.
- Having a boat is a nightmare.
I wouldn't want that.
After my shift, I want to talk to you...
You've always said good things about me.
After you're done, we'll talk...
He's going to ask.
People are working, may I?
Never put off anything you can do now.
Let's say it right now.
Here's the thing.
I was invited with all the guys
to take a boat ride tomorrow.
There's going to be a party.
There's going to be a lot of boats...
A ride on the high seas with the gang.
But we don't have a boat, you do.
I can't believe he's doing this.
And I'd like to propose some way
of paying you back, working for you...
The nerve of you guys!
- For us to enjoy our...
- You want my boat again?
You can come as well.
"You can come." The nerve.
I have an appointment
at the end of the day,
- not the whole day.
- Okay. Right.
- I'll need it by evening.
- Deal.
- Cool?
- Cool.
- We'll use it in the morning.
- You're the best boss in the world.
Ramon, I'm not lending it to you,
but to João.
Oh, fuck!
In your face, well done.
He must've watched
that episode
where they call him a son of a bitch.
One for all, all for one!
People arrived.
That's the guy
who was in the house yesterday.
Last week, in that mess.
They're the guys who were in that mess.
What is Nathalia doing? She's loving it.
She's laughing.
Look at Nathalia's face. Again, Luan.
Hang in there, Luan.
Guys, did you see Nathalia's face?
Nathalia? No.
- In a flash...
- Yeah.
Nathalia is dying to cause trouble.
That girl really is a troublemaker.
She knows there will be trouble.
I think, look...
- Nathalia celebrated, did you feel it?
- Yes.
- Very much.
- The fire in her eyes.
...there was going to be a lot of trouble.
Look, fight in the house, okay.
The house isn't mine, I'll leave.
But fighting at the party is so wrong.
It's make it or break it, honey.
Do you want a kiss?
It's Blondie with her boyfriend.
-"I take care of you."
- She wants to have sex again.
No. She wants to have sex now.
She's right, they cockblocked her.
It's true.
Thais rules the world,
and we're her servants.
Nath kissed him...
What is this guy doing here?
I asked him to dance.
The box is yours and mine, too.
She put the guy inside the box, brother.
It was Nath who did the inviting.
Didn't I say this girl is a troublemaker?
He asked, "What is this guy doing here?"
In theory, the box was everybody's.
She said, "I invited him.
The box is mine too."
She put that guy from the mess
in the box next to the guy who...
But did she kiss him?
Guys, wait, wait, wait.
Those guys put a lot of women
in the box at all parties.
But no one had fought with...
John, you, too, go fuck yourself.
- Fuck you.
- Who's going today?
After all, she just wanted to be with him.
The one in the black shirt
and checkered scarf
threatened him.
He said, "Do you have a problem?
"Do you wanna face me?"
Nath is hooking up with the guy
wearing white shirt.
I want Nath to fuck off.
- Stop it.
- Stop the bullshit, Felipe.
That girl is a jerk.
Stop it now.
I'm mad at that girl, for real.
- Let me tell you something...
- Get a grip. Childish.
#CHILDISH
Childish.
You're hooking up with some guy.
His friend was looking for trouble.
You can't be with him.
Don't curse because it's wrong.
But she broke up with Ramon?
But that's not the problem.
If she broke up or not...
I don't like Boca Rosa,
because I don't like her.
She wears pink lipstick...
I prefer red, there you go.
Yesterday I almost fought with her,
I called her names.
Are you gonna put her beside me?
On purpose?
There's going to be trouble.
You have to avoid that. It's common sense.
- It's common sense.
- Common sense.
- Is Nathalia being an asshole?
- Everyone agrees?
Everyone but John Drops.
He's the one who likes to complain here.
Man, she could even hook up with the guy.
She could do it outside the box, you know?
We talked too much. Press play.
God...
Is this the afterparty?
I think it is.
Really? Look...
- The same guys again?
- Two...
That's not possible.
Look, that dude came in.
The one Nath is hooking up with is cool.
This one is the asshole.
...me and Bia.
Nathalia!
Everything is a mess.
Me and you.
Let's play. Nath, pay them back.
We have to make him lose.
It was my turn, right?
Hey...
High five, fuck.
I'm here to work hard.
Don't smell my neck.
But the guy she was kissing at the party
went with her, now she's with...
There he is, look.
She's flirting with Ramon.
Jeez, look at his face...
- I'll remain quiet.
- Me, too.
Look at him, he's eating like a lord.
Stop it, guys.
Almost hanging himself with the scarf.
Did Nath bring that guy
she hooked up with?
She's now flirting with Ramon,
and the boy is eating peanuts.
That's it.
Just watching.
Man, she does that...
Have you noticed
she does that to every boy?
Has this ever happened to you?
- Never.
- Abandoned.
I'm going to get it for you.
Man, you're wasted.
- I'm going to go.
- Already?
- I'm beat.
- Okay...
- No.
- Nath, I'm leaving.
Bia, I'm winning.
I came to say goodbye.
Take care.
Good to see you.
- That's true.
- Write down my number.
Oh, no. Are you kidding?
- What a prince.
- Jeez, I swear.
- He's like a businessman.
- He looks like he's bad in bed.
Stop it.
What?
"Businessman" is allowed?
And bad in bed is not?
You say men stick together, right?
I see now.
I wonder if she never really had
feelings for Ramon.
What? Do you doubt, bro?
- She was just horny.
- Are you kidding?
Yeah, man. She even said that to him...
- I won't forget that thing.
- What a whore.
"I regret I met you.
You're a piece of shit, a brat.
"The man who acts like a man..."
I think...
She didn't mean it, but it was hurtful.
Could've hurt him a lot, man.
The feeling she has for him is possession.
She thinks she owns him.
She thinks she owns everybody.
Literally, she doesn't make up her mind.
She says one thing and does another.
Bianca, it was worse saying those things
- she didn't mean.
- Yeah...
I think so, too.
She wanted to hurt him on purpose.
Girl, you were a total fucking loser.
- She was, yesterday.
- What? Why?
You have to make up your mind.
You brought the dude
to be with you, and abandoned him.
He left.
- You abandoned him to stalk Ramon.
- You were ignoring him.
I was playing.
No. You were stalking Ramon.
You abandoned him to chase another one.
And you said, "I don't want anything."
Come on.
Fuck you. I won't say anything anymore.
Don't ask for my opinion anymore.
Hey, Thais is right, you know?
- Fuck no!
- She is.
He didn't go after her, man.
She even hooked up with another guy.
She hooked up with him there.
She brought the guy to her house.
She hooked up with that guy,
took him home
and hooked up with Ramon.
He didn't...
Ramon saw her with the blond guy.
That's what I'm talking about.
- No, it's time...
- Fuck it.
It's time Nathalia and Ramon...
Ramon doesn't do what she does.
- It's time...
- Yeah.
Let's see what happens.
It's time Nathalia made up her mind.
I think there's going to be a fight.
Did I chase her tonight?
I'm talking about the other parties.
He didn't even care
about her tonight.
- Not tonight.
- She was after him.
- Me?
- Yes, girl.
- You were after him here, girl.
Your boy left
because you said you were after him.
Jeez, Nathalia was an asshole.
It's like what he said...
I've lost track of how many times
those guys said she was an asshole.
She doesn't listen to anyone.
When she drinks, she gets worse.
- Man, if she dated Luan...
- Jeez.
...they would fight all the time
because she would make things up.
I feel like picking this lamp up
and throwing it in your face.
But I was acting unconsciously.
She said "Unconsciously."
- Look.
- Girl, stop blaming the booze, you know?
She's that kind of girl, right?
I'm fucked up if I blame the booze
for everything I did wrong.
She's been like this
since episode one. Until now.
This is not booze.
Booze is temporary.
That's one of the reasons I don't drink.
I don't want to feel guilty.
I don't have to blame anyone.
Damn.
That's awesome.
I miss riding a boat.
Guys, I'm picturing
my hood guys over there.
Man, we would get wild.
I've never been to a boat party.
- Stop lying.
- I haven't.
- You have a boat in Niterói.
- Stop fooling around.
- Don't you have a boat?
- I'm going to be kidnapped.
Tell the truth.
Who has ever gone to a party on a boat?
I went a few times.
- How long is your boat?
- Guys, no.
It's in the end.
The last...
It's almost over. Ramon is sad. One day.
One day...
Guys, what an awesome party.
If we'll miss this,
- let alone those guys...
- He's going to cry.
Carol, will you miss this?
- Obviously.
- Man...
Of course I'm going to miss you guys.
I'll miss you guys, too.
You dreamed about my hair?
I dreamed my cousin had hair like hers.
If we'll miss it, imagine those guys.
Imagine them...
It's a fucking awesome vibe.
Wonderful. By the way...
Sleeping and waking up together, you know?
Waking up naked... I'm kidding.
What will you miss the most?
What party will you miss the most, Pabllo?
I think the first one, when they arrived,
they were all pumped up.
There was trouble right away.
At the Green Valley.
Yes, the first party, right?
I think it's the best.
What about you, Mariano?
The first one, too.
That guy came in all pumped up.
All gassed up.
The house was smelling fresh.
Smelling like what?
Fresh.
I'm not excited for this party,
but for the last party later on.
There's going to be trouble.
Where's your... Headset?
Headset?
I'm asking, please.
They should have some funk music there.
Yes, there could be some.
- Ramon is with another girl, look.
- Guys, Nathalia is a DJ groupie, you see?
No, groupie...
- Nathalia is with the DJ again.
- She's disturbed.
I would love seeing her hook up
with everyone if she had dumped Ramon.
I'm starting to miss this...
Guys, that DJ is not my type.
- I would hook up with him.
- Girl, be my guest.
Again?
Who is it?
- Who's with Ramon?
- Some girl.
Guys, João is the most iconic person
in the whole world.
Some beautiful girl, I must say.
Hook up with her!
She's right.
Nathalia hooked up with the DJ,
and Ramon hooked up with the sailor?
Guys, if I'm kissing someone
and people come in shouting,
I'd say, "Are you nuts?"
Man, they're in a very good vibe,
right? Everybody.
Take her home, I'll pick her up there.
I'm waiting.
He wants the boat back. He's right...
There's a party at the house.
Fuck, a party at their house.
Oh, my God!
- Yeah, right.
- Everyone's there.
- Hey, isn't that...
Yes, it's Mauro.
- It's Mauro.
- Everyone is there.
Mauro, Tomás, everyone.
Is Victoria there, too?
- Victoria, Amanda.
- Everyone.
Yeah, it's the season finale.
- Everyone they knew is there.
- A reunion.
That's cool.
It's really the last party.
Everyone who was part of it is there.
Enjoy it. This is the party.
It's for you, guys.
Let's go!
Fuck! You're crazy!
Fuck, bro.
You're crazy, bro! Come on, fuck you!
We thought it was a fight,
but they were celebrating.
Pabllo, you said it.
You're awesome, Pabllo.
Pabllo said she'd roll on the grass.
Pabllo is not Pabllo for nothing.
- A happy friend rolls on the grass.
- Fuck, look.
- We thought it was trouble.
- I thought asses were being kicked.
Pabllo and Carol are the best.
Look, it's Mauro...
Oh, my God.
Mauro was very respectful.
He kissed her forehead.
He didn't want a kiss.
- It's Vic!
It's Vic!
Vic is an icon. I want to go out with Vic.
Vic is going to get me a lot of boys.
Murilo is still wearing
his patterned shirts.
Since the first day,
he's just been wearing them.
Such a loving atmosphere going on there.
How can there be a fight?
I don't think...
Because of booze.
There's a fight in the teaser.
No, that roll was a love roll.
It was on the grass.
There was a fight.
Remember the girl...
That fight at the club...
Let me say something.
Guys... They will fight.
Do you think there's not going
to be a fight in the last episode?
There's somebody you met in day one.
- I want to tell you she's here.
- I can't believe it!
Do you know who she is?
Joyce is over there!
- Who?
- Joyce, João.
Joyce. João dressed the broom like her.
- You became a caricature.
- I'm not that crazy.
- And it's identical.
- Really?
Wow, what a beautiful girl...
I didn't know...
I can't believe it!
That's so cute!
"What a beautiful girl. I didn't know."
He now realized she's pretty.
He's going to fall down with that chick.
May I have one minute of your attention,
to the blue curtain,
to welcome tonight's great number...
Pabllo Vittar and MC Carol!
Then Carol shows up and says,
"I'm a bandit."
- Dennis!
- DJ Dennis!
Icon!
- Damn, man, that's cool!
- Oh, no...
It's my heart
Now we're talking.
The theme song.
- I miss funk music, guys. Can I dance?
- What?
What?
My friend, Cantini. Go.
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
This song is by Dennis.
Waking up naked with you by my side
I hope our love...
I ship you two.
Do the little square dance move.
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with you by my side
I hope our love never turns into routine
- Guys...
- I love those two.
Do you know when a show
is ending and you,
"I can't believe
my favorite show is ending?"
Yes, that's it. I'm like this.
- Damn, man.
- Man, this is so cool, huh?
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Waking up naked with Carol by my side
And João...
It's not me.
I'm just paying homage.
Carol doesn't bang women.
Thanks, Dennis!
- Wonderful.
- Very good.
Look at this festival finale.
Guys, look at the fireworks, look!
Fuck, Amazon.
Amazon nailed it on the fireworks.
She's happy with the fireworks.
I love fireworks.
Look, what they're...
- Bia! You're perfect, Bia.
- First time.
Bia is my spirit animal.
- Bia is confident.
- Bia is fucking awesome.
- Blondie!
- Look at Blondie, look.
Blondie! Blondie!
Blondie.
- After all, did she have sex?
- Go, Nathalia!
God bless that shirtless guy.
- Drops...
- I remember him.
I cried on my reality show
because of the food.
- Ramon!
- Ramonzera.
- Ramonzera is a nice guy, too.
- Ramon!
- Ramon. My crush.
- I love Ramon.
Ramon is a nice guy.
Tay... Beautiful Tay.
There are a lot of beautiful people.
They're showing each one's moments.
His eyes welled up with tears.
Fuck. Oh, my God.
Now it's Murilo.
Murilo! Murilo!
- I choose Murilo, no doubt.
- Murilo, too.
I'll miss João, let me tell you.
- Guys.
- João!
João!
He has the most beautiful ass.
I want to be friends with João.
João, please, add me.
I don't know where but do it.
Luan.
- I like Luan.
- Luan...
Luan screwed up,
but he was a nice guy after that.
He made mistakes, then made it right.
Who doesn't make mistakes?
Exactly. You said it all.
All right.
Stop it.
I think we deserve to toast, too.
Let's do this!
Let's have a toast. Wait.
Titto, come here.
Oops. Let's do it.
Help him, Titto. The house is yours.
Every day...
Come here, everybody.
Waking up naked
Get the glasses. I open it.
I get the glasses.
- Do we have to get up?
- Champagne.
Take it, here. Everyone gets a glass.
- Honeymoon.
- That's right.
We'll pretend we're in Floripa.
- Young lady.
- Can I open it?
- Wait. Are we going to toast?
- Look.
One, two, three and...
- Floripa!
- Open it.
I feel like I'm on a show.
Waking up naked
- Making love every day
- With Titto by my side
Come on, Carol!
You deceive me.
Waking up at 11:00 a.m.
Waking up naked with Carol by my side
Where's yours, Titto?
Mine is Red Bull, I don't drink.
No, just pretend it.
- Go.
- You are shameless.
Pretend.
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- I want it. Come.
- Toast!
Cheers!
Let's take the picture. Let's do the pose.
Let's do the pose.
- I'm like João.
- Blondie.
- I'm like Blondie.
- You really are.
- I'm like Tay.
- I'm like Bia.
Yes.
- Let's start drinking.
- Such a whore.
Fill my glass.
Titto doesn't know how to serve.
This could be better.
But it's what we've got now...
Oh, my God, at the end?
- Everything was fine, he toasted...
- They just clicked.
He didn't do it in the end.
What a gorgeous brunette.
There's more where that came from.
Luan kissed that girl.
It's not Beatriz.
"Now I'm going to enjoy it."
- You thought it was over.
- Did you hear?
- No way he did it.
- Fuck.
Guys, this is madness.
He realized Beatriz saw that, look.
Hey, no...
Hey, no jealousy, my baby.
No jealousy, okay?
Enough... Tonight I'm going to go wild.
Jeez.
What did I tell you, guys?
There's going to be trouble.
They probably ran out of booze.
I can't believe
he made that mistake at the end.
- I see trouble.
- Is it him over there?
Is it him?
- That's Luan.
- Murilo and Tay.
- It's Luan.
- That's Luan.
- Murilo and Luan.
- On the floor?
- It's Luan.
- Is it Luan?
- What about Tay?
- No!
He kissed two people.
Fuck it.
I'm going to beat him tonight.
Me, too. This is mean.
God.
He said, "I don't want it anymore.
This is going to end..."
Luan said he didn't want it anymore?
- No.
- Luan?
- He's there.
- Luan said that to her?
No, he didn't.
He hooked up with one more.
He's acting crazy.
He went around kissing everybody...
- Yes.
- He said nothing.
But they didn't decide
what they were feeling.
He said he loved Bia. Beatriz.
In the red room.
- Look!
- But he betrayed her.
Ouch. She came at him. She's upset.
Easy, easy.
Easy, girl.
I want to talk to this chick.
I want to talk to this girl now.
- Easy, easy.
- This girl.
Come with me, young lady.
Wait, wait, wait.
If this chick goes inside,
I'm going to kill her!
Don't go, don't get mad... She's there.
Can I go in with them?
Better not. There will be trouble.
I'm going to take both of them.
Murilo, they don't even know
what happened.
Work things out with the girls.
Fuck you!
- Once again, you're a clown!
- Easy... Stop it...
Piece of shit!
Easy, girl.
Nath...
How can there be
such bad people in the world, man?
- You're good.
- How?
- You're here to teach a lot of people.
- I can't take it.
This is you.
I can't take it, man. God, help me.
What's that? Is that because of booze?
No, that's fucked up.
- It's Luan causing trouble.
- That's fucked up.
There's booze...
One thing is seeing him dancing.
...he hooked up with another girl,
when you see him doing it.
You know, he could've...
He could've talked to her.
No. Baby, I'd impersonate Kimberly
and I'd end the whole party.
Yeah, man...
I'd get Dennis DJ's mic...
He could be a little more smart...
Not smart. He's being smart.
He's not smart. He's a jerk.
He could've been a person of character.
- Yeah.
- Just a little bit.
He could've told her on the previous day,
"I don't want you anymore."
He wasn't a person of character
at any moment.
Because the whole time...
He was with Bia the whole time
and hooked up with other girls at parties.
He didn't tell her
and pretended they were a couple.
Right in front of her.
Here's the thing.
I don't judge Nathalia.
He wanted somebody to have sex
with in the house,
and, on the last day,
"I'm going to stop caring and fuck it."
He should've told her.
- I don't judge Nathalia.
- No, but also...
I wouldn't say those girls were sluts.
- Never.
- Yeah.
That is something else.
Nothing to do with that.
If they step inside,
I'm kicking their asses.
Warn them.
What's the deal, Murilo?
They won't come in.
No woman will step foot in the house.
If they come in,
I'll grab them by their hair.
- Shut up, Taynara!
- You sexist!
Shut up!
You sexist!
You're going to pay.
Hey, bro. The two of them
have nothing to do with this.
Fuck it, they'll never get in here.
If you bring them over, I'll beat them!
What a crazy woman.
Chill. She's not crazy.
- Respect her.
- Easy, easy.
If you guys don't control yourselves,
I will. No more sexists, not anymore.
The whole season,
I put up with him insulting women.
- Not today!
- Tay.
- But listen...
"You'd better not bring them over.
Things are ugly over there."
It's about the guy's character.
He doesn't have one!
Everybody's noticed...
- Easy, man.
- It's okay.
I'm going to pull their hair out
if they come in.
- Manu has nothing to do with it.
- Tell them to leave.
She knows the situation.
If she comes to my house...
If she comes to my house,
I'm pulling her hair out.
- Is Keila allowed?
- Sure.
- Keila is allowed.
- Okay.
So-and-so says, "Is Bianca allowed?
She's the only one
I want to have sex with..."
- Bro...
-"Is Bianca allowed?"
João is the best.
Again, he...
Again, he's helping her, look.
She blacked out because of booze.
Murilo is a gentleman.
Murilo deserves a medal
for being so cute, God.
- Who's helping him? Is it Tay?
- I think it's Taynara.
Tay and Murilo are my dream couple.
I wish we were a throuple. Maybe.
Jeez...
Jeez, I was such a fool.
How did I make this kind of mistake?
Don't do this to yourself.
He's two-faced, girl. He's two-faced.
But how did I do this?
Girl, you didn't know. You took a while.
You took a while.
Well...
It's normal.
Any person could experience this.
Part of him is a psychopath
and pretends to be someone he is not.
He is crazy.
That's it.
Any person could be like you are now.
We just found out who he is now,
when there was alcohol involved.
Then we saw who he is.
The nobleness of character...
He had to be a man and say,
"I don't want you anymore.
Today's the last day. I'm going wild.
Don't be upset because we're not dating."
- He didn't...
- Let me finish.
The only thing missing was a real talk.
He didn't undervalue the woman.
He was just a jerk. That's all he's done.
Because both of them
did this the whole series.
She did, she brought someone over,
she did something...
- Her?
- No, no.
I didn't see her kissing anybody.
- She just danced.
- No...
She was the quieter one.
I am talking about the house itself.
The same way
the guys kicked those dudes...
She's right about calling him a sexist?
Okay, he's a sexist.
"And if those chicks come,
I'm pulling their hair out."
If he's a sexist, then she's a feminist
because you're defending
the women here, right?
One woman beats another one
who has nothing to do with it?
- No.
- That's wrong.
You're contradicting yourself, man.
Fuck. Did you get it?
- She was wrong in saying that.
- Right, Bia?
And those girls would be wrong
if they got in the house,
pretending nothing...
It's not because of that.
Her calling him sexist,
if she's a feminist,
I don't know if she is,
but if she is, feminism asks
for gender equality.
Just like Luan got all the girls
at the party,
as well as those girls
in front of her now,
she'll feel hurt
for not hooking up at all.
She's with Luan.
Luan broke down on her,
he said he loved her
and they were fine again,
so that he messes up on the last day?
He's totally wrong.
I told you, he's got some nerve.
He's got some nerve.
No. Things got out of control,
and there were a lot of wrong people.
No one can start... defending. They can't.
No, that's for sure.
That's not possible, do you know why?
That's why I thought
it was very annoying...
You can't judge.
Don't say that.
Why can't I say this?
Because I'm not judging either.
- That's my opinion.
- No, buddy.
I have the right to think...
- I do.
You said she was defending and whatnot...
Wasn't she defending a cause?
In the heat of the moment, she wasn't.
She talked about sexism.
And then she acted like a sexist.
She said she was going to hit those girls.
You can't be a hypocrite.
I'm going to say what I think, I'm sorry.
Felipe, take it easy, look at me.
Felipe, do you think
I'm being a hypocrite?
Telling me I can't speak
is such hypocrisy.
No.
- That's my opinion.
- No...
Do you think I'm being a hypocrite?
At any moment? Here?
Your opinion is perfect.
That's what I said.
We won't defend causes 'cause...
...it's not about sexism or feminism...
He's just got some nerve.
That's it.
When you say,
"I don't know..." You're judging, too.
Who am I judging?
"She does it and whatnot..."
You can't judge.
I'm just saying she can't
defend causes like that.
- No one is doing that.
- Where's everyone...
She is, fuck.
Didn't you see her defending a cause?
If you're against...
I'm not against a cause.
you're defending a cause.
Pabllo, the drink. Is it over?
We must be impartial.
The house is destroyed.
It looks like a hurricane did that.
It looks like my house.
Looks like it's been like that
for two days.
- High five!
- Jesus.
Fuck.
Looks like my house on a normal day.
An abandoned banjo...
Looks like my bedroom...
It's like that.
Jeez, man.
Guys...
My pool, for now
- My bedroom.
- Look at that, bro.
It's a total mess, man.
It's like that.
That's the reality.
- Fuck...
- Cell phone.
What a mess, man.
Blondie is alone, as usual, poor girl.
Jeez, poor girl, man.
She's sleeping.
I wouldn't want to pack,
waking up with such a hangover.
Jeez, give me two days.
Who's calling?
Girl, they have to go, baby.
You feel me?
Hey, guys.
I'm going to need help this summer.
Who wants to come back?
What?
Did you see João's face?
He didn't even know...
Then he woke up. He didn't even know...
"Who wants to come back?"
There's going to be a recap.
They're going to stay at that house again.
No, I hope some people don't go.
There were some people there who...
I think this was genius.
"Who wants to come back?"
Invite me...
In case there's Season 2, Amazon,
take us to a party one day? Just one day.
Thanks, guys.
Bye, I'm going to take food...
I'm going to pretend I'm an alcoholic.
I want a chocolate milk combo!
I want to check...
Help me out, Carol.