WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
THE REVIEW
We've been invited by Amazon Prime Video
to watch the first episode of the new
series Wild and Free: Florianópolis.
All we know is they're not actors
and there's no script.
It's all for real.
We'll have to check that out.
- Hi, Ramon.
- Dancing every day, right?
Hi, Ramon, how are you? What's up, Tay?
- Is that your man?
- João is my crush.
That one? I like João, too.
- I like Thais.
- Looks like a blogger.
Hi, Luan, how are you?
I felt different about Luan.
I don't know what it is.
They call it "axé."
We all had this dream
of hitting the road with friends...
I've never done it.
You've never done it? Too bad, honey.
No, I'm kidding,
I've never done it either.
A mad trip, baby.
Spoke with authority.
Yep, we pretend...
Just pretending to be happy.
Oh, my God! Look at that house.
They rented Daddy's house.
Of course we'd get into that.
That's crazy.
Yeah, my home is an apartment.
It's a one-bedroom apartment.
Where's Amazon?
- Guys, it's huge.
- My heart is beating faster.
- Thick calf, I think it's a boy.
- Oh, girl.
He has a vintage suitcase.
From the 18th century.
...made of cobblestone.
That would break the wheels.
Where did you find it?
- This is Jaguar João.
- Good. This is a jaguar.
This is Tarzan.
I don't like tattoos.
This tattoo was a mistake.
I want a reality...
The guy wants
to pretend he's the owner, right?
Yeah... He thought he's the owner.
Honey...
They're not models, actors, they're not...
They were thrown in there...
They must be from Floripa,
born beautiful...
- Crazy...
- Floripa is my dream.
They're already friends. Right?
They know each other from parties.
They know each other.
What a gang!
I think it's going to be three men.
Brother, I saw you earlier.
That girl was really wild.
His oblique muscles, guys.
Zoom in on that oblique.
The first two minutes of the series...
Tarzan already banged Jane.
It was a peck.
I think they hooked up before.
"How are you?"
Out of the blue... French kiss.
I would come in like that.
Oh, sis.
You say hi with a French kiss?
I think the personality...
When someone
has that kind of personality...
Sure.
- No, that's despair.
- I just go and kiss.
You gotta be like that, you know?
If you like someone, why not?
If you like them...
I don't play games either.
How do you know
there's reciprocity?
You just say,
"Hey, how are you? How's it..."
If she jumped on his lap...
They knew each other...
I guess they hooked up before.
Sometimes, just a look...
Tay is my favorite.
I loved the way she came in...
I think you have a lot
in common, you know?
Yes, I can relate.
I got something to say.
I think she's direct.
I like direct people.
You're such a Don Juan!
We have a couple in the house.
The first couple!
Look at Luan. Look at his arm!
Yummy, Luan. Stick it all!
Here comes Luan.
- But João is better.
- I loved it, loved it.
I imagine João asking my family's
permission to go on a date with me.
I was going to say that.
That house is insane, man.
That house is fucking awesome.
It's very modern,
like a Toyota Land Cruiser bumper.
- What?
- Like a Toyota Land Cruiser bumper.
Tay arrived hooking up with a guy.
It's got to be like that.
I was going to say...
You'd cry on day one?
I'm very...
Were you going to cry on the first day?
If you drank, you would.
I was going to say, "I'm going to fuck."
I'm very easy.
I would sleep. I love sleeping.
Did you hear that? She'd arrive
and do you know what she'd do?
She'd sleep.
I would go to sleep.
I'd choose a room and...
- Oh, girl.
- Holy cow.
Everyone would say, "Carol, we're on
a reality show, let's go out and drink."
"No, just give me a chocolate milk."
Chocolate milk and a warm bed.
She's on a drip,
and the chocolate milk is falling.
Blondie! Open your mouth.
They started to drink. Chug.
I'm going to chug it.
Hey, that thing's just started,
you'll see.
Guys, I'm going to take
a sip from my drink, I'm hot now.
Let's go to a club tonight?
I have good...
Good?
...and excellent news.
You love me?
I got us a VIP box at the Green Valley.
I like his accent, it's like mine.
I love accents.
I didn't know Mariano
was in that show, guys.
"I got us a box at the Green Valley."
Who's the one
that gets a box for the others?
At the Green Valley.
I'm the one who asks.
She's got a lot of connections.
If Bianca and Carol joined forces,
it will be the box and the whole party.
Carol gets the box.
Carol, you're the best, huh, girl?
I get the drinks.
I get the combos.
Carol, the bus and I, behind.
The bus and I go in.
He took the shirt off! Take the pants off.
I think he's a show-off.
What does it mean?
He likes to attract attention...
When you want to get attention...
He wants to be noticed.
That girl is over there...
this guy takes his shirt off. Big mistake.
I'm not even listening...
Putting the...
Oh, my God, that's all right.
First little kiss in the house.
It's red lipstick!
It shouldn't be
a movie kiss, you know?
I think we should do the same.
So go to the party.
Oh, my God!
- Murilo!
- Crap, little smooch?
I won't judge. I did that recently.
- I'm not going to judge.
- I enjoyed that at Rock in Rio.
If she was wearing Boca Rosa lipstick,
it wouldn't come off.
Lasts 24 hours and it's waterproof.
Thanks, brother.
Such a nice kiss!
There's going to be more.
What did she say?
"There's going to be more later."
That guy is a show-off...
I didn't like him. Neither did you.
Take the guys to the shore...
No... Listen to Felipe Titto.
I'd hook up
with Nathalia and João if I was there.
- Would you hook up with Nathalia?
- I would.
- Do you hook up with anyone?
- Aren't you gay?
- Everyone is free. It's Floripa, no rules.
- Do you hook up with women?
Are you flexible?
Freedom.
- Yes. It's a vast menu.
- Now, tell me something.
That girl is always chewing.
Yes... Exactly.
Will they wear makeup full-time?
He who doesn't go
on a diet eats everything.
She's free. There's no diet.
I think so, too.
There's a dressing table
for them to talk, to put on makeup.
- Holy crap, your jacket!
- I love it.
- Pour it. Go. Put it all in.
- Pour it all!
I got a surprise for you guys.
Just stay here, real quick.
Give me one sec.
Come on, bus!
- It's here. Oh, boy!
- The bus.
The bus party.
The bus and us.
To go to the party.
Looks like your mother is taking you
to your first party.
Yep, exactly, man. That's not good.
Have you partied in a bus?
I haven't even partied on foot.
Man, it's fucking awesome.
But that is a room.
You can walk and dance in the bus.
I wouldn't fight
anyone in a party like that.
That beach over there
is like the one in São Gonçalo.
What a mess.
They're all hooking up with each other.
When they start bringing women
and men to that house, it's going to be...
How is this going to work out?
Bringing men and women over there.
They hooked up with each other a lot...
...those girls hook up
with other boys...
...with other girls?
That was a crazy party!
- Very good.
- Is it good?
It's salmon. Rich people thing.
Have some.
João's hooking up with Thais.
Get out of there! I hate you!
Those guys brought a cake
to a birthday party.
That's right.
That's it, now everyone
will start kissing. Let's kiss now.
What?
Look, he hooked up with an unknown girl.
Now he's calling another girl.
What about that girl there?
- Look at her face.
- That's not necessary.
Didn't you say,
no strings attached?
Stop it right there.
We have the first betrayal.
He hooked up with one girl, then hooked up
with another in front of her?
Smoked a Derby.
I have a problem with that.
She even started smoking after that.
She'll begin to listen to modão and cry.
I don't like it like that.
She'll listen to "Boate Azul".
If you want to be
part of a reality show...
...everyone will hook up with others.
- Hook up with boys, too.
- Get out of there, João!
They got pissed, look.
She's furious, opening her soda there.
Some boys don't come to talk to us.
We have to approach them sometimes.
João? Is it João?
João is fast.
João knows it all.
If I were one of the girls,
I'd start hooking up
with other girls and other boys.
- Now it's good.
- Look over there.
She's already crying! Crying on day one?
- She can't do that.
- I told you. Am I lying?
- Is she really crying?
- Everyone is free.
- That's the booze.
- Kiss, girls. Kiss.
- It's booze.
- That's the booze.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
- That's booze, not love.
- Two pretty girls.
- It's booze.
- She didn't have time to love.
- Not love.
- It's not.
That's booze.
No way I would cry.
Look how many people is at the party.
Fuck, for Christ's sake!
I would get out of there
and you'd only see me next week.
She's in Floripa.
Afterparty at the house!
That's great!
Now it's started.
Thank God! Look at Taynara.
- Now we're talking!
- Look!
Look at Taynara.
Guys, she almost hit her head.
Taynara is... Look at Taynara.
Man, I want Taynara.
And I want to see that bulge...
Everyone wants you.
I'll tell you what...
I wanna see the Speedos.
They're already taking a shower together?
That's quite a lunch box.
What a gentleman.
If Taynara farts in a blowing horn,
bulls from all over would come.
Wait.
I saw Taynara first, stop it.
Moaning.
You see? You're wasting time.
It's a dog in heat.
Yep. Looked like a bunny
doing it really fast, like this, "Go."
Like a trembling thing.
I'm shocked, but I loved it.
I've never judged anyone having sex.
- I didn't.
- I've never seen it.
I wanted to be like that
with my beau...
Damn it, man.
I've never seen this.
I've never seen anybody having sex...
What is that, guys?
You gotta name it.
I love that position, on foot.
Would you stop
being loud over there, motherfuckers?
Murilo. João is already
cockblocking them upstairs.
I'd get a boy to fuck me, too.
You think I'd be listening
to people fucking?
You think it's easy?
I think this makes you do it, you know?
If I see a friend
kissing someone at a party,
I feel like kissing
so I don't end up by myself.
Yes. And if things
get really serious, I get really horny.
You think it's easy for me?
Chill, kid.
An eleven-inch cock and I don't...
No, go to hell, Luan.
Cover up that dick, motherfucker.
He played.
Just warming up.
Look!
Do you want something better?
Rewind and take a look at his shorts.
I'm going to rewind this.
Wait.
Look at his shorts! Look at his shorts.
Fuck!
No bullshit.
I'm nervous.
- Open the door! Open the little door!
- Man, how did you notice that?
I noticed it real quick.
- You have bionic eyes.
- No one had noticed.
She has. Fast.
Titto looked at that girl's ass...
I didn't even notice that
he was in the room.
This way you see how a person...
- Nice, let's press play.
- Man, looks like a camera tripod.
Interesting.
I love the baked chicken position.
You love what?
The baked chicken position. You like?
It's Tay. I like it. I like it all.
Guys, what is that?
- Seriously, man? It's not possible.
- My God.
- Guys, it's not possible.
- Guys, where's the infrared?
I'm shocked. They are really liberal.
- These people.
- Why am I like this? I'm shocked.
Me, too. It's crazy. How...
- I'm shocked.
- If that girl's dad sees that...
Imagine my mother
seeing me doing the commentary.
It's bad enough 'cause I'm doing this.
Can you imagine...
Mom, I don't do that.
Mom, I'm just commenting.
- Is it stroganoff?
- No. It's sushi, fuck.
Idiot.
- Rude! Take the pillow...
- Stroganofferson.
Guys... Why does everyone
eat stroganoff after partying?
Because it's too easy to make.
I'm still trying to get
the peanut off my tooth.
I'm like this... Look.
Rinsing my mouth with Red Bull.
I'm rinsing my mouth
for two hours,
trying to get the peanut off my tooth.
Do you need me to buy anything?
I could go out.
We should think about
what we'll cook.
Get stuff for a barbecue. And we're good.
- Garlic bread!
Let's go get some garlic bread.
That's me.
They're buying garlic bread.
People got excited
about garlic bread. Did you see it?
Garlic bread is everything.
Who doesn't like it?
Let's buy garlic bread.
That's delicious. It's food.
You're messing with me.
All right, but do you have to get excited?
Girl.
Taynara looks responsible.
They're the most beautiful girls there,
Taynara and Nathalia.
I like... Everyone is beautiful,
but I like their vibe.
I didn't say they're bad-looking.
It was my opinion. Respect that.
It's my kind of girl.
Look, my kind of boy, I wouldn't
hook up with... I don't know.
I'm going to tell you who
I'd hook up with, not who I wouldn't.
I'd hook up with Luan,
who was banging that chick.
I like weird and funny guys.
No... Taking a better look at João...
The man with the beard, I want him.
Did you hear that?
Then kiss me, you son of a bitch.
Write it down, "Joyce."
He's going to laugh so hard...
He's going to get attached to this.
- You need to write...
- Joyce Kelly.
- Hold it up like this.
-"Joysse."
Now, "Kelly."
He's not even
going to kiss Blondie anymore.
Wow...
- Fuck, with two "S."
- Joysse Kelly. I love it.
- For Christ's sake.
- I love it.
- My drag name now is that.
- Joysse Kelly.
Joysse Kelly.
Luan looks like those boys
from São Paulo who like
to take you to a funk party.
Look at those tactel shorts.
He's going
to take us to a funk party. Yes.
- Me, too.
- Take us to a funk party.
That boy has a tattoo,
tactel shorts and flip-flops...
I love it!
- Flip-flops from?
- From Kenner.
Juliet.
I don't bother to watch
if he doesn't appear on my living room TV.
Excuse me?
- You can't come in.
- So, I can't come in?
Fuck you!
Kiss!
- I love it!
- Hey, João comes and...
A Maria Eugênia. João knows...
Maria Eugênia...
He knows how to do his thing. He knows it.
He hooked up with her real fast.
João is doing a lot
and is doing nothing.
He knows how I like it.
João didn't hook up with anyone...
But that ass shaking was right.
I see. So, he's a dancer, honey.
- He's what?
- A dancer. He's a dancer.
No, you can feel it when someone knows it.
Oh, my!
What will my family think of me?
- Me neither.
- Yeah, me neither.
Girl!
The grandma...
The snake will look at this and be like...
No, not with me.
Your grandma is going to be cool.
But she will, girl...
Hey, Nath?
- Yes?
- Are you ready, love?
I can't believe I'm so hot.
Take this heat from inside...
Before, it was "love," "Nath,"
"Nath," "love."
Now, it's "love," "baby."
- Nathalia! Are you ready?
-"Nathalia."
And...
I love it!
You've bitten the pussy in the bus?
I love it when my pussy is bitten.
It's not possible, dude.
I can't believe this.
Or in the pub.
I love when my pussy is bitten, Amazon!
Is biting the pussy allowed?
Because someone is not going to get it.
It's the best!
Do you like it?
Having your pussy bitten.
- Fuck.
- Tell us, Carol. Carol's shaken.
Carol, do you like
having your pussy bitten? "Fuck!"
Carol is... She said something
like this... Her hand was shaking.
Guys, wait, they want to interact
with the other table. Look.
They're right.
Look me in the eye.
- If I steal a kiss, would you kick my ass?
- No.
No?
- Nothing.
- No, really?
No?
You got cheated on
I got cheated on
Women don't know
what to do in those situations.
That's empowerment.
When she looks and says, "Really?"
Empowerment is not making
a scene. It's saying, "Really?
You're doing this to tease me? Watch me."
Go and hook up with three guys.
Empowerment is equality.
She has to do the same.
You don't have to fight.
There's no need to make a scene.
They're hurting.
Empowerment is equality.
She has to do the same.
What, girl?
Empowerment is equality.
She can do the same.
She's in pain...
I don't know if the answer
is doing the same.
Yes, that's true.
She must have the right
to do the same.
Equality is not vengeance.
She can do whatever he does.
It's not the same thing.
It's only...
That chick there is in pain, those guys
are doing what they want,
and the girls are crying.
They can do anything.
You know what the problem is?
Men can hook up
with 50 women, and it's cool. Women can't.
No, that is wrong.
Yes, real nice guy. Super cool.
He wanted to be the best. Well, he got it.
For all that matters, he's the man!
Stop it.
It's what society dictates,
some women can't deal with that.
Because men hook up
with a lot of women and everyone...
He's a total jerk...
Most people don't think like that...
Some women can't handle that...
...they don't want
to be judged by everyone.
I'm going to talk.
I get what you're saying.
Yeah, she has the right
to speak, it's like this...
No, that's what I'm talking about.
So, she wants to do something
and she suffers for that jerk,
you know? Stop it. What?
Unfortunately, it's the reality.
Men who hook up with
everyone are stallions.
Women are sluts, but it's not like that.
Yeah, but that's reality.
Let me tell you something.
It was a long time ago.
She has the right to speak.
We, as men, can't judge it.
It's just... Hey... Wait.
Everyone who has the ability...
- It's not a fight.
- Guys, look. Let's...
It's not anything at all.
You can plot, too.
You can vanish for one hour and come back
with an untidy hair,
smeared lipstick. "Hi, guys, what's up?"
I'm going to change the subject.
This subject is too boring.
Let's do that.
Patriarchy sucks, guys.
Let's hook up with everyone, women.
You can get as many guys as you want.
Who cares what people say?
- And if you don't, that's fine.
- Yes, they can.
It's not about what they can do.
They should. They can and they must, man!
If you want to go vegan,
you can do it. I hate it.
Don't feel pressured, hook up with them.
A lot of women don't hook up
because they feel the pressure.
John said something nice.
If you want what?
Come on!
If she wants to go vegan, she can.
The day hasn't even...
So be it! Be free.
Do you know what I would do?
- Carol, say it.
- Say it, Carol.
I'd tell the other friend,
"Did you see that?" It's crocodile tears.
"What he did to me."
And I'd hook up with the other friend.
This is proof that the attitude of guys...
But, girl...
- Crocodile tears.
- No, that's it, that's it.
Things are ugly for them, but I think...
But I think everyone is free...
Everyone is having fun.
It's ugly, that's what...
It's ugly for them, man. Got it?
I don't think he's wrong either. I don't.
Nowadays, there's no right or wrong.
There's no "can" or "can't."
I just think he's being ungraceful.
I think so, too.
Now let's continue,
because there's still a lot.
I just wanted to get one more...
This is exactly what we came here for.
Well, I am.
No, that's not what I came here for.
It would be the same thing
if I wanted to control Murilo.
You see?
All I want is to be at that party now.
I want to be there, I'd go, "Oops!"
But karma is a bitch!
You reacted just like I did.
I didn't like that.
- There's nothing we can do.
- And he kissed her.
They're from another table,
he's hugging them, right?
João comes up to the table,
but doesn't bang anyone.
He's that guy
who doesn't pick up any girls.
He likes to show off for his friends...
He doesn't pick anyone up.
What is it called?
Wire fence with no spikes.
It just surrounds you.
It doesn't jab you.
Everyone has...
The microwave friend.
He heats up the food and other people
eat it.
Do you have friends like that?
I have a lot of microwave friends.
They heat up the lunch
and other people bang.
Who never hooked up with someone who
your friend talked the whole night with
and you went there and picked up?
Man, you fucking suck.
I fuck, what?
You got cheated on before,
and now you're cheating on him? Payback?
Girlfriend.
- Girlfriend, don't fall down.
- Sit down.
- That's me talking.
- I'm that one.
"Don't fall down. Girlfriend."
- I'm the one who falls down.
- Nathalia is wasted.
I say, "Don't fall down."
You're the one who falls down.
"Don't fall for him,"
that's what I'm saying.
I'm not talking about falling down
because you're wasted,
"Don't fall for him."
- He's sober.
- Nathalia is wasted.
We have ordered some water for you.
Do you need to use the restroom?
You know I was with him, right?
He told you that.
I got cheated on.
I asked him about that. So sorry.
No, relax, he's all yours.
Because I don't...
No. About that...
- I don't think that's the point.
- You... Fuck you!
- Princess, you...
- Fuck you, Ramon.
You're falling down
like crazy, damn it.
- Girlfriend, I am from Magic Island.
- Fuck you, Ramon.
Go on, then. I was serious.
Stop falling down.
- What he did was stupid.
- He's a jerk.
I didn't get it. I didn't.
Now the show's on.
Now's the time the baby cries
and the mother doesn't see it.
That's the booze talking.
I love it. I do!
This is a pub, it's not even a party.
- Me and Bianca there.
- It's the end of me.
I'm the one who's with Bianca.
I really am.
The guys got upset now.
Do you see how shocking it is?
Then the guy says, "Now I'm fucked up.
The chicks are on the loose."
I'm that one, you bet I am.
Baby, I'd make a scene on that floor.
I'd stand up beautiful.
"What? Are you blowing me off?
Because I'm going to make a scene."
- They're upset.
- Fall down again.
"What?"
João is a showman.
She'd fall down and say, "What is it?"
No somersaults,
for the love of God!
You're such a sweetheart, you know?
Thank you!
Putting up with me is not easy.
Now, with me and your friends together...
Attention, everyone!
Good morning, João!
Whoever wants to go to the afterparty,
stick with Daddy! It's time!
He'd have to be very good...
Wearing that track suit,
like an elderly...
What did he say?
Who's ready for the afterparty?
I think I wouldn't look at a guy
like him, I'd just fuck him.
But I'd ask him to tell no one.
Like, "Don't tell anyone, please."
"In the name of our friendship,
don't tell."
In the name of my Instagram profile.
In the name
of my merchandising publications.
In the name of my "at" sign.
...being a loser is totally different.
- No!
- But what happened?
You're my friend.
He is talking...
Do you think she'd be happy
if I talked to you like this?
- Bia, come here.
- Look, you're a grown woman.
Hey, wonderful girl!
Don't lose your mind, okay?
That one over there is going crazy.
Don't you dare tell me not to lose
my mind, we haven't even talked yet.
I'm talking to them, not to you.
Get in the groove.
Things are going
to get real ugly now.
We're home! Make yourselves at home!
Hey, that's fucked up, look.
It's already fucked up.
Those guys banged the girls,
now they brought two other girls
to the house.
The chicks
are not going to like them.
Of course not.
Check out this view!
I'd be very upset if this happened. João!
This is Nathalia.
João, come on...
She's drunk, wasted.
Guys, if I don't see João hooking up
with someone until the end of this series,
I'm going to be very upset.
It's personally.
- Disappointed.
- Because he's the most annoying.
Jesus, there are some guys there,
"Thanks for asking me
to be a part of the show."
They were the last ones to be asked.
- Cigarette.
- Where am I going to sleep?
I'm just going to put
a mattress here.
...over there Tarzan?
- She's too wasted.
- Tarzan.
Who's Tarzan?
This is Luan.
Luan wants to fuck Nathalia's pussy.
Tarzan is that guy from earlier.
It's windy inside that room.
Boy! It's a tsunami.
I found it cute when he took her upstairs.
He has to bathe her
and put her to bed. He has to do it.
Disagreement is not the point.
If he tries something...
- That's it.
- Attention!
I think I'll have to go upstairs...
Is there something going on...
Nothing is going on.
He's just protecting her.
She's going to hug and cuddle...
Just like she was with her...
That's it. That's what I'm saying.
It was his fault, not hers.
- I find it cute, but...
- He's going to give her some medicine.
- See if he doesn't have bad intentions.
- I think I'd fuck him.
Shut up.
She isn't thinking right at the moment.
She's drunk. She can't tell...
I was going to ask you.
If one comes to me, then the other...
Please! Get me out of there,
throw me in the pool.
But don't let me,
because shit is going to hit the fan.
I'll smack one or the other.
That's the way things are.
- It's all right, it's UFC.
- She's Carol. She has Carol's instincts.
It's Carol. It's true, man. Isn't it?
Did you sleep? Tell the truth.
Guys, look at that girl's face,
the one who isn't staying in the house.
"What am I doing here?"
It's like that aunt who gossips
looking out the window.
Let's go downstairs.
That's just trouble. She's drunk.
Go to the stairs.
He wants that trouble.
- Hey, pretty thing!
João is the funny guy, that João.
You left that drunk chick over there.
The cell phone.
My God, I wonder who it is.
Good news or bad news first?
- The good news.
- We're going to have to work tomorrow.
- Cool!
- All right?
- Then we'll work.
- Work was never the problem.
I just wanted to tell everybody.
I'll let you know the time tomorrow, okay?
You just need to know
that we're working tomorrow, all right?
And the good news?
The good news is we're here in this house.
- I like him. He's the guy I like.
- He's good, too. I liked him.
I'd be his friend... I'd suck him...
It'd be a bromance...
A dick in my mouth...
What?
I'd suck him because he's nice, got it?
I don't know if I'd suck him.
Wouldn't you suck someone because
he's charismatic? If the person
was nice to me, I'd say,
"Give me that."
My rule is being charismatic. Always.
Being charismatic
is not even having a sex appeal.
Does anyone have
an energy drink for Carol?
She drank chocolate milk.
She had chocolate milk and fell asleep.
I'm trying to understand
the charisma thing...
No, I don't like nice guys. No, man.
Since the start of the series...
What kind of man do you like?
I like serious men.
He is serious, he said,
"We'll work tomorrow, stay tuned."
A family guy doesn't hook up.
He's not hooking up with anyone.
But where do you find that guy?
He's real.
It's just wrong that you didn't talk to me
and then said bullshit behind my back.
Don't talk shit to me, just don't.
Crap, talk to me, then.
I'm right here. I'm a man!
- And I'm a woman!
- Then tell it to my face.
Take it.
I'll think that now
because I'm a mature person...
She stuttered, he's fucked up!
You're mature?
- It's clear.
- I am wasted.
If we talk now,
things are getting ugly.
If I talk to you right now...
Blame it on the booze.
I've never seen a drunk person...
Because you're being selfish again?
You didn't even want
to face your own stuff.
This is why I don't want talk.
So we're sleeping together for no reason?
I was just chilling.
You're pointing a finger at me.
Because I don't want to talk today?
- You are being fake.
- I am being myself!
Oh, yeah? That's cool,
be yourself. Just be yourself.
I don't want to talk to you or to her,
because I am drunk.
So go upstairs, it's our house.
Luan is fucking up the scenario.
He's needy. That chick doesn't want
to talk to him,
she already said it, he's on to her.
Get out of there. Just bounce.
João is just laughing.
- João is needy and sad.
- Guys, I'm like João.
Who's that again?
Guys, she was my animal. If I was wasted,
I wouldn't want to talk to anyone.
Let's talk tomorrow morning.
- I think they're going to talk in private.
- No one saw anything.
- Things are going to get nasty.
- Right? Now it's...
No, for heaven's sake. We're good.
I want to hear your version now.
I was with everybody, like you were
with everybody.
Nath's guy hooked up with someone else.
Do you think I was going
to leave her alone?
If you're fucking me...
Lower your fucking finger, fuck.
Don't stick a finger in my face.
Look. That's ungraceful.
"You're fucking me."
Fine. For me, it doesn't.
Hey, you have
a loose screw in your head. You're crazy.
If I wanted to hook up
with her, I would have.
You said I have a loose screw.
Have I offended you?
Have I said that you're weak?
You're crazy. You haven't?
Is disrespect.
Learn how to talk to me.
You wanted to talk.
Learn how to talk to me. Got it?
We are talking. Stop being a bitch.
Shove that loose screw up your ass.
- Stop being an asshole?
- That was you. She's Bianca.
"Shove that loose screw up your ass."
I used to say.
We're not on the same vibe anymore.
We haven't been for a while.
Your little head is full of shit.
See? They're not even married. and
the man's sleeping on the couch. See?
Well, if the shoe fits, wear it.
If you're sleeping on the couch,
you're in trouble. "Man, that was wrong."
If someone's upset, go somewhere else.
He really stayed away.
The girl is going
to talk to him on the couch.
But she was also...
She's going to wake up
the next morning,
they're going to have a chat
and kiss again...
I believe we can expect it
on this same episode.
The truth is you can never win
an argument with a woman.
You'll never win an argument.
They're always right.
It's better being happy than being right.
- I like this sentence.
- Did you get it? Be cool, put up with her.
Yeah, baby.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
- João?
- Girlfriend!
João?
- I want to see if he has a big dick.
- Shut up.
I said it out loud.
What's a man able to do
when he wants to fuck?
- Holy shit!
- He cried!
D-I-C-K. On vacation.