WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
THE REVIEW
Carol, I feel like banging you today.
- My God.
- I hate it!
Did I miss it?
Remember that man...
That's Titto...
I'm to be seen.
Titto's jokes are the best.
Titto, do you like chocolate?
Sure.
Nice to meet you, Carol Show.
Carol Show!
My joke is an old uncle's joke,
but did you hear what Carol said?
What did she say?
"Titto, do you like chocolate?
Nice to meet you, Carol Show."
Buddy, when she's awake, she says it all.
When Carol wakes up, she just talks.
Is your name Google?
No, why?
Because I find
everything I look for in you.
Fuck, John normally drools,
and with his mouth full...
He crossed the line. Holy shit!
"Sorry"? That's really an accent.
Guys, we're back to watch
Episode 4 of Floripa Beach House.
The last episode ended
with Murilo's guests kicked out
after fighting
with girls from the house, take a look.
Let's press play,
I'm dying to watch it. May I?
Oh, please.
Did you find it cool? Did you like it?
Jeez, a lot.
It was really cool
when you got to the party.
The only one who had sex
last week was João.
Wait, look.
All of a sudden,
you came in. At the right time.
Blondie and João
are not friends with benefits anymore.
I don't have anything to do...
Jeez, man.
She put him down. What a bitch.
I know, this was bad.
Now he's playing hard to get. There it is!
Do you want me to hook up with you
when you have nothing to do?
That's it. When you have
nothing to do, you come and use me.
- Yeah...
- We use each other.
That's nice!
- That's why we're here.
- I loved it.
I thought it was abusive.
Tell me more.
I use you, you use me.
I like when the person is honest, got it?
I like using people.
Am I going to like being used?
Let's get ready,
we're gonna go for drinks in one hour.
Guys, João got married, right?
Oh, my God... He's married.
João's girl went to the house...
- Did she stay there?
- She's in the house.
- She's one of them now.
- One more...
- Look at the makeup.
- So, is João in a romance?
Now that João's had sex,
he won't let her leave.
He'll say, "You're going
to stay here forever."
He'll send her away now.
Are they going to the party? Already?
It must be Saturday.
We can start earlier on Saturdays, right?
Yeah... Makes sense.
I'm gonna do the lucky lick.
Excuse me.
Lucky lick. Wait, let me see. Sit there.
But I want to be lucky.
No, I told you.
João licked that girl's boobs.
- Look.
- It really was that, look.
What did I say in
the last episode? I said João would lose
his virginity
and would have sex a lot, see?
That he would get loose.
Yes.
I wonder if the chicks are going
to let him do what he wants
or if he became a friend...
No, she let him lick her boobs.
Girl...
I don't let
my girlfriends lick my nipples,
but anyway... This could be a friend zone.
He does that and shows off.
- João... He's handsome.
- He is.
He's the hottest.
I don't find him handsome,
but I find him... He's a show-off.
I find him handsome.
He's a good kisser.
No, now my vibe has changed.
I'm digging Murilo now.
Fuck, man...
How long since you've been here?
How long haven't I been here?
Man, about...
ten years.
Ten years since he's been on a beach.
I don't judge him...
Like my bank account.
...seen a positive balance.
I go to Rio three times a week.
I just see it...
I've been living
in Rio and the last time
I got into the water
was about seven months ago.
From time to time,
it's good to salt your ass, but...
Poor Murilo, ten years without...
Salt your ass!
#SALTYOURASS
From time to time, it's good to salt it,
but... You get breaded.
"Salt your ass," that's great.
I'm just stealing your... I'm warming up.
They're so cute.
It's not all about sex. You see?
It's already touching, did you see it?
It's Carol.
It wants to say hello to you.
Stay put, fuck! Stop it!
It doesn't work when it has to.
- Jeez.
- He slapped her in the face?
I found it really aggressive.
Yeah, look, I think
they should kick him out of the house.
What do you guys think
about that slap, Bianca?
I thought it was abusive.
But they had a relationship...
It depends on the vibe.
He wasn't aggressive, he didn't go there.
Maybe that happened when they had sex...
...but she didn't like it.
She didn't.
- She made drama.
- That could happen at the bar.
In the bedroom is one thing...
She didn't like it.
You noticed she got kind of mad.
There's a pet peeve in a couple,
sometimes that happens.
- But she's wrong.
- He took a lot of makeup off of her face.
One time,
when I was talking, I was getting angry,
I said, "I don't know what..."
But in that situation, I don't know...
You're not ridiculous. You're real.
I do this a lot, too. Sometimes...
Hit me again.
- I'm very cold, I swear...
- It's too cold.
I'm shaking.
I'm trying to drink, but I can't.
Bro, I got out of there
because something annoyed me.
What?
Didn't you see Ramon slapping my face?
Slap your face?
- He was messing with you, right?
- Yeah, but...
I can't accept that, even if he was.
She's joking, right, guys?
She's upset.
She feels like she suffered an aggression.
The man who slapped her...
Yes, he was messing around.
It was a little push. He was kidding.
Let me say something.
We as men are stronger than women.
- It's obvious, man.
- One little slap became...
It was misinterpreted, maybe.
He didn't intend to...
She didn't... Yeah. Got it?
I'm not saying it's okay,
but she didn't allow that.
She let him know she didn't allow that.
- You think?
- All starts with a joke.
How didn't she have intimacy with him?
She's talking about his dick...
"Look, it works when it has to."
Do you want more intimacy?
Guys, a dick spanking
is very different from a real spanking.
It doesn't give him the right to...
Man, you slapped me in the face.
Come on, Nath.
- You're not supposed to.
- Did I slap you hard?
I didn't like it.
What if I did that to you?
You did that to me many times.
You hit me three times in the gut
with your elbow. Three times.
Should a man slap a woman in the face?
- She flopped the situation.
- She flopped, baby.
If you apologized to me
and I accepted it, we're good.
Yeah, man, she's a troublemaker.
That's bad.
She picked a fight
and then filed her nails.
You fucked up, huh, Nathalia?
She was filing her nails
and eating chicken.
Big mistake.
I want to understand what
"flop the situation" means.
I want to understand.
"To flop" means...
It's like "ruined."
"It didn't work out," got it?
Like, "The person ruined my thing."
"I went to have sex
with Titto, and his dick is small."
He flopped the situation.
You flopped the sex.
You're not supposed to expose
our intimacy here.
I've already told you. All right?
It's like "ruined," "interrupted."
Pabllo, has anybody
ever flopped your thing?
- Many times, but...
- The way John said?
Yeah, but I don't stop dreaming
about better days because of that.
Go, Cinderella from Bahia, Carla Perez.
I can't stand her look, man.
No, look at her look, man.
She's absolute, right?
She stays here.
Does anyone have a funny story
of a flopped situation? A story. Anyone?
Anyone?
Carol! Carol! Carol!
- Carol, our oracle.
- About dick?
A flopped situation.
About a ruined situation by someone.
Because this person was late
or didn't have an invitation to the party.
Or he had a small dick.
We go to parties with friends,
then they fight
with each other, and I just leave.
Obviously, it's flopping the situation.
What about you?
Did anyone flop like this...
Other than me? Small dick.
Penis? Man, it doesn't happen
because I ask to send me a picture.
Once this happened, there was one time
I hooked up with a guy,
when we got to my place.
We started making out, he said,
"I have to tell you a little thing,
but I'll do it later."
"A little thing" is great.
Then he said,
"I'm married. I have two kids."
"So, you have to leave, right?"
Then he came back, had sex and left.
I didn't get it.
He said he was married, had two kids.
That was a flopped situation.
- It was a flopped situation.
- I won, baby.
What about you, Bianca?
Are you talking about fighting?
- No, about flopping.
- It could be without...
Yes. The only time I used a dating app...
Tell us more, Bianca. The only time.
No, I like to know the person.
If the talking is good,
I'll meet the person, got it?
The guy had a nice chatting style.
He used to make me laugh a lot.
When we met, his voice was terrible.
And I care a lot about voices,
man, I don't know why.
Why didn't I ask him
to send me a voice message?
No WhatsApp at that time?
What about the dick?
I chatted on WhatsApp,
but I didn't send...
What about the dick?
I didn't even get there, no.
-"What about the dick?
- It was disappointing.
It gobbled, babe.
I never used those apps anymore.
What kind of voice do you like?
Like Mariano's?
- Who talks like this? Placing his voice...
- What about mine?
No, girl, but...
His kind of voice is not...
- What about mine, Bia?
-"What about mine? Girl..."
- What about mine?
- I love you.
Thanks, girl.
Mariano, say something as if...
As if you were on an app and would send
Bianca a voice message,
a girl who likes voices.
Let's do this.
How would Mariano send a voice message...
To Carol, dressed as money.
How would you send her a voice message?
Fuck, my nipple got...
Carol, huh? Let's spend some money?
- Oh, fuck.
- Let's do this.
- Look.
-"Let's do this." That's very good.
- Let's do this.
- Hey, stop it.
Fuck, seriously. That voice means sex.
Hit play, I want to see this mess now.
Fuck.
- Got it?
- No.
We were joking around, talking,
and he slapped me in the face.
I thought about hitting him back
at that moment. Anyway. I bounced...
Fuck, you're still into him?
Come on, Nathalia. Jesus Christ.
Luan is defending me.
I'm defending you. Fuck, man.
She's kind of an idiot,
I'm sorry to say that.
Murilo is going to talk to her.
- She's really being an asshole.
- Totally.
I think she was too quiet
in the last episodes,
then she decided, "Today is the day."
Fuck, girl,
why did she say that to that boy?
That's not necessary.
If a friend of mine says,
"So-and-so slapped my face,"
I'll think he slapped her in the face.
I would tell the guy,
"Are you going
to slap her in the face?
Are you nuts?"
But that didn't happen.
I would throw the TV...
He had already apologized.
He was kidding... Luan is shaken.
I think he's arguing.
Why are you looking at her this way?
- That's the troublemaker.
- Look, he's dying to fight.
That's what I'm talking about.
Luan, stop it.
No way. He's pissed.
I'm devastated.
Get out of there, man. He soaked Thais.
- Luan, stop it...
- You piece of shit.
He spilled... The drink on the girl.
For Christ's sake, he soaked everybody
in here, soaked everybody but me.
Fuck you.
Come on, man. Hey, Luan...
For Christ's sake, Luan.
It takes four men to stop me.
You piece of shit.
Can't you deal with me on your own?
Show me you can deal with me alone.
Stop it, stop it! Please, don't do...
Who was the girl that...
It was Nathalia, right?
Yes. She's an asshole.
Luan was told she was attacked.
Do you guys think he did the right thing?
- No. He was already upset.
- I think you can't retaliate an attack.
A real man says, "Hey, pal, come here."
Exactly.
No, wait, I understand his situation.
He interfered even if that had
nothing to do with the situation.
I understand that... His resentment.
The problem is that people...
They want to talk under the influence.
At the club...
But the way he talked to him, right?
I've already defended someone at a club.
I've seen a guy beating a woman...
Me, too, I've already fought.
In that case, he was upset...
I don't drink and I've already seen this
and I said, "Are you grabbing
this woman's arm?
If she wants to talk to you,
you don't have to grab her arm.
Let her go."
I've done this a lot of times.
I've already fought.
It's wrong to take it out,
but I understand. It's hard to see
someone close to you being attacked...
It's...
- It's inadmissible.
- Thanks.
I think he should have talked to Ramon,
but he said, "What's the deal?"
He threatened him on the bus.
He was showing off.
He was an asshole. A hooligan, got it?
Exactly.
Do you know who the aggressor was?
He was.
He wanted to fight in front of everybody.
Got it?
He wanted to be the hotshot...
I think he has feelings for Nath.
Do you remember
he took care of her in the bedroom?
Remember that?
I don't know what he's thinking,
but I don't agree.
He took care of her. He went there
and got mad, he was jealous of him.
He went there and defended her.
I wonder if he's just a good friend
or if he has ulterior motives.
Talking to her was wrong.
She told Luan about being slapped
and didn't explain it to him.
- Exactly.
- No, it was wrong...
She didn't admit to him
what he'd said to her.
It was wrong to apologize
and leave unfinished business.
I'm sorry to tell you this.
But, to me, he's a man and you're a kid.
When a man realizes
someone is acting like a kid,
they take someone's side.
I'm sorry to tell you this.
But, to me, today...
Today he's the greatest.
That's fair.
Do you know why? Because
he's got nothing to do with this.
He's got nothing to do with both of us.
And he defended me.
I agree. That's true.
And you also could be...
I didn't behave well.
No, bro.
I wish I'd never met you. I swear.
She humiliated that guy a lot.
I think he's going to apologize...
And he didn't say a thing.
If he does that, he'll be a genius...
Because he's not that wrong.
And he was scolded by her,
she'd rather not have met...
And he didn't... didn't answer.
Man, she broke his heart.
She couldn't have said that, man.
Yes, I'm very touched...
She's sad. How unfortunate.
Imagine how many men
she deceived by crying crocodile tears.
It's a valid lesson
because I think it's the moment...
But the context itself...
She made a mistake.
- Are you making fun?
- No, I'm very shaken.
Do you think...
She's a crying crocodile. She's laughing.
- No.
- Yes, she has no emotions.
But she's very unpredictable.
Carol, you're laughing, stop it!
Carol is very unpredictable.
I don't want...
I'm crying.
My little dollar bundle, stop it!
Come eat, man. Sit, let's eat.
Look at this tasty food I made you guys,
one big plate.
I love you, my friend, you know?
You too, my friend.
I'm going to miss those hot nights
in the Tiger Room.
Jeez, I'm kind of sick of Luan now.
Now Luan is...
He's the man. He thinks he's the man.
- Look, you see? Look.
- You, too, my friend.
If he stared at me like that,
I would headbutt him
three times.
What is he thinking, man?
What?
Something is going on at that table.
He's making a bad boy face,
a hooligan face.
That guy asked him to talk...
Get a clue, bro. Look, poor Ramon.
He doesn't know what to do.
He was scolded.
- Yes.
He... wants to resolve nothing.
He wakes up the other day,
"Hey, sorry, I won't do this
anymore. My vibe is going to change."
- Yes.
- I hope so.
He's already done that.
He'll do it again.
Look at that table,
it's a rich people's thing, right?
It's a soap opera thing.
I like that pool inside the house,
I want that.
She's going to call someone now.
I want to see who she'll call.
Calling...
Call the sheriff!
Those who humble
themselves will be exalted.
- She's going to bring a boy.
- She's the devil.
- Hello?
- Hi.
- Look who's there.
- Are you okay?
"Are you okay?"
I am, what about you?
Things are great,
but I need my crush over here, right?
This house gets ugly without you.
What? I thought
your vacation would be longer.
I miss our parties and getting wasted...
I'm coming, easy, honey!
Embarrassing ourselves. Jeez.
Mariano,
what does "embarrassing yourself" mean?
Yeah. "Embarrassing yourself"
means to do something stupid.
- Fucking up.
- Making a scene?
No, at the moment...
Do you know "screwing up"?
- Yeah.
- Do you embarrass yourself, Pabllo?
- Always.
- I love it.
What kind of embarrassment?
Falling down in heels,
showing underwear unintentionally,
but who doesn't?
I don't show my underwear.
When I'm with my crush...
...show my Victoria's Secret underwear...
He tears his pants at the club.
She's bringing meat to a barbecue.
She's been in Floripa for 30 days.
Meat to a barbecue.
She's bringing a skewer.
She's bringing cake
to a birthday party.
She would have to go to a club...
Now she's bringing
another guy from her city?
She wants to tease him.
Do you think she's bringing a guy that
she's already been intimate with to shock?
Maybe the guy stays there
and she gets stuck for the rest
of her vacation. She's stupid.
Send him away.
Isn't it going to be cooler?
I hope he's very hot.
Didn't you hear what she said?
She said, "Those who
humble themselves will be exalted."
She's doing that to tease Ramon.
- To tease him.
- Exactly. It's Regina George.
Do you know what's worse?
Ramon is very cute. He'll be hurt.
- Of course. Look.
- Look, look.
But he's a womanizer, right?
Look, she takes initiative.
Do you know what's worse?
She felt she had the right to do that.
When you see the person
with someone else, you get hornier.
That's great. I want
to see you with someone else.
Ramon will be very horny if Nath really
called her crush, when he arrives, right?
The guy will hook up with her,
then he'll leave.
Do you want to bet those two...
He'll bounce. Ramon will go insane.
- Or the boy could stay...
- He'll have to leave some time.
Ramon could meet another person.
Are you nuts?
You're being naive. He'll say,
"Really? I'm going over there
to get laid."
Ramon will hook up...
Then you look and say, "I'm upset," and
you don't care about that person anymore.
- Anything can happen.
- Ramon is a womanizer.
Do you remember he was hitting on
that woman?
He's surely going
to hook up with another girl.
Who, Ramon?
And both of them are going to be hornier.
We've talked a lot of times. But I think
this situation is not good for me.
It's not that I don't want it,
just to make things clear...
Look him in the eyes, bro.
But... I need some distance right now.
Right before the guy gets there,
because she called him. She's a snake.
Of course I noticed.
But I need some time for me, because
this situation is making me feel bad.
I don't want the house
to get affected like it was.
I want you to have your space,
that I have mine.
You do whatever you want. I'll do
whatever I want, what I feel like doing.
- Live your life.
- Exactly.
I noticed you were different and...
I gave you some space,
even if you didn't talk to me.
- Poor Ramon.
- Come here, Ramon.
I totally understand.
I think, sometimes...
Although we liked each other,
we need some space...
...when a person
doesn't look me in the eyes.
Look me in the eyes.
I get upset when people
don't look me in the eyes.
He was looking her
in the eyes all the time.
She didn't look. And she was speaking...
She knows what she wants to do.
She's being a snake, man.
Ramon is acting like a man.
And she didn't tell that guy is...
She looked him in the eyes
yesterday and said he was a child...
He looked her in the eyes
and had a real talk with her again.
But Ramon is a womanizer, man.
Fuck it, he's a respectful womanizer.
Let him be it.
He hits on everybody.
He can't hook up with other girls?
He may be a good guy to women.
That's weird talk, let him be a womanizer.
What's the problem
with him being a womanizer?
- Guys, but I'm different.
- Why?
Well...
Ramon is wrong? Really? What do you think?
"I'm different.
I'm allowed to do it, I'm different."
Here's what I think.
He's really a womanizer,
but he wasn't her boyfriend.
And what's the problem
with him being a womanizer?
There's a problem when you're committed.
No.
Got it? He's really a womanizer.
I don't think that's a problem...
That's it. Right.
They had no relationship, they had
no deal, did they? I don't think so.
- No.
- They didn't.
But they respected each other, right?
Yes.
But this is different.
He's being honest now, and she isn't.
I think this is going to snowball...
From that moment she lied,
saying she had only told that chick.
She's not being honest with him.
Then she said all those things,
even if he's a womanizer...
I think he's right in that situation...
- Of course.
- He's acting properly...
But I'm on his side.
- Are you going upstairs?
- No.
- Let's talk.
- You're a pain in the ass...
Look. "I need to talk to you."
Will you go with him?
I'm going to talk to Ramon.
When I talked to Nath
about touching her face,
I talked to her,
I apologized for what happened.
Then I heard things escalated,
with one person
telling the story to the next.
Exactly. I did.
I imagine you heard it like,
"Ramon hit Nathalia in the face."
So I put myself in your shoes and wondered
how I'd deal with that.
I'd probably get mad.
This guy is acting like a grown-up.
- Yeah, man.
- He really is.
Yes. Let me tell you
some truths you might enjoy or not.
Sure.
I see her hurting. Bro, me and Bia...
I'm going to tell you what we have.
If she kisses somebody, I kiss, too.
We've talked about it.
But you don't let her
live her life. You have a...
Luan has feelings for Nath.
You shield her, you know?
But you're not protecting her as a friend.
Nath is very defenseless, Ramon.
He's judging their relationship
and his is, "If I kiss, you kiss, too."
Really? Who called him, guys?
But sometimes, I want to be with you.
Then I'm forced
to hook up with another guy
because you hooked up with another girl.
That Luan, no...
I'm going to say something about Ramon.
Now it's serious.
He was honest. He said,
"I put myself in your shoes..."
He's trying...
Everyone heard
a story and told it differently...
"...he slapped her."
He wasn't negligent
at any moment. Then that guy wants
to take advantage of the situation.
He wants to educate him,
use him as an example. What example?
- What example, baby?
- No, it's wrong.
So what? Are you still in love with Luan?
With Luan? My friend used to say,
"A blowjob is not a marriage."
A blowjob is not a marriage.
I'm hating him,
but I'd give him a blowjob.
"I'm hating him,
but I'd give him a blowjob."
- Obviously.
-"Obviously."
Bro, I also make mistakes.
I'm not perfect.
Far from that.
I don't know if I want to be perfect.
We learn from mistakes.
"I don't know if I want
to be perfect." Priceless.
"I hate being so perfect.
I don't know if I want it."
So many good things...
Oh, my God. Excuse my beauty.
Wish you all the best.
To us. Amen...
"Wish you all the best."
I hope the mood here
gets back to what it was.
It's going to...
If that depends on me, you know...
We ended this and, in time...
Booze separates, food reunites.
Amen! We'll get back
into the groove in time.
We're going to be in sync again.
- Wish you all the best.
- Amen. We made it.
-"All the best"?
-"All the best."
No, man, that Luan...
The most...
Luan thinks he's the best.
- I think her crush has just arrived.
- No way! It's him, of course.
I wonder if it's him.
He's a great straight man, a manly man.
"He's a great straight man."
What's up, baby?
- What?
- Didn't you ask me to come?
That's not the correct way
to conjugate the verb.
He started making a Portuguese mistake.
Mauro is making this harder.
Sorry, it was stronger than me.
This is Mauro, Blondie.
How are you? Nice to meet you.
- Can I drink this?
- Are you going to mix us some cocktails?
Yes, coming right up.
I said the invitation...
Were you nervous? You don't need to be.
- Jeez!
- He's full of himself.
- She's a little shaken, did you feel it?
- It's normal, right?
Girl, I found him very cute.
I don't know, I want to see him...
his height. I don't like short guys.
Less than 5'3" is friendship.
You? When you see a short guy... What?
You have to play
in the NBA to date me. For starters, okay?
Your boyfriend has to play in the NBA.
You need money and determination
to date me, we'll figure out the rest.
You have to be cool to date me.
You have to tell bad jokes.
Don't you know any bad jokes?
I'm fucked.
Titto...
What did the duck tell the lagoon?
This is a very bad joke.
I want a bad joke that's good.
No... It's me.
- Now it's her turn.
- One Aperol?
Two Sex on the Beach.
That boy is going to stay there?
Yeah, until she's off the clock.
- I missed you!
- I missed you, man.
- It's good to see a familiar face.
- Familiar...
- Oh, my God.
- I missed you.
I wonder if somebody will cry tonight.
- Yes... A lot.
- Who? Ramon?
- Guys...
- They're already kissing?
He went there for that.
- She's at work, man.
- Gaia left.
I've never seen those people here
in São Paulo. Where do they live?
- Who?
- Those guys.
- Get out of here, man. Shut up.
- You're jealous.
- Stop being jealous.
- I don't like it.
I'll be a happy worker.
Take your hand off my leg, it's yours.
Okay, no problem.
That table over there needs service.
- Jeez!
- Man, she was scolded.
- Yeah, she's at work.
- Of course. She deserved it.
Because...
Ouch, now things are going to get ugly.
Ramon was clear he's going
to live his life and it's all right.
Look at what's written on Luan's shirt.
- What's up, guys?
- It says... "I am positive energy."
I want to see him
fighting wearing that shirt.
- She grabbed his hand.
- See?
How lame.
Obviously, Titto.
That's bad. Bro, Ramon is cool, really.
I'm already a big fan of Ramon.
Yes, he's cute.
He's the nicest person.
I want him to ignore her
so she says, "What?"
Yeah, I want him
to ignore her, bro. Really.
- Let's do this!
- What's up?
- How are you?
- I'm great.
- Somebody is calling you.
- Treat him like a brother.
- Sure.
- Welcome.
- Man, nice to meet you. Thanks.
He's my friend for all moments.
He wakes up with me.
She kissed in front of him.
That's bad, huh?
But Ramon reacted really well.
He didn't do anything.
He's great, but I want to see what's
going to happen when he starts to drink.
Fuck, bro, I hope Ramon hooks up
with a hot babe tonight, man.
If that depended on me, Ramon would
hook up with Gisele Bündchen tonight.
This is fucked up... This kills the mood.
There's not going to be trouble tonight.
Everyone will be upset.
I think there isn't going to be.
I think everyone will be upset.
- Man, Ramon did very well.
- He was elegant.
I told you João had lost his virginity.
He's with that girl at the bar.
Did you see it?
- It's another one?
- Another one.
Jeez, bro!
- No harm at all.
- No...
I won't harm you at all.
I hope so.
I don't believe it.
Look at Nath, man... With...
- Girl...
- Call the other one, Nath.
Look at Ramon,
drinking to forget with a pint.
- What a hot boy, oh, my God.
- What a beautiful ass!
- That's a beautiful ass!
- Man, you're kidding me.
- Short guys are wonderful.
- Beautiful ass!
- They had sex before.
Yeah, they've been
hooking up for a long time.
Is anybody here? Nobody is in here.
Yes...
The couple from Goiás. They've already
slept here. Leave them alone.
Our bedroom is huge, bro.
There's João. See?
Is João going to do an orgy?
- Damn, Titto, it's true.
- Look at João, man.
Guys, João has grown on me now.
- Has it ever happened to any of you?
- Never.
I don't want to know about this.
Look at Mariano. Press pause.
Has it ever happened
when you were having sex...
- And somebody opened the door?
- Yes...
I was once in a motel, I had just eaten
and I was taking my tray
outside the bedroom...
So they could take it away. The bedroom
in front left the door opened...
Who leaves the door open?
The door was left ajar. They might've
tried to shut it. Then I heard, "Oh! Oh!"
Curious...
It was a gay couple.
I said, "Can I join you?"
They let me in...
- Did you?
- What did you do?
Obviously. I had just had dinner,
I was bloated.
But if everybody agreed...
But was it good?
You were well-fed, that's great...
He did.
...I didn't want trouble.
I wonder if this happens in real life.
Would you take a look at that?
But everyone was going to look.
- I wouldn't look, guys.
- You wouldn't?
Would you guys have sex...
Seeing someone by my side
having sex would be such a turn on.
I want that scene...
I wouldn't look.
I would do it beautifully...
- Only if I was wasted.
- I've never done that.
- Have you ever done this?
- No... If you ask me...
Pabllo! Tell the truth.
Have you ever had sex next to anybody?
- No.
- Really?
Didn't I just say I would?
If I'd done it...
- Mariway?
- During holidays, being single...
No. Have you done this?
As single
as a one-legged person's slipper.
Are you going to
say you wouldn't do it?
I love his catchphrases.
You're in a...
I'm talking about the past,
not the future.
So... If I've done it?
Yes, I have.
Have you had sex next to somebody?
In a summer house, with friends...
Everybody in the same house, sure.
- Then there's modão...
- Could you get it up?
Sure.
She's wasted, wants to show off. Fuck.
Murilo, fuck you.
- Fuck you, bro.
- Fuck you.
You're wasted and wants to show off.
We know... Everything you did.
Someone sensible. Thanks, Murilo!
- Jeez!
- Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God, that's my dream!
- Get out of here, John!
- Guys...
I'm so going to spank
the monkey watching this.
- Shut up! Don't say that!
- I'm sorry.
That's inappropriate.
She called that guy,
fucked him, it wasn't good
because she's complaining, wanting...
He's going after her,
and she's flirting with Ramon...
She's upset, look.
That's it, baby, you reap what you sow!
You get what you give, Nathália.
I think she's feeling bad...
That's it, right, guys?
She tried to do what Taynara did.
And it backfired.
She got fucked up.
I think it's funny to see that, right?
How people behave.
Because we are like that.
That's real life.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
I wonder if she'll catch the guy in bed.
Ouch, she's drunk, she's going... Oh.
- I can't believe she did that!
- Look... You see?
- That's what I'm saying
- Jeez, man, she's clueless, dude.
She has something that doesn't exist
anymore, she needs to have good sense.