I want to see what's happening.
Guys... garlic bread, no way.
This is not your garlic bread.
I brought some garlic bread.
I brought some garlic bread, right, guys?
- Guys, garlic bread...
- Today, I'm muerta.
We're back to watch the second last
episode of Wild and Free: Florianópolis.
It's ending.
I was eager to watch this.
You again with this appetizer...
I'm dying to watch the next season.
Do you remember the fight between Bia
and Nathália, who argued because of Luan?
I remember. Unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
They aren't actors, there's no script.
Everything happens freely...
Ouch.
That's why they fight,
there's trouble...
Let's watch this?
Press play.
Go, pass me the remote.
It's me, fuck!
This is my moment! My moment's come.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
Good morning, guys.
- Look who's up.
- Dear Lord...
- Did you have a good time yesterday?
- Awesome.
Good. João is very happy.
He is, right?
- They said you betrayed me. How so?
- Really?
I swear. I got up from that bean bag
and it seemed my friend had eight heads.
I was very dizzy.
I don't even remember coming in the house.
Bia, let's drive Vic
to the airport with me?
- She's leaving already...
- I'm leaving...
Let's go.
- Guys, Vic is leaving.
- Leaving already?
Beautiful!
- Thanks.
- Aren't you going to eat something?
- Don't cry...
- Don't cry, Blondie...
See you around...
- In Sampa, at the fairs.
- Absolutely...
Did you like the guys?
Yes, guys. Great people.
You're awesome. You guys rule.
I wanted you to stay longer, girl.
What about you and Nath?
Are you okay?
Man... She ran up there, girl.
She ran up there and said,
"Bia! Bia! Bia, go downstairs!
Go downstairs!
It's Luan!" Bro, I went there
like a fool... I made a scene,
'cause I went downstairs like
a crazy woman, "What's going on here?"
I was pissed.
- Obviously, you know? Pissed, right?
- Yes.
Don't you know me?
We're not here for a day, for a week...
My friend...
Take care.
You're wonderful, girl. It's near...
Yes, it's near.
- Bye, baby.
- Bye. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Bye, girl.
I'll miss you.
- Bye, take care, girl.
- Take care.
Take care.
Kisses.
Oh, girl... Yeah.
You'll see her again soon.
Here's what I think...
I'll have to like myself,
so I won't accept acting
like a fool anymore...
If you don't really want to be with me,
don't sit on the fence
and show me another thing.
Besides confusing yourself,
that's your problem...
...involving you in another thing.
- That has nothing to do with it.
- I agree.
...nothing to do with your problems.
That has nothing to do
with your frustration.
I think it's super honest
we have this conversation...
and talk about it
because I apologized later.
Face your feelings, you know?
Even if it's the opposite
of what you want... you know?
I faced mine and accepted them
since the beginning.
I've been doing it the whole time.
- Yes, I know you did.
- But it's like...
Unfortunately, it's gone.
I'm going to move on.
- Okay.
- So... Take care.
So, guys, I was a little sad, right?
Because I was going to leave...
But I managed to leave tomorrow, man.
What are we doing now?
You fag!
What do you want to know?
What are we fucking doing tonight, man?
We have to celebrate this
at a sertanejo party.
Today is the day to enjoy the party,
like this...
We're going crazy tonight.
I want to see everybody excited.
- We're leaving soon.
- I'll start dressing up.
Aren't you dressed up, princess?
Okay, go.
Thanks for everything.
One for all...
All for one. One for all, all for one.
One for all, all for one.
Fuck, man.
Chug, chug, chug, chug.
Go!
Let's party!
- You've already noticed, right?
- What?
I don't know, you've already noticed
that thing with... your girl.
- She's flirting with me a lot.
- She's only looking at you.
It's like, man...
- I'm not with her.
- I didn't want to hook up with her.
I didn't want to...
Do whatever you want.
No, bro. I don't want to...
If you like her,
I'd never do such a thing.
No, be cool.
No, weren't you going to see...
We like each other, but it doesn't work...
Will you be mad
if I hook up with her?
I don't know, man. I have no idea.
No, no. I'm cool, no.
Man, do this for me...
- It was because...
- Man, I get sad.
You won't be as sad as I will be.
I won't hook up with her.
- Come on, man.
- That's it, man.
- You know, if I hook up with...
- Chill out.
Do you have a lighter?
Just in time. Do you have a smoke?
Talk to me, heart, how do you...
Do you want me to hold yours?
- Man, I was...
- Let me borrow the lighter?
I was talking to the guys. I didn't have
the chance to talk to you about this.
When I first got here, Nath,
I wanted to hook up with you pretty bad.
I talked to him, he was...
I noticed it, too...
I don't know, really,
I got the same feeling from you.
I talked to him and I said
I wanted to hook up with you
and asked him
if he would be mad if I did it.
Then he started to stall a bit.
He was totally stalling, like,
"No, I'm not with her, chill out,"
and so on.
I know that today you guys broke up.
I don't know how it happened...
And...
Then I said,
"Man, really, tell me the truth.
Would you mind if we hook up?"
He said, "I would."
I asked, "Then, you want to be her?"
He said, "I don't know."
He's like on the fence, you know?
We argued because I broke up with him.
That's it. I'll never be chosen
again by anybody.
I'm the one who's going to choose,
'cause I can.
I'm not bad-looking...
I'm not a fool. You know? No, bro...
- Exactly.
- Fuck him.
I'm going to go in.
If it happens, won't you get upset?
Of course not.
- Then give me a hug.
- It's sorted.
So, it's going to happen.
You don't have to peck me,
but I want a hug from you.
If it happens, please, don't be sad.
Of course not.
I admit to everything I feel and do.
Let's toast here.
There's a right time...
I got this for you to give to Nath.
Go there, act sexy and give her the drink.
Look at my brother.
What's up?
Are you nuts?
- It was like this, I had this.
- So...
He was selling whisky and...
This is Blondie's.
If she tells you, are you coming?
Are you throwing it away?
I'm throwing it away.
Can I throw it away?
You're not doing this to me...
You stole from... Hey, Blondie.
You... killed my vibe.
Go there, she's there.
You killed the vibe.
Man, you lost your flower.
You didn't accept the flower...
I thought he'd stolen from Blondie.
It's mine.
I got it for him to give to you.
Look, I'm going to tell you the truth.
You were very bad.
Forget her.
She doesn't deserve it.
- Give the flower to me.
- Man, you know nothing.
I do. You rejected his flower.
I thought he'd taken Blondie's flower.
Do you think he'd do this?
You have to know how to be complimented.
The boy didn't...
Jeez, these things don't amaze me anymore.
You're dumb. Tell me...
What a situation, huh?
Hey, let's have the afterparty at home.
Let's go.
Where's my flower?
My flower was torn to pieces.
- I can't see anything.
- This one got blurred.
I look fucking amazing in this picture.
Jeez, these pictures are crazy.
Say what you have to say.
Let's live one day at a time.
This bullshit again?
- What?
- You keep saying the same thing.
But you were the one who said this.
Make it work.
Me?
Let's go.
You're in, right?
Guys, I'm shocked. I'm shocked.
- I'm shocked.
- Tomás was very ethical.
I didn't find it cool.
He's asking Ramon
if he can hook up with Nath?
Girl, they broke up,
but he knows there's
something going on.
I just thought his approach's
a little different.
But it was ethical of him.
Girl, I think he had to ask Nathália,
since he's the one who wants her.
He didn't have to ask Ramon, like,
"Can I hook up with the girl
you're hooking up with?"
It's a good perspective.
Ethics. That's because among boys...
It's a guy thing, you know?
- Men stick together.
- Yes, guys, but...
The girl is there like a coin,
in the middle...
- No.
- She'll be like a coin if she wants some.
- Yeah.
She's been doing this at times.
She wants some.
But he said, "I want to hook up with her,
but my friend is over there."
Tomás was explaining himself to Ramon.
Why did he only talk to the guy?
- Why is that?
- Yeah... Yes.
It's a guy thing.
Let's try to understand.
So, men stick together
so they don't fight.
Nobody cares about anyone.
Of course they care.
Nobody gives up
fucking somebody because...
Stop it!
We don't express our feelings.
Carol, I disagree. Here's what happened.
Turns out one friend said,
"Man, I met an awesome person
and stuff..."
Then he says he's deeply in love.
Then I signed up on a dating app.
I found the guy there, but I didn't
recognize him. We started to talk,
and I remembered he was
that boy and scolded him,
"Man, you did this to my friend. My friend
likes you and you're on this app."
Even if I wanted to hook up
with him later,
I didn't do it.
I knew he was with my friend.
- I'm loyal to myself. I think...
- No.
I have a friend who says that.
If I didn't think this way...
If I didn't think like this,
he wouldn't have tried to kiss me because
he hugged me and came... you know?
Nathália did what she's used to doing.
She must've looked at Ramon,
I don't know what happened there.
Regardless if it's right or wrong,
he hit on her. What did she do?
Once again, she played, left,
looked to the side, laughed, mocked.
Do you think she always does it
to play with Ramon?
I think she's not playing with Ramon,
but with that situation, you know?
She wants to feel important, you know?
She wants to show off.
She was saying, "I'm hot,
I'm beautiful, I'm this, I'm that."
To me, the best-case scenario would be...
The best-case scenario would be
if she hooked up with him.
At least both of them wanted
the same thing.
She played with him.
In the end, the dude hit on her,
- and she ran away.
- Nathália is a player.
She's a player. She plays with everybody
and causes trouble in the entire house.
- What for?
- She likes to provoke.
She says somebody said something
about somebody else...
"I'm going to flirt
with the friend, cause trouble..."
Who thought they would never come back?
- Me.
- I never did.
Girl, I don't believe in...
I only believe in looseness.
No, girl, their kissing is different.
They like each other.
Even if she acts weird, she likes him.
Jealousy...
She's doing all that
because she likes him.
I think he doesn't like her.
- She hooked up with many guys.
- What guys?
- She didn't.
- She fights more than hooks up.
She did.
She summoned that guy from Goiânia.
But she had sex, then she got up.
She didn't want to.
She had sex with the guy...
Cool, she had sex and got up.
She didn't spend the night.
She didn't cuddle with him.
She brought that guy to make him jealous.
Carol, the best out of all of us.
I think she invited that friend of hers...
because she likes Ramon.
That's why she didn't stay until the end,
because she likes him.
She flirted with Tomás because of him.
She didn't hook up with Tomás
because of him.
She loves badly, but she likes him.
Will this relationship evolve?
I don't think so...
It will be this
on and off relationship forever.
I feel like slapping his face
and saying, "Wake up, you idiot."
Who are you in this situation?
Neither of those two, thank God.
- I'm the bean bag.
- He's João.
He's João and Blondie.
I think that when we love,
we have different strategies.
But she's not good at strategy, you know?
No, but that's too heavy.
It's not about strategy.
It's about knowing...
Like, if you love,
you need to know your limit.
Bro, your life is a war, right?
Her life is a war.
She's always coming up with a plan
to destroy the enemy.
The person she has
a relationship with is her enemy.
Bro, that's the best Titto comment ever.
Carol's life is like Battleship.
Carol is Sun Tzu, Art of War.
She manipulates...
"That man wants to fuck me?
I'm going to come up with a plan...
One mortar shell, if he comes..."
She's crazy, man, that woman.
I've never done...
To me, it's like, "I want it? Yes."
I don't like this strategy...
If I want it and she wants it, okay.
If not, "See ya later."
I understand he can have the hots
for other people...
But, man, I wouldn't care.
You don't care?
Would you allow it?
I'd be cool, because I know...
If I really like the guy.
I'm talking about real examples, okay?
If I like a guy, and he likes me,
We like each other.
That's his environment,
parties and bars.
I know he might be there.
But, deep down, he likes me.
So it's like, "Baby? What's going on?
Let's go, honey.
What about all these chicks?"
He's going to explain to me.
In the end, we'd be laughing about it.
So, you think cheating is okay?
It's not okay.
Attraction is one thing,
liking somebody is another.
People feel attracted...
Because of a flirting thing...
I learned one thing.
Human beings are not, how do we...
When we like only one person?
Monogamous. We're not.
It's natural we feel attracted to others.
But having the option to hook up
with another person
is totally different from just attraction.
We want to watch this.
1 for all
all for 1
I feel lazy, but it's a beautiful day.
It's nice, right? Fresh air...
What do you think about
going out of the house?
- I think it's great.
- Do you?
Thank you. So, let's go to the beach?
What's this? Wake up! Wake up, Blondie!
Let's go?
Let's go!
Let's go to the beach!
Look at that!
Let's drown...
You're crazy.
This beach is a nude beach... Naturalism.
Couples that want to, what is it called...
To get naked...
Don't do it...
Let's go.
Go, Luan!
Don't listen to this guy, man.
- I want to see if you're going.
- Me, too.
Just this fool won't go with the others?
Go, baby. Go.
I want to see the asses.
I'm going to take my glasses off.
Hey, Ramon!
His balls are going to hit the ground.
No!
No, your dick is going to be very tiny.
Look how João's is...
I can see it from here.
Where's the ass?
What a funny dick...
We want to see the front of your bodies!
But you have to shake it.
You've got to shake this dick!
- Yeah, man.
- It's here. That's what I like.
WELCOME
BABY
- Drink it.
- I said I wanted to talk, right?
Drink it!
I said I wanted to talk.
There, bro, can you answer for us?
I said I wanted to talk, but I didn't.
- I couldn't...
- Okay, baby. You're forgiven.
Go. Cell phone?
Yeah.
Hi, everybody, how are you?
Once again I'll need you guys at the bar.
Tonight I'm counting
on the girls here. Okay?
See you then.
This is going...
Good one, Ricardão!
I wonder if he's going to separate
the house tonight.
We're the bosses.
That'd be crazy.
But, for real, those two times...
- For example, those two times...
- In a good way.
If we were here by ourselves,
we would rock this place in two days.
I was single for two days with João,
we fucked four chicks.
That's what I need.
Tonight I'm having sex.
They let the boys out, fuck!
WE WENT TO THE RAP PARTY
WE LOVE YOU
Guys, I'm glad for this warmup,
you're family!
That's the best night.
Tonight's the night.
Let's rock and roll.
- I think that's not enough.
- Let's get some air...
I can't right now, but later
I'll drink with you guys, I promise.
As soon as we're off the clock,
we're going to have a drink.
- Are you going to have a drink?
- Of course.
- It's a deal.
- Do we have a deal?
Let's do this.
Okay, boys.
Call me if you need me.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
What's up, baby?
What's up, girl...
We'll have one drink with them
when we're off the clock.
- You are?
- We are... All of us.
I wonder if the guy from Minas is leaving.
- He wants you.
- You're cute.
Tonight, I'm erasing everybody's memory.
This is the real "one for all," right?
One for all.
This is the "one for all."
One for all!
One for all and all for one!
Come in...
Hey, it's her birthday...
Let's dance for her.
In the middle.
Dance for her.
It's her birthday.
Start, Luan.
You start.
What do you do here?
Hey... What's your name?
Nice to meet you, I'm Luan.
I guess we have to enjoy this...
What happens here, stays here.
We trust each other, so... Forget this.
Tomorrow we sort this out
if anybody wants to say...
Nobody is saying anything.
That's it.
The same thing...
What happens at the party,
stays at the party...
Nobody is going to scream.
- You know?
- Yes.
If they ask... We say,
"Awesome, we went up on the table
- and that's it."
- I recall
Nathália arriving
and I was with another woman...
Are you sleeping on my bed?
That's messed up.
At least, let me see your face.
She wasn't okay.
Get them?
Can you... give me a shot?
One shot, you know?
I'm going to pour just a little.
I swear.
Just a little.
Let's see this...
You've got to represent.
What I say and do
are two different things.
I'm going to pour just a little.
Is it just a little?
If that belongs to the bar...
All friends have to drink together.
This is partnership, right?
Can you open your mouth, please?
Those could be us, you know?
The four of them drank. Congratulations.
I want to invite you guys to our house,
for a warmup.
If you're doing nothing.
Are you in? The four of you?
Deal?
- After this?
- Yes, after this.
He looks like he has a six pack.
Does he, man? Let's see...
Well...
Can I see it again?
Applause.
You deserve more than applause.
Why?
Do I deserve you?
I think you do.
Let's go to the afterparty!
This is going to be wild, man.
Tonight we're the bosses!
We're the fucking bosses!
Come here.
Welcome.
Welcome to our humble home.
- This place is rad, right?
- Make yourselves at home, boys.
This place is fucking awesome.
- Is it yours?
- Yeah.
It's ours.
Here is the warm pool, the cold pool.
- Is this warm? This?
- The drinks.
- Let's drink.
- Have you been here?
Take a sip...
- Floripa?
- Floripa.
Floripa is on fire!
Our house requires...
Every man has to take his shirt off.
Who's going to be first?
I guess it's you, Vitor.
The room is rad!
Look, come here, buddy.
Didn't you say you were my buddy?
I told you I'm going to trust you.
"We went to the rap party..."
Let's go...
"We love you." Look at my boy.
Me and him. This is him, look.
- Is this your boyfriend?
- He's my man. Yes.
Okay, and where is he?
He went to the rap party.
He seems nice.
You guys have to know him.
WE WENT TO THE RAP PARTY!
LOVE YOU
I've never played this...
That was my first shot, beginner's luck.
Ouch.
Where's Nath?
Let's go to the pool.
- Where are we going?
- To the pool.
And I'm going fully dressed?
Take the pants off.
Why are you leaving?
Man, you have to wait for the boys.
They'd love you guys, really.
- Really?
- It's true, man.
I believe it, but we're leaving.
They'd love you guys.
All of you... They'd love you.
- See you next time, okay?
- Okay.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
- God bless you...
- Go for it, have fun.
- God bless.
- Bye-bye.
Yeah, you, too.
- What is your name?
- Amanda.
- Amanda?
- Amanda Meire.
Amanda Meire...
Nice to meet you, Amanda Meire.
I'm Ramon.
- Do you live here too?
- I'm from Floripa.
- You, too?
- No, I'm from Rio.
Really? Why are you here?
I came down here to enjoy holidays.
Let's go, man...
I can tell we're in this together.
I see it this way...
Tell her she's not coming with us.
- Because she's going to talk...
- That makes no sense...
Got it?
I've already seen you with her.
It's the second time I've come here.
I'm going to fuck the hell out of you.
You're going to sleep
with your girlfriend.
He's not going to hook up with...
It has to be me, right? It has to be me...
Your friend is in trouble here.
Four men looking at her.
She's attracting attention.
You four, go grab her, she's in need.
Bia dates a guy, I know,
who's cool wherever he is.
Oh, my God.
It's hard to be myself.
I'm all wet.
On the ground?
Tay, don't do that.
Tay.
Get up, baby.
- Go to bed.
- Why are you up here?
Let's go to bed, okay?
I'm fine... Who let you come up here?
Me. Get a grip. It's cool...
Leave me here.
No, let's go to...
I don't want to.
You'll make me lie down on the floor.
The floor is the limit.
That's my saying.
Buddy, the floor makes me drunk.
- Can we lie down there and talk?
- No.
- Just talk, don't worry, bro.
You know we get along.
Man, Murilo is at Art's.
I won't do anything, thinking about him.
He's an asshole.
You are.
The kitchen is full of men.
Jeez, I missed you, baby.
There are some men in the kitchen.
That's not possible.
Hey.
- Cooking our food.
- What?
I don't believe this.
What's this, man?
I can't believe
you're eating our food, man.
Where's Tay? Where's Tay?
Where's Tay?
- Where's Tay?
- Sleeping.
Great, that's good.
Good to know.
I'll cook for the others.
See, I hate these things.
If I wanted to go to bed, I'd be in bed.
Man, go to bed.
I'm going to take a look upstairs
because...
What's up?
This is my boyfriend.
- Murilo?
- No, I'm Luan.
Fuck, man. We were talking.
I said, "This is Murilo."
Is that Luan?
What's up?
- Did you get here alone?
- Yes.
Where's Tay, man?
- She's in the bathroom.
- She's just gone downstairs.
- Tay?
- Man, he annoyed me.
Which guy annoyed you?
There was a guy up there,
I was sleeping, and he was there.
Who was the guy who was upsetting my girl?
- Was it you?
- Go figure...
- Not upsetting...
- Was it you?
Then bounce, or else there's going
to be some ass kicking here.
Thank God your chick was sleeping.
Then go downstairs.
You're in our house, you know?
Respect that.
- Take off.
- But...
Take off now.
Or we're going to fight.
Fuck it.
She's just said there was a guy
upsetting her, and she wanted to sleep.
- Who's your chick?
- Take off.
Take off.
- Who is she?
- Go home, man.
Leave.
Leave now.
Or else things are going
to get fucking ugly, bro.
Things are going
to get fucking ugly.
It has nothing to do with you. Come here.
- I'm cool, man.
- I know you are.
The problem is that Tay...
Tay and Bia have boyfriends.
The guys are going to get jealous
of the others, got it?
What is this, man? How rude...
How rude.
Rude, my ass!
You know the party where you were at?
I'm the one who plays there, man.
I was playing there, man.
So, please...
You deserve...
You have to respect me.
Nobody has to respect you.
Respect is essential.
Please, get out.
Or else there'll be a fight.
Why?
I'm going to call you an Uber.
Was it that "chubby"?
- Was it him who woke you up?
- Yes.
Fucking asshole!
- He's an asshole.
- Get back here. Stay with me.
I'll stay close because you're wonderful.
I fucking love you.
Me, too.
I'm upset tonight. I hate being woken up.
You have no idea how much I love you.
That's cute.
I want a kiss.
...you wouldn't hook up with anybody.
I don't want to go downstairs.
If you don't take off...
If you don't take off, I'll kick your ass.
Who woke you up?
It was him, right?
He woke you up, he has to leave.
Go into the room.
Man...
If you don't take off, buddy, you...
- Hey, is that your woman?
- Fuck you.
Fuck you, kid!
Get the fuck out.
- Get out!
- Easy.
Get out.
Don't touch me.
Easy, easy.
Nobody is touching anybody.
You're a fucking jerk.
Get out.
Are you nuts?
Go home!
- Easy.
- Get out of my way.
Get out of my way.
Get the hell out.
Take your hand off me.
I am what? I am what?
- What?
- What's up?
It's okay.
Get your hand off me, bro.
Luan, it's over, I'm going out...
You're next. Are you nuts?
- Are you an idiot, bro?
- Be cool.
Are you what?
What did I say?
Come here.
Are you nuts?
These guys are facing us. Are you nuts?
Do you want to get in trouble?
Come fucking outside.
- I won't go.
- You're leaving.
You don't have an option...
What the hell?
You don't have the option.
Leave it to me.
You have no options.
- You know me...
- I don't fucking know you.
SECURITY
You don't have the option, kid.
Stay outside.
Fucking leave, fucking leave,
fucking leave.
You know? Get out, buddy. Get out.
- Go outside.
- Brother...
Chill out, be cool.
I didn't pick this fight at the moment...
I know, brother. Don't worry.
You weren't even here
when the fight started.
Let me talk to you.
If he leaves, then I'll leave...
- Can I talk to you?
- Yes, go ahead.
Are you seeing these bad vibes?
I want to talk to the boys because...
Can I speak?
Nath and I brought everybody here.
Nath and I caused all of it.
I fucking liked you.
Let's not stay here.
It's a big mess, the guys are not...
I want to talk to you later, you know?
No, I'm leaving. Chill out.
Why did you stay downstairs?
When Tay was sleeping?
Was I supposed to leave them?
You were the hostess?
Everybody went to bed...
- But you and Blondie?
- Yes...
Blondie was upstairs in the room?
She was...
And you were alone
in the pool like a crazy person?
All right...
Can I tell you something?
What's the name of that game
we played here?
When Blondie scored a goal, I did this...
- I gave him a peck.
- Why?
Why were you the only one
to give him a peck? Why you?
I don't know...
Okay...
Let me tell you...
Don't blame the others
because Bia would've done it...
I'm not blaming anybody.
- I'm telling you, bro.
- It's okay.
Let's move on.
It's cool...
Ramonzinho, there's a bunk bed here
if you want to sleep here.
I'm sleeping there.
You're kidding.
I'm going to sleep here alone.
Bro...
Those people are crazy, repressed.
Everything is funny...
Yes, that's fucking true.
I could have hooked up with all of them.
I have to stop being a fool.
That was intense. Good night.
Murilo got there, saw some guys
and wanted to cause trouble.
I think that I'd get there
and would get kind of mad.
- I swear to God...
- You would.
I wouldn't be mad.
It's that same old story...
Tay is cool.
The only girls going hard are Nath, right?
And Blondie.
Because the other two are committed.
But until you explain
that things are not what they seem...
You're going to look for things
that don't exist, right?
Look for things...
- I think that...
- What was taken?
Mariano, have you ever lost anything?
He always says that...
Are you a farmer?
Yes, I am.
I'd make a scene. I'd tell the woman off.
I think he was refined.
Because I wouldn't leave that way.
"I'll call you an Uber,
and you're getting in the Uber.
Okay, buddy?"
What did you say?
What were you going to say?
"I'm going to call you an Uber,
and you're getting in the Uber, okay?"
And she'd leave, right, Carol?
"Get in the Uber,
it's better for you."
Man, I think that "chubby"
deserved to be beaten a lot.
When the girls went...
Twenty times, he said, "Get out."
"Why, man? Why?"
When the girls went...
- Get their ass kicked.
- When the girls went...
He didn't have to go upstairs.
That chick was sleeping.
That girl was drunk, you know?
Sorry, I don't want to separate
this by gender, nothing like that.
But where me and my friends come from...
That thing doesn't exist.
You're in this house,
my five friends
and in a house full of women.
Men show up.
I'm in the bedroom with a girl.
My friends get in trouble downstairs.
They kicked out.
Am I staying there?
I leave with my buddies.
Are you nuts, man?
You could lose the love of your life.
Baby, let me talk. Let's say there's me...
Me, Pabllo
and Carol with you at a party...
I'd leave with you guys.
I pick a fight
with some friend of yours.
Would you leave your boy?
- Sure.
- Obviously.
Are you nuts?
He's not part of my life.
True boys are rare nowadays.
I'm not needy.
Depends on the situation in the bedroom.
If things are on fire,
you're not going to leave.
I don't even have a boner for this.
If I'm there,
and things get messed up...
It's over. You're crazy, bro.
If it's the police, then...
I would leave. Unless the guy is very...
I'd forget about it...
You're banging a lot.
Then you hear a riot.
"Let me see if it's the police."
It's not, it's trouble.
Do I want to get involved in gossip?
Man, at that moment...
Thais is perfect. I could be in her life.
Do you think I won't help my friends
because I'm banging?
I'd stop.
Let me tell you... Thais fought.
Do you know why?
Every day there's gossip.
She was going to lose,
and there'd be another...
There was a mess going on.
Just finish your sex and then go help.
If I wasn't there,
I'd help with something.
I guess I'll always help.
If I wasn't there.
Then the man is sucking you off a lot,
you're there coming...
Excuse me.
And if he wouldn't come with me,
to help, then, "Goodbye, baby."
I'm not that needy.
I'm independent.
- I'm self-sufficient.
- Bianca, life coach.
I can't believe...
My God.
Nothing...
Oh, my God...
Only one more episode.
I want to take a leak.
She wanted
to be in a soap opera.
What is that?
I can't believe.
There's only one more episode, man.
- She's a real actress, guys.
- No, please, no.
No!
Director, you asked her...
No, director.
She even lay down.
What did you do to her?
Please.
Lucas,
What did you do to her?
Need help, girl?
I'm not going to see Murilo banging, man.
We're going to enjoy
our last day in big style.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
There's got to be trouble.
Asses being kicked. Oh, my God!
Two guys or a guy and a girl?
It was a girl.
I guess that was an editing trick.
I think they were rolling on the lawn
because they were happy.
No, we're pretending...
You roll on the lawn because you're happy?
At Coachella, I rolled on the grass.
Coachella? You were wasted, stoned.
Anyway, when we're happy,
we roll on the lawn.
You saw that girl kicking the door?
Looked like Taynara.
I guess it was Bia.
You think it was Bia?
Bia was...
You saw Bia having an argument.
I think it was with Luan.
Did you see the boy...
Did you see the guy in that week's fight?
That guy who did this to him...
That guy from the house,
who said, "Are you facing me?"
Do you know what happens
on the last episode?
Everybody will find out, baby.
They'll find out the boys hooked up
with everybody in the party.
Last episode. Anything can happens.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that?