I'm super excited about today.
Yeah, me, too!
For Christ's sake!
So, guys, how are you?
Have you seen Carol?
Is Carol coming?
- Right here.
- What's up, guys?
What's happening, sis?
Hey, hi!
I wonder if they'll argue
and kiss a lot today.
- I think so.
- I'm scared, you know?
I'm checking out Pabllo's look.
Look at those boots.
I'm shocked.
The size of the skirt is still worse.
Let me take a look. Hi! How are you?
Look! What the hell? You're slutty.
That's perfect.
Her butt is saying, "Hi, how are you?"
Are you ready to start this thing?
I'm very excited.
I'm nervous.
I'm anxious to see
what happens next.
I want to see a fight.
Is everybody ready for the second episode?
Let's do it.
- Wild and Free: Florianópolis.
- I can't wait.
A lot has happened, right?
Bia had an argument with Luan...
Luan slept on the couch...
Nothing but trouble.
It's a circus. I'm shocked.
I was shipping this couple
and now I'm un-shipping them.
Then they had a falling out. Remember,
it's eight friends on vacation in Floripa.
No actors, no script, nothing.
We can't just start shipping.
Let's watch this episode.
We wouldn't know...
There's no telling now.
Let's watch it.
- Hit that play.
- Hit that play, Bia.
- Wow, Bia!
- I love that play.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
Fuck.
Shit, man, it's freaking cold.
Shit, bro! Nice and cool, huh?
Nice.
This is great. You know, when you're
feeling... unbalanced, kind of weird?
Yeah, me, too.
Just breathe, man.
Breathe, look at the sun, feel it...
Feel the grass.
You know that thing I said?
I wasn't telling the truth.
I was pissed...
Not so much for Ramon,
but for Bia, you know?
I was pissed.
I know, it sucks. I know what you mean.
I don't let stuff get to me, though.
Me neither. I'm going on "fuck you" mode.
Exactly.
At least I'm going to try.
Why are you here?
You're here to have a good time.
Nath has this look in her eyes,
kind of... It's not very sexy.
I passed out, too.
Remember when you fell down?
Remember when you grabbed me
when I was with that girl?
You grabbed him good.
She didn't cry for me either, right?
Just like...
Man! No... I didn't cry for him.
Of course you didn't.
Nobody saw that last night.
Did you sleep well?
I fell asleep snuggling...
with Nath and Bia.
And I slept well. Alone.
I saw that. I woke up to go
to the bathroom and saw you alone.
I couldn't resist.
I came over to give you a kiss.
You really thought
I was hooking up with Luan?
I still think you're gonna.
No, I'm not.
Of course you are. This is a free country.
You can do whatever you want.
- Exactly.
- So... but...
You didn't have to act
like that yesterday.
I was upset with you and, like...
I'm not upset with you or him, right?
- With me? I didn't do anything.
- Right...
Pass the olive oil, please?
We should wait for the girls, right?
Oh, man. I'm starving.
I'm not in a good mood, okay?
Wait? You should start.
- What?
- I think you can start eating.
Good, let's eat, then.
I wanted to talk to you guys.
Sorry I was rude with last night.
I was... Shit...
You were angry, bro. The booze...
I can't accept some stuff.
I was chilling, minding
my own business, man.
You're pointing a finger at me...
Be yourself.
You're being fake.
But I am being myself.
Oh, yeah? Fine. Be yourself.
I think it's nice to admit what you did.
That's it.
Life goes on.
I'm sorry, I was rude to you guys.
Man, just be who you are, seriously.
One thing I don't like is
talking about what I did.
I don't like gossip. I was helping
someone and, like... Forget it.
Forget it, no worries.
Sorry. I slept alone,
didn't have breakfast with you.
I'm not staying in this vibe.
Keep that vibe.
Forget it.
I like seeing you like that.
You dog!
Keep that vibe.
- Thank you.
- All good.
You've got a great vibe.
We're here for each other,
for one another, bro.
It happened.
You've slept it off,
woke up feeling better. Relax.
I'm apologizing to the girls, too.
You are awesome.
Yeah, man, way to go.
It's all good.
Seriously, you should have
a chat with Bia, man.
If you have to break up, no problem.
But the friendship
and love for you all will stay,
and I want it to grow positively.
Of course.
That's what it's all about, man.
That's obvious.
You guys keep fighting,
but the initial problem is still there.
You don't solve it, you get drama
all over again, like yesterday.
I was talking to the guys...
It's freaking cold.
Bia, I was talking to them,
apologizing for my behavior.
I was out of line with you, too.
I'm sorry.
Let me give you a hug.
I want us to be good.
Just like a family.
No hard feelings. Nice!
Way to go.
Are you apologizing, too?
I'm sorry, too, for everything.
Can we kiss already?
This is good food.
Isn't it? Guys, I can't eat it all.
- I can.
- No, I'm like dynamite.
Come on, then. Let's do it.
Slow down, I'm eating it.
I called dibs.
Are you having problems?
Not me.
It's all falling down.
Is it possible?
Are we going on a boat?
I can't believe it.
Crazy, man.
For real?
- Look at that.
- Hi!
Hi, guys, how are you?
Hey! We're fine. All good?
What's up? Good morning.
- Doing good?
- Right. How are you guys?
Just fine.
Excited.
I'm Ricardo, your bar manager.
RICARDO
BAR MANAGER
- Perfect.
- Great.
Today, I'll show you the place.
Fun!
I'd like you to see it.
I have a boat for us.
I already like the boss.
- Awesome!
- Can we go now?
- What a job!
- Now!
- All right.
- Wonderful.
- Can we drink on the job?
- Can we?
We'll talk about it later.
Let's go to the boat.
- Come on!
Crazy good, man.
Let's go!
Guys, let's go to the bar. Easy now.
- Okay.
- On the sand, over there.
Look at this. Gosh, I don't want to work.
I want booze, please.
Yeah, it's all right.
Oops. We can't.
Go to work!
I forgot.
Well, guys. I wanted
to talk about your tasks here.
Shoot.
Waiting tables
and preparing drinks at the bar.
This job is what's going
to pay for your parties.
- That's what we need right now.
- Yes!
Right now.
But today...
It's expensive...
...is the only day you get
to enjoy the place.
Today, I'm paying the tab. It's all free.
- I think I'm going to cry.
- Fuck!
But we can't get in trouble, right?
We're going to drink today, shit!
Welcome, thank you.
Thank you.
I want to talk to you.
I like being with you,
get to know you better.
We had something good going on.
Somehow, we went from heaven to hell in...
In a second.
Are we going to be
doing that all the time?
We talked about it, but it happened.
I need more than that, you know?
Because I'm going to end up getting hurt.
I only asked to be respected, got it?
I really...
I just want to enjoy myself.
I just want to be happy, you know?
You wanna hook up with her?
Go ahead, I'm cool.
When you make out with her, I'd rather...
Are you jealous?
Yes.
Why are you jealous?
Don't know.
Trying to understand.
Do you like me?
Yes, I do. I told you that.
I'm not easy to get, you know?
Cheers, then. Are we good?
Are you going to be all right?
Yes, we're good.
What do you want to do?
I want to enjoy,
I want to party, go crazy.
One more shot, please.
How's it going? Good? No?
I actually like the one
in the jeans.
The one sitting down?
Standing up, jeans and glasses.
But I'm sure he's got a girlfriend.
No, but...
He's hot. Very handsome.
If I get him here, would you kiss him?
Out of the blue?
In a heartbeat, brother.
Hey, what's up, bro? Man, there's a chick
over there, she's hot... She's with us.
She kind of likes you.
I asked her if... She said,
"He doesn't need to... He's hot,
no need to ask. Just kiss me."
Look, it's the blonde in white pants.
Oh, yeah?
- Are you in?
- Let's go.
I'll go with you.
Come with me. Go ahead.
Look how gorgeous he is, man.
You said it.
Man! She's a fucking hurricane!
Wow, man! I told you!
What's going on here? I can't believe it.
Now you can get to know each other.
I can't believe it.
I have to kiss you, man.
Today's the day.
Blondie! Oh, my God!
I can't believe my eyes. Fuck!
You're welcome?
I love you.
There, there.
Enough already. You guys go chat.
- What's your name?
- Thais, pleased to meet you.
She's shaking all over.
Blondie is fast.
Come on. Let's go talk over there.
I'm in the middle of a game.
No, you're not. Come on.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Come on, give me your hand.
I'm sorry about ruining your game.
I hope it was for a good cause.
I hope so, too.
Yeah? Let's find out.
What do you think?
I'm thinking about the game.
I like to play.
You're here thinking...
- Do you play pool?
- Yes, at home.
Let's play, then.
- Okay. But can we kiss beforehand?
- No.
That's not fun. So, if I win...
I'm... We'll kiss.
You win, we kiss.
A little kiss.
If I win the game of pool, we'll kiss.
Whoa! What if you lose?
If you lose, you shut up.
There's no cue and there's no chalk, shit!
Are you scared already? Go on!
If she beats him...
- What does this look like?
- I'm cold.
You, of all people?
Are you going to play games with me now?
This is no game.
If you don't want it,
I'll stop coming on to you.
No, I do want it.
- Do you?
- I do.
No...
But... I don't want to be an idiot.
You got this, man.
Go, João!
João!
Tay, what do you think of all this?
Now kiss him.
Thank you, my fans, for rooting for me.
Let's go to the after, all right?
Today, we're going to party hard.
Someone stop me.
You've got to drink it all.
Tonight the room upstairs is mine.
Blondie called dibs on it.
It's mine! But we can share it.
Let's do it. It's going to be beautiful.
The four of us.
- An orgy?
- Yeah.
Shit, let's go home.
Let's go, girls. I can't wait.
To the right... Here. Get that seat right.
Holy crap, you're fast.
Come on.
I'm going to ask him to be my boyfriend.
Shit, did I just hear that?
Are you sure?
- I'm going to ask him to be my boyfriend.
- You are a couple now?
My love.
Let's go. Go!
Don't go kissing yet.
Get the cachaça first.
Holy shit, what a mouth.
Give it to the monster.
Chug it down, Jack Sparrow.
Holy crap. This is fucking strong.
Drink it and go upstairs,
I'm going to get you good.
Hey, you guys.
Hey. Welcome, feel at home, okay?
And there's food.
- João?
- What is it, bro?
Where's Ramon?
Introduce your wife to them.
- To whom?
To the bedroom...
Come here,
I want to show you my girlfriend.
Oh, shit.
True...
Joyce, I'm coming.
Here, look! Here.
Someone get a pizza, please?
I can't believe it.
You're not jealous, are you?
It's Joyce.
He doesn't hook up with anyone.
Only Joyce.
Man...
Joyce...
Put her in the bathroom, right here.
She killed Joyce.
Poor Joyce. Joyce, don't be upset.
Don't be upset.
Turn around, Joyce.
She'll turn around...
She's facing the wall,
she won't see it.
I'm going to apply concealer on Joyce.
Man, you're funny.
It's just that... Look,
I think I deserve more than she does.
Goodbye, Joyce Kelly.
I'm going to eat a lot of fucking pizza.
I bet nobody here can eat a raw egg.
- No.
- I have never eaten a raw egg.
I don't want one.
I bet nobody will eat it.
If you eat
a raw egg...
She'll eat your ass.
Yeah!
Holy crap!
She's game.
Daddy will take the bet
because he can't take the pressure.
She's game.
You're screwed.
Man, he really ate the raw egg. Fuck!
Wow, he really did.
She's going to sleep here.
She's kissing with the egg...
Wait, I'm going to burp a chick.
Listen, here's the thing.
I don't want to fuck you anymore.
I want to hang out with you.
I want to be...
I don't want to fuck in the living room.
Please, that's all I ask.
No, João.
All right.
Then, stop talking, man.
Look at those two over there.
They're idiots. I'm talking to you.
Is anyone there with you?
Can you see them gossiping?
Gossiping, man?
Are they going to have sex?
It's their problem...
They're not enjoying.
Brother, stay strong.
Stop! Hey... No!
It's okay.
Stay cool. Son of a bitch.
The chick eats raw egg, man.
I drank egg, man, all right? Screw you.
I love this house.
I'm glad that...
I just wanted to talk to you, man.
Maybe hang out, that's all.
Why can't you talk right here?
I don't want to talk in front
of everybody. I want it in private.
You never thought
you were going to meet me.
I like you a lot, man.
Half for you, half for me.
I like you, too, it's just that...
There's nothing we can do, you know?
I just want to know one thing.
Do you want to do it or not?
Don't be mad, man. We're enjoying
this moment. You're leaving...
I'm not mad. I'm just sad.
Man...
You're not enjoying because...
I was enjoying until now.
You're wonderful, man.
It's freaking cold here.
It's cold, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Live and enjoy the moment.
Do you want to spend the night here, too?
No, I'm going home.
Really? Why? Stay here tonight.
- I can't.
- Tomorrow is a new day.
Why can't you stay?
Do you have a cigarette?
Shit, it's inside.
- Because I'm grounded.
- I'm going to smoke now, too.
Why is that?
I went out last Saturday
and didn't come home
until 5:00 in the afternoon on Sunday.
She's still a baby, she's 20...
How old are you?
Twenty-two.
Jesus Christ!
Don't be shocked,
she's the love of my life.
I love them young.
Shit. I'm precocious.
So you like them all young?
You're naughty.
No, especially the girls...
The ones from Floripa.
By the way, do you want to spend the
night here? Or do you want to leave?
But it seems that you want me to leave.
No, it's not that. I'm going to bed now.
I don't know if you're leaving,
if you want to stay overnight...
I want to sleep with you.
It doesn't matter
if nothing happens.
I just want to sleep with you.
Okay, then, come.
What if we keep kissing? Don't you see?
One day at a time. One step at a time.
Let's enjoy what we have now.
Man, let's... Let me smoke first.
- Okay, go.
- You can't. You stay right here.
Okay, but my boot got stuck.
Stay put, I'll be right back. Stay warm.
No, I'm going to the kitchen to see if...
So, now, how's João going...
Do you think he's going to get lucky?
You guys are loud.
I think he is going to get laid.
I don't think he is.
How about the pressure
we put on her with the raw egg?
Oh, my God! Oh, yes!
I told you, guys!
Just shoot me. I don't want to see.
Oh, my God!
Hard to believe.
- I can't believe that.
- Guys... He...
When I'm partying hard
and my alcohol levels are above my neck...
If someone said to me,
"I don't want...
Let's just talk..."
What would I say? I'd just say no, okay?
Snuggling in bed
with someone when I'm drunk?
- Talk? Right...
- No.
So, I think she...
She didn't want to
and he tried to convince her
using some lame excuse.
He should have
been more candid
and say "Let's go upstairs alone."
Don't you think, Carol?
Yes, but she didn't wanna.
The guy couldn't be like,
"Come upstairs, I want to fuck you."
He should have said,
"You told me to eat an egg.
You said that if I ate a raw egg
You'd do it."
Hold on. Titto,
have you ever used that line?
- I think she wants...
- What?
Have you ever used this line?
"Let's go over there, I just wanna talk."
The moment he said...
I never said,
"Let's go over there, I wanna talk."
I did say, "It's so noisy here,
I can't hear you."
Everybody wants to...
I'd love that, I'd say I'm deaf.
"It's noisy here, I can't hear.
Let's find a quieter place."
"I'll go, Titto, I'm deaf!"
I'd start to shout right away.
I feel embarrassed for João.
- No, João...
- That's bad.
João is a big disappointment.
Is he a Pisces? He's a Pisces.
No, he's desperate.
Do you wanna know his sign?
Pisces men are like that.
He's desperate, for sure.
He's desperate.
He is very emotional.
- Emotional?
- Absolutely.
He's in total despair.
No...
He's emotional, every emotion is extreme.
He was trying to get laid, at any cost.
That's exactly right.
He'll even cry to get laid.
He was desperately trying...
He probably has blue balls.
Tears of horniness.
- Let me say this.
- I think...
They hit the floor...
And he cries...
Listen, I think that João,
he may be this or that, but...
He's a key player in this thing.
Obviously.
He's a friend who makes it fun.
He didn't buy into the whole drama...
There's always a friend...
It has to be João.
...who doesn't get laid.
The problem is not João getting laid.
The problem is
he cries when he doesn't get laid.
I like a man who cries.
Man, Carol is the most peculiar person
I have ever met.
She doesn't kiss, she just has sex.
She sleeps with her legs open.
She said she likes men who cry
and naked men wearing ties.
Men who are serious and young...
I like a man who cries.
I like them...
I once said "I love you"
to someone just to kiss,
just to have sex.
Wow.
What's the worst thing
you guys have done to get laid?
You said "I love you"
to a person you'd just met?
No, two days later.
I pretended to be
friends with them.
It's just too much, saying "I love you..."
To get laid, that's fair game.
It is a bit too much.
Men are silly.
You'll believe anything we say.
What's the worst thing you've done
to get laid?
Something you've done, for sex.
Man, I bought a very expensive video game.
A video game?
It cost me 2,500 reais.
She has the best stories.
A video game for 2,500 reais
and I never touched it.
To give to the boy.
No, it wasn't, like, a person.
Several people...
I wanted to lure people in...
I got it.
Like, "Let's play video game in my house."
And you played
Mortal Kombat in your bed.
- I see...
- Got it?
Shit, man.
He plays the video game
and you end it in bed.
But it wasn't one person,
but a collective frame-up.
- Like a trap?
- She did that...
A trap.
How did she lure the boys in?
Mariano.
You're a married man now and all...
But in the old days,
when you were 15...
You wanna play with the Xbox?
Oh, boy. I have done so much shit.
- Anything shocking?
- The worst?
I've hitched a hike in a bone truck.
I traveled 50 miles in a truck,
from one city to the next.
In a truck full of ox bones...
- Were you in the cab?
- No, in the...
In the cargo compartment?
Nice to meet you, it was me.
Did you kill someone?
No, I got to the city...
I took a shower, right?
- Did it work?
- It did.
That was some weird stuff.
Riding on a bone truck to get laid.
I think it was hot.
Imagine this man coming to you
smelling of bones.
He gets there with a femur in his hand...
"Honey, I'm home!"
It's like going to bed
with Fred Flintstone.
I would say, "Don't bathe."
I think the video game story
is what made my nipples hard.
- What?
- Video game.
My nipples are hard, see?
You're drunk.
The perfect trap.
It's going to be there forever.
The question is, does it work?
- Sure.
- The video game or the sex?
Yay.
Did you get some sleep?
- No.
- I didn't.
No?
I didn't sleep well at all.
Where's your man?
He just won't leave.
I think he took it seriously when I said
I'd take him in my luggage.
- Yes.
- How do you feel?
I don't know.
Have you talked to him?
I'll talk to him.
He's going to... He's hot.
He's hot, a prince.
He loves snuggling.
He turned his head...
Don't you want to get his number?
What are you gonna say to him?
I don't know. I'm not good
at asking people to leave.
Just say, "It's time to say goodbye."
Bye!
- Guys, look at Blondie.
- Look at Blondie.
- That's why it didn't work.
Blondie will dump the guy.
Yes, it's Blondie.
I'm going to work soon.
- You guys are working today?
- Yes, soon.
Is everybody going?
Yes, we're going to start getting dressed.
We're going to get dressed and all.
Maybe I'll take a shower before I leave.
I think I'm leaving, too.
Do you know where your stuff is? No.
Do you want... Come on, I'll help you.
I guess I do. I'm going
to look for my things.
Bye, prince!
Are the girls upstairs?
Hey, Blondie!
Good morning, João.
I'm back.
Come on, I'll get you now.
Come on, come in strong.
Hello? Hi, how are you? Now?
All right. Thank you.
We'll be there soon. Bye.
Guys, we have to pick four people
to go to work today, in an hour.
Let's draw lots?
I'll go, no problem.
But we have to draw...
Everybody could go.
- Let's draw...
- Yes.
Two guys and two girls.
Two or one!
- Two girls...
- Right.
- Two girls and two men.
- Show your hands!
Zero or one! Zero or one!
Two or one!
Go, Nath!
Are you two going?
- Yes.
- Cool.
- Guys...
- Are you going, too?
Fuck! It's going to be badass, man.
Let's go to work, huh?
God's children also have to work, right?
God's children also have to work.
For example, if it's necessary...
If it's necessary, sure... Fuck!
How about the four of us
take this time to go see Floripa?
- Let's do it.
- Yeah.
Watch the sunset.
Wow. Let's do it, it's really good.
We have 20 minutes
to get dressed and be ready.
Let's go see the sunset.
Wow, that's top.
Let's do it.
Girls in front, guys behind.
We're in charge today.
Sounds good. You guys are the bosses.
We're here to obey.
You're here to obey.
You know it.
Would you like me to get the door for you?
Nice!
Man, I've never been in a car like this.
Fucking good!
Play the game.
Look, the boss looks mad.
Good afternoon.
Hello, guys.
- How are you?
- Good, you?
- All good.
How are you? Do you remember
I told you the job started today?
Yes.
Dress up, get the bar ready,
the customers are coming in.
Let's go.
Sounds good.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
You look so handsome.
Well... Fuck, yeah.
Things are going to get crazy.
Guys? Is the lounge ready?
We're good to go.
You got it, right?
Good service, a smile on your face,
come to me if you have any questions.
- All right.
- All right?
Feel free to greet them, too.
Welcome them.
Hello, welcome.
Hey, bro, what's up?
I'm Ramon, how are you?
If you need more chairs,
I can get them for you.
Thank you.
It's five sex...
Do you like "Sex on the beach"?
Man, you're something else.
So, I want to know...
Where are we going?
I'm in charge today.
Can we trust you?
You can trust me.
Are we getting any booze?
Guys, we're here.
We're here.
Look at the view, man. Sick!
Gratitude.
Great.
It's good to be out of the house.
Go for a ride, right?
What are we doing tonight?
We'll drink.
I wonder if the guys will join us tonight.
- Heck, yeah.
- Of course.
Let's do this thing. Let's go.
Come on.
Can I sit down?
Sure. Be my guest.
Where are you from?
I was born here, but I don't live here.
Where do you live?
Do you know a good beach around here?
I wanted to see the sunset somewhere...
Santo Antonio is good...
Is it near here?
Morro do Sol is nearby.
It's near...
Back in our house,
the sunset is stunning...
Is the house by the lake?
It's by the lake. The house...
totally awesome. Massive, like...
Oh, yeah?
If you want see it,
we can show it to you.
For instance, there's some wine there,
heated pool...
We were making a little fondue,
because of the cold...
That's nice.
When you say that, it's like...
No, but the Law of Return, it...
Excuse me. Ramon, let's go back to work?
Come on.
Now. I need you there.
I'll be right back.
Work?
I'll be right back,
with ideas for the afterparty.
Are you interested? What do you think?
Always interested.
Whoa... No. Right? Let's work on that.
Listen up, guys...
You're waiting on tables.
Perfect.
And let Ramon work the bar.
The girls can take a break, okay?
I was so happy here, drinking...
I don't want to work at the bar.
Five minutes?
I think Nath and Bia
are worried back at the house.
Nath, for sure. Nath must be furious.
Yes, look.
Ramon's ears must be burning.
Speak of the devil...
Do you guys live around here?
We live... In São José, actually.
- Where?
- São José.
- Is it nearby?
- Somewhat near.
- Ramonzito.
- Talk to me.
A gin tonic?
Another one? Coming right up.
Now you have to do a perfect job.
Focus, because I'm out here alone.
They say that pretty women
don't have to pay.
Well, I'll... Perfect. Gin.
Okay.
Easy now.
Hey! Holy crap!
Am I looking good?
Awesome!
You're looking nice.
So you approve. I behave well, then.
Man, come here.
Come here.
We have a proposal for you.
- A nice proposal.
- I'm listening.
We're having a super top evening,
and it's going to get better,
and we couldn't do it without them.
- Are you taking us with you?
- We want to take them with us.
Easy there... Easy.
Say yes, Ricardo.
Fuck!
- The shift isn't over yet.
- No, wait...
But what about your proposal?
We have a proposal.
The four of us.
The four of us for them.
Any time you want us...
We'll work tomorrow...
We'll come tomorrow,
plus we'll cover their time.
I'm the one who makes the decisions here.
When the shift starts,
who is working... Okay?
Since today was the first day...
Ramon did well.
Ramon!
Luan. Congratulations on your service.
- Thanks, man.
- The girls put on a show on the floor.
- You go, girls.
- You're all clear to go.
All for one! We're in this together.
All for one and one for all.
That's crazy. Where are we going?
Let's go.
Come with us, it's a secret.
Come on. Let's go.
I just... Can I change?
Let's go, yes, come on.
Come on!
Come on! Let's go!
Hey! Let's go!
All good.
We have arrived.
Whoa! Skate park.
Look at that.
A shot to warm up?
Everybody wants one.
Shot!
I'm a little jealous.
- Relax.
- Are you jealous?
I wanted to be like you, but I can't.
Shameless. Look!
You know what... Funny thing is... Look.
Did I give you any reason to be jealous?
No, and even if you did...
You're not jealous? I'm a little jealous.
Not if I trust the guy. Otherwise...
If there's one thing that
drives me crazy, it's jealousy.
There's real jealousy.
I'm being upfront.
- Okay.
- It drives me nuts, girl.
If I see you making out with another girl,
do you expect me to be zen about it?
You'll never see that.
That's fine. It's great.
That's the point.
So, I get jealous if I have a reason.
Everyone has to be free, got it?
You do it if you want to.
No, you don't want to be jealous, it's a
matter of respect for the other person.
That's it.
This, "You do it if you want to..."
I'd never stop you...
That's wrong.
...or I'd never say, like,
"If you do this or that."
Because you know what's at stake.
I don't need to mention it,
and I know it.
Exactly.
And we're both free,
we can make the choices we want.
That's for sure.
I'll be honest with you.
I like you, but... That's the point.
I know, man.
But brother, I'm totally free.
I'm totally free...
And you've always
made it very clear to her.
I'm going to sit down with her...
I'm going to say, "Here's the thing..."
Or you... No.
Brother, it's not going to happen anymore.
It's your decision.
I don't want the girl
to have any more expectations.
I love you, man.
I love you, too.
Stop it, I want to roll with you.
With no jealousy around.
Relax. All cool.
What's going on?
I was waiting for you
so I could drink some more.
One step at a time.
Are you all right?
I just have to pee, that's all. Come on.
What's up, man?
- I heard João saying some stuff to Murilo.
- Seriously?
João said,
"You're going to be a player again, right?
Back to the game." And then he...
- João?
- Jo... Girl...
Come on, girlfriend.
One, two, three and... Whoa!
Who can chug it faster? Go!
Always. Same old, same old.
Blondie... Hey, you...
Nothing has changed.
I'm home, that's all that matters.
Yeah, man. Man!
That's all that matters. I am perfect.
Hey, be careful.
I can't open my eyes, but I got it
under control. I'm still in control.
I need a shower. I feel like I stink.
I know... Like this...
Wait...
Hey, okay... Murilão, I'm waiting
to have a chat with you.
Have a chat, João?
Every time you have a chat...
Hey, easy. Please.
Stop talking, seriously. Easy.
What? Easy, my ass! I'm furious!
Man, have I ever said to you,
"Let's get married"?
- No! You haven't.
- Get real, seriously. Today. Now.
Murilo, you need to be more sensitive
to my feelings.
- I'm not?
- I came here...
- Do you think I'm doing you wrong?
- I really came here to fight...
Saline. Make her drink this.
I didn't want to like you, but I do.
Turn on the shower.
Let's lie down, okay? Please, lie down.
- No, I need another shower.
- Please.
- I wanna know...
Take a shower... I want my friends.
Your friends will talk
to you in the bedroom.
No, I want you out of here. Please.
I'll get out.
But I'm taking you to the bedroom safely.
- Get out...
- Guys, can I come in?
I didn't want to like him, but I do.
Can I come in?
I... Get out of here, please, Murilo.
Okay. Stay here. Come here.
Stay with her in the bathroom.
I'm done with it.
Girl, stop saying this shit.
What happened? What's going on, girl?
What happened is that Murilo makes me cry.
She made her statement,
"We're doing it today."
Then she got hammered.
She's going to bed to sleep.
She's a fucking idiot.
Brother, I don't need the maximum,
I need the minimum, get it? The minimum.
The minimum, man. Got it?
We're not living in the minimum.
We are living at the maximum.
- That's good. Okay.
- You need to be firm.
All he said was true.
You just have to mind what you say,
what you talk about and, shit...
Be upfront about it.
If you think that she felt it,
talk to her tomorrow, say,
"Did you feel this and that?
You got it wrong.
It was this and that!"
I told her several times. Today...
- Do you understand?
- I talked to her.
It's over... Guys.
It's the relationship.
We just have to say things as they are.
"You'll do this or that with Luan."
You guys figure it out, okay?
Do you want an example?
You don't have to say a thing.
It's the lion and the lioness.
- I'm sorry.
- It's over, okay, guys?
I'm not getting laid,
you've ruined it for me.
I'm the one who should be mad.
Well, now I'm going to bed, partner,
because tomorrow it's going to be hard.
I have to work. Good night.
No...
I was in bed, but I need socks.
Hey, Tay...
Hi, honey.
Let me ask you something.
When you overheard Murilo and João...
- Careful there.
- Hey, sit down.
My only problem is that he told me...
Easy...
...he liked me and then that
he didn't feel anything,
that my heart doesn't belong to him.
But did he say that?
He did. To my face, in front of Blondie.
A flower is always nice...
The boy gave a flower,
but he gave his heart.
- No.
- But she's got your heart.
No, she hasn't.
If he doesn't acknowledge my feelings,
shut up and no talk.
That's all I ask.
- Careful there.
- I'm not a child.
Sit with me
and tell me exactly what it is.
That's what I want,
sincerity and maturity.
That's where you look me in the eye
and say, "Relax. Just relax.
If I said I'm with you, if I ever
screw up, you'll be the first to know."
What if he's honest with you
and you don't like it?
Exactly, but he said it.
What's the truth?
He was upfront with you. Then you hurt me.
He's free? That he's a player?
Look me in the eye. Look me
in the eye and say, "I'm a player.
What we have in the house is one thing.
Out here, it's a different story."
I just need honesty. I was upset today...
He's being upfront with you.
I was very upset today because...
Girl, I didn't even know
what was going on.
You were assuming things, then.
No! She said,
"But aren't you falling for her?"
And he said,
"No. Not falling for her at all."
Fuck! Then, in the afternoon,
Thais says he's falling for me.
He looks me in the eye and says,
"Not even close."
If he doesn't acknowledge
my feelings, shut up.
No, João, if you don't know shit, shut up.
What upset me today
was that he told me and Blondie
that he's not falling for me.
- Easy. Calm down.
- Fuck!
No, my friend. Screw it.
But then he comes and says...
He keeps telling me, all afternoon,
that I'm different and stuff,
that my soul is this and that...
But that's how he feels.
But then... Don't come...
- He was lying.
- It's not... It's not a lie, man.
So don't tell me that he's not
falling for me at all.
- Got it? That got me very upset.
- The thing is... Easy.
If he wants to hook up
with several people,
that's fine.
Calm down.
Look what you're doing with me!
Girlfriend. Come here, give me a hug.
Calm down, he understands.
He got it. He already...
That's why I was mad. He told me...
Screw it. Look, I'm your brother, man.
Hey, what's going on? Easy, man.
Don't fucking shove me. Fuck you!
Fuck her... She's shoving me
and hitting me! Her!
Don't just say stuff you don't mean...
He wasn't really serious.
Take it easy.
Hey, take it easy!
He didn't mean that.
- That's all I asked.
- No, it wasn't. Calm down.
...both points of view.
What happened?
I didn't see, I was in the bathroom.
I don't even know, bro. I'm so fucked up.
Oh, my God!
This is the booze talking.
"I don't even know, bro."
Guys, João is the best.
Yes. "I don't even know.
I'm so fucked up!"
João said the only sensible thing there.
"What happened?"
"I don't even know, I'm so fucked up!"
There. He solved the problem.
- Guys, I only argue like that for food.
- Really?
I'm not going to get stressed for a man.
If I was drunk, I would play some music.
-"Stop fighting! We are here!"
- But let me tell you something now.
I like to keep the peace, too.
I think that it's all very intense. Okay.
But I mean... "I'm so fucked up!"
Lying to a liar.
I have a meme.
No... It was completely senseless.
He didn't hook up with another woman.
He didn't do anything.
He was honest. He said,
"I'm not as involved as you are."
I don't even think it's true.
He told it to João.
The other girl went there
and played broken telephone.
Chinese whispers?
Yes. Oh, yeah, Chinese whispers,
that's when they talk.
If it's broken, you can't hear it, shit.
Maybe where she's from,
phones don't work...
Have you ever been dumped in your lives?
Yes, but, seriously,
there's no reason for all this stress.
Obviously, girl.
And how do you feel about it?
It's super important to experience
the sadness.
Then get over it.
He said to his friend,
"It's not working anymore.
I'll talk to her tomorrow."
He wakes up in the morning,
"I'm going to keep seeing her."
- Then what?
- Hold on.
Here's the thing.
It's not, "Ain't going to happen."
He was playing her from
the beginning and now he says,
"I don't want it anymore."
- How do you mean, playing? Playing what?
- He was kind of... undecided.
No... It's...
No, they were having
a good relationship.
They were getting along pretty well.
And what did you think
about this whole situation?
If you were in her shoes?
Oh, my God! I don't know.
- No, seriously.
- Crocodile tears.
Yeah, girlfriend... Would I be mad?
I would be mad.
Titto, I'm going to smack you.
I love it!
Would I be pissed? I would, but like...
Do we want to make out?
Let's make out. Let's drink, that's it.
I like getting even more than...
Getting mad.
That way, the guy sees I'm into him.
Does getting even show you're into him?
- But that's...
- Maybe, maybe not.
It depends on how you do it.
If you know how to do it.
Like, for instance, look.
You're with one guy and then you see
the guy's with someone else at the party.
Then you make out in front of him.
To show him that you were
so upset that you do that.
Or that you could care less...
Yes, look, but in this case,
it was just... It was just
talk and gossip, right?
I would pretend my friend
didn't say a thing and then,
the next day, he would say,
"I don't want it anymore, so..."
"No, it's all right, man,
I'm also here to enjoy the vibe
and stuff, relax."
On the inside, I would be like,
"I'm going to kill him."
But I wouldn't show it.
Like, "It was on my mind."
Then I'd go to a party,
get another guy, but...
But, like... I wouldn't let
him see, but he would know it.
I would do it in front of João,
and João would tell him. Got it?
You know what I would do? Worse than that.
I would tag him
as a close friend on Instagram...
I would only post things
for my close friends
and he would see that I'm happy.
I think that if you eat quietly,
you eat more, my opinion.
What if you're not getting anyone,
like João?
No, João is a different story.
João isn't getting laid at all.
Let's take a poll here, now.
You guys at home.
Do you think João will get laid?
Before the end of the series?
I think he will.
Call zero...
Dude, I was so sorry for João, man.
Like, it was not his fault, you know?
You see, he's hot... The guy is funny,
as much as he can...
- He cries...
- And he didn't get laid.
So, it was all for nothing?
Everything was thrown away?
I'm not... Do you think I'm a fool?
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
You want to be respected, earn it. If you
can't handle it, don't get involved.
- I told you...
- Fuck you!
Friendship's over.
No more respect. It's over.
The fight gets ugly.
Sooner or later that's what happens.
No matter how hard you try.
Just imagine, the two are drinking booze,
confined in that house, there's a crowd...
At some point, things get ugly.
Can't wait for the next episode.
Me, too.
A, I want to know if João
is going to get laid.
- B, if...
- Letter B... Number A, number B.
Look, B.
To see if that fight
is going to continue like that.
They have been showing signs
of that since the first episode.
In the second one, there was that fight,
but he got away...
He turned away from the fight,
but now he's coming in strong.
There's going to be more
fights besides Murilo's...
Do you know what?
João is getting laid
in the third episode.
Honest to God, the third...
The way he's doing things,
he'll never get laid.
He'll get laid in the third episode.
Wanna bet?
Actually, I think João is a virgin.
But if he doesn't get laid,
João will help calm things down.
Or make things worse.
The third episode
will show João getting laid
and Taynara making up or breaking up...
- Or what?
- Have sex with what?
With what? With a tree...
He will... The exhaust pipe of the jeep...
I don't think João is going to get laid.
They are fighting
and making out again.
I agree. I think João will get laid.
He won't. João is not getting laid.
If he didn't that time...
I think João will not get laid
and he will be blamed
for all the trouble.
João will die a virgin.
It's not happening in the third, fourth...
No, not the end of the series.
I think it's the last one.
It's going to be in the third.
Let's talk about the third.
João gets laid in the third episode?
No.
- Will he get laid?
- No.
- Will he?
- I think so.
- I think he will.
- No...
So, we'll find out next week.
- Let's wait.
- It's going to be...
I think they are all
goofing around, seriously.
If João gets laid, I'll be surprised...
- What do you think?
- They're goofing around.
- Get some drops, then.
- João...
- You idiot! That was really bad.
- I think we make a great duo.
- If João...
- Those two...
If João gets laid, he'll be surprised.
He'll lose his virginity.
That's true. But... A duo.