WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
REVIEW
Hello, people. How are you? Look...
We're here together to watch episode six
of Wild and Free: Florianópolis.
Remember that on the previous episode
ended with Nathalia
catching Ramon red-handed.
"Catching him red-handed?"
That was a good one. Great.
What? Did you know about this?
To catch red-handed is a soap opera
back in Cuiabá, got it?
- So, let's watch it?
- Let's do it.
Take the remote and press play.
Bye, thanks.
With your heels.
With your clog heels.
Let's do it.
Get out of here. You're sassy...
No, it's not.
Guys, let me talk...
Did you see Ramon's little smile?
I think he's doing it on purpose now,
hooking up with another girl.
Look how she left.
She was very cold...
- She grimaced. Look at her disgusted face.
- But he didn't see it. He didn't care.
- He smiled at the friend.
- She also grimaced.
It was because of that girl.
- But he's enjoying she got pissed.
- She's being fussy.
I think it was for the girl,
after the situation Nathalia caused.
The girl must be embarrassed.
- The girl must be...
- But he's cute, right?
- He's cute.
- She's very embarrassed.
- Who? Ramon?
- Yeah...
But she's beautiful, too, right?
Hit pause, Bianca.
- Let's see what's inside this box.
- Open it.
CRUSH PARTY
- It's the party thing.
- That's rad.
Look at this flyer.
That's why...
It's the manager's party.
They have to promote.
Crush party.
I wonder if I could ask my brother
to show up at this party.
I don't know.
Dear Lord.
Imagine if his brother is like him? Hot...
If his brother is a fucker like him...
- He's a fucker, that's real.
- Who? Johnny?
- João.
Pretended to be humble, said,
"I'm a kisser, not a fucker."
In two days,
he fucked more than anyone.
- Hello?
- What's up, Tô? What's up, man?
Thor?
They talk like...
It's like Scary Movie.
Wassup!
Scream, right?
Is it cool? Really?
It's hard to explain.
It's crazy here, man...
I'm shaking, talking to you, man.
I even farted.
Really?
- What did he say?
-"I even farted."
Talk to me about everything,
but don't talk about fart and poop.
- Yeah.
- It's such a turn-off.
It's not a turn-off,
it's out of line.
It's too much intimacy
and it ruins relationships.
That's my tip to you.
Don't shit in front of your women.
If the boy farts on your face,
what do you do?
- What?
- On my face?
It's a metaphor. I mean, in front of you.
- When I'm lying down?
- He's with you.
- Lying down, standing, doing a handstand.
- I say, "Get up."
- It pisses me off, fuck.
- Of course.
Bro, that's the tiff bus.
Everything starts there.
Yeah... It's called devil bus.
- Luan is seated.
- Look at Luan's face.
Beatriz over there...
- His woman is calling...
- I get it. Look.
What is that? Is he jealous?
Obviously!
Poor guy. She's not allowed to dance...
Look at that uncomfortable face.
He looks like he wants to fight.
He looks like he's not confident.
He has a small dick.
His woman dances and he gets sad.
Guys, she's dancing in front of a girl.
- João is kissing.
- João, the kisser.
Oh, no, bro!
Guys, come on. She didn't do anything.
She was just dancing.
She was dancing like this with her friend.
She was like this... Right, Carol?
Then he said,
"I didn't like the way you were dancing."
She said, "I didn't do anything."
With her friend.
- Yeah, but I think Murilo was there, too.
- No, he wasn't.
Murilo was there, mister.
Guys, Murilo was just passing by.
Has anyone here had a date
who didn't allow it?
No, but I've seen
someone doing this to a friend of mine.
I've seen it, it makes me mad
because I've seen girls get scared
and change, you know?
It's called possession.
That's why I'm single.
If my girl dances with another man,
I don't even...
She wouldn't be my girl.
If I had to tell her this,
she wouldn't be my girl.
So, you're jealous.
She has to know
she can't rub her ass against another guy.
So, you're jealous.
It's not jealousy, man. It's respect.
If I do that with another girl,
my girl would say,
-"Holy fuck."
- But if it was her?
She doesn't need to tell me this.
Dancing with her girlfriend...
I'm going to say...
- With her girlfriend?
- Yeah.
She knows what she can do, got it?
She's only my woman because of that.
Bê is dancing on the counter,
and he's after Bê.
What's the deal with Murilo?
No. I think Murilo
has no ulterior motives.
No, of course...
When the person is not right
or they make something up...
Yeah... There's no more reason.
But there's another thing.
He can hook up with everyone,
like he did with that girl
from that club because of João,
and she can't dance because
he's assuming she's going to do...
- Exactly. He doesn't trust her.
- That's crazy.
- That's insecurity.
- This is something...
Yeah, and Bia killed it. She was there.
That guy came,
and she said, "No, no, wait."
This is because
the guy has a small penis.
Bia nailed it.
Bia said, "No, it's not going
to happen now, respect me."
And he did what you said, Titto.
There's no reason...
Says bullshit and walks away.
That's ungraceful.
He made a mistake.
It's over... Let's go.
Let's go.
- Fuck, Murilo is wasted.
- Everyone is hammered.
What did you call it?
"He flopped the party," right?
- He asked everyone to leave.
- Look at Murilo.
We ruled, baby.
This one wanted things to get ugly...
Fuck him. Fuck him.
That's who you are, Beatriz. This is you.
What did I say to you?
- Baby, shut up, you know shit about me.
- Be free.
- This is you.
- That's right.
Don't pretend to be a good person.
Jeez, he's being loud.
There's no reason...
- This is me.
- Fuck you!
You, go fuck yourself.
Jeez, what an asshole, bro.
He has flopped big time.
- Man, what?
- Man, we danced a lot.
Man, what?
I danced a lot with Bia. Fuck it.
I saw it. What if it was me with Tay?
Now, you're upset, right?
Bro, you do whatever you want,
right, Luan?
Respect me, boy. Know your place, boy.
- I know my place.
- Get your hands off me.
"Get your hands off me." What a hero.
I danced with Bia.
Like I danced with Tay,
like I danced with Blondie.
There's no reason to fight.
- Do you wanna fight?
- What do you want?
I'm not going to ignore this!
I want to fight you!
Oh, my God.
Taynara showed up.
I love when she defends her boy.
- Murilo...
- Are you fucking with me?
I'm going to tell you something.
I always respected you.
- Me, too. So what?
- Look, I'm going to tell you something.
I never treated you like this, you know?
- Easy...
- Stop it, man... Please, bro.
If there's one thing I understand
is a situation like this.
Because I used to pick fights.
I'm a better person now.
- That guy is a coward.
- It's obvious.
He said a lot of things,
repeated the same sentence
because he's desperate, like,
"Are you fucking with me?"
The guy is very close.
If you want to hit him, just do it.
He's a coward, he won't do anything.
Yeah. Exactly.
He only incites a fight.
When things get ugly,
he doesn't do anything.
He's an asshole who wants to show off.
There could be 50 guys, if you want
to hit someone, you will do it.
There's no talk.
- Do you think you're a man?
- Easy.
Who do you think you are?
They're going to kill him.
Easy, Murilo.
I respected your girl a lot.
Because yesterday when you were wasted,
I took care of her, you fucker.
That's because I care about you.
-"Fucker..."
- He's full of reason, look.
Easy, Murilo.
Fuck, I love Murilo.
- That Luan is a...
- He's wrong.
I would be like Tay.
I would come at someone who's
attacking the person you love.
If someone attacks who I love, I go crazy.
It's about the other person.
Especially when you're right.
...but if I have to defend who I love,
I go crazy.
At any time, she didn't question whether
her man danced with another woman.
- At any moment.
- She didn't even bother.
She was confident and said,
"You can dance. You're my man,
but you can dance with my girlfriends."
She was in the dark, she had no fear.
The most controversial couple
in the beginning of the episode.
Yeah, there was more trouble.
Would you break up that fight
or would you cheer?
I hate fights.
Girl, obviously, I would shout,
"Fight, fight!" I'm joking...
You need to be in a good mood.
I think I would be Taynara.
I would shout, "Stick together!"
I think Murilo said beautiful things.
- He was very reasonable.
- I'm a cool person.
When I want to have sex, I have sex.
I don't need to date.
He's not ready to have
a good woman beside him.
He has to hook up with someone worse than
her 'cause he can't handle that woman...
He's not willing to be with her,
no guts to be with that kind of woman.
It's over. He's not ready, brother.
Go seek a worse woman
'cause she's out of your league...
She's too much for you.
Do you think he's going to
apologize the next day?
Obviously. He always does that.
- He always does that.
- He doesn't apologize.
Ramon's turn, Ramon went there.
He thinks he forgives people. He says,
"No, you were wrong,
but you're going to be a better person."
He thinks he's the man. He's God's voice.
I think Bia is not going back to him.
Girl...
And João was absolute.
"I'm going to have to make you pass out."
- I wonder if he did.
- João's funny.
He applied a rear naked choke hold.
He just had to choke, and he'd pass out.
João is that famous person who doesn't
want trouble.
He didn't get involved with those girls.
He'll make that guy pass out,
but he'll caress him.
I want to know the mood in that house now.
- I wonder if they're going to have sex.
- Of course not.
- There's no mood for sex.
- Look at him pretending to be tough.
João is great. He's great.
He's a coward.
Inflated pecs.
I want to see him now, when he wakes up.
Sitting at that table, looking like shit.
- That's going to be bad.
- Breakfast gets hard to swallow, girl.
Look at João, he doesn't know anything.
Poor thing, he's full of bruises.
- Poor thing was hit a lot.
- No, he wasn't hit.
Luan...
What are you doing to yourself, man?
Beatriz did it... She did it...
But I don't think like that.
In my opinion...
Murilo wanted to talk to you respectfully.
Even I danced with Murilo.
I hug Murilo,
and there's nothing going on.
He never disrespected me.
Just saying that you are wrong.
But I won't leave you alone.
- It's cool.
- That's it.
Thanks.
Guys.
- It looks like a soap opera.
- But she's sensible.
She's already changed the episode.
She can't deal with her relationship.
But she can do it with her friends.
She's supportive
because he defended her.
Yeah, exactly.
I wanted to explain what I thought, okay?
I know I'm wrong, okay? I apologize
before starting this conversation.
No problem...
I'm a little aggressive. People know me.
I got really jealous of Bia.
When I came back from the smoking lounge,
Bia and Nath were dancing
with you behind them.
For me that's very serious, you know?
But I'm truly sorry, bro.
I didn't even sleep, you know?
He's apologizing for the assault,
but not because he was an asshole.
He's just admitting he's jealous.
He's admitting he was wrong.
Let him admit it.
It's like, "You got me, right?"
No, he's just saying he's a jealous guy.
And he has no control.
He's just saying this.
Let's hear him out.
Don't be so judgmental, Judge.
- I'm here to judge.
- Judge Drops.
I know I can trust few people here,
and you're one of them.
I should've never suspected you
and involved you
in that unpleasant situation. Really.
Relax. We're good.
I apologize from the bottom of my heart.
- Look!
- I don't know...
He admitted he was wrong.
But he has to talk to Beatriz.
Yes, he has to do it now, right?
Bê... Can you go to the Tiger Room
so that we can talk? Five minutes.
I'm just going to shower. Just a second.
Okay.
Let's change this attitude, right?
Holy shit.
I still want to hook up with him.
He's going to apologize,
but he's going to break up.
"You're not the kind of woman..."
I don't think so.
I think he's gonna do this.
Or, since he called her to that room,
he's going to resolve that with sex.
- She's going to break up with him.
- That's my dream.
- It's cold in here.
- The way I like it.
Is he really going
to resolve this with sex?
Can I give you a hug first?
- No...
- Hey, guys, it's back.
Look, it's back.
Baby, they hugged, it's gone.
They're going to have sex.
I talked to Murilo... I'm here to
apologize to you for the things I said.
You're a very important woman to me.
You became very important
in a very short time.
I know I want you in my life forever.
No matter what.
- I understand your motives...
- Do you want to know the truth?
- What?
- The truth is that I love you.
What? Does he want to be her boyfriend?
"I love you."
Did he say, "I love you"?
"Do you want to know the truth?"
I just need this.
Bullshit.
That dude fucks things up,
the next day, he...
He even says "I love you..."
If Bia buys that...
...you realized what you had to
and apologized, you know?
You were humble to see
that nobody is perfect...
- Can you hug me again?
- Yes.
The guy is exaggerating.
- I believe him.
- Bia, what would you do?
I've already been in love at first sight.
Like, "Fuck, I love this guy"?
- Yes. On the first day.
- It was not "love," but...
Did it work out?
- We got married.
- You got married?
I think he's pondering.
He was honest with Murilo, not a phony.
He was really honest.
He's not playing.
He's listening to his heart, really.
He likes her because she's awesome.
No, but I think he's saying
all those things to Bia
because he regrets it.
No, man. I think he likes her, man.
He doesn't like her.
- But it'll end there.
- He's just disturbed.
But I don't think so, you know why?
Because they're on vacation in a house
and, in a month... They can never
see each other again, so I don't...
Why am I going to talk to someone?
But there's that story...
He's talking to her again
because he has feelings.
- Bianca, would you accept his apology?
- I would.
- Pabllo?
- I would, but I'd say,
"Look, baby, you have to change,
because like this, we're not gonna last."
- Exactly, you have to be clear.
- Either you change or goodbye.
- Carol?
- I've forgiven so many things.
- Love...
- Titto, would you forgive him?
If that happened to you?
Titto...
I want to know...
Let's do this, righteous man.
No, he's a saint. A big, fat saint.
Of course he would. Obviously.
Do you realize you won't be
100% yourself, right?
Are you aware of that?
You can change, man.
- I'd forgive, but I'd break up.
- That's okay.
You'd forgive, but you'd break up?
I've changed...
I would,
depending on how much I loved him,
at that moment, and I'd stay, too.
But we understood it's not possible.
There's no way.
Have you changed people like that?
"If you want me,
you'll have to stop this."
And the person did so for you?
People don't change, people adapt.
Yes, they adapt, but he can do it.
I believe people can change.
He can think this over...
A cheater, when the relationship ends,
doesn't stop cheating?
Can't he be faithful?
Is he going to cheat forever?
- He can be faithful.
- Then he changed.
No, it's different.
I'm the most sincere person I know.
After me, right? After me.
Then I made a mistake with an ex of mine,
who was extremely hot, I couldn't help it.
- I'm not talking about this.
- No, no. Take it easy.
I made a mistake.
The guy called me and said, "Carol..."
You have that chocolate...
I broke up with a guy
to marry another one, you know?
Then he told me, after five months,
"Hey, Carol, I miss you as a friend.
I miss your friendship.
Can you come over real quick
and have lunch with me just to talk?"
Just to suck me.
As friends.
Then I got a cab and went there.
- As friends?
- When I got there, "Hi, how are you?"
But he was extremely hot, man.
"Hey, let's get out of here."
And I went with him.
When I got home at night,
I had a guilty conscience.
I told the person,
"Man, the other day,
I was in a hotel with so-and-so..."
-"I made a mistake."
-"I made a mistake,
but, man, if you forgive me,
I won't do that anymore."
When I felt like hooking up with others,
partying and stuff,
I broke up with him for two months.
I did all of that...
- I wasn't saying that.
- ...then we got back together.
I'm a woman of character.
I told him. I swear to God I told him.
That's true. You are.
But when I was talking about...
About character...
You know what's fucked up?
Lying your whole life, not telling it.
Cheating...
- That is lack of character.
- Cheating... There are lies.
- To me, lying is lack of character.
- But I didn't lie.
Pabllo is very quiet today.
- Speechless.
- Just listening to the story.
Carol is the only person
who shocks Pabllo Vittar.
I'm just learning here.
Look, it's back.
Let's invite these guys.
Let's invite them.
Let's get started.
Hi, how are you? Good afternoon.
Here's an invitation for you guys.
This party is tonight, at the lagoon,
downtown, at 7:00 p.m.
They stick together, right?
They all soaked their feet, man.
- Those ladies soaked their feet.
- Imagine the foot odor...
- Those feet are going to stink.
- Jesus.
It's uncomfortable to watch those shoes
getting wet. I even feel my feet itching.
Walking with wet shoes.
Jeez! It's Thais' friend.
- Victoria.
- Victoria, babe!
Did you go to Wolf Maya? You're rich.
I did...
Look at Ramon.
- She's beautiful.
- Look at Ramon.
Look at those guys...
Look...
- I love João.
- João is the best.
What's that, man?
I love it. Guys, she's hot, you know?
João is a naughty boy.
- What's your name?
- Ramon. Yours?
- Victoria.
- Nice to meet you.
Hi...
- How are you?
- All good?
- Are you the famous Vic?
- I'm Victoria. Vic.
- Blondie said good things about you.
- Really?
- Welcome.
- How are you, buddy?
I smell like garlic.
How are you? You're cooking? That's great.
Let's do something here, right?
- João is feeling sick.
- Why?
Seems like food poisoning. I don't know.
What is it?
Is he with someone?
- Is João with her?
- No, it's a joke.
That's cute.
João wanted to joke with the girl...
João is fast, right?
He's sharp as a tack.
That's the cue for him to ask her,
"Do you remember that joke?
"Let's go make another joke..."
- Guys, I loved the fuck room.
- I loved it. Guys, I loved it.
Fucking with red lights...
You sweat a lot.
The sweat reaches your eyes...
- I love sweating.
- I love sweating, too, you know?
I like the smell of sweat.
I hate cold. I hate air conditioning.
I hate it.
Sex with the air conditioner on?
Do you want to get a cold?
And your dick goes like this,
that's impressive.
Only yours because
other people's get bigger.
Really? That's delicious.
The actors' dinner.
Voice message from the manager.
Hi, what's up?
Today is the big day.
Our party is tonight.
I wanted to thank all of you
for your hard work with promotion.
Look at Taynara
holding the cutlery, wonderful.
She looks like a Flintstone holding that.
They're a match. Taynara and Murilo.
They have to eat after so much booze.
- Fuck it.
- Motherfucker.
"Motherfucker."
Man, I love Ramon. "Motherfucker."
Imagine the manager watching.
He'd say,
"Fuck, he borrowed my boat and he says...
- I'm a motherfucker."
-"Motherfucker."
Last week, they made everyone
get drunk for free at...
Imagine him watching everyone
drinking those tequilas...
That "motherfucker."
I fear for Luan at a club.
No, tonight,
he'll be a saint like never before.
She'll be able to pole dance tonight,
naked, and he'll say, "Yay! I love it!"
He's in her hands now.
She's wearing
a Kardashian-style dress.
She wants to cause impact.
- Thais loves little dresses, right?
- She likes moods.
João's brother arrived.
- Fuck, he's the spitting image of him.
- Damn! No way.
They're the true Jonas Brothers, got it?
- That's cute.
- Jonas Brothers.
- Guys...
- They are very retarded, right?
He has a familiar face, that Tomás.
No, João's last name is
Turbation, you know?
Man, they must be very cool, right?
No, I'm sorry. "Tomás..."
Jeez, Titto, you're an idiot.
Did you see he was very sad?
"My brother didn't come."
Then, he arrived.
Guys, his brother has a familiar face.
Buddy, his brother is hot.
Welcome. Fuck!
- Shapes of beautiful guys.
- Yes. What a cast?
Where do they hide?
These shapes of beautiful guys.
I think they're rich. Rich people
are beautiful. "We did that."
- They're all beautiful.
-"Rich people are beautiful."
- I'd fuck both of them.
- I don't think...
They're just friends.
They're not brothers.
- They're brothers.
- But they don't look alike.
- They look alike.
- Of course not.
Not physically, just the height.
What's up, are you excited?
We're very excited...
To start drinking.
- I'm drinking for you, girl.
- Drink for me.
You come here with us.
First of all, what's your name?
Renata.
Renata? Tomás... And you?
- Luará.
- Luará?
- That's it...
- I'm still learning.
- You toasted, you drink it...
- You can use the straw.
Your friend is winning.
This way, look, let's do it.
Ouch!
Guys, what is that?
- Fuck, I want this Tomás.
- Guys, it's in the family.
- João, as usual, is celebrating.
- Look at João, he's a fool, man.
He kissed a fucking lot.
He kisses a girl and says,
"I kissed her! I kissed her!"
João, I love you.
He should've been
the one getting wedgies...
He thought, "I'm going to grow up,
hook up with some girls and celebrate."
- The DJ is cute.
- I love it 'cause he's weird.
He looks like an old man
from the '60s dancing.
Man, I swear, I'm a big fan of his.
I love it when we give them nicknames.
"Mowgli," "Blondie..."
- The wolf boy...
-"Blondie" is great.
- Pabllo, I like the DJ. Look at him.
- DJ, hit it for me.
I get to be the old uncle joker, right?
That's cool.
That was the first joke
I told on this show.
- Guys, Murilo wants everyone to get drunk.
- It was the worst joke ever.
- The first one...
- The first and last, please.
Wait.
- What? What was that?
- He said she looks amazing.
Do you think I didn't want that, too?
I'm loving it, guys.
I love this show. I swear to God.
Tay is hitting on him...
- Son of a gun.
- She hooked up with the DJ.
She hooked up with the DJ.
Go, Blondie!
Look who encouraged her. Vic.
- The DJ was mine.
- Vic. How cute.
Did you hear that? "The DJ was mine."
"He was mine."
Damn.
- Girl, no one belongs to no one.
- She's naughty.
No one belongs to no one, Carol.
- They do.
- No, they don't.
They are much more in love now,
after that.
You said it, Carol,
those things make you...
Damn, I was the only one
to notice the DJ, man.
And hooked up with him.
Whenever I go to a party,
I'll fight with my ex.
What did you notice? You were sleeping.
I noticed him. I said it to Pabllo.
Do you like DJs, Carol?
- I noticed him.
- But do you like DJs?
- Do you dig a DJ?
- I found him quiet.
- Don't do this.
- Do you hook up with your DJ?
No, don't do that.
- Why?
- Why not?
- Don't do that.
- She does it.
- She's already done it.
- Don't do that, man.
Why, man?
I don't hook up with
anyone from my team.
Have you done it
with someone from your team?
Have you given a job to your lover?
No, not in my team because I only work
with friends and family. It's true!
#FRIENDSANDFAMILY
Very good. "And family."
Friends and family. But I love
hooking up with the DJ, at least...
If he's a DJ...
The DJ, the producer...
A techno DJ at an alternative party.
- Any famous DJ or famous producer?
- I can't say.
She picks the DJ rhythm.
I love hooking up with the PR.
I love not getting in line at clubs.
- I love this fetish.
- It has to be a techno DJ.
That's cool.
I've given a job to a lover.
He worked with me.
- Hey, attention, DJs, look.
- Lover?
You can't have lovers, man.
I love it...
But it wasn't a relationship.
DJs, send messages
to Pabllo Vittar's inbox...
I used to hook up with a guy.
It was serious.
What does it mean for you?
For how long?
Three years.
A serious hook-up with her...
Did you kiss him?
- Yes.
- It wasn't just his dick?
But was it a relationship?
No. He had a girlfriend.
I get steady relationships.
That's how I kiss.
- Did he have a girlfriend, too?
- Yeah.
He was your friend with benefits.
- What's this, boy?
- It's a fuck buddy.
- A fuck buddy. It's a dick buddy.
- Yeah.
Or pussy buddy.
- What?
- Yeah, pussy buddy.
Anyway, I used to hook up with him,
so no one could know about him
because he had a girlfriend.
Then I said, "Work with me..."
Ouch, girl.
He became a member of your team...
Was he your lover?
You can't have lovers, Carol.
- No, the relationship wasn't...
- There he goes, the saint.
- Let's canonize him.
- Shut up, man.
I dated someone, and he had a girlfriend.
It was a serious relationship, you know?
So you messed things up with him.
You were the reason for the mess.
- No one knew.
- No one?
So everything was right,
it was just a mistake.
Just a long mistake.
I've hooked up with bloggers.
- Blogger boys?
- Yes.
- Who? No way.
- I've dated people who worked on TV.
- People who work on TV...
- Who? Tell us names.
- No names.
- But I like this party environment.
- How many followers?
It's not just that.
It's about the importance in Brazil.
It's not enough...
"Importance in Brazil."
How many movies? How many leading roles?
There are a lot of things.
I feel it's Felipe Titto.
No, I'm just an extra on soap operas.
I pass by in the background.
I do this, got it?
I'm not a leading actor.
I don't have lines, just pass by and nod.
That's enough.
No, don't do this.
That's me.
I'm the one who has to talk about you.
That pisses me off.
I don't like it.
Do you hook up with famous people?
No, I'd hook up with Titto...
Jeez, Titto is such an idiot!
I'm going to throw it on Titto's face...
He's that old uncle...
No, I hook up with
cab drivers, fishermen...
- I think...
- What did you say about me?
Until the last episode,
Titto has to get down with Carol.
- Do what with Carol?
- Get down with you.
-"To make out"?
-"Making out."
- Here's what you'll have to do.
- Can you two peck?
Let's play a video game...
You'll be playing with me and then,
"Titto, I'm very tired, I'll sleep."
I'll pass in front of your room,
the door will be open, I'll hear the fan.
No, Titto, it's not like that.
I want you to peck each other...
Ramon and Nathalia
are going to make out again.
- No!
- Don't do that.
- Who made out?
- Ramon is messing around.
Don't do that.
He deserved it. She learned her lesson.
I didn't like it, girl.
- I'm a Scorpio. I don't forget things.
- Scorpio! I hate it!
- I didn't like it.
- I'm with you.
Let's go to the afterparty.
- You see? I take care.
- I don't see it, girl.
- If I see it, I stop you.
- I don't see it.
- Hey, Luan.
- Ramon...
Luan, tell your brother to go there.
I can't even leave the kitchen because...
This guard is...
Luan and Nathalia have
a beautiful friendship.
That's true. They're friends.
See how a big fucked-up situation
became a friendship.
Come, come, come.
Thais is shit-faced. Look.
I know. I trust your potential.
Poor girl.
- Pabllo is like Blondie.
- Thais is going to fall backwards.
...taking her to the bedroom.
But, girl...
- The DJ will give up. She's shit-faced.
- But a real friend does that.
They are close since day one.
The DJ will hook up with the other one.
...I turned too much.
Do you want to take these heels off?
Girl, where are you?
- Bia.
- I don't know.
But, Bia, go have fun, relax.
Go have fun. Easy.
- Bia. Go there...
- What is it?
- Nath was causing trouble again, man?
- Yeah, again.
She really is a troublemaker.
Jeez, I tried to like Nath, you know?
I really tried.
"Go downstairs, something's going on."
Jeez, man.
I am starting to dislike that girl.
Tell that motherfucker to come here.
She's a gossiper.
I made us two burgers.
Okay. Let's see what's going on.
He's making a burger for you.
Then why did you call me?
Why did you say, "Bia, go downstairs"?
- To eat.
- Baby...
Look, Ramon is so cute.
- She's going to be jealous. It's payback.
- No, wait.
I'm out of patience.
So, you talk to Nath.
Tell her to drop the bullshit...
'cause something's wrong.
Yeah. I understand her.
Don't you know me? Do you get it?
You've created...
It's good she goes downstairs...
She walks away...
Go after her, make her listen to you.
You talked to me. Know how to talk to me.
Got it? That's it.
- Oh, no... I'm out of here.
- I'm not arguing with you, girl.
I'm just trying to explain
that you already know me.
You have to know how to talk.
I loved that she made
everyone understand.
The same way you didn't like it,
I also don't like it.
You talk like something's going on.
Jeez!
Wait, Bia, shut up.
Then you'll see.
I see what's going on.
I did what a friend should do...
You said,
"Go downstairs."
You didn't do anything.
You said, "Go downstairs, Bia."
Exactly. Not because of him.
Was it because of you?
The chick checked me out...
People were annoying Luan,
saying he wanted to hook up
with somebody. He didn't.
I held him... Am I lying?
I held him and said,
"He's not going to hook up with anybody."
He said,
"Are you with the SWAT?"
"She's a cop."
I said, "Yes, 'cause Bia is my friend."
Am I lying?
I'd rather the attitude of a woman.
You pointed your finger at me.
Fuck you. If my attitude doesn't...
You don't get to say "fuck you."
I've been by your side...
She's a troublemaker.
She really is. It's annoying.
Look, she's drunk and talking shit.
Holy Mother of God.
If she did that thing downstairs,
she didn't have to go upstairs
to make that other chick fight Victoria
because of Luan.
She had sorted it out.
Is she going to involve her?
Isn't she...
I think she didn't intend that fight
between Luan and her.
The way she explained,
even Luan agreed with her.
Separate Luan from those girls,
"Hey, go downstairs..."
That chick was in the pool.
"I'll call my friend to grab her man
because there are women hitting on him."
- No, no. No, it's not that.
- Wake up, girl.
I'm saying this in a good way.
Don't point your finger at me.
What, girl?
Wake up.
The afterparty
was better than the party.
It was crazy.
Give it up to Victoria,
who got a lot of attention.
What is this? Are you clapping?
My fancy applause.
It's applause.
Would you like some chocolate?
- Spoon-feed her.
- Open your mouth.
The little tongue.
If you argue with your friend,
your boyfriend is defending your friend,
he's hooking up with your friend, not you.
I'd be pissed.
- Yeah.
- I'd be fucking pissed.
I'd be fucking pissed.
- What would you be?
- Fucking pissed.
-"Fucking pissed"?
- You can't be like this, fuck.
- Now you're rich.
Let me be. I hate it.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Welcome to our humble home.
Murilo will get that boy,
and she's on the floor.
Holy shit, that's fucked up.
- No one cares about fucking anyone.
- Of course they do.
No one gives up fucking someone...
Yes, they do.
- Stop it!
- I do.
Jeez, now I'll feel like
a 4'11" girl with Murilo.