- Hello there... Guys, who cooked today?
- Me.
I do the laundry and I iron,
but Pabllo cooks.
- That's the best.
- Hi.
Hi, Bia.
- You're welcome.
- So cute. Oh, girlfriend.
Carol, I feel like banging you today.
- Oh, my God.
- I hate it!
Remember that man who says,
"Is this to be eaten or seen?"
I'm to be seen.
Titto's jokes are the best.
- He's like an old uncle!
- I like Titto's jokes.
Guys, we're back to watch
Episode 4 of Floripa Beach House.
Last episode ended with Murilo's guests
kicked out after fighting with girls.
- That was tense.
- Was that fair?
That's the very definition of trouble.
I felt bad for those girls.
Everything was tense...
If they went there,
they were expecting something to happen.
Something good, not being kicked out.
"Give me my flip-flops back!"
No, but... That flip-flop moment,
when she threw them...
She wanted something.
I thought Murilo didn't take them
because he liked them. He was teasing.
Is that what you think?
- Absolutely.
- I'm sure.
When he realized it didn't work,
he walked away...
They had dinner and didn't pay for it...
They had dinner for free and took an Uber.
I want friends like those.
He noticed she didn't bring
anybody with her and said,
"Tay is okay with this,
I'm gonna send these girls home,
I'm gonna hit on Tay today, then..."
I think he imagined...
...embarrassed about that situation.
You got to remember
that Floripa Beach House is a show
that follows eight friends,
and they are not actors.
There's no script, nobody influences this.
Anything can happen.
No rules.
It's real.
Sometimes I can't believe it.
When I saw the flip-flops,
I said, "This is a soap opera."
It looks a lot like...
I loved that look on her face,
"I found my flip-flops."
- It was really good.
- I loved it!
"I'm gonna kill this girl."
However, she had food on her hands.
That's true.
Do you think he was gonna bring them
if there was no trouble?
On that table there?
If everybody had luck,
do you think he was gonna
bring those girls?
He was gonna fuck them.
He was gonna bring...
I think he'd stall and wouldn't go. Yeah.
- I think he would.
- He wouldn't.
- He would do the honors.
- No.
He wouldn't because
I think those two girls
wouldn't hook up.
- He would if they hooked up with him.
- Sure.
I'm dying to watch Episode 4. May I?
- Let's do this...
- Please.
Great, I'm all set. Go.
FLORIPA BEACH HOUSE
Did you find it cool? Did you like it?
Jeez, a lot.
It was really cool, that moment
when you got to the party, bro.
I saw you and said to Murilo,
"Look at that chick in the middle."
Then, all of a sudden, you came in.
At the right time.
Blondie and João
are not friends with benefits anymore.
I don't have anything to do...
She wants to keep doing it.
Yeah.
Only when I don't have anything to do.
You see, Ramon?
But I'm not like this.
Now he's playing hard to get. There it is!
Do you want me to hook up with you
when you have nothing to do?
- No, I...
- That's it.
When you have nothing to do...
- Yeah...
- We use each other.
Yeah, right.
Bunch of boozers!
Let's get ready,
we're gonna go for drinks in one hour.
The party is about to get started!
One hour, one hour...
In one hour, we leave.
Let's drink again.
Thanks for everything, you know?
Thanks for coming.
We'll meet at the party.
- See you.
- Later.
Everybody ready?
Everybody ready!
- Let's go, the bus is here.
- What?
Is everybody alive?
I'm well again.
Everybody's ready for more.
What about the champagne?
No champagne. No champagne today.
Drinking champagne
is the same thing as drinking the stars.
I'm gonna do the lucky lick, now.
Excuse me.
Wait, let me see. Sit there.
But I want to be lucky.
I give you...
Oxygen.
- Our place for partying.
- That's it!
Oh, fuck!
What a wonderful place, guys.
I wanna make a toast
to this wonderful place.
Look at this! Everybody together...
- Hey...
- That's it.
Let's toast because Joãozinho had sex.
Look at this party, man.
Fucking awesome, right?
Amazing.
- One of the best.
- Rad.
That's because it's near the sea...
It's the best thing in the world.
Bro, for me... I live on the beach,
Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday...
When it's possible in Rio.
I missed this, you know?
To be in contact with nature.
We're privileged, right?
Look at this, man!
Fuck, man...
How long since you've been here?
How long haven't I been here?
Man, about ten years.
Fuck!
I swear to you.
- That's fucked up.
- I swear.
You've been on a beach in Rio?
Yes, bro.
I went to a church retreat in Rio.
Can you believe it? Fuck.
That's old stuff. Yeah...
Things over there, you know?
I remember we all...
We went for a ride in Rio.
In Copacabana, bro.
It was very cloudy.
Still, we enjoyed it a lot.
Beaches are something...
That was the only time I was on a beach.
- Beaches...
- Now's the second time.
Hey, Murilo!
- Let's go upstairs.
- Okay. Let's go upstairs.
This is relaxing...
Just to be here, man.
Very unusual for me.
To us, the most beautiful, wonderful,
kindhearted women I've ever seen...
Yes... We are real.
Yes... And polite.
- Polite, remember this...
- Thanks for everything.
Here's to friendship, girls.
I got a lighter, baby.
Lighter. Are you nuts, bro?
I said, "Baby."
Don't talk like that. Get out of here!
Nath, come here and give me a hug.
Come here.
Let's be friends.
I'm just stealing your... I'm warming up.
It's getting... It's far.
Yeah... It's touching you.
When I want you,
it wants to say hello to you.
Stay put, fuck! Stop it!
It doesn't work when it has to.
Yeah? It'll work tonight, no?
What is this, bro? You're tripping.
Come on!
- Let's talk?
- Okay.
Aren't you gonna talk to me?
Are you mad at me?
- Why?
- Go where?
Where do you wanna talk?
- There.
- What?
Oh, fuck!
Hey, I'm very cold, I swear...
It's too cold.
I'm shaking.
I'm trying to drink, but I can't.
Bro, I got out of there
because something annoyed me.
What?
Didn't you see Ramon slapping my face?
Slap your face?
But he was messing with you?
Exactly, he was messing, but...
I can't accept that, even if he was.
I got out of there so I wouldn't hit him.
I can accept he kissed another girl...
Bro, we're not committed.
He can kiss whoever he wants,
I can kiss whoever I want...
Was it good? It's over...
Every jack to his trade,
- but I can't accept some things.
- I'm shocked.
- Get it? I can't accept that.
I got really pissed.
I got really pissed
and it really bothered me. I want to...
You want to stay away.
Exactly. I don't want him.
What is it?
You slapped me in the face.
Come on, Nath.
I don't care if you're messing.
Don't do that.
- Did I slap you hard?
- I didn't like it. I got pissed.
Would you like it if I did it to you?
You did that to me many times.
You hit me three times in the gut.
Three times, remember?
Should a man slap a woman in the face?
You of all people?
Okay. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you...
I know you didn't. I know. That's why...
- Not in the least.
- I know you didn't.
- You know I didn't hit hard.
- I know.
I won't mess with you anymore.
Don't do that again.
You can mess with whoever...
Come here, dude.
The dance floor is rocking right now.
And it's fucking cold.
Let's have a great time!
If I hooked up with him...
He's a pain in the ass today.
I can't even talk to you,
and he comes to bother me.
Fuck. No.
Fuck. No?
We were joking around, talking,
and he slapped me in the face.
I thought about hitting him back
at that moment.
Anyway. I bounced...
Fuck, you're still into him?
Come on, Nathália.
Jesus Christ.
Luan is defending me.
I'm defending you. Fuck, man.
Thanks.
Welcome to our bus.
This is it!
Jesus Christ, man. Jesus Christ.
Is everything okay in here?
Why are you looking at her this way?
Leave her alone, you piece of shit.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
- Fuck you.
- Motherfucker!
- Luan, stop it.
- Fuck you, man.
- Get out of there.
- Luan, stop it.
Get out of there. He soaked Thais.
Luan, stop... Don't do this.
He soaked everybody in here,
soaked everybody but me.
You piece of shit. Fuck you.
Come on, man.
Hey, Luan... For Christ's sake, Luan.
It takes four men to stop me.
Can't you deal with me on your own?
You can't take me out yourself.
I wanna see you dealing with me.
Zip it!
Can you just shut up?
It's over.
Maybe we can talk? Can we talk?
I'm with you.
Now's not the best time.
Didn't you want to talk yesterday
when we were getting on the bus?
- Let's talk now.
- We've already talked.
Want to talk again?
I was drunk.
There's no more need.
Or else I'm gonna fuck things up.
You're thinking bad things about me.
I don't know what to tell you.
Okay, I'm wrong. Go with them...
No, no... I'm not saying you're wrong...
I never said that.
I'm just trying to say
that you're better than this.
But you don't see it.
You're not wrong. Everybody knows...
No... I don't want anybody to see it.
- Enough.
- So... But...
Enough, Bia, please.
Go with those girls,
leave me alone for a little bit.
Okay?
Then I said, "That's right."
I went to talk to Tay.
- At that time you joined Tay?
- That...
Yes. Tay.
That's all.
Everybody asked me, "Are you okay?"
I said, "Yep."
- Then Luan asked...
- After we talked?
Yep. After I said to Luan...
What we want is different from what I...
Honey, no. You got to...
No, it's not feel...
I don't love you,
I'm not in love with you!
Saying you love or not is a feeling.
No... I don't love you.
I'm not in love with you.
I respect you.
You don't know how to respect me.
Everybody is pissed, not only me.
I think I'm the least pissed.
Everybody is watching what you do.
The way you treat me, the way you act.
You don't have to agree.
If you are like this, you say,
"This is me.
I'm always going to do this."
Now's not the time.
You have to man up.
You're right about this.
No, I'm right about everything.
- I'm right about everything.
- Everything you're saying.
I'm sorry, but I'm right about everything.
I wish you well,
I don't wanna see you sad.
I know, me, too.
I'm sorry to tell you this.
I'm sorry, but, to me,
he's a man and you're a kid.
When a man realizes
someone is acting like a kid,
they take someone's side.
- I'm sorry to tell you this.
- It's okay...
But, to me, today...
Today he's the greatest.
That's fair.
- 'Cause he's got nothing to do with this.
- It's fair.
He's got nothing to do with both of us.
And he defended me.
I agree. That's true.
And you also could be... defending me.
I didn't behave well.
No, bro.
I wish I'd never met you. I swear.
That's it.
I'm hungry. Let's go.
Come eat, man. Sit, let's eat.
Look at this tasty food I made you guys,
one big plate.
I love you, my friend, you know?
You, too, my friend.
I'm going to miss those hot nights
in the Tiger Room.
I'm going to take over now.
- Do you want some salad?
- Yes.
We'll talk later.
I don't want to talk to you.
Don't look at me.
No problem.
What do you think about that slap?
- Bianca, talk to me.
- I...
I thought it was abusive...
I'd slap him back.
Guys, that depends on the vibe...
He wasn't aggressive...
- I thought...
- That vibe...
What do you think?
Maybe that happened when they had sex,
he thought he could do that to her.
That that could happen at the bar.
In the bedroom, it's fine.
She didn't like it.
She didn't like the slap.
Nobody likes it, right, guys?
But there's a pet peeve in a couple...
- He just can't beat her.
- But she's wrong.
He took a lot of makeup off of her face.
She didn't like it.
I'm not going to lie.
One time, when I was talking,
I was getting angry,
messing around. 'Cause I'm ridiculous.
Not ridiculous. You're authentic.
- Look...
- Hit me again.
I thought you were going to hit me.
A dick spanking is very different
from a real spanking.
For Christ's sake.
What does that have to do with it?
It doesn't give him the right...
She picked a fight
and then filed her nails.
It was a serious mistake, Nath.
Filing her nails
and eating chicken.
Big mistake, it was huge.
Luan wants to play the hero.
- What?
- I think he wants to play the hero.
Do you think that was all about one issue
or he has feelings for her?
No...
Absolutely.
He likes her.
I think he knew he'd win there...
Luan, I have nothing against you.
If you have an issue,
you just solve it,
you don't cause another one.
He wanted to fight and show off...
He'd look good.
You have to remember...
I think he has feelings for Nath.
Do you remember
he took care of her in the bedroom?
- Yes...
- Remember that?
- I don't agree.
- He took care of her.
He went there and got mad,
he was jealous of him.
He went there and defended her.
I wonder if he's just a good friend
or if he has ulterior motives.
But I don't know if
he has feelings for Nath...
- I think Nath may have feelings for him.
- For him. Really?
I wonder if they're swinging
in that house.
Did you hear her?
- She said, "Dude is awesome."
-"He's a man, you're a kid."
"He's a man, you're a kid.
He was awesome."
Talking to her was wrong.
She told him about the slap...
- Yeah...
- No, it was wrong...
She didn't admit to him
what he'd said to her.
It was wrong to apologize
and leave unfinished business.
After everything was settled,
she apologized to him.
He said, "I won't mess with you."
She talked to Luan at the party.
Luan was also wrong
because he didn't talk to Ramon.
He didn't have a straight talk with Ramon.
Everybody is wrong.
What happened?
Exactly, exactly...
- How many times we've been through this.
- Sure.
...something that's totally different.
- Yeah...
- That happens a lot.
I had a lot of trouble like this.
I thought I was completely right.
Then you know the truth
and feel embarrassed,
- and you say, "Fuck, I'm sorry."
- Yeah...
But... That's why I talk.
You can't say something
if you're not sure...
Man, but... In the heat of the moment,
you're stressed out,
you don't want to postpone it.
That's why you have to talk.
That's what I said last week.
Everybody was emotional, drunk.
Here, we are okay. It's different.
And it's strategic here.
Let's see if they'll talk it out
or keep fighting?
- I think there's going to be trouble.
- Yes.
- My brother.
- Good morning.
- Is everything all right?
- Yes.
You saw the girl riding a SUP over there?
A stand-up paddle?
- Do you want to go?
- Sure.
Let's go, then. Let's go SUP?
You're crazy, man.
Let's take a spin. Let's go SUP?
I'm going to get the SUP boards
with Ramon.
- Really?
- Yeah...
That's great.
- Fuck...
- Cool, I'm on my way.
Let's go, we'll be right back.
Let's go together. See ya.
- Look at this ride!
- Let's go.
Amazing car, man.
Calling...
Those who humble
themselves will be exalted.
Have you gone... SUP?
- Have you ever ridden a stand-up paddle?
- Yeah, I did.
- Race you later?
- Sure.
That's insane! Yeah...
Are we going to be in trouble?
We'll fall flat, bro.
We'll fall flat, but let's do it.
Bro, I think it's over there.
I wonder if they have SUP boards
over here.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Look who's there.
Are you okay?
I am, what about you? How is everything?
Things are great,
but I need my crush over here, right?
This house gets ugly without you.
I thought your vacation
would be longer.
I miss our parties
and getting wasted together.
Embarrassing ourselves.
Jeez.
Do you think you can come?
For us to embarrass ourselves?
I'm going to try.
I'm going to check the airline tickets.
Okay.
Pack your bags because I miss you.
Okay, I'm going to take a look.
I'm going to do my best.
Okay.
Bye. God bless you. Bye.
This is our show, right.
It's huge, huh.
The view isn't as pretty as the lake,
but the color of the sails...
There's a lot of sails, right.
There's another board here.
There's like 30 over here.
So many of them.
I got you this wider board.
- All right.
- It floats better.
It's better because not everybody
has experienced it.
It's going to be easy.
This one over there is pretty easy.
Is it good?
I'm going to get it.
We'll come back soon.
If you need us, we're here.
No, we'll return them soon.
- Let's go.
- You go first... This way.
Let's go.
Cool?
All set, bro. Thanks for everything.
- Have a nice paddle.
- Thanks.
- We're here!
- Hey, kids!
We're here!
We need help with the boards, man.
What are you doing?
Help me, bro. Fuck.
The phone wouldn't ring
if we weren't talking about it.
I wonder if we have to work...
Hello?
So... it's Ricardo.
Hi, are you all right, boss?
All right, then.
All right, then. Thanks.
Guys, the four of us
are going to work today.
- Damn...
- Everybody?
The four girls.
Let's go, guys!
Let's go!
Ramon, we need to talk.
Yeah...
We've talked a lot of times.
But I think this situation
is not good for me.
It's not that I don't want it,
just to make things clear,
but... I need some distance right now.
I don't know if you noticed,
I was more distant today.
Of course I noticed.
But I need some time for me,
because this situation
is making me feel bad.
I don't want the house
to be affected like it was.
I want you to have your space,
and that I have mine.
You do whatever you want.
I'll do whatever I want, what I feel.
- Live your life.
- Exactly.
Be cool. I noticed
you were different and...
I gave you some space,
even if you didn't talk to me.
Be cool. I totally understand.
I think, sometimes...
Although we liked each other,
we need some space...
If it's meant to be, it'll be.
That's it. Don't worry.
If you need me...
- Are you going upstairs?
- No.
Let's talk.
You're a pain in the ass...
Will you go with him?
I'm going to talk to Ramon.
When I talked to Nath
about touching her face,
I talked to her,
I apologized for what happened.
Then I heard things escalated,
with one person telling the story
to the next.
I imagine you heard it like,
"Ramon slapped Nathália in the face."
I did.
So I put myself in your shoes
and wondered how I'd deal with that.
I'd probably get mad.
Yes. Let me tell you some truths
you might enjoy or not.
Sure.
I see her hurting.
Bro, me and Bia...
I'm going to tell you what we have.
If she kisses somebody, I kiss, too.
We've talked about it.
But you don't let her live her life.
You have a... You shield her, you know?
But you're not protecting her as a friend.
- Nath is very defenseless.
- I believe that.
Nath is very defenseless, bro.
- Then there was that...
- That set it off.
Yeah, and it was not only that.
I saw it every day, man...
You know? I've already forgiven you.
I think you're a good man,
but you made a mistake.
- You didn't act like a man.
- I realize that.
That's important.
I also make mistakes.
I'm not perfect.
I don't wanna be perfect.
- Nobody is perfect.
- We learn from mistakes.
I think... Nobody is perfect.
Man, we realized how many
good things happened
- because of this mess.
- Because of it...
Got it? Wish you all the best, brother.
To us. Amen...
I hope the mood here
gets back to what it was.
It's going to...
If that depends on me, you know...
We ended this, and in time... Thanks.
That, which booze separates,
food reunites.
Amen!
We'll get back into the groove.
We're going to be in sync again.
- All right.
- We'll forget this.
Wish you all the best.
Amen. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's make some money.
My brother. Good job.
- Let's go.
- Baby.
- Hi, honey.
- Give me a hug.
Good job. Great.
I hope it's light. I hope it's wonderful.
Take care.
- God bless you.
- Bye, girls.
Bye.
Good evening, welcome.
Girl, there's a blond guy over there
who's just arrived.
I can't see.
He's hot!
Over there, black shirt.
Remember at Donna?
Murilo introduced me to a guy...
Let's see if he's the same.
He's not, this one is hotter.
I would have noticed.
I like blond guys.
What's up, baby?
What?
Didn't you ask me to come?
You're kidding me?
- I'm working.
- You just needed to call me.
I'm working right now.
I'll hug you soon.
This is Mauro, Blondie.
- How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
- Can I drink this?
- Are you going to mix us some cocktails?
Yes, coming right up.
I said the invitation... Were you nervous?
You don't need to be.
What would you like to drink?
Gin tonic.
Wait a minute, coming right up.
One gin tonic, please.
I'm kinda lost. Where is this place?
How long are you going to stay?
- I moved here.
- Wow!
Do you need some help?
- I missed you.
- Me, too.
- I was dying to see a familiar face.
- You needed a partner, right?
I needed a partner.
- It's very good to see you, man.
- Likewise.
- How are you?
- What's up?
- I'm Mauro.
- I'm Ricardo.
The bar's manager.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
Nathália, you need to take five, right?
To rest a little bit, take a walk...
I think I need...
Yeah. Switch places with... Taynara.
- Okay.
- Is it okay?
No... It's me.
- Now it's her turn.
- One Aperol.
Can I order, girl? Two Sex on the Beach.
- Yes.
- I ordered Aperol.
- Take care. Thanks.
- One Aperol.
- I missed you!
- I missed you.
It's good to see a familiar face.
Oh, my God.
I missed you.
I wonder if somebody
will cry tonight. Absolutely.
Yes... A lot. A lot.
Who? Ramon?
My baby!
We've come here for this.
Gaia left. Gaia left.
I like it this way.
That's a proper welcome,
with a kiss and all.
- How are you?
- Hi, what's up?
I noticed you're very happy.
You met your friend.
- Sure...
- Yeah... Break is over.
Let's get to work.
I'll be a happy worker.
You can wait the tables. Then we'll see.
That table over there needs service.
Can I get you anything?
Hey, girls...
What's up, what's up, what's up?
What's up, guys?
Hey, get me a Sex on the Beach.
They're here.
- They are?
- Yes...
This is my fellow citizen.
- Mauro.
- Really?
- What's up?
- Luan, my brother.
Have you already caught the flight?
- I have...
- Man, you're fast!
What's up, Mauro!
- What's up?
- Are you okay, kid?
Hi, São Paulo!
- I'm Ramon.
- What's up? I'm Mauro...
- Mauro...
- Let's do this!
- What's up?
- What's up, bro?
- How are you, bro?
- I'm great.
Treat him like a brother.
Nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
- Thanks, thanks.
He's my friend for all moments.
He wakes up with me...
Is he from Goiânia?
I think he is...
She spoke very highly of you.
Did she?
Remember that guy
Ramon said he didn't like?
The hot blond guy... He's here, right?
The one you were flirting with?
I want his number.
I'll go, I was already talking to him.
I'm going to get his phone number.
Maybe some other day. Okay?
Excuse me. Aren't you from Nonna?
- We've met at Donna.
- At Donna.
Don't you remember me?
- We talked for three minutes.
- Us?
Yes, you and I...
That blondie friend of yours
and one friend of mine.
I don't remember.
Do you work there?
I play there, I work there.
Now, I remember.
Exactly.
Somebody wanted to kiss you,
but you were working.
Now I remember.
Exactly.
I got it.
There's going to be
a great party the day after tomorrow.
Not like Art's,
but it's a party with style.
At Jurerê. I'm going to play.
It'd be awesome if you come.
It's gonna be awesome later.
The whole gang is
going to be there.
Sure, bring everybody.
This party will be amazing.
I'm gonna get your number
for this party later.
It'll be on Thursday.
Let's go, go with me.
It's gonna be amazing.
What music do you play?
I play electronic.
I'll get your beers
and I'll be right back.
It's a deal. Tell them.
Girls, wrap up what you're doing here...
In two minutes,
you are free to enjoy the party.
I'll handle this.
You're really something...
Everybody is drunk.
Really?
Baby, you deserve no harm at all.
No...
I won't harm you at all.
I hope so.
I'll wait for my guest.
I hope he stays forever.
I'm going to show you the bed.
I approve this. It's approved.
- Upstairs?
- Yes.
There's a double bed
and bunks for singles,
which isn't the case for us.
- Where are we going to sleep?
- Here.
I just want to know.
I don't believe this.
Are you sure?
Hi.
Is anybody here?
Nobody is in here.
This must be the friend...
Yes...
The couple from Goiás slept here.
Leave them alone.
Our bedroom is huge, bro.
This is my bed.
- Is this your bed?
- Yeah.
Go, Ju!
- Go, João!
- Come on, clean it.
- That's my bed.
- Luan saw...
- Yeah, right.
You're fucked up.
You're going to sleep
in the Tiger Room.
I've already slept there.
- Okay. Hey.
- Come on. It's okay.
...get Murilo out of there.
This bed is mine.
You're annoying.
Fuck off, Nath.
Go away, go away, go away,
go away, go away.
You're going to sleep on the Tiger's bed.
You're sleeping on the Tiger Room.
- Murilo and Tay are going to sleep here.
- Go away.
You're fucking with me.
Fuck you, Murilo.
- No. Fuck you.
- Go fuck yourself.
This whole drama is your fault.
She wants to have a boyfriend
And I know pretty well how all this ends
Now this is the life
Fucking every day
Waking up naked with Nath by your side
Dear Lord.
Oh, my God. I loved this episode!
Nathália brought her dream boy.
I don't know, dude came in.
Everything happened,
but she didn't like it...
She likes Ramon. She's in love.
I think she is...
She doesn't have a good strategy.
What is a good strategy?
To kiss in front of a friend
of the person you're targeting.
She wanted to rub it in his face.
She invited that guy to have sex with her.
And she kissed the guy in front of him.
She invited an old lover,
a boy she was already intimate with.
She kissed a lot in front of him.
It was clear she'd fuck the dude...
Then he looked and said,
"I'm not doing anything either."
He wasn't going to show...
But it did more damage to her than to him.
He wasn't going to show he was pissed.
But he wasn't even pissed.
Looks like he understood
she didn't want him anymore.
No, he was. He didn't show it.
He was pissed 'cause he was ditched.
He wasn't pissed. He got mad
because she called him a boy,
that she wished had never met him.
It was over for him that moment.
He said, "I'm over this girl.
I'm over her.
That shows Luan... Luan's done so much.
She said she was mad
and was going to his bed.
She went to his bed,
she was sleeping with him.
Who was the fuckup now?
Was it Luan who defended her?
Or was it her,
who made up that fanfic...
I think it's exactly that.
- It's gone bad, John.
- Bro, that's it.
Then they are not going to look
like Murilo and the other girl.
Nathália is not...
Man, she wanted to hurt him
and it backfired.
She invited him and now
she'll have to put up with him
while she wants other...
- She's fucked up.
- She went overboard.
Everything was wrong.
Nathália screwed up. And so did Luan.
Now he's like, "I defend her."
- Taking meat to the barbecue is wrong.
- She screwed up.
I think that, in the end,
Nathália's strategy didn't work. Right?
Because she was mad in the end...
I thought Ramon was great.
Yeah...
He didn't insult her.
He didn't want to tease her.
He was amazing.
- He apologized to Luan...
- He didn't play...
- And to her.
- I'd be Ramon's friend. Absolutely.
- Let's watch the rest of it.
Girl...
Ramon is with somebody, easy.
Let's go out to funk dance?
MOMMIES
ARE HERE
- Friday night at home, bro?
- Fuck you!
The girls left the guys at home
and went funk dancing...
- And Nathália was crying because of Ramon?
- She wasn't crying.
She came in, the girls said,
"Stay there."
I think she was
trying to tell something...
Let's watch to find out, guys.
- But it's next week.
- Come on.
Come on, guys.
Hey, Amazon, I know
I have the premium package.
Send it home.
I can't wait to see it.
Oh, no, I can't wait until then.
I'm going to check some threads...
I just wanted to know
if João is going to fuck...
If he'll keep banging next week.
No, I'm sure, you got it right...
I'm going to the bathroom.
Can we go? For Christ's sake.