I'm super excited!
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
THE REVIEW
- Yep, me, too!
- Me, too.
All good?
- What's up?
- How are you doing?
Hey, hi!
So, are you ready to start?
- I'm excited.
- What's happening?
A lot has happened.
Bia had an argument with Luan...
Luan slept on the couch...
It's a circus. I'm shocked.
What a mess.
I was shipping this couple
and now I'm un-shipping them.
- Hit play.
- With my heel.
Hit that play, Bia.
I love that play.
He slept in the living room.
- He slept in the living room.
- Luan.
He slept
in the living room.
My boy over there.
- He got burned.
- João's not yours?
- No, it's Luan, I've changed.
- Okay.
Who's coming downstairs?
She is.
- Yes, it's her.
- It's her.
Yeah, she woke up like Carol,
wearing shades... Got it?
She wakes up like Carol.
She turned around.
She saw him and bounced.
Jeez, she saw him and turned around.
- Rewind this.
- I wonder if there is.
She went there like this,
"I'm hungry, I want bread and coffee.
Oops, the loser!"
"I won't start my day like this."
Murilo is hooking up with her.
My boyfriend.
That's my couple, let me in.
- I'm kidding.
- Pabllo's boy.
Murilo, you are my boy. Know this.
I loved that little room.
Guys, my makeup! My brand.
Is that your makeup?
I knew it, man.
I knew there was an Easter egg.
Thanks, guys.
This is so Amazon Prime,
there's an Easter egg.
Thanks, guys.
Forget it.
Forget it, no worries.
I slept alone,
didn't have breakfast with you guys.
I'm not going to stay in this vibe.
Keep that vibe.
I like seeing you like that.
Telling it like it is.
Drama queen.
I think it's cool he says "vibe."
I find "vibe" to be a cool word.
"Vibe" is like "top."
"Vibe" is similar to "top."
I don't know what to say,
I say, "What a vibe."
What a vibe.
It won't ever come out of my mouth.
Neither "vibe" nor "top."
This show is "top."
Topper is better.
I think men always have
a partnership like that.
But women, too.
See how all of them are united?
I hope so.
Putting on makeup...
- Yeah. What?
- Even the...
I think men are more united.
Yeah, it's obvious.
Sadly, we hold grudges
because we're more dramatic.
A lot more than men.
- What do you guys think?
- What? I think...
Women are better...
So, women are mentally faster.
He didn't even drink...
It's too much Red Bull. Mentally faster.
They organize things better.
They don't take over the world
because they fight amongst themselves.
- Gay people, too.
- It's true.
Gays are united.
Women don't take over the world...
...because they are jealous...
Gay people still are,
but there's a part which is not.
There's a separation everywhere.
Guys are like this.
They mess up with each other...
But women? What?
- Gay people don't.
- That's true.
But gay people are not totally united.
Jesus Christ!
Yeah, so...
Mess with João
and see if I don't take Pabllo's wig off.
That's gossip.
Everything has to be discussed.
Since he said he's going
to change his vibe,
he'll be a good person. Let's wait.
- I think so.
- Yeah...
He's got to know
if Nathalia's into it,
I think she's not. She's upset...
Girl, it's obvious.
That pretty girl,
in the middle of the others...
He made a scene.
Do you guys think
he's going to hook up with her friend?
I don't think so.
Well, girls,
I was talking to the guys here...
I was talking to the guys here
and I apologized, okay?
I was out of line with you, too.
I'm sorry.
Let me give you a hug.
I want us to be good.
Let me kiss you...
He's fixing it.
You see? Women hold a grudge.
You say, "I fucked up, do you forgive me?"
"Are you mad at me, baby?" "No, I'm not."
"No, I'm not mad. Be cool..."
Yeah, I think so, too.
No! I don't forget it.
I'll tell you something.
This season will end,
and she's going to rub it in his face.
Exactly.
- Look at the face.
- You see?
The guy laughed, and she's very angry.
I told you she's like this...
"I'm very angry."
Guys, does she have to smile at him?
He's in a good mood, maybe she's not.
Does she have to be in a good mood
right at that moment?
Guys, think about the food.
Carrots, tomatoes,
rice, beans, and chicken.
I loved it.
- I'm checking the food.
- You only talk about food.
They have a boat now.
Those guys...
I know.
Imagine staying in a house
with open bar, food, women, boat...
The boat is coming with someone.
The boat belongs to the mayor's son...
Look. No, I think...
Oh, my God, it's my sugar daddy. It's him.
The owner of the boat is arriving.
He's the boat owner.
Is it possible? Are we riding on a boat?
I can't believe it.
Crazy, man.
For real? For real?
- Who is it?
- João loves a boat, right?
He loves being the center of attention.
Check out his look in the boat.
It's Zé Neto and Cristiano.
Does he look like him?
He could be gay, right?
To make that group better.
Hi, guys, how are you doing?
Ladies and gents.
- Doing good?
- Right. How are you guys?
Just fine.
Wow, the sheriff.
- Did you see it?
- Yeah...
I'm Ricardo, manager of the bar
where you're going to work.
Jeez, seriously?
Yes, it is.
You like serious men like him...
- She liked him.
- Is this the kind of guy you like?
Leave the door open
for you to go on the boat.
Bearded... Bearded man
from a barber shop...
He goes to a barber shop
to get the beard oiled?
The guys were like, "Fuck, a boat!"
"I'm the manager of the bar..."
- The guys went...
- Oops.
Right on time.
They thought they'd be
parading on a boat...
Who wants to work during vacation?
I think that will be the reward.
They're going to work, but...
...they're taking the boat.
I hope so, right?
D-I-C-K, vacation. No one wants to work.
- What?
- D-I-C-K, vacation.
"D-I-C-K, VACATION"
DROPS, JOHN
It took me some time to understand.
Fun!
I'd like to invite you to come see
the place. I have a boat waiting for us.
I already like the boss.
- Awesome!
- Can we go now?
- What a job!
- Now!
- All right.
- Wonderful.
Can we drink on the job?
We'll talk about it later.
"Can we drink on the job?"
"Can I drink?"
Priorities, right?
Even the boat's name is "Naked Moon."
When I go to Floripa...
Look at their job.
He's going to work on the boat.
My dream is having sex like this,
on high seas.
- Never?
- Never done it.
Stop it.
You don't know what you're missing.
Have you done it?
- No.
- Of course not.
I've done it.
Let's go to the bar.
NAKED MOON
- Easy now.
- Okay.
- On the sand, over there.
- Look at this.
- Guys, come on.
- That's beautiful.
I'd work wearing a bikini, serving people.
And a wet, tied blouse like that.
I'd take a sip of each drink I served.
But today is the only day you get
to enjoy the place, too.
Today, I'm paying the tab. It's all free.
I wish my boss said that.
Guys, the owner will have a big loss.
Guys, that's my dream.
That's a wonderful job.
They'll be registered workers?
- No.
- Of course not.
...going to pay them in booze?
Registered workers?
One of those dudes
should be dying to work.
But it's obvious...
I won't work here.
I'd rather work over there...
In Mato Grosso.
Bottom line, they work to get laid
and get laid to work.
- Right. It's insane.
- Wild and Free.
We need someone who knows...
- Carol.
Carol is a guru.
She's there, few words, few ideas...
She says the right thing...
What did you think about that work day?
Man, I think it's cool, right?
Once, I was sleeping at home...
- Carol.
- Door open...
- She's always cool.
- Door open.
What do you think about this episode...
I tuned the fan on.
I found it very easy. Piece of cake.
Did it have to be hard?
- Yes, it did.
- I see.
It's gotta be hard...
Hard work...
Carol's fan does all the hard work.
Now I got it...
That's the only thing that works hard.
I like being with you...
We had something good going on.
Somehow, we went from heaven to hell in...
In a second.
It's cold here.
Look, it's coming back.
That bullshit is coming back.
I need more than that, you know?
Because I'm going to end up getting hurt.
I only asked to be respected, got it?
I really...
I just want to enjoy myself.
I just want to be happy...
Nathalia likes booze, too, see?
Nathalia likes it.
It's a DTR.
I'll tell you something...
When you make out with her...
Are you jealous?
She's honest, I like her.
What did I say
at the beginning of this show?
"Are you jealous?"
Two days later, go...
Guys, they're having a great experience.
- This intensifies it.
- Yeah...
- It's obvious.
- What?
Did you choke on the olive?
Dramatic pause.
Let me say something.
First of all, it's a unique experience.
They're taking a hell of a trip.
They're not spending any money.
It's inevitable things get more sensitive.
So, it could be...
More sensitive?
Things could happen,
but I can't feel jealousy
for anyone in two days.
I'm already feeling jealous
of Mariano here...
Why?
He's looking at me differently.
Imagine on day two.
If I get him to come over here,
would you kiss him?
In a heartbeat, brother.
Guys, weren't they going to work,
for Christ's sake?
No, they're allowed to drink.
- I get it.
- Day off.
They drink one day and work the next.
Guys, if I had a VIP pass and a drink,
I wouldn't bother anyone.
That looks like a trap, huh?
"No need to ask. Just kiss me."
Look, it's the blonde in white pants.
Oh, yeah?
- Are you in?
- Let's go.
I'll go with you. I'll go with you.
That one is an outsider.
Go ahead.
Is he hiring?
There's one who's an outsider.
Is he hiring a guy to hit on...
That's the outsider...
Wearing the dark jacket.
Man! She's a fucking hurricane!
I just don't like
that mockery, "Oh, kiss!"
- Let them kiss.
- Twelve years old.
There. Enough already.
Go ahead and talk to him.
- What's your name?
- I'm Thais.
She's shaking all over.
Blondie is fast.
A little game of pool... Hot weather...
Jeez, I'm bad at pool.
- I play well.
- This is so Pabllo playing pool.
- Girl, I love pool.
- Really?
Do you guys play?
I love pool, but I suck at it.
I have a table at home,
I really play.
After this we're going to your place.
Let's go now!
I'm going to pocket you.
I don't want...
Making a mess in other people's houses.
Pocket it.
That's delicious.
Yummy, right?
I want to see it.
If someone says this...
A lot of new people...
I see two outsiders.
João hasn't hooked up with anyone yet.
I'll tell you something,
João is hiding his game.
- Got it?
- She's beautiful.
He's not going to hook up...
but he's talking to a dozen girls
at the same time outside the house.
João kissed women at some parties...
It's João Drops.
He kissed two girls already.
He didn't fuck anyone.
He just kissed. He's there.
I want to know if he has a big dick.
Shut up, man.
Oops, I said it out loud.
Are you going to play games with me now?
This is no game.
Don't you want it?
If you don't want it...
No, I do want it.
Do you?
I don't want to be an idiot.
All that acting and now
they're going to make out again.
What did I say, Mariano?
There's no way. That's what I said.
- That's a mistake.
- Luan is with her again.
- They got back together.
- He kissed her.
That is love, guys.
Now the sex is going to be better, huh?
- You see? Look.
- Yes, it is.
If Carol said it, then it'll be.
I love a kiss like that.
Wow, they nailed it, guys.
Go, João!
João!
Are they rooting for João to kiss someone?
If he won, he'd hook up with someone.
If she doesn't win, he'll kiss her.
Is that it?
Did you know? Do you remember?
Did he win?
If he won, he'd hook up with someone.
With that girl who's playing with him.
Yeah.
She wasn't even that...
The coolest thing,
he's wearing a banana shirt
and banana shorts, too.
- Look, João hooked...
- It's an outfit.
He had to win to hook up with her.
João hooked up with a babe, bro. I'll say!
Yeah.
Look at her. She's a babe.
Jeez, he has to ruin the kiss with...
That girl is like, "Oh, my God!"
What?
That girl is like, "What am I doing?"
But she's cute.
She's beautiful.
- She's pretty.
- See?
Oh, my God.
He's going downhill...
Things are going to get worse.
You know when the boy...
Now it's going down...
Let me tell you,
everyone's going to the house.
That's no shocker.
Everyone's going...
That girl went with them.
Really?
- Will João get laid?
- Yep. It's tonight.
- Look.
- Ouch.
Is he taking her home?
- He is.
- Go.
He's going to get laid.
He took her. No escape.
No, what for?
Is he going to have sex in the shower?
If she's going there, they'll have sex.
Where will they have sex?
He's going to have sex?
I wouldn't miss that.
That's true.
Who thinks he'll have sex,
raise your hand.
I think he's going to have sex...
I think it'd be right.
I don't know. I'm scared.
I think it'd be nicer.
Even if he doesn't want to,
he will because of his friends.
If he doesn't have sex...
You're saying the guy can't fuck anyone.
If he doesn't have sex,
you're going to order a pizza...
João Drops.
Go, João! Have sex. Those...
Do you know what I think?
They've learned on day one
they can't fight...
- Everyone is...
- Pretend you're a friend.
Everyone's scoring.
- Look.
- That was good.
They are getting João's girl drunk
...she's going to have sex with him.
- Yeah, I don't know.
- But she wants it.
- She wants it.
- She doesn't.
She went there to play checkers.
If you guys notice, João is right there.
Drinking, too.
Look.
- Jack Sparrow.
- Wow.
Who knows what satanic liquid
they're drinking.
I wish I was...
It's Rihanna's piss. Rihanna's piss.
- João?
- What?
Ouch.
You're so delicious, Luan.
What is it, bro?
Introduce your wife to them.
Look at João...
- Neiva, get over here! Neiva!
- Dear Neiva.
- Who?
- Not even a small sign, Neiva?
What's going on?
Joyce, I'm coming.
Fuck!
Let's pause a minute to talk.
Luan's body is beautiful!
Luan's body is really beautiful...
You're not jealous, are you?
All of them are really beautiful.
But Luan has something. He's manly, girl.
- He smells good...
- I wish I could get Luan's mic.
Bia is nice, huh. I'll say!
That's delicious. I do the same.
Just give me half an hour.
I bet nobody here can eat a raw egg.
That João doesn't want to fuck.
Yeah, bro. What "raw egg," João?
Go fuck yourself.
João is a pushover...
At a moment like this,
he wants to eat a raw egg?
- Go fuck...
- Did you hear it?
Wow.
If you swallow a raw egg...
Obviously, I'll kiss you. Got it?
She meant...
I'd eat the shell and the egg box.
Oh, yeah? That's crazy.
I'd eat the whole chicken.
I'd fuck the farm owner to fuck...
...you're going to fuck anyone but me.
His mouth would stink.
Just brush your teeth.
Fuck! Tasting like huevos.
He's going to fuck her.
"Now I'm going to hatch my chick."
He kisses real nice, girl.
He's very romantic, guys.
I think he won't.
Twelve hours kissing that girl...
That's not possible, man.
João is very soft.
Listen, here's the thing.
Ouch, you rascal.
I don't want to fuck you anymore.
Oh, my God!
Fuck...
I told you, guys! I told you, guys!
I don't want to see.
- I told you.
- Oh, my God.
What did he say to that woman?
"I don't want to fuck you"?
Rewind it, I even broke the mic.
There's no need to rewind it, look at her.
- No...
- Oh, no, João!
Wait, wait, guys.
Sweetheart... She wants it.
Holy shit, hit play.
- Girl...
- Wait.
No, wait, everyone, quiet.
Listen, here's the thing.
I don't want to fuck you anymore.
I want to hang out with you.
He said, "I don't want to fuck you."
Sweetheart?
Go have sex, boy.
Look at the boy there.
Jesus Christ!
Look at those two.
They're idiots, man. I'm talking to you.
Hard to believe.
I can't believe it.
Guys...
Are they going to have sex?
Everyone is laughing at him.
Man, João, João is messing up.
When I'm partying hard
and my alcohol levels are above my neck...
If someone said,
"Come on, I don't want...
Let's just talk."
What would I say? I'd just say no, okay?
I'm not snuggling in bed
with someone when I'm drunk.
Talking? Wake up!
She didn't want it,
and he tried to talk her into it,
using some lame excuse.
"I want to chat with you."
He should've been more straightforward.
Don't you think, Carol?
- Crazy!
- I think...
I think she wasn't...
He's asking to have sex.
He's begging, you know?
- His balls must hurt, right?
- Be cool...
You never thought
you were going to meet me.
I like you a lot, man.
Half for you, half for me.
She's sharing her pizza,
and he wants to eat...
She's got a romantic vibe.
He wants to eat pussy.
She shares her pizza...
Do you want to do it or not?
Don't be mad, man.
We're enjoying this moment.
I'm not mad. I'm just sad.
Man...
He's crying!
Fuck!
What a man does when he wants to get laid.
He even cries...
Holy shit!
Look. "We have so much in common.
We're a couple." That's crazy.
Please, rewind it.
- What the hell...
- Fuck, man.
- God...
- Look at João!
Holy shit!
Do you want to spend the
night here? Or do you want to leave?
Look, Thais has a long face, too, look.
"Do you want to spend the night here?"
It's not that.
Man, what's going on with those guys?
Everyone is in love, right? Yeah...
She wants to dismiss him...
This is good sense, right?
That dude wants to stay there.
He wants to become a participant.
I hate sleeping with someone
I've just fucked.
Guys, don't ask me
because I'll tell a different story...
Don't ask me...
Come on, Carol, tell us.
But be brief, Carol.
Tell us a short story, come on.
Please. "In 1972, my grandma..."
- Just a little bit, a nugget.
- Go.
I have a song called,
"Propaganda Enganosa."
It goes, "The guy is handsome,
has two daughters..."
Holy fuck.
"Send me a picture of your dick."
I thought, "The guy's gotta have a dick."
Okay. We started talking.
We made a date.
When I realized,
I was talking for three hours with him...
Oh, no.
I thought, "Man, won't this guy
invite me to fuck?"
Then I thought...
"Hey, buddy, let's go
to the room and do it."
"Buddy." How intimate.
He said, "Let's do it."
When we were in the room,
the only thing he did was suck me...
And nothing else.
Fuck, man. God, what's going on?
- Praying, you started praying.
- When he started...
I swear to God,
he stuck his dick two times,
I got up and said,
"Buddy, I'm not feeling well,
I don't drink..."
I went to the bathroom,
started talking to the mirror.
I said, "I'm going to go back there
and kick his ass."
How come he talks to me
without having a dick?
Did he have a tiny dick?
He had no dick, man! No dick!
- I said, "I'm going to kill him!"
-"Dear Neiva."
Then I started walking around
the backyard.
It was already morning.
I was very sweaty, horny big time...
Then what happened?
I wrote this song, "Propaganda Enganosa."
Do you send nudes?
I send nudes.
I think it's amazing sending nudes.
Do you receive a lot of nudes?
Speaking of which,
boys send me nudes that I love.
It's the only English sentence she knows.
She memorized that text just because...
Let's go back...
For Christ's sake. Look.
He kissed the broom. Look.
He'll stick it in his ass. He should.
Stop it... Will he masturbate?
What the fuck, man.
He's going to masturbate
his ass with the...
Not with the broom, right?
He's going to sleep with the stick.
- Call me, João.
- Guys...
- João let me down...
- It's embarrassing.
Is he a Pisces? He's a Pisces.
He's desperate.
Do you wanna know his sign?
I don't believe in that tear over there.
He's desperate.
- Every emotion is extreme.
- He was trying to get laid, at any cost.
I think he's out of control.
He'll even cry to get laid, man.
He was desperately
trying to get laid.
Tears of horniness.
I think it's a mix of booze
and a desire of getting laid.
I think that's it, guys.
João is wrong
for addressing women as "bro."
I think "chick" and "bro"
is better than "girlfriend".
-"Bro" is not that bad.
- No...
Girl, I love when a boy...
Do you know what turns me on?
When a boy comes and says,
"How are you doing, princess?"
What?
The boy comes and says,
"Hey, princess, let's go over there."
I love "queen of backcountry."
Do you like "princess"?
Obviously. I get super horny.
I like it when they call me "bandit."
She likes men that cry,
do the right thing,
and call her "bandit."
Where is she going to find them?
Look, let me explain.
My childhood nickname is "bandit."
Where's my wallet?
Then I know guys and they say,
"Hey, MC Carol."
What? It's not MC Carol.
That is my stage name.
Here, it's "bandit."
Take this away.
Bandit.
Did you get some sleep?
- No.
- I didn't.
No?
I didn't sleep well at all.
Where's your man?
He just won't leave.
I think he took it seriously when I said
I'd take him in my luggage.
Yes...
- How do you feel?
- I don't know.
Have you talked to him?
I'll talk to him.
He's going to... He's hot.
He's hot, a prince. Very cute.
He loves snuggling.
He turned his head to the side...
Don't you want to get his number?
What are you going to say to him?
I don't know.
I'm not good at asking people to leave.
Just say, "Time to say goodbye."
Bye!
I'd pay, at least,
for the boy's transportation back home.
- I'd say, "Hey, buddy."
- Yes.
We're going to get dressed and all.
Maybe I'll take a shower before I leave.
I think I'm leaving, too.
Do you know where your stuff is?
No.
- I'll help you.
- I guess I do.
I'm going to look for my things.
It's not possible.
She's cute.
He exaggerated. No good sense.
He has no good sense...
It's real quick.
Explain something to me.
When you have sex,
what do you do afterwards?
You go away just like that?
That depends a lot. Because...
Guys.
I'd rather go to the person's place.
If the place is bad, I bounce.
You don't have to send the person away.
And I bounce when it's over.
I hate sleeping with someone
I've just fucked,
especially...
Don't ask me
because I'll tell another story...
Carol would be sleeping.
I'll tell you one move of mine...
Carol would be already sleeping.
Yeah... Bianca, for example.
I say to Bianca, "Girl, watch out."
Then Bianca calls me and say,
"Girl, I need you now. Get over here now."
Right.
"Hey, baby, unfortunately,
I'll have to leave."
There's always a way out.
Or you say
you have an appointment after the sex.
I don't have to say it.
There's going to be...
I'd rather go to the person's place...
There's going to be.
I'm saving on transportation.
- Are you pointing at me?
-"The person's..."
Street, avenue...
She looked said, "Person's place."
I'd rather go to the person's place.
If it's bad, I bounce.
Yeah, it's better
than dismissing the person.
This avoids the embarrassment.
Come on!
Let's go! Yay! Fuck, let's go!
Hey! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
All good.
We have arrived.
Whoa! Skate park.
Look at that.
I'm a little jealous.
Are you jealous?
I wanted to be like you, but I can't.
Shameless. Funny.
- Look!
- Funny thing is... Look.
Did I give you any reason to be jealous?
No, and even if you did...
You're not jealous? I'm a little jealous.
Not if I trust the guy.
Hey, bro. I...
If there's one thing that
drives me crazy, it's jealousy.
They started fighting again.
They're going to be the couple...
There's always a bad atmosphere.
...do you expect me to be Zen about it?
You'll never see that.
That's fine.
When a woman says something like that,
hit the pause.
Things will get ugly.
She's starting to get jealous.
It's the same if a woman comes
into a room, you are talking...
You're watching TV and she says,
"Let me tell you something,
I'm not going to fuck you."
You didn't even mention sex
and she said, "I won't fuck you."
You go ahead and do it...
I'll be honest with you.
I like you, but...
- That's the point.
- I know.
But, brother, I'm totally free.
I'm totally free.
When the time comes...
And you've always
made it very clear to her.
I'm going to sit down with her...
I'm going to say, "Here's the thing..."
Or you... No, no.
Brother, it's not going to happen anymore.
It's your decision to make.
I don't want the girl
to have any more expectations.
I want to roll with you.
João is so emotional.
João is a... Holy shit, man.
João became a good friend. The buddy...
Yeah...
If he sits down with her
and says, "Look..."
He was honest.
I think it's better
than messing things up...
Yes.
It's straight talk,
but she's upset, look.
Look at that person's face,
who likes to be unattached.
She's very upset.
Man, she's hunting him.
- She's looking for trouble.
- Yes, exactly.
No, it wasn't like that.
He stalled a little to tell her that.
Yes, he kind of stalled.
He didn't stall.
He doesn't want that anymore, man.
He had to say it from the beginning.
There are some people...
Yeah, I'd be upset.
They're in a house.
Above all, you have to talk.
Are you all right?
I just have to pee, that's all.
- Come on.
- What's up?
- I heard João saying some stuff to Murilo.
- Seriously?
João said,
"You're going to be a player again, right?
Back to the game." And then he...
- João? João?
- Jo... Girl...
João?
Come on, girlfriend.
One, two, three and... Whoa!
Who can chug it faster? Go, go, go!
Taynara went to the party.
Look at João's face...
She's right. Go, Taynara!
Check out the drama.
Check out the music.
He's drinking, right, huh, fellow.
Paola Bracho.
Do you want drama? Slow-motion scene.
It's drama.
Brazilian version, Herbert Richers.
They're really drinking.
Ouch.
You're done, Taynara.
Don't play his game.
It's hard to resist, I know,
but don't do it.
Don't do it...
Look at John eating all the food.
- The food ended up on his lap.
- Yes, man.
He put the plate on his lap.
I'm still in control.
I need a shower. I feel like I stink.
He's bathing her wearing clothes.
Wait...
Hey...
Get out of there, João!
João, get out of there!
Emotional João...
Every time you have a chat...
- Every time you have a chat...
- Please.
- I end up getting hurt.
- Stop talking. Easy.
- Man, have I ever...
- What? Easy, my ass!
Easy, my ass! I'm furious!
Murilo, you need to be more sensitive
to my feelings.
And I'm not? I'm not?
Do you think I'm doing you wrong?
I really came here to fight...
Saline. Make her drink this.
Saline, guys.
Saline. He got seawater to give her.
Fuck, take this water from Praia Grande.
How cute. Saline.
Guys, there's always someone...
It's that famous...
It's like you're fighting.
In the middle of the situation.
Holy shit, right?
...will talk to you in the bedroom.
No, I want you out of here.
I'll get out.
I'm taking you to the bedroom safely.
...it's dangerous in the bathroom.
Really.
"I want to take a longer shower!"
I've never seen anyone
crying to take a shower.
Man, she's wasted.
They suffer for everything...
"I want to take a longer shower!"
I want you out of here.
I'll get out of here...
That's the best, girl.
Hey, stay here. Come here.
Stay with her in the bathroom.
I'm done with it.
What did he say?
He's done with it.
Girl, stop saying this shit.
What happened? What's going on, girl?
What happened is that Murilo makes me cry.
I think I'd react differently.
"Go crazy with me."
She put on a little show,
"We're doing it today."
Then she got hammered.
She's like me. Look at that pot...
She's eating. That's the best.
Let me ask you something.
When you overheard...
- Careful there.
- Sit down. Over there.
My only problem
is that he told me he liked me
and then he said he didn't feel anything,
that my heart doesn't belong to him.
But did he say that?
He did. To my face, in front of Blondie.
A flower is always nice.
The boy gave a flower,
but he gave his heart.
No, no, no...
- But she's got your heart.
- No, she hasn't.
If he doesn't acknowledge my feelings,
shut up.
- That's all I ask.
- Careful there.
I'm not a child.
Yes, she's consistent.
Sit and tell me exactly like it is.
Even if I was very drunk, I'd never...
That bunk bed is in pain, huh.
That bunk bed is in pain!
I've never gone up on a bunk bed...
"Relax. Just relax.
If I said I'm with you,
if I ever screw up,
you'll be the first to know."
And if he's honest and you don't like it?
But he said it.
What's the truth?
That he's a player?
He was always upfront with you.
Then you fucking hurt me.
Look me in the eye. Look me
in the eye and say, "I'm a player.
What we have in the house is one thing.
Out here, it's a different story."
- Enough, João.
- The house is the house.
I just need honesty. I was upset today...
He's being upfront with you.
I was very upset today because...
Girl, I didn't even know
what was going on.
You were assuming things, then.
No! She said,
"But aren't you falling for her?"
And he said,
"No. Not falling for her at all."
Then, in the afternoon,
Thais says he's falling for me and shit.
He says, "Not even close."
Everyone is drunk, that's funny.
It's drunk talk, man.
I'm loving it.
Just like me, wasted in the clubs.
She's upset because he said he liked her,
then he said he didn't...
I'm like this when I buy gin...
She's taking it out on João.
When I buy gin and there's no tonic,
I get like this.
She's taking it out on João.
What does João...
She doesn't want...
João is going...
He's going to cry. Don't do this to him.
- Look, she's pissed at João.
- Fuck!
People's energy...
So don't tell me...
Fuck! She's taking it out on João, man.
Oh, my God.
It's not a lie.
- That got me very upset.
- The thing is...
I hate people who talk and touch me.
Are you zooming in?
Take your hands off me!
...to hook up with several people.
Look what you're doing with me.
"Stop it, I'm going to cry!"
Out of the blue.
That's why I was mad. He told me...
Screw it. Look, I'm your brother, man.
Don't fucking shove me.
Brother, brother.
What's going on?
Girl!
They are in Narnia, right?
Her! Her!
Don't just say shit.
Don't just say stuff you don't mean...
Easy. Shit, take it easy!
He didn't mean that.
That's all I asked.
Both points of view.
What happened?
I didn't see, I was in the bathroom.
I don't even know, bro.
It was completely senseless.
He didn't hook up with another woman.
He didn't do anything.
He was sincere.
He said, "I'm not as involved as you are."
But he told it to João.
The other girl went there
and played broken telephone.
- You get it?
- Chinese whispers?
Oh, yeah, Chinese whispers,
that's when they talk.
If it's broken, you can't hear it.
- It could be.
- Makes sense.
If it's broken, you can't hear it.
It's got to be Chinese whispers.
Have you ever been dumped like this?
That guy didn't say a thing
and started messing up
while they were drinking.
What if he hooks up with...
He didn't hook up with anyone.
He didn't do anything wrong.
He wakes up...
"I'm going to keep seeing her."
- Then what?
- Hold on.
It's not about,
"It's not going to happen."
That's obvious.
He was avoiding it for a very long time,
two days, actually.
He was playing her from the beginning
and now he says,
"I don't want it anymore."
How do you mean, playing?
He was kind of... Kind of undecided.
- They were having a good relationship.
- Right!
They were getting along pretty well.
That guy came in the house and said,
"Bro, I won't date."
Did you hear what he said?
"Are you going to be my woman?"
"So, let's have fun
while we'fre we're here."
She liked him more than he liked her.
And she got hurt.
He realized that,
if he got involved with her,
he'd have to stay only with her...
Here's the thing, we're here talking
because I'm sure, on the next episode...
...Murilo is going to hit on that girl.
He's going to kiss her again...
And everything's all right.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
So, it was all for nothing?
I'm not... Do you think I'm a fool?
For me, kissing...
For me, kissing has a lot of feelings.
What about fucking? No?
- I see!
- That's fucked up.
Guys, I had sex, look.
No!
- That's a lie!
- João!