WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
THE REVIEW
Remember the fight
between Bia and Nathalia,
- who argued because of Luan.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
- It's unbelievable.
Unbelievable, brother.
Let's watch this?
Go, pass me the remote.
Press play with your heels.
It's me, fuck! This is my moment!
My moment's come.
Good morning, guys.
Look, the DJ slept there.
Did you have a good time yesterday?
You... Jeez, awesome, man.
The DJ is with another girl, huh?
- They said you betrayed me? How so?
- Who did?
Blondie is very evolved, she's so zen.
Would you hook up with him after that?
Obviously, I'm not dead.
She got him there so they'd be together,
but she got shit-faced.
Not his fault.
But would you hook up with him
after everything?
I wouldn't hook up with him ever.
- I'm just assuming, Blondie.
- I'm not Blondie.
Bia, let's drive Vic
to the airport with me?
- She's leaving already...
- I'm leaving...
Vic is so cute. I'm in love.
- And the girls like her.
- Yeah.
I think I'd be like her...
Nathalia picked a fight
with her, remember?
She said she wanted to hook up with...
- Yeah... Luan.
- Hook up with Luan.
She's leaving, no way.
What about you, girl? You and Nath.
- Are you okay?
- Man... She ran up there, girl.
She ran up there and said,
"Bia! Bia! Bia, go downstairs!
Go downstairs! It's Luan, Luan!"
Bro, I went there like a fool...
I made a scene, you know?
I went downstairs...
- Pissed.
- Obviously.
Do you realize there's
always a DTR in the car?
- In the car.
- And the fight on the bus.
Men fight in the bus and women in the car.
Are you guys explosive?
That depends, depends on the moment.
Man, me, too. That depends.
Sometimes I'm very chill,
but a hothead, too.
I try to understand what's going on.
But I think that,
as much as Bia is explosive,
she's already shown it sometimes,
I think she couldn't take it anymore...
She put up with a lot of things
from Nathalia.
- Yeah, that was kind of the last straw.
- I think so, too.
What?
Here's what I think... There'll be moments
when I'll have to like myself,
so I won't accept...
After everything she said to him.
How does she say that?
She's messing around, man.
...to be with me, don't sit on the fence
and show me another thing.
Is she breaking up with him?
...confusing yourself,
that's your problem...
I don't know.
I end up involving you
in another thing.
Got it? That has nothing to do with it.
That has nothing to do with your problems,
with your frustration.
Nobody has anything to do with it.
I think it's super honest
we have this conversation...
and talk about it...
Are they together?
Did they sleep together? What's going on?
Yes, we saw at the beginning.
I don't know anymore.
But did they have sex?
I don't think so...
But we haven't seen it, right?
But they slept together.
Got it? I faced mine and accepted them
since the beginning.
I've been fucking doing it the whole time.
Yes, I know you did.
Now, unfortunately,
we're done and I'm moving on.
- No, it's not unfortunately.
- Bye.
I'm already tired of Ramon.
So, they broke up, right?
They made it clear they're single.
But Ramon wants to break up.
That's funny because
he's not into her anymore.
She was the one who said.
She said, "Come off the fence."
João hits on everyone, look.
He's there for everyone.
I love Murilo's outfits, really.
Those patterned shirts.
Ramon always does
those dance moves, right, man?
He had to represent Niterói, guys.
What's that? He's all stiff
But I think he has a cute way, you know?
- You've already noticed, right?
- What?
You've already noticed...
- This again, guys?
- But they were free, right?
I wonder if that will get messy.
Fuck it...
- I'm not with her.
- But...
Dear Lord.
- It was because...
- Man, I get sad.
You won't be sad because
I won't hook up with her.
- Come on.
- That's it.
- Chill out.
- You know, whatever you need... You know?
Man, that's cool.
I like it. I think that's cool.
I didn't find it cool. He's asking Ramon
if he can hook up with Nath...
They broke up, but he knows
there's something still going on.
I thought his approach
was a little different.
- No.
- But it was ethical of him.
- Let me tell you.
- But Nathalia...
But if he hooks up with her,
it's messed up.
Let me say something.
There was that conversation
between Nathalia and Ramon.
Nathalia didn't want him.
Probably, everyone in the house knows,
but they like each other.
It was nice to say,
"Man, your girl is flirting with me,
now what?" He was cool with it.
But he told her.
It was cool, but he said to him,
-"We're not together anymore, go on."
- No.
And he said, "Are you going to be sad?"
Then he said, "I don't know."
"Then I won't do it."
He asked for permission.
The guy didn't give it
because he still likes her.
Here's what I think.
She flirted with him
because she's single and so is he.
But he knows the other guy likes her,
so he tried to handle the situation...
- He was ethical.
- ...with everyone drinking...
Girl, here's what I think.
He had to ask Nathalia,
since he's the one who wants her.
He didn't have to ask Ramon, like,
"Can I hook up with the girl
you're hooking up with?"
That's a question of ethics between men...
That's because men stick together.
Men stick together.
Yes, guys. The girl is there like a coin,
in the middle...
- No.
- She'll be like a coin if she wants some.
She's been doing this at times.
She already wants to stay.
But he said, "I want to hook up with her,
but my friend is over there."
Tomás was explaining himself to Ramon.
Why didn't he say to Nathalia,
"I want to be with you.
Are you with Ramon?
How are you two doing?"
Why did he only talk to the guy?
It's not like that.
- Men don't argue.
- No.
It's a guy thing. Men want to fight.
So, men stick together
so they don't fight.
Nobody cares about anyone.
Of course they care.
Nobody gives up fucking somebody
because of another girl...
- Stop it!
- We don't express our feelings.
I give up. No, Carol, I disagree.
A friend of mine met a guy
and he liked him a lot.
Then he says he's deeply in love.
Then I signed up on a dating app.
I found the guy there,
but I didn't recognize him.
We started to talk,
and I remembered he was that boy
and I scolded him,
"Man, you did this to my friend.
My friend likes you
and you're on this app."
Even if I wanted to hook up
with him later,
I didn't do it.
I knew he was with my friend.
I'm loyal to myself.
- Do you have a lighter?
- Do you a have a smoke?
- He's hot.
- Wait, listen.
When I first got here,
I wanted to hook up with you
pretty bad. But first...
Look, she's like you, a seducer.
She made a face...
She tried to avoid him, but she'd do it.
...if he was gonna be mad, you know?
Then he started stalling, like,
"No worries,
"we have nothing going on."
That's cute, he cares.
She's upset because she wanted
to hook up with Tomás.
I said, "Man, really, tell me the truth.
Would you mind?" He said, "I would."
I asked, "Then, you want to be her?"
He said, "I don't know."
It's kind of... you know?
We argued. I broke up with him. That's it.
I'll never be chosen again by anybody.
From now on,
I'm the one who's going to choose.
I'm not bad-looking...
- I'm not sure about annoying.
- You're just crazy.
Guys, put yourselves in her shoes.
I want to fuck Tomás.
He was amazing, huh? He did it right.
He'll hook up with her.
Look.
That's what I wanted.
He went to talk to her, got it?
But they're going to kiss.
Kiss him. It's okay.
If you're the good one.
Jeez.
Everything happens at the right time
- Let's toast here.
- There's a right time for everything.
I have a friend who says this, you know?
To my way of thinking,
he was not trying to kiss her.
He hugged her
- and did this.
- He tried to kiss her.
It doesn't make sense.
- Then he comes with a flower.
- He is, man.
A guy tells another guy,
"Is it bad if I hook up with this girl?"
And he says, "I don't know,
I think I would be bummed."
It was his play.
That's what I'm saying.
It was a game. He thought
he was going to have an answer.
He thought he was going to have
an answer from Ramon, you know?
Men have their ego.
They won't say that they care.
But Ramon is being totally honest,
you know? He said...
- Can I speak now?
- Speak, girl. Speak, Bia.
What's going on? Man, there's no other
explanation for what happened.
He asked a question and had an answer.
- He had to stay out of it, but he didn't.
- Yep.
Nathalia did what she's used to doing
again. She must've looked at Ramon,
I don't know what happened there.
Regardless if it's right or wrong,
he hit on her.
What did she do? Once again,
she played, left, looked to the side,
laughed, mocked.
Do you think she always does it
to play with Ramon?
Girl, no, I think
she's not playing with Ramon,
but with that situation, you know?
- She wants to show off.
- Yeah, I don't know.
She was saying, "I'm hot, I'm beautiful,
- I'm this, I'm that."
- The best scenario...
There's a tube...
Buddy, the best scenario would be
if she hooked up with him.
Both of them wanted the same thing.
But, no, she played with him and flirted.
The dude hit on her,
she ran away.
Do you know what to call Nathalia?
She's a player.
She plays with everybody
and causes trouble in the entire house.
She likes
to provoke disagreements.
She says something about...
She likes a mess.
I'm tired of this.
- Man, I can't stand this yo-yo.
- What?
#YOYO
Yo-yo. That comes and goes.
- I can't see anything.
- This one got blurred.
Jeez, these pictures were crazy.
Say what you have to say.
Let's live one day at a time.
This bullshit again?
- What?
- You keep saying the same thing.
But you were the one who said this.
Let's make this work.
- Me?
- Let's go. You're in, right?
This includes you.
- I've had enough.
- Who thought they would never come back?
- Me.
- I never did.
I said they'd get back together.
I don't believe in anything of that.
I only believe in looseness...
No, girl, their kissing is different.
They like each other.
She likes him.
Even if she acts weird.
But I think...
She's doing all that
because she likes him.
Pay attention, Carol.
She might not love, but she likes him.
Otherwise, she'd hook up with others.
He doesn't like her.
More guys than she's hooked up with?
Others? She didn't.
Not so much. She fights more.
She summoned that guy.
She brought that guy from Goiânia...
And that's it.
She didn't spend the night.
But she went there
and had sex...
She had sex and got up.
Then I don't know.
She got up.
She didn't cuddle with him, right?
I think she brought that guy
to make him jealous.
Carol, the best of all of us
at games.
I think she invited that guy
because she likes him.
That's why she didn't stay with him
until the end. She likes him.
She flirted with...
- Tomás.
- Tomás because of him.
She didn't hook up with Tomás
because of him.
She loves badly, but she likes him.
Will this relationship evolve?
- Hey, Ti, pay attention. Otherwise...
- She'll be in this forever.
I feel like slapping his face,
"Wake up, you idiot."
You're here to try to understand these...
I'm neither of those two, thank God.
Titto is the boss.
He's João and Blondie.
- Man, I think...
- I'm not...
I think that when we love,
we have different strategies.
But she's not good at strategy, you know?
No, but that's too heavy.
It's not about strategy.
it's about knowing...
Like, if you love,
you need to know your limit.
Your life is a war, right?
Her life is a war. She's always coming up
with a plan to destroy the enemy.
The human being that
she has a relationship with is her enemy.
I'd bounce, too.
I wouldn't speak to anyone.
- Not even to your brother?
- I'd speak to my brother.
It was my brother who called me, right?
"Are you in Floripa?"
"Yes, but I'm leaving."
Didn't you like it?
- No.
-"Yes, but I'm..."
Sorry, is this the bench
from A Praça É Nossa?
Fuck, I got the pun now.
- I'm sorry.
- Give it up for him.
Jeez, "lol."
Shut up, you have to laugh at my jokes.
If you met one of the members of this show
on the street, what would you do?
I'd say this, "Jeez, I watched the show. "
I think I would say to Murilo,
"Murilo and Taynara,
you're both my crushes." Really.
I'd say this, "Let's be a throuple?"
This beach is a nude beach... Naturalism.
Couples that want to
get naked... Don't do it...
Look at João.
- No way!
- Damn. Take it off, Luan. Take it off!
No way, guys.
They're squeezing their junk...
- He wants to guarantee his place.
- You're an observant person.
Girl...
Go, Carrara!
Jeez, bro. I can't believe it, man.
Those guys got naked there.
- What an ass.
- I can't see it.
- Rewind it, I want to see it.
- Shut up! No fucking way!
I didn't see it very well when Luan...
I think Luan is
the most well-hung of that house.
Who do you think is
the most well-hung of that house?
- I'm sorry.
- MC Carol from Niterói, go.
- I think it's the Indian.
- I think it's Luan.
Guys, I'm so shocked by that dick.
- I loved this.
- Did you see Luan's cock? I'm shocked!
- I think it was offensive.
- That's not fun.
- Baby, I loved it.
- I loved it.
- Stop it, Carol!
- That's not fun.
- Go. Cell phone?
- Yeah.
Hi, everybody, how are you?
Once again I'll need you guys at the bar.
Tonight I'm counting on girls here. Okay?
See you then.
- This is going...
- Good one, Ricardão!
Murilo, "There's a funk party tonight!"
Like, he's getting even.
You see, Carol? It's your day.
Guys, I'm shocked by... With Luan.
They let the boys out, fuck!
- Guys, Murilo is ironing his clothes.
- Dear Lord.
WE WENT TO THE RAP PARTY
LOVE YOU
They're leaving a note for the girls.
But they're going to get screwed.
They're doing the same.
"We went to the rap party."
They've already gone to that club.
It was that one where everyone
kissed everyone and it was a big mess.
-"We went to the rap party."
- Caps Lock.
When Caps Lock is on.
Aren't you from São Paulo?
How do you not know "Caps Lock"?
- Never heard of it.
- Caps Lock.
Caps Lock? Stop it, you're old!
- Caps lock.
- Caps lock. That huge font.
No, Caps Lock is the name of a party.
"Hi, how are you?" Caps lock.
This is the real "one for all," right?
This is the "one for all."
They're erasing their memories
because they're going to fuck things up.
One for all...
One for all and all for one!
Jeez, they're going to fuck things up.
They know they're being filmed...
Keeping a low profile, got it?
- But they don't see it.
- Yeah.
"What are you doing here?"
I came to buy some bread.
- What the hell, man?
- João...
João, right?
- Luan? Luan!
- Luan...
Where's Murilo?
Man, did those guys go to the club
and really go crazy.
- I'm shocked!
- Where's Luan?
I hope Murilo doesn't kiss anyone,
- for Christ's sake.
- João again?
But João is single. Everyone is, but...
What happens here, stays here...
We trust each other, so...
Forget this. Tomorrow we sort this out
if anybody wants to say...
- Nobody is saying anything.
- That's it. The same story.
Have you done that? Mess things up
and make an arrangement with your friends?
- You're crazy.
- What happens...
...in Vegas, stays in Vegas.
If you're saying this,
you've done it.
No, I've done it.
- Men suck.
- I didn't understand what they said.
"Nobody is saying anything."
Men suck.
- Men suck.
- That's fucked up, baby.
Men suck.
There's always a son of a bitch.
That will tell...
I'm going to pick them.
Do you give me a shot?
Look at his face, he's a "bifooloft."
- My God.
- He's big, a fool and soft.
A lot of "bifooloft."
He looks like a Volkswagen
Beetle with the door open.
Looks like those guys came
out of a factory. They all look alike.
- Yeah, they're all clones.
- They're all similar.
The four of them drank it.
I want to invite you to our house,
for a warmup.
Are you in? The four of you?
The boys are thinking
they're going to fuck everyone.
Would you rather an afterparty,
or taking him home?
I don't take boys home.
I don't couple up at parties.
I'd rather be alone
because I'll be enjoying
- rather than coupling up.
- I think so, too.
- What about you, Carol?
- I'd rather take one home.
He looks like he has a six pack.
Excuse me.
Does he, man? Let's see...
- Just a little. Just a little.
- Can I see it again?
Applause.
You don't deserve it.
You deserve the limbs together.
What about the whole body?
Do I deserve it?
- That was too easy.
- Look at Nathalia.
Guys, Nathalia is very crazy.
Guys, but Nathalia... is single, right?
- She's not working, right?
- Show him, Titto, how you do it.
- How do you do it?
- What?
Get up, show...
Guys, I'm really shocked.
Me, too. Not with the girls,
they're working,
giving free shots like the boys.
I'm loving it.
They're doing exactly
what the guys are doing.
No, they're doing much more.
Yes.
They're doing that
because they're working, right?
Let's watch the afterparty.
I'm shocked with the guys.
- They wanna hook up with everybody.
- But those women...
I think the girls are amazing.
They are so amazing. They are empowered.
- They are empowered.
- They are role models for Brazil.
You are amazing.
I'm not going to say much...
I think those guys
they took home are tidier
than the guys from the house.
They're cute, right?
I think we have to wait
to see the end, right?
- Yeah, I'm going to wait to see it.
- We'll see.
Oh, my God. It's hard to be myself.
Let's see if they're becoming friends?
We've realized they're not.
Yeah, let's see.
I'm going to root against those girls.
- It was Thais.
- She deserved that.
Blondie is having sex!
No way!
- Poor thing.
- Blondie went upstairs to have sex.
Tay.
Don't do this. Tay, get up.
Let's go to bed.
Why are you up here?
Taynara, let's go to bed.
Get out of the floor.
I'm fine... Why are you up here?
"Why are you up here?"
Leave me here.
No. Go to bed.
I don't want to.
You'll make me lie down here.
The floor is the limit.
That's my saying.
"The floor is the limit.
That's my saying."
- ...lie down there and talk?
- No.
- Just talk, don't worry, bro.
We have a nice relationship.
- Murilo is at Art's.
- He's going to have his ass kicked.
I won't do anything, thinking about him.
- He's a fucker.
- Oh, my God, the butt crack...
What?
He said her boyfriend is a fucker,
he was at the club.
"I missed you, baby."
Who said that? Murilo?
Murilo is going to catch that boy.
She's on the floor.
- Holy shit, that's fucked up.
- Knife in hand.
- Cooking our food.
- Where are you from, bro?
- I don't believe this.
- What's this?
Where's Tay?
"Where's Tay?"
- She's sleeping.
- Great, that's good.
"That's good" and he...
The guy is on the floor...
Go check on Tay, go!
This is like a soap opera.
Only if you go to bed, man.
Man, go to bed.
Damn it.
That's going to be fucked up.
Which guy annoyed you?
There was a guy up there,
I was sleeping, and he was there.
Who was the guy who was upsetting my girl?
- Was it you?
- Go figure...
I was just seeing your house.
Was it you? Then bounce, my friend,
or there's going
to be some ass kicking here.
She's just said there was a guy
upsetting her, she wanted to sleep.
Who's your chick?
I don't want to know who is.
You know the party where you were at?
I'm the one who plays there, man.
- So, please...
- I was playing there.
Fuck, what a guy!
Boy, you really did it now.
Why haven't they left yet?
I'm starting to go crazy.
- Please, get out.
- Respect is essential.
Or else there'll be a fight.
- There'll be a fight.
- Why? No, I'm saying that...
I'm going to call you an Uber.
I love Murilo.
Damn, Murilo is fucking awesome.
Jeez, I felt like a little girl
hearing Murilo.
Like, he's defending me!
Wow.
Until you explain that
things are not what they seem...
He always talks about these things.
Things that don't exist.
But I think, at first, I'd be pissed off,
seeing the girls there, in the middle...
Then you have to know
what happened.
Man, I wouldn't stay.
If you came home and saw
your boy with a lot of women there...
- I'd be pissed off.
- Can I say something?
- Are you nuts?
- It's wrong. What?
Can I say something?
Would you leave pissed off?
I'd smash the bed, flip the table and say,
"What the fuck do you think this is, man?"
I understand he can feel
attracted to other people...
But, man, I wouldn't care.
- You don't care?
- Would you allow it?
- You seeing your boy hitting on...
- I'd be cool.
Because I know...
If I really like the guy.
I'm talking about me, okay?
I've been there.
If I like a guy, and he likes me,
I know we like each other.
I know that's his environment,
the party scene.
I know he might be there,
enjoying himself.
Deep down, he likes me. So it's like,
"Baby? What's going on? Let's go, honey.
- What about all these chicks?"
- Stop it, don't do this.
We'll be laughing about it.
That's it, man.
So, you think cheating is okay?
Physical attraction is one thing...
Attraction, not betraying.
People feel attracted...
But attraction is not cheating?
People are not, what do we...
Yeah, when we like one person?
- Monogamous.
It's natural we feel attracted to others.
Yes.
Having the option to hook up
with another person
is totally different from just attraction.
Murilo got there, saw some men
and wanted to cause trouble.
- No, he didn't.
- No, he got there...
He got there making jokes about the food.
"Where's my woman?"
He got there,
"The guys are eating my food."
Then he asked, "Where's my woman?"
Someone said, "She's sleeping."
He said, "It's okay."
Making jokes. Exactly.
No, John, he was cool
considering the situation.
When he saw those
guys, he wanted to cause trouble.
No. She was the one complaining.
He didn't want trouble.
I'd make a scene. I'd tell the woman this.
I think he was refined.
Where are you going, man?
"I'm going to call you an Uber, and you're
getting in the Uber, okay? That's it."
What did you say?
What were you going to say?
"I'm calling you an Uber.
You're getting in the Uber."
And she'd leave, right, Carol?
"Get in the Uber
because it's better for you."
I don't want to go downstairs.
If you don't take off...
- What's this?
- If you don't take off,
I'm going to kick your ass, buddy.
Who woke you up?
It was him, but...
It was him, right? He woke you up, leave.
You can go there...
- If you don't take off...
- Of course, brother. No, no...
- Hey, is that your woman?
- Fuck you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Take off, buddy. Get out.
No, guys, you know what?
His tone turned that into a bad situation
and that resulted in an argument.
That could have been just a conversation.
What conversation, John?
That guy got home drunk...
By any chance,
do you work in telemarketing?
I've worked. No, man.
He got home drunk.
- Easy, buddy.
- Get out. You don't touch me.
- What happened?
- Don't touch him, man.
Don't touch me.
- Nobody is touching anybody.
- Take off.
Fucking jerk.
We're going to finish... Look, bro...
- Are you nuts? Get out!
- Fuck you!
- Easy.
- Get out of my way.
- Easy. No.
- Take your hand off me.
Luan doesn't like to fight.
He's there, look.
Holy shit. Luan and Murilo are fighting.
- What?
- Fuck!
Get your hand off me, bro.
Fuck!
That guy was fucking wrong.
He did wrong.
- Do you want to get your ass kicked?
- Are you nuts?
"Are you nuts?" Now you're really a man.
I've never seen this, man.
Where's the fighting?
What's this, man?
And he says, "What's this, man?
What are you doing?
What's this, man?"
You need to have your ass kicked.
That guy was a fool to go in the bedroom.
Why did you stay downstairs?
When Tay was sleeping?
Was I supposed to leave them?
- You were the hostess?
- Blondie and I...
Everybody went to bed...
- You and Blondie?
- Blondie and I.
I get it.
Blondie was upstairs in the room?
She was hooking up with...
And you were alone
in the pool like a crazy person?
Oh, my God, he kissed a lot
of girls at the rap party.
- It's such hypocrisy.
- Luan is a hustler.
Not Luan, Ramon is a fucking hustler, too.
He's a hustler, bro.
It's such hypocrisy, lord.
I think Blondie was a fool.
She could've left her boy there
because he wasn't even...
But he's friends with them, right?
But that's fucked up.
He wasn't involved, he was with Blondie.
Now you're going to mix this?
Your friend fucks things up...
Titto is with me at a party,
and I brought you home...
You're going to sleep with me...
- Look.
- Obviously.
- Really?
The bubble.
Bro, I don't know if I... Sorry,
I don't want to separate this by gender,
but where me and my friends come from,
that thing doesn't exist, bro.
You're in this house. My five
friends and I go to a house full of women.
Men show up
and I'm in the bedroom with a woman.
My friends get in trouble downstairs...
Am I going to stay there?
No way, I leave with my buddies.
Are you nuts, man?
Okay, then.
You can lose the love of your life.
Give me a kiss.
- That was crazy. Good night.
- You deserve it.
Hey, the man is desperate.
I'm not needy. I'm independent.
There it is, Coach Bianca.
I can't believe... There's only...
- Oh, my God.
- What a shame.
Nothing...
- What the fuck?
- It's Rubi. My God.
There's only one more episode.
Oh, no!
I thought she was
auditioning for a TV show.
I can't believe it, guys.
She's an actress, man.
There's only one more episode.
I don't want to. No...
I need more episodes, man.
I'm not going to see Murilo banging, man.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
They did the same thing
to each other the whole series.
What he did, she did, too.
She brought someone over.
She did something, I don't know...
The only thing missing was a real talk.
I didn't see any sexism.
He was just a jerk.