WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS
THE REVIEW
Guys, where's John?
I don't know, but we can't pretend
he's not here.
- Yeah. Look at this.
- My God!
You say that you love me when you drink
But your mouth prefers me
Dear Lord, bro!
That's talent, right, guys?
- What is it, man?
- Get up, girl.
Oh, my gosh.
That's great, man.
Look at the heels!
These are phantom heels, girl!
- These are phantom heels.
- And he tiptoes!
I thought there were heels.
- Me, too.
- Here! He's here!
Previously, Tay and João had an argument,
she was dumped by Murilo,
bad vibe in the house.
And I don't know
what is going to happen today.
Let's press play real good? I'm beat...
Go, Titto. Kill it.
- What's up?
- What's up, ma?
- Beautiful image.
- Our palette.
It's like that meme,
I woke up early to watch that sunset.
Oh, my God, look at this house.
- It's the dynamite couple.
- Look, girl.
It's better than crying in front
of the cameras saying you're heartbroken.
Look into my eyes
and say you feel nothing.
- Booze.
- We said she was going to regret it.
Yes...
At least, it's an eye for an eye.
Crying over a broken heart,
that's a shame.
Shame, look. It's regret.
See? That's booze.
But she's a real friend.
She's telling the truth
about her acting like a fool.
A true friend says,
"You've made a fool of yourself."
-"You were quite ridiculous."
- Yeah...
So... In the bathroom...
I don't remember what you said...
- I heard João saying some stuff to Murilo.
- Seriously?
He said,
"You're going to be a player again?
Back to the game."
They fought in the bathroom.
I said, "I can't believe he did that..."
Are you making a fool of me?
Hey, people, for Christ's sake.
They're already fighting?
She was honest.
She said she was hurt because...
not because she's getting too involved,
but she has feelings for him
and he said those meant nothing.
- I wouldn't do that, you know?
- Oh, no...
- Okay...
- He was honest, and so was she...
- Life goes on.
- He was honest.
What do you think?
They have to talk
or each one of them moves on?
I think it won't work anymore...
They have to enjoy the days they have...
- But if they enjoy it together...
- If it's already bad, he won't.
- It's true...
- She'll be the only person to enjoy it
because she's with him.
- But if they...
- Why?
- Because he wants to party all the time.
She's attached to him.
If they become a couple...
He won't enjoy it.
But if they go their separate ways,
she'll get hurt, and he'll party.
- Got it?
- But she...
- There's this middle ground.
- Exactly.
It's a two-day fling.
She'll get over it quickly.
- Yeah...
- In Floripa... Yeah.
- Guys, work cell phone.
- Cell phone. Where's the phone?
How do I answer it?
- Hello? Hold on. That's hard...
- Who is this?
- It's Amanda!
- Who is this? Is it for you?
I like it.
That's what friends are for.
- She cried...
- Guys, this is beautiful.
She'll have someone to trust,
outside that house.
- Yeah.
- She cries a lot.
Why is she crying?
Because she's in bad shape.
She's in bad shape.
She cries too much.
She's emotional, but if Bia says,
"Girl, I've paid..."
Carol is quiet...
I also cry when my friends call me.
That's cute.
Her friend called to meet her.
I'd cry because they're going to eat
all the food in my fridge.
We're gonna go to this party.
Let's drink before.
I have nowhere to stay.
It's crazy, girl...
- Two days?
- But the stress, arguments...
Baby, it's intense...
Boy, two days of booze
and she's crying like that?
When you're out on tour, after two days,
do you feel homesick?
But two days getting wasted,
how will you be homesick at that point?
But she got upset...
Titto, what makes you cry?
When my female friends call me, telling me
they're coming to my place, I cry.
- Yeah?
- Oh, my God.
I'm kidding, of course not.
I don't have female friends.
I'd cry. I'm emotional in a house,
and there's been two days I'm getting
acquainted with these people.
You're here with us.
If I say I'll meet you at your place,
will you cry?
Yes, I will.
- You're emotional...
- Hit play.
May the night be unforgettable!
It's gonna be! Amen. Amen.
Better than yesterday
and worse than tomorrow!
What is ours is ours!
It will always be ours!
Guys, João...
- She arrived.
- Is that her? I loved her look.
She seems to have a good vibe.
- Will she do Pilates there?
- She didn't drink...
Yes... I loved her.
She's a sociologist.
She'll light some incense.
Social science for sure...
She went to sociology school.
No, she can be a good person
to go out with,
a friendly person, "Stop it, don't fight."
Or, "Let's drink and go skinny dipping."
That one who's arrived?
- She drinks kombucha.
- What?
She won't do anything. Look at her.
- Don't judge a book by its cover.
- Why not?
There are some good vibe people
who nail it.
I'm just saying
she doesn't look like a party girl.
Yeah... She looks like
she digs vegan food, meditation.
Mystical stones...
- Exactly. She prays with crystals...
- Let's see...
- You got to enjoy it!
- Fuck, you got to enjoy it!
Let's enjoy it, come!
- That's it.
- She's already with... with Ramon.
- Man, I am...
- She takes initiative, huh?
Guys, I think that friend
is going to hook up with Murilo.
Or she might think,
"They're not together," and just...
No, she's her friend.
If she said she's in love...
I don't agree with that.
She just said she cried...
I already hooked up
with my best friend. No...
That's not new, right?
- I did.
- That's not wrong.
Wrong is hooking up
with your friend's crush. Or girlfriend.
I'm a person of character when I'm sober.
When I drink, I'm not.
There's nothing, just sex.
I'll hide my boys from you.
Sex, sex, sex
Nonstop, nonstop
- Look, look!
- I love it!
- Mischief.
- I want to see, huh?
Guys, she was the last one
to arrive at that house.
She should know what's up.
Yeah, she went crazy.
She has the right to party.
She'll be there for two days.
No, girl, she's just arrived.
She has to understand the atmosphere.
She's staying for two days
and is going crazy.
I arrive like this.
I'm quiet, she's quiet.
Just don't hook up with my boy, look.
If you do it with my boy,
I'm gonna kick your ass.
"If you hook up with my boy..."
I'm going to kick your ass.
- It's not like that.
- We are best friends.
It's a deal. This boy is yours.
But, man, think about it...
I'm a little interested
in hooking up with your boy.
But never mind, this boy is not yours.
This boy is... He gets to...
- Ouch...
- It's true.
Guys, I'm like her.
That one who hooks up with everyone?
I'm authentic. She speaks her mind.
- I'll hide my boy from you.
- Do it.
Everyone is on vacation having fun.
She's getting attached.
He'll drink and kiss another girl.
Everyone can hook up with anyone now...
The thing is she's just arrived.
Don't get attached.
You can date afterwards.
She barely arrived and wants to take
advantage of the situation.
What would you do if you were her?
I wouldn't do anything.
You would say no, but as soon as you
had the chance, you'd go for it.
You wouldn't have the guts to admit it.
She did.
She had. I think that's awesome.
Got it? She didn't lie.
She didn't lie.
I can't stand lies.
Mariano, what would you do?
I think like Titto.
I wouldn't want to either.
It has happened to me before.
- Have you done it?
- No.
It's already happened to me.
Once, a friend's girl hit on me...
They're not friends.
Guys, just think.
Only two days!
- There's been two days. Two days.
- Everyone is free.
Where's that freedom
we were talking about?
You can't do this to a friend.
What friend? He's not my friend.
The problem is getting
there just to do that.
What I'm about to say
is going to sound like bullshit,
but I'll take the risk and say it.
Don't get me wrong, women,
but, between men,
there's a thing,
there's a different kind of respect.
Of loyalty.
There's no such thing!
From my perspective, a man who shakes
another man's hand and says,
"Look, she's my girlfriend."
I believe it.
"From now on, she's off-limits."
- Exactly.
- I've seen
so many nasty boys...
...who say what you said and then...
I'd never hook up
with a friend's girl.
Man, usually, a guy doesn't hook up
with a friend's girl,
but when they break up, he does.
That person is not a friend.
That means that person is dead?
What? Are you nuts?
Do you hook up with your friend's ex?
I already did.
He's not your friend.
He's my friend, but it's history.
He's dating now. This is history.
Boyfriend is different than fling, right?
Fling is one thing.
If he's your friend
and dated a woman for two years,
- she's dead to me.
- Listen,
"A deal is a deal."
No one made any arrangements.
If he said he wouldn't hook up with her,
that's okay, he gave his word.
But no, there was no such thing.
Those girls are...
They pretend to be not attached,
but when things get complicated, they say,
"Are you going to dance with that girl?"
But there's no deal yet.
No one is committed yet.
- She's just friends with Tay.
- That's fair.
If she hooks up with Tay's boyfriend,
it's going to be messed up.
I don't agree with that.
But if she hooks up
with the other girls' boyfriends...
Let's watch and see.
It's wrong to say she'll kick her ass.
But she's not wrong. She was honest.
She was herself, you know?
Let's see.
We were getting along.
Good, because you made a little mess.
What did I come here for?
-"What did I come here for?"
- Did she say that?
- That she made a mess.
- She's a Leo.
When people talk about star signs,
things will get bad.
- What's her star sign?
- Leo...
When people talk about star signs...
And she wants to teach
her friend a lesson.
I'm not jealous, man.
Yes, you are.
What would you do if someone
wanted to kiss your boy?
- You're not a couple.
- You can't judge others, girl.
You are all too committed.
You can't judge others.
You don't know what they're going through.
No one knows what's going on.
She wants to send...
Ramon hit on her, right...
I can't judge. Two days...
She wants to send her friend back.
Ramon hit on Amanda!
Look, look, look. Oh, fuck...
- Who is that?
- It's Luan.
Fuck!
Now I'm enjoying it. We'll talk later.
What did she say? What did she say?
"Now I'm enjoying it. We'll talk later."
- Awesome. Give me this.
- Switch with me.
I guess she's going to the afterparty.
You must be five foot eight-point-five.
Is he going to kiss another girl?
I am five foot three.
Ouch, it's not going to be her.
What about João, bro?
Once again, he is the insignificant one.
All the girls are attached.
One is fighting for him,
and he's with another girl.
Let me say something.
Do you know what's going on?
The girls know what she's doing,
but the boys don't know
what she's doing yet.
- The one who arrived at the house.
- Amanda.
Amanda.
The girls already know
she intends to hook up with someone.
The boys don't know yet.
The girls are pissed
and the boys are pissed at the girls.
"I'm not doing anything!"
The girls are attached to those men,
and they don't care.
I think the same way.
You think they can't separate
their feelings?
The girls are too attached and fighting...
"Don't hook up with my boy."
And he's with another girl.
Do you agree those girls are attached
to the boys, and the boys are partying?
She's fighting for one
who's already with another girl.
She should be with another guy.
She shouldn't be dating.
Carol, would you be this attached or not?
No, I wouldn't either.
She almost had a heart attack...
Imagine you see your boy
at the club with another girl...
I would have a heart attack
in the bathroom.
- But you wouldn't demand anything, right?
- I wouldn't say anything.
- Go kiss her!
- I've already kissed her.
Kiss her again. For real.
A real kiss.
Looks like he's a good kisser.
Looks like he does, but he just kisses...
- He's like that 14-year-old boy...
- He admitted it, buddy.
Who went to the matinee, kissed a lot...
But someone who likes kissing
is a good kisser.
Yeah, each person is good at... Expert.
There are people who don't know
how to kiss...
Really don't know how to kiss...
Carol...
What about Carol?
I'm saying
he must be a really good kisser.
She lives in a different reality.
There are guys
who don't know how to kiss...
It's like she doesn't like to kiss.
She only kisses
who she loves, right, Carol?
Are you a good kisser?
I've learned, right?
I must...
- I must be...
- I love it!
When you guys go to a club...
But do you know why?
Do you know why?
For me, kissing...
Kissing has a lot of feelings involved,
you know?
What about fucking? I see...
That one...
But how do you know... about feelings
if you don't kiss anyone?
How do you know you're in love?
So, you fall in love for sex.
She falls in love for sex.
No, but I kiss one person
or another, get it?
But I don't kiss every guy I hook up with.
- Did you hear that?
- Who?
"I don't kiss every guy I hook up with."
I make an exception for
one or another. The guy has...
- Has to kiss you?
- The guy has a pretty mouth.
You eventually fall in love?
Then I make an exception...
You're at the club...
Those you don't make an exception for...
What?
...you spread your legs?
- Yeah.
- But if I...
No, but you say to him,
"No kissing." Right?
I don't say anything.
The dude comes and I... "Hey, buddy..."
Hey...
He bangs you, right?
You know a guy at a club
and you tell him to suck your pussy?
I don't go to clubs. I go to funk parties.
The guy fucks your pussy right away?
Did you hear what she said?
"I go to funk parties."
Then I rub up against someone... What?
Okay, you rub up against someone...
He fucks your pussy
and you don't kiss at any moment?
At any moment.
But I don't even rub up
against anyone.
And the dude already knows what I want.
What about when you're in the missionary
position? Looking you in the eyes?
- No, no.
- It's too much, man...
I'm going to put
her on an altar, at home, like this.
I've never been through this...
But I think that if I have a relationship
with someone...
I'd rather he cheats on me with sex.
Like, "Carol, I had sex...
I was in need..."
- But when do you kiss?
- I don't know... What?
When do you find out
this person deserves a kiss?
I already have someone, got it?
How did you know he was the one?
Because she goes to church.
He's from church...
Mouth is very...
Carol is a case study.
It's something very intimate.
I don't know
where the guy put his mouth yesterday.
- Carol.
- And the...
He could've put his dick in a dead goat.
There's a condom, boy.
Let me tell you...
- She uses condoms.
- There's a condom.
- Carol should be studied.
- Carol is like a medical specimen.
Carol is the only woman
who shocks Pabllo Vittar.
It's true!
"Don't you kiss?"
I'm not shocked. I'm learning lessons.
- Learning...
- I'm learning, too.
A life workshop.
People say I have no feelings,
but I really do, got it?
It's just... They're just hidden...
Because I have feelings...
That's it. Kissing is...
It's about a lot of feelings. Anyway...
Let's play.
Can you get me a cigarette?
- Yes, I can.
- And a kiss?
I can, too.
Are we allowed to kiss?
Tay hooked up with another guy, look!
All right, Tay, beat Murilo.
But you know why she did it, right?
She hooked up with him in front of João,
then João will say something.
- Is she doing that in front of João?
- Look.
She stains everyone with lipstick.
Her signature.
- I already kissed.
- Really?
Jesus.
She's talking to João?
Hey, exactly.
Then João will tell him. Damn!
I'll say, fuck!
I'm a bandit, fuck.
- What are you?
- I'm a bandit, I do this, guys.
- I'm shocked.
- She's doing this to tease him.
When you want to affect someone,
you do things in front of his best friend.
You don't show it...
You hook up with someone
in front of his friend.
- This friend will tell the person.
- This is strategy.
And the person will think you don't care.
He's very jealous, man.
Let's bounce.
- Invite your chicks.
- Do we have a deal?
João is not going to have sex.
Carol, you're experienced,
what do you think?
I think he's not going to have sex...
Because he's very anxious to...
Maybe in the last episode.
- You kissed a lot of people, didn't you?
- You kissed seven.
- Seven?
- I counted.
Seven? Look at João, huh?
I kissed one person,
I think it was too much.
- You kissed seven people.
- I'm not a fucker, I'm a kisser.
Didn't I say he's not a fucker, buddy?
He's just a kisser.
"I'm not a fucker, I'm a kisser."
- Did you guys notice she...
- Carol, what do you think?
Hit pause.
Pause, pause.
No one cared about her...
She said, "I kissed one person,"
in front of Murilo.
- She wanted to mention she kissed too.
- She's a bandit, too.
Will they have sex today?
Murilo and Tay?
- What?
- I hope so.
I think they won't.
I think they'll fight again...
Holy shit. One kissed in front
of the other, by their side...
I, Kimberly, think they're
going to have sex...
- Who are you?
- Kimberly.
I think they won't have sex.
Or they're going to have sex, but they
won't have a healthy relationship.
Bianca, and you?
I think they're in a troubling moment
until they figure it out,
but they can do it.
It's clear they like each other.
I don't even wanna talk to you.
You got to respect my brother here.
- So the chicks that were here left.
- Did you kiss one of them?
- I just kissed one person.
- No, you kissed the ginger.
- It was just a peck...
- It was a French kiss.
No, I didn't. It was a peck. She bit
my lip and I left. I said, "No."
- No, bro, you used your tongue.
- Buddy, no.
I kissed one person.
- Come on, bro. I saw it.
- One mouth.
She is a liar. That's disgusting.
You're mistaken.
Who is a liar? Me?
That's fucked up.
- No, girl... People...
- No, it was Murilo. That was it.
It wasn't like that.
He likes her too.
Otherwise, he wouldn't be mad like that.
It's not... Crossfire, son.
I think he should...
They like each other.
That little scene...
They tease each other.
It's a teasing game.
That's it.
It's not like...
- But it's good.
- It's good, but that's it.
She was going to kiss
someone in front of João.
I kissed one person,
I'm not gonna expose the chick.
I'm not a brat.
- I told you. I told you he kissed.
- Muzinho, say you kissed somebody.
Fuck off. I respected you, you know?
- And I didn't respect you?
- You know shit.
- Didn't I respect you?
- You don't know half of it.
You're a fake. I'm disgusted.
Please. I'm gonna go...
You got to impose respect.
Want to be respected?
If you can't handle it, don't play.
Don't bother me.
She's totally right.
She pissed him off. That's it.
Dude is... Yes.
But let me tell you... Yeah.
Now he's going to want her even more.
- I don't know.
- Go...
It's going to become a grudge.
Not now, but after a while...
It's a very dangerous game.
That grudge makes you horny.
Who wants to fuck again, got it?
That João is the crying one.
But, guys, it's a very dangerous game
because it's going to get tough.
She won't stand it
- because you've seen...
- Let's see if she will or won't.
Maybe she doesn't want him anymore...
She wants it...
See if he'll do the same.
...to hook up with someone
in front of João.
Did he hook up with
any girl in front of her?
No. Let's see if he'll do the same.
If he does,
it's because he's pissed,
he has feelings, too.
I think it's bad for both of them.
I love the opinions.
But no one can judge them.
If you like the person, what will you do?
I wouldn't be like this.
But we can't mistake
opinion for judgment.
An opinion is like an ass,
everyone has one.
No, but I understood what Bia said.
We can't give an opinion...
From what I've been watching,
it's bad for both of them.
I think it's interesting to see.
They are pretending...
...they're both doing things
to hurt each other.
It's bad, but the desire is rising.
Yeah... I've already done this a lot.
I used to say men are fragile.
We know that, but fuck...
I didn't know it was like that.
- No, guys...
- Fucking sensitive.
No... It's all wrong.
- I swear...
- It's all wrong.
Again, girls proved they're badasses.
And men are useless.
Yesterday what happened to Murilo
was beautiful. One day I cried,
the other day, he was pissed.
Everything that goes around
comes around, honey.
Grandma used to say,
"Men are only good for sex,
then you walk away."
I already said, "Use their body
and toss them away."
Hit pause right now. Look...
"Grandma used to say."
Is her grandma named Kátia?
Is it fair to hear...
If a woman says something like this,
and a guy says this thing about a woman...
What did she say?
...aren't we trying to fight for equality?
Don't compare this to that.
- Did she lie?
- I'll tell you something.
That woman saying to the whole world...
Because this is streaming, right?
The whole world can watch this.
And she saying, "Grandma used to say...
'Men are only good for...'"
Hi, guys.
"Only good for sex, then you walk away."
Imagine a guy saying this about a woman?
They are people.
She's talking about...
Let's not treat this generically...
I'm already bored. Look...
...this is about her.
You're saying
women talk about men.
I made a mistake. I don't like it.
But a man could've said that, too, Felipe.
- Men really say this.
- That's why I don't...
...judge men or women.
Do you think men don't say that?
- Like that?
- Yes...
"Women are only good for sex,
then you walk away"?
I know lots of them who say it.
Men and women, both of them say it.
Do you think they don't do this here?
No, tell me if I'm wrong.
If a man says that,
it'll be a mess.
- Of course they say it.
- I also...
There are men who say it.
I don't have friends
who say something like this.
"Women are only good for sex,
then you walk away."
- No...
- Titto, go to church.
Really... You're a wonderful woman.
- Do you think?
- No, I'm sure, bro.
- Sweet-talker.
- No, I promise you.
Fuck the rest.
Hey, mister...
Why do you have a girlfriend?
I'm dying to kiss you.
- Really?
- I swear.
That's okay, I respect that.
Not even a little kiss?
I wanna kiss you pretty bad.
She was rejected pretty bad.
Jeez, bro! I can't believe it, man.
Was she rejected?
I missed it, I'm careless. Stop...
I have a moon in Pisces.
And she hooked up with another one.
She's doing that to tease that guy...
- That's what I'm saying.
- He's also doing that to tease her.
It's okay. He did that to tease her.
You have to listen to me.
She's hitting on those guys.
Fuck, that's bad, man.
No, he also hooked up with...
...to get rejected?
For no reason? That's nonsense.
But if he was rejected,
the situation would be the same.
- That's lame, right?
- Don't judge.
Those two are in the same situation.
They are in love, love is beautiful.
That chick was pretending to be
unattached... Don't do that.
Do you know what I think?
This show will end, and they
will be together forever.
I think so, too.
- Why don't they enjoy that?
- When this show ends...
Are they together? That's what I asked.
His Instagram profile was not provided.
They're not together. I'm kidding.
- But he kissed...
- I think...
- Let's go to the after party, then?
- Is it gonna be nice?
No, but are you a good cook?
Because we are starving...
- Let me tell you...
- Look...
Is there a private room
for me and her to get some sleep?
You can sleep there...
- He wants to tease.
- Murilo's gonna hook up with two girls,
and Taynara looks like she's upset,
but she's confident.
João also took her home.
- I wonder if now is the time.
- It's today.
Place your bets.
Guys, I want to see it.
Is it now?
What will he come up with?
Show her my closet.
She wants some shorts.
-"Please."
- What is your name?
- Evelin.
Right. I remember.
That girl has a skin chafing.
Does Beatriz have chafing
or is she limping?
I get like this after Carnival.
- Will they play?
- They won't.
- They will play rock, paper, scissors.
- João is taking her to the room.
João is going to the room with that girl.
I can't believe João's gonna have sex.
I can't believe it.
What if he has a small dick?
- You won't see it.
- They went in so...
It's time to have sex.
No, but you saw that
"the makeup is here, look."
It's time for sex.
I wonder if...
What did she say?
That he wants to hook up with her.
I wonder if João is going to
lose his virginity.
Jeez, Virgin João.
He's going to lose his virginity.
- Yeah, I find it very ugly...
- Jeez, man...
It looks like...
There's a weird mood there.
Those girls are making a mess.
- It's not João!
- It's João.
- It can't be...
- It hasn't begun yet.
If there's no explicit scene for João,
I'll leave now.
I don't think so...
Guys, are they eating?
Look how Tay looked
at those girls. Blazing.
I found my flip-flops.
I love it. Oh, my God,
looks like a soap opera scene!
It's really like a soap opera.
Can you take those flip-flops off, please?
"Sure, honey."
- Jeez...
- She's upset...
- Would you ask your flip-flops back?
- I wouldn't!
- Sure, honey.
- Sure, baby.
Will you eat this much?
- It looks like...
- If she was phonier,
she'd be awarded a prize.
What? If I was phonier,
I'd be awarded a prize?
- What?
- You said that.
- Phony what? I didn't get it.
- I said...
I was the one who said it.
...she'd be awarded a prize."
Why did you say this?
Because she said, "Bye..."
Do you know what I'd say?
I'd say to her,
"He's just hooking up with you,
brought you two here because of me.
Would you say that to her?
"Because he loves me."
...that would be too low.
But that would be too low,
and I'd show him I care.
Thank God, Lord.
It's been a week, he was in need.
It's been more than that.
Because he came back
from Amazonas and came straight here.
In Amazonas,
he didn't do anything.
He was there for a month.
Shit, women in Amazonas are hot.
Put some clothes on.
He nailed it!
This is talent.
If you work a little bit, it may work.
Stop it, let me see if it worked.
Let me see.
Oh, yeah!
He got out of the room
celebrating in front of her.
- That's fucked up.
- Fuck, what a shame.
That's fucked up.
"Guys, I had sex, look!"
Yeah, that's a dickhead, bro, really.
But at least I won that bet
since João had sex.
João had sex!
Do you remember
who bet he was gonna have...
I bet he wouldn't.
I lost the bet.
I know, you have to pay me.
- You're crazy.
- Come here.
What?
She said, "What?"
'Cause I already turned.
What?
Bye. Good night. God bless you.
It was very good to see you. Sorry.
No problem.
- See you tomorrow?
- See you. Let's stay in touch.
Imagine those chicks leaving 300,
which is in Jurerê,
and taking the car to get to Lagoa
to be with that guy in that house.
Then she arrived there,
took those flip-flops, and they weren't...
She ate, changed her clothes again...
It's going to take an hour to come back...
Go fuck...
Baby, she ate for free
and got a ride home.
- She took a cab.
- Then it's all right.
Thinking about this, in the beginning...
One salad is worth an hour by car.
What a shame, man.
She went to have dinner with her friends.
That's part of... Anything goes.
She was humiliated there.
She wasn't humiliated.
I'm not gonna be
able to sleep till next week.
I wanna watch this now.
I'm very anxious.
It could be now.
Bia, are you anxious?
I think Tay is gonna marry Murilo.
Me, too. I'm gonna have to have...
You're crazy, especially now
with this in trouble.
It's gonna be here, in your house.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Why are you looking at her this way?
If a friend of mine talks like this,
"So-and-so slapped me."
What am I going to think?
That he slapped her face.
I would go talk to the guy.
"Are you going to slap her face?
Are you nuts?"