Previously on Mad Men:
- We'll be bicoastal.
- I quit my job.
Megan.
You wanted to be alone.
I love you, I'm going to leave my wife.
I'm your daughter.
What do I have to do to
get on the list of girls you give money to?
- When are you leaving for Los Angeles?
- It's not the way I wanted it.
We think it's best for you and the firm
if you take some time off and regroup.
I want a return date.
I've been doing account work in one form
or another since the day I started.
But you're not in that department.
I'm going to California.
Let this be the past.
Get out.
Hello, Don. This is Lou Avery,
from Dancer Fitzgerald.
We've met.
I've got to much to do.
And you thought you'd do it in here.
Sync & Corrections by Darcade
- Addic7ed.com -
Are you ready? Because I
want you to pay attention.
This is the beginning of something.
Do you have time to improve your life?
Do you have precisely 30 seconds
for a word from Accutron Watches?
The watch appears bottom third.
The second hand moves with a fluid sweep
and above it... "Accutron Time."
You go into a business meeting.
Is there food in your
teeth? Ashes on your tie?
And you've got nothing to say.
The meeting is boring, but you can't be.
But you're wearing an Accutron.
This watch makes you interesting.
It's a boardroom. It's black and white.
We hear light traffic. No talking.
We just see our man, you, late 20s,
shaggy with a youthful cowlick,
but in a suit and tie.
This is a businessman staring at his watch
as muffled conversation swirls around him.
Now we just hear the electronic hum.
Omm-mm.
He stands up and the faces come into view.
A couple of white-haired
men and a contemporary
who looks like Steve McQueen.
You shake hands and "Steve
McQueen" gets a look at your watch.
We hear the first words. "Is that Swiss?"
Now we're in color and it's a
little interview for the two of them
while the other men look, outlining
the benefits of this watch.
It is Swiss. It is accurate.
It is the height of design and technology.
"Accutron. It's not a timepiece.
It's a conversation piece."
Wow, Freddy.
That's a home run.
Actually, it's kind of an end run.
That is not what I expected.
There's a nice way to say that
and there's the way you just said it.
Well, it's really good.
They're going to resist
that black and white thing.
Yeah, but nobody's done
it. Not that I know of.
"Accutron, it's time for a conversation."
It's not as dramatic
and it hides the benefit.
I don't know. It sounds more elegant to me.
Yes?
You wanted me to tell you when it was
five minutes until the status meeting.
Thank you, Shirley.
So, I'll see you next week.
I'm gonna have another cup of coffee.
You really put the "free"
in freelancer, don't you?
Ahem. Hello?
Hello, Daddy.
Oh.
How are you, honey?
I'm well.
I thought I'd catch you
before you went to the office.
Right.
I'd like to have brunch Sunday morning.
Sure. That'd be nice.
I'll bring vodka. We'll have Bloody Marys.
No, in a restaurant.
How about the Plaza? They have vodka.
It'll just be me.
Sounds touching.
10:30. Bye-bye.
Bye, honey.
I feel like we really
got somewhere last night.
Hello, Dawn.
- Gentlemen.
- The team is here.
Fire when ready.
How long is this meeting?
That depends on you, doesn't it?
Who do we have here?
Gladys Knight and the Pips?
That's very hip, Lou.
- Should I get the door, Lou?
- Yes, Nurse.
So, how is everybody today?
Ready for your routine checkup?
Just open your mouths and say "ahh."
Gentlemen.
Get me those brand reviews.
It's a deadline, knuckleheads!
You know what it says to me?
It says you don't care.
And anybody who doesn't care
doesn't have to work here!
And you do not have the weekend!
- I can come back.
- No.
Clara, can I get a buttered
roll, please, from the lobby?
Yes, of course.
Come on in.
What are you holding?
It's Avon. You said you wanted to see me.
How many accounts do I have?
Well, it's all of them.
It feels like more.
I'm walking into this office every day
and I barely get ahead of things
before I get Bob from Detroit
around noon and Pete from LA around 2:00.
Is this Avon related,
or did you just need
someone to hand you a tissue?
I have no real help except Torkelson,
who's Cutler's guy.
And I think he's making Clara nightly.
- That's juicy.
- He can have her.
The point is Butler Footwear
just hired a new head of marketing
and if I meet with him, it's a demotion.
You're head of accounts.
He'll think he's important.
That's what it looks like to him.
But to Charles Butler
Jr., it looks like I'm only
as important as his head of marketing.
If I have no underlings, I'm useless.
Have Roger or Cutler meet with him.
That's two dumb ideas.
You're not listening to me.
This is a hierarchy.
Do you understand that?
Tell him I couldn't make
it at the last minute.
I'm having dinner with Jerry
Lewis or GM or somebody.
No, don't mention other clients.
Certainly.
I appreciate your confidence in me.
- Make him go away.
I have your roll and I have
Bob Benson on the line.
You see this? I don't
have time to take a crap.
And last but not least,
any news from the Motor City?
Chevy XP collateral is
scheduled to go to press Monday.
- Hallelujah.
- But we don't have approved copy.
We don't even have a name for it.
Dang it.
Chevy graphics people keep telling me
there's a "Chevy way" of doing things.
- And money is no object.
- Get it in writing.
You didn't pick an angle for Accutron.
Wow, is that today?
Sure, I did. Dawn, what did I say?
"Just in time to be on time."
That wasn't one of the choices.
I think that was a digression.
How about "Accutron is accurate"?
That was one of the choices, I'm positive.
"It's time for a conversation."
I think that one's more finished.
And I think you're putting
me in a position of saying
I don't care what you think.
Why would you put something in front
of me that you don't want me to pick?
Because you told me to give you two ideas.
You apparently only gave me one.
Last week I gave you 30 choices
and you told me to bring you two.
That's the way we do it.
I like your car.
Your flight was late. We
don't have time to go home.
One quick dinner, and the rest
of the weekend we're alone.
So let's go.
I can't move the seat.
Where should we start, DDB or K&E?
Surprise me.
Oh, hey.
Well, hello there.
Why aren't you brown?
- It's January in LA, too.
- That's no excuse.
Oh, Moira, can you remind me to pick up
two dozen bagels before the end of my trip?
Aha.
So, the missus misses New York.
No, they are for Pete.
Nan loves California.
Aren't you done with your adventure?
You know how many times I've
come down here looking for fun?
Isn't Lou fun?
Lou's great. We just miss you.
Why don't you move St.
Joseph's back another day?
You'll still have time to catch up.
You can come to the inauguration with me.
I'm supposed to take Sterling,
but say the word, I'll jettison.
Moira, let's start with Chevy.
You're really going to work?
Pencil him in for tomorrow.
That's what I've been saying.
I know. Okay, Ira. I've got to go.
Hello, Alan.
I'm sorry, I think I'm a little early.
First actress ever to say that.
You look wonderful, honey.
- Don Draper, this is Alan Silver.
- Don't get up.
The husband is a matinee idol.
I told you.
Don, I want to get one
thing out of the way.
Know that it was important
to me that you know
the man your wife is
spending so much time with.
I assure you, it's greed
and nothing else.
I feel completely at ease.
My partners in New York
promise a lot of things
to girls when they come West.
They passed off a lot of dogs.
But your girl is something.
I mean, she's the kind of girl
who's gonna shine for the network
in her callback for the
"Bracken's World" pilot.
What?
- Get out of here.
- I will not.
I thought the guy hated me.
But his boss loved you.
I'll say one thing about this girl,
she evokes strong feelings.
I feel like I just ate
a bag of butterflies.
Let's celebrate.
Young man.
Let me get a bottle of French champagne
for my French TV star here.
I can't believe it. When is it?
Wednesday, 9:15. We can hold
off on fixing your teeth.
Obviously I jumped the gun on that.
Okay.
What network?
NBC.
Such great news, honey.
Look at you two.
You're my favorite couple.
- Mr. Barnes? Wayne?
- That's me.
I'm Joan Harris from SC&P.
Should I tell them that
we're ready for a table?
Maybe we should wait for Ken.
Please, sit.
What can I get you?
I'll have a Coke.
Two Cokes.
I'm so sorry. Ken was
called away on an emergency
and rather than risk cancelling
on someone so important,
he asked that I stand in.
Look, I must be crazy to be disappointed.
I'm sure you had a hard
time keeping this seat empty,
but this conversation is best for Ken.
Tell me about your new position.
Head of marketing.
That's not just new for you,
that's new for Butler Footwear.
They pay me to think about the four Ps...
price, product, place,
and promotion. Thank you.
That's a smart way to think about it.
I have a degree in business.
It's not a science, but
we try to make it one.
Advertising is just a small
piece of the marketing mixture
and it might be more effective if it's
better integrated into our business.
So are you thinking about bringing
one of our account
executives into your office?
Actually, I'd like to move
all our advertising in-house.
It does sound like the conversation
is getting bigger than the two of us.
There's someone above
you and someone below you
and everybody's buying everybody dinner.
Wouldn't it be cheaper for Mr.
Butler to just walk down the hall?
SC&P's relationship with Butler Footwear
is very important to our company.
And I think you're being
shortsighted about our value.
Well, I was hired to be bold.
And I'm prepared to make my recommendation.
Forgive me, but my wife will be excited
to have me tuck the kids
in at least once this week.
Certainly, I just...
could you hold off on your
recommendation a few days
so that you can at least have the
dinner you thought you were having?
Sure. Pleasure to meet you.
You as well.
Excuse me.
Could I get a splash of whiskey in this?
I'll get the bag. You go sit down.
Take a quick look.
Then I want to turn off the
lights so you can see the view.
I like what you did with it.
I love it. But my next
house is gonna have a pool.
Our next house.
You sure you don't want to
move into a more populated area?
It's like Dracula's castle up here.
They're far away, Don.
It's just what happens to
the sound in the canyon.
I'm scared, but I don't want
to turn the lights back on.
I'm a little dizzy. I just... I need
to keep walking just for a second.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
I'll make it up to you tomorrow.
Get some rest.
Don, honey.
Please don't flick any
cigarettes off the balcony.
I don't know how, but everyone says
they can tell where the fire starts.
Don.
I love my scarf.
I thought with the
convertible, you'd need a few.
It's 9:00 and I have to get to class.
You want me to drop you at the office?
No, I'll take a cab.
Just don't work all day, okay?
And don't rip the ads out of my magazines.
Stan, you want coffee?
What are you doing here?
I'm just catching up on all
the work that's been going on.
Looks good. Lou, he's...
Yes, absolutely.
- So...
- I have a lot to do.
Stan, do you want any coffee?
- Yes.
- What?
He said yes.
Stan!
You don't have to make me any.
I'll be out of here in a minute.
Hey, Ted. Good to see you.
Hey, Stan.
I thought you'd be tan.
Well, you're in an office
here, you're in an office there.
What's the difference?
You know what? I'm just
going to get my work
and get out of here. Good to see you guys.
None of this seems related to coffee.
Buck up, chief.
I'm fine. It's fine.
You look good.
You look wel too.
Iced tea.
You really branched out
into a new environment.
I did discover it in a homesick moment.
I flew back New Year's Eve
after a week with my brother
and Christmas with Tammy and my in-laws.
Sat at the counter by myself
and immediately felt divine.
I'll have a Brooklyn Avenue.
It's a pastrami with the
coleslaw right on the sandwich.
Two of those.
Believe it or not, Brooklyn Avenue
is a street in East Los Angeles.
The New Yorkers here, they
brought as much as we need.
But the bagels are terrible.
Where are you living?
I have an apartment by the tar pits.
It's one bedroom, but it's two stories.
Must have quite a view.
The city is flat and ugly
and the air is brown,
but I love the vibrations.
You not only dress like a
hippie, you talk like one.
What have you been up to?
Keeping busy. You sign anything out here?
Yeah.
The first week I signed
H. Salt Fish and Chips.
Four stores. Didn't Roger
make an announcement?
I wouldn't know.
Oh, of course.
Listen, you know if it was up to me,
you'd be back there already.
How's Ted?
I noticed you timed it so you'd be
out here while he was back there.
I came to see my wife.
Yes, of course.
I've been meaning to look her up.
It's incredible, but he's sour.
Maybe he doesn't like the sun.
Last weekend, middle of January,
Sunkist sent us out to the groves
and I picked an orange right off the tree.
It's 75. There's snow on the mountains.
Ted sat in the car with the
door open writing on a pad.
It's good, isn't it?
So although Beverly Hills has
the patina of show business,
it's really just accountants,
lawyers, and dentists.
And you can walk to
lunch, although I don't.
Very nice.
So this is the chamber of horrors.
And then that's my office.
Well. Wonder who that could be.
- Hello there.
- Bonnie Whiteside.
This is Don Draper.
Bonnie's a real estate agent.
She's helping me find the ideal pad.
What, and leave the tar pits?
It's cute, but he shouldn't be renting.
Those are some nice-looking properties.
Where are you living?
I told you, honey, Don's bicoastal.
I wanted to be by the ocean, but
my wife rented a house in the hills.
- Great view.
- City or valley?
I don't know.
Well, when you're tired of commuting,
give me a call.
Don't get excited, Don.
She turns it on for everyone.
Ooh!
Professor Podolsky?
Mrs. Harris, I presume?
I appreciate you meeting me on a Saturday.
Well, the price is right
and the company looks interesting.
What exactly is the company, by the way?
The client is in footwear.
Shoes, women's.
The new head of marketing
wants to cut costs.
I get it.
It's 20 degrees out there
and the kids are in sandals.
Lowering overhead is not a bad idea.
Is that where you'd start,
keeping in mind "the four Ps"?
Do you have an MBA?
No, but their head of marketing does.
These kids.
Believe me, Rockefeller didn't
worry about "the four Ps."
Still, I'm going to need an argument
and I think it's going to need
to be more technical than that.
I mean, if they're not
quitters, it makes more sense
to diversify their lines
or open foreign offices.
How much to get an analysis
like that in writing?
Well, let's see if you
have anything to trade.
This is a business school.
Doesn't money work here?
I'm doing an advertising research study.
I wanted to know what
percentage of your clients
work on fees versus commission.
Oh.
Well, when I started working,
my goodness... 16 years ago,
all of our clients were on commission.
We started discussing a
fee-based model three years ago.
Now we're at 50-50.
I don't know if you can answer this,
or even understand it,
but what is the difference?
Actually, I can answer that.
You're going to need another pad.
Hello.
You frying bacon?
It's in the coq au vin.
And I made bread pudding with
blueberries in it for dessert.
Any wine left or did
the chicken drink it all?
I picked you up a bottle.
Better.
Oh, I think you have the
wrong address. I don't know...
Fellas, why don't you put it over there?
Over where? It's huge.
By the window. There's a
wall. That's where it goes.
- Thank you very much.
- You've got to sign.
Thank you.
Why did you do that?
- You have an antenna on the roof?
- It's huge.
It's the way they make them now.
How's it gonna look, Don?
You know, everyone I know here is starving.
You're going to be on TV.
Don't you want to watch
yourself in "living color"?
Don't jinx me.
I didn't know an expensive
gift would upset you.
You're not here long enough for a fight.
What are you doing up so late?
My mama said to tell
you the toilet's clogged.
Well, she's not supposed
to flush things down it.
She'll know what I'm talking about.
My mama said some people
just throw it out the window,
but she's not gonna. You got to fix it.
I'm sorry, Julio, but I
just got home from work.
It's Saturday. Why you got
to work? You got to fix it!
You could ask nicely.
That might work better.
- She said to yell at you.
- Why?
Because you don't listen.
I don't understand her.
Here. This is yours.
It's a gift. Good night.
What is this?
Let's go to bed.
Hey.
Yes?
We haven't celebrated.
Oh, I didn't know if you wanted to.
I do.
Let me brush my teeth.
Hold on.
Are you okay?
I'm just...
I don't know why I feel nervous.
About this?
About everything.
Don't.
Good morning.
How much time do we have?
I'm on the red-eye.
I hate this.
We have the rest of the day.
I know.
I'm sorry, but I have to get back to work.
Hello.
They saved all the construction for Sunday.
It's okay, Daddy. Catch your breath.
It's so good to see you.
Sweetheart, being
summoned makes me nervous.
No, everything's wonderful.
Can you give us a minute?
To the fear of an ambush.
To being together.
What the hell are you up to?
I just wanted to see you
and tell you that it's been too long
and that, well,
when all is said and done,
I forgive you.
That's beautiful to hear.
Because I forgive you, too.
No, Daddy.
I forgive you.
And I forgive you.
All of your transgressions...
abandoning Mother,
making me ask for money,
your intermittent interest in Ellery.
I don't even care
that you smell like incense
or have any thoughts about your
current, quote, "state of affairs."
I simply forgive you.
You want me to say I'm sorry?
Because I don't agree with all that.
Where the hell is this coming from?
Well, if you must know,
I've been searching.
And with a little help,
I've come to understand
that anger can be vanquished by love.
You going to church?
Not in any way you'd understand.
- What do you want from me?
- Nothing.
You can't make it better.
So now we're just supposed
to eat eggs Benedict?
I would love that.
Good evening.
Evening.
Thank you.
Do you want a sleeping pill?
No, thank you.
You know what?
Me either.
I'm sorry. Don't tell me you enjoy flying.
I fly a lot.
And I'm always hoping I was seated next to,
well, someone like you...
instead of a man with a
hairpiece eating a banana.
But why would I expect anything else?
You can blame Madison Avenue for that.
Ladies and gentlemen, this
is your captain speaking.
Where were you? I was worried.
I thought we hated all things domestic.
You sound uptight.
Man walks in, obviously having tied one on,
the woman says, "Where were you?"
Kind of establishment.
Why are you being so mean?
Move over.
Oh, Christ. Move him over, too.
Is that my vest?
If you were with someone, I don't care.
You know anyone's welcome in this bed.
I just want to get some sleep.
I'd like to put this on,
but vanity is preventing me.
You want me to wear
mine so I don't see you?
This is nice. I usually sleep alone.
What about the man that gave you that ring?
He passed away.
A year ago, actually.
I was...
he wanted his ashes
scattered at Pebble Beach.
How was that?
I failed.
It's a very popular spot for such things.
Apparently, they don't
want another sand trap.
I ended up at his second choice.
Disneyland.
Really?
Have you ever been there?
I have.
Where is he now?
Tom Sawyer Island.
That's probably a popular destination, too.
Yes, they were very vigilant.
It took some doing.
How old was he?
He would have been 50.
So, much older?
He worked fast, too.
What happened to him?
He was thirsty.
He died of thirst.
His company sent him to a hospital.
I went with him.
I was supposed to be
part of the cure somehow.
And all I did was observe.
I thought
he was really getting better.
Then a doctor told me
he'd be dead in a year.
All of them would be.
I'm gonna close my eyes now.
Ladies and gentlemen, good morning.
Despite our best efforts,
we're still stacked up,
but it looks like we're two away.
I think that we'll begin
our descent in 15 minutes.
Sorry, I think I dozed off.
You have a few more minutes.
If I was your wife, I wouldn't like this.
She knows I'm a terrible husband.
How long have you been married?
Not long enough.
I really thought I could do it this time.
- Did she kick you out?
- No.
She doesn't know that much,
but she knows.
Well, if she doesn't know,
you should just keep it that way.
That's what people do.
I keep wondering...
have I broken the vessel?
If you did, what can you do about it?
It's done.
I bet I could make you feel better.
I bet you could.
There's a car waiting for me.
I can give you a lift.
I'm sorry, but I have to get back to work.
Your tenant Mrs. Rodriguez
called again about her toilet.
She was hard to understand,
but I think she said
she's calling the alderman.
Ugh.
Call my sister Anita
and tell her to get Gerry
and his friend the plumber up there.
- Shouldn't I just call Gerry?
- No.
Anita can ask her husband, I can't.
- Good morning, ladies.
- Good morning.
- How was your weekend?
- Peachy.
Cut up some firewood.
I'm sorry about last week.
You' right that I shouldn't have
suggested something I didn't like.
I never gave it another thought.
Well, I did
and I realized that Freddy's original idea
was the best, but I didn't do it justice.
What are you doing? I already said yes.
"Accutron,
it's not a timepiece,
it's a conversation piece."
Forget it.
- Morning.
- Morning, Lou.
This is actually a big idea.
Why are you making this so hard?
Open the door and walk in.
You do not need to parachute
in through the ceiling.
But I don't mind. I just
want to give you my best.
I don't know, Peggy.
I guess I'm immune to your charms.
Can I get some coffee?
Good morning, Clara. Is Ken in yet?
No, he's on the plane.
As soon as he lands, I need to
speak with him regarding Butler.
Good for you. Mr. Butler
is coming in this week.
What?
Get Wayne Barnes on the line... now.
Mr. Barnes on line three.
Joan?
- You already set a meeting?
- Good morning.
I took you seriously, but
you didn't take me seriously.
Look, I know you're fighting for
your job, but don't get emotional.
I'm fighting for your job.
Okay, well, I appreciate it,
but don't worry about me. I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
Let's talk about your
in-house advertising agency.
You think you can go into
a network or a newspaper
with your checkbook
and get the space we get
when we deal with them
every day with 30 clients?
You will be competing against us,
not against other shoe companies.
We both know the shoe
business is going to decline
for some time in the future.
If you make a bold move now,
that decline will be your responsibility.
What are you gonna do then?
You can only fire us once.
So what am I supposed to do?
I already set the meeting.
Cancel it.
No, I'm asking you,
what do I do?
Tell them we cancelled the meeting.
We need more time to present
a revised media strategy.
- Yes.
- Good.
I'm still expecting to meet with Ken.
I'll follow up on that today.
You'd better.
Did you tell him to prepare
more boards for Accutron?
- Do you want to do it?
- No, I want to do it.
- I don't know what I did.
- Get out of here.
He may be in the art
department, but he reports to me.
We already have boards
for "Accutron is accurate."
You know that's a loser.
I think if he could see both
of them, he'll change his mind.
Or at least let us show both to the client.
Let it go, baby. It's dead.
No, I just don't think he's
given it the proper thought.
You're telling your boss
you think he's stupid.
Well, I'm tired of fighting
for everything to be better.
You're all a bunch of hacks who
are perfectly happy with shit.
Nobody cares about anything.
No one wants things to be better, I got it.
I'll just stand out here all by myself.
We find ourselves rich in goods,
but ragged in spirit...
reaching with magnificent
precision for the moon,
but falling into raucous discord on Earth.
We are caught in war wanting peace.
We're torn by division wanting unity.
We see around us empty
lives wanting fulfillment.
We see tasks that need doing...
- Come in.
- ... waiting for hands to do them.
You know I'm breaking a rule here.
I haven't had one of these
sausages since I quit.
If this makes me have dreams about
beer, I'm gonna be mad at you.
Oh, no, no. Come on.
I should be paying you.
You want that balcony door
open? It's freezing outside.
Peggy went bananas for your Accutron work.
Of course she lifted her leg on it.
Also, I swang by J. Walter Thompson,
thinking there was an emergency
with our copy for 7-Up.
- You want a sweater?
- Nah.
Turns out they're looking
for help on Oscar Mayer.
You are making quite a
name for me out there.
Bologna? Hot dogs? It's
moms and kids either way.
Why don't you stop this Cyrano bit
and march your ass in
there and get us both a job?
Because I have a job.
It's been two months.
Nobody's called, right?
Still being paid.
Well, they had Christmas without you.
The Super Bowl. Pretty
soon it's gonna be Easter.
You know, I've been there.
You don't want to be damaged goods.
I tried to get a hold of you.
Why? I spoke to Clara. Thank
you for solving that problem.
I bailed it out, but I
think it's irreparable.
It's only a matter of
time before we lose it.
Every account man who's ever
come into my office has said that.
But they haven't all left one of these.
- Oh.
- Stay out of my office.
Sorry.
I dozed off.
Well, Jimmy says he'll
be back in the morning.
He needed a part.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
It seems silly for you to go all the
way out to Brooklyn and come back.
It won't take long this time of night.
Are you sure?
I don't like Anita
there alone in the house.
Of course.
- See you in the morning.
- Okay.