( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( taps )
I'm sorry to bother you,
but we're the people
who paid for your meal,
and as much as I am committed
to you enjoying your food
while it's still piping hot,
I do have a few more
questions, if you don't mind.
I'll give you
the $3.10 back.
I have to beat my husband home.
Would your husband be
happy if you were late,
but had another $10?
Well, I guess it would help.
Good evening, ma'am.
What's your name, little girl?
It's Stacy.
Is that your question?
Would you say that you eat
here weekly, monthly?
Too much.
What's your favorite
thing about Burger Chef?
The taste or the price?
- It's near my house.
- Convenience.
Usually.
Does your husband
ever pick it up?
Oh, he wouldn't do that. It's bad
enough that I'm not making dinner.
Is that all?
Come back soon.
How much money do you have?
Two more families
and Chinese for us.
It's not a listing.
It's Sybil's apartment.
I'm not squatting.
I can afford a hotel.
It's seven nights.
I'm not paying for it, bonita.
Let me at least pay for
the theater tickets.
I get them for free.
Well, I'm going to buy you a
pair of loafers on Fifth Avenue.
I want you shopping all day...
and screwing all night.
You'll spend the weekend
with me, won't you?
I will need to spend
some of Saturday
afternoon in Cos Cob.
Well, I'll come.
Why would you want to do that?
I sure would like
to meet Tammy.
I picked out her Barbie.
I don't want
to confuse her, baby.
She's probably more confused
that her parents
aren't actually divorced.
So that's something
that bothers you.
Of course it bothers me.
I don't know
where this is going,
but I don't want it to
fail on account of delay.
I haven't seen her in a while.
Next time...
I promise.
I thought you were never
going to get married again.
Meet me in the restroom
in 60 seconds.
I've always wanted to do that.
( TV playing )
- Aren't you going to eat?
- I'll have a roll at the office.
Well, you're disappearing.
Every time you say
something like that,
I go off my diet.
( TV off )
Go outdoors today, please.
( clicking )
I hope I'm not interrupting?
It's Bonnie.
I remember you.
You can't just walk in here.
Bonnie, this is Meredith.
Do you want me to come and
get you in five minutes?
Meredith, that'll be all.
Pete's having quite a homecoming,
so I thought I'd duck in.
You're the only one
I know here.
How long are you in town?
I hate to say it, but I
knew where to find you.
- Don, how are you?
- Good to see you.
I like what you've
done with the place.
I heard you have
quite the home.
Pete says it's
2,000 square feet.
Not quite.
Peggy's going to be leading us
through the work, as it were.
I assume you're attending?
- Burger Chef?
- You're on the team.
I'd like you to be there.
I guess this is my cue.
Baloney. Walk me to
the conference room.
He wants to make sure
everyone's seen you.
( chuckles )
- Ta-ta.
- Very well.
Is this the billboard?
It's kind of lackluster.
That's the tray liner.
- That's everything, chief.
- Thank you, Stan.
- Hello, Stan.
- Good to see you, Pete.
How's life treating you?
I'm in New York
and I'm in love.
Me as well.
Hello, Pete.
Well, I think we should
get this started.
Did you need something, Don?
I've asked Don to join us.
I didn't know
you wanted the team.
Should we get Mathis as well?
No, Don's plenty.
Well, he has been instrumental.
I think we're
circling a strategy--
all the research
points to the fact
that mothers feel guilty.
They don't eat
at the restaurant
because of what Mathis calls
a "cleanliness fetish."
( chuckles )
And even when they get home,
they're embarrassed.
Our job is to turn Burger Chef
into a special treat
served with love.
So the more these women
go to Burger Chef,
- the worse they feel.
- Yes.
We need to address how to
give homemakers permission.
Well, who gives
moms permission? Dads.
It's a dark night.
Reveal our mom, driving,
girl in a tutu next to her,
boy wearing a football
helmet in the back.
Push into a close-up
as we hear Mom's voice--
the things on her mind.
"Let's see, check that list for
the marching band fundraiser.
Get the sink trap checked.
Get Jim to take down
the storm windows.
( gasps )
Jim!
Jim will be home
in a half an hour."
Just then the little
girl says, "I'm hungry."
The boy says,
"I'm starving."
Mom says,
"One more stop."
We see the reflection
of the Burger Chef sign
on the station wagon
windshield as she pulls in.
Mom gets out of the car.
A handsome man comes out
holding a bag.
Mom walks up to him
and gives him a deep kiss.
The kids in the car
looking surprised.
He laughs and says,
"Can I take you to dinner?"
She says, "Next time,
let me get dinner.
You take down
the storm windows."
( chuckling )
Cut to them
at the kitchen table,
camera moving from face
to smiling face.
They're laughing,
Mom looks around, smiling.
VO, "Aren't you glad
everybody loves Burger Chef
as much as you do?"
Very nice. I think
it's coming along.
It's nice to see
family happiness again.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Dad surprising the family
absolves the mom.
It's right on strategy.
It's exactly what they wanted.
Don worked the tag over
by the syllable.
- It's deceptively simple.
- Thank you.
Why don't you take us
through the legs?
Let's start with radio.
Looky here.
A sight for sore eyes.
Ah...
Hello, Jim.
How's your Burger Chef
work going?
Better than yours, I guess.
Thank you, by the way, for failing
and giving us a shot at it.
It's not McDonald's.
It's run by morons.
A lot of companies
succeed that way.
But look who I'm talking to.
You don't mean that.
You're going after fast food,
you've got
your little car--
it's not Buick, but it's cute.
I know you folks want to be just
like McCann when you grow up.
When we grow up, we're going to
kill you and marry your wife.
( chuckles ) Listen, I hear
you're talking to Philip Morris.
Is Leo Burnett in here, too?
Well, I'm just curious how you think
you're going to pull that off
with Don Draper
haunting your halls.
( sighs )
You're so lucky my problems
aren't your problems.
What if I wanted them to be?
Are you looking for a job?
No. No.
I'm just looking
to enrich the lives
of people I respect.
The New York Athletic Club
frowns on people
making advances
in their steam room.
I was kidding around,
but I think you're
making eyes at me.
I'm gonna go get a massage,
relieve some of this tension.
Fellas, we got a live one here.
Come in, join us
I'm drinking rum.
Do you want some?
- No, thank you.
- That bar, it's hysterical.
My wife's a card.
I'm very pleased with the
direction I saw this morning.
- We all are.
- Thank you.
And-- not but--
I think with my understanding
of George Payton,
that our success would
be further assured
if Don delivered
the presentation.
- Oh.
- Here's the but.
It is completely your decision.
Why are you doing this now?
That's what I said.
She's doing fine.
Lou, first of all, you've
never seen Don at his best.
It'll be a tearjerker.
Number two is Peggy, in my
mind, will still speak,
but as the mother.
A change of tone.
You were wonderful in there.
I don't like
being in this position.
I know I can bring this home.
Peggy, you didn't walk into
this office and see Don here.
This is your client,
and you're going to write as
much of it as you want to.
Don will give authority,
you will give emotion.
I have authority.
And Don has emotion.
I prefer you
as an expert witness.
- You will introduce him.
- Intercom: But it's your decision.
- What?
-  It's Ted.
Ted's on the phone.
Oh.
Hello.
I've seen the work so far.
I'm impressed.
And what would you do?
I would use everything
at my disposal to win it.
If you think George Payton
will prefer it,
I'm not going to ignore that.
You know that she's
every bit as good
as any woman in this business!
I do.
He'll be great.
Keep up the good work.
It's big and powerful and costs a
fortune, but it can't make coffee.
They've got a computer
twice that size
working on the
engine for the XP.
- Clara?
- Nice to see you, Mr. Benson.
Gentlemen, there's coffee and
cake in Mr. Crane's office.
May I take your hats?
Hey, fellas.
Jack, Bill, nice to see you.
- Hello, Kenny.
- How's the kid? Is he flying yet?
Are you kidding? He's
crawling all over the place.
You've really got
to keep an eye on him.
Joan!
Come say hello.
Welcome back, Bob.
Gentlemen.
How the hell did we end up
with him instead of you?
- No one asked.
- This is Bill Hartley.
Bill's been bumped
to vice president of brand.
Congratulations.
You certainly picked the
right place to celebrate.
You mean New York City
or this very spot?
( laughs )
So far all we have lined up
is six hours of network pilots.
Clara, could you take
them to Harry's office?
- Enjoy.
- Very funny.
Pleasure, ma'am.
I'd love to see you Sunday.
Unless you've made plans
with some married guy.
I am all yours.
But if you want to see Kevin, you're
going to have to see my mother.
I want to see everyone.
- You need something?
- Yes, actually, I do.
I've given it careful thought,
and I think you should give the
presentation to Burger Chef.
Hold on.
You did a great job
this morning.
That's good to hear,
but I want to have
the best chance
of winning this,
and I'm not going to
pretend you're not it.
- Whose idea was this?
- Mine.
I'll introduce you, and
when you're rounding third,
you hand it off
to "the voice of moms."
And then you turn and hit the tag
like you just thought of it.
- Do I do that?
- Yes, you do.
- Whatever you want.
- That's what I want.
Thank you.
You know, I was just noodling
around with the idea
of seeing the whole thing
from the kids' perspective.
- "Mom, can we go to Burger Chef?"
- Excuse me?
I don't know.
Just a thought.
I appreciate it, but we
already have a strategy.
( door closes )
Megan?
Hello!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Why didn't you say something?
No, Marsha, this is
Megan, Don's wife.
I didn't know he was married.
So nice to meet you.
Marsha, can you
get Megan some coffee?
I'm fine.
This is very impressive,
but where do you work now?
My office is right here.
- Are you a surprise?
- No, he's expecting me.
Well, you're a surprise for me.
How is everything in LA?
It's exciting
and new and different.
And a lot quieter.
What a great office.
Sooner or later you're going
to get Don's, aren't you?
I don't know
how much better it is.
He's right next door.
Oh.
Hey!
I didn't expect to see you.
- Peggy: Megan's in for a visit.
- Thanks for the subtitles.
- Did you hear about Ginsberg?
- Yes. Have you seen him?
I did.
She won't go.
Don: All right,
Meredith, I'm gonna go.
Don?
What are you doing here?
I couldn't wait to see you.
I thought
we could eat downtown.
That's a great idea.
Well, it was so great
to see you both.
Is it okay?
I have a visitor.
Enjoy yourself.
Good night.
I miss her.
You didn't even ask me
how the dry run went.
Was there a problem?
No, they loved it.
Are you mad at me?
No.
Good night, Stan.
Good night.
Ah, good, you're still here.
That's your opinion.
I played a round this
morning with Les Clark--
my friend from Philip Morris?
The brand commander
of Commander brand.
Your name came up
and I sure would appreciate
you helping us pave that road.
Your secret plan
to win the war?
Stop thinking about Don
and start thinking
about the company.
( ringing )
Who's here for William Hartley?
- Bill?
- Don't say anything.
But you should say thank
you to your boyfriend
- for posting bail.
- Has he seen a doctor?
- What did I just say?
- Take him to a headshrinker.
He tried to fellate
an undercover officer.
May I go?
Good night,
"ladies."
( distant siren wails )
I called you because
I knew you could keep this to yourself.
You should go to the hospital.
You know they're just
going to call the cops.
( sighs ) I wish I
was back in Detroit.
I've got that place wired.
Have you ever been arrested?
No.
Never.
I guess you've been lucky.
Well, I appreciate this.
I'm going to miss
having you around.
I am not of your stripe.
And you should think twice before
you threaten me like that.
Please.
I'm not threatening you.
We're moving the XP over to
Campbell-Ewald, and you're moving on.
- We're losing Chevy?
- Don't worry.
GM loves the work,
and they really love you.
Obviously not.
Your agency had
a successful tryout,
but the plan was always
to take the XP in-house.
But Buick is going
to come to you
with a great job offer.
What?
Well, that's very good news.
- When does all this happen?
- Imminently.
What about you?
I'm gonna call in sick.
My wife understands, thank God.
That's a good idea.
How did you live in this city?
There's so much temptation.
It was hard.
( sighs )
( birds chirping )
Hello?
Trudy?
Come along, let's go say hi.
Hello, sweetie.
It's Daddy, sweetheart.
I got you a Barbie all
the way from California.
Go ahead.
I don't believe we've met.
- Where's Trudy?
- She's at the hairdresser.
I'm Verna.
Well, Verna's going to
come with us to the car.
Tell me it was all a dream.
You're in a good mood.
Tell me you didn't miss this.
I missed you.
Well, we're going to eat
this delicious breakfast,
and I'm going
to take you shopping.
Okay.
( ringing )
Hey, baby, I'm almost ready.
"Hi, baby" yourself. I've
been here since 10:00.
- Oh, it's you.
- Are you coming in?
Find something else to do today.
That's an order.
I don't like the idea.
Of doing something else?
No, the idea for Burger Chef.
You haven't been "noodling"
with anything else, have you?
It came easy.
You don't trust it.
- It didn't come easy at all.
- So find a new one.
So you don't like it either.
The work is great!
I'm positive,
exclamation point!
How do I know you're not
just saying that
so you don't have to come in?
( sighs )
Do you need me to come in?
No.
Your "baby's" calling.
But we both know
there's a better idea.
There's always a better idea.
Bye.
( TV playing )
Look at you.
You say goodbye to your daddy, and
then you're going to take a bath.
- Where's Trudy?
- She's out, Mr. Campbell.
Her car's in the drive.
Well, she came back,
but then she went out.
Why don't you give Tammy a
bath and let me tuck her in?
Of course,
Mr. Campbell.
( ringing )
- Hello?
- Hello, dear.
I'm afraid I've been
waylaid in Cos Cob.
You go without me. I'll pick
you up for a drink after.
You really want me to see "Oh!
Calcutta!" by myself?
Trudy must've forgotten.
There's no one
to look after Tammy.
Oh.
That's rather
inconsiderate, isn't it?
I'm sure it's just a mistake.
Well, I'm going to wait
until the very last minute.
That's sweet.
I'll make it up to you.
You most certainly will.
( line clicks )
( phone ringing )
- Should I get it?
- It's not for me.
- Hello?
- Oh, I'm glad I caught you.
- Are you on your way out?
- Just sitting down to dinner.
Well, it's just--
I just wanted to let you know
that I tried your
"kids' point of view" idea,
and it's not good.
( chuckles )
Well, it was great
hearing from you.
It's just I know,
now that you're presenting,
you're prone to more
serious thought,
and I just wanted you
to know that one's a loser.
I'm always working, Peggy.
So are you.
Why are you undermining me?
From now on
I won't express myself.
Well, now it's tainted.
It's poisoned, because you
expressed yourself.
If you don't want to
do it, don't do it.
Did you lose your appetite?
Absolutely not.
Oh, hello.
Did you just get back?
No, but you did.
Is Tammy still up?
No. We said
our good nights.
Verna's back there
hiding somewhere.
Well, did you have a nice time?
I was in fine spirits
until I thought
about you pulled over
on the side of the road
necking with Charlie Fiddich.
- Charlie Fiddich?
- Well, who was it, then?
Or are you going to keep
it a secret from me
like your father's
heart attack?
You've seen your
daughter for the year.
Don't you have
a plane to catch?
I don't like you carrying on like this.
It's immoral.
- You have a child.
- What?!
You picked tonight
for your date?
You still care about me.
I know your
debutante maneuvers.
We're getting a divorce.
We're still married.
You're not part of
this family anymore.
Good night.
( door closes )
( doorbell dings )
- ( Kevin coos )
- Well, hello there.
Well, hello yourself.
Somebody missed you.
You're early, but welcome.
These are for you.
And that is for you.
- Wow.
- It's an Erector Set.
America needs engineers.
What do you say to Uncle Bob?
Thank you.
I know everybody got something,
but I was shopping in Midtown
all day yesterday
and I struck out.
The Jews close
everything on Saturday.
I'm starving.
I see a day that
starts with pancakes
and ends with
an ice cream sundae.
Should I bring the stroller?
I'll carry him if I have to.
Let me get my bag.
_
What are you looking for?
Oh, good morning.
The fondue pot.
It's not in the kitchen.
Coffee's fine.
No, I thought it would
get some use out there.
I thought you just
needed summer clothes.
I miss my things.
You were dead to the world.
I sleep better
when you're here.
Oh, I miss you, too.
I'm sorry the visit's so short.
Can I just check this
in on the plane?
How much is there?
I can take some.
When?
The next time I come.
End of July.
You know what?
I want to see you somewhere
where there's
nothing else going on.
Not LA.
Not here.
Just us.
That'd be nice.
( TV playing )
Air-conditioning.
Delicious.
- Did you have fun?
- You ate already?
I'm sorry, I was hungry.
I can eat again.
Look at these feet.
I wore my sandals
and I look like a hobo.
My toenails are black.
You can't wear
those in the city.
You might as well be barefoot.
Will you try on your wares?
Slowly?
Well, at least
you're in a better mood.
Come over here.
Did you get your work done?
Some of it.
Well, this is my vacation,
and I knew you were
going to the office,
but the first Saturday
we spent here,
you needed to see
your daughter.
Then you didn't come home,
which I understand
was Trudy's fault.
Then you were grumpy.
Okay.
Then I amused myself
all morning,
and when I come back,
you ordered room service?
I'm inundated, sweetheart.
I don't like you in New York.
Well, then you don't like me.
You're not going to
fuck your way out of this.
What?
I'm going to wash my feet.
How's it going?
( huffs )
Did you park your
white horse outside?
Spare me the suspense and tell me
what your "save the day" plan is.
I don't have anything yet.
The idea I had wasn't great.
It wasn't great.
It was terrible.
I want to hear the real one.
Or are you just going to pull
it out during the presentation?
This idea is good.
I think we can get
the client to buy it.
No, you don't, or you
wouldn't have questioned it.
I'm going to do
whatever you say.
So you're going to pitch the
hell out of my shitty idea,
and I'm going to fail.
Peggy, I'm here to help you do
whatever you want to do.
Well, how am I
supposed to know?
That's a tough one.
- You love this.
- Not really.
I want you to feel good
about what you're doing,
but you'll never know.
That's just the job.
What's the job?
Living in
the "not knowing."
You know, I wouldn't have
argued if it was me.
I would have just given
you a hundred ideas
and never questioned why.
You really want to help me?
Show me how you think.
Do it out loud.
You can't tell people
what they want.
It has to be what you want.
I want to go to the movies.
I just came back from
"I Am Curious Yellow."
I'm still scandalized.
Of course Megan would want
to see a dirty movie.
- Do you want to work?
- It doesn't matter if I want to.
I have to, because
all of this is crap.
Pros and cons.
Pros--
it's almost done and it's good.
The account man's overjoyed
and the client's on board.
Those are the cons,
and you know it.
Well...
whenever I'm really
unsure about an idea,
first...
I abuse the people
whose help I need.
And then I take a nap.
Done.
Then I start
at the beginning again...
and see if I end up
in the same place.
Mom's job is to make dinner.
Burger Chef's job
is to stop her.
What is it about that thing?
Little boys love it.
( "The End of a Party"
plays in background )
You're a very lucky person.
Have I been
complaining too much?
No.
- Did Gail go to bed?
- She did.
( sighs ) I know I
shouldn't be saying this,
because my heart is pounding.
What?
I know I said I didn't
get you anything...
but I did.
Bob, put that away.
I know I should have done
this a long time ago.
Did I miss my chance?
No.
I don't know.
So you don't feel
anything for me?
My face doesn't please you?
I don't believe it.
You don't want this.
You're not listening to me.
Bob...
you shouldn't be with a woman.
I have been, you know.
Why are you doing this now?
Well, honestly,
I'm moving on to Buick.
And GM expects a certain
kind of executive.
- You're leaving the agency?
- Yes.
But that's why
it would work so well.
You could stay here,
do whatever you want.
Kevin would have a father.
Or you could come with me.
You'd love Detroit.
We could have a mansion.
- When did all this happen?
- I just heard it.
And you can't relay it,
because they're moving
the XP to Campbell-Ewald.
- We lost Chevy?
- Yes.
But the audition was a success.
There's something else
coming down the road.
The times
like this, Joan--
this is when you need someone.
We could comfort each other
through an uncertain world.
I can't think
about this right now.
I'm thinking about you, Joan.
Is this what you want?
To be near 40 in a
two-bedroom apartment
with a mother and a little boy?
I know I am flawed,
but I am offering you more
than anyone else ever will.
No, you're not, Bob.
Because I want love.
And I'd rather die
hoping that happens
than make some arrangement.
And you should too.
I'm just being realistic.
Good night.
( "Forever and Ever"
plays in background )
Okay, so in this new version,
Dad's driving the car.
Mom's next to him, admiring?
How about a convertible?
Little boy and little girl
in the back,
Dad's got a pipe in his mouth.
( chuckles )
Jesus, it's going to look
like 1955.
1955 was a good year.
I don't remember.
1965 was a good year.
I got married.
Moms love Burger Chef
because it's an answer
to a crisis.
What if Mom's
coming home from work?
What's her profession?
You are surrounded
by all kinds of mothers
who work, Don.
It's too sad for an ad.
( sighs )
Fine.
She burned the roast,
she dented the fender...
Keep going.
She backed over the dog,
little Katie's pregnant,
Jimmy got drafted,
but there is still a burger
and fries on that table?
Does this family exist anymore?
Are there people who eat dinner
and smile at each other
instead of watching TV?
Did you ever do that
with your family?
I don't remember.
What the hell do I know
about being a mom?
I just turned 30, Don.
Shit. When?
A couple of weeks ago.
It doesn't matter.
I kept it as secret as I could.
Now I'm one of those women
lying about her age.
I hate them.
I worry about a lot of things,
but I don't worry about you.
What do you have
to worry about?
That I never did anything,
and that I don't have anyone.
I was in Ohio,
Michigan, Pennsylvania.
I looked in the window
of so many station wagons.
What did I do wrong?
You're doing great.
What if there was a place
where you could go...
where there was no TV...
and you could break bread...
and whoever you were
sitting with
was family?
( "My Way"
playing in background )
That's it.
That's more what it is.
( sniffles )
♪ my friends,
I'll say it clear... ♪
- Do you hear this?
-  ♪ I'll state my case... ♪
I know, they're playing
it all the time.
Do you think
that's a coincidence?
♪ I've lived ♪
♪ a life that's full ♪
♪ I've traveled
each and every highway... ♪
Come on.
♪ and more ♪
♪ much more than this ♪
♪ I did it my way ♪
♪ regrets ♪
♪ I've had a few ♪
♪ but then again ♪
♪ too few to mention ♪
♪ I did ♪
♪ what I had to do ♪
♪ and saw it through ♪
♪ without exemption ♪
♪ I planned ♪
♪ each charted course ♪
♪ each careful step ♪
♪ along the byway ♪
♪ and more ♪
♪ much more than this ♪
♪ I did it my way... ♪
It's official.
The XP is no longer ours.
But they've thought of a name.
They're going to call it
"Roger Sterling's failure."
- I thought you signed them.
- Where did you hear this?
You knew?
Cutler: I think we should
get ahead of this.
I am proposing a "New
York Times" article
and the "Journal," too, announcing
that we're open for business
with our IBM 360 and our
proprietary software.
And there's a big
picture of Harry Crane,
- our newest partner.
- What?
The rest of it's fine,
but Harry Crane's a partner?
If that's what it takes.
I'm not going limping
into Burger Chef.
Why does he
have to be a partner?
Say what you will,
but he's very loyal.
All in favor?
Opposed?
The motion carries.
With two abstentions.
All right,
everybody back to work.
I've got it.
- What the hell do you want?
- Not Harry Crane as partner.
Well, you knew about Chevy,
and you didn't tell me.
- I could have done something.
- There was nothing to do.
Spill the beans or get out.
Bob Benson told me.
- He's going to Buick.
- Bob Benson?
- Please don't get him in trouble.
- You're kidding?
- I knew McCann was up to something.
- What are you talking about?
They're afraid we're
going to steal Buick.
What?
Just forget it.
Thank you.
Now we have nothing.
We're only weeks away.
Just hear her out.
She'll have you done
in time for dinner.
My plans got cancelled.
Look around.
I want to shoot the ad in here.
- It's not a home.
- It's better.
It's a clean,
well-lighted place.
Okay, Hemingway.
As long as it's
still about moms.
It's about family.
Every table here
is the family table.
I hate
even the word "family."
It's vague.
"Mom" is more specific.
Tell her, Don.
She's doing it the way
she wants to do it.
You want it right or not?
( instrumental music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com