Previously on Mad Men...
You killed him.
You killed the ad.
You killed everything.
She's the kind of girl
who's gonna shine for the network
in her callback for the
"Bracken's World" pilot.
What?
Don and I signed Chevy.
Don who?
Our collective ex-wife
who still receives alimony?
I agree with Jim.
Do you still love Megan?
Of course I do.
Why don't you just tell her that
you don't want to move to California?
I will continue to answer your phone
and keep you up to date.
That's all I ask for.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( "Scheherazade I. The Sea
and Sinbad's Ship" playing )
( man coughing )
( horn honking )
Dawn Chambers, please.
( phone rings )
- Dawn Chambers.
- I'm glad I caught you.
I need ribbon
for my typewriter.
It's a Coronet.
And I have letterhead, but I
could use a ream of onionskin.
- Okay. - And I wrote a letter
to Fritz over at Leica.
I'm going to need
an airmail envelope.
I can get these
sent over to you right now.
- Just bring them with you.
- Mr. Draper, I'm swamped.
I have to get a schedule out
for a shoot.
So you can come a little later.
What are you shooting?
- Mountain Dew.
- Oh.
What is it?
Um, it's called
"Invisible Boy."
It's this kid--
Ginsberg finally
got that through.
I guess so.
Anyway, Mr. Draper, I can get a
messenger to you in 20 minutes,
unless you're going out.
Obviously I didn't
make any plans.
I was expecting you
to come over.
Were there any calls?
-  ( phone ringing )
- Just Mr. Alan Silver
from the Paul Kohner Agency
in Los Angeles.
Can you get him on the line?
I'm sorry, my phone
is ringing off the hook.
I hope it's okay.
He says you have his number.
Or I can give it to you again.
No, Dawn, I want you
to call him.
I, uh--
can you hold?
Don Draper for Alan Silver.
Don.
Glad I caught you.
I was beginning
to give up hope.
How can I help you?
It's a bit of a casting issue.
I don't know if I
can help you with that.
Well, it has to do
with our girl.
And I'm probably overreacting,
but you're the closest thing
to a manager
and, let's face it, you
probably have more influence.
( laughs )
You better.
Just get to it, Alan.
Megan went into an audition
and performed adequately
from what I can tell
and by the time she got
to the parking lot
decided to call casting
and ask if she could come back
in and do it differently.
So she's persistent.
On Sunday she got
the director's number
from someone in her
acting class,
called his home,
then managed to run into him
at the Brentwood Country Mart
while he was having lunch
with Rod Serling.
She met Rod Serling?
I don't even know
if she knew he was there.
She apparently pled
her case in tears
and demanded another reading.
Why would she do that?
It's not like I've never
seen this before.
They lose their confidence.
But I don't want anyone
to have that anecdote.
It's best we nip this
in the bud.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
You know her better than I do.
I tried to talk to her,
but she hung up.
You have to tell her to relax.
She really is doing well
as the new girl in town.
- Yeah.
- Well, then,
I don't want to take up
any more of your precious time.
Yeah, thank you.
( typewriters clicking )
It's the Clios.
Who cares?
I do. But you shouldn't
give them the power
to decide who shall live
and who shall die.
Stan and I are part
of the agency
and Playtex is our client.
We'd feel the same if it
was the other way around.
Would you describe that
as patronizing?
I'm not taking anything
away from anybody.
But I'm not going to do better
work than St. Joseph's.
Lou's finishing his call.
You'll get 'em next year.
I gave that account
to you when I left.
I worked Playtex for years.
Well, maybe you
didn't work it right.
Lou:
Send in the cavalry.
Mr. Draper.
Good morning.
A weekday?
What a treat.
Nice to see you, Tricia.
No briefcase?
I'm going to surprise my wife.
I've said it before,
I hate her.
What can I get you?
Tomato juice.
Freeze-frame as our stallion
runs through the background.
The bottle appears.
Announcer--
"Chevalier Noir.
More horsepower."
Why is there artwork?
Well, I believe it really
helps if you see it.
You understand every hour
he works costs money?
You can't be hypothetical.
- It took a second, Lou.
- Stay out of it, Rizzo.
It's already done.
Would you just look at it?
Who put a knot
in your pantyhose?
She's upset because
I got nominated for a Clio
and "Rosemary's Baby" didn't.
I don't care about awards.
Oh, sorry, Peggy.
Jim pulled it because
St. Joseph's
was still unhappy
about going over budget
and all the awards
Ted's already won for them.
They're upset about winning?
You know clients hate awards.
That's why Ogilvy
never submits.
He does it for the clients.
Trust me.
Wasn't Ogilvy the chairman
of the Clios last year?
That's comforting--
you weren't rejected.
You weren't even considered.
- Are we finished?
- Sorry about that.
- You want to go to color?
- Ask your boss.
I'm usually by his side.
The real challenge in our life
has been trying to get
Rocky's attention.
Rocky.
I told you last time to tell
him that I'm an admirer.
( chuckles )
After Henry patched things up,
he'd hoped to be on
the short list for AG.
Attorney General.
But I shouldn't be
talking about this.
How are things in real estate?
I'm a travel agent, Betty.
But you're still going to take
that exam again, aren't you?
No, it's going swimmingly.
I'm in the office
three days a week now.
"Wanderlust Travel."
That's spicy.
Take a few.
I'm sure you'll need them.
Henry's secretary
takes care of all that.
But she still has to
book through somebody.
Trust me, it's not all about breaking
the rack rate on the hotel room.
It's about perfection.
One of my clients
told me that I redefined
his definition of first class.
Three days a week in an office.
What's that like?
It's a little shopping
center in Dobbs Ferry.
Just a storefront, really.
Bunch of desks.
Everybody's on the phone
all the time,
so you have to keep
one finger in your ear.
I have three phones
and no secretary.
Sometimes I can't turn
my neck when I get home.
Doesn't Carlton complain?
He likes the money.
He wants me to let the girl
go, and I probably should.
Ernie and Jenny
are walking to school now.
Well, Gene's a few years
away from that.
Oh, your time's occupied.
But for the rest of us,
as they get older,
there's less and less to do.
Being alone in the house
all that time.
I really needed a challenge.
Well, there's still plenty of
challenges ahead, believe me.
Fine, I needed a reward.
I thought they were the reward.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm old-fashioned.
Betty Draper, that is indeed
how I would describe you.
I want that streusel coffee cake.
Will you split?
Of course.
Well, hello.
How you doing, Tom?
- Randall.
- Good.
Our good friends at Koss here,
and frankly
I'll include myself,
have a few questions for you.
Love to explain anything.
I think it's the media
plan we agreed upon.
No.
It's about this article
from a few weeks back.
Yes, I've seen this, obviously.
I'm very happy
with our media plan,
but Grey has this computer that
they're opening up to everybody.
We just thought maybe
we should look into it.
Or you should.
Look, may I sit down?
This is a very enviable
piece of PR.
Grey gets "The New York Times"
to tell all about their computer
by offering their services
up to the world.
But I swear, as clever
as it is, it's just PR.
I'm an engineer.
You can explain to me
what the difference is
between their computer
and your computer.
Well, computers don't think.
People do.
And the data accumulated
by me and my department
reflects the same national
availability of media.
What we will be able
to offer soon
is local data as well.
We will be able to integrate local and
national markets into one report.
We are developing that program.
There you have it.
You'll forgive me,
but Grey's does sound
very impressive.
They're a different
kind of agency.
I wasn't even invited to this meeting
because this is about your business.
Koss, that's the only name
that should be in the paper.
Very well put.
Tom, does that put you at ease?
I'm really sorry
to put you through that.
Randy warned me, but,
you know, I got to ask.
( laughs )
I'll walk you out.
You said you wanted to poke your
head in and say hi to Peggy?
It's good to see you. Got to
get you out on that boat.
Thank you, Jim.
Harry, always a pleasure.
What are you smiling about?
Did you not call for a fireman?
Why the hell is Grey Advertising
coming up in my meeting?
Well, that article
could have been about us
if anyone appreciated
our media department.
Are you aware your
self-pity is distasteful?
You know what? This
conversation is over.
I'm really not interested.
( car approaches )
( car door shuts )
Hello.
You're here!
You surprised me!
Maybe I got your hints.
I've never, ever admitted
that I've wanted this.
What happened?
Did you get fired?
I just had a hankering.
Oh, really?
Well, an extra special
hankering you shall get.
( TV playing )
Hello.
Loretta, please.
They're not watching.
No, I believe they're not
interested in that.
Aren't you helping
Bobby with his homework?
Yes, ma'am. You got to sign this
slip for Bobby's field trip.
How was everyone today?
They're little angels.
They're looking for chaperones.
I can take Genie along.
Well, if you can remember to turn
this in, I want to go along.
You do?
You're gonna come?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Great. It's Miss
Keyser's dad's farm.
She grew up there and they
make butter and grow eggs.
Well, we'll see all that,
won't we?
I'm going to change.
I really needed that.
I really needed this.
So I could have been anyone.
It's your own fault.
I think I've been
alone too much.
You have so many friends,
I can't keep track.
I don't know.
( sighs )
It's sunny here
for everyone but me.
I'm walking around
in a cloud of "no."
Megan, you know,
they're getting rejected, too.
Maybe they're just
handling it better.
That's a terrible thing to say.
I'm speaking from experience.
You can't let it
erode your confidence.
And you can't get
angry or desperate.
I know that.
I know all that.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Alan called me.
What?
He called you?
I'm your husband.
He was worried.
Great, now I have to fire him.
What am I gonna do? How am
I gonna find someone new?
You don't have to fire anyone. You just
have to stop acting like a lunatic.
What did he say?
You know what? Forget it.
So you came out here to what?
Pull me out of a bathtub
where I slit my wrists?
I'll admit it, I was worried.
Well, thanks
for the visit, Daddy.
I was stupid for thinking
you could possibly miss me.
I do miss you.
No, you don't.
I should fly in
and surprise you.
Yeah, that's a scary
thought, isn't it?
- No.
- Really?
You're never there when I call
and you always
have to call me back.
And it's always quiet.
Where is it quiet
in that office?
And I've never even
heard a typewriter.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is true.
I'm sorry I had to
interrupt your love affairs
with the disaster of my career.
Megan, sit down.
I was your secretary, remember?
I know what you're like
when you're left alone.
- You're acting crazy.
- So where are you?
Why can't I reach you?
Who's your new girl, Don?
There is no one else.
I've been at home.
They put me on leave, okay?
You lost your job?
Don't worry,
I'm still getting paid.
I don't give a shit.
When did this happen?
Right after you left.
They fired you last year?
I didn't get fired.
That's the thing.
I don't know if they want
me or they don't want me.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I messed up
and I didn't want you
to know until I fixed it.
And there is no one else.
I've been good.
I haven't even been
drinking that much.
So with a clear head,
you got up every day
and decided
that you didn't
want to be with me?
Megan.
( sighs )
Mm, I'm not walking
out of my own house.
So that means
you have to leave.
Have you calmed down?
I'm not kidding around.
I want you to call a cab,
get on a plane, go home.
I don't want you to worry
about me anymore.
Stop it.
It's okay, Don.
This is the way it ends.
It's going to be so much
easier for both of us.
-  ( intercom buzzes )
-  I have Mr. Grady calling.
He's from
"The Wall Street Journal."
Really?
Put him through.
Harold Crane here.
We have a situation.
I know this isn't the message,
but we can all learn something
from the funeral business.
Did you tell "The Wall Street
Journal" to give me a call?
( sighs )
I felt badly about
diminishing your contributions
in this morning's meeting.
And let's face it, this computer
situation is an arms race.
There's no point in winning
if people don't know.
Well, we're not winning.
We don't have a computer.
What?
Believe me, I ask for one
every Christmas
and no one even bothers
to say no.
Well, why did you tell
the client we do?
It's semantics.
We use a computer, therefore
I call it our computer.
But it's actually
someone else's computer.
And the local markets program?
It's a great idea. I'm sure
someone's going to do that.
You have stiff competition,
but I believe you to be
the most dishonest man
I have ever worked with.
I didn't call
"The Wall Street Journal."
Kill it.
( phone ringing )
Woman:
Dave Wooster's office.
Is Dave in?
It's Clarence Birdseye calling.
Just a minute.
Let me see if he's available.
Dave:
Well, hello, Don.
Enough dancing around.
Let's have dinner.
How's tonight?
7:30.
The Algonquin.
( exhales )
Well, while we're digesting,
perhaps you should do
a little digesting.
You can look at it now or you
can put it in your pocket,
but you can't use it
as a coaster.
Why don't you just
tell me what's in it?
Why don't you look?
- That's coy.
- No, that's drama.
Woman:
Excuse me.
I'm sure you caught
my eye during dinner.
I was only staring because I
believe we know each other.
Emily Arnett?
I'm afraid I can't place you.
I'm sorry. I don't mean
to interrupt anything.
Would you like to join us?
No, I'm off to bed.
Hopefully I'll be able
to sleep.
I'm on the top floor
right next to the elevator.
Well, it's a pleasure
to meet you.
Have a good night.
Who was she?
Fellas, there's no need
for the hard sell.
We had nothing to do with that.
I wish I'd thought of it.
Should we get another drink or
do you have someplace to be?
( chuckles )
( knocks )
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Are you alone?
For the time being.
I came by because I had
a quick question.
- Shoot.
- How do you sleep at night?
You know what?
I called you at Christmas.
I'm sorry I opened the door.
I was expecting a BLT.
Why would I want to talk
to you when you fired me?
I got the message.
"Merry Christmas, love, Judas."
What is this?
That's a nice offer.
They're really trying to make it
sound like it's not a demotion.
So I take the job?
That's your advice?
If that's what you want to do.
Well, I know what you want me to do.
Go away.
I guess you don't remember
I started that company.
I had to talk you into it.
I guess you forgot I found you
at the bottom of a fur box.
I would never have
done that to you.
Oh, come on. Don't be
a big baby about it.
You were a disaster.
We did you a favor.
The man who talked to Hershey?
I've seen that man wandering the
streets with a sandwich board
saying
"The end is near."
- So I have my answer.
- I didn't know the question?
You want to come back?
Come back.
I miss you.
( knocking on door )
- Who is it?
Sherry: - Room service.
Oh.
I didn't know we had company.
Yeah, for once,
it's a friend of mine.
Sherry, this is Don.
I was just leaving.
Come in Monday.
( phone ringing )
Megan: - Hello.
- It's me.
Hello.
I wanted to hear your voice.
I don't have a lot to say.
Then you can just listen.
I...
I shouldn't have lied to you.
And I'm sorry.
And I want everything
to be okay.
( sighs )
Are you there?
Yes.
I can see now that I wasn't...
thinking clearly
and I had this logic
to what I did and...
Hopefully now
things can be the way
we want them to be
because I'm going back
to the agency.
Good for you.
I don't know if I can undo it,
but I think I fixed it.
"I fixed it"
is you got a job out here.
That's what you promised me.
That's why I'm here.
I just thought that if you
found out what happened...
you wouldn't look at me
in the same way.
I can't believe
after all this time
you don't know me.
I know how I want you
to see me.
Don't lie to me.
Don't do that.
You can't do that.
I'm your wife.
Stop pushing me away
with both hands.
I could come back out.
I have the weekend.
( sighs )
Not now.
It's not a good idea.
I love you.
Good night.
There's basically
Frankenstein, Dracula,
Wolf Man, the Mummy, and the
Creature from the Black Lagoon.
- That's quite a few.
- There's also King Kong, too,
but he's not really a monster.
I like all of them,
but I guess Wolf Man's
my favorite
because he changes into it.
Dracula changes into a bat.
That's true.
16, 18...
It's nice to see
somebody getting along.
We were having a conversation.
Thank you so much
for helping out.
( bus thumps )
Makes my job so much easier.
Bobby asked
and I couldn't say no.
My mom loves animals.
She really likes you.
Yes, well, that blouse
says she likes everyone.
It's Lou, right?
Oh, hello there.
Good to see you.
Sure.
How are you, Don?
Ready to get back to work.
Good for you.
Hello there.
Oh, Don.
Look at you.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
It's been too long.
Here I am.
Why don't you let me
take that up to him?
( laughs )
To Roger?
No, he's not in yet.
That's mine.
Do you want some?
When do you expect him?
I think we have a meeting.
I'm always the last to know.
It's fine.
I'll keep myself occupied.
Great to see you again.
Keep that.
- Is Jim Cutler in yet?
- I think he's at breakfast.
I don't care if he's in bed
with Joey Heatherton.
Get him on the horn.
Ginsberg:
Don?
Is that you?
Hello, Michael.
Ed, come here.
Look who's here.
Oh, hi, Don.
Great to see you.
Boy, you smell good.
Hey, you know what?
Are you busy?
- What do you mean?
- Don't bother him.
He'll know.
Come here.
Chevalier Blanc has
started Chevalier Noir.
That's "night,"
or "black."
Either way, it's the
opposite of Blanc.
And we're supposed
to work up print
based on this voiceover
tagline, "More horsepower."
And you gotta see the words, but
it ends with a freeze-frame.
What does?
The TV spot.
Oh. I assume
you have storyboards.
Exit stage left.
What have you been up to, Don?
Just R&R mostly.
Do you want to see
the strategy?
Sure.
What happened to the storyboards
from Chevalier Noir?
She gave them to Lou.
What do I do?
Don wants to see 'em.
- Don?
- Don-- Draper.
Says who?
Says him.
He's outside.
Right now?
What's he doing here?
You want I should ask him?
What's he doing?
Who cares?
What's going on?
Shh. Look.
What is he doing here?
Maybe he finished drying out.
Meredith, we better
get back to work.
Hello, Don.
Hello, Stan.
Where you been?
Riding the rails?
- Turns out Lou's got the boards.
- It's fine.
Mr. Draper.
Morning, Dawn.
Seems to be some lapse
in communication
- regarding my return.
- No one told me.
Could you just let me know
when someone tracks down Mr. Sterling?
- Can I get some coffee?
- Certainly.
Why don't you fellas
catch me up?
You want me to get everything?
Whatever you got handy.
Let's start with the garbage.
Children, this is my
father, Farmer Cy.
You can call me Cyrus
or Cy or "Hey, mister."
( laughs )
If you look around,
you can see pigs
and goats and chickens.
And Pammy's favorite,
the horsies.
We've got all the animals.
But this farm is mostly
for growing potatoes.
So there's not a lot
above ground.
But I know you're all
here to see the cows.
So why don't we walk this way?
I'm sorry, ladies, but there's
no smoking in the barn.
I'll be along.
You're not afraid of
missing them milk the cow?
I'll be done in a minute.
Well, I hope no one accidentally
grabs on the wrong udders.
Excuse me?
Farmer's daughter needs a bra.
( laughs )
( clicking )
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you need my lighter?
Would you mind?
Don?
Is that you?
Boys, excuse me a minute.
Don, what a pleasant surprise.
You're looking well, Joan.
What have you been up to?
What are you doing here?
- Waiting.
- For what?
You two just getting in?
We had a breakfast meeting.
What are you doing here?
I guess I'm waiting for Roger.
Oh, I see.
Well...
it was nice seeing you.
Guess what?
Cynthia had a little boy.
Edward, but we call him Eddie.
Eddie Cosgrove.
That's the carousel
in Central Park.
Always makes me think of you.
- Now I know what you'll look like bald.
- ( laughs )
( knocks )
May I have a word?
Don't linger in the door.
I'm wearing boots.
Yes, fine, dear.
Did you know that
Don Draper is downstairs?
Doing what?
He says he's waiting for Roger.
Does that ring a bell?
He shouldn't be here.
So obviously I would
like to get married,
but, you know, I don't
really have any savings.
I mean, it doesn't make any sense
to borrow money from my parents
just so I look successful
in front of hers, does it?
I don't know.
That is a tough spot.
What the hell
is going on in here?
We were just catching up.
That's nice, ladies.
You four, in my office.
- We have that meeting.
- What meeting?
Sorry, Don.
( cow moos )
Don't get no fresher than that.
Who wants to try it?
I will.
- Really?
- Sure.
See how warm it is?
It's sweet.
Don.
Where the hell were you?
- Had an early lunch.
- I can smell it.
I didn't know you
were gonna beat me here.
You could have told somebody.
Anybody.
I don't have to tell anybody. That's
my name on the door out there.
This is my agency. I'm the
president of this agency.
I don't have to ask
anybody anything.
You know what? I could call a holiday
for the whole office right now.
I've been sitting in here
waiting for you.
I'm not gonna slink out of here
with my tail between my legs.
- Now call a damn meeting.
- Let me ask Joan.
- Don't ask Joan.
- Wait here.
Chicken salad on rye
and a Nesbitt's?
Yes, thank you, Dawn.
( children laughing )
You eat. I'm going
to wash my hands.
Okay.
You can't sit there.
That's my mom's spot.
Jim:
Don?
Hello, Jim.
I'm surprised to see you.
Well, here I am.
Mr. Cutler.
There you are.
I can go down to the lobby
and sell newspapers,
but you're still gonna pay me.
- I have a two-year contract.
- Calm down.
I'll find out what's going on
and I'll take care of it.
What am I supposed to do? Just
hide while he sits down there
cooling his heels
like Longfellow Deeds?
We're going
to ask him to leave.
May I?
Be careful.
I've seen this before.
You might want
to call security.
Lot of bees over there.
They live in drawers.
- Where's my sandwich?
- What do you mean?
There were two.
I traded it.
- You traded it?
- With Susie Rogers.
She didn't have a sandwich.
I got her gumdrops.
Bobby, that was my lunch.
I'm sorry.
I'll go get it back.
Stop it.
It's fine.
- I'm sorry.
- Sit down.
I'm sorry. I swear I didn't
know you were going to eat.
There were two sandwiches.
- You want them?
- No.
You eat them.
I don't want them.
Eat your candy.
Your shoes.
What about her?
I just discovered
you're our best hope
to explain why
Don Draper is downstairs.
He came to me in remorse
and said he's ready
to come back.
Ah, I see.
Well, unfortunately,
we fired him.
No, we didn't.
We deliberately put him on
leave in this very room.
We didn't fire him.
I would never agree to that.
The leave of absence
was a very clear message.
We were allowing him
to preserve his dignity
while seeking other employment.
Ah.
Well, I remember clearly
that Cutler said
the leave of absence was
to give him time to think.
I didn't want any more rancor.
Is that what you thought?
That we fired him?
Not necessarily,
but I did expect
to revisit the topic
after some time as a group.
Well, here we are.
Let's take a vote.
- I'll speak for Ted.
- And I'll speak for Pete.
All I can say is that Don
is a very talented man,
but how does he fit
into everything now?
This is working.
Besides, we're still mopping
up the damage he's done.
I do not like the way
this agency
is spoken of out there.
You don't think that's because our
creative is invisible right now?
One nomination.
Lou didn't put in anything
he couldn't tag his name on.
He barely worked here
last year.
Lou is adequate.
I think it's more important
we discuss Harry Crane.
Harry Crane?
He's gone.
Anything else?
This agency is too dependent
on creative personalities.
You're still talking for Ted?
If we want people
speaking about this agency,
what they should be speaking
about is our media department.
We need to invest
in a computer, period.
We need to tell our clients we're
thinking about the future,
not creative hijinks.
Don is a genius.
He's costing us a fortune.
- You hate him.
- I don't.
I hate what he did to Ted.
Enough! This is a
financial decision.
Obviously, it's not.
Right now Don draws
a sizable salary
and has a partnership stake.
That costs more
than a computer.
- He has a contract.
- He's in breach.
No, he's not.
He's on leave.
And even if we do fire him,
he's a partner.
We have to buy him out.
That's true.
That's a big hit.
As tough as it is,
I'm confident
it'll be more profitable
in the long term.
Since when are you allowed to use the
words "long term" in this office?
It'll be 1973
before we're even.
We fire him,
we lose the noncompete.
You want to walk down
some hotel hallway
and see Mary Wells sitting on Don's lap
the next time you go in to present?
( TV playing )
How was the farm?
How was your day?
Did you eat?
I'm not hungry.
I was hungry, but now I'm not.
It was a long day.
I'm going to give Gene a bath.
Come on, Genie.
What happened?
I wish it was yesterday.
How was your day?
( chuckles )
That remains to be seen.
Are you coming back?
I thought so.
Now I'm not so sure.
Well, I can't say
that we miss you.
Thank you, Peggy.
( TV playing )
What happened?
I couldn't get it out of Bobby.
It was a perfect day
and he ruined it.
How is that possible, Betty?
Do you think I'm a good mother?
Of course.
Then why don't they love me?
What are you talking about?
Look at him.
It's just a matter of time.
Mr. Draper.
Yes. Dawn...
can I get some coffee?
Of course, but they want to see
you in the conference room--
the partners.
Oh.
Hello, everyone.
Come on, sit down.
- Bert, how are you?
- Capital.
Well, this is
the meeting I assumed
you were gonna have
before I came, Roger.
Sorry if I disrupted your day,
but I've had a productive time
catching myself up with everything.
Well, we've discussed it
and we've reached the conclusion
that we'd like you
to come back to work.
I'm pleased to hear that.
But there are
some stipulations.
Violation of which
will result in termination
and a reabsorption
of your partnership shares.
You are not allowed
to be alone with clients.
You are to stick
to the script in meetings
and that means the script
will be approved
by the people in this room.
Outside of client hospitality,
there will be no
drinking in the office.
You'll be in Lane's old office.
And you will report to Lou.
Okay.