( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( whirring )
Hello!
Hi, Mom.
- You want me to do that?
- In gloves?
The blender was broken
at the diner.
And you wouldn't dare
deprive them of dessert.
You look swanky.
Fundraising?
Much better.
We had dinner with the dean
of Fairfield University.
Some distant Rockefeller.
Actually, I'm planning
on enrolling in the fall.
Master's degree.
Really?
In what?
Psychology.
( whirring stops )
I know it's beyond
your experience,
but people love to talk to me.
They seek me out
to share their confidences.
It should be fascinating
for everyone involved.
Oh, hello, Don.
We're making chocolate shakes.
I should go.
Don't rush off.
You can finish your milk shake.
Make Henry one.
You give him a sip of yours.
Bye-bye.
Maybe I'll make my own.
Did you have fun?
( blender whirring )
( phone ringing )
- Hello?
- Oh, you're home.
I was expecting the service.
I just walked in.
Well, I wanted to let you
know that the movers
are gonna come on Wednesday
to pick up my furniture.
What time you want me
to be there?
Just tell the doorman.
We're coming at 10:00.
Does that give you enough time?
You know what time
I go to work.
There's one other thing.
It's the 24th already.
How could you be out of money?
Well, between the movers
and the flight--
Why am I explaining
myself to you?
I'm tired of asking
for an allowance.
Can we just sign the papers
and be done with this?
Your lawyer is very aggressive.
That's not how I heard it.
I'm starting to think
you're enjoying this.
Well, my finances are a mess
since the McCann deal.
You were a millionaire
when I met you.
Just tell your lawyer he won.
I'll sign whatever you want.
I can't live like this.
This is what they do, honey.
How much do you need right now?
I'll leave a check.
500.
Who's moving you,
the New York Jets?
I have to go.
( TV playing )
Roger:
I'm ready, Caroline.
- What's she doing here?
- It's too much.
- I can't do it by myself.
- Well, you should have asked me.
You're too busy.
Sit down, Shirley.
Well, this morning,
immediately following this,
you have a meeting
with Mr. Campbell and Mr. Torkelson
- regarding Lester Chapman.
- Who's he?
Secor Laxatives.
I'm sorry, but actually,
he's at Life Cereal.
This is working out already.
They want to set
a call for 4:00.
Hold on a second.
Isn't he NAC?
I'll check the Rolodex.
I'm sorry, what's NAC?
No afternoon calls.
Lester's blotto after lunch.
- He is indeed.
- Well, let's call him now.
So it's 798...
Well, this certainly
is a two-man job.
3...
So you just fly to Los Angeles
for the weekend?
Isn't that tiring?
What's tiring
is coming back here.
So beautiful.
You should go sometime.
I don't know if I'd like it.
How do you go to sleep at night
knowing that the Manson
brothers could be running around?
Good morning.
- The Manson family.
- Are they coming in?
No. A quick word?
Coffee.
So, I got a strange phone call.
Well, not strange,
but unexpected.
- Megan called me.
- Really?
I guess she's coming into town
and she wants to buy me a drink
to see if I can help her
find a new agent.
Can you?
Of course I can.
I do it all the time.
It's just, well,
I wanted to let you know.
Been down this road before
and you always find out.
Because you always tell me.
Yes, but she didn't want me to.
It's never stopped you before.
So should I meet with her?
She's not my wife
any more, Harry.
( intercom buzzes )
Meredith: You have a
call from a Nicholas
Constan...tin...opolis.
- Probably Greek.
- Oh, yes.
- I need to take this.
- I'm sure that's a story.
Nicholas, it's Don.
[ "It Takes Two" playing ]
Good evening.
Can I get you
something from the bar?
Are you expecting...
Hello.
How are you?
I'm surprised.
This isn't a coincidence.
I was looking for you.
What do you want?
I want to eat dinner with you.
Even if it's five minutes
at a time.
No.
You're making me uncomfortable.
This is my phone number.
Call me when you get off work.
I'll meet you somewhere.
I'll show you her work.
You will absolutely
recognize it. Ed!
All I'm saying is you dug
pretty deep to find a woman.
Do you know where
Samantha Ryan's portfolio is?
She calls herself Pima.
- Pima Ryan?
- Exactly.
She came and spoke at RISD
when I was there.
She's a very sexy lady.
I thought you were queer.
Where's Pima's portfolio?
I took it home.
Does she want it back?
Does she need it?
No, I need it.
Peggy forgot this
is my account, too.
We're really lucky.
She's never done an ad.
Stan, I'm sorry,
but you do not have any of the qualities
that either I or Cinzano are looking for
other than being cheaper.
You know, it's hard
to keep my balls at this job.
Ed, what do you know
about vermouth?
No.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Hello.
It's Diana.
You know, the waitress.
( chuckles )
I'm glad you called.
I didn't think you were gonna.
I don't know anybody
in New York.
So strange to see
somebody that I know.
Just pleased you're not cross.
I was pretty mad.
How did you find me?
Are you a private detective?
You kind of look like one.
Why don't we have a drink?
I've already got one.
Let's talk now.
I waited a little,
maybe too long,
and you were gone.
So I told Nick at the diner
to let me know
if you ever came back.
I went home.
Where's home?
Racine, Wisconsin.
I had to get a divorce.
( chuckles )
I'm divorced.
Well, I happen to be
in the same boat.
Right now I'm in the boat.
I must have known that.
Come over.
Where are you?
I'm at work.
I don't have a phone yet.
Fine, I'll come there.
Welcome.
Do you sleep like that?
I'm vain.
May I?
It's a very lovely apartment.
It's like
"Architectural Digest."
My...
She decorated it.
It's what I pictured.
So you were picturing it?
I took a cab to some
stranger's apartment
with $6 in my pocket.
I was hoping it was like this.
I'm gonna sell it.
I was just apartment hunting.
It's going to be hard to beat.
Can I fix you a drink?
I don't know how I feel
about getting to know you better.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
You know why you're here.
Do you want a drink or not?
I'm already drunk.
Would you like
a glass of water?
Hey, I can't sleep like this.
You were.
I don't want to.
Do you want to go?
No.
Are you really divorced?
Yes, I am.
Really. Why?
Got a lot of coats
in that closet.
She lives in California.
She didn't need them.
Do you want one?
I was going to go
to San Francisco.
I flipped a coin.
I always wanted to live here.
It was in all the movies,
all the magazines.
I haven't seen any of it.
It's a great city.
How long were you married?
12 years.
I don't know why
I thought it'd be easy.
It's never easy.
I've been through it before.
There's no children this time.
You?
No children.
( inhales )
You smell incredible.
What is that?
Shampoo.
Avon.
( sighs )
I bought it in my living room.
In my ranch house.
My two-car garage.
( alarm buzzing )
( buzzing stops )
Diana?
They're here
every other weekend.
Well, not my little girl. She's at
boarding school, but the boys come.
Are you okay?
No.
What's wrong?
I lied to you.
Already?
No, I left home because
I have a little girl.
I had a little girl.
Oh.
I'm so--
I'm so sorry.
Yes.
When?
Two years ago.
The flu.
Can you imagine?
I'm so sorry.
I don't want to talk about it.
Obviously,
I'm in New York City.
You should go.
It's my house.
Don't you have to
get ready for work?
I don't feel like it.
( chuckles )
Gentlemen, I'm going
to be strict,
but this is Torkelson's law.
Take a good look.
You got your models,
you got your bottles.
If you make it to lunch
without bothering anybody,
we'll let you have
whichever you want.
( laughing )
Ah, well, if you'll
all excuse me.
Come on, I'll introduce you.
Pima Ryan, this is our
art director Stan Rizzo.
So you'll be cutting up
my work, will you?
Well, I try
to treat it like art
even though it's just
selling something.
All art is selling something.
No, we're actually
selling something.
Today it's vermouth.
I apologize the models
have so many teeth.
I know you're not used to that.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm sorry about that.
He has a hard time
with... new people.
- No, he hates himself.
- ( laughs )
I don't think so.
He's got a huge ego.
And he's a photographer.
Ah, men like him
don't bother me.
And they shouldn't
bother you either.
Look at all you're doing here.
Just my job.
Good morning, girls.
Could you take your places?
- Good morning.
- It's 11:30.
Where were you?
I was worried.
- I was sleepy.
- Mr. Sterling's in there.
He's not to be disturbed.
Who are you hiding from?
Got two secretaries
and three telephones.
I feel like Marlin Perkins
is chasing me on the savannah.
- Hiding is pointless.
- I've got work to do.
That's the other
reason I'm here.
McCann represents Derby Foods.
Peter Pan Peanut Butter.
- They're making a cookie.
- Sounds delicious.
McCann also represents Nabisco.
National Biscuit Company.
They got the word cookie
in their name.
No, they don't.
Do we have a shot at Derby?
No, it's just a cookie.
McCann's clients are our clients.
We're helping out.
You and Peter are taking them
golfing tomorrow.
- I can't make it.
-  ( intercom buzzes )
Meredith: There's a messenger
here from your attorney's office.
He needs your signature.
So why can't you go golfing?
Since Burt Peterson's
the account man.
Good news or bad news?
Good news.
It's almost over.
Well, don't settle until
you get the number you want.
Take it from me,
no matter what she says,
you have given her
the good life.
She would never have had it.
Megan is not Jane.
So she never said you squandered
her youth and beauty?
Used up her childbearing years?
Thwarted her career?
What career?
- She's a consumer.
-  ( intercom buzzes )
Meredith: Mr. Sterling,
are you still at lunch?
They're wondering.
She made her choices.
( door opens, closes )
[ "Golddigger" playing ]
You're very good.
( sighs )
Can I help you?
Well, I've been told that my
negatives belong to the agency
and therefore processing
has to be done at your lab.
I'm not comfortable with that.
I hate to break it to you,
but it's not really
yours anymore.
Don't you have a darkroom here?
Yes, but I can't do that.
I started off as a clerk
with a newspaper in Sarasota.
All I wanted was to get
in that darkroom.
It's a nice thing to have,
especially in the city.
So, you're a photographer.
I do everything.
I'm an art director.
You must show me your work.
I don't know.
I can feel the tension
of your need for my opinion.
( scoffs )
I wouldn't mind
you taking a look
if you promise to be honest.
Let's see how brave you are.
Hello?
Mother?
Marie-France?
Bonjour.
_
-  ( knocks )
-  Bellman.
Oh, please come in.
Please, just put the bags here.
_
Thank you.
For you to enjoy
and for him to pay for.
I'm not changing rooms.
Well, she's made plans for us.
_
Absolutely not.
This isn't a vacation.
( sighs )
_
We'll have a contest.
We'll see if we can get
drunker than Maman.
( laughs )
_
- Doorman: Evening, Doctor.
- Arnold: Can you hold that?
Oh, hello, Don.
Hello, Arnold.
- Good evening.
- This is Diana.
- Arnold and Sylvia.
- Hello.
Brought the whole
restaurant home, did you?
( chuckles )
You're not on call, are you?
Mitchell's CO got married.
The girl, very young
but very homely.
( elevator bell dings )
Good night.
Don, we should play
squash sometime.
You know, if you have
the energy.
- Sylvia: Arnold!
- Sounds like fun.
( doors close )
How many girls have you
had in this elevator?
That's not what that was.
( elevator bell dings )
Elaine:
Hello?
( groans )
I said hello.
You didn't even grunt.
( grunts )
Are you in a creative mood
or a bad mood?
I don't know what I'm doing.
Everything good I have
is from a long time ago.
So what?
You think Picasso
looks at "Guernica"
and says, "Ignore that.
It was a long time ago"?
I got nothing to show her.
Who cares about her?
You should see what she does.
It's so sensual.
Get your camera.
Why?
I want you to take my picture.
No, you don't.
No touching the model.
In here?
I'm not going outside.
You must sit out there
all the time.
I want to see where you live.
How could I be
nervous at this point?
I know.
There's a twinge in my chest.
A pain?
No, it's not that.
I'm positive.
Are you hungry?
Not really.
( phone ringing )
Hello?
Oh, of course.
Yes.
Thank you, Meredith.
Everything okay?
I--
We have to get out of here.
She's coming to take her things
and I don't want to be here.
Oh.
- Okay.
- No, look.
What?
I think if I were you,
this would bother me.
And it shouldn't
because it's almost over.
Good.
I want to see you tonight.
At my place, okay?
Let's go.
( elevator bell dings )
Shit.
We'll swing by
your place on the way.
- I'll rent.
- You're going to rent pants?
I'll throw my tie over my
shoulder and roll up my sleeves.
- They'll love it.
- Probably will.
_
What's the difference now?
Stop it this minute.
I have to go change for lunch.
It's $200 including the tip.
_
- He gave me a check for $500.
- Like a whore?
_
In the States,
it's the 20th century.
People get divorced
all the time.
Exactly.
You can still get an annulment.
I'm not like you.
I don't spend my whole life
feeling ashamed.
_
Marie-France,
don't be a bitch.
I am not a servant here
to wait on her
while she goes for lunch.
I know you don't
understand this,
but it's for my career.
Good luck with
your bright future.
Wait.
_
No.
( sighs )
It's not much.
It's just the boxes,
Granny's cabinet,
that chair, and the mirror.
Go. Have fun.
I'll take care of this.
_
Hey, where's everybody going?
Oh, my mother's here.
Thank you so much.
Do you have to smoke in here?
It's taking my mind
off your driving.
[ "The Train" playing ]
I don't know why we couldn't
swing by your apartment.
What will the clients think
that you're renting clubs?
I'll buy a set in the shop.
Megan's moving
her things today.
( sighs )
I didn't know that
was still going on.
They want to punish you.
And then you get mad
and you want to punish them,
but you know it's your fault.
I've been through it before.
Well, how did you handle
client dinners?
I got a date.
I don't have a steady,
so it's too unpredictable.
You don't know how much
they're going to drink
and suddenly
you're with a floozy.
Golf is better.
Jiminy Christmas.
You think you're going to begin
your life over and do it right.
But what if you never get
past the beginning again?
Watch the road.
You filled the whole truck.
That wasn't what we agreed.
I told you
it was gonna be more.
More than double?
Fine, how much you got?
I have $350.
That's enough for me
to leave it on the sidewalk.
That's extortion!
Lady, you are a pain in my ass.
( phone rings )
Donald Draper's office.
I need to speak
with him immediately.
It's Marie Calvet.
Well, I'm sorry, he's not
available right now.
Interrupt him.
I can take a message.
May I say what this
is regarding?
No.
( intercom buzzes )
Caroline: There's a Marie
something on the line.
Marie who?
I got it.
Get off the line.
-  Bonjour.
- I am in desperate need of you.
Well, hello to you, too.
I need you to come
to Don's apartment
with $200 and not a penny more!
Calm down.
I'll send someone.
What did I expect? Every time you
get what you want, you run away.
Don't say that.
Bring cash!
-  ( knocks )
- It's fine.
[ "A Shallow Sparrow" playing ]
Look where you are.
( clears throat )
Don't.
I'm not ready.
Your subject certainly is.
That's Elaine.
She's...
Overdeveloped?
She's not worthy of you.
You can see it in her eyes.
She doesn't want
to tell you the truth.
Drawing is a much more
rare talent.
Oh.
I expected more.
Holy shit.
- What?
- Where is everything?
- On the truck.
- Pay him.
180 bucks.
My pleasure.
Don agreed to this?
He was very generous.
And you are a true gentleman.
Uh-huh.
Let's get out of here.
I'll buy you a drink.
I hate what he did
to my daughter.
Mon Dieu.
I'm trembling.
You really are.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
( chuckles )
You already emptied
the place out.
You want to defile it as well?
Please.
Take advantage of me.
- You look ravishing.
- Thank you.
I'm really sorry I'm late.
You know that office.
Should we get some wine?
I already did.
I am certainly
picking up the check.
I insist.
It's just you had such good
advice for Miranda and Jill.
Well, they didn't
have agents at all.
My advice was get one.
Well, whatever you did.
To whatever I did.
So, give me the lay.
You know, of the land.
There's not much to tell.
I haven't booked anything
in the last few months.
Not even pilot season?
Well, I turned down
some smaller parts
because Alan thought they'd take
me out of the running for leads.
I'm not in his business,
but I find it hard to believe
that you're losing any contest.
I bet he doesn't know
how to get you in one.
Well, I read
all the time, Harry.
Do you read for lead parts?
Because that's just getting
your name on the right list
with the right
casting director.
Good agents with
real track records
can make that happen.
Alan represents
Angie Dickinson.
You are every man's fantasy.
You're like Ali MacGraw
and Brigitte Bardot had a baby.
You should be the most famous
person in the world right now.
Oh, my goodness.
You should be in this business.
I can't believe
Don threw you away.
He's not a loyal person,
but I am.
You don't think
he could have helped you?
I'm willing to put my money
where my mouth is.
It would be much appreciated.
I'm gonna be honest.
I'm not hungry.
I'd rather get to work
on this immediately.
Well, we can work and eat.
I have a pen.
Well, I have a room upstairs.
It has a phone.
I could make some calls.
Oh, Harry.
I'm not interested.
Megan, you're a big girl.
Maybe you're in this situation because
of how you're reacting to this.
Hold on.
Forget all that.
Come on, have
another glass of wine.
Caroline, I was busy, okay?
Now how about at least
giving me a pat on the back
for remembering
I had a meeting?
Megan:
Hello?
What are you doing here, Megan?
Where the fuck is everything?
Roger...
( gasps )
_
He came to help me.
I should go.
Why are you here?
I told you to go to the hotel.
I felt guilty that I left
you here, but obviously...
_
I'm late for a meeting.
I guess you don't care that
she's married to my father.
It wasn't my idea.
You don't get to stand
in judgment of me.
( door opens, closes )
( door slams )
Could you give us
a second, honey?
No, thank you.
Have you spoken with Megan?
I just walked in.
Well, I think I should
warn you, we had lunch
and, uh, she's not stable, Don.
She said a lot of crazy things and
I'm sure will continue to say them.
And what will
she say about you?
Crazy things.
All I can say is
she really wants a job.
What does that mean?
Don, come on, nothing happened.
You know she hates me.
You know what?
It's none of my business.
Well, I don't think I could
have helped her anyway.
She quit her soap
and left New York.
That was a really dumb idea.
Pima?
Could you come in?
I have the selects.
Could you get the door?
I put the ones that I like
best on the top row here.
I like this one,
but Stan doesn't.
Stan already
showed these to you?
He was eager to share.
But he knows nothing
about women.
What does that mean?
It was just his opinion.
Well, mine's the only
opinion that matters here.
- It's my account.
- Of course, you're in charge.
I know that.
Which one do you like?
I think number three.
Top row.
You've never been married.
Nope.
Me either.
The adventures
I would have missed.
Number four.
I would love
to take your picture.
Well, I'm--
I don't know about that.
The way you're looking
at me right now...
I would capture that.
How are you?
Where is he?
He was right behind me.
I don't want anything of yours.
I wasn't going to say a word.
I wasn't going to give you
the satisfaction
of knowing that
you ruined my life.
Megan.
Why did I believe you?
Why did I believe
the things you said to me?
Why am I being punished
for being young?
I gave up everything for you
because I believed you.
And you're nothing but a liar.
An aging, sloppy, selfish liar.
You're right.
You're gonna write me a check?
I want you to have
the life you deserve.
( scoffs )
Are you kidding me?
No.
A million dollars?
Why are you doing this to me?
It's not funny.
I don't want to fight anymore.
Well, I know it's not real.
Nothing about you is.
It is real.
Please take it.
Megan, I'm sorry.
Send me the papers.
I want you to be honest.
Should I let my hair grow out?
Good night, everybody.
Ed, you were right.
Pima's a treasure.
Is she?
You don't like the work?
Because I was thinking,
you know, she'd be right
for Butler Shoes.
Or maybe Topaz Pantyhose.
She's got a thing for legs.
Women's legs.
Sorry to disappoint you.
I'm not disappointed.
Neither was she.
Really?
Does that bother you?
No.
But I bet it might
bother Ellen.
Elaine.
This is none of your business.
No.
It's Pima's business,
which turns out to be
more advertising than art.
She's a hustler.
You're jealous.
She tried
the same thing with me.
But she didn't get as far.
And that's why I'm not going
to give her another job.
I don't believe you.
Which part?
( door closes )
_
Not particularly.
So you ordered room service?
_
I don't care.
She's leaving Papa.
I'm going to pack.
_
I don't want to hear about it.
You know it's a sin
to be a ghoul
and feed on everyone's pain?
She's been very unhappy
for a very long time.
At least she did
something about it.
( sighs )
I'm exhausted.
Me, too.
Did you print anything?
They're drying.
You did?
How were they?
What did Pima say?
She loved them.
How about you?
( siren blaring )
Do you want a drink?
I just have vodka.
Yes, please.
Oh, I got you something.
Open it.
It's a New York City guidebook.
Finally start your tour.
Go on.
Can't you see
I don't want anything?
Look, I'm pretty sure
I had a worse day than you.
Please don't be in a mood.
I'm not in a mood.
And you've never had
a worse day than me.
You don't think
I've felt grief?
You knew that about me
the first night we met.
I've been trying
to talk myself out of it.
Don't.
No.
Talk myself out
of what I have to say.
You're scared.
I understand.
But I took care
of everything today.
I've been separated
a long time.
You're not the first
thing to come along.
I'm ready.
( scoffs )
You're fooling yourself
if you think this'll make a difference.
You don't think I know
what's going on here?
Look at this dump.
I know you think
you deserve this.
I've done it.
I left my daughter.
Stop blaming yourself.
No.
I had two children.
Two girls.
One died and one...
my oldest is in Racine
with her father.
Why? Don't you want
to ask why?
No.
I told you about my heart.
I don't want to feel
anything else.
When I was with you,
I forgot about...
her.
I don't ever want to do that.
[ "C'est Si Bon" playing ]
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com