Previously on Mad Men...
- I have a two-year contract.
- Calm down.
I'll find out what's going on
and I'll take care of it.
I forgive you.
And I forgive you.
Well, we're not winning.
We don't have a computer.
What?
There are some stipulations.
Outside of client hospitality,
there will be no drinking in the office.
You'll be in Lane's old office.
And you will report to Lou.
Our fortunes are
in other people's hands...
and we have to take them.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Well, now, we have
three options--
Catalina, which
includes a boat ride
one of us will enjoy,
Yosemite, which is
a very long drive,
or Palm Springs, which--
are you listening to me?
Don't look.
Turn around.
That man is staring at me.
Well, I'm relieved that you weren't
looking for a better conversation.
It's a little rude,
but I'm fine.
- What were you saying?
- Very well.
What are you doing?
George?
I didn't want to bother you.
You're obviously
here on business.
What?
No.
Trudy and I are divorced--
getting divorced.
I've relocated to our
West Coast office.
George Payton, this is Bonnie,
my real estate agent.
I wish you would stop
introducing me that way.
Why? It's good
for business.
Okay, what if I say,
"Bonnie, my girlfriend,
your real estate agent"?
- Nice to meet you.
- Charmed.
What brings you to LA?
There's no cough-and-cold season.
- George works for Vicks.
- Oh.
Actually, I left.
Please, sit.
I'm working
for Burger Chef now.
You can't be in
the hamburger business
without taking a swing
at Disneyland.
When did that happen?
Right after Tom's heart attack.
I thought of you.
- Tom who?
- Tom Vogel.
He had a heart attack?
Who's that?
My father-in-law.
I hadn't heard about that.
He's fine.
Who knew he had a heart?
Yes, right.
You know we're putting
McCann in review.
Be nice for us to work together
without old Tom in the way.
Hm.
It would kill him.
( chuckles )
Do you want to join us?
How about I give you a call
when I get back
to the home office?
Of course.
Have a wonderful evening.
I love watching you work.
That was skillful.
Those conversations
happen all the time.
Doesn't mean anything.
( elevator bell dings )
( slow tapping )
( faint voices overlapping )
Ahem--
any questions?
Where are we supposed to work?
You all have offices.
Lloyd, from LeaseTech,
has informed us
that the footprint of the
machine was prohibitive.
And then it occurred to us,
why not let every client
who sets foot in that door
know that this agency
has entered the future?
( applause )
And please, we will try
and keep the construction
and installation process
as brief as possible,
but steer clear of the
area for your own safety.
You might want to wear shoes.
Thank you all.
Dawn: If you have any personal
items in the creative lounge,
please remove them immediately.
Anything left behind at noon
today will be assumed garbage.
They're driving us underground.
You know Lou didn't
fight for our space.
He doesn't believe in creative because
he doesn't know how to do it.
Trust me, you're going
to use that computer
more than you use that lounge.
Did he hear me?
Why were you late?
You know that's a no-no.
I wasn't late.
I didn't get a memo.
I don't even know
what's going on.
Well, we're getting a computer.
It's going to do
lots of magical things,
like make Harry Crane
seem important.
This decision must have been
made at the partners' level.
It preceded you. You got a
problem, take it up with Cutler.
Think it's too early
to come in and celebrate our
technological advancement?
I think that's worse than
being late, isn't it?
You're right.
Good thinking.
Maybe later, off campus.
Harry Crane took a huge dump,
and we got flushed
down the toilet.
Ginsberg, don't you
believe in advertising?
That computer
is the "Mona Lisa."
People pay entry
to the whole Louvre
just to walk by that thing.
This is what was unique
about this place.
I want the couch.
That is not going to
fit in our office.
Why don't we switch it with
the one in Lane's office?
Because that one's really good.
You mean Don's office?
Don! Will you take
the other end of this?
Okay.
You gotta hold your
side a little lower.
I'm on the heavy side of
the seesaw right now.
A little to your right.
My right.
Damn it, Ginsberg.
Put it back.
It's too big for our office.
Come on, Stan.
I wanna try.
The other one's full of farts.
You're on your own.
Ginsberg: Let me put this in terms
the art department can understand--
they're trying to erase us!
( yells ) But they can't
erase this couch!
( sighs )
So, in addition
to the fruitful nature
of our previous
relationship at Vicks,
George is very excited about
our bicoastal presence.
Are we concerned about a conflict
with H Salt Fish & Chips?
Pete: - Ted?
- H Salt views themselves
as a specialty restaurant,
not fast food.
( chuckles )
That's a joke, right?
Pete, what did your friend
at Burger Chef say?
They're going to open
their thousandth store
and that's across 45 states.
George Payton knows
who his competition is
and he loves that we
understand the franchise game.
Well, Ted, you're the
king of fish and chips,
but I don't want you running
the team from out there.
We're calling you home.
Sorry, Jim,
I'm not going anywhere.
I think we should
put Peggy on it.
This is a national campaign.
It's almost three million
in billings.
The whole thing's
about the kitchen
and the cleanliness and
getting to the homemakers.
They'll want a woman.
Lou?
I think Peggy
is the right choice.
Well, I'm glad all agree the
client is going to love
having a woman's
point of view--
or whatever
Peggy counts as--
but is Don not even
on the list?
I was thinking the same thing.
He's spent three weeks
alone in that cave,
and he hasn't clubbed
another ape yet.
High praise indeed.
Lou?
Don's a very valuable
piece of talent.
He should be put
to work already.
Absolutely.
Roger:
Good work all around.
That's what I always say,
this business
is about relationships.
Bye-bye, boys.
Ted:
Dee, we're done.
Let's see them give that
to Bob Benson.
We done here?
I thought we had an
understanding about Don.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
He's an exquisite copywriter,
if nothing else.
He's gonna implode.
That's a distinct
possibility, isn't it?
On the other hand, you
might get some good work.
( squealing )
Hey, spud.
Get over here.
- What's going on?
- We're playing "hide-and-go-seek."
You hear that, Caroline?
Someone's hunting big game.
And someone's looking for you.
- Is Mommy here?
- No, Daddy and Nana.
They're in there.
Ellery and I are supposed to "go play."
See ya later, alligator.
( rattles )
Mona, Brooks.
What a pleasant surprise.
Mona: - Margaret's run away.
- To where? Bergdorf's?
It's not a joke.
She's upstate
with some sort of
religious cult.
- What?
- It's a commune.
Mona: - You don't know that.
- What the hell happened?
I can't get a straight story.
Because I don't know
why you need to know.
Apparently, she
woke up one morning
and got in a van with some
hippies that she barely knew.
She's only been gone
a few days.
10. Brooks and I
think it best
if you go up there
and retrieve her.
The only reason I even told you
is because I need someone
to watch my son,
and I thought it best
it be family.
If you don't want to do it, I've got
a long list of strangers I can pay.
You're upset.
You're not thinking right.
We can't help you if you
don't tell us what happened.
Look, she hasn't
been herself lately
and we went to this
marriage encounter group.
( chuckles )
You're kidding.
She wanted to, and I thought
it would be good for her
to talk to people.
That's always a mistake.
Roger!
Brooks, sweetheart,
I don't mind watching
my grandson,
but it sounds like
you tried to stop her
and you obviously failed.
- A father is a powerful thing.
- What are you doing?
Of course, she'll watch him.
Let the man be a man.
I appreciate that, sir.
I'm gonna go say goodbye.
I'm telling him that I'm
joining her on vacation.
Good idea.
-  ( door closes )
- What kind of a sales pitch was that?
- That was terrible.
- I agree with him.
She is off her rocker
and she has run away with,
from what I can glean,
more than one lover.
I only know one other person who
would do something like that.
How is this my fault?
Because she is a perverse child
who only thinks of herself.
Look, I know you're upset.
I am terribly worried.
It'll be fine.
( door closes )
( whirring )
Harry: Well, it was
a variety show,
and it featured this computer
that was programming
the variety acts.
And they had a lot of
psychedelic graphics.
It was obvious that
whoever did the sets
had never seen the
IBM 360, I can say.
Lloyd: Maybe I'll go buy a TV.
I can catch it.
You should get a TV, but it got
cancelled 11 minutes into the premiere.
Tim Conway plays a guy who's trying
to kill himself the whole show.
Probably to get out
of his contract.
Don Draper, this is
Lloyd Hawley.
- Lloyd's with LeaseTech.
- I saw you at the announcement.
And what do you do
around here, Don?
Oh. Don is,
uh, a partner
and our creative director.
I thought Lou was
the creative director.
- We have two.
- We have three.
I mean, there's Ted, too.
You must have a hell of
a business right now.
We'll see.
It's tough,
because we both sell IBM's
product and compete with them.
Who's winning? Who's
replacing more humans?
Listen, I apologize
about your work area.
It wasn't my idea.
Look, I'm sorry
you lost your lunchroom.
- It's not symbolic.
- No, it's quite literal.
I'll talk to you later, Lloyd.
Some of us have work to do.
This is why I supervise
the installations.
There's always
some kind of trouble.
Don't worry,
that goes back years.
Well, I go into
businesses every day,
and it's been my experience
these machines
can be a metaphor
for whatever's
on people's minds.
Because they're
afraid of computers?
Yes. This machine
is frightening to people,
but it's made by people.
And people aren't frightening?
It's not that.
It's more of
a cosmic disturbance.
This machine is intimidating
because it contains infinite
quantities of information,
and that's threatening,
because human existence
is finite.
But isn't it godlike
that we've mastered
the infinite?
The IBM 360 can count
more stars in a day
than we can in a lifetime.
But what man laid on his back
counting stars and
thought about a number?
He probably thought about
going to the moon.
Pleasure to meet you, Lloyd.
I should get back in there.
- You wanted to see me?
- Close the door.
( hammering fades )
( faint drill whirring )
It's quite a view, isn't it?
I like to think of myself
as a leader, Peggy,
and that means
doling out discipline.
But it also means tempering it
with encouragement.
Which should I be prepared for?
I didn't hire you,
but I would have,
and I would've paid you
as befits your senior status.
I'm giving you
$100 more a week.
I'm writing it
on this piece of paper
because I've found that
saying things around here...
is useless.
Well, I...
appreciate that.
Very much.
Well, with it comes a mission.
I'm putting you
in charge of Burger Chef.
Really?
Carve out hours for whomever
you want on the team.
And Don.
- Don Draper?
- He's the one.
Thank you so much, Lou.
Knock 'em dead.
Have you told Don?
You're in charge, sweetheart.
( tools whirring )
( hammers banging )
- Is he in?
- He never leaves.
Marsha, can you bring Don
and Mathis to my office?
Certainly.
-  ( knocking on door )
- Come in.
Please don't eat that.
You're so trim.
- Anything else?
- Miss Olson would like to see you.
- Send her in.
- No, I'm to send you in.
Okay.
- You wanted to see me?
- Can I offer you something?
It was a long walk, but no.
I have what I think
is very good news.
I hope you'll see it that way.
Hey, Don.
I don't know if you've
heard the rumors,
but Pete Campbell has gotten us a
presentation with Burger Chef.
All I know is it's
national fast food.
- They run a new spot every month.
- That's right.
But we have to win it first,
and that's why I wanted
you both on my team.
Congratulations.
Congratulations to you.
Mathis:
How long do we have?
I don't know yet, but I want
to get started right away.
I think 25 tags
should get the ball rolling.
- I'll get right on it.
- Apiece.
That's 50 total
between the two of you.
- What's the strategy?
- Lou likes to start with the tags
and then sneak up
on a strategy.
You'll get used to it.
Well, that'll do it.
- Thanks for thinking of me.
- I look forward to your work.
Monday.
( door closes )
( door slams )
( thumps )
( elevator bell dings )
- How was your weekend?
Don: - Lonely.
- How was yours?
- Wouldn't you like to know?
Oh, I'm sorry. You have a
meeting with Miss Olson,
and the Burger Chef
research came in.
- Is he in?
- Yes.
Good.
Oh, good.
Don't act like you
were looking for me.
I was looking for you.
I need coffee.
I didn't sleep last night.
Well, Mona called,
and I'm supposed
to read you this message.
"Hey, genius!
Brooks is in jail in Kingston."
From now on, you don't listen
to her, you listen to me.
And what I really like
is no matter what you order,
they give you
a side of spaghetti,
even if you order spaghetti.
What, Burger Chef does?
No, Vito's.
I can go get him.
Don:
Come in.
It's time for the meeting.
I can't make it.
Oh.
Do you want me
to turn in your tags?
Nope.
Okay.
He's not coming.
- What?
- That's what he said.
Is that right?
I guess he's not ready.
I mean, we did
just get the research.
I would really appreciate a chance
to beef these up, as it were.
I mean, if Don's
going to get more time.
Here's a better idea.
Why don't we move the meeting
to the end of the day,
and you give me what you've
got now plus 25 more?
That's going to be 50.
But now you have the research.
( bangs glove box )
- Hey.
- Nothing works.
You need to calm down.
I don't want this
turning into "The Guiding
Light" the moment we get there.
Ha. I'm worried,
but you're angry.
Don't lose your temper.
How much cash do you have?
Why don't you reach in
and check?
His bail is 180.
Let Brooks spend another day
in the slammer.
- He'll just get in the way.
- No, obviously.
I meant we should spring
him on the way back.
He's a bum. If he wasn't a bum,
she wouldn't have left him.
She told him she was
never leaving that place
and that he and Ellery
could stay there.
And what was he supposed to do?
He was supposed to get into
a fight with those hippies,
not some rednecks in a
bar three hours later.
It's my fault.
I always let her
out of everything.
She only had one job and
that was to find a husband,
- and she mucked it up.
- You liked him.
I thought he was good
enough for the time being.
( sighs )
I wanted her to wait
like I did.
You only waited
because I wasn't available.
Well, look how that worked out.
What was she supposed to think?
"Things are hard, I'll
just find another man."
That can't be it.
Oh, God, I hope she's
not a drug addict--
although they usually
stay in the city.
- How do you know that?
- "Life" magazine.
It's probably another man,
who probably has drugs.
You and me is not
such a bad example.
I mean, what psychiatrist is
Ellery going to be telling one day
about the weekend
his dad was in jail
and his mom was in a commune?
I'm sure you can recommend one.
You know, I haven't
seen her in a while,
because the last time I did,
she was so cruel and so serene.
She has been strange lately.
And a little bit philosophical?
Yes.
( chuckles )
I thought she was
finally happy.
( knocks on door )
Come in.
Sorry to bother you.
Do you have a light?
Mine crapped out on me.
The perils of technology.
It's 1969 and you're
unable to make fire.
Human error.
Forgot to fill it.
You're the only one here.
It's lunchtime.
- I'm not hungry.
- Probably have too much to do.
I'm not doing anything.
Look, I don't want
to put you out,
but if you have
a second--
I have an advertising question.
Go ahead.
Advertising--
does it work?
On some people.
It helps to have
a good product.
I'll tell you how great it is.
I started LeaseTech
with two old friends,
and six months later,
we have 19 new employees
and three new competitors.
Well, the first question
is how is what
you're selling unique?
IBM's leases
are short and expensive
because they're always
replacing the equipment
with the newest model.
Ours are cheaper
because we don't do that.
Don't yours become obsolete?
They all become
obsolete eventually.
The question is,
how long does that take?
IBM doesn't care because
they just sell new machines.
At this point, I usually ask,
"How did you get
into this business?"
Well, I was at IBM
for a few years.
- I knew it.
- Yes.
And I saw that they
have got a great product,
but they don't trust it.
I've worked
with these machines.
I know how resilient they are.
I don't want to find them
in a junkyard in two years.
So you're betting that
they'll last longer
- than even IBM thinks?
- Yeah.
But the problem is, so are a
bunch of other companies.
But they don't have you,
and they don't advertise.
Very nice.
What's IBM like?
Oh, there you are. I thought
we were going to lunch.
Thanks for the light.
Pleasure to talk to you.
You were going to give me the
name of a good keypunch service.
( door closes )
- When's Roger back from lunch?
- He's gone for the day.
- ( knocks )
- You got a second, Bert?
Of course.
LeaseTech--
the company that we're leasing
the computer from-- is a virgin.
And I think we should
prepare a presentation
while their guy is hanging around.
Push him over the edge.
New business?
That whole industry
is exploding.
This guy has
exponential growth.
Have you forgotten
the stipulations?
Fine, tell somebody else.
I mean, the apple
is right there.
You have a fundamental
misunderstanding
of what went wrong here.
So, that's it? You want
me to be a janitor?
Whistle while I work?
You thought
there was going to be
a big creative crisis and
we'd pull you off the bench,
but in fact, we've
been doing just fine.
So, why am I even here?
I could've gone anywhere.
- Why are you here?
- Because I started this agency!
Along with a dead man--
whose office you now inhabit.
I left something in there.
When?
Thank you, Caroline.
I got it.
( trickling )
What are you doing?
Are you looking
to buy some jelly?
The stand's up the road.
No, we're looking
for Margaret Sterling.
Hargrove.
Margaret Hargrove.
I know who
you're talking about.
Marigold?
She doesn't want any trouble,
and we don't want any trouble.
Nor do we.
These two are looking for you.
You know 'em?
Of course I do.
This is my mother and father.
- Mother, you look wonderful.
- Stop it.
I know why you're here,
and I just want to welcome you.
Margaret, darling,
we just--
Could you call off your dogs?
I'd like to have
a private conversation.
Hey, everybody, I understand
the dry cleaning's ready,
but can you bring it
back in an hour?
There's 50 bucks in it for you.
I'm fine, everyone.
These are my parents.
Will you let me show
you around at least,
before you start railing against
something you don't understand?
I don't know what happened
between you and Brooks,
but your son misses you.
Things have never been better
between me and Brooks.
Ever.
And...
I miss Ellery so much.
I think about him all the time,
but he can't be happy
if I'm not happy.
I didn't know how dire it was,
but if you need money, whatever
you want, whatever you need.
She doesn't want money.
Margaret, listen.
Sugarplum, these people
are lost and on drugs,
and they have
venereal diseases.
That's not for you.
You don't know them.
And I'm tired of accepting
society's definition of me.
I don't pray to that anymore.
Darling, I understand.
Being a young mother
can be overwhelming,
even with help.
You sit with your child
at the end of the day
and you're exhausted
and you don't even know
what you did.
And everything you do
seems wrong.
It's hard to accept that
those are the definitions,
but they are.
I'm sorry you had
nothing to live for.
I did. I had you,
and I was grateful.
I'm grateful.
I don't have to lock
myself in a bathroom
with a pint of gin every day.
I ought to slap you.
Why are you talking
to your mother like that?
Daddy, I'm-- I'm sorry.
I'm telling her the truth,
and she doesn't
want to hear it.
Let's go!
You didn't even
let me talk to her.
There's no more point
in talking.
I'd think she was brainwashed,
but there's nothing to wash.
You can't make her turn on a dime.
You'll embarrass her.
Fine. You want to wine and
dine the account, Roger?
Knock yourself out.
There's a four-year-old
in Manhattan
crying himself to sleep.
I'll get "Cletus"
to drive me to the train.
( door slams, engine starts )
Marigold!
You want to show me around?
( sighs )
( hammering )
( saw whirring )
Hey, it's Don.
Look at that, I got you.
I didn't know where you'd be.
You're here, there, everywhere.
No, I'm not in the bag.
I'm in the office.
Listen, let's go to Shea.
Let's go see a game, I mean it.
Is there a game today?
You shouldn't have
told me that,
because now we're really going.
Okay. Your wish is my command.
I will not move.
Can I hang up the phone?
( chuckles )
( groans )
When you're done with that,
one of us should
find some firewood.
When he's done with that,
he's not going to be able
to find his ass
with both hands.
I'll tell you what, Clay,
why don't we switch jobs?
You want to get firewood,
help yourself.
There's no hierarchy, man.
Believe me, there's
always a hierarchy.
We do things
by true consensus here.
If we can't all agree
on something,
we think of something else.
Everyone does what they want.
Good.
Because I haven't felt
this at one with nature
since I was in the Navy.
Go ahead, it's dynamite grass.
Now, I see why
we're eating so early.
No, it's because
we follow the cycles
of the Earth.
It's gonna get dark.
Electricity and all that?
It just brings problems.
But you've got a truck.
Yeah.
That's been up for debate, man.
Doesn't it get cold up here?
Margaret:
We light a campfire.
And there's other ways
to keep warm.
It's all right, sweetheart.
He's expecting me.
Freddy, what
a pleasant surprise.
- You know you called me.
- I sure do.
- There's someone I want you to meet.
- Who?
I want you to...
♪ meet the Mets ♪
Meet the Mets!
♪ Step right up and greet the Mets. ♪
Great idea.
Can you walk?
Hello again.
Meredith, we're off
for the day.
- Way off.
- Okay. You two have fun.
( saw buzzing )
Where are you going?
( hammer rapping )
Don, I didn't hear you.
No, I didn't hear you.
Come on, Don, we're
gonna miss the game.
You talk like a friend,
but you're not.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
I know your name.
It's Lloyd.
I told you.
No, you go by many names.
I know who you are.
Don, let's go.
Why don't you listen
to your friend?
You don't need a campaign.
You've had the best campaign
since the dawn of time.
Pull yourself together.
Freddy?
We're knocking off early.
- Okay.
- Ball game.
I just wanted to make sure you
saw the memo from the partners.
Your raise was approved.
Congratulations.
What?
Oh, yes-- thank you.
This office is so great.
Everyone can just drop by
on their way out.
Don't worry,
it won't happen again.
Joan!
I'm sorry.
I'm just having a day.
I have exactly two minutes.
It won't take that long.
You already know the problem.
Burger Chef's a big account,
but they obviously thought
you were ready for it.
They didn't want to give me
Burger Chef.
They wanted to give me Don.
What are you talking about?
You didn't hear?
Lou put Don on my team.
To cowardice.
Mine or theirs?
He owes me work, and he's
going to the ball game?
And there's nothing I can
do, and he knows that.
Have you told Lou?
You don't know this,
but there were rules
set for Don.
- Is he breaking them?
- I don't know.
( sighs )
So, they just
dropped it in my lap,
hoping one of us would fail.
Well, Peggy, I don't know if
this makes you feel better,
but I don't think they
thought about it at all.
Roger: I can't believe my
little "princess and the pea"
is sleeping like this.
You never even wanted
to go camping.
Margaret:
Well...
I used to think
the country was lonely.
Now I realize the city is.
I mean, look at that.
It's beautiful.
You think we'll put
a man up there?
With all the brainpower
around here?
I'm certain you'll put
a man on the roof.
I'd like to go to the moon.
Well, I guess if you can make
an allowance for a truck,
you can make an allowance
for a rocket.
Don't you want to go?
Of course.
Every little boy
wants to be an astronaut.
Astronauts didn't exist
when you were a little boy.
Jules Verne--
"From the Earth
to the Moon."
You read that to me.
They shot a cannon into space.
I don't think so.
Must've been your mother.
I'm really happy here, Daddy.
I know.
Oop, oop...
Get my binoculars.
They're in the hallway closet.
Good idea.
We're going to miss
the national anthem.
( door closes )
( Margaret giggling )
Stop it, not here.
( sighs )
( car horn honks )
Come on.
It's as black and strong
as Jack Johnson.
Thank you.
How'd you get in?
I'm glad you passed out.
I got a lot less to explain.
Did the Mets win?
What the hell are you doing?
Aren't they giving you
a second chance?
They weren't serious about it.
They finally gave me
something to do,
and it was write
25 tags for Peggy.
- What's the account?
- Burger Chef.
Hm-- Peggy.
Have you been
to the restaurant yet?
What, and have some pimply kid
who should be writing taglines
hand me a milk shake?
How would you rather have it?
Would you rather be
in my situation--
bouncing from office to office?
"Ding-dong,
Don Draper calling."
I want my job back.
How the hell do you think
that's going to happen
when you're at
the bottom of a bottle?
You know you never have to
have another drink again.
I don't want to hear
that right now.
You're hungover. It's the
best time to hear it.
I mean, are you
just going to kill yourself?
Give them what they want?
Or go in your bedroom,
get in uniform,
fix your bayonet,
and hit the parade?
Do the work, Don.
( birds chirping )
You're up early.
Where's my daughter?
She's probably at the
creek getting water.
I don't think so.
It's a beautiful night
and a beautiful morning.
Did you see the sunrise?
It's a beautiful
morning, isn't it?
It's time to leave
Shangri-La, baby.
Take a good look, say
goodbye to your friends.
You were doing so well, Daddy.
Fine, you don't want to say goodbye?
Let's go.
Hey, man, leave her be.
Come on, Sprout, feel like
driving the truck today?
No one's going to help you
take me away from here.
They know this is
where I want to be.
I don't care what you want, and
I don't care what they want.
It's over.
Let's go.
I don't know why I assumed
you were more open-minded.
Well, I'm not. I
understand the temptation,
and I know everyone your
age is running away
and screwing around, but you can't.
You're a mother.
- Ellery has everything he needs.
- He needs his mother.
I'm sorry, but you
don't get to do this!
Goodbye, Daddy.
Let me go!
Let me go right now!
( grunts )
How could you just leave him?
He's your baby.
How did you feel
when you went away
to work, Daddy?
Your conscience must
have been eating you alive.
Calling your secretary
from a hotel
to pick out a birthday
present for me?
I'm sure you were sick.
It's not that hard, Daddy.
He'll be fine.
( elevator bell dings )
You sure you don't
want a Danish?
Nope.
- Coffee?
- Yes, please.
Good morning.
I'll have your tags by lunch.
Great.
( "On A Carousel" playing )
♪ riding along on a carousel ♪
♪ trying to catch up to you ♪
♪ will I catch up
to you? ♪
♪ horses chasing
'cause they're racing ♪
♪ so near, yet so far ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ on a carousel ♪
♪ nearer and nearer
by changing horses ♪
♪ still so far away ♪
♪ people fighting
for their places ♪
♪ just get in my way ♪