Previously on Mad Men...
This agency has
entered the future!
( applause )
I know what you're like
when you're left alone!
You're acting crazy!
As usual, you have
acted impulsively!
Most of your questionable
behaviour is beyond explanation.
You are not allowed to be
alone with clients.
You are to stick
to the script in meetings.
And you will report to Lou.
I thought we had an
understanding about Don.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
_
Good morning.
( elevator bell rings )
Plans for the weekend?
- California?
- Next weekend.
I want you to know
I haven't forgotten
your request
regarding Handi-Wrap.
I spoke to Lou and he's very happy
to have you on the business.
( doors open )
And, of course, you can
assume from our conversation
- that I am, too.
- Thank you.
I hope you understand
I mean on the team.
That's exactly
what I asked for.
( elevator bell rings )
Stop humming!
You're not happy!
Do you want me
to introduce you?
I'm not interested in her.
She belongs to it
and it belongs to her.
- What is "it"?
- What, am I Cassandra?
That machine came for us.
And one by one...
- Meredith: Good morning.
- Marsha: Morning.
Morning, lovely.
What's wrong?
Do you know anything
about this?
Where did you get this?
I found it on
the Xerox machine.
And I thought,
"Wow, Shirley's gonna be
in a lot of trouble
for leaving it there."
- It's sensational stuff.
- I didn't leave it there.
But I appreciate its return.
It's got to be pretty recent.
He's got one about
Eisenhower's funeral.
I'm sure he'd prefer
you hadn't seen this.
Hmm, that's not
what Dr. Freud would say.
No one has seen this.
( laughs )
All:
"Scout's Honor."
( laughing )
Mr. Ginsberg?
This thing's on the fritz.
( laughing )
S-T-R-A-T-E-G-Y.
Meredith, honey, I don't
want that spelled out,
I just want it spelled right.
-  ( intercom buzzes )
- Meredith: Mr. Draper.
I was just talking to you.
There's a Stephanie Horton
calling collect.
Would you like
to accept the charges?
She says she's your niece.
Yes.
Yes, absolutely.
Hello, Stephanie.
It's Don.
I wasn't sure
if you'd remember me.
Come on.
How are you?
How are you... Don?
About the same.
Is everything okay?
Well...
I suppose it probably sounds
like an emergency,
but it's not. I thought
of you because, well--
it's not an emergency.
You're making it sound
like an emergency, sweetheart.
I'm pregnant.
I'm expecting.
And I'm running out
of bread and...
I hate that this is why I'm talking
to you after all this time.
I'm glad you called me.
That's what I'm here for.
I mean, you're my...
( chuckles )
what'd you call yourself?
My niece.
I don't know why I said that.
No, that's what you are.
I like that.
Are you still in Berkeley?
I'm in LA.
That's where I ended up.
It's gonna be fine.
Do you have a pen?
How far along are you?
I think around seven months.
But my mom says I came early.
My wife, her name is Megan
Draper, lives in LA.
Can you get to Laurel Canyon?
I've got a car.
You got married again?
Yes.
She's gonna take care of you.
I want you to stay there.
I'm coming out tonight.
I don't know.
I want to see you.
It's not up for debate.
Thank you, Dick.
( phone ringing )
You may find the time
by dialing
Meridian 7-1-2-1-2.
I'm sorry, can I speak
to Megan, please?
-  Hello.
- Listen, I'm coming out tonight.
Oh, okay.
Is everything okay?
Not really. You're gonna get a
visit from Stephanie Horton.
She's Anna Draper's niece.
She's expecting and she's alone
and she needs money
and I should see her.
Poor thing.
I'll cancel my party
and you can catch up.
What party?
You said you weren't
coming this weekend,
so I'm having the party
for my acting class.
- Tonight?
- Tomorrow night.
But I don't need to have it.
Or you can come.
Stephanie can come.
Don't worry about it.
We'll stay out of your way.
You don't have to pick me up.
I'll be in by 10:00.
I'm so sorry, Don.
We'll make her feel at home.
Who's there with you?
Amy from Delaware.
Could you get rid of her?
I'd rather keep this
a family matter.
Okay.
I'm sorry this is the reason,
but I'm glad I get to see you.
Me, too. Bye.
Oop.
Burger Chef's mascot
Little Chef is a flop
because he's, what,
another chef?
He doesn't eat the
burgers, he cooks them.
But what if you replaced
him with a fresh recruit?
A saucy little retard
named Scout.
He can't work
at a hamburger stand.
He can take anything
but an order.
( laughing )
Hey, Don.
Stan, once the smoke clears,
I need you to rush some
things out for Handi-Wrap.
- I need it by 4:00.
- Mmm.
I'm really, truly busy.
( laughing ) _
What the hell is that?
Turns out Lou thinks
he's Mort Drucker.
- Mort Walker.
- How'd you get this?
It wasn't our fault. Why is
Scout always up to no good?
He peeled a bag of grapefruits.
- Thought they were potatoes.
- ( laughing )
I'm gonna get rid of this.
He left it on the Xerox. He
obviously wanted us to have a copy.
You're just gonna
force me to draw my own.
I've got a plane to catch.
Get to work.
Don's still part
of the faculty.
Naw, he's gonna
stroke to 'em later.
Why don't you let
Loretta do that?
She can handle the homework.
I'll handle the silver.
What'd you land on?
Rumaki, Crab Louie
on toast points,
and little franks
in barbecue sauce.
You know they've got four more
houses to visit after us?
I wanted to go first
to put everyone at ease.
They get so
tongue-tied around us.
They can only pretend so long
we're just "regular neighbors."
Could you stock the bar?
( doorbell rings )
Hi. Did you have
any trouble finding us?
No.
I'm Megan, by the way.
I'm Stephanie.
You are so beautiful.
I know, I'm a Madonna.
But you are truly magnetic.
What do you do?
Don didn't tell you?
I'm an actress.
Uh, welcome.
I'm grateful.
For some reason,
I'm not crying, man.
Well, why don't I fix
you something to eat
and then you can take
a shower if you want?
- Is it that bad?
- No!
I don't know.
I think you'd want to relax.
Don didn't say much about your
situation other than the obvious.
Your place is out of sight.
I'm at a flop
in MacArthur Park,
but I'm headed up to Oakland
with a little help.
I have some friends there and one
of them's old man's a doctor.
So, assume
it's no trouble at all.
What's your pleasure?
Grilled cheese? Spaghetti?
Do you have any meat?
I've been dreaming about it.
( laughs )
Sure.
Now you go into the bedroom
back there.
I changed the sheets.
There are towels.
You can lie down, run a bath,
whatever you want.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you.
I'm pretty beat.
You know I want her.
You can't have her.
Why can't I have her?
Because Scout's on 'er.
( toilet flushes )
Nice of you to join us.
Don, why don't you take the
mound, throw out the first pitch?
Sure.
Stan has some
very preliminary work.
Stan?
Should I move over there or do
you want to come over here?
I don't know, Stan. Can you
be smug from over there?
Lou, I don't know
what you think you heard.
I heard everything!
From your first fart
to your last dying breath.
- ( chuckles )
- You think it's funny?
I apologize deeply.
What happened?
Let me ask you, Peggy.
- You ever heard of Underdog?
- The cartoon?
Yeah.
Sweet Polly Purebred.
Saturday morning.
It makes hundreds of thousands
of dollars a year.
Mostly for its creator Chet
Stover of Dancer Fitzgerald.
- Did you know him there?
- He was nothing special.
"Scout's Honor"
is 100 times better.
I can tell you right now,
it's a winner.
You know who had a ridiculous
dream and people laughed at him?
- You?
- ( laughs )
What?
Oh, I did not mean that
the way it sounded.
I mean, if you're telling us
that this is your dream,
I apologize for being one
of those naysaying idiots.
I hate people like that.
Bob Dylan.
Is he hip enough for you?
He was 20 years old when he
wrote "Blowin' in the Wind"
and he's a genius.
Look at where he is,
look at where you are.
( stifled laugh )
You know what?
You're a bunch of
flag-burning snots.
You've got a thing to learn
about patriotism and loyalty.
The very fabric of "Scout's
Honor" is a joke to you.
We're gonna have
this meeting later.
So order dinner because
I want finished work.
And if any of you
don't like it,
you can thank your
hilarious friends here.
Last flight's at 9:00.
Put me on that.
- I'll cancel my plans.
- Just mine, not yours.
I don't know if it's vandals
or just kids being kids.
What is it?
Someone broke all the
streetlights on Peck Avenue.
And you want Henry
to get them fixed?
No. Mike was just saying
it's a national disease.
The wildness of the kids.
I just don't expect it
in Westchester.
I know all everyone wants
to talk about is Vietnam,
but things are
falling apart here, too.
The rumaki is exquisite.
Thank you.
Well, I don't know, that
those things are unrelated.
I mean, first the kids
start off protesting
and the next thing you know every
authority is up for grabs.
I mean, if they learned
how to support their country,
sacrifice in hard times, we'd
have the morale to win the war.
Mike, you have plans
for the summer?
Even Nixon wants to bring
the war to an end.
I'm surprised, Henry.
Don't be, Mike.
I agree with Nixon.
I think it's too costly.
It has to be done
on the right terms,
but I think we should get out
while the getting's good.
Since when?
I've always supported
the president, honey.
I think that maybe everyone
should fill up here.
I don't know
if my lamb turned out.
I'm sure it's delicious.
Let me check the Sterno.
( knocks )
Well, I think I worked
every side of the strategy.
Don, you've been the boss.
The briefcase and the hat,
that's a rookie maneuver.
You got someplace to be?
I'm afraid I do.
How's it going to look
for them if I let you go?
Well, you could let
everybody go.
Is that what you would do?
No, I'd let you go, Lou.
Well, I'm afraid
it's too late for that.
I'm gonna do you the
courtesy of reading these
so that you can continue to work on them
instead of coming up with new things,
because I'm gonna
tuck you in tonight.
About your cartoon.
Here we go.
This is an office made out of people
who have problems with authority.
You know you have to have a thick
skin, but don't help them.
I'm not taking management
advice from Don Draper.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
I can't get out
of here tonight.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Is she there yet?
- She's taking a bath.
How is she?
She's pretty far along.
So beautiful.
Well, don't bother her. Tell her
I'll see her in the morning.
Don't worry.
I made her a steak.
Thank you.
Okay, I'll see you
tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Damn, that smells good.
Don's stuck in New York. He's
flying in tomorrow morning.
Was that him?
Yeah, he's frustrated.
I told him not to worry.
Wait, do you want
to eat outside?
I do that all the time.
I love that you're
wearing Anna's ring.
Oh, yes.
It's beautiful.
I'm sorry I never met her.
She's around.
Believe me, you've met her.
She's happy it's in the family.
Well, maybe you'll have
someone there to give it to.
Oh, no.
It's yours now
You'll probably have
someone of your own.
We'll see.
I don't know.
Don's kids are plenty for me.
( sighs )
I haven't eaten meat in a year.
I don't think
this is a good idea.
I can make spaghetti.
It's probably hard
with you here and him there.
Are you with someone?
Not right now.
He was a musician.
They're the worst.
Dropped out of school.
Followed him down here.
Started flush at the beach,
ended up downtown panhandling.
And then he got busted
dealing grass
and we celebrated
before he went away.
He'll be out in a month.
So will this little guy.
Does he know?
No.
I'm afraid he'd murder
someone just to stay in jail.
- I won't tell Don.
- Oh, I don't care.
I know all of his secrets.
But you don't
know him very well.
You're right.
It's just I'm looking at you
and seeing how, well,
disorganized this all is.
And I don't think
he'd stand for that.
I don't think he'd trust you
to make your own plans.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
This is a dumb idea.
No, no, I mean,
he wants to help,
I'm sure, in his way.
We both do.
I'm going to give you...
would $1,000
get you far enough?
That's very generous.
This comes with no strings.
Thank you.
I really think
it's better this way.
You're right.
I'm gonna take off.
You haven't eaten anything yet.
I guess I got what I came for.
There's no rush.
Nothing ever happened
between us, you know.
Of course not.
You're his niece.
I know that.
( door slams )
The children are asleep.
- What about your headache?
- Keep your voice down.
I did not appreciate going stag
to four people's homes
whom I barely know.
I'm sorry. I wasn't feeling well.
You didn't have to go.
Hey, "Emily Post."
Why were you
talking about the war?
I didn't bring it up.
But maybe I should more because
I didn't know where you stood.
I shouldn't have to brief you
because you shouldn't be
talking about those things.
I'm not a dinner companion.
I'm their elected
representative.
- You ran unopposed.
- We'll see if that lasts.
From now on, keep your
conversation to how much you hate
getting toast crumbs in the butter
and leave the thinking to me.
Henry!
I'm sorry. It just
caught me off-guard.
Well, you embarrassed
yourself way more than me.
( door slams )
You know what?
I decided I can
see that Monday.
Good night.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
What?
Is she okay?
( water running )
Hello?
Oh, hi.
- Who are you?
- I'm Amy.
- We met on the phone.
- Is Megan here?
Oh, Don.
I...
Amy, do you mind?
I'll just use the ladies'.
I'm sorry, but she left.
You told her
I wanted to see her?
I really tried
to get her to stay.
But the money already came up
and I gave her $1,000.
She must have been embarrassed.
She said she'd call
you from Oakland.
You should have called me.
At least let me talk to her.
She's an adult, Don.
Do you want to go
to the market with us?
You know, I'm gonna
have company tonight.
Maybe it'll cheer you up.
We'll go.
Amy.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes.
- We should go.
- Anything for you, Don?
I know what he likes.
( computer humming )
( humming continues )
( clears throat )
( muffled humming )
( sighs )
( no audible dialogue )
We're back.
- Let me see.
- She's fine.
Couple of black eyes.
Ow.
Can I go lie down?
I want to know
what really happened.
They were sword fighting
with golf clubs.
- We're idiots, okay?
- You are.
You can't be
trusted on your own.
That's your face, young lady.
That's right, it's my face.
- Why am I even here?
- Girls! Girls! Please.
Sally, you can understand how your mother
and I are both worried about your nose.
Yeah, I know, because where would
Mom be without her perfect nose?
She wouldn't find
a man like you.
She'd be nothing.
It was a perfect nose.
And I gave it to you.
You're lucky Henry
is important enough
to get Dr. Kramer
to fix it this weekend.
I suppose you'd rather do
it in a barn in Farmington.
It's a nose job,
not an abortion.
- I'm going to break your arm next.
- Betty!
Don't worry about me
finding a man.
I already have you
to keep me in line.
You're going to your room and you're
going to wait there until morning.
Good, I prefer it.
Hello.
Just a minute.
It's for Megan again.
Megan?
It's Greenblatt's.
Hello.
( knock on door )
The main door was open and you
didn't check the peephole?
It's a bad neighborhood.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to tell you--
May I?
Michael.
I was just in the office and
there's something going on.
- What?
- The computer.
It's Saturday.
Take the day off.
That's right. So why
were Lou and Cutler
having a secret meeting in
that air-conditioned lair?
- I don't know.
- But I do.
They're homos.
( chuckles )
Okay.
Anything else to report?
Peggy, it's serious.
That machine makes men
do unnatural things.
What did you see?
( knocks )
- Who are you?
- This is Julio.
- Hello.
- Hey.
I'd like to say Peggy's mentioned
you at work, but she hasn't.
Julio lives upstairs.
Interesting arrangement.
Very modern.
I live with my mama.
I live with my pop,
which is why I can't
work at home.
Can I please work here?
I can't go back to the office.
Not right now.
I'll stay out of your way.
Fine.
Can I use your typewriter?
It's too loud.
( TV playing )
( "You've Made Me
So Very Happy" playing )
( guests chatting )
♪ you've treated me so kind ♪
♪ I'm about to lose my mind ♪
♪ you make me so very happy ♪
♪ I'm so glad you ♪
♪ came into my life... ♪
I wouldn't have invited
them both if I had known.
I swear, I thought she
was his daughter.
Don't you kind of want
to see what happens?
I'm doing fine.
I don't think
you are doing fine.
Maybe I'm not in the mood.
-  ( laughter )
-  ( glass breaks )
This is why I never
invite musicians.
( music stops )
( plays "Dixie" )
Crowd:
Boo!
What a merry band
of players we are.
So you're an actress, too?
I will be
if someone will let me.
( "Petite Fleur" playing )
Come on.
Come on in.
( snaps fingers )
Want another drink?
Is that Harry?
Don. Megan.
I'm sorry.
Miranda here
invited me to a party.
I didn't know this was it.
Hi, Miranda.
This place is out of sight.
I've been trying to help
Miranda find an agent.
You're so helpful.
Harry, what do you say
we go get a drink?
- Do you mind?
- No, of course not.
As long as Harry drives.
Well, I-- We--
Should I bring Miranda along?
Do you want to?
Sorry, honey.
We'll get you a ride.
She better not
catch you in here.
But then I'm not
gonna get to see you.
That's the way Betty likes it.
Are they gonna get divorced?
What? No.
They're the Dynamic Duo.
That's never going to happen.
The other night, they were
really screaming at each other.
I saw Henry take
a pillow to the den.
I'm gonna hitch
back to school tonight.
Can I come with you?
You want to run away?
I have a stomach ache
all the time.
You're not gonna piss, are you?
I don't do that anymore.
I'm sorry.
They'll never let you out.
You're too little.
- Michael.
- I'm sorry.
The kid left an hour ago.
It's interesting because
first you were dead,
then all this activity
started in your eyelids.
Time to go.
There's this pressure
in my head
like there's a hydrogen
bomb that's gonna go off.
And then I realize
it's that hum in the office.
It's getting to me.
I caught myself looking
at Stan's shoulders
and getting, you know, excited.
- Really?
- That's the computer's plan.
Turn us all homo.
Peggy, we got to reproduce.
If there was a way to do it
without having sex, I'd do it.
Stop it!
You have to leave.
Great. What am I doing?
It's building up.
Well, maybe you should
see a doctor or something.
Why?
'Cause I want you?
No, because you're not right.
Did you notice the radio
doesn't work in there anymore?
That's not my imagination.
It's just a computer!
No, you're right.
I'm gonna go.
You don't have to report
this information.
Good night.
( "How Much
Can a Man Take?" playing )
This is so much better.
Do you not want to talk?
Because you seemed
so happy to see me.
I was. I am.
Good. 'Cause I was
happy to see you.
You know what, Don?
I am put in a strange position.
But I want you to know
I respect you.
Agencies change.
For the better, maybe.
But guys like us, we've got
to look out for each other.
I'm not gonna tell your wife.
That's not what I meant.
You wouldn't do that.
We go back a long way,
don't we?
We do.
Well, I'm going to make sure
that you're still important.
I don't know how.
It's gonna take some thought.
It's gonna take
some major brain power.
In fact, you might
have to figure it out.
I think the solution here
is not to get rid of you.
You should be in LA.
Your wife's out here.
Ted Chaough is useless.
Use-less.
Ted Chaough.
Broken man.
What solution?
Oh, this is the final solution.
Cutler and Lou
are pursuing Commander.
Commander who?
No, Commander cigarettes.
Philip Morris.
I think they're pretty sure
that they can land it
and you'll have to go.
How long has this been going on?
Is there work?
Don't make me sorry I told you.
I hope you know how much
I appreciate this.
So far, just phone calls.
But I turned in
the media plan yesterday.
Can we get another round?
( laughing )
Hello.
Everybody just left.
Not everybody.
Wilma!
- Ah!
- ( laughing )
How was the night on the
town with Harry Crane?
Educational.
You know what would
make you feel better?
Drugs.
( laughs )
I'm tired.
But you just got here.
I'm going to bed.
There goes the fun.
( knocks )
I'm supposed to tuck you in.
And what does your friend say?
I don't want you
to be in a bad mood.
Stop playing around.
You're stoned.
Don't you like Amy?
Leave him alone.
This is the best place
to be right now, Don.
Right here.
Kiss her.
I know you want to.
I don't want anything
right now.
Don't lie.
( birds chirping )
- Hey.
- I can't find the coffee.
I'll get it.
Good morning.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
Oh, yes, hi.
He made it.
It's Stephanie.
Oh.
Where are you?
I'm back in Oakland.
I felt bad about missing you,
but I didn't want
to break my word.
You did. You told me you
were gonna be here.
I know, but I kind of
promised Anna
I'd let you live your life.
That is not what she meant.
Like it or not,
I'm worried about you.
I want you to call me
when the baby comes.
I want to take care
of anything you need.
I'm so grateful. And that
Megan's really solid.
Thank her for me again.
You have my number.
Bye-bye.
( distant siren blaring )
- I'm sorry.
- She sounds okay.
I have to get back.
Harry told me some things
I shouldn't have been told.
- What is wrong with him?
- No, I'm glad.
But I have to get back.
Really?
But you're still coming
back next weekend, right?
Of course.
Hello, everyone.
Bye, everyone.
I'm making coffee.
I'm gonna split.
Great party.
( door closes )
I'm gonna shower.
( sighs )
( "Abendlich Strahlt
Der Sonne Auge" playing )
How'd it go?
She doesn't need an operation.
It's not even broken.
Come on.
Let's go inside.
I'm comfortable here right now.
I just drove to White Plains
and back up to Farmington.
I don't want to sit
in the kitchen like the help.
"The help"?
I'm going to assume
you're not referring to me.
What's gotten into you?
You come in and ask me to move
just because you feel
like moving.
I'm comfortable in here or I
wouldn't be sitting in here.
- Knock it off. - I'm tired of
everyone telling me to shut up.
I'm not stupid.
I speak Italian.
I'm sorry I embarrassed you.
You're sorry you forgot to inform
me what I'm supposed to think.
Guess what?
I think all by myself.
You're so smart. Why don't
you run for office?
Know what, Henry? I don't
know what I'm going to do,
but that's a good idea.
( sighs )
( knocks )
Good morning, Michael.
How are you?
Can't you tell?
I'm myself again.
Oh, good.
I'm glad to hear that.
But I do want to say
in the clearness of day,
I have feelings for you.
Well, I'm flattered,
and that happens
when you work with people.
But it's not real.
I realized it was
the waves of data.
They were filling me up.
I had to find the release.
I removed the pressure.
Now it just flows through me
without affecting me at all.
It has an outlet.
Open it.
You don't have to
thank me for that.
It's obviously something
you did on your own.
( screams )
What is that?
It's my nipple.
It's the valve.
It's weird.
They'll sew it up,
but they won't take it off.
I had to do that myself.
Anyway, I'm grateful,
so I wanted to show it.
Michael, sit down.
I want you to wait here.
Did Mr. Ginsberg
find you?
( "Savoy" playing )
Jim, Lou.
Sorry to interrupt.
You must be Les.
Don Draper.
Don.
This is Stephen and Tony.
We weren't expecting you, Don.
I know that and I apologize.
I just wanted to say
something that I think
these gentlemen from Philip
Morris are too polite to say.
We know who you are
and we're only talking
about a presentation right now.
But we do have
a problem working
with the man who cut our throat
in "The New York Times."
Well, if you were
to give us a shot,
I'm prepared
to leave the agency.
Don, thanks for saying that
so that we don't have to.
Just know the man
who wrote that letter
was trying to save his
business, not destroy yours.
Like Lou, I have over 10 years
of tobacco experience.
Since my first day
on Lucky Strike,
the government
was building a scaffold
for your whole industry.
And I found a way
to stay that execution
in '60, '62, '64, and '65.
I'm also the only cigarette man
who sat down with the opposition.
They shared
their strategy with me
and I know how to beat it.
That may be true,
but we don't turn on our
friends as easily as you do.
I just keep thinking
what your friends
at American Tobacco would think
if you made me apologize.
Force me into your service.
They are still your
competition, aren't they?
Gentlemen, thank you
for your time.
Get out while you can!
I'm gonna ride down with him.
( whirring, humming )
( horn honking )
You're incredible.
Thank you.
You think this is going
to save you, don't you?
( "Only Daddy That'll Walk
The Line" playing )
( whistles )
Taxi!
♪ and I'm getting
pretty tired of it ♪
♪ you keep stepping
out of line ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ 'cause ever since you were
a little bitty teeny girl ♪
♪ you said I was the only man
in this whole world ♪
♪ now you better do some
thinking, then you'll find ♪
♪ you got the only daddy
that'll walk the line ♪