Ready about!
Go about!
What's that one?
Oh, it's called an anchor bend,
surprisingly.
Hello.
Manage to find your way around?
Oui.
-Ahoy there!
-Charlie!
Poirot, you've arrived.
Merci.
My guess is you're in the
entertainment business, too?
Non, non. Non, monsieur,
I am a spectator merely.
Been down here before?
No. No, I was introduced to
Sir Charles at a bridge party.
Oh, it is now many years.
And you, monsieur, you have
known him for a long time also?
Ah, yes.
We were at Oxford together.
Tell me, why do you think
he has retired?
Well, cherchez la femme,
old fruit.
That's all I'll say.
Tollie, welcome.
Good to see you.
-Poirot.
-My dear Charles.
I'm so glad you two
have finally met --
my two best friends
in all the world.
Good afternoon, Sir Charles.
Gentlemen.
Here is the menu for dinner.
Before sailing,
it was racing cars, remember?
Oui, d'accord.
What next?
Hot-air balloons?
If you will excuse me,
Sir Charles,
it might be a good idea
were I to dine with you tonight.
Well, that would be lovely.
Otherwise, we shall have
an odd number of males
and females at table.
I'm glad you agree.
Gentlemen.
Remarkable specimen.
How long have you had her?
Six years.
First in London, then here.
Runs the place like clockwork.
But now the bloody woman
wants to leave.
She's leaving?
Why?
She says she has
an invalid mother.
Sounds unlikely to me.
I'd be very surprised
if Miss Milray had
biological parents at all.
Je te remercie
for your invitation.
This is a spot most beautiful.
So, tell to me, if you please,
who are to be the other guests?
Yes, come on, Charlie. Who are
the figures in this drama?
The dramatis personae?
Very well.
Down from London
are Captain and Mrs. Dacres.
Cynthia is, in fact,
Ambrosine of Bond Street.
Not the dressmaker
that is so celebrated?
That's it.
Whilst Dacres,
once a jockey himself,
is now something
of a flat-racing fanatic.
Who else?
Also from London
is the up-and-coming playwright
Anthony Astor.
Oh, splendid.
Does this London lot know
the others who are coming?
No. Why should they?
My ingenue tonight
will be Miss Lytton Gore.
Egg Lytton Gore?
Accompanied by her mother,
Lady Mary.
The genuine article.
Long on breeding, short on cash.
Then there are the Babbingtons.
Nothing very notable there,
but protocol demands, et cetera.
Best to have the parson along.
Then, last
and in every way least,
the young squib Oliver Manders.
The villain of the piece?
Let's just say
he's a little bit devious.
Accompanied by the chip
on his shoulder.
Never goes anywhere without it.
And that is my cast.
Ah, but we must not forget
Mlle. Milray,
for she is also to join us.
How could one forget
Miss Milray?
The specter at the feast.
This is Captain Dacres
and the very beautiful
Cynthia Dacres.
For many years, madame,
I have admired
your creations formidable.
How penetrating of you.
Any chance of a drink, old boy?
I'm just about to mix
some cocktails.
As soon as the others arrive.
Any tips for Goodwood, Dacres?
You're a man of the turf,
I hear.
What else do you know?
I beg your pardon?
What else has she told you?
Who, man?
Her.
Well, I'm not ashamed
of my profession.
Not one bit.
There may well be miners
and stevedores and so forth
whose budget does not stretch
to couture,
but if any woman is misguided
enough to marry one of them,
that, as they say,
is her lookout.
Mademoiselle, who is that lady?
Oh, that's
Anthony Astor, the playwright.
Her real name is Muriel Wills.
Oh, here come the locals.
Oh.
You're here.
Good evening.
Vicar.
Come in, come in.
Drinks.
Aye, aye, Skipper.
This is Mlle. Lytton Gore
who calls herself
something amusante?
Egg.
Don't ask me why.
Boiled, I like to think.
Have a cocktail, Egg.
Cheers.
Thank you.
I say, Sir Charles, you do know
some very reactionary people.
People are people.
I'm not political.
Oliver's not political either.
He just went to the East End
once, by mistake,
and had
a "Road to Damascus" moment.
You of all people, Egg, should
know how degrading poverty is.
Oh, I say, steady on.
It's all right.
I can fend for myself.
-Madam?
-Oh, do I dare?
Go on, Mums.
Show Mr. Manders we're not
completely ground down
by the iron heel of capitalism.
I think I might have one, too,
if my wife permits.
May I have my annual drink,
dear?
He'll do exactly as he likes,
as usual.
Do come and meet
a friend of mine
who is actually a detective.
A real one?
-A real one.
-Golly.
This tastes slightly...
It's a cocktail, Stephen,
not a pint of mild.
Mr. Babbington!
What's happened?
Is he ill?
Out of the way.
-Stephen, what is it?
-Is he all right, Tollie?
Talk to me. Stephen.
No, I'm sorry, he's not.
He's dead.
What?
Oh, my God!
Stephen!
Stephen, please!
Did you ever see anyone die
like that, Tollie?
I'm a psychologist.
I don't see people die much
at all.
A nerve specialist tries rather
hard to keep his patients alive.
Something is out of joint.
I can't put my finger on it.
What if he was murdered?
Murdered?
Who'd want to murder
a harmless old clergyman?
What if he wasn't harmless?
Look, Charlie,
you're a thundering good chap,
but you do let your imagination
run away with you sometimes.
Poirot, you're a crime expert.
Do you think anything untoward
happened here tonight?
We're planning to get
that glass -- his glass --
chemically analyzed.
Ah, oui?
It can do no harm.
Yes, and what do
you think will be the result?
All I can do is to guess,
Sir Bartholomew.
And my guess, it is
that they will find the remains
of a dry martini most excellent.
To poison a man with a cocktail,
one of many handed
around on a tray --
it is a technique
très difficile.
So, what do you think happened?
All I know, Sir Bartholomew,
is that he was taken ill
most suddenly.
Mes amis, perhaps the inquest,
it will reveal to us, hein?
I find nothing to indicate
foul play of any kind.
No trace of poison in his glass,
no sign of any wounding.
I conclude that the decease of
the Reverend Stephen Babbington
was occasioned solely
by natural causes.
Natural causes?
What a lot of tripe.
That coroner should be
struck off at once.
But the vicar
is elderly, mademoiselle,
and his health,
it is not so good.
Oh, he had a touch of arthritis,
nothing more.
He should have lived
till he was 90.
Did you know him well,
this M. Babbington?
Yes.
He was a sweet man,
a devout Christian,
and never unkind to anybody.
They had a son, you know,
Robin.
Actually, I used to have
rather a pash for Robin.
And Robin is?
He's, well, in India.
So, you see, I feel
rather strongly about this.
Supposing it wasn't
natural causes...
Ma chère, there was nothing
in that cocktail glass
but vermouth and gin.
It is proved.
Oh, yes, yes,
but it's still damned odd.
I mean, the Babbingtons hadn't
an enemy in the world.
And yet why would he just
keel over and die?
I'm going to find Sir Charles
and give him
a piece of my mind.
I suppose he's had loads
of affairs, has he?
Mademoiselle,
je suis désolé,
but it is not for --
It's all right.
I like a man
to have had affairs.
Shows he's properly red-blooded.
Unlike him.
But I thought the two
of you, you were friends?
Yes, he's gone into
his uncle's office in the city,
and, well, he's getting a bit
oily, if you know what I mean.
He just wants to get rich,
which I find odd,
as he's always saying
he's a Communist.
But, then, I find most people
rather disgusting
when it comes to money.
Mademoiselle,
so many people are disgusting
about so many things.
I'm going to say good night,
Poirot.
I've got an early morning train
to catch.
Will you return to London,
M. le Docteur?
No.
I'm going to Yorkshire.
I have a private clinic
up there.
I hope we meet
under better circs next time.
Oui d'accord.
Charlie.
When you two leave,
I shall be quite alone.
I'm sure you'll find
some attractive company.
No, I'm an old man, Tollie.
Hair grows out of my ears.
Fifteen years ago, perhaps,
but now I think
I'm deluding myself.
Damned nice though she is.
I'm thinking of selling up,
actually.
Ah, oui?
Well, then we may resume
our weekly lunches at the Ritz?
No, I mean to get away.
To where?
I thought the Riviera.
Monte Carlo.
I made a visit to Monte Carlo
each year.
Oh, yes, of course you do.
Where do you stay?
At the Majestic, isn't it?
Naturellement.
Excellent.
I need something to take my mind
off this awful murder.
But, then, you don't think
it is murder, do you, Poirot?
I do not wish to disappoint you,
mon ami,
but I do not see
how it could be.
No.
Well, anyway,
I don't mean to stay in Cornwall
a moment longer.
I wish to God I'd never come
to the wretched place.
Goodness, there must
be some money in psychology.
Yes, Mums,
but why has he invited us here?
We barely know the man.
It takes me back
to my younger days.
The shooting parties, the balls.
Of course not, you idiot.
We received an invitation,
that's all.
I'm warning you, Cynthia.
First sign of a white coat,
I'm making a dash for it.
Welcome! Welcome!
Do come through.
Thank you so much
for inviting us.
Evening.
Straight through.
That was a very
fine meal, Sir Bartholomew.
One found the meringue
especially captivating.
And you don't stint
on the firewater as well,
I'm pleased to say.
Shall we clear now, sir?
By Jove, yes, do.
Serve the cheese now, Ellis,
would you?
Oliver!
My God, Manders.
What happened?
A bad smash, I'm afraid.
I've been up in Cumberland
for the shooting.
I was on my way back to London
when I lost control
of my machine.
Bit of luck I was right outside
your house, Sir Bartholomew.
I'll say.
Shall I pour the port, sir?
Yes, thank you.
Is this where
your sanatorium is?
Yes. In the grounds.
Oh, tucked away?
What caused the crash?
I think I hit an oil slick.
Plowed into your wall.
Sorry about the medieval masonry
and all that.
That is an extremely
tall tale, Mr. Manders.
However, we drink
to your miraculous escape.
As a matter of fact,
I am very fortunate to have you
amongst the company,
amongst my good friends
from Cornwall and London,
for the reason that I have
something remarkable to reveal.
I'm only sorry Charlie
Cartwright can't be here.
He'd relish it.
Why can't he?
He's in the South of France.
What a pity.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
it has recently been brought
to my attention
that one of you...
Help! Somebody get some help!
Quickly!
En bord! En bord!
Le train bleu!
Gare de Lyon
pour Monte Carlo.
"Be cheerful, sir.
Our revels now are ended."
-Jouez avec moi.
-Non.
Jouez avec moi, monsieur.
Amuse-toi avec ton ballon.
Non, non, madame.
Poirot.
Ah, Sir Charles.
Quelle surprise.
Thank heavens
I've found you. Look at this.
Oh, non, non.
Oh, yes.
"We regret to announce the death
of Sir Bartholomew Strange,
the eminent nerve specialist.
His demise occurred suddenly
at the end of a dinner party.
He was drinking a glass of port
when he had a sudden seizure
and died
before medical aid
could be summoned."
A glass of port?
Now will you take me seriously?
Oui.
We must return to England
tout de suite.
Dear Sir Charles,
I'm so worried.
You'll have seen in the papers
that Sir Bartholomew is dead.
Well, he died in just the same
way as poor Mr. Babbington.
Also, I'm worried
about someone else.
My friend Oliver.
He's acting rather strangely.
I can't explain it all
in a letter.
But you could find out
the truth.
I know you could.
Do come back. Egg.
May I say what a pleasure it is
to see you again, Sir Charles?
Oh, thank you, George.
I hope you have enjoyed
your time in France.
Splendid. Thank you.
Merci, George.
Now, let us see
who else was present
at the death of Dr. Strange,
hein?
Ah, ici.
Sir Bartholomew Strange
is having his usual party
for the St. Leger.
Among the guests
are Lord and Lady Cardigan,
Lady Mary Lytton Gore,
Captain and Mrs. Dacres,
and, ah, Miss M. Wills.
"Seduction after Dark."
I beg your pardon?
That was the play
written by Mlle. Wills.
Oui, but there is no mention
of M. Oliver Manders
and it was Mlle. Egg herself
who suggested
that he also was there.
Tell to me about Melfort Abbey.
Well, Tollie bought it
a few years back for a song,
restored it, and put up
a sanatorium, nursing home,
whatever you want to call it.
Nuthouse, basically.
I've got to find out
what happened.
Someone has murdered my friend.
I'd better get off to Yorkshire.
I know the chief constable
quite well.
One moment, my friend.
In Cornwall, I felt you to be
guilty of overstating the case
because I just found it
incredible
that such a gentleman
who was old and harmless
should die a death
anything that was but natural.
But now we have another death,
in circumstances very similar.
And Hercule Poirot,
he must admit an error,
and so, if you permit,
I, myself, Hercule Poirot,
will make the investigation.
Hercule Poirot
will travel to Yorkshire.
That's very handsome of you.
Won't it take up your time?
What is time
in the face of death?
I see you have changed
your shoes.
Yes.
I always start with the feet.
Comment?
With the shoes.
Get the walk right.
Then the costume.
Before you know it,
you've got a character.
Ah, oui, d'accord, d'accord.
Welcome to Yorkshire, gents.
Sorry about the weather,
but some of us like it.
I was expecting Fred Johnson.
The chief constable's away.
I'm stood in.
Name's Crossfield.
I may as well say right off,
I don't hold with amateurs
coming up from London
and telling me my business.
Superintendent, if you permit,
we are here because of the death
of Bartholomew Strange.
Dr. Strange?
He were highly spoke of
round here.
But I'm afraid to say
it looks like he were murdered.
There's nowt
to indicate suicide.
Tollie would never kill himself.
A friend of yours, sir?
Very much so, yes.
You look oddly familiar.
Anyway, there's nowt for you
to do here.
We're pretty sure
that the butler's our man.
New chap.
Strange had only had him
for a fortnight.
The morning after the crime,
he disappears,
vanishes into thin air.
Where did he come from?
Any idea?
Oh, yes, his name is Ellis.
Gave a London agency
and a reference
from a previous employer,
Sir Horace Bird,
Holland Park.
And have you spoken
with Sir Horace?
I'd be happy to,
only he's away in East Africa
on safari.
So, these references,
they could be --
Well, they're forged,
obviously, Poirot.
Anybody can see that.
And the houseguests?
They are to be called
as witnesses?
We have asked them to stay on,
yes.
Can we have a look
around Melfort Abbey?
No, you can't.
Now, look, I'm very pally
with Fred Johnson.
We used to play polo together
in India.
Hang about.
Aren't you
Sir Charles Cartwright?
At your service.
Well, why the heck
didn't you say so?
Eh.
I saw you in "Lord Aintree's
Dilemma." I did, yeah.
I took the wife to London,
and she wouldn't see owt else.
It had to be Charles Cartwright
in "Lord Aintree's Dilemma."
And I remember
we queued for hours
for the Pall Mall Theatre.
But it were worth it.
Superintendent, if you please.
Are you absolutely convinced
in your little gray cells
that this M. Ellis is your man?
Why else did he bolt?
My dear Charles, do you realize
that almost every person
who was present at your dinner
in Cornwall
was also present here?
Please don't assume
that because I'm a thespian,
I'm also dim.
Of course I realize.
What can we deduce from it?
No, it's just that
it appears to me
that the doctor,
he was making an experiment.
He must have thought that
one of the people in Cornwall
was responsible for the crime,
and so he has invited them here
to Melfort Abbey.
I wore this
as Galbraith of the Yard.
Rather authentic,
don't you think?
Hello, Annie.
Good morning,
Sir Charles. Come in.
Merci.
You've no butler?
Mr. Baker.
He's in Margate.
Sir Bartholomew gave him
two months' holiday,
for long service.
Excuse me, sir.
That's why Ellis was here.
It's a caller for you,
Sir Charles.
Oh, thank you, Annie.
Mademoiselle.
Crossfield here.
Now, listen, I've a pal who
works at the coroner's office,
and he's slipped me
the mortuary report.
They think it were
nicotine poisoning.
But couldn't you get that
just from smoking?
You'd have to smoke
a heck of a lot.
The nicotine is an
alkaloid, colorless, odorless,
and is used habitually
by the gardeners
for the spraying of the roses.
Ah.
Also, they got a toxicology
report on the glass.
It contained port
and only port.
Exactly the same as last time.
With one difference
most important, mon ami.
This time,
we know it was murder.
So, how did you find it
serving under M. Ellis?
Oh, it were quite fun,
actually, sir.
Yeah.
He'd been in service all over.
He knew things, scandals.
About some very grand
households, too.
Is it possible that he was not,
in fact, a butler?
Oh, no, sir.
No, he'd been in service
for sure.
Well, he arranged
the work different
from any butler
I ever knew before.
Got his own method
sort of thing.
So, tell to me, if you please,
about the Dr. Strange.
On the night that he died,
how was his mood?
Oh, he were happy, sir.
Very jolly.
He even larked about
with Mr. Ellis,
a thing I'd never heard him do
with Mr. Baker.
Pardon, but what does it mean
"he larked about"?
Mr. Ellis came up
with a telephone message,
and the doctor asked him if
he was sure he'd got it right.
And Mr. Ellis said,
"Quite sure,"
and the doctor laughed and said,
"You're an excellent butler,
Ellis."
I were that surprised.
What was this telephone message?
Oh, it were from the sanatorium,
about a patient who'd arrived.
A Mrs. Rushbridger.
Or something like that.
That'll be them coming back
from the inquest.
Miss Wills, do you mind
if we ask you some questions?
Do you mind
if I call my solicitor?
Um, do we, Poirot?
Je pense que Mlle. Wills,
she makes a little joke,
non?
What is it you want to ask?
Did you notice anything unusual
about the arrangements
that night?
I heard there was
a secret tunnel.
Did you hear about that?
No!
Yes.
There's a secret tunnel
that leads to open countryside.
-Is there?
-Yes.
And they think the butler
crawled along it and escaped.
Crikey.
Where is it?
Ah, well, that's the sort of
thing that detectives detect,
isn't it?
I'd start with the bookshelves
if I were you.
Miss Wills?
I couldn't say what Miss Wills
thought about anything.
Eh bien, will you tell to us
what you thought about her?
Someone said she lives
in Tooting,
which she can't help, I suppose,
but she does poke and pry
something terrible.
She was in my room.
-She was what?
-In my room.
Poking about.
No, she wasn't.
You're seeing things.
Oh, here we go again.
The funny farm's
round the corner.
Do be quiet, Derek.
There's supposed to be
a secret tunnel.
Have you heard about that?
The coroner said
it was nicotine poisoning.
What's that?
Well, Egg,
it's a colorless,
odorless alkaloid,
widely available, in fact.
Often used by gardeners
to spray their roses with.
I use it.
Everyone does.
If you please to tell me,
mademoiselle,
where is Oliver Manders now?
Oh, he went straight back
to town after the inquest.
He had to get straight
back to work, poor love.
Did Ellis poison Dr. Strange?
Well, how am I supposed
to know that?
Do you have any information
about the secret passage?
-Do you?!
-I certainly don't.
And I don't think
Mums does either.
Oh, God, this is hopeless.
We haven't found out
a single thing.
But you're doing
wonderfully well.
The police have already searched
Mr. Ellis' room, sir.
Yes, thanks, Annie.
Merci, mademoiselle.
Well, what have we here?
Ah!
He had athlete's foot.
Oh, look.
What is that?
It's ink.
There is something that is
discomposing in my mind.
Yes? Go on.
It is simply the way
that Sir Bartholomew Strange,
he made a joke with his butler,
as was told to us
by Mlle. Annie.
It did not seem in keeping
with his character.
By God, you're right.
Tollie would never have spoken
to the staff like that.
Alors?
And when did the incident occur?
When Ellis brought the telephone
message from the sanatorium.
I'll bet there's no such person
as Mrs. Rushbridger.
I'll bet you
it's a coded message.
I've just returned from abroad
to this dreadful news.
I wanted to call in
and make sure that everything
was shipshape.
Dr. Strange was very proud
of this place, Matron.
Thank you.
His experimental treatments
are often a great success.
Well, yes,
I was speaking to a chap
in Monte Carlo
who has a relation coming here.
Missus...
Damn, what was the name?
Bridger?
Rushbridge?
-Mrs. de Rushbridger?
-Yes.
Oh, yes, she arrived.
Rather a bad breakdown.
Lapses of memory,
severe nervous exhaustion.
She won't be seeing anyone
for a very long time.
Oh, dear.
Thank you so much, Matron.
Merci.
Damn. Damn.
The bloody woman exists.
This whole thing's giving me
a headache.
What do you say we go somewhere
for a stiff whiskey?
Non, non, non, mon cher.
We must return
to the bedroom of Ellis.
Ellis?
Why?
The stain of ink?
Now you remember perhaps?
Yes, it's just a stain
on the skirting board, Poirot.
But how does it come
to be there?
No, something, it is amiss.
Yes, by God, you're right.
He didn't drop his ink bottle.
There'd be more ink.
He dropped his fountain pen.
And he must have been writing
at the time
or the top wouldn't
have been off.
Perhaps he laid it on
the mantelshelf and it rolled?
Non.
You know, in the theater,
we have to examine the internal
logic of all our actions.
There's this Russian cove
called Stanislavsky who...
He's writing a letter.
He thinks he hears something.
He has to hide the letter.
No time to rip up a floorboard.
Non.
He can't burn it.
Because of the cinders.
Là, là, là!
Only one place.
Behind the fire?
Have a look, mon ami.
Non?
Oui?
Bravo!
Excellent!
We believe they are letters
drafted by the fugitive Ellis.
"This is to say that the writer
does not wish to cause
unpleasantness, but..."
"John Ellis, butler,
presents his compliments
and would be glad
of a short interview
touching the tragedy tonight,
before going to the police
with certain information."
"I am badly in need of money.
£1,000 would make
all the difference to me.
Meet me at..."
So that's it.
Blackmail.
May I ask
who you're telephoning to?
Cornwall.
The Loomouth Police.
So, Ellis knew something
and he was paid to disappear
and that's exactly what he did.
The question is
"Where's he gone?"
My friend, I am convinced
that this M. Ellis,
he is dead.
That is why there...
That is why
there is no trace of him.
We are dealing with a maniac
that is very dangerous.
Oh, my Lord.
Well, what about Egg?
Is she going to be all right?
There is something
that concerns me
about the Mlle. Egg Lytton Gore.
The stain on the wall.
It's ink.
How did she know
that it was ink?
To me, it was simply a stain
on the wall.
Women have a better-developed
color sense than us, don't they?
But it makes me
to be suspicious.
Of Egg?
-Oui.
-Oh, no.
My dear friend, forgive me,
but we must consider
every eventuality.
Of course we must,
but it's not her.
It can't be. No, no, no, no, no.
No, can't be.
George.
I am so fatigued.
Sir, I'm afraid
there are visitors
in the drawing room.
Visitors in the drawing room?
Yes, sir.
But it is 11:00
at night, George.
Indeed it is, sir.
It is 11:00 at night,
therefore we do not have
visitors in the drawing room.
No, sir.
Take this.
Of course.
Mlle. Lytton Gore.
Oh, call me Egg,
for Pete's sake.
What is it that you do here?
-Good evening.
-M. Oliver.
Oliver has something
to tell you.
Tell him.
The motorcycle crash
was a stunt, sir.
I faked it.
Comment?
Why did you do such a thing?
And do not make me angry,
monsieur.
I am very fatigued.
I was told to do it.
By whom?
Bartholomew Strange.
He wrote to me
and told me to fake a crash
and arrive about half-past 9:00.
But when I got there,
he seemed as surprised
as everyone else.
And 10 minutes later,
he is poisoned?
-Yes.
-And there is no connection?
No.
I had nothing to do with it.
You have not told this
to the police?
Well, it's going to look
a bit windy, isn't it, sir?
Why did you obey
his instructions?
I heard you'd be there.
And I knew Charles Cartwright
was in France.
Oh, Ollie, why are you so wet?
-I'm nervous.
-Why? I don't bite.
I'm mindful of Robin Babbington.
Don't be ridiculous.
Excuse me, what has happened
to Robin Babbington?
Well, Robin fell in love
with her, too,
and she sent him to India.
He never came back.
-Why not?
-That's enough!
He went all mystical, went to
live in an ashram or something.
-Totally gaga.
-He did what he wanted!
Did he,
or did you drive him away?
You drive us all away
in the end, Egg!
Miserable business.
I know.
But it must be done.
Stephen Babbington
was a gentle old soul
without an enemy in the world.
And yet he was killed.
Or at least
we think he was killed.
We're about to find out.
What reasons are there
for killing a person?
Babbington knew something.
Babbington recognized somebody.
What did he know?
Perhaps it was something
he didn't know he knew.
Perhaps he was the cause
and Dr. Strange the effect.
Précisément.
What?
If we are to believe
that the second murder,
it sprung directly
from the first,
then it is the first murder
that we must investigate.
The murder of the Reverend
Stephen Babbington.
If I hadn't moved to Cornwall,
none of this
would have happened.
I'm deluding myself, Egg.
I'm no detective.
Mlle. Wills,
what is it that you do here?
Well, I've never seen
an exhumation before.
Ah, so, this is all --
How do you say --
grist to your mill?
Your command of English
is really rather wonderful,
isn't it?
Poor Stephen.
He told Egg
to steer clear of Oliver.
But girls are very foolish,
M. Poirot.
There's something attractive
to a girl
about being told
that so-and-so is a bad man.
She at once thinks
that her love will reform him.
It may seem a wicked thing
to say,
but I was relieved
when my husband died
and it was just Egg and I,
a little roly-poly baby,
trying to stand up,
always falling over.
Yes, it's a ridiculous nickname.
But don't let that deceive you.
She's a girl who knows
what she wants.
On the night
that Dr. Strange died,
did he appear to be worried
about anything?
No.
He was in high spirits.
He seemed to be amused
about something,
some private joke.
He said he was going to spring
a surprise.
Sadly, he did.
Do you really think
someone murdered my husband
with nicotine?
That's what
they're trying to find out.
All we know is that Tollie
Strange drank some port,
and, well, it was...
It was just the same.
I was there.
You have some lovely flowers,
Mrs. Babbington.
What are these?
Lupins, dear.
But I have such trouble
with greenfly,
I have to spray them
constantly.
Forgive my forthrightness,
Mrs. Babbington,
but did your husband leave you
very much money?
What?
He gave away everything.
Missionaries were better off
than we were.
I used to scold him about it.
What about when he was younger?
Did he have any enemies?
Enemies?
No.
Stephen was my father's curate.
We were engaged for four years,
then he got a living
in Kent, in Gilling,
so we were able to get married.
We lived in Gilling
for 16 years.
Then we came to Cornwall.
We were happy.
I have a little idea
I would like to suggest.
Is it possible that the poison
was intended all along
for Sir Bartholomew Strange,
and then
the Reverend Babbington,
he drank it by mistake?
No one who knew Tollie
at all well
would have tried to poison him
with a cocktail.
Mais pourquoi pas?
Because he never drank them.
Couldn't stand them.
Ah, oui?
May I speak to you the truth?
You know
this whole investigation,
it has been conducted with great
enthusiasm and great skill
but it has yielded very little.
And there is danger.
Real danger.
So, now, Poirot,
he will take charge.
We will return to London
by the early train.
And if you please, mademoiselle,
you will make the visit to the
showrooms of Ambrosine Limited.
Sir Charles will receive
his instructions from me.
It is the approach classique,
you see,
the technique of elimination.
We eliminate the suspects
one by one.
We do not scamper around
like the puppies.
Cynthia Dacres.
Thank you.
Fleur-de-lis on the cuffs.
Witty, don't you think?
And the waistline's
rather penetrating.
I shouldn't have it
in the red lead color, though.
I should have it in español.
And you've come into some money,
you say?
You have so much personality,
you mustn't wear
anything ordinary.
Have you been back to
Cornwall since that party?
Oh, my dear, I couldn't.
It was too upsetting.
I know.
And you knew the vicar
from before
I think I remember him saying.
In a place called Gilling
in Kent?
Oh, no, no, no, Marcel.
No.
I asked for the blue pattu.
No, I would never go to Kent.
Why would I go to Kent?
What's in Kent?
-Perhaps Captain Dacres.
-Him?
No, he never leaves
the Seventy-Two Club,
except to lose money at some
stupid racecourse or other.
Which we can scarce afford
at times like these.
Oh, now, look.
This is lovely.
What did you say
your name was again?
Egg.
Hello, I'm bacon.
You have lovely eyes.
Has anyone ever mentioned that?
Tell me about
Reverend Babbington.
Who?
Babbington.
You knew him, didn't you?
In Gilling, wasn't it?
If you say so, my dear.
Sorry, just back from Newbury,
had a bit of a poxy day.
Funny thing is, I can understand
bumping off a doctor,
for obvious reasons,
but I can't understand
bumping off a parson.
Who'd want to bump off a parson?
Who'd want to bump off a doctor?
Lot of people.
Doctors are interfering swine.
Did Bartholomew Strange --
Bartholomew Strange.
Bartholomew Humbug.
I'd like to know what goes on
in that sanatorium of his.
Nerve cases very likely.
All I know is, doesn't matter
what your nerves are like,
they lock you in
and you never get out.
And they call it a cure,
the swine.
Cynthia told me
not to talk about it.
Talk about what?
It. The thing.
-The Arab.
-The Arab?
There was this Arab gentleman
Cynthia was wooing.
He was going to invest
in Ambrosine,
which, by the way,
it badly needs,
because her head for business
is about as sound
as her dress-sense.
But he had some awful trouble
with his nerves.
He was seeing a fellow
in Harley Street, a specialist,
who packed him off on a cruise,
a world cruise.
Gone for good.
Arrivederci.
And his checkbook with him.
And that specialist
was Bartholomew Strange?
Well, we don't know,
but if it was,
things would look a bit fishy
for us, wouldn't they?
Which is why I'm not supposed
to talk about it.
Now, you tell me something.
What was that woman doing
in my room?
What woman?
The rabbit face.
The playwright.
Always poking and prying.
She's like a ferret
up a drainpipe, that one.
William.
"Evening Standard"!
Cornish exhumation!
Taxi! Taxi!
Miss Milray.
Oh.
Isn't it dreadful?
Miss Milray, are you all right?
Oh, hell.
I know, it's terrible.
Sorry. I'm overreacting.
I'm fine.
Really, really fine.
It's just I've known him
all my life.
-Mr. Babbington?
-Yes.
I grew up in Gilling
where he was vicar.
All my family come from there.
Gilling?
But when --
Sorry. I must dash.
Awfully nice to see you again.
"Evening Standard"!
Vicar poisoned!
Such a pity you left
the profession, Sir Charles.
You would have been perfect
in this one.
What's it called?
"Sin in Suburbia."
Who's playing my part?
Geoffrey Winchester.
Oh, God.
No, no, no, he'll be wonderful.
I adore Geoffrey.
When do you open?
Next Thursday.
Come to the dress rehearsal.
Love to.
And you, M. Poirot.
I like an audience.
Bring your friends.
Merci beaucoup.
Mademoiselle, I would like
to ask you something more
about the events so terrible
at Melfort Abbey.
Because if there was anything
to be noticed,
I believe that you,
the connoisseur of human nature,
you would have noticed it.
"Grist to my mill"?
Peut-être.
I was intrigued, I admit.
I'd never seen a murder
at close hand before.
Actually, there was one thing
I suppose I ought to have
informed the police,
if truth be known.
What was it?
Well, it was about the butler,
Ellis.
What was it?
He had a kind of strawberry mark
on his right wrist.
I noticed it
when he poured the port.
Ah.
No one else mentioned
a birthmark.
Where exactly was it?
It was right here.
Roughly the size
of half a crown.
When you were in Yorkshire,
did Sir Bartholomew mention
a Mrs. de Rushbridger to you?
One of his patients.
Suffering from loss of memory.
No.
Well, can you
tell us anything else at all
about any of the other guests?
Sorry.
Oh, well.
Sorry to disturb your rehearsal.
Goodbye, Miss Wills.
Mademoiselle.
She knows something.
I'm sure she does.
Faites attention, mon ami.
You must be careful.
It may not be Mlle. Wills
that we must watch.
So, Cynthia Dacres
is desperate for money.
Possibly Dr. Strange ruined her
best chances of getting some.
What about Oliver Manders?
Does his story ring true?
Tollie Strange
writing him a letter?
I have the impression
that it is not in keeping
with the character
of Dr. Strange
to behave in such a fashion.
I'm very suspicious
of Oliver Manders.
What is his relationship
with Mlle. Milray?
With Milray?
He has none.
The woman is incapable
of relationships.
Osmosis, perhaps,
but not relationships.
Now, Oliver Manders was present
at both murders
and now he's keeping
his head down.
Is there a link
between Manders and Miss Wills?
I do not believe so.
So, what are we going to do?
Think.
Think?
It is a mental process.
I know what it is.
But can't we do something?
For you, always the action,
eh, mademoiselle?
Voilà. There are inquiries
to be made at Gilling.
The mother of Mlle. Milray.
And I wonder, if you would be
so kind, the both of you,
to find out what you can
about the past
of the Reverend Babbington.
Righto.
In the meantime,
I will make the preparations
for my sherry party.
A sherry party?
Oui.
Tomorrow evening at 8:00.
It is the fashionable thing
to do, n'est-ce pas?
Ah, mesdames et messieurs,
un moment s'il vous plaît.
Let us have no talk
of murders and poisons
because it spoils the palate.
Sir Charles?
Thank you, Poirot.
Thank you, George.
Cynthia, charming dress.
Thank you.
Why do you bring me
to these awful places?
It's how I pick up custom.
Oh, like you picked up the Arab?
Like you picked up Sir Charles?
Keep your filthy insinuations
to yourself.
Ah.
To marry an older man,
I think, is safer.
His follies are behind him.
Not, as with younger fellows,
still to come.
I wish that I shared
your certainty, madame.
Oh, but we have been
so badly off.
I want Egg to see
people, places,
great cities, great art.
Don't know how you put up
with it.
What do you mean?
Him barging in like that.
He's a has-been.
A washout.
A flop.
You're right.
I should --
M. Oliver,
I wish to ask you something.
The letter you received
from Dr. Strange --
the invitation to --
How do you say --
gate-crash the party --
where is it?
Oh, I burnt it.
But why?
Well, after he was killed,
I thought
it might incriminate me.
But the police
didn't even notice me.
And tell to me, if you please,
what is it that prevents you
from proposing to Mlle. Egg?
I haven't any money.
Can't you see?
Here's to you.
You've changed my life.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm bad luck.
Like a bad penny.
Oh, don't be absurd.
Poirot, off to Gilling tomorrow?
Oui.
But Mlle. Milray, where is she?
She is not here.
I'm sure that I invited her.
Good health,
and God save the king.
I'll have another sherry, chum.
The sherry,
I prefer it to the cocktail,
and a thousand times
to the whiskey.
Ah, the whiskey, quelle horreur.
But the delicate wines
of France,
you have merely to taste these.
Charles.
Charles!
Dear God!
Charles.
Charles, no.
Not you, Charles.
Mes amis.
You fool.
You absurd, play-acting
little fool!
You think you know everything
about everything.
But look what you've done.
Gently, Egg.
A performance magnifique,
Sir Charles.
Bad luck.
Still here.
You beast.
Golly.
But why?
Messieurs et mesdames,
I demand pardon of you all.
This little farce,
it was necessary
to prove to you,
and also to me,
one little fact that my reason
told to me it was true.
I placed into
one of these glasses
a teaspoon of the plain water.
This water was to represent
the pure nicotine.
And I asked Sir Charles to play
the victim here tonight.
Sir Charles, superb.
But suppose for one moment
that this was not a farce,
that it was a real life.
What do you think the police
will be the first thing
they will do?
They'll analyze the glass.
They will analyze the glass,
and traces of the nicotine
it will be found, oui?
Non, you make the error.
No nicotine will be found.
Why not?
Because that is not the glass
from which Sir Charles,
he drank.
This is.
The theory of
the conjuring trick, mes amis,
it is very simple.
The attention can never be
in two places at the same time.
While you were looking
at the body,
Hercule Poirot,
he switches the glass.
And this is how
both of the murders
were hidden so expertly.
Alors, faites attention.
I demand that you listen to me
most attentively.
This murderer may strike again.
If any one of you
knows anything at all...
...now it is the time to speak.
So you planned it all?
Oui.
Just to see if anyone noticed
if you switched the glasses?
I also had another purpose.
When Sir Charles, he fell dead,
I wished to see the expression
on the face of one person
in particular.
And did you?
Oui.
Which person's?
Ah, that is my little secret.
So you know who the murderer is?
Oui.
Then have them arrested.
I cannot.
Because until I know why
Stephen Babbington was murdered,
I have no proof at all.
And I do not know why.
Excuse me, sir.
A telegram.
Milles tonnerres.
"Please come at once.
Can give valuable information.
Death of Bartholomew Strange.
Margaret de Rushbridger."
Margaret de Rushbridger?
Merci.
Just change at Doncaster.
Thank you.
Looks like we're
not going to find out any more
about the Reverend Babbington
from old Mother Milray.
She died a month ago
when I was in France,
and Milray didn't tell me.
Oh, this is hopeless.
I wish Poirot was here.
Egg?
Look at these names.
There are some
frightfully strange ones.
There's a family of Shovepennys.
And here's
a Mary Ann Sticklebucket.
None of them
are as strange as mine.
Cartwright?
That's not strange.
That's not my real name.
It's an acting name.
What's your real name?
Couldn't possibly tell you.
-Why not?
-You'll laugh.
No, I won't.
No, I can't tell you.
What is it?
It's Mugg.
My father's name was Mugg.
That is genuinely catastrophic.
To go through life as a Mugg.
And are you really a Charles,
Sir Charles?
Or are you a sham
in all respects?
Well, are you really poisonous?
Are you the Black Widow
everyone says you are?
What?
What do you mean?
What about Robin Babbington?
Oh, I don't know.
He was always wet.
He wore sandals.
Anyway, you were in Madras
with him. You tell me.
No, I was not in Madras
with him.
I found out afterwards
from the consul
that he'd sold his passport
and grown a beard.
And you had nothing to do
with it?
But of course I didn't.
And what about Oliver Manders?
Are you trying to implicate him
in these murders,
because Oliver
couldn't kill anyone.
What are you up to?
Trying to clear the field
for yourself?
See off the opposition?
No, of course I'm not.
I love you, Egg.
And I would very much
like to marry you.
I just haven't found
the courage to ask you.
So, you mean
you've just been dithering?
Well, yes.
Yes, I remember you.
With Sir Charles.
But you never told me your name.
I call myself Hercule Poirot.
And who do you want to see?
Mme. de Rushbridger.
But don't you know?
She's dead.
She died this morning.
She's been poisoned.
A box of chocolates
came for her by post.
They're liqueur chocolates.
Nicotine?
Chemical analysis will show.
Was she killed
to prevent her telling us
what she knew, eh, Poirot?
Or what she did not know,
Superintendent.
I must waste no time.
A lad from Melfort village says
he were given the telegram
by a tramp.
-A tramp?
-Aye.
The tramp says it came from
a loony lady in the nuthouse,
this nuthouse.
Said he could have two bob
if he sent it.
To me.
Aye, to you.
Bon.
Superintendent, if you please,
to take me
to the railway station
as quickly as you can.
And also,
there is one other thing
that I would like you to do
for me.
Merci, George.
Sir Charles telephoned from
his Belgravia residence, sir.
He's concerned that Miss Wills
has gone missing.
He motored out to Tooting
for the purpose
of a further interview,
but when he got there,
she was nowhere to be found.
Miss Lytton Gore, sir.
Merci, George.
M. Poirot will see you now,
miss.
Mademoiselle, s'il vous plaît.
Good heavens,
what are you doing?
Alors, I find that the building
of a house of cards
is -- is most stimulating
to my little gray cells.
And so, whilst I was in the
railway station in Yorkshire,
I purchased this pack of cards.
But these aren't real cards.
Non?
They've sold you Happy Families.
It's a children's game.
I haven't seen these in years.
Master Bun, the baker's son.
Mr. Grits, the grocer.
Oh, and here's me.
You?
Mrs. Mugg, the milkman's wife.
For I am to be
Mrs. Mugg, Poirot,
when I marry
Sir Charles Cartwright.
For that is his real name.
Well, wish me happiness.
I've just told you
I'm engaged to be married.
Pardon, oui, oui.
But I do wish you happiness,
mademoiselle.
But not the brief happiness
of youth,
but the happiness that endures,
happiness that is built
upon the rock.
I'll tell Charles
you called him a rock.
He'll think you're referring
to his acting.
God, they're paranoid,
aren't they?
We think it's Miss Wills,
by the way.
-The murderer.
-Pourquoi?
Well, because she's gone missing
and she's creepy.
And the funny thing is,
we're going to see a dress
rehearsal of her play tomorrow.
But will she be there?
Will she show up?
I'm so excited. I've never been
to a rehearsal before.
And Charles says
he'll take me backstage.
Sacre.
Poirot?
But Poirot has been blind.
Blind.
Are you coming?
-Hmm?
-To the theater?
Oui, but of course.
And I shall bring everyone.
Everyone must come.
Oh, do!
It's going to be fabulous.
I shall round up the audience
but immediately.
Paddington Station.
One moment, driver.
Follow that taxi if you please.
Stop!
You cannot do this,
mademoiselle.
It is evidence.
It's so exciting.
It's only Geoff Winchester, Egg.
Don't expect fireworks.
Mesdames et messieurs,
you have come to watch a dress
rehearsal of a play, hein?
Instead I give to you
Hercule Poirot.
When the Reverend
Stephen Babbington died,
Sir Charles advanced the theory
that he had been murdered.
I did not think it likely.
Stephen!
Stephen, please!
I could not figure to myself
why Stephen Babbington
should be murdered,
never mind how,
as there was no trace of poison
in his glass.
Until 24 hours ago,
when I saw that this murder
was both reasonable
and possible.
Who had the opportunity
to poison the cocktail
of the Reverend
Stephen Babbington?
Only Sir Charles
and his serving maid
who handed around the drinks.
But were either of these two
at Melfort Abbey?
No, no, they were not.
So they could be eliminated
from being suspects
very swiftly.
So, who had the best chance
to put the nicotine
in the glass of Dr. Bartholomew
Strange at Melfort?
The butler, Ellis,
who disappeared.
But he, we knew,
was a blackmailer, merely.
But then I was visited
by a sensation curieux, hein?
Très curieux.
I was certain that the person
who committed both of the crimes
must have been present
on both occasions.
Well, alors, that was obvious.
But it appeared to me
that this obviousness was
an arranged obviousness.
In other words,
it was too obvious
and therefore
not obvious at all.
I was certain that the person
who murdered
the Reverend Stephen Babbington
and Dr. Bartholomew Strange
must have been present on both
occasions but not apparently so.
And so, I am forced to
investigate once again
this butler so mysterious,
this M. Ellis.
He appeared suddenly, hein,
out of the blue
a fortnight before the crime
and disappears
but immediately afterwards.
And Poirot,
he comes to the conclusion
that he is dead,
and, in a way, I was correct.
I recalled the remarks made
about him
by the parlormaid at Melfort,
Mlle. Annie.
Well, he arranged the work
different
from any butler
I ever knew before.
Got his own method
sort of thing.
And, eventually, Poirot,
he came to realize why.
Alors, this butler, M. Ellis,
was indeed dead.
Why?
Because he never ever existed.
But Dr. Bartholomew Strange
was another matter.
He must have known
the true identity
of his temporary servant.
Do we have any evidence
for this?
Ah, oui.
His remark facetious.
You're an excellent butler,
Ellis.
Said as the joke, hein?
But as told to us
by Mlle. Annie,
the lark.
And it would have been
a lark perfectly understandable
if the doctor had known
the butler.
It would have been
a lark totally understandable
if the butler was indeed...
Sir Charles Cartwright,
his old friend,
and the doctor
had known of this all along.
Serve the cheese now,
Ellis, would you?
And then we'll...
I say, what's this?
Oliver!
I'll say.
Shall I pour the port, sir?
Oh, yes, thank you.
Is this where
your sanatorium is?
It has recently come
to my attention
that one of you...
And now, my heart,
it is breaking.
And, Charles,
it is you
who have broken my heart.
I hope you know where
you're going with this, Poirot.
Sadly, mon ami, I do.
You see, if anybody at
the dinner table that evening
had spotted that Sir Charles
was the butler.
the whole thing could be
passed off as a practical joke.
But nobody did.
Oh, Sir Charles Cartwright
is the actor supreme.
He is in disguise, and he played
the part but to perfection,
even adding the little detail
of painting the birthmark
on the right wrist.
And so, the Dr. Bartholomew
Strange, he dies,
and this butler escapes
by the secret passage.
And two days later,
he is strolling about
the gardens of Monte Carlo.
Now, what of the letters
of blackmail
behind the fireplace
in the room of this M. Ellis?
Sir Charles himself
uncovers them.
And the letter asking M. Oliver
Manders to fake the accident?
What could be easier
than for Sir Charles
to write the letter himself
in the name
of Dr. Bartholomew Strange?
Because he wants to bring you
all together again, hein,
so that there are many,
many suspects.
And so I return to Mlle. Wills.
En effet, mes amis,
Mlle. Wills noticed
the butler Ellis
more than anybody else
at the table that evening.
And when I interviewed her,
in this theater,
Sir Charles, at first,
he is gratified
that she spotted the birthmark.
Well, of course, he likes his
audience to notice his skill.
But then la catastrophe.
I do not think
that until that moment
Mlle. Wills connected Ellis
with Sir Charles.
But she is an observer, hein?
And when the drinks,
they are poured,
she notices not the drinks,
but the hands that held them.
And at that moment,
Mlle. Wills understood
that Sir Charles,
he was the butler,
because with or without
the birthmark,
the hand, it was the same.
And now he is worried.
He thinks she knows something
and believes
she is a danger to him.
When Sir Charles acted the death
scene at my sherry party...
Charles.
Charles!
...the face that I was watching
was that of Mlle. Wills,
and I saw a look upon that face
of complete astonishment.
And it was then that I knew
that Mlle. Wills
suspected Sir Charles,
and if Mlle. Wills suspected
Sir Charles,
then Sir Charles indeed
suspected Mlle. Wills.
And now she was in
the danger most grave.
So it was on the advice
of Hercule Poirot
that she leaves her London home.
S'il vous plaît,
entrez, Mlle. Wills.
S'il vous plaît.
Asseyez-vous.
And she was wise so to do, hein?
Because the following evening,
Sir Charles,
he drives to Tooting
to dispose of the one person
he feared could expose him.
Mlle. Wills.
And now we come
to murder victim number three,
Madame de Rushbridger.
How does she fit
into the puzzle?
It is my belief that on the day
of the sherry party
given by me, Hercule Poirot,
Sir Charles Cartwright rises
early that morning,
perhaps even at dawn,
to make the long journey
to Yorkshire
where he disguises himself
as a tramp,
gives to a small boy
the telegram addressed to me,
Hercule Poirot,
at Whitehaven Mansions.
Ostensibly
from Mme. de Rushbridger,
when on my one and only visit to
the sanatorium with Sir Charles,
I had never even mentioned
my name.
And why does he do this?
Because he needs Poirot
out of the way.
Oh, pardon, one other thing.
He even posted
a box of chocolates
to this poor woman
who knew nothing.
In fact, she would tell to
Poirot that she knows nothing.
Nothing at all.
How could she?
She was a decoy merely.
And it is for this simple reason
that she is dead?
Suddenly, I saw how this murder
of Dr. Bartholomew Strange
was not only essential
but purposeful.
Well, I'm hooked.
Oh, go on, tell me,
what was my motive
for murdering my dearest friend?
A man I had known since boyhood?
It was the doctor himself
who gave to me the clue
when he said,
"Cherchez la femme."
You know, Sir Charles,
it was obvious to me
that you were in love, deeply
in love with Mlle. Lytton Gore.
You loved her with a passion
that was so arid, so terrible.
So, why the hesitation?
Why did you not ask her
to marry you
when you were sailing
around Loomouth?
What was the obstacle, hein?
Poirot, he will tell to you.
The obstacle, it was this,
that you already had a wife.
Oh, but, of course, you enact
the role of the bachelor,
but this marriage of yours,
it took place
since many years before,
when you were young.
Long before you were
Sir Charles Cartwright,
the actor renowned,
and when your name,
it was something else.
Voyez, mes amis,
there are only two situations
in the law of our land
when a divorce,
it cannot be permitted.
The first when either
the husband or wife
is serving a life sentence
in prison
and the second
when one or either of them
is confined to a lunatic asylum.
Ah.
And, of course, Sir Charles,
you cannot kill her yourself
because immediately you would
become the prime suspect.
But what if nobody knew, hein?
Well, then, you'd be free
to marry Mlle. Lytton Gore
without ever having the need
to tell to her the truth.
But one person did know
and one person only.
Your oldest friend.
The best man at your wedding.
And so before you can re-marry,
it is necessary
that Dr. Bartholomew Strange,
your friend so dear to you,
he must be eliminated.
And Babbington?
I suppose he knew, too, hmm?
That was the one flaw
in my theory.
Because even if it was you,
Charles,
who placed the liquid nicotine
into the glass,
you could never make sure of it
reaching one particular person.
No, the poison was never
intended specifically
for the Reverend
Stephen Babbington.
No.
It was intended for anyone
who was there present.
Except, of course,
Dr. Bartholomew Strange,
who never touched the cocktail,
and Mlle. Lytton Gore.
The young lady
with whom you were in love.
You handed me my cocktail
yourself.
Have a cocktail, Egg.
This tastes slightly...
The murder of
the Reverend Stephen Babbington
was nothing more nor less
than a dress rehearsal.
Sir Charles, he is the actor.
He rehearses the murder
before he commits it.
And the rehearsal, it goes well.
Stephen Babbington, he dies,
and foul play,
it is not suspected.
Not even by Hercule Poirot.
Which is why, of course,
I was invited to go to Loomouth,
because if Poirot
suspects nothing,
nor indeed will anyone else.
Et enfin, Mlle. Milray.
You knew that your employer
conducted
the chemical experiments
in the tower in the wood.
In fact, it was you who paid
the bills for the solution
for the spraying of the roses.
But you knew he was no gardener.
And when you read
about the death
of the Reverend
Stephen Babbington,
that he was poisoned
by this very same solution,
you did not know what to do.
You had known
the Reverend Babbington
since you were a little girl.
But now you are in love
with your employer,
who is so fascinating.
But when you heard about the
death of Mme. de Rushbridger,
you decided that enough,
it was enough.
So you traveled
all the way to Cornwall
to destroy the apparatus
in the tower
to protect the man who you love.
But Poirot,
he has prevented you.
Superintendent, if you please.
What I have here, sir,
is your passport.
We know exactly
when you went to France.
And I have here a note
that proves that in
the Haburton Asylum in Essex,
there is a lady by the name
of Gladys Mary Mugg,
58 years of age,
who is your lawful wedded wife.
Is it true?
Egg...
...it's all lies.
It is true, mademoiselle.
I loved you.
God damn you.
What have you done?
What have I done?!
It is you who have deceived me!
These last two days,
they have not been genial.
You are deranged, monsieur.
Deranged.
You don't know what it's like.
People think you're so happy,
so glamorous.
Girls run after you,
beautiful girls.
You kiss them,
and then they go home.
They take off
their pretty costumes,
and they go home.
And you're alone.
I would have loved you, Egg,
till the day I died.
That's all I wanted.
Love.
Is that so much to ask?
It's not enough to kill
three people for.
My friend.
Your revels now are ended.
Oh, well.
Damn you.
Damn you all.
Don't worry, sir.
M. Manders,
I think now is the time
to take home the Lady Mary
and Mlle. Egg.
Yes, sir, of course.
You will look after her now.
I shall.
And, mademoiselle.
You fall down, hein?
But you will get up again.
A tragedy in three acts,
I think.
Oui.
A great man brought low.
I can see now I should have gone
to the police.
Don't judge me too harshly.
Ah, mademoiselle, I investigate.
I do not judge.
I've just had
a terrible thought.
If anyone could have drunk
the poisoned cocktail,
golly, it could have been me.
And there is a possibility
even more terrible,
mademoiselle.
It could have been me.