(alarm)
OW!
Hey,Ed?
- You OK?
- There's blood.
It's only a paper cut.
Uh, listen, Ed. I need to talk to you.
Ed, I... This is never easy.
And everybody down here
sure likes you a lot, Funschie.
And I know it's tough
cos you're new to this area.
Ed, I'm sorry, but I'm
gonna have to let you go.
I mean, your work is first-rate
and, like I said, you're a good guy.
But you know the story:
cutbacks and seniority.
And you're a low man on the pole.
Could I work part time?
The guys took up a collection today.
It's a hundred bucks.
Look, why don't you stay on
till the end of the week?
(lift door opens)
- Is there room here for me?
- I think we can make some.
Thank you.
(woman) Excuse me.
It's OK.
(uneven breathing)
- Hey, Ralph. How you doin'?
- All right.
Thanks for coming at short notice.
I realise the FBI's Behavioral Science Unit
mainly profiles murder suspects
still at large.
It must be odd being asked to profile
our suspects, all of whom are dead.
I am relieved the Bureau
answered our request and sent you.
In all honesty, Agent Mulder, whatever's
going on here is way over our heads.
The suspect's body is out on the sidewalk.
We're holding the security guard
who shot him.
The witnesses in the elevator
are down at the hospital.
Talk to them whenever you're ready.
I've asked all the businesses
in the building to close for the day.
We've done our best to preserve the area
for you. We've photographed the scene.
The area's been sketched,
but we haven't dusted for prints yet.
We wanted to wait for you
before collecting further evidence.
Was this damaged during the incident?
- I'll find out.
- May I see the suspect?
Things like this aren't
supposed to happen here.
A 42-year-old real-estate agent
murders four strangers?
That shouldn't happen anywhere.
Since colonial times there's only
been three murders in this area.
In the last six months,
seven people have killed 22.
Per capita, that's higher than
the combined homicide rate of Detroit,
DC and Los Angeles.
This town is not any of those places.
In Franklin, you never have to
pull off the road...
...to make way for a celebrity
driving with a gun to his head.
In each incident, the suspect was killed?
Suicide. By cop.
Each incident occurred in a public place.
The suspect went crazy
and refused to desist.
Officers used deadly force to save lives.
Were autopsies conducted
for substance abuse?
This town is mainly made up
of apple and cherry growers.
Folks here don't drink much.
They certainly don't do drugs.
The coroner's tests were negative.
(radio) This is Dispatch. Can you provide
additional backup for unit 42?
Played softball
with this guy over Labor Day.
He was one of those nice guys. Couldn't play
and didn't bitch about being in right field.
What's wrong with right field?
Always the first to shake hands at the end
of the game, whether he'd won or lost.
You gotta have an arm to play right field.
Bought a round of beers afterwards,
even though he didn't drink.
[played right field.
Let's have this analysed by the Bureau's lab.
What the hell could bring anyone to do this?
- (child) I wanna go home.
- (mother) Don't be in such a hurry.
You'll just have to wait
for the man to finish, OK?
- Mommy...
- Baby, you're bleeding.
Come on, tilt your head back.
I told you to leave it alone. OK?
Now, don't touch it or it'll bleed again.
Tilt your head back. There you go.
Lucky we had a Kleenex, eh?
Good girl.
Hey! Hey!
What the hell's wrong with you?
(Mulder) Mass murderers
are divided into two classifications:
the spree killer and the serial.
The violent outburst in a public locale...
...and the suspect's disregard
for anonymity or survival...
...define the Franklin incidents
as spree killings.
The confounding element of these profiles
is that, given their backgrounds...
...the perpetrators would be, statistically...
...more likely the victims of violent crimes
rather than the originators.
The killers were all middle-income,
responsible people...
...none with a history of violence.
Relatives reported only minor
displays of dysfunctional behaviour:
...sleep disorders, headaches,
eating difficulties.
But witnesses did report the last suspect
displayed a claustrophobic reaction.
I'm convinced
an outside factor is responsible...
...but I must concede frustration
as to a determination of the cause.
A residue on the fingers of
the most recent perpetrator was analysed...
...and reported to be an undefined
but non-toxic organic chemical
found on plants...
...perhaps remaining from gardening.
There have been reported abductee
paranoia in UFO mass-abduction cases.
I was wondering when you'd get to that.
I find no evidence of this to be the case.
The single connecting trace evidence...
...is the destruction of
an electronic device at the crime scene.
A pager, a fax machine.
A cellular phone, a gas pump digital display.
In all honesty, Scully, We never had
a more difficult time developing a profile.
There is no way to know who will be a killer.
Or who will be killed.
(whistling and chinking)
Hello?
- You're late.
- I'm sorry.
I called earlier.
A deadline came up at work.
If it's ready, I'll just
pay you and be out of here.
How did you manage
to break that, anyhow?
Oh, it's a long story.
- Did you fix it?
- It's fixed.
What do I owe you?
I'll tell you. In fixing that,
I found some other problems.
Serious problems, Mrs McRoberts.
Come back here. I'll show you.
I'm sorry... My husband's waiting for me.
- I have to go.
- OK.
But you ain't gonna go very far
unless you get this fixed.
Come here.
(mechanic whistles)
(engine starts)
This is a diagnostic test of your engine.
You're supposed to have an output
of 168 horses at 6200rpms.
You're nowhere near that.
Come over here.
Next to me. I want you to take a look at this.
Well, first of all, you're leaking oil like crazy.
Your throw rods are chattering,
valves need adjustment...
A couple of engine mounts
should be replaced.
To tell you the truth...
If you don't believe me, take a look here.
Aarghh!
Agent Mulder?
Larry Winter, county supervisor.
Uh, pardon my rubber.
Can you tell me if this murder
is more of the same?
They don't seem to be connected.
Well, should I be relieved or more scared?
I mean, is this the start of copycat killers?
Larry, it's not a copy
of the other homicides.
This wasn't a public area.
The suspect fled, covering his tracks.
The killer appears
not to have had a premeditated weapon.
They are connected.
- Mrs McRoberts?
- Yes.
This is Sheriff Spencer. I'm Agent
Fox Mulder with the FBI. May we come in?
- I'm late for work.
- You can blame me.
- Been having some car trouble?
- That's my husband's department.
May I speak with him?
He took the car to Pittsburgh for a meeting.
- Is it OK if I have my breakfast?
- It's the day's most important meal.
Um, this invoice was, uh, signed by you.
Did you pick up the car last night?
Yes.
Can you describe to me exactly how
the dashboard read-out was damaged?
Mrs McRoberts?
I did it.
- I broke it.
- Why?
Mrs McRoberts?
Did you see something in the read-out?
I can help.
Mrs McRoberts?
- Stop!
- No!
(Scully) Anomalies were found
during postmortem analysis...
...that were undetected
in previous autopsies.
Levels of adrenaline are high
in cases of violent death...
...twice as much as in victims
of natural death.
This subject's levels were 200 times normal.
The adrenal gland displayed
extensive adrenal haemorrhage,
yet not from disease...
...but rather from wear.
Other physiological evidence present
indicated episodes of intense phobia.
Analysis of the vitreous humour,
extracted from the eyeball...
...indicated the presence
of high concentration
of an undetermined chemical compound.
This compound, at its base...
...is similar to the substance analysed
earlier on a perpetrator's finger.
Although further qualitative
analysis must be performed...
...it is my opinion that this chemical,
when reacting with adrenaline...
...and other compounds
secreted during phobic episodes...
...creates a substance similar
to iysergic acid diethylamidez...
...LSD.
Pardon me. I'd like to apply for a job.
Sorry. They're not accepting
applications at this time.
Sir, may we ask you
to sign up for the blood drive?
Are you all right?
Sir?
(insects buzz)
Hmm.
In our April edition of The Lone Gunman,
we ran an article
on the CIA's new CCDTH-2138...
...fibreoptic-lens micro-video camera.
Small enough to be
placed on the back of a fly.
Imagine being a fly
on the wall of the Oval Office.
Been there. Done that.
That is a Eurasian cluster fly.
They infest vegetation
like apples or cherries
and can inflict a lot of damage to crops.
It's been irradiated to control propagation.
Or... agents of competing
agricultural corporations...
...posing as Franklin City employees, are
releasing fertile flies to destroy the crop.
No. This bug's been nuked.
It was a fine effort, though.
Have you ever come across
this chemical compound?
LSDM?
Obviously you haven't read
our August edition of TLG.
Oh, I'm sorry, boys. It arrived the same day
as my subscription to Celebrity Skin.
Come over here.
- So, Mulder, where's your little partner?
- She wouldn't come.
- She's afraid of her love for you.
- She's tasty.
Frohike, it's men like you
that give perversion a bad name.
Here. Toxic pesticides.
The chemical in that report
is called Iysergic dimethrin...
...an unreleased experimental
synthetic botanical insecticide.
- It acts as a natural pheromone.
- LSDM is sprayed on the plant...
...which invokes a fear response in the pest:
"Get out of here. There's danger."
- The insect leaves the plant.
- Why won't they release it?
Is it possible it affects
humans in the same way?
Possible?
Let me show you something.
This is actual newsreel
footage taken in the '508.
They're spraying DDT, a chemical the
government did release and determine safe.
30 years later they found out
women exposed to it
had higher rates of breast cancer.
They convinced local officials
it was safe to spray on children.
It took a decade
of bureaucratic and industry heel-dragging
before it was banned.
Different chemicals. Same stunts.
They just learned how not to be so obvious.
Hey, Frohike, can I borrow those?
If I can have Scully's phone number.
(distant rumbling)
(rumbling)
Stealth helicopters?
Experimental pesticides
responsible for violent behaviour?
I saw the chopper from two
different locations. Look at my skin.
Feel my hair. The insecticide is still on me.
I've checked up on you.
You have a penchant for "spooky" evidence.
- Don't start that crap. Don't divert blame.
- Hang on a second...
If you're the one who's responsible...
...the sooner you take responsibility,
the sooner people will stop dying.
The killers all resided
near heavily sprayed areas.
You don't live here, Mulder.
I live here. I have my heart in this town.
I have three children.
I'm not gonna dump poison on them.
Yeah, well, if it's so safe,
why was it done in secret?
- What kind of a crusade are you on?
- Answer the question. Are we spraying?
This county lives on money
generated from its crops.
Irradiated flies were not effective.
The delays to get approval would
have caused millions in crop damage.
Look at the hell they raised over Malathion.
Meanwhile, people's lives were
being ruined by a damn bug.
Ruined? 23 people are dead.
There's no proof the spray caused
violent behaviour. It was proven safe.
By who? Who proved it to you?
(door closes)
I'm sorry, Mulder, he's right.
I'd love to say I flew 300 miles
in the middle of the night...
...to prove you're about to become
the next Charles Manson.
But I find little physiological evidence...
...that states that LSDM has toxically
affected you, even after massive ingestion.
Your own autopsy says
the killer had chemical anomalies.
Yes, but you are proof that
it wasn't from exposure to LSDM.
May I see that chart, Agent Scully?
Sure.
Look here. These are normal...
(Scully) ..perhaps subjected
to repeated LSDM spraying.
Scully, are you familiar
with subliminal messages?
You mean like... sex and
ice cubes in liquor ads?
- That's paranoia.
- No, it's a fact.
Stores use subliminal messages in
their ambient music to deter shoplifting.
The Russians use electro-encephalographic
techniques to control behaviour.
- How is this connected with the spraying?
- Electronic devices were always destroyed.
- I'm still waiting.
- The insecticide LSDM...
...is known to cause fear in cluster flies.
What if it causes the same reaction
in humans?
All the perpetrators were phobic.
Taber was claustrophobic. McRoberts's
husband said she had a fear of rape.
The insecticide heightened
their phobia to an unbearable level.
The electronic devices relayed messages
that told them what to do
in order to alleviate it.
- The messages were relayed purposely.
- By who?
He's probably one of those people
that thinks Elvis is dead.
Mulder, I was wrong. Exposure to
the insecticide does induce paranoia.
I think this area is being subjected
to a controlled experiment.
Controlled by who? By the government?
By a corporation? By Reticulans?
They've done it before.
DDT in the '50s, Agent Orange,
germ warfare on unsuspecting areas.
Yes, but why, Mulder? Why intentionally
create a populace that destroys itself?
Feat
It's the oldest tool of power. If you're
distracted by fear of those around you...
...it keeps you from seeing
the actions of those above.
I just had a talk with Mr Winter.
I've persuaded him to a compromise.
He's agreed to stop the spraying...
...and to blood testing extensively
of people exposed to the spray area.
But?
But the official explanation for the testing
cannot be linked
to the side effects of LSDM.
Franklin and Venango Counties
are participating...
...in an important nationwide
study on cholesterol.
Volunteers will be coming to your door...
...or you may report at your convenience
to Franklin Community General.
The procedure is very simple and painless.
Just a little prick on the fingertip, and your
participation is complete - and appreciated.
So remember, cholesterol
screening can save your life.
So when those volunteers
come to your door, answer readily,
or you may report at your convenience
to Franklin Community General.
(door buzzer)
(door buzzer continues)
(watch alarm beeps)
And the test results on the blood samples,
did you double-check? Are you sure?
Uh-huh.
Last area just reported in.
OK, these are the sectors
that have tested negative.
These people, for one reason or another,
haven't checked out. There's about 25.
(Mulder) Only seven more to go.
This is odd.
Frustrated Jehovah's Witness?
Door's unlocked.
Here it is.
Edward Funsch. Age 52. No diploma.
No vehicle or driver's licence.
Navy radio man. Wife died ten years ago.
No kids. No known family. Just been laid off.
Medical history?
Nothing. He hasn't seen a doctor in decades.
- When was the blood tester here?
- About 10.30 this morning.
10.30?
The blood test.
I know what he's afraid of.
And I know where he's going.
Hey, wait. Stop! Stop!
Stop! Hey!
All right, all right. Hold on a second.
Thank you.
- Pardon me.
- Wait for the next stop.
- Please, I'm on the wrong bus.
Open the door! Open the door!
Open the door, dammit!
(radio) C-1, this is X-ray-4.
Negative on that north-south line.
Copy that.
If he's on it, it's gonna be this line.
- Here it comes.
- Get the uniforms out of sight.
Have you seen this man?
I picked him up.
Drove four feet and he went apewire.
- Where'd you let him out?
- Near the college.
- We'll have to wait him out.
- I don't think he's waiting.
- Scully, anything?
- Nothing.
(siren)
Get down! Get down! Everybody down!
Get down! Get down!
(loudspeaker) Everybody remain calm.
Stay away from this building.
Stay down.
Take cover.
I've seen that. I've seen that and
I don't want to see that again, baby.
(gunshot)
All units, forthwith. Franklin College.
Shots fired. Send emergency vehicles.
(gunshot)
Put it down!
- Don't kill me.
- Then put it down, Ed.
I can't. They won't let me.
I know they won't, Ed.
I know they won't let you.
Then...
You make me put it down, then.
You do it.
If you don't put it down...
...I'm gonna have to shoot you.
Or you're gonna have to shoot me.
There's gonna be blood everywhere.
Oh... Ah.
Agh!
- Don't kill me.
- It's all right.
Agent Scully will
examine him at the hospital.
I want unrestricted access
to him for questioning.
Mulder, you know more about
what happened to him than he does.
(computer code)
(ringing tone)
Scully.
Hello?
Mulder, is that you?
Mulder, where are you?
Mulder?
(child) I made this!