(tape rewinding)
(Scully) Mulder, it's me. I just had something
incredibly strange happen.
This piece of metal that they took out of
Duane Barry, it has some kind of a code on it.
I ran it through a scanner
and some kind of a serial number came up.
What the hell is this thing, Mulder?
It's almost as if...
It's almost as if somebody
was using it to catalogue him.
(Scully gasps, glass smashes)
- (man) Come on!
- (Scully) Mulder! I need your help! Mulder!
(man) They're taking that
down to the lab now.
- Mulder!
- Lady...
I need your help! Mulder!
Mulder!
- (man) You can't disturb the crime scene.
- It's my daughter's apartment.
Just let me go. I have to get through.
I have to get in!
Mrs Scully?
She's not in there.
Where is she?
(police radios)
Holly Reardon reporting live. Police have
refused to identify the kidnapping victim.
We have received unconfirmed...
(Mrs Scully) I knew it would happen this way.
I had this dream
about Dana being taken away.
It's so strange.
I, uh... I was gonna call her...
...but I was afraid I was gonna scare her.
She would've laughed at me, anyway.
She doesn't believe in
that kind of thing, you know.
According to the reports, Agent Scully states
that Duane Barry's propensity for violence...
...is due to brain damage
from a bullet wound in the head.
Is this the operational opinion?
Yes, sir.
Is there another?
He's convinced he's going to be
abducted by aliens.
That by taking someone to the abduction site,
he won't be abducted himself.
That he's following orders
from alien voices in his head?
(Kryfiek) Yes.
Well, that's an interesting spin
on the Nuremberg defence.
Which explanation do you
subscribe to, Agent Mulder?
There's a question of
how he could've gotten to her.
And you think these alien voices told him?
Scully was carrying a piece of metal that
was removed from Duane Barry's abdomen.
He described it as a tracking device.
Agent Scully... thought that
you had made a miscalculation...
...in Duane Barry's psychosis. Is that true?
Yes. But that still doesn't explain
how he could have found her.
- Where would he be taking her?
- (Mulder) I don't know.
He talked about a mountain.
He wasn't specific about the location.
Well, however he got to her,
he took Agent Scully's car and her weapon.
We all understand the seriousness of this
matter and should proceed ahead quickly.
- Turn over your files to HRT.
- I'd like to brief them myself.
- Go home. You've been up all night.
- Sir, I know Duane Barry.
- I've been in his head. I know how he thinks.
- You're too close to this case!
If we can use you, we will.
- Sir...
- That's an order, Agent Mulder.
Make sure he gets home safely.
(car radio) You'll see him in your nightmares
You'll see him in your dreams
He'll appear out of nowhere
And he ain't what he seems
You'll see him in your head
On the TV screen
Hey, buddy, I'm warning you to turn it off
He's a ghost, he's a god
He's a man, he's a guru
You're one microscopic cog
in his catastrophic plan
Designed and directed by his red right hand
(Siren)
Sir, could you turn off your radio?
I would, Officer, but I gotta keep going.
An FBI ABP has been issued for a suspect
in the abduction of an FBI agent.
Sir, I asked if you mind turning that off.
OK. But could you just give me the ticket
now so I can go? I gotta be someplace.
Where?
I'm not sure,
but... they'll tell me when I get there.
Sir, put your hands on
the steering wheel where I can see 'em.
You don't understand.
They're waiting for me. I can't be late.
Put your hands up and exit the vehicle.
No, I gotta keep moving.
Please.
For your own sake.
Don't stop Duane Barry.
Sir, put your hands up.
(gunshot)
(car door opens and shuts)
(footsteps)
Right there.
Back it up a few frames.
OK, now magnify this area.
- Oh, my God.
- She's still alive.
Print this up.
- (Barry) I just wanna go back to the place.
- (Mulder) What place?
Where it started.
Where they first came and got me.
(Mulder) Where is that?
A mountain.
We went, uh... up and... up.
Ascending...
...ascending to the stars.
- ...ascending to the stars.
- Coffee'?
Yeah.
Thanks.
- How'd you sleep?
- I didn't.
(Barry) They're not taking Duane Barry again.
A mountain.
We went, uh... up and... up.
Ascending...
...ascending to the stars.
- ..ascending to the stars.
- What is it?
- Where was that patrolman killed again?
- Rixeyville, Virginia. Route 229.
- Doesn't it lead to the Blue Ridge Parkway?
- I don't know.
What?
"Ascend to the Stars. Skyland Mountain."
- You know where he's goin'?
- Get your car. Meet me downstairs.
- Where are we going?
- Get your car.
- What about Skinner?
- I'll deal with Skinner.
He thinks Scully's been taken to Skyland
Mountain. I'll hold him off till they locate her.
Wait, here he comes. I'll be in touch.
Come on, let's go.
(truck horn)
Hey!
- You're dozing off. Maybe I should drive.
- I'm fine.
- Well, you haven't slept yet. I have.
- I said I'm fine.
You know, Chernobyl, Exxon Valdez,
Three Mile island...
...they were all linked to sleep deprivation.
The department of transportation estimates
that over 190,000 fatal car crashes...
...every year are caused by sleepiness.
Did they estimate how many people are
put to sleep listening to their statistics?
I'm just trying to keep you awake.
Look, if Skinner sends in the whole cavalry,
Duane Barry might go over the edge.
You're right.
If we find him first,
we'll notify the Bureau. All right?
Yeah. You really think
he tracked her down with that implant?
Well, that's the easiest explanation.
- It's also the most implausible.
- Is there another possibility?
Somebody could've given him her address.
I don't know who.
There's our turn-off.
- Have you seen this guy?
- Yeah, he was here.
He's wanted for kidnapping a federal agent.
Did you let him go up on the tram?
It's shut down in the summer.
I told him to take the back road.
- How long ago?
- 45 minutes.
- Did he have a woman with him?
- No.
- How long does it take to drive?
- Over an hour.
- You gotta get me up there.
- No. No way.
We just got done refitting the cable.
It hasn't been tested with passengers yet.
- You have to drive.
- I don't have time.
- You don't have a choice.
- No. You don't have a choice.
I can't stop you from going up there.
But if there's a problem with the cable,
I'm shutting this thing down.
I'm not gonna be responsible for your death.
What are you doing?
Stay here. And whatever happens,
don't let him stop the tram.
You hit your "run" and "up" button
on the panel.
"Speed indicator" controls your ascent.
Now, when you wanna slow down...
Don't crank it faster than 15!
What the hell's he doing? I told him not
to go that fast. Base to car one. Pick up.
- (machinery whirs)
- D'you hear that sound?
At this speed the cable can't hold.
This is base. Please pick up the handset.
Can you hear me?
Slow it to 15 or I'll shut this thing down.
Base to car one. Pick up.
- Base to...
- Go ahead.
- Slow it down.
- You're breaking up.
Slow it down or the cable will jump the tower.
Second tower's coming up.
Slow it through the next tower.
- How close is he?
- He should be up top in a minute.
There he is.
What are you doing? Turn us back on.
Krycek, what's happening down there?
Krycek, do you read me?
Tell the operator to restart the tram.
Hello?
I've got him stalled up there.
I'll hold until you advise.
Is there an emergency system on board?
Can you read me down there?
Can anyone read me?
(car radio) ..with scattered rain
and intermittent thunder showers.
Look for highs tomorrow around 65 degrees,
with tonight's low dipping to 48 degrees.
That high-pressure ridge has moved
east now. There will be unstable activity.
Joining me now for
the business report is Susan Roberts.
The dollar turned on the foreign exchange
markets, while closing stronger here.
Gold dropped almost two dollars, in spite of
the speculation about inflationary trends.
Silver was down 80 cents.
(news report continues)
(man laughing)
Yes!
- Federal agent!
- Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
- Freeze!
- Yes!
I said freeze! Where is she?
I'm free, you son of a bitches!
You can't touch Duane Barry any more!
Don't move! Don't move!
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Where is she? Where'd you leave her?
- They took her.
- Who?
Them! I told you they were gonna
take somebody else.
They did!
No!No!No!
No! No!
No!
(man) A search and rescue chopper
has found them on the mountain.
We've sent out five teams to search for
that missing federal agent.
Some water?
You can wait outside.
Now what happened after
you took her out of the trunk?
We walked a little ways
up to the top of the mountain.
Right where you found me.
- Then where'd you take her?
- I didn't.
They cm.
That was the deal. Her instead of me.
- Did you kill her?
- No.
I swear.
- How'd you get this?
- From the ship.
- What ship?
- You saw it.
- I saw a helicopter.
- They were here!
I'm not lying to ya!
There they are! Ask them.
They know what happened.
- Sit down, Duane.
- No! You've gotta stop 'em!
Hurry! Hurry! They were just out there!
They were right outside! They...
- Duane, settle down!
- No!
They'll tell you where she is!
The military's in on it. Just ask 'em!
Did you hurt her? Did you hurt her?!
- No!
- What is this?
(coughing)
I'm sorry.
They had to take her.
I hope they're not hurting her...
too much with the tests.
I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
- What's the matter? What did he say to you?
- He's given me nothing.
Were you out here alone?
Yeah. Why?
Nobody goes in or out of that room.
Hey, Mulder...
(high-pitched whine)
(man) Rescue two...
- What are you doing?
- I heard him...
Come here. Come here.
I heard him gagging. He couldn't breathe.
- He said you choked him.
- No one is to interrogate the suspect.
- Except you?
- Except me.
- Did you ask him about Scully?
- Yeah.
- What did he say?
- He started whistling "Stairway to Heaven".
- Keep an eye on him.
- OK.
- You've got Duane Barry?
- Yes, sir.
Agent Mulder,
you disobeyed my direct order.
(man) Call the paramedics!
- What happened?
- He was gagging.
Duane. Duane.
Duane.
(paramedic) Coming through!
- Respiration?
- Nothing.
Start CPR.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three...
Excuse me?
I'm Agent Mulder. I'd like a copy
of this man's autopsy report.
I'm sorry. It's still incomplete.
- Are you the pathologist?
- Yes.
Can I ask what your preliminary findings are?
Um... second-degree burns on the face,
contusions about the neck, bruised larynx.
If I had to list cause of death at this point,
I'd have to say asphyxiation.
Were you expecting something else?
- You haven't run a toxicological yet?
- They should be finished shortly.
I'd be interested to see what you find.
When will it be on file?
- Later this morning.
- I'd like a copy as soon as possible.
Well, I'm sorry. You'll have to go
through regular military channels.
What do you mean, "military"?
- You're not FBI?
- Quantico's under militaryjurisdiction.
There wasn't an FBI pathologist
available this morning.
Skinner's expecting my report on the
Duane Barry incident. What do I tell him?
The truth.
- What do you mean?
- Confirm Mulder's version of events.
You've earned his trust.
You have to preserve it.
- For how much longer?
- Until your assignment is completed.
If Mulder's such a threat,
why not eliminate him?
- That's not policy.
- It's not?
After what you had me do?
Kill Mulder and you risk turning
one man's religion into a crusade.
- What about Scully?
- We've taken care of that.
How?
- We tell you what you need to know.
- I've a right to know.
You have no rights,
only orders to be carried out.
If you have a problem with that,
we'll make other arrangements.
The victim appears to have expired
from prolonged hypoxemia...
...secondary to asphyxiation. Of several
etiologies, the most likely is strangulation...
...due to the presence
of contusions and a bruised larynx.
- Do you want to speak, Agent Mulder?
- I didn't kill him, if that's what you mean.
- But you attacked him?
- I was interrogating him about Agent Scully.
- He wasn't cooperating, so I pushed him.
- And you lost control.
Momentarily. But then I left the room.
He was very much alive. I spoke to him.
Agent Krycek spoke to him.
Agent Krycek says he entered the room
because the suspect was gagging.
Is Agent Krycek asserting
that I killed him too?
No. He corroborates your story. But the fact
is we've got a dead suspect, Agent Mulder...
...and no other plausible cause of death.
OPC wants both of you to take a lie-detector
test. You're to report there immediately.
There is another plausible cause of death.
- Which is?
- Poisoning by injection or ingestion.
Poisoning?
You won't find that
on the Navy pathologists report.
- What are you saying?
- That the autopsy is incomplete.
That the military covered up
the toxicological findings.
- And why would they do that?
- Because they know where Scully is.
Why are you so paranoid, Mulder?
Oh, I don't know... Maybe it's because
I find it hard to trust anybody.
- Alex? Alex? Can I borrow your car keys?
- Why? Where are going?
- There's somebody I gotta see.
- We're scheduled...
I know. Just give me the keys. Please.
Thanks.
You wasted a trip, Mr Mulder. There's
nothing the senator can do for you now.
- What?
- Not without committing political suicide.
Why? Do they have something on him?
They have something on everyone, Mr
Mulder. The question is when they'll use it.
- I need his help.
- No one can help you now.
Your channels of appeal
and recourse are closed.
Your predecessor could've helped me.
You know, don't you?
- You know what's happened to her.
- This reaches beyond any of us, Mr Mulder.
- Even my predecessor.
- I want an answer!
Why kill Duane Barry
if there was nothing to hide?
- You mean the government?
- There are no answers for you, Mr Mulder.
They only have one policy:
Deny everything.
- This is a serious allegation, Agent Mulder.
- Only so far as it is true.
"Agent Krycek was hired by an outside
agency to impede a federal investigation...
...and may be responsible for the death
of a suspect in a capital murder case."
It goes on.
"And the possible murder of
the tram operator at Skyland Mountain."
There's a lot of blood on this document. Are
you standing behind this going on record?
Yes, sir.
Then you damn well better
have the facts to back it up.
I need to see Agent Krycek, immediately.
I can't protect you, Agent Mulder.
Past a point, this will become
a larger Bureau matter.
All right, what have you got?
I found this in Agent Krycek's car.
He doesn't smoke.
Agent Krycek was the last person
with Duane Barry before he died.
He was also the last person to see
the tram operator before he disappeared.
When I got to the top of Skyland Mountain,
I saw an unmarked helicopter in the area.
I believe Krycek gave away
the whereabouts of Duane Barry and Scully...
...to whoever he's working with.
- And who is that?
- I don't know.
The military? Some covert organisation
within the government?
Whoever the man who smokes
those cigarettes works for.
Why?
Because Agent Scully got too close
to whatever they're trying to deny.
Because she had hard and damning evidence
- that metallic implant - in her possession.
Or because her termination would prevent
further involvement with me and my work.
Do you think Agent Scully's dead?
I don't know.
How far do you think they'd go?
What do you know about Krycek?
- I didn't give him the assignment. I only...
- (phone)
Yes.
Thank you.
Agent Krycek didn't show up
for work this morning.
His home number has been disconnected.
That's it? He's gone?
He just disappears into the woodwork?
So it would appear.
Who are these people who can murder with
impunity and we can't do anything about it?
- Let it go.
- Like hell!
- There's nothing you can do.
- What can you do about it?
There's only one thing that I can do,
Agent Mulder.
As of right now, I'm reopening the X-Files.
That's what they fear the most.
Agent Mulder? Thank you for calling me.
- Sorry I don't have better news.
- Do you know something? ls Dana OK?
I don't know anything more about it.
I know you're doing all you can.
I had that dream again last night,
about Dana being taken away.
I can't tell you how it scares me.
It's probably scarier
when you stop having the dream.
Don't you think?
I found this.
It's something l...
I never considered about her.
If she was... if she was such a sceptic...
...why did she wear that?
I gave it to her on her 15th birthday.
Don't you want to keep it?
When you find her, you give it to her.
Subtitles by Visiontext
(Child) I made this!
ENGLISH HOH