Trees.
Surely among the most magnificent
of all living things.
Some are the largest organisms on Earth
dwarfing all others,
and these are the tallest of them all.
The deciduous and coniferous woodlands
that grow in the seasonal parts of our planet
are the most extensive forests on Earth.
Their sheer extent stuns the imagination.
The barren snows of the Arctic.
A thousand miles from the North Pole,
and heading south.
This is the very first place
that trees can grow.
To begin with the conifers are sparse
but soon they dominate the land.
This is the Taiga Forest.
There are as many trees here,
as in all the world's rainforests combined.
The Taiga circles the globe
and contains a third of all the trees on Earth.
It produces so much oxygen, that it
refreshes the atmosphere of the entire planet.
At the Taiga's northern extent
the growing season can last
for just one month a year.
It can take fifty years for a tree
to get bigger than a seedling.
It's a silent world
where little stirs
But there are occasional signs of life.
Stories written in the snow.
The prints of an Arctic fox
and the hare it might've been stalking.
A female polar bear and her two cubs.
Some animals are so difficult to glimpse
that they're like spirits.
One could live a lifetime in these woods
and never see a lynx.
The cat must roam hundreds of miles
in search of prey
and may never visit
the same patch of forest twice.
It's the very essence of wilderness.
With so few prey animals here,
life for a hunter is particularly hard.
Creatures are scarce
because few can eat conifer needles.
The moose is an exception.
Growth is so difficult
that conifers protect their precious leaves
by filling them with resin.
That reduces water loss,
but it also makes them very distasteful.
At least the conifer's seeds are edible
but they're protected within armor plated cones
and it takes a specialist to reach them.
The crossbill's extraordinary beak
can prise apart the scales,
so that it's tongue can extract the seeds.
Birds are fortunate.
When the seasonal crop is gathered,
they can fly south
But one animal is so expert at survival
in this frozen forest
that it stays here and is active
all year long.
In local folklore,
the wolverine is a link to the spirit world
and a cross between a bear and a wolf.
In reality,
it's a huge weasel.
It's bulk helps to conserve body heat
and also broadens it's menu.
It's so big and powerful,
it can even bring down an adult caribou.
For it's size, it's said that the animal can eat
more in one sitting than any other
which is why it's also known as the glutton.
Being gluttonous here
is a very effective strategy.
It's wise to eat all you can,
when you can
and when even a glutton can't eat more
it stores what's left for later,
in the surrounding deep freeze.
Spring in the ice forest.
The capercaillie can also digest conifer needles
but feeding is not it's priority at the moment.
Like gladiators,
the males square up for a battle.
Each may have just a single chance
to impress a female.
Neither can afford a lapse in concentration.
The injured loser may not survive.
The inhabitants of this great wilderness
may live and die
without ever having contact with humanity.
Long may it be that way.
The northern forest may be the largest on Earth
but to see coniferous trees
that have reached their full potential
you must travel a thousand miles south of here.
The Pacific Coast of North America.
The land of hemlock, douglas fir
and giant redwood.
Here, water is never locked up in ice
and even if rains fail
the needles can extract moisture
from the fogs that roll in from the sea.
The Sun's energy powers these forests
not for one month as it does in the Taiga
but for half the year.
These conifers grow at ten times the rate
of those near the Arctic
and they live for thousands of years.
One grove of redwoods in California
contains three of the tallest trees on Earth.
This one is over a hundred meters high,
the size of a thirty story building.
These forests were growing here
long before humans walked the Earth.
They were in their prime
twenty million years ago
and existed before the Swiss Alps
or the Rocky Mountains were even raised.
There is more living matter in a forest
of giant conifers, than in any tropical rainforest
but it's all contained within the trees.
These are as inedible as those in the Taiga
so animals are still scarce,
but they are present.
A pine marten. It's spring,
the best time of year for a marten to find food.
Bird's eggs are a seasonal snack
and for a short time, there's plenty of them
Sometimes perhaps, too many.
But to live here permanently,
the marten needs a more reliable food source.
Squirrels fit the bill.
They thrive here on the pine cones
and although these are also seasonal
they can be stored and eaten
throughout the year.
The squirrels are busy mating
Good news for the hunter.
A distracted squirrel, is a vulnerable squirrel.
But, this time, the amorous couple is safe.
There is a loner stocking his larder,
who will be the easier target.
Early summer,
and great grey owl chicks are fledging.
Adults can only raise young here
in years when the seasonal vole crop
is big enough to support them.
The moment has arrived for their first flight.
Leaping from the world's tallest trees
is not for the faint hearted.
If you're going to fall here
it's quite a good idea to do it in stages.
The ground is no place for an owl.
If he's to climb to the top of his class
he'll need to persevere
So now, let's have another go.
The American conifer forests
may not be the richest in animal life
but their trees are extraordinary.
This giant sequoia, a relative of the redwood,
is the largest living thing on Earth.
Known as General Sherman,
it's the weight of ten blue whales.
Higher up in the nearby mountains, bristlecone pines,
the oldest organisms on the planet.
Some have been here
for five thousand years.
They were alive before the pyramids were built
and were already three thousand years old
when Christ was born.
Across the Equator, in the southern hemisphere
there are forests that mirror those of the north.
Here in South America
araucaria trees or monkey puzzles
are like the conifers of the Taiga.
They have waterproof scales,
instead of needles
and their cones look a little different
but the principles are the same.
Slender billed parakeets
rather than crossbills, extract their seeds.
Where the growing season is longerm,
there are alerce trees the redwoods of the south.
As in the frozen north, the Valdivian forests
of Chile support very few animals
but that is the end of the similarity.
This is a bizarre world of miniature creatures.
The pudu, the world's smallest deer
feeds on the giant leaves of the gunnera plant.
The female is just thirty centimeters high
at the shoulder
and her infants are hardly bigger than kittens.
The male must stay alert.
There are hunters here who would snatch his young.
Another miniature.
The kodkod cat.
It's the smallest cat in all the Americas
and a young pudu would be a feast for it
But, with the male on guard,
the kodkod must lower his sights.
Moths are hatching.
They're the last of the summer.
The tiny cat
should be able to score with these.
No one knows why the creatures here are so small
but at least they can survive on meager rations.
You might call this
a game of cat and moth.
As winter approaches in Chile
spring is arriving in the northern hemisphere.
These are the deciduous forests of Homme.
Dormant throughout the winter,
they now undergo
one of the most magical transformations
in the natural world.
By late spring
the landscape is wrapped
in a vibrant fresh green.
Here, instead of conifers,
there are broad leaved trees
and that makes the character of this forest
entirely different.
Being broad, these leaves trap
much more light than needles
but they're also thin, soft and edible.
And others can eat
the leaf eaters.
It's spring in the great broad leaved forests
of Eastern Europe and Asiatic Russia.
The mandarin ducks are courting.
The female mandarin nests in a tree hole
and when it's time for everyone to leave
she leads the way.
The ducklings are only twenty four hours old.
It's a long drop,
and a few calls of encouragement are required.
Two down
seven to go.
There are still two missing.
All present and correct.
But they won't be safe
until they reach water
and the forest pool
is almost a mile away.
By June the days are at their longest
and all across the northern hemisphere
the broad leaves are hard at work.
On the east coast of North America
it seems like any other summer's evening
but tonight is special.
After seventeen years underground
creatures are stirring.
The nymphs of the periodical cicada
have been biding their time.
Now they march like zombies
towards the nearest tree, and start to climb.
At first, there are merely thousands
but soon, more than a billion
swarm all over the forest.
The biggest insect emergence
on the planet is underway.
They invade the upper branches,
where they climb out of their external skeletons
and assume their adult winged form.
At first they're white and soft, but they have
until dawn to complete their transformation.
After an absence of seventeen years,
the forest is now overrun by cicadas.
The adults are clumsy
and very edible.
For turtles and other inhabitants of the forest
this is a feast they're lucky to see
once in their lifetime
and they gorge themselves while they can.
Times have never been so good.
The cicadas have no defenses
and virtually offer themselves to their attackers.
The stream of insects is so relentless
that soon all the predators are full
to the point of bursting
and still the cicadas come.
With the predators overwhelmed
the survivors can achieve their purpose.
After mating, the adults lay their eggs
and then their job is done.
In just a few days they will all die
and the forest will fall silent.
The cicadas here, will not be heard again
for another seventeen years.
Having fed the predators, the cicadas
leave one final gift for the forest itself.
The nutrients in a generation of cicadas
are returned to the soil, all at once
and the trees enjoy a marked spurt in growth.
This may be the single largest dose
of fertilizer in the natural world.
In the great
broad leaf forests of Eastern Europe
the days are beginning to shorten,
and a primeval sound heralds the onset of autumn.
Male red deer are starting their rut.
The air is heavy with the scent of females.
The rules are simple.
Winner takes all.
Across the northern hemisphere
the deciduous forests are changing.
Leaves that have provided food and shelter
since the spring, are now shed.
In the broad leaf forests of Russia
winter is particularly severe
but there will always be some
who benefit from hardship.
Black vultures scavenge from the carcass
of a seeker deer
that has died of cold or starvation.
These endangered birds are visitors.
They've come down from the north to escape
the even colder conditions in Siberia.
An Amur leopard.
The rarest cat on Earth.
Winter is a difficult time for this hunter.
There are no leaves for cover
and no young prey animals.
This female has the added pressure,
of having to provide for her one year old cub.
It'll be another twelve months,
before he'll be able to fend for himself.
The bickering vultures
have abandoned the carcass.
It's a valuable discovery for the leopards.
But the cub doesn't share
it's mother's sense of urgency.
The vultures have left behind
plenty of good meat
but it's stiff with frost.
The mother works to open the hide,
and make feeding a little easier for her cub.
There are only forty Amur leopards
left in the wild
and that number is still falling.
The harshness of the winter here
hinders their increasing numbers.
It takes one of these females
longer to raise her young to independence
than it does a leopard in Africa.
If the mother can sustain her cub
for a few more weeks
spring will bring an increase in prey
and her task will lighten.
For all the inhabitants of this seasonal forest
the long, cold wait is nearly over.
Spring in a deciduous woodland
is special.
With no leaves overhead, the rays of the sun
strike the forest floor directly
and their warmth rouses plants
from their winter sleep.
The ground living plants are in a hurry.
Before long the trees above
will come into leaf and steal their light.
Their flowers decorate the forest floor
as they advertise their sweet nectar
to the newly emerged insects.
The spring blooms of the deciduous woodlands
have no equivalent
in either the great conifer forests,
or the tropical jungles.
Within a matter of weeks
the canopy has closed
and only a few wheeling shafts of light
penetrate the woodland.
In the treetops, the broad leaves
rapidly expand to their full size
to make the most of summer
while it lasts.
Then, after a few months,
the days begin to shorten again
and the trees must shut down
and shed their leaves in preparation
for the cold dark time ahead.
Great tracts of North America flush red
as the season progresses.
The effect is so spectacular
and so extensive
that it can be seen from space.
The threat of winter frost is not
the only reason for trees to shed leaves.
These forests stand in the tropics.
Here day length never changes
but the dry season is so severe
that the trees can't afford to loose
the amount of water
that would evaporate from their broad leaves,
so the leaves must be shed.
The forest resembles a European woodland
in mid winter
but the heat is overpowering,
and it's inhabitants, unfamiliar.
For the creatures of India's teak forests,
these are desperate times
but salvation is at hand.
The mahwa tree is about to bloom.
It's flowers are full of liquid
making them irresistible.
The mahwa is an oasis
in a hot dry desert.
Those that fly or climb
are not the only ones to get a share.
Chital deer follow the langur monkeys
collecting the flowers that fall.
The monkeys welcome the deer,
for deer are unrivaled at spotting predators.
If they are relaxed,
it must be safe to come down to the ground
and gather the food that lies there
but it's not wise to travel far
from the sentinels.
Tropical Madagascar.
The wet season.
It's now that the baobab trees
regrow their leaves
and collect water to store in their huge trunks,
ready for the dry season ahead.
The prehistoric shape of these trees
is rightly famous
but few have ever witnessed
the baobab's real magic
for that happens at night
and high in the treetops.
Flush with water, the baobab prepares itself
for an unforgettable display.
Once started the foot long flowers
can open fully in less than a minute.
As the flowers open,
the creatures of the forest wake.
The mouse lemurs have been hibernating
throughout the dry season.
With the return of rains
it's time to get busy.
A dozen share this tree hole,
but there's plenty of room.
The world's smallest primate
is no bigger than your hand.
High in the branches above,
the baobab's nectar is starting to flow.
A drink of this sugary energy packed liquid
is an ideal way for the lemurs
to start their day.
Liquid oozes from the flower's center
and trickles down the petals
But the nectar is not intended for lemurs.
These giant hawk moths
are the drinkers the tree needs to attract.
As they sip, moving from tree to tree,
so they transfer pollen and fertilize the flowers.
Nectar was an excellent first course
for the lemurs
but moths are the main dish.
The moths are very important to the lemurs
for they will replenish the fat reserves
that the lemurs need to survive the barren dry season.
The lemurs might seem to be a pest
for the baobab.
They kill it's pollinators
and rob it of it's nectar
but they do give something in return.
For, as the wrestle with the moths,
their fur inevitably becomes dusted with pollen
so they, too, become pollinators.
As the alternation of wet and dry seasons
brings change to some tropical forests
so the progression of summer to winter
dictates life in more temperate regions.
Whether trees have needles or broad leaves
it is their ability to survive annual change,
that has enabled them to cover
such vast areas of the Earth
and made the seasonal forests
the greatest forests of all.