Our planet's continents are fringed
by shallow seas.
Rarely more than two hundred meters deep
they lie on the continental shelves
which may stretch sometimes
for hundreds of miles
before the sea floor drops into
deeper darker waters.
All together they constitute
a mere eight percent of the world's oceans
but they contain the vast majority
of it's marine life.
A male humpback whale sings to attract a mate.
The whales have just returned
to their breeding grounds
in the shallow seas of the tropics.
The calf is no more than a few weeks old.
Despite being three meters long
and weighing nearly a ton
he is nonetheless vulnerable.
but his mother watches over him
and, as he begins to tire,
she supports him close to the surface
so that he can breathe more easily.
These shallows around the equator
are excellent nurseries.
They're warm, calm, and contain
very few predators.
The playful calf is now drinking
five hundred liters of milk a day
but his mother must starve.
There is nothing for her to eat here.
Like many tropical shallow seas
these crystal clear waters
are virtually lifeless.
They receive year round sunlight
but they lack the nutrients
essential for the growth of plankton.
The mother will be trapped here
for the next five months
until her calf is strong enough to make
the journey to the feeding grounds, near the poles.
Coral reefs are oases in a watery desert.
Most tropical shallows are barren
but these coral havens contain one quarter
of all the marine life on our planet.
Reefs are the work of polyps
tiny colonial animals like minute sea anemones
yet the great barrier reef is so big
it can be seen from the Moon.
It's actually two thousand separate reefs
that together form a barrier
stretching for over a thousand miles
along Australia's northeastern coast.
Despite it's vast size
this reef does not contain the greatest variety
of marine life on the planet.
For that one must travel north to Indonesia.
There are individual reefs in Indonesia
that contain almost as many kinds of fish
as live in the whole of the Caribbean.
There are also ten times the number
of coral species.
Corals thrive in these waters
with the help of microscopic plants, algae
that grow within the tissues of the polyps
and the polyps feed by snaring passing
morsels with their tentacles.
At night, the algae are inactive but then,
the polyps put out even more tentacles
so coral in effect feeds around the clock.
This well balanced alliance
brings benefits to both polyps and algae
and between them, they turn the barren seas
into rich gardens.
The Indonesian reefs
contain such a variety of life
because they lie at a giant crossroads.
This is the meeting place for different seas
the Indian Ocean and the Pacific.
Here everything demands a closer look.
On the surface of this sea fan,
there are two polyps that are not polyps.
They're pygmy sea horses, the world's smallest,
less than two centimeters high.
They are males, settling a territorial dispute,
by head butting.
An electric flash?
No, the display of a file clam.
Perhaps this extraordinary pulsation
of the clam's fleshy mantle
is a warning to frighten away nibbling fish,
but no one really knows
And there are snakes here, too,
lots of them.
These are banded sea crates.
They lay their eggs on land
but they hunt here in the water.
They're too slow to catch fish
in a straight chase
so they seek prey that is hiding
in the nooks and crannies of the coral.
Their bite is highly venomous
and paralyzes their victims.
And on this reef
the snakes do not hunt alone.
Shoals of yellow goatfish and trivali
are seeking similar prey
And they attract the snakes' attention.
As one group of hunters searches the reef
they're joined by the other.
At least thirty snakes
have now joined the caravan.
The big fish scare the prey into cracks
and there the snakes can catch them
And anything fleeing from the crates will swim
straight into the mouths of the waiting trivali.
There's nowhere to hide.
As the raiders scour the reef,
more and more snakes join the hunt.
This cooperation between snakes and fish,
spectacular though it is,
has only recently been observed, for it only happens
on the most remote reefs in Indonesia.
Perhaps such hunting alliances
were once a common sight
but today no more than six percent
of Indonesia's reefs are in their pristine state.
Beyond the coral
stretches a world of shifting sand.
Out there with nowhere to hide
survival is not easy
and camouflage can be crucial.
If this wasn't moving, you might think
it was a shell or a rock. In fact it's an octopus.
A gurnard.
It's huge pectoral fins disguise it's shape
and they can also help in clearing away sand
when searching for food.
The jawfish hides underground.
The wonderpus octopus on the other hand
has such a powerful bite
that it has a special warning display
to tell others to keep out of it's way.
Here and there,
plants manage to take root
and they're cropped by green turtles.
Seagrasses are the only flowering plants
that have managed to grow in the sea
although they put out a few ribbon like leaves
they produce very extended networks
of fleshy stems, risomes,
that are buried in the sand.
At their lushest
they can transform the sea bed
into an underwater meadow.
The largest expanse grows in the shallow waters
of Shark Bay, in Western Australia.
These vast aquatic grasslands
stretch for fifteen hundred square miles
and, like terrestrial prairies,
they support herds of grazers.
Dugongs.
Dugongs are the largest herbivores in the sea.
They can be three meters long
and weigh half a ton
and they eat nothing but seagrass,
mostly the fleshy risomes,
which they excavate with their mobile lips.
A herd can clear a patch of seagrass
the size of a football pitch
in a single day.
Food is not evenly distributed
in the tropical shallow seas
and it can take a lot of finding
but bottlenose dolphins are inquisitive,
energetic,1 and very intelligent
and they have discovered a shoal of baitfish.
Together, they ride a wave,
using it to carry them into the shallows
and there, it will be easier to make the catch.
In Western Australia
these dolphins have taken on
an ever tougher challenge.
The fish have taken refuge close to the beach
where the water is only a few centimeters deep.
Tail slapping is a method dolphins often use
to stun their prey
but it doesn't seem to work here.
The fish are tantalizingly close
but they're still out of reach,
so the dolphins try another technique.
Vigorously pumping their tails,
they work up some speed
and then, they hydroplane.
Their momentum carries them right through
the shallowest waters, and onto the fish.
Now they're in real danger of being stranded
but fortune favors the brave.
Younger dolphins lie alongside, watching
but so far only eight individuals here
have mastered this daring technique.
Although most life in tropical waters
is concentrated around the coral reefs
and the seagrass meadows,
there are some spectacular exceptions.
The desert of Bahrain
seems a very unlikely place
to find a crowded bustling colony of seabirds
But every year, a hundred thousand
socotra cormorants gather here to breed.
It's swelteringly hot
and only vigorous panting can prevent the birds
from fatal overheating.
This hardly seems a good place to rear young
but at least, there are no
land based predators here.
The only source of trouble
is likely to be the neighbors
so each nest is built
just beyond pecking reach
But what about food?
There's only bare sand
and the warm shallow sea beyond.
Neither seem likely to produce enough
nourishment to support bird life on this scale.
The answer is blowing in the wind.
Sand whipped up by Shamals offshore winds
blows into the seas of the Arabian Gulf.
With the grains come nutrients,
which act as fertilizer
and they transform the shallow sea
into a rich fishing ground
So, paradoxically, it's the roasted
sands of Arabia that prevent the gulf
from being another desert in the sea.
The whale calf is now five months old.
He's almost doubled in size
and his days in his tropical nursery
are coming to an end.
It has been a warm and safe place
in which to grow up
but there's nothing to eat here
for his mother.
She has been living off her fat reserves
for the last eight months
and she's close to starving.
She must leave now,
while she still has enough energy
to guide and protect her calf,
on the long voyage ahead.
All across the tropics,
humpbacks are heading away from the Equator
towards the rich temperate seas of both
the southern and the northern hemispheres.
These are colder, rougher,
and more dangerous waters.
Mother and calf must stay close.
They can send sound signals to one another,
above the roar of the ocean
by slapping fins on the surface.
In winter, the temperate seas
are lashed by violent storms.
The turbulence stirs the water,
and draws nutrients up from the depths
but nutrients alone can not support life.
There must also be sunlight.
In the spring, as the sun
daily climbs higher in the sky
the algae start to grow.
Blooms the size of the Amazon Rainforest
turn the seas green.
Individually the algae are tiny
but together, they produce three quarters
of all the oxygen in our atmosphere.
They're eaten
by an array of bewildering creatures.
Salps appear in the plankton soup.
Individuals link together to form chains
which can stretch for fifteen meters.
Pumping water through their bodies
they strain out algae and other edible particles.
Comb jellies cruise through the water.
They too flourish in this seasonal soup
and for short periods, they appear
in astounding numbers.
Krill, shrimp like creatures.
By weight they're the most
abundant animals on the planet.
A single swarm can contain
two million tons of them
and that is a lot of fish food.
The shallow temperate seas support
the greatest concentrations of fish on our planet.
Huge shoals migrate from their
overwintering grounds in the depths
to feed in these rich waters.
It's these shoals that support most
of the world's sea mammals.
Sea lions have all the agility and speed needed
to collect what they want
and seemingly delight in doing so.
Dusky dolphin,
often in pods two hundred strong
work together to reap the harvest.
They break up the shoals into smaller,
more manageable balls, and all the hunters benefit.
By midsummer, the surface nutrients
have all been absorbed.
The algae die
and the food chain collapses.
In a few special places, however
the temperate seas sustain these levels of life
throughout the summer.
Along the coast of California,
ocean currents carry a constant supply
of nutrients up from the depths
to the surface layers.
These upwellings fertilize forests of giant kelp,
that thrive in the summer sunshine.
The algal towers are
as high as a three story house
and they can grow by half a meter a day.
Life in the kelp is as full of drama,
as in any other forest
but the cast is less familiar.
An army of sea urchins is mounting an attack.
The urchin plague strikes at the kelp's holdfasts
their crucial attachments to the rock.
Holdfasts are extremely tough, but each
urchin has five teeth, which are self sharpening
and are replaced every few months.
Urchins fell vast areas of kelp forest
creating clearings know as urchin barrens
yet barrens is a poor description.
Millions of invertebrates invade the seabed.
The most fearsome predator here is a giant.
The sunflower starfish is a meter across,
with an appetite for brittle stars.
It uses it's feet to taste for prey.
When it's actions are speeded up, it becomes clear
that the predator's fondness for the brittle stars
is almost matched by the brittle stars
ability to get out of the way.
Sand dollars flat sea urchins
cluster together as a defense
But it doesn't seem to work
against the sunflower starfish.
The predator extrudes it's stomach, and wraps it
around it's victims liquefying their soft parts.
Nothing is left of them,
except their white skeletons.
The Californian upwellings are seasonal
and relatively small
but in Southern Africa they're so big
they create seas rich enough to support
colonies of over a million seals.
The Benguela Current sweeps along
the western coastline of Southern Africa
driving nutrient rich waters up to the surface
and then, at the southern tip of Africa it meets
the Agulhas Current, arriving from the east.
The result: even richer waters.
The seals here
thrive on a diet of fish and squid.
In temperate seas there may actually
be more squid than fish.
These are chokker squid,
and they lay their egg capsules
in sandy shallows bathed by the warmer
Agulhas Current.
Each capsule contains a hundred tiny squid.
Within a few days
they develop spots of pigment
which, when they're adult, they will use
to communicate with one another.
With females continuing to lay eggs
and males still preoccupied with repelling rivals,
the squid drop their guard.
Stingray.
Short tailed stingray
can be up to two meters across.
They're the largest of all the stingrays,
and they have appetites to match.
Another predator is on the prowl.
The aptly named ragged tooth shark.
Raggies grow to three meters long, but they share
these waters with a shark twice their size.
The great white.
The largest predatory fish on the planet.
Each dawn cape fur seals leave their colony
to go fishing.
To reach the open sea,
they must cross a narrow strip of water
and that is patrolled by great whites.
Each seal is indeed swimming for it's life.
The shark relies on surprise.
The great white's turn of speed
is powered by a high metabolism.
They only thrive in cold temperate seas
for only these waters contain sufficient food
necessary to fuel such a ravenous predator.
As you travel towards the poles
north or south
the colder, stormier seas
can become even richer.
Midway between South Africa
and the South Pole
lies the isolated island of Marion.
The island sits in the infamous
"roaring forties"
where incessant gale force winds
draw nutrients up from the depths
ensuring plenty of food for king penguins.
The kings are returning from a three day
fishing trip, with food for their chicks
But first they must cross a crowded beach,
threading their way between gigantic
and bad tempered elephant seals.
The two hundred thousand penguins
breeding here
are testament
to the richness of the fishing.
King chicks are dependent on their mothers
for over a year
and this puts a great deal
of pressure on the parents.
Being flightless, the returning penguins
must cross the open beach on foot.
Fur seals, that have come to the beach to breed,
are waiting for them.
Fur seals normally live on krill
but these have now acquired
an unexpected taste for blubber rich penguins.
Penguins may be featherweights by comparison
but they have razor sharp bills
and a feisty character.
The seal could easily lose an eye.
The only safe way to grab a penguin
is from behind, and the birds are well aware of that.
Both animals are clumsy on this terrain
but the penguin has the more to lose.
Made it.
Two out of three penguins
survive the seal attacks
and succeed in reaching
their ever hungry chicks.
The humpbacks are nearing the end
of their epic journeys.
After two months and thousands of miles,
they're entering the polar seas
both in the north and the south.
In the far north, winter is over at last
and the ice is starting to melt.
The Aleutian Island chain
running west from Alaska
is the gateway to the Bearing Sea.
With the retreating ice, rough weather
and ferocious currents stir up these shallow seas.
Add sunshine and the mix
is spectacularly productive.
Five million shearwaters have flown almost
ten thousand miles from Australia to get here.
In all eighty million seabirds
come here for the summer
the greatest concentration
to be found anywhere on Earth.
The humpbacks have finally arrived.
The giant shearwater flocks
hunt the krill swarms
sometimes diving to depths
of forty meters to reach them.
A large humpback
eats three tons of krill a day.
The polar seas in summer
are the most productive on the planet
and the whales gorge themselves
round the clock.
The fat reserves they lay down now
will keep them alive during the year to come
but it may not always be this way.
Fish and krill stocks
are declining so rapidly
that spectacles like this
may soon be part of history.
Once the mother and calf have reached
their feeding grounds, they will separate.
With luck, the calf will make
the epic journey across the oceans
from equator to pole another seventy times
cruising back and forth
between the shallow seas
where life proliferates so abundantly
on our planet.