Human beings venture
into the highest parts of our planet at their peril.
Some might think that by climbing a great
mountain they have somehow conquered it,
but we can only be visitors here.
This is a frozen, alien world.
This is the other extreme.
One of the lowest, hottest places on Earth.
It's over a hundred metres below
the level of the sea.
But here, a mountain is in gestation.
Pools of sulphuric acid
are indications that deep underground
there are titanic stirrings.
This is the Danakil Depression in Ethiopia,
lying within a colossal rent in the Earth's surface
where giant land masses
are pulling away from one another.
Lava rises to the surface
through this crack in the crust,
creating a chain of young volcanoes.
This one, Erta-Ale, is today the longest
continually-erupting volcano on the planet.
A lake of lava that has been molten
for over 100 years.
These same volcanic forces
also created Ethiopia's highlands.
Seventy million years ago, this land was just as
flat and as deep as the Danakil Depression.
Molten lava, rising from the Earth's core,
forced up a huge dome of rock 500 miles wide.
The Roof of Africa.
Over millennia, rain and ice carved the rock
into a landscape of spires and canyons.
These summits, nearly three miles up,
are home to some very remarkable mountaineers.
Gelada baboons.
They are unique to the highlands of Ethiopia.
The cliffs where they sleep
are for expert climbers only.
And geladas certainly have the right equipment,
the strongest fingers of any primate
and an utterly fearless disposition.
But you need more than a head for heights
to survive up here.
A day in the geladas' life reveals
how they've risen to the challenge.
For all monkeys, morning is grooming time,
a chance to catch up with friends.
But unlike other monkeys,
geladas chatter constantly while they do it.
It's a great way to network
while your hands are busy.
But these socials can't go on for too long.
Geladas have a busy daily schedule
and there's work to be done.
Most monkeys couldn't live up here.
There's no fruit and few insects to feed on.
But geladas are unique.
They're the only monkeys in the world
to live almost entirely on grass.
They live in the largest assemblies
formed by any monkeys.
Some groups are 800 strong and they crop
the high meadows like herds of wildebeest.
The geladas graze alongside walia ibex,
which are also unique to these highlands.
These rare creatures are usually very shy,
but they drop their guard
when the geladas are around.
You might expect that grazers
would avoid each other's patch,
but this is a special alliance
from which both partners benefit.
It's not so risky to put your head down
if others are on the lookout.
Ethiopian wolves.
They won't attempt an attack in broad daylight.
But at dusk, the plateau becomes
a more dangerous place.
With the grazing largely over,
there's a last chance to socialise
before returning to the sleeping cliffs.
An early warning system
puts everyone on the alert.
Their day ends as it began,
safe on the steep cliffs.
The Ethiopian volcanoes are dormant
but elsewhere, others still rage.
Volcanoes form the backbone
of the longest mountain chain on our planet,
the Andes of South America.
This vast range stretches 5,000 miles
from the equator down to the Antarctic.
It formed as the floor of the Pacific Ocean
slid beneath the South American continent,
buckling its edge.
At the southern end
stand the mountains of Patagonia.
It's high summer.
But the Andes have the most unstable
mountain weather on the planet
and storms can erupt without warning.
Temperatures plummet and
guanacos and their newborn young
must suddenly endure a blizzard.
Truly, all seasons in one day.
A puma, the lion of the Andes.
Pumas are usually solitary and secretive.
To see a group walking boldly
in the open is extremely rare.
It's a family, a mother with four cubs.
She has just one brief summer
in which to teach them
their mountain survival techniques.
Rearing four cubs to this age
is an exceptional feat,
but she does have an excellent territory,
rich in food and water.
Although the cubs are now
as large as their mother,
they still rely on her for their food.
It will be another year before
the cubs can hunt for themselves.
Without their mother's skill and experience,
they would never survive their first winter.
Battered by hurricane-force winds,
these slopes are now lifeless.
Further north, they hold other dangers.
Moving at 250 miles an hour,
an avalanche destroys everything in its path.
In the American Rockies, 100,000 avalanches
devastate the slopes every winter.
This huge mountain chain
continues the great spine
that runs from Patagonia to Alaska.
The slopes of the Rockies, bleak though they are,
provide a winter refuge for some animals.
A mother grizzly emerges from her den
after six months dozing underground.
Her two cubs follow her
and take their first steps in the outside world.
These steep slopes provide
a sanctuary for the cubs.
A male bear would kill and eat them
given the chance
but big animals find it difficult to get about here.
Males may be twice the size of a female
and even she can have problems.
Her cubs, however, make light of the snow
and of life in general.
But the mother faces a dilemma.
It's six months since she last fed
and her milk is starting to run dry.
She must soon leave the safety
of these nursery slopes
and lead her cubs away from the mountain.
If she delays, the whole family will risk starvation.
Summer reveals the true nature of the Rockies.
Stripped of snow,
the peaks bare their sculpted forms.
Only now can mountaineers
reclaim the upper reaches.
Two miles up, the crumbling precipices
seem devoid of life.
But there are animals here.
A grizzly bear.
It seems to be an odd creature
to find on these high rocky slopes.
It's hard to imagine
what could have attracted it here.
At this time of the year,
bears should be fattening up for the winter,
yet they gather in some numbers
on these apparently barren slopes.
They're searching for a rather unusual food.
Moths.
Millions have flown up here
to escape the heat of the lowlands
and they're now roosting among the rocks.
Moths may seem a meagre meal for a bear,
but their bodies are rich in fat
and can make all the difference
in a bear's annual struggle for survival.
Another battle is being waged here
but on a much longer time scale.
These loose boulders
are the mountains' crumbling bones.
The Rockies are no longer rising
but slowly disintegrating.
All mountains everywhere
are being worn down by frost, snow and ice.
The Alps were raised some 15 million years ago
as Africa, drifting northwards,
collided with the southern edge of Europe.
These spires are the eroded remains
of an ancient seabed
that once stretched between the two continents.
But these are just the Alpine foothills.
The range at its centre rises to three miles high
and is crowned with permanent snows.
The Matterhorn, its summit too steep
to hold a snowfield.
Mont Blanc, the highest peak in Western Europe.
The distinctive jagged shapes of the Alps
were carved by those great mountain sculptors,
the glaciers.
Immense rivers of moving ice, laden with rock,
grind their way down the mountains,
gouging out deep valleys.
They're the most powerful
erosive force on our planet.
A moulin, a shaft in the ice opened by meltwater
as it plunges into the depths of the glacier.
Like the water running through it,
the ice itself is constantly moving,
flowing down the valley with unstoppable force.
Alpine glaciers may seem immense,
but they're dwarfed by those in the great ranges
that divide the Indian subcontinent from Tibet.
This is the boulder-strewn snout
of the giant Baltoro Glacier
in the Karakoram Mountains of Pakistan.
It's the biggest mountain glacier on Earth,
43 miles long and over three miles wide.
This huge, ice-filled valley is so large
it's clearly visible from space.
This is the greatest concentration
of peaks over five miles high
to be found anywhere on Earth.
They're the most dangerous mountains of all.
K2 and her sister peaks
have claimed more lives than any others.
The peaks here rise so precipitously,
the glaciers are so steep and crevassed,
that few except the most skilled mountaineers
can penetrate these ranges.
Markhor gather for their annual rut.
Males must fight for the right to breed,
but on these sheer cliffs,
any slip by either animal could be fatal.
A snow leopard, the rarest of Himalayan animals.
It's a female returning to her lair.
These are the first intimate images
of snow leopard ever filmed in the wild.
She greets her one-year-old cub.
Her den is well chosen.
It has exceptional views of the surrounding cliffs.
On these treacherous slopes,
no hunter other than the snow leopard
would have a chance of catching such agile prey.
A female with young makes an easier target.
Her large paws give an excellent grip
and that long tail helps her balance.
Silently she positions herself above her prey.
She returns with nothing.
Golden eagles patrol these cliffs
in search of the weak or injured.
With a two-metre wingspan,
this bird could easily take a young markhor.
Eagles hunt by sight and the thickening
veil of snow forces them to give up.
For the leopard, the snow provides cover
and creates an opportunity.
The worsening weather
dampens the sound of her approach,
allowing her to get within striking distance.
It was an act of desperation
to try and catch such a large animal.
Wolves have made a kill,
giving other hunters a chance to scavenge.
The worst of the blizzard
brings success for the snow leopard.
But having descended so far to make the kill,
she has a gruelling climb to get back to her lair.
The cub must be patient.
It will be a year before
it has the strength and skill
to kill for itself on these difficult slopes.
The snow leopard is an almost mythical creature,
an icon of the wilderness,
an animal few humans have ever glimpsed
for its world is one we seldom visit.
The Karakoram lie at the western end of a range
that stretches across a tenth of our planet,
the Himalayas.
These, the highest mountains in the world,
like other great ranges,
were created by the collision of continents.
Some 50 million years ago,
India collided with Tibet,
thrusting up these immense peaks
which are still rising.
This vast barrier of rock and ice is so colossal
it shapes the world's climate.
Warm winds from India, full of moisture,
are forced upwards by the Himalayas.
As the air rises, so it cools, causing clouds to form
and the monsoon is born.
At high altitudes, the monsoon rains fall as snow.
Here, at the far eastern end of the range in China,
one inhabitant endures
the bitter winters out in the open.
Most other bears
would be sleeping underground by now
but the giant panda
can't fatten up enough to hibernate.
Its food, bamboo, on which it totally relies,
has so little nutritional value
that it can't build up a store of fat
like other bears.
Most of the creatures here
move up or down the slopes with the seasons,
but the panda is held captive by its diet,
for the kind of bamboo it eats
only grows at this altitude.
But these forests hold fewer challenges
for the more mobile.
The golden snub-nosed monkey,
like the giant panda, lives only in China.
Their thick fur allows them to survive
at greater altitudes than any other monkey.
And when the cold bites,
they have these upper slopes to themselves.
Even if you have a warm coat,
it apparently helps to surround yourself
with as many layers as possible.
But at least these monkeys have a choice.
If they tired of tree bark and other survival food,
they can always descend
to lower, warmer altitudes
and not return until spring.
As the snows retreat, trees come into bloom.
Cherry blossom.
Rhododendrons. Here in their natural home,
they form great forests and fill the landscape
with the colours of a new season.
These forests are host
to a rich variety of springtime migrants.
Beneath the blooms, another display.
It's the mating season for oriental pheasants,
Himalayan monal,
tragopan and blood pheasant.
Musk deer make the most
of a short flush of spring foods.
This male smells a potential mate.
The red panda, rarely glimpsed in the wild.
It was once considered a kind of raccoon
but is now believed to be a small mountain bear.
By midsummer, its larger more famous relative
has retreated into a cave.
A giant panda nurses a tiny week-old baby.
Her tender cleaning wards off infection.
She won't leave this cave for three weeks.
Not while her cub is so utterly helpless.
Progress is slow, for milk produced
on a diet of bamboo is wretchedly poor.
Four weeks old and the cub is still blind.
Its eyes do not fully open
until three months after birth.
But the chances of the cub
reaching adulthood are slim.
The struggle of a giant panda mother
to raise her cub is a touching symbol
of the precariousness of life in the mountains.
On the highest summits of our planet,
nothing can live permanently.
The highest peak of all, Mount Everest.
Five and a half miles
above sea level and still rising.
The roof of our world.
Of those humans who've tried to climb it,
1 in 10 have lost their lives.
Those that succeed can stand
for only a few moments on its summit.
The Nepalese call it,
"A mountain so high no bird can fly above it."
But each year, over 50,000 demoiselle cranes
set out on one of the most
challenging migrations on Earth.
To reach their over-wintering grounds in India,
they must cross the Himalayas.
By late morning,
ferocious winds are roaring past the peaks.
The cranes must gain height
to avoid the building storm.
They've hit serious turbulence.
They must turn back or risk death.
A new day and a new opportunity.
The flock stay in close contact
by calling to one another.
Weak from lack of food and water,
they use thermals, rising columns of warm air,
to gain height.
For many, this is their first journey
across the Himalayas.
For some, it will be their last.
The golden eagles have been expecting them.
The eagles work in pairs
to separate a young crane from the flock.
It escapes the clutches of one
and is caught by another.
But even a young crane is a heavy prize
and the eagle has to struggle to control it.
The mother can wait no longer.
This is a desperate race
against worsening weather.
The rest of the flock battle on.
In the final ascent, every wing-beat
becomes an exhausting struggle.
At last, they are over the highest barrier
that lies in their way.
But like all who visit the world
of the high mountains,
they dare not linger.