© anoXmous
@ http://thepiratebay.sx/user/Zen_Bud
This is our planet's hothouse.
The jungle.
The tropical rainforest.
Forests like these occupy only three percent
of the land
yet they're home to over half
of the world's species.
But how do so many different kinds of plants
and animals
find the space here to live
alongside one another?
On the dark, humid forest floor
the jungle appears to be lifeless.
Often the only signs of life
are what you hear.
A male blue bird of paradise
is advertising for a mate.
It's quite a performance
but he's not the only bird of paradise here
keen to make an impression.
There are nearly forty different kinds
on the island of New Guinea
each with a display
seemingly more bizarre than the rest.
A riflebird of paradise.
Like many jungle animals,
birds of paradise avoid competing with each other
and these do so by living in different parts
of this jungle covered island.
The six plumed bird of paradise
displays in his special clearing, on the forest floor.
The magnificent bird of paradise
favors the low branches of bushes.
His female is modestly dressed.
The male has a good set of lungs
but he'll have to do more than
flutter his eyelids, if he wants to impress her.
It'll all depend on his performance.
The females may be dull looking
but they're very picky
and it's time for a really close inspection.
His right side looks fine...
but what about his left?
Pretty impressive,
but is he magnificent enough?
Oh dear. Her departure says it all.
Generations of choosy females
have driven the evolution
of these remarkable displays.
The more extravagant a male is,
the more likely he'll be noticed.
New Guinea lies in a warm tropical belt
that girdles our planet around the equator.
With abundant rainfall
and twelve hours of daylight
three hundred and sixty five days a year,
it's here that rainforests flourish.
Surprisingly only two percent of the sunlight
filters down to the forest floor.
Down here seedlings struggle to grow
but the gloom is not eternal.
The death of a forest giant
is always sading
but it has to happen
if the forest is to remain healthy.
The sudden blaze of sunlight
will bring life to the forest floor.
A single hectare of rainforest
may contain as many as 250 species of tree.
That's nearly ten times the number
that grow in Britain
and the thirst for light
triggers a race for a place in the sun.
There's no time to waste.
A seed that may have fallen
only a few days ago, now bursts through the leaf litter.
With so many competitors,
getting a good start is critical
but each plant has it's own particular strategy
for making the most of this rare opportunity.
The seeds of hardwoods are quick to germinate
but, like the fabled tortoise,
their strategy is to be slow and steady.
Vines and other climbers put all their energy
into rapid vertical growth, rather than girth
though they'll need to be well supported.
The climbers' strategy looks chaotic
but there's method in their madness.
Their growing tips circle like lassoes,
searching out anchors for their spindly stems.
They put coils in their tendrils
so that if their support moves,
they will stretch and not snap.
But the frontrunners at this stage,
the first to fill the clearing,
are pioneers like the macaranga.
Their immense leaves capture
huge amounts of sunlight, so fueling their growth.
As a result the macarangas grow
a remarkable eight meters a year
surging ahead of almost all their rivals.
In the race for the top sport
hundreds will start
yet few will ever reach the finishing line,
their growth cut short by the diminishing light.
In less than four years,
the gap will have gone
but that's not the end of the race.
The ultimate winners are the tortoises,
the slow and steady hardwoods.
When the short lived pioneers have fallen
it's the hardwoods that take their place,
and a fifty meter giant, like this one,
may keep it's place in the sun
for another two hundred years.
At the top, is the canopy,
the engine room of the jungle.
It's up here that most of the animal life
in the rainforest can be found
But despite the apparent abundance
of vegetable food, gathering it is seldom easy.
With no real seasons
each tree flowers or fruits
at a different time of the year
which means that food is very widely spaced.
Monkeys, like these tamarinds,
must search the canopy for all kinds of food
if they're to survive.
but across the world's rainforests
there's one type of fruiting tree
that always delivers:
the fig.
Wherever they grow, figs are a magnet
for the great diversity of animals.
In the Amazon, the first to appear
are the spider monkeys.
These large primates
are big fig eaters
But they won't have the tree
to themselves for long. Others will want a share.
like the diminutive emperor tamarinds.
The tamarinds love figs too, but being petite
means they're easily scared off.
Squirrel monkeys are also small
but they have strength in numbers.
Their timeshare on the tree may be short,
so their tactics are more smash and grab.
Capuchin monkeys are the bully boys
in these forests
and they want the ripe figs for themselves.
Figs are one of the few trees
that fruit the year round
so when other food is scarce, these fruits
are always available somewhere or other.
Even for leaf eaters, like howler monkeys
the ripe figs are just too good to miss.
And howlers are too big
for the capuchins to chase off.
Figs are so popular, that as many as 44
different kinds of bird and monkey
have been seen working a shift system
on a single tree.
Because fruiting trees are so valuable,
many monkeys are territorial
And if you live in the treetops
there's perhaps no better way
of staking your claim to a territory, than this.
The calls of the siamang gibbons begin
as a duet
between the dominant male and female.
The rest of their families soon join in,
and it results in a frenzy of activity.
The calls can carry over a mile,
and their message is clear.
They tell any neighboring siamangs
this is our territory. Keep out.
Up here the calls of siamang gibbons
seem to dominate the airwaves
but with the jungle's incredible diversity
there are countless others
trying to be heard too.
Every layer seems to beat to a different tune.
In the early morning
the forest's chorus is particularly rich.
Sounds travel further in the cooler air
But few calls can penetrate as far
through the dense vegetation as this one
the deep bass solo of a male orangutan.
In the middle of the day
little stirs in the jungle
and the hot dense air muffles the sound.
As the afternoon wears on,
a different set of players begin to warm up.
Insects work in harmony, timing their calls
to fall between the notes of others.
Many singers stick to precise schedules
and right on cue the six o'clock cicada.
Night brings out a whole new orchestra.
The cacophony of competing calls
seems deafening to us
but frogs ears are tuned
to hear only the calls of their own kind.
The songs of courtship echo from all around.
Male gliding leaf frogs
leap from the treetops.
To slow their descent,
they use their huge webbed feet as parachutes.
These large tree frogs
spend most of their lives in the high canopy
and only come down when it's time to breed.
Once settled,
they begin to serenade their unseen females.
Now it's time for the females
to make their move.
There's no shortage of suitors,
but this female has already made her choice.
She's heading towards the loudest call,
because loud calls come from big frogs
and big is best, but to reach him she must run
the gauntlet of a gang of smaller suitors.
Their only chance of mating
is to make a sneaky interception.
He's scored.
But with more females arriving all the time,
it's not over until the fat frog stops singing.
Feet, so vital for gliding,
are now put to other uses.
Two's company,
three's inconvenient
but in any case, all male frogs
are equipped with dry thumbs
which enable them to get a vice like grip
on their moist partners.
It's a case of first come first served.
Living in such a humid environment,
means jungle frogs are less tied to puddles and pools
and these even lay their eggs out of water.
There's little chance of them drying out
and up here they're safer from predators.
Surprisingly, it doesn't rain every day
in the rainforest
but more still falls here
than anywhere else on Earth.
On average,
over two meters a year.
A single tree can suck up
hundreds of tons of water each year
But the trees can't use all this water
so, much of it returns to the air as vapor,
forming mist and clouds.
In the Amazon, the largest unbroken stretch
of rainforest in the world,
half of all the rainwater that falls,
comes from clouds produced by the trees themselves.
With so much rain, it's not surprising
that many of the worlds largest rivers
are found in rainforests.
Inside the forest, the high humidity
creates the perfect conditions
for a strange world, where life is built on decay.
Amoeba like slime molds cruise the surface,
feeding on bacteria and rotting vegetation.
Fungi also flourish on decay.
These are the fruiting bodies of the fungi,
the only visible sign
of a vast underground network
of fungal filaments.
In temperate forests, the buildup of leaf litter
creates rich stores of nutrients.
That however, doesn't happen here.
Nutrients that reach the soil
are leeched out by the rain
but fungi are connected to tree roots
by their underground filaments
and by quickly consuming the dead
they help to recycle crucial minerals
straight back into the trees.
And this recycling happens faster here,
than anywhere else on the planet.
There are thought to be nearly a million
different types of fungi in the tropics.
The vast majority still unknown to science
But one thing's for certain
without fungi, rainforests could not exist.
Nothing goes to waste in the rainforest.
The fungi become food for others
like these beetle larvae.
Finding the fungus isn't a problem
for the grubs
since their caring parents
actually show them the way.
Incredibly, 80% of all insects
live in jungles
fewer more successful than the ants.
There can be 8 million individuals in a single hectare.
but jungle ants
don't have it all their own way.
These bullet ants are showing
some worrying symptoms.
Spores from a parasitic fungus
called cordyceps
have infiltrated
their bodies and their minds.
It's infected brain
directs this ant upwards
then, utterly disorientated,
it grips a stem with it's mandibles.
Those afflicted,
that are discovered by the workers
are quickly taken away and dumped
far away from the colony.
It seems extreme,
but this is the reason why.
Like something out of science fiction
the fruiting body of the cordyceps
erupts from the ant's head.
It can take three weeks to grow
and when finished,
the deadly spores will burst from it's tip
then, any ant in the vicinity
will be in serious risk of death.
The fungus is so virulent,
it can wipe out whole colonies of ants
and it's not just ants
that fall victim to this killer.
There are literally thousands
of different types of cordyceps fungi
and remarkably, each specializes
on just one species
but these attacks do have a positive effect
on the jungle's diversity.
Since parasites like these stop any one group
of animal getting the upper hand.
The more numerous a species becomes,
the more likely it'll be attacked by it's nemesis
a cordyceps fungus.
With so much competition,
jungles have become the home of the specialist.
Now this animal, in the island of Borneo,
is one of the most unusual.
It's a colugo, or flying lemur,
though this is something of a misnomer
as it doesn't actually fly
and it certainly isn't a lemur
in fact nobody's quite sure
who it's closest relative is.
The colugo depends on a diet of young leaves
and to find enough of them,
it must move from tree to tree.
The leaves are not very nutritious, but then,
getting around doesn't use much energy.
In a single night, a colugo might have to
travel as far as two miles
but that task is made easier
by it's superior gliding skills.
The secret of success
in the competitive jungle is specializing
and this has led to the evolution
of some very intimate relationships
between plants and animals.
These are pitcher plants
also from Borneo.
Adapted to living in very low nutrient soils
the pitcher plant gets most of it's nourishment
from insects lured to nectar glands
on the underside of the lids.
Once onboard, the waxy sides of the pitcher
ensure there's little chance of escape.
Most slip to a watery grave.
At the bottom of the pitcher
glands secrete enzymes
which help to digest the corpses,
so feeding the plant.
But not all visitors have a fatal attraction
to the pitchers.
The red crab spider spends it's entire life
in the pitchers, hanging on with threads of silk.
Instead of building a web, it relies on
the water filled pitcher to trap it's food.
When an ant falls in,
the spider simply waits for it to drown
and then abseils down for a spot of fishing.
Alive, this ant would be far too dangerous
for the spider to tackle
so, using the pitchers as traps,
means it can get bigger meals
and the spider doesn't rob the pitcher
of everything.
The digested remains of it's booty
will end up in the water
providing instant food for the plant.
Other food, like mosquito larvae,
seems to be out of reach
but the spider has another sup rising trick.
By taking it's own air supply
trapped in a bubble
the crab spider can actually dive
to the very bottom of the pitcher.
Once the prey is captured, the spider
hauls itself back up it's silken safety line.
The pitcher is a one stop shop for this spider,
but it's not alone.
In the jungle there's competition for everything,
even a small water filled pitcher plant.
Such specialists create
the jungle's remarkable diversity
but finding enough food to survive
is so challenging
that most animals living here tend to be small
though there are exceptions.
This is the Congo in Africa.
It's a vast wilderness
and the least explored of all jungles.
From up here the forest looks similar to the ones
that grow in the Amazon or Southeast Asia.
but down below
there are some unexpected sights.
Crisscrossing this forest,
are countless miles of highways
and they were made by something big.
Forest elephants roam great distances
in their search for food
but to survive, they must emerge
from the gloom of the forest.
And clearings like this one,
are a magnet for elephants from far and wide.
These elephants live in much smaller groups
than their savanna cousins.
This might be the first time that one group
will have seen another for a month.
For the adult males it's a welcome break
in an otherwise largely solitary existence
and they're not the only animals
attracted to the clearing.
Forest buffaloes and red river hogs
are also regular visitors
as are bongos, which are very difficult to see
outside these clearings.
All these large forest animals have come here
to collect an essential element of their diet
that lies buried beneath the mud.
And the elephant's trunk
is the perfect tool for reaching it.
To get what they seek
the prospecting elephants must first
blow away the covering layer of silt.
Satisfaction at last.
They're collecting
a particular kind of clay
that contains vital minerals
scarce in their natural diet.
It may be mud, but there's just nothing
quite like it for enriching the blood.
The clay also helps to absorb the toxins
found in many leaves that the elephants eat.
There are other benefits to coming here.
These clearings are the only places
where the forest elephants
can get together in such numbers.
When they return to the forest, they will have to go
their separate ways, once more.
If large animals are rare in jungles
then groups of large animals
actually living together, are even rarer.
This posse of hunters is not only formidable,
it's also very large.
In their search for food
chimpanzees move effortlessly
between the forest floor and the canopy.
They're one of the few jungle animals
able to do so.
Figs are a vital part of a chimpanzee's diet
and some just can't seem to get enough of them.
But there's something special
about this stretch of forest in Uganda.
Fruit is actually abundant
and a lot of food supports lots of chimps.
At a hundred and fifty strong,
this community of chimps
is the biggest yet found in Africa.
Their numbers are so large, that they need
a big territory, lots of fig trees
and they're willing to fight for it.
These calls announce the start of a raid
into land controlled by their neighbors.
As they leave their core zone, the patrol
goes silent, occasionally stopping to listen.
Signs of the enemy are detected
and examined closely.
The chimp militia are now
at the very edge of their territory.
All need to be on maximum alert.
Then it's wait and listen.
An unfamiliar chimp call
raises the tension.
It's an uncertain time. The size
of the rival group is as yet unknown.
Not far away the neighbors
are feeding in a fig tree
oblivious to the approaching dangers.
The patrol moves off
with a sense of purpose.
They must remain silent
until they close in on their rivals.
The attack is on.
To intimidate their opponents, the aggressors
scream and drum on buttress roots.
Several males corner an enemy female.
It's a ferocious attack,
and she's lucky to escape with her life.
Others are not so fortunate.
The battle won,
a grizzly scene unfolds.
An enemy youngster
has been caught and killed.
The carcass is shared between
members of the group, and eaten.
Killing a competitor makes sense
if you want to protect your food supply
but exactly why they cannibalize
the dead chimp, is not fully understood.
It may simply be a chance
for some extra protein.
Teamwork has brought this
group of chimps great success
but they'll soon reach
the limits of their power.
The competition for resources ensures
that no one species dominates the jungle.
The rainforest's great diversity
has come at a cost.
It has made them the most finely balanced
ecosystems in the world
only too easily upset and destroyed
by that other great ape
the chimpanzee's closest relative
Ourselves.
© anoXmous
@ http://thepiratebay.sx/user/Zen_Bud