The frozen seas are worlds
unto themselves.
Beneath their ceiling of ice
they have an eerie,
almost magical stillness, cut off
from the storms that rage above.
In the winter, the feeble slanting
rays of the sun bring little warmth
and the temperature seldom rises
above minus fifty degrees Centigrade.
For much of the year,
it is dark and cripplingly cold.
Yet, there is life here.
At both ends of the earth...
the Arctic and the Antarctic.
For most animals, whether they
live in or out of water,
the winters, when much of the sea
is frozen, bring the greatest challenge.
The Northern hemisphere.
It's February, and as the Earth
tilts on its axis,
the sun's rays creep
slowly northwards
and the Arctic emerges
from its harsh winter.
The Arctic is a frozen ocean
surrounded by continents
and when the surface of the sea
between the continents freezes
from shore to shore, land predators
walk out onto it - to hunt.
It's early March and the sea
is still covered with ice.
But there are patches of open water.
Polynyas that never freeze over.
Here, where tidal currents
are squeezed between islands,
the water movement is so strong
that ice cannot form.
Walruses spend the
winter in polynyas.
Here they have permanent
access to the air,
but they can also retreat to
the sea to shelter to hunt.
Other sea mammals overwinter
in the polynyas as well
in this one, a young bowhead whale.
Here the current is really fast
and the shifting ice is dangerous.
This whale became trapped when
ice encircled it last autumn.
There is no food here, but a whale
must breathe and the only place
that it can do so, for miles around,
is in this tiny hole.
It's living entirely on its reserves
of fat, but now they are dangerously low.
It will be some months yet,
before it can escape.
Elsewhere, other whales
have also been trapped.
These are belugas.
Their tiny hole in the ice
has been kept open,
not by currents but by
the belugas' continuous movements
as they rise to breathe.
Open water is now some
twenty miles away.
It will be two months yet
before the ice melts.
The belugas are extremely thin.
And most of them are horribly scarred.
But their wounds were not
inflicted by the ice.
A whale would be a huge prize for
any meat-eating hunter and these belugas,
trapped by the ice,
are within reach of polar bears.
Well aware of the danger, the belugas
stay submerged as long as they can.
But they can only hold their breath
for about twenty minutes.
Catching a four-metre long whale
that weighs one ton is no easy task
even if that whale is
weakened by starvation.
But a beluga is well
worth waiting for.
Day by day, as the hole
gets bigger,
it becomes increasingly difficult
for the bear to land a whale.
Keeping its fur in good condition and
free from salt is important for warmth
and the bear uses snow
like blotting paper.
These belugas have been attacked by many
bears over the last six months
and some have been caught.
It may have taken a long time and
a lot of patience, but a catch,
when it's made, brings abundant
rewards of energy rich blubber.
Gulls rely on bear-kills
at this time of the year
and the colour of blood staining the
ice attracts them from a long way away.
The remaining belugas still have
a long wait before they are released
from their prison and
the threat of slaughter.
Arctic foxes also rely on the
polar bears to hunt on their behalf.
They're the jackals of the north and
scavenge from bear kills whenever they can.
In winter and early spring,
they are wholly dependent on bears.
Only in the summer,
when the sea ice melts,
will they regularly
catch prey for themselves.
They are not strong enough
to tackle adult seals,
but can certainly take
new-born pups or birds.
This canny individual
is going to bury its prize
it may need it during
the uncertain times ahead.
The presence of bears
affects the behaviour of almost
all the animals here.
Big and small.
The bears tend to avoid the fringe of
fragmented ice bordering open water
where travelling can
be very laborious.
But that very fact makes
this area - the pack ice
a particularly good place
for seals to pup.
Harp seals breed here.
Their pups are born with white
coats which camouflage them
very effectively against the snow.
Harp seals have a very
short nursing period
a necessity on this
unstable pack ice.
But suckling is intensive.
The pup feeds for just twelve days
on milk that is 45 percent fat.
Then it is abandoned
and has to fend for itself.
A male hooded seal.
This impressive nasal display is used
to warn away other males...
...and to win a mate
Hooded seals also breed on pack ice.
Their pups suckle for only four days
the shortest nursing period
known for any mammal
and all because the
threat of polar bears
caused them to breed
on the unstable ice.
Another Arctic seal opts
for the solid ice further north.
Because it's easy for
bears to hunt here,
these ringed seals must be particularly
vigilant and have to hide their pups.
Ringed seals are comparatively small,
so they can give birth
to their pups in little caves,
or lairs, under the snow.
Here, a pup is out of sight
and protected from bad weather.
In late March and into April,
female bears emerge from winter
dens with their new cubs.
The mother has not eaten for at least
five months and she's hungry - very hungry.
If she doesn't succeed in catching
a regular supply of seals,
her milk will fail and
her cub will die.
Bears have an extraordinarily
sensitive sense of smell
and can detect seal pups hidden in
the snow from two kilometres away.
But a female ringed seal
uses several lairs
and a bear will almost certainly
have to break into a number
before it finds one
that is occupied.
This is a crucial time
for the cub.
By watching its mother hunt
and by copying her actions,
it's beginning to acquire the
rudiments of its own hunting skills.
Play is also important for developing
muscles and improving co-ordination.
As the days go by,
the sun rises higher
and remains above the
horizon even at night.
The female bear continues to hunt
until her cub is too tired
and can't keep up.
She has smelt something.
The pup escapes through a hole in
its lair that leads to the sea below.
Only one in twenty hunts
is successful.
But this mother must find a seal pup soon
if her cub is not to starve to death.
As spring turns into summer, the sun's
heat begins to melt the sea ice.
Now the ocean is accessible and
the Arctic's summer visitors return.
Migrating birds arrive
from the south to nest
and feed on the seafood
that's now within their reach.
Brunnich's guillemots are the
northern equivalent of penguins.
But they have retained
the power of flight,
for they need to
reach cliff ledges
where their nests will be safe
from predatory bears and foxes.
Nonetheless, they are as at home
in the water as in the air.
They dive down to a depth of fifty
metres or more to catch fish.
In June, the ice begins
to fracture.
The cracks - or leads.
Form useful corridors
of open water for
air-breathing animals.
Belugas, migrating to
their feeding grounds,
use these leads to penetrate
the ice-covered seas
and reach areas where
their preferred food,
Arctic cod, has spent the winter.
The males regularly dive to about
five hundred metres to find fish.
The females and young, which have
smaller lungs, only go to about 350.
In late June and July,
narwhals arrive.
The females, who usually lack tusks,
come first with their new calves.
The males follow a little later.
They also move up the leads in
search of fresh feeding grounds.
Bowheads. Up to 18 metres long
and weighing a hundred tonnes,
these are the only large whales
that stay in the Arctic all year round.
They are not after fish
They are seeking smaller prey.
Despite having the largest mouths
in the animal kingdom,
the size of a small garage,
they eat tiny crustaceans
copepods - straining them from the
water with the four-metre long strips
of baleen that hang from
their upper jaws.
In the summer they store
enough energy to last them
through the following winter,
when food will be less abundant.
As the ice melts away, the polar
bears are forced to head for land.
They are excellent swimmers
and can cover a hundred miles
of continuous open water
if need be.
Off east Greenland,
there is little ice left by August,
so walruses haul out
to rest on land.
At this time of the year
they are moulting,
getting rid of their old scarred
and parasite-ridden skin.
A bathe in the cold water brings
some relief from the itching.
But even there,
the odd scratch is irresistible.
They make daily excursions
out to deeper water.
Down at 20 metres, they root
around in the sediment,
using their sensitive bristles
to search out soft-shelled clams.
Once they find a clam,
they suck its flesh from the shell
with their powerful,
muscular mouths.
Walruses can feed for about
five minutes at this depth
before they have to return
to the surface to breathe.
Elsewhere in the Arctic, belugas are
gathering in their thousands.
They congregate in just
a few large estuaries.
Belugas of all ages
and sizes come here.
There are even young calves.
Some are so young - born only a week or
so ago - that they need help.
They swim on their mothers' backs so
that they can breathe more easily.
As the tide moves up the estuary,
the belugas follow,
swimming into surprisingly
shallow water.
Like walruses,
they also need to moult.
A combination of warm fresh water
and vigorous rubbing
against the gravel does the trick.
They remain here for days,
or even weeks,
so it's likely that socialising
is also important to them.
After moulting, they head back
out to sea to feed.
It's now autumn and the sea
begins to freeze over, once again.
Thin sheets of ice form at
the surface and pile up,
layer upon layer, gradually
creating an impenetrable barrier.
By late November, the Arctic Ocean
is sealed once again by ice.
The lights of the aurora play
in the winter sky.
At the other end of the planet.
In the Antarctic
there is the southern aurora
Antarctica is now emerging
from winter.
This is the coldest,
windiest place in the world.
Temperatures are still hovering
at a numbing minus 50
and the returning sun has
virtually no warmth.
Very few animals can survive
such extreme conditions.
But emperor penguins can.
Standing on the frozen sea, they endure
the full force of the Antarctic storms.
Only by huddling together can they can
survive the appalling winter months.
They take it in turns to bear
the brunt of the gales.
They can only live here at all because
Antarctica is surrounded
by the Great Southern Ocean and no land
predators have been able to reach it,
so unlike Arctic animals,
they're not threatened by polar bears.
The sea is still frozen.
But one seal, nonetheless,
manages to stay here,
even throughout the winter...
...the Weddell seal.
Underwater, it's protected
from the storms above.
But it must have access to the air
all year - in order to breathe.
And they keep their breathing holes open.
With their teeth.
Only by continually scraping away at the
ice can they maintain access to the air.
But that means that their teeth
get badly worn down.
Then they can no longer hunt
and eat effectively.
Weddell seals die young.
The continent of Antarctica
is so isolated
and so high - almost five
thousand metres in places
that it's considerably colder
than the Arctic.
Ice slides slowly down from its centre
towards its rim in immense glaciers.
During winter, the continent effectively
doubles in size as the sea freezes over.
Ice forms around its shores
and extends outwards
for hundreds of miles around
the entire land mass.
Under the sea-ice live small
shrimp-like creatures - krill.
They have been here all winter.
During these dark months, they feed by
scraping algae from the ice.
Remarkably, they also
shrink in size
and revert to their juvenile
form to save energy.
As the temperature
rises in spring,
the ice begins to melt and little air
bubbles trapped within it are released.
Microscopic algae grow around these
bubbles and the krill now graze on them,
gathering them up with
their beating legs.
As the sun's rays grow stronger
and penetrate deeper into the water,
floating algae begin to
flourish and krill leave
the dwindling ice and gather in swarms
as they harvest this new crop.
Far to the north, beyond the
blanket of sea ice,
chinstrap penguins have been
overwintering in the open ocean.
The occasional iceberg gives
them the chance of a rest
if they can get onto it.
But at this time of year, where they
really want to be is on land.
It's just getting there
that's tricky.
It's spring and the penguins
are returning to breed.
Their need to get ashore is now
urgent and imperative.
Doing so is all a matter of timing.
And picking the right wave.
But their journey has
only just begun.
Most of them will have to walk many miles
before they can find a nest site.
This is Zavodovski Island, which has the
largest penguin colony in the world.
About two million chinstraps
breed here
and they come to this island
for a good reason.
It's an active volcano.
The heat from the crater
and the fumeroles
keeps the slopes free from
the ice and snow,
allowing these chinstraps to start
breeding earlier than those further south.
But then again, living on an active
volcano is not without its risks.
Unlike the emperors, these penguins are
able to lay their eggs on the bare ground.
Little wonder so many
of them choose to brave
the mountainous waves
in order to get here.
Further south, near the continent,
the blanket of sea ice
is beginning to break up.
Icebergs are gigantic fragments
of ice that have broken away
into the sea from the
front of glaciers.
During the winter they
were frozen into the sea ice,
but now they are set
adrift once more.
As the bergs break up,
they form brash ice.
It litters the backwaters
of the Antarctic Peninsula.
Minke whales make their way into
these placid waters in summer.
This is the most abundant whale
in the Southern Ocean.
Minkes are one of the smallest
of all the baleen whales.
And like all others,
they come here to feed.
The majestic humpback whales
are also summer visitors.
They have travelled thousands of miles
from their winter
breeding grounds in the
tropics to gather the food
that becomes available
here in summer.
In just four months,
they accumulate enough fat
to provide them with energy for
the whole of the rest of the year.
All these animals have come here
in search of one thing - the krill.
Krill is the mainstay of
the Antarctic food web.
It occurs in phenomenal quantity
billions of individuals
in a single swarm,
and swarms can stretch for miles.
Fur seals also collect this
rich superabundant food.
Krill swarms are very patchy,
but once found, feeding is easy.
Humpbacks engulf hundreds of thousands of
them in a single gargantuan mouthful.
When the going is good,
the whales feed continuously,
each eating up to two tonnes
of krill in twenty-four hours.
Further south, near the continent,
the sea ice is still sound.
Here, where the ice remains
for most of the summer,
emperor penguins make their home.
These have been feeding out
at sea and are now ready
to make their way back to the
colony to feed their chicks.
Instead of heading straight
for the ice edge,
the penguins hesitate
some distance from it.
They're nervous.
They dive down and
investigate the ice edge.
And for good reason
Leopard seals patrol this border.
Leopard seals are the Antarctic's
equivalent of polar bears.
They are the top predators.
But they hunt most successfully
in the water,
so by and large, the animals they prey
on are safer out on the ice.
They have a lazy grace that belies
their ferocious nature.
Confident that the coast is clear,
the emperor penguins head for the ice.
But they certainly don't linger.
Now they have a long walk
back to the colony.
Emperor penguin colonies are some
way back from the ice edge.
In winter they may be as much as
a hundred miles from it,
but as the summer progresses
and the ice melts,
the edge comes ever
closer to the colony.
So by the time the chicks are fledged
and ready to take their first swim,
the water is close by.
This colony is in the lee
of a headland
and that prevents the ice from
being broken up by ocean currents.
The returning adults are so full
of food that they can barely walk.
But with no predator to threaten
them now, they can take their time.
Somehow, in this melee of sixty
thousand or so penguins,
a parent has to find its chick.
It returns to the place where it last
left its chick in the hope that
it might still be close by.
But chicks tend to wander,
so the adult has to call to it.
The chick responds - and they slowly
home in on one another.
The plaintive entreaties
of the chick stimulates
the adult to regurgitate
a mouthful of fish.
With the return of one parent,
the other is free to go
to sea to feed for itself.
Aware of the leopard
seal's presence,
the penguins press
together at the ice edge,
unwilling to be the
first to risk diving in.
Occasionally, the seal comes out
onto the ice and attempts to grab one.
But its most successful strategy
by far is to lie in wait.
It hides behind a corner of ice.
The emperors gain confidence
and make a dash for it.
The first wave of penguins escape.
Once in open water,
they will be safe.
But the seal is alerted by the noise,
and through the mass of bubbles,
it makes its attack.
Almost invariably,
it makes a kill.
Encouraged by the absence
of the seal,
the remaining penguins
make a break for the open sea.
In time, their chicks will fledge.
And when the Antarctic
autumn is near its end,
these adults will walk across
the newly formed ice,
to endure yet another winter
on the frozen sea