For www.forom.com
Previously on "Dexter"...
No blood
What a gorgeous idea.
Refrigerated truck.
He wants a cold environment...
to slow the flow of blood.
I suppose I should be upset,
but I'm not.
In fact,
I think this is a friendly message,
kind of like, "hey,
want to pla? "
Kara, it's me.
It's James.
You just opened
a dangerous door.
No, man.
You did...
when you murdered a cop
and an innocent lady.
Was Kara sleeping with
someone other than Ricky?
Was it you?
What the fuck were
you thinking?
Going out tonight with the guys,
blow off steam. You in?
Hey, man.
Sounds good.
I thought you said you
wanted to go get shit-faced.
I am shit-faced.
I showed my face to Guerrero,
to his whole church.
They're gonna think
I'm behind this shit.
You fucked my sister.
You fucked a cop's wife.
Now you're just fucked, buddy.
He's escalating the thrill,
posing his victim
in the middle of a 20,000-seat
arena for all Miami to see,
to show us what he's
capable of doing.
What did I miss?
- Fingertips.
- Fuckin' asshole, that's my girl.
This body belongs to the frozen
fingertips in the truck.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you Tony Tucci,
the ice-truck killer.
Bullshit.
Of course I agree
with my sister,
but unlike her, I'm not upset.
He's still out there,
and I'm waiting...
breathless.
I find people around me are always
making some kind of connection,
like friendship or romance,
but human bonds always lead
to messy complications...
commitment, sharing,
driving people to the airport.
Besides, if I let
someone get that close,
they'd see who
I really am...
and I can't let that happen.
So, time to put on my mask.
- I need your expertise.
- I live to serve.
Excuse us, fellas.
- Interesting hand job.
- That's funny.
It is?
So, how long you think
it's been there?
This feels familiar.
Okay. So,
how long has it been there?
Blood stopped pooling, still wet...
couple hours at the most.
What time was it found?
A jogger called it in
this morning about 7:30.
No prints. Wiped clean.
Real creep show, huh?
Any sign of the
rest of the body?
Just Mr. Hand.
Do you think this is our guy's work?
The ice-truck killer?
It's hard to say. There's blood.
That's different.
Plus, it's a male victim --
haven't seen that before.
The cut appears to
be almost delicate.
You see between the first
and second row of carpals...
Very surgical.
Check out what else
he left behind.
A little postcard
to remember him by.
- How far is Rand Beach from here?
- This is Rand Beach.
It was renamed Petrie
Beach a few years ago.
Okay, everybody.
Everybody say "stinky feet".
Stinky feet!
Wait. Nobody move.
Dexter, were you smiling?
- No.
- Okay, we'll do another one.
This time, everybody smiles.
You, too, Dex.
Yeah, pretend you're
burning ants.
- Shut your damn face, Deb.
- Hey, language, please.
What?
She always talks like that.
Enough, you two.
Dexter, come here.
What's your problem?
I hate the beach.
It's sandy and gross and
nasty, and I want to go home.
Too bad.
You're part of a family.
And being part of a family
means smiling for photos.
Why should I
pretend I'm happy?
Because it'll make
your mom happy,
and because it's
how you fit in.
- Remember we talked about that?
- Yeah.
This is how you do it.
When somebody takes your picture,
you smile.
It doesn't matter if
you're happy or not.
You just do it to fit in.
Okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
Come here, handsome.
Okay. Everybody ready?
One more time.
Stinky feet!
Yeah, I just need to stop by my
apartment to pick up a few labs.
Straight to the station after, yeah.
Thanks, lieutenant.
Dexter Morgan,
this is your life.
It is my new friend --
The ice-truck killer.
When he broke into my apartment,
he took some time to get to know me...
my life...
my secrets.
...have even brought in
manpower from other counties
in an effort to
expedite the search.
Officially, Mr. Tucci has not
been charged with any crime...
Then tell the fucking governor
to free up funds for overtime.
I mean the more guys I got out there,
the sooner we find Tucci.
Kelly, I'll get back to you.
What's wrong?
Fingerprint I. D. came back
on that hand from the beach.
It belongs to Tony Tucci,
your ice-truck killer suspect.
What?
Wait a minute.
No. No, no, no. No way.
No way!
I mean, this --
This has to be a mistake!
The mistake, Maria, was
unleashing a high-profile manhunt
before you had all the facts.
Fuck!
Okay. This doesn't mean that
Tucci is not the killer.
Don't!
Just... just don't.
You wanted to be on tv --
well, get ready...
'cause the press will
annihilate us for this.
We'll be lucky if Tucci's
mother doesn't file a lawsuit.
All right.
You go talk to that woman.
Do your mea culpas.
If we handle this right,
maybe we can mitigate
the fallout.
Tom!
I'm the last person
she wants to see.
I called her son a killer!
And now's your chance
to make it right.
So Laguerta screwed the
pooch on this one, huh?
I'm taking point.
You can help by getting all
non essentials off the beach.
Secure and separate any witnesses,
all right?
Will do. What did the Captain say?
Did he make her cry?
Just control the
fucking beach, Angel.
I knew Tucci wasn't the killer.
I knew it.
Laguerta whipped
up a manhunt
for a rent-a-cop.
Man, I wish I could have been there
to see the Captain rip her a new one.
Morgan, calm down.
Laguerta insulted the real
killer's intelligence,
and now he's getting back at us
for chasing after the wrong guy.
You see all these
people over here?
- Yeah.
- What are they?
Potential witnesses.
And what do we do with
potential witnesses, Morgan?
We -- we interview them.
Got it.
Where is he...
The rest of him?
We're -- we're still looking.
The entire force is looking.
We're making every effort.
Are you sure it's
Tony? Because...
Yes.
I'm afraid so.
Mrs. Tucci...
I said some very harsh
things about your son.
Thank you.
"Thank you"?
For what?
- For coming to tell me in person.
- For God's sake, please.
There's nothing more
important than this.
Can you find my son's body?
If it's the last thing I do.
I made a grave...
Bring him home, please.
I just want to bury my son.
I do love Halloween.
- What's inside of a pumpkin?
- See for yourself.
You don't like this stuff?
I do. Come on. Get in there.
I'll finish cleaning this out.
You can carve it tomorrow.
There he is again, mom.
My god.
It's every night now.
That dog?
Where's it coming from?
Next door --
My neighbor's.
Leaves the poor thing in
the yard all day and night.
It's been getting worse.
I mean, I would talk to her,
but I don't want to
start something.
Listen to him, mom.
He's so sad.
I just wish he would shut
up so I could sleep.
Do you want me to talk to her?
No, you don't have to do that.
I insist.
Hello.
I don't think we've met.
Boyfriend of the blonde next door.
I've seen you around.
Look, I'm just getting in.
I'm tired.
That's precisely why I'm here.
We can't help but notice your dog,
uh, cries... a lot.
I know.
My ex moved out and left his dog.
Trust me,
I wish there was something I could do.
You could, uh, take him inside.
Walter's an outside dog.
You put Walter inside,
Walter's an inside dog.
He doesn't like being inside.
Did he tell you that?
We'd really appreciate it if you
could find a way to keep him quiet.
The kids are upset.
Maybe that's 'cause they think their
crackhead father is gonna come back
and beat their asses again.
You know what works
for me? Earplugs.
I could make things so
much easier for Rita...
but that would be wrong.
I love Halloween --
the one time of year when
everyone wears a mask...
not just me.
People think it's fun to
pretend you're a monster.
Me, I spend my life
pretending I'm not.
Brother, friend, boyfriend...
All part of my costume collection.
Some people might
call me a fraud.
OK.
Let's see if it will fit.
You stabbed me in the back!
I prefer to think of myself
as a master of disguise.
They're so excited.
Sure they are. They get to binge
on sugar for an entire day.
Who wouldn't love that?
What about a costume for you?
Maybe this one?
No. No. I think I'll be Snow White
again. It's kind of tradition.
Dexter, look.
I'm a princess, too.
Just like your mom --
Two perfect princesses.
Let me guess.
You're gonna be a dwarf.
No way.
I want to be Joe from "Blue's Clues. "
I keep telling him that a
rugby shirt is not a costume.
Another photo from
my family album.
He's re-creating my past with
Tony Tucci's body parts.
He's forcing me to see this.
Nobody paying you to stand
around and goddamn stare.
I thought Angel was working
this case, Sergeant.
Sergeant?
Friends of yours?
Don't worry about it.
Worry about this.
The foot was severed between
the tarsus and the metatarsus.
The wound is circular --
again, almost surgical.
And there's blood. Guy gives us
body after body with no blood.
- Why he's making a switch now?
- He's trying to send a message...
One that's more important than his
ritual need to drain the blood and
wrap the parts.
- Okay, so what's the message?
- I'm not sure.
- Well, who's he sending it to?
- I can't tell you that, either.
What fucking good are you?
No fucking good at all,
apparently.
- You okay?
- He's mocking me.
Don't take it personally.
Doakes hates all you lab geeks.
Who?
- Relax, bro.
- Sorry.
I need to bag this photo under the ball.
Do you mind?
He knows.
He's not corrupting the happy
hallmark images of my youth.
He's revealing the ugly
truth behind them.
Come on, Simon. You want it?
It's right there.
Over there.
Oh, yeah.
- Guys, give it back!
- Come on, Simon.
All right. Enough.
Get out of here.
- What the hell is going on?
- We're just having fun.
It didn't look like Simon
was having too much fun.
You're always
telling me to fit in,
and I'm just trying to
be part of the team.
You can't be a bully, Dexter.
First of all it's wrong.
Secondly, people
remember bullies.
People like me -- cops.
A bully is a felony
waiting to happen.
- So...
- Blend in.
Go on.
Officer Morgan,
I have an assignment for you.
Yeah, I heard we found a
foot this morning.
You want me to head out
to the crime scene?
No.
Look, we pulled these from security
cameras around the beach...
Stores, hotels, ATMs.
I want you to check every frame.
You are shitting me.
If we're lucky, we can see the
ice-truck killer coming and going.
We have techs who can do this.
Not all techs have the skill
to spot suspicious activity.
I'm taking a huge leap
of faith that you do.
And keep your eye out for another
box of surveillance tapes.
It's on its way from
the new crime scene.
Hey, Doakes, what's up?
Fuck anyone's wife lately?
Thanks to your little
chickenshit stunt,
Guerrero's guys are tailing me
everywhere I go. Did you know that?
That's not good, James.
You should alert the police...
Unless, of course, for some reason
the officers of Miami metro
wouldn't want to help you... like,
you know, you fucked one of their wives.
You think this is a joke.
I'm gonna end up dead.
It's just a matter of when.
You should have thought of that before
you stuck your dick in my sister.
You're right.
I should have waited until
the divorce came through.
Bullshit.
What? She didn't tell you?
She filed the papers, jackass.
You don't believe me,
ask the Captain.
He tried to pull Ricky
out of his assignment,
but Ricky didn't
want to come out.
Of course not.
His job was to bring down Guerrero.
It was his job to
protect his wife.
Ricky's the motherfucker
who got her killed.
You backed the
wrong cop, asshole.
Let's go, guys.
Time for school.
Guys? Come on.
You don't want to be in
the Halloween parade?
Shut up!
Shut up! Just --
I need to talk to
you about your dog.
- I talked to your boyfriend.
- My kids are exhausted.
All right, when it comes to my kids,
I stop being nice.
So I need you to
bring him in at night,
feed him on a schedule,
and take him for some
exercise every now and...
I'm sorry.
Is this funny?
No, no, no
It's... it's sad.
But you're funny.
Look at you, all tough.
I'm gonna call the police.
I can do that.
There's nothing you can do.
The cops will tell
me to keep him quiet,
and I'll say I will, and then
they'll leave,
and he'll go back to doing what he does.
But you're funny.
Unlike Harry, my new friend doesn't
place much value in blending in.
He wants me to see who
he is and what he does.
Everything about him
is brazen, authentic.
What does that make me?
Crap.
- You okay, man?
- No.
Hey, don't let this
bastard get to you.
You're the best blood
expert in the state,
and we need you to stay with this,
my friend.
I'll be all right.
Wait. Before you get back to work,
check this out.
What is that, a butterfly?
No, socio,
it's a diamond-studded four-leaf clover.
I'm...
I'm giving it to Nina for our
anniversary tomorrow night.
Congratulations.
How many years?
10 years she's been
my lucky charm now.
Tin is the
traditional gift, but
I didn't think she'd
want a tin clover.
No. It's probably a good plan.
Are you sure that's not a butterfly?
Well, it does kind
of look like a bug.
- This can't be right.
- What's up?
You see that?
You see it?
I don't know.
What do I see?
The blood flow in the hand suggested
the heart was still pumping
- when it was severed.
- Mean son of a bitch, no doubt.
But look at the foot.
It's the same blood flow,
plus the lividity. Look, it's the
same bruising, same ashen color,
same level of decomposition as
the hand the day we found it.
But... we found
them a day apart.
I know.
Dios santo.
L. T.,
you got to listen to him.
It's the guard, Tucci...
I think he's alive.
What are you talking about?
The ice-truck killer is keeping
him alive to perform amputations.
Tucci's alive?
Both limbs were taken
from a live body,
and we found them 24 hours apart.
That's not all.
Tell them, Dexter.
If the hand came off
yesterday at 7:00 A.M.
and the foot this
morning at 7:00...
We get another body part
first thing tomorrow.
But he's alive.
Put together a task force.
I want all available personnel on this,
and put a priority status on all
forensics related to this case.
Captain Matthews, please.
Have him call me back immediately.
Mrs. Tucci?
Maria Laguerta.
I have some amazing
news for you.
We believe your son is alive.
No. No.
We haven't, but I promise we will.
No, thank you.
Yes. Yes.
Okay, we'll be in touch. Bye.
We've got a live
body now, people.
We want to find Tucci
while he's still breathing.
That means trying to figure
out where tomorrow's drop is
so we catch our man in the act.
Any ideas?
Don't forget the photos.
They're new.
Thank you, officer Morgan.
We're doing just fine out here.
Why do we think he's
taking photos?
He wants to be remembered.
You use photos to
record memories.
I almost feel sorry for them,
trying to put together a puzzle
when they don't know pieces
are missing from the box...
...pieces he gave me.
He wants me to play
the game his way.
Okay, what else could it be?
Change.
You got something to say,
speak up.
The beach changed names.
The office park used
to be a soccer field.
He's dumping the body parts in places
that used to be something else.
Okay. Places that have changed.
Let's make a list,
assign surveillance to each
location for the morning.
South beach used to
be a mangrove swamp.
Homestead park was originally
an air force base, right?
They turned Versace's
mansion into a hotel.
Thank you, officer Morgan.
The whole city of Miami
reinvents itself every 5 years.
Then we'll stay up all night
until our list is complete.
"I once was lost
"But now I'm found,
"Was blind but now I see".
Lieutenant.
Anything?
Well, I am so glad
you could make it.
Well, I just came by
to show my support.
It's been a long time
since I've been to church.
Excuse me, everyone.
Excuse me.
I would like to introduce
you to someone very special.
This is Maria Laguerta.
She's the policewoman looking for Tony.
Not just me.
Actually, there's a lot of us looking.
You brought us all here
together by giving us hope.
May the Lord bless you
and guide you, Maria.
This is Saint Anthony,
- patron Saint of
- The lost.
Find him.
I tried to apologize,
but I couldn't get a word in edgewise.
And you wanted to
apologize why?
You don't think I should,
the way I went after her son?
Yeah, you did fuck that up.
Yeah. I crucified him
without having all the facts.
I need to tell her
that I'm sorry.
I need to let her know that I'm sorry.
I need to tell her.
Who is that gonna make feel better,
you or her?
Leave that woman alone with
her candles and "kumbaya".
So, where we at?
I added additional patrols
at Dolphin Stadium,
Bayside marketplace,
and Casa Casuarina.
That's everybody we have
out in the field --
Homicide-Robbery, off-duty patrol.
So what's next?
What's next is you
should go home.
You've had the shit kicked
out of you all day.
I like it here with you.
You're the only person
people hate more than me.
Come on.
Let's both get out of here.
Nothing left but the
waiting now, anyway.
Officer Morgan.
Call me on my cellphone
if you find anything.
Son of a bitch.
Fuck this.
What?
Want a piece of me?
Fucking asshole!
I will pay you $1 million
if you help me figure out where the
next piece of Tucci's gonna show up.
I'm afraid I'm lost
on this one, Deb.
It's like it's staring me
right in the face, but --
$1 million.
You don't have $1 million.
I'll steal it from evidence.
I've been stuck in a
goddamn fishbowl all day.
I want to be part of the hunt.
- I'm almost off duty.
- Sorry, sister.
$2 million.
I know you made a list of locations.
Just pick your favorite spot.
We'll stake it out together.
My favorite spot. Of course.
Come on.
I want to play.
Deb, I got to go.
We'll compare notes tomorrow, okay?
I used to love this place --
The bulldozers pressing garbage,
layer after layer,
right into the earth itself,
burying it, hiding it.
I found it soothing.
But it wasn't condos back then.
This has to be the right place.
So what am I missing?
Sorry about that.
Go back to sleep.
Hello.
Mr. Morgan?
Dispatch.
You've been called to the
McCaffrey pumpkin patch.
- Do you need the address?
- No, I know exactly where it is.
Are you okay?
Are you kidding?
That was awesome.
You've got some
hay in your hair.
- Where?
- Right there!
Okay, okay, okay, okay. Enough.
Enough, you two. Come on.
Let me take a picture
of you and the kids.
You'll miss these moments
when they're older.
Thanks.
It's great to see you having
such a good time, Dex.
Are you kidding me? This hay's
giving me a total allergy attack,
and we're going around in circles
on a pumpkin patch. I don't get it.
Ready?
Smile!
What do we have?
Ankle to knee.
He's moving up the leg.
You think Tucci's still alive?
If he is, he won't be for long.
Unless you're toting
a portable DVD player,
you better be finished watching
that security footage.
I am on break.
I'm on my own time.
So you are,
but your shift starts in two hours.
So if I were you,
I'd head back to the station.
Traffic at this hour's a bitch.
Speaking of bitch...
Didn't dad bring us here
once when we were kids?
I don't remember.
Hey, Dexter, come here.
Take a look at this.
Excuse us.
She's right, you know,
about the traffic.
It's interesting. There's
no sign of infection
where the foot was cut off,
like he gave Tucci
prophylactic antibiotics
before amputating.
At least he's looking
after his patient.
Hey, check this out.
Is this appropriate?
It's our anniversary...
and it's the big one.
Nina deserves the best.
"Ox"?
No. Fuck!
What's the matter with you?
It's x's and o'S.
Like tic-tac-toe?
No, like "hugs and kisses".
Diamond-filled hugs and kisses
in a white-gold setting.
Well, that's good,
'cause you wouldn't want it to look like
someone's playing
tic-tac-toe on her head.
Goddamn it.
Where's mom?
She had to run a few errands before
she takes you two trick-or-treating.
But I'm too tired to
go trick-or-treating.
I heard you two were
up a lot last night.
It was that damn dog.
Hey, Code,
grown-up language is for grown-ups.
I don't think that dog will
be bothering you anymore.
- How do you know?
- My mystic powers told me.
Heard Lindsay Lohan say "damn".
All right, tell you what --
I'll make you a deal.
When you become a rock star,
you can swear, too.
- Walter! Walter!
- You're right. He's gone.
Where's my dog?!
What did you do with it?!
All right. Here he is.
Just remember to walk him,
feed him, and love him, okay?
My nieces are shy sometimes.
Girls, say thank you to Rita.
Thank you.
They already made a doggy bed --
sweaters, towels.
It actually looks more
comfortable than my bed.
I knew this would
be a perfect fit.
You did a good thing, Rita.
Thank you.
Harry was the only
one who saw me...
...really saw me...
So he taught me to hide.
That's what's kept me safe.
But sometimes, I'm not sure where
Harry's vision of me ends
and the real me starts.
If I'm just a collection
of learned behaviors...
bits and pieces of Harry...
maybe my new friend is right.
Maybe I am a fraud.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Where's Astor and Cody?
They're passed out in a
sugar coma at Colleen's.
- Can I come in?
- Yeah, sure. Sorry.
I should warn you,
I haven't really been myself lately.
Maybe I can cheer you up.
Trick or treat.
You look great.
- Who are you?
- Lara Croft.
"Tomb Raider".
You raid tombs dressed like that?
That's impressive.
What happened to Snow White?
Well, I'm -- I'm sick of her.
You know, I never did
get to thank you for
picking the kids up for me.
You took care
of your "errand"?
Yes.
The beagle has landed happily in
the arms of two loving girls.
You are a superhero.
It was such an incredible
feeling rescuing that dog.
You upset your neighbor.
Fuck her.
Well, I guess you're used to dealing
with people like her, right?
Considerably worse.
Is that why you haven't
been yourself lately?
There's a case I just can't
seem to get out of my mind.
Maybe I can help.
No. I'm afraid there's
nothing you can do.
Oh, I don't know.
I'm a dognapper now...
and a tomb raider.
There's all sorts
of things I can do.
What -- what are you doing?
Whatever I want.
I've come to appreciate the
comfortable moments with Rita...
The easy, quiet moments--
This...
...might be better.
Look, there's Mr.
Tub-of-Lardy bringing
Mrs. Tub-of-Lardy another
bucket of fried chicken.
- Where's your brother?
- I'm not his keeper.
What do you think of this?
It's an anniversary
present for Nina.
See, it's...
it's a diamond key to my heart.
It's... it's a key,
but, you see,
it's shaped like a heart.
You can't tell me that it
looks like anything else,
'cause that's what it is.
That's it. That's what I like.
And I'm not gonna take it back.
It's perfect, Angel.
She'll love it.
Really?
I would.
How... How do I look?
Like the tie?
Angel.
Happy anniversary, baby.
You know you can't just
walk in here anymore.
I just thought...
...our anniversary...
Maybe tonight we could
put all that behind us.
It doesn't matter
what night it is.
I told you I need time.
It's been three months, baby.
How much time do you need?
Don't turn this around
on me, Angel...
...Not after what you did.
I need as much time as I need.
Angel...
As long as you're here,
you want to see Aury?
Lo siento, princesa.
Lo siento, lo siento,
lo siento.
Thank you.
That was...
...unexpected.
Yeah.
For me, too.
I have no problem with...
unexpected.
No, you...
certainly don't.
I have to get back to the kids.
What are these?
I've been reorganizing
my photos a little.
Look how cute you are.
And your dad --
such a nice face, just like you.
- I was adopted.
- I know.
But you're both good men.
I can tell.
Very poetic.
Poetic?
It's a water fountain.
Well, yeah, but look at the
way your dad took the photo.
His shadow's on the
wall right next to you.
It's like he's always with you.
I'd frame this one.
All this time the
answer was right here.
Harry... photographer and
foster father extraordinaire.
He is always with me,
and he's the common denominator.
Rita...
you're a genius.
All those years of
smiling for the camera...
It was empty and fake,
the pictures meaningless, until now.
Pictures of Harry.
So this is it.
It's cool.
Cool.
Dexter, this is the
place where my father,
your grandfather,
worked for 30 years.
He started out as the janitor,
worked his way up to
chief of maintenance.
This place put
food on our table.
In two weeks,
it'll all be shut down.
I know.
Excuse me, miss! Miss?
- Would you mind?
- Oh, come on, dad.
Hey, you all right?
It's nothing.
Bad medianoches for lunch. I'm okay.
I'm sorry, miss.
It's okay. Thanks.
We're not gonna be needing a picture,
after all.
Yeah, we are.
Dex, I really don't feel
like doing this now.
Don't be a baby --
Being part of a family means
smiling for family photos, right?
My friend left this.
He's showing me where to go.
Am I going because
it's what he wants
or because that's what
Harry would want?
What do I want?
The hospital's shut down now,
abandoned for years,
but tonight it's
visiting hours again.
Well, James...
Why did you have to be such
a pain in the ass, huh?
Fuck !
I didn't tell you
you could get up.
Please, please.
Now you get up.
You traumatize my little
girl in church...
break the knees of
my best turner.
You're a wild dog, Sergeant.
The only thing to do
with a wild dog...
Police!
Hands in the air!
Thought you could use backup.
You could have filled me in,
man. Shit.
Got you going after a
goddamn cop, motherfucker.
We own your ass now.
So this was the
plan all along...
To use me as bait to
bring down Guerrero?
Yeah, and now my sister
can rest in peace.
We're done now, Doakes.
We're even.
I'll call this in,
bring the paramedics.
Get this piece of
shit out of here.
Please.
Just do it.
Kill me.
I'm ready.
Just don't cut me anymore.
Please don't cut me anymore.
Gift-wrapped and
begging for death.
Tools at the ready.
Just kill me.
It's okay.
He was left here so
I would kill him,
but my new friend doesn't see
me as clearly as he thinks.
I can't kill this man.
Harry wouldn't want it.
And neither would I.
Are you Morgan?
Message came through
dispatch for you.
Who left this?
Who left it?!
Jesus, stop that.
I'm getting bruises.
I'm sorry.
I'm so excited.
Try a hug once in a while.
I don't know who your
contacts are, Morgan,
but you are my up-and-comer.
You saved a man's life tonight.
I'm just the one who
got the call, Sir.
But you followed it up.
Right place at the
right time, Sir.
- Where we at?
- Morgan's tip was good.
They're taking Tucci
over to county.
- Alive?
- Alive.
So, I suppose this gets Deb
off of surveillance-tape duty.
Really?
Is that what you suppose?
I got your page, Lieutenant.
Doakes is caught up
in the Guerrero bust.
- You're taking point here.
- You got it.
I'm tired of chasing this guy's shadow.
I want forensic evidence.
I don't care if you have to tear
apart this building brick by brick.
- Entiende?
- Si.
Use Morgan here.
How did your wife like that necklace,
Angel?
Oh, you were right.
She loved it.
You nailed that one.
Everyone hides who they are,
at least some of the time.
Sometimes you bury that
part of yourself so deeply
that you have to be
reminded it's there at all.
Good work, man.
I told you we'd get that piss-poor...
And sometimes you just want to
forget who you are altogether.
And what about me?
Maybe I'll never be the
human Harry wanted me to be.
But I couldn't kill Tony Tucci.
That's not me, either.
My new friend thought I wouldn't be
able to resist the kill he left for me,
but I did.
I'm not the monster
he wants me to be.
So I'm neither man nor beast.
I'm something new entirely,
with my own set of rules.
I'm Dexter.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com