For www.forom.com
Previously on "Dexter"...
What happened changed
something inside you, Dex.
It got into you too early.
I'm afraid your urge to kill
is only gonna get stronger.
I want to catch this guy before
he kills another one of my girls.
What can I do to help?
No blood.
What a beautiful idea.
Refrigerated truck.
He wants a cold environment
to slow the flow of blood.
I suppose I should be upset,
even feel violated,
but I'm not.
In fact,
I think this is a friendly message,
kind of like, "hey,
want to play?"
Finding that truck is your
golden ticket into Homicide.
So Miami's the haystack,
and the ice truck's the needle.
I just found the
fucking needle.
Oh, this is seriously fucked up,
my friends.
I think he's trying
to impress me...
...and it's working.
The Captain believes you should be
reassigned from Vice to Homicide.
Thank you, sir.
Rita is, in her own way,
as damaged as me.
- Are you gonna kiss him?
- Actually, yes.
We just got an I.D. on the body
from under the causeway.
His name is Ricky Simmons.
He was a cop.
They told me Ricky Simmons was under
deep cover in Carlos Guerrero's family.
Guerrero's crossing
a whole new line.
Now he's gone and pissed off the
entire Miami police department.
It's me. It's James, okay?
It's okay.
Was Kara sleeping with someone
other than Ricky? Was it you?
James, she died.
Miami's full of good cops,
a lot of them here today.
But no offense -- I wouldn't want
any of you hitting on my sister.
Ricky was different.
He was the kind of guy you hoped
your sister would fall for.
Most people have a hard
time dealing with death,
but I'm not most people.
It's the grief that
makes me uncomfortable.
Not because I'm a killer --
Really. I just don't
understand all that emotion,
which makes it tough to fake.
In those cases,
shades come in handy.
Mac.
- I'm sorry, man.
- Thanks, man.
It's a fucking travesty.
- You going after Guerrero?
- Guerrero ordered these hits.
I'm gonna make something stick
to that cartel cocksucker.
I didn't know you and
Ricky were so tight.
Ain't about that.
Fuck with a cop,
you lose the privilege
to walk the streets.
- I'm not right?
- You're right.
...tragic loss of our fellow officer.
But we praise his courage.
Ricky knew no fear.
People believe Laguerta?
She didn't even know Simmons.
She knew he was a cop.
Wait.
Did you tell her?
Proud of you for coming, bro.
I know you hate funerals.
- How you holding up?
- I'm managing.
No, I'm not.
Keeping one's face pinched in sorrow
for two hours straight
is a real chore.
A whole life reduced to ashes.
For Ricky Simmons, it's over.
But sometimes,
you get a second chance.
Florida prisons kick free
25,000 inmates a year.
They don't do that for me,
but it sure feels like it.
I search for the ones who
think they've beat the system.
They're not hard to find,
like Jeremy Downs.
Jeremy got off easy:
four years in a juvenile
facility for manslaughter.
To the coroner, the knife
strokes looked random, impulsive,
but I saw the work
of a young virtuoso.
Too many major arteries
were severed --
Femoral, brachial, carotid.
Today Jeremy is just another
piece of trash on the street,
but four years ago,
he was the toast of Miami.
It was a gruesome
scene today --
The bloody body of a teenage
boy found stabbed to death
inside this south Miami park.
Police haven't released
the name of the victim yet,
but our sources are telling
us that investigators
are holding a 15-year-old
suspect in custody.
We're hearing that the suspect
lured the older boy to the
pond to spot alligators,
but once they were alone,
the victim was robbed
and repeatedly stabbed.
But I knew what he was
and what he'd do again.
All I had to do was circle
my calendar and wait.
Lemonade for my sweaty workers?
What do you say, crew?
Anybody parched?
What's parched?
When we put in the
new lemon tree,
we'll be able to make our
own fresh-squeezed lemonade.
Can we have a lemonade stand?
I'll apply for a business license
first thing in the morning.
Thank you for
doing this, Dexter.
You know, I moved here
from Michigan
with dreams of fruit trees
in my yard.
But they keep dying.
I can't help it.
I kill things.
That must be awful.
Fortunately, I have a green thumb.
The key to happy citrus
is a fertilizer.
Bone meal works the best.
Hey, Rita.
Paul doesn't live here anymore.
No shit. He's in jail.
But...
See, he still owes me for
two ounces of blow,
which means you owe me.
Don't get involved.
I never know in
these situations.
- I don't have money.
- You got a car.
- You want my car?
- Yeah. The keys in it?
You know my dad?
I sure do, little man.
And you want to know something?
You look just like him.
I'm gonna tell him
you said hi, okay?
Look, if you want,
I could go in the house,
throw your furniture around,
make a real mess,
but what kind of message would
that send to the little ones?
Just give me the fucking car.
Why don't you go inside and get the
keys? I'll wait with our friend here.
What?
You think you can take me
with your little red shovel?
- Everything okay in there?
- Yeah.
- You need toilet paper?
- No.
The guy clearly had no idea
who he was dealing with.
I'll file a report at work.
We'll get your car back.
No... No reports, Dexter.
Thank you, but...
Paul's out of my life.
I filed for divorce.
I just want my past to go away.
Well, it went away
in your Rav 4.
Whatever it takes.
I can give you a ride to work
until you get another car.
Or I could take the bus like
millions of other people.
Come on, let's go outside
and enjoy this beautiful day.
Come on, kids.
What did they use, an ax?
It's blunt force.
See the way the head's caved in?
You guys check out the new
hottie McGotass in dispatch yet?
She's a butter face.
- What's a butter face?
- You know, compadre --
She's got a hot body,
but her face...
How great would it be to
pull a bronco on her? Yeah.
Yeah? Mira a quí.
You do it doggy-style, right?
And just when she's
getting into it,
you grab her by the hips and you yell
another woman's name, and bam --
you're riding her like a bronco
'cause she's trying to buck you off.
Many times in life,
I feel like I'm missing
some essential piece of the human
puzzle. This is one of them.
What are you doing?
Oh, the bronco.
See, socia?
She knows.
I just got
my first official Homicide call.
He's back.
Who's back?
The ice-truck killer?
That's right. You won't
believe where he left the body.
I knew he'd be back.
Feels like Christmas morning.
Look at that --
A miracle on ice. Stunning.
You all right, Dexter?
This is like a dream.
Standing on the home
ice of the Miami Blades.
I never pegged you
for a hockey fan.
There's something about standing in
a big cool hole I find very relaxing.
So, what do we know?
Same as the others.
No blood.
So far,
I don't see any hesitation cuts.
No bones flayed.
I think our boy's got
his confidence back.
He never lost it.
He was just getting bored.
What do you think he's
trying to tell us?
That hockey's a violent sport.
- What else?
- He's escalating the thrill.
Posing his victim in the middle of a
20,000-seat arena for all Miami to see,
to show them -- to show us --
what he's capable of doing.
What did I miss?
- Relax. You didn't miss anything.
- Yeah, but she is -- fingertips.
This body belongs to the frozen
fingertips we found in the truck.
Sherry Taylor.
It's another prostitute.
No blood -- no need for me.
Morgan, come up to the command center.
We may have a suspect.
- Is there really a suspect?
- I'll let you know, bro,
when I get back from my first
official Homicide investiga--
- I know her.
- Sherry?
Yeah, she called
herself Cherry.
We worked the same corner
when I was undercover.
You were, like, friends?
Yes.
- Do you want a hug?
- Fuck off.
I tore apart the security office.
A surveillance tape is missing.
Let me guess --
The one covering the ice.
- They said you were good.
- Don't bust my balls.
I've got the press knocking
on the door outside.
Somebody who was here last
night saw something --
Rent-a-badge,
cleaning crew,
crack whore in the men's room?
Come on, work with me.
They got a night watchman,
but we can't find him.
- Well, then, he's a suspect.
- Unless the ice-truck killer
abducted him to gain
entry into the arena.
Did your brother help
you out with that logic?
The night watchman could've just been
at the wrong place at the wrong time.
We need to get to his apartment
to see what we can find.
Actually, I was hoping I could hit
Calle Ocho, talk to my old contacts.
I thought you wanted
to get out of Vice.
Isn't that what you cried
to the Captain last week?
Yeah, I mean...
I didn't cry.
Listen, my girls know
this victim, okay?
They may have information
that could help us.
No, I want you to
work with Doakes.
Maria, she has contacts.
- You still got your tube top?
- And my nipple clamps.
Don't come back without
any information.
Everyone moves to Miami to die,
which means we have more junk
than any city in America.
A skilled bargain hunter
can find real treasure here,
but that's not my
idea of hunting.
I prefer a
stalk-and-ambush approach.
My instincts are impeccable,
but I have to be sure of my prey.
We're all adrenaline rush, you know?
Kill it til it dies.
We all meat hunters,
just out looking for dinner.
What you looking for?
- Can I see that one?
- Eh, good eye.
It's a fixed-blade skinning knife.
Full tang, stainless steel.
Real time-saver for
the hunter who likes to...
...do his own butchering
in the field.
See the way that blade
curves like that?
It's like the talon of an eagle.
15 bucks and she's yours.
I'll take it.
Hell, yeah, you'll take it.
Why would you not?
I'll get your change.
Easy, kid.
What the fuck are
you doing, boy?
I didn't see him.
- You all right, mister?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Honest mistake.
No harm.
Hey. You be careful
with that thing, huh?
Sorry about that, boss.
I only sell them.
So, what you hunt --
trophies or meat?
What do you think today, Dex?
The Winchester?
- What about the 9mm?
- A handgun?
Not exactly the weapon
of choice for pheasants.
You need a wide spread
to bring them down.
Did you ever shoot
anybody, dad?
- Afraid so.
- Any of them die?
Just one.
How'd it feel... to kill a guy?
Not so great, Dex.
When you take a man's life,
you're not just killing them.
You're snuffing out all the
things he'll ever become.
As a cop,
I only fire my weapon to save
a life. That's a code I live by.
Killing must serve a purpose.
Otherwise, it's just plain murder.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
Changed my mind.
I think we'll take the Ruger.
Rifle? I thought that shotguns
were best for pheasants.
We're not gonna hunt pheasants.
- It's a big one.
- Yeah.
This deer will put meat
on our table tonight.
It's still alive.
For now, this hunt will
control the urges you feel.
Channel them.
Why don't you go ahead, son?
Really?
Put the poor animal
out of its misery.
- Hi, Rose.
- Hi.
Congratulations on
your confirmation.
Thank you. Do I know you?
My name's James Doakes.
Miami metro P.D.
I'm investigating the murder of
an undercover cop and his wife.
That's terrible.
Were they members of the church?
- No, Rose, they weren't.
- I don't understand.
Rose, have you ever
seen this man before?
I don't know.
Why are you asking me?
Get away from my daughter.
It's okay.
At my church?
In front of my family?
Ricky and Kara
had a family, too.
You just opened
a dangerous door.
No, man, you did...
When you murdered a cop
and an innocent lady.
What is he talking
about, daddy?
Come on, honey.
Let's go.
- Daddy.
- Let's go!
You don't play by the rules, Guerrero.
Why should I?
You've got five minutes,
Bizach, okay?
Yo, look who's back.
Pero mirela,
como está caliente!
Who'd you fuck --
Dolce or Gabbana?
I let them both
pull a train, okay?
Listen, I... I got a confession
to make. I'm...
I'm not who you think I am.
I'm a cop.
Bridgett, get back --
Bridgett! I'm not gonna bust --
You're not a cop.
You're a whore.
- I'm not a fucking whore.
- Fucking who ?
What's wrong with being
a fucking whore, huh?
We trusted you, Brandy.
My name's Debra, okay?
And I'm not here to bust you.
He hit again --
The ice-truck killer. He got Cherry.
Cherry?
Shit.
This shit's crazy. I'm out.
I got a sister who lives in Ohio,
runs a fashion-boutique store.
I'm on the bus tomorrow.
I ain't closing my shop for no sick,
psycho bitch.
Fucking woman-hater.
I was on the street before him.
Fuck it.
I can get him, you guys.
You just got to give me something.
Did any of you all see Cherry with
anyone the night before last?
Well, I saw her last night,
and then she got into a
car and never came back.
But I was working
all night, so...
You know the driver?
No, but the car was,
like, one of those
old station wagons that have,
like, wood panels on the side.
This is good. This is good.
This is a lead.
I should go get
Laguerta to listen.
Who's Laguerta?
She's my lieutenant.
She hates me.
But I'm close with the Captain.
I'll talk to him.
- What?
- Never piss off your pimp.
- Laguerta's not my pimp.
- Is that right?
Bitch tell you what to do?
Is your pussy taking
all the grief?
Does she steal
everything you earn?
Yeah, she definitely does that.
Then she's your pimp, baby, and she
will mess you up if you play her.
I told you --
I'm not a fucking whore.
What's wrong with
being a fucking whore?
Hey. Bought you a present
to celebrate your first
official homicide case.
Seriously? It's a cactus.
You only have to water
it three times a year.
Gee, Dex,
you didn't have to go out of your way.
I didn't.
I was at the swap meet.
So, any news on
our frosty friend?
One of my contacts said
she saw Cherry getting in
a wood-panel station
wagon the night she died.
Did you check the DMV database?
As we speak. There are thousands
of registered station-wagon owners
in Miami-Dade county,
but guess who's not on the list?
The night watchman.
I knew Laguerta had her head
up her ass on that one.
She doesn't have shit on
the real ice-truck killer.
Good.
Why good?
It's good for you.
You're gonna be the one to apprehend
that heinous murderer, not her.
- Thanks.
- All right. Good night, sister.
- Don't stay up too late.
- Okay.
Thanks for stopping by.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Are you --
Is this a bad time? It's Rita.
No, it's fine.
Hi.
I was just...reading a sad story.
Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm --
Look, the thing is...
You need me to pick
up Cody after school?
No. Colleen's gonna take
him to karate with Hudson.
- What about Astor's piano?
- Jen's got that covered.
Look, it's social services.
There's a caseworker coming
by the house this afternoon.
I should be home by 4:00,
but with the buses...
I'll be there.
Don't worry about a thing.
Thank you, Dexter.
As you all know, a night watchman
from the hockey arena is missing.
Till now, we presumed he was abducted
or murdered by the ice-truck killer.
However, we searched
his apartment and found
a stolen surveillance tape
from the night of the murder.
Chief of security at the
hockey arena confirmed it.
The man you're looking at is Tony Tucci,
the missing night watchman.
And here's the best part --
Tucci has a record.
He pulled a knife
at a party in '97.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you
Tony Tucci, the ice-truck killer.
Bullshit.
Captain Matthews is coordinating
with the FDLE* to launch
(*Florida Department of Law Enforcement)
a statewide manhunt
as soon as we get clearances.
Does he drive a station wagon?
Excuse me?
Tucci --
What kind of car does he drive?
The last-known victim was seen
getting in a station wagon.
I don't recall asking for any questions,
Miss Morgan. Thank you.
Now, from this moment on, all our
resources go to finding this man.
Your individual assignments
will be coming shortly.
That's all for now.
Doesn't make sense.
After being so careful for so long,
why would he leave
recorded evidence?
Of course I agree
with my sister,
but unlike her,
I'm not upset.
He's still out there,
and I'm waiting... breathless.
You sure we can't
get you anything?
I'm fine.
Rita's usually home
in time for the kids.
I'm just backup.
Her bus must be late.
My file says Miss Bennett's supposed
to have personal transportation.
Yeah, well, she did and
will again very soon.
Probably next week.
Nothing to worry about.
I just have to make a note of it.
She's doing an exemplary job.
I wish all my home
visits were this lovely.
So why do you keep
coming around, then?
Routine follow-up for all
domestic-violence cases.
We need to ensure a stable
home environment exists.
It's a good thing.
The system does work from time to time.
I was actually taken in by a
wonderful family. No abuse.
In fact, my foster father
understood I had special needs.
Without him...
You're lucky.
Lucky.
I'm here!
Hey, everyone, I'm here.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
I am lucky.
What do I know about abuse?
Without the code of Harry,
I'm sure I would've committed
a senseless murder in my youth
just to watch the blood flow.
Just try and keep
him comfortable.
It's about all we
can do for him now.
I don't understand.
A week ago,
the doctor said he was getting better.
He is getting better, sweetie.
A body cannot suffer
in sweet repose.
What does that mean?
What the hell does that mean?
She's weird.
Listen, you two...
I'm not going to be
around much longer.
Dad, don't say that.
You can make it through
this if you fight.
When I'm gone,
I won't be able to stop
you from being who you are.
Sooner or later,
you'll need to do it.
Do what?
Just remember our lessons.
What lessons?
What are you talking about?
- I can't make it without you.
- Yes, you can.
If you feel like
you're slipping...
...lean on your sister.
She'll keep you connected.
Fucking forensics report.
- What'd they find?
- Tucci's hair and fiber.
Of course Tucci's hair and
fibers are on the body.
He's hauling her around with
his pork hands, isn't he?
Any word from the chem lab?
Same as the other murders.
The killer used liquid nitrogen
to preserve the tissue,
give it that bleached look.
You know how unstable
liquid nitrogen is?
You'd have to be a lab rat just
to mess around with that shit.
Tucci didn't even pass
high school chemistry.
Watch carefully.
Right there -- see?
Right before he
repositioned the torso.
He turned his head.
Like someone's giving
him directions.
Someone like the ice-truck killer
olding a motherfucking gun
to his back.
- The killer's framing Tucci.
- It looks that way.
Laguerta's gonna lose her
sheep shit when she finds out.
She's gonna have to cancel
her press conference.
And you know how Laguerta
loves her press conferences.
Can I borrow this tape?
Bingo.
I know what happens next in
this gruesome little scenario.
Jeremy is trying to
re-create his first kill,
ritualize it.
You ready?
I don't know if I
want to do this, man.
What's wrong? I thought you
wanted to see an alligator.
I do.
Come on.
It's in the marsh up here.
- Wait. Are you a pussy?
- No.
Okay.
Where is this place, man?
It's right up here.
Come on, Jer.
What are you talking about?
Don't be a bitch.
- Here we are.
- I don't see it.
It's right there.
See its eyes sticking out?
You have to get closer.
I still don't see it.
Really?
Maybe I was wrong.
There's no gator here,
is there?
I don't know, Lucas. Is there?
Anyone see a frisbee?
It flew in here somewhere.
Shit! Let's get the
fuck out of here.
What am I doing out here?
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
All I had to do was drive home,
have a taco, plan my attack.
Instead,
I tried to act human,
like it's my job to save lives.
Code of Harry
never covered this.
At least I know where Jeremy is
and what I need to do.
Don't let her.
Okay, my brave little soldier.
Let's get this nasty
shot out of the way.
- No!
- Wait!
- What is it, honey?
- He doesn't want the shot.
Your father's very sick.
He's in a lot of pain. He needs a shot.
- I want pain.
- He wants pain.
I'll have to tell the doctor.
He's not going to be happy
you're refusing your medication.
You can tell.
About the nurse? Yeah. She's...
...like me.
How could you tell?
She gives too much... morphine.
It's something else.
It's making me worse.
She's drugging you.
She's killing you by overdose.
Not just me.
Others, too.
Stop her.
What do you mean, stop her?
It's time.
Before she hurts anyone else.
See the look on his face,
like he's scared?
Like he has a gun
pointed at him?
I don't know, Debra.
It's not much -- a look off-camera.
There's more. One of my Vice contacts,
Gabrielle -- I trust her --
she saw the victim get
into a wood-paneled wagon
the night of the victim's death.
That was the last time anyone saw her.
Did a background report on Tucci.
He doesn't even own a car.
There's no fucking way this guy
can be the ice-truck killer. Sir.
What does lieutenant
Laguerta say about all this?
I came straight
to you, Captain.
You went around the back of
your commanding officer?
Laguerta doesn't listen to me.
Every time I open my mouth,...
You don't violate the chain of command.
You just don't.
Now, listen, Debra.
I gave you a shot in Homicide
because I think you can make
a halfway-decent detective.
But if I find you can't
swim in these waters,
I'll put you right
back on the street.
You got it?
Yes, sir.
Your father never would've pulled
the kind of shit you just did.
Did you know that one of your
officers has information
that casts some doubt on
this manhunt of yours?
Who, Morgan?
I realize you're something of
a folk hero around here, Maria,
but it would be a mistake to ignore
the work of a promising officer
just to further your
political career.
Is that what you
think I'm doing?
You were a middle-of-the-pack detective
before the press got ahold of you.
Thanks for the vote
of confidence.
It's a reality check,
and you need it.
And I got it.
Let's cut to the chase. Are you
telling me to call off my manhunt?
'Cause I will remind you that Jeb
Bush himself signed off on it.
No...
No. You go ahead and hold
your press conference, Maria.
People of this city need to know
we're doing something about this mess.
But don't expect
me to bail you out
if that night watchman
turns out to be a dead end.
A statewide manhunt is under
way right now in Florida.
According to police,
a night watchman is on the run
after the dismembered body parts
of a young South Beach
woman were found Tuesday,
stacked on the home ice
of the Miami Blades.
The woman is believed
to be the latest victim
of the notorious
ice-truck killer,
now responsible for five deaths
in the greater Miami area.
These terrible
attacks have to stop.
And we have to stop them.
With Tony Tucci now
linked to the murders,
it's our mission to find him.
Fucking joke.
Hey, going out tonight with the guys,
blow off a little steam -- you in?
- Hey, man, sounds good.
- Pick you up at 8:00.
Elevator's around the
corner and to your left.
Enjoy your stay with us.
- Hello?
- Rita, this is Mr. Curtis.
Are you coming to
pick up Astor?
Oh, no, a friend of mine is --
Denise. Is she not there?
I'm afraid not,
but your daughter is.
She's the last kid
left here at school.
I don't have a car.
Is she okay?
Yeah, she's just fine,
but we can't keep her here much longer.
Okay. Okay,
I'll work something out.
Do it again!
Shh. Let's not wake up Cody.
Now, let's see
about that splinter.
That's a deep one.
This might sting a bit.
But the magical Splinter Fairy will
soon make you forget all about it.
Who's the magical
Splinter Fairy?
She's the second cousin
to the Tooth Fairy.
She brings candy if you put your
splinter under your pillow at night.
The Tooth Fairy is make-believe,
just like the boogeyman.
Hi, guys.
You're right, Astor.
There's no such thing
as the boogeyman.
But the Splinter Fairy --
she's the real deal.
Will the Splinter
Fairy come if I cry?
Thanks for picking her up.
If I had a heart,
it might be breaking right now.
Oh, sorry.
Who we picking up now, man?
'Cause he sure ain't
sitting on my lap.
We're not picking
up anybody, bro.
Well, what we doing
in the Gables?
I told you. We're blowing
off some steam. This is it.
What the hell is this?
It's a disguise.
One of Guerrero's top lieutenants --
he lives here,
and we're gonna fuck him up.
Hold up, Mac. I thought you said you
wanted to go out and get
shit-faced, man.
I am shit-faced.
How do I look?
Man, I'm all for sending the message,
but this --
This ain't the way, man.
Why the hell not?
The guy's scum.
Mac, listen.
I've got to talk to you.
Mac, Mac! Hey, listen up, man.
I showed my face to Guerrero.
They gonna think I'm
behind this shit !
- That's part of the plan.
- What plan?
You fucked my sister.
You fucked a cop's wife.
Now you're just fucked, buddy.
Open the door!
Shit.
Fuck.
Hey, quit fucking around.
Turn on the lights.
Come on, man.
Turn on the fucking lights!
You're mine now.
- What do you want?
- Silence.
You gonna fuck me, faggot? 'Cause
I killed the last guy who raped me.
What guy?
He raped you...
The guy you killed
when you were 15?
Why didn't you tell anybody?
Would you?
He fucked me, and I killed him,
and if you try,
I'll kill you, too.
I understand now.
Why didn't I see it before?
Jeremy didn't murder
that boy four years ago.
He was taking out the garbage.
Just like I do.
Look, I really don't want to
cancel all my credit cards,
and I hate waiting in line
at the DMV*,
(*Department of Motor Vehicles)
so give me back the wallet
you stole from my car,
or I'll break your
fucking neck.
It's in my backpack.
Wait --
Is that all?
You want more?
That boy who raped you four years ago --
did he deserve to die?
Yeah.
He did.
Well, the boy the
other day didn't.
Remember that.
It could save your life one day.
Mr. Tinker?
Mr. Tinker, where are you?
Are you trapped behind the couch again,
Mr. Tinker-stinker?
The nurse was my
first playmate.
I'll always be grateful to her
for opening up so many
magnificent new doors for me.
Things were a little
messy in the beginning.
Hey, perfecting a
new craft takes time.
But I was trained well.
Those who witnessed my early
stumbles never had a chance to tell.
I've just been looking
through your photo album.
Hope you don't mind.
Are all your victims in here?
I'm sorry.
Let me help you with that.
Scream and lose a tongue.
I helped them...
All of them.
I took their pain away.
I understand.
Now it's time to
take away your pain.
It was messier than
I anticipated,
but it was still a special day.
But, of course, it was really Harry
who paved the road to my salvation.
With the nurse put down,
Harry lived another year
before hardening arteries squeezed
the last bit of life from him,
but his lessons have
never failed me.
Harry taught me that
death isn't the end.
It's the beginning
of a chain reaction
that will catch you if
you're not careful.
He taught me that none of us are who
we appear to be on the outside...
....but we must maintain
appearances to survive.
But there was something
Harry didn't teach me,
something he didn't know,
couldn't possibly know.
The willful taking of life
represents the ultimate
disconnect from humanity.
It leaves you an outsider,
forever looking in,
searching for company to keep.
Sweet ride! Is it yours?
It's yours,
until your mom can get a new one.
I borrowed it from impound
right before auction.
- Dexter...
- Can we get in?
You better.
All you can do is
play along at life
and hope that sometimes
you get it right.
Thank you.
Score one for the
little wooden boy.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com