Everyone was aiming
for the eye of the fish,
but the guy who hit the bullseye,
was the founder of Apha1, Mehta.
And that's how
Maharashtra offline princess
KC Enterprises, finally tied the knot.
We need to wait and watch,
where the princes of undersized
kingdoms like Pragati will aim for now.
What will be their next target now?
To find out like, comment
and subscribe to RRR.
Who the fuck is this Startup Kumar.
Since I mentioned don't write dickhead,
he keeps writing dickhead
when I come online.
We should have seen this coming.
But we didn't.
The founders should have seen it.
But this is backstabbing.
How would they know?
And this idiot Pappi
bought an extra cake.
It was for everyone,
to celebrate.
Can deals be cancelled like this?
Pappi, all this is very common.
It happens. If we couldn't crack this
one, we'll partner with someone else.
So what?
The guys must be planning something big.
Not to worry.
Yogi didn't tell us anything.
I'll go ask him.
I'll come too.
Jeetu sir's deal--
You're not supposed
to talk about the CEO.
You'll get us in trouble, Pappi.
Five million was already locked.
Why did VC cancel that?
We were the ones who unlocked it.
Don't tell brother anything.
That's the third mail from Prachi.
Asking when are we meeting.
Did you ask Naveen?
He hasn't been answering
my calls for two days.
That's why I told him not to move out.
You can't get mad at your roommate
if your girlfriend dumped you.
A sensitive guy should not live alone.
That's why I moved in with you.
Yes, brother. Are you here?
We're coming.
So Elon Musk...
Jeff Bezos...
So you finally bought the SUV.
-Touch screen, four-ways AC.
-Sunroof.
Yeah.
Yogi, how is it?
Big.
This isn't what you call big.
It's going to look timid
compared to a private jet.
That's what you guys are gonna buy,
when you release your IPO.
IPO.
See this...
Perks of having a job.
Right, screw me.
We employees keep running
between salary and bonus.
You startup guys are changing the world.
No, brother.
Don't call me brother, Yogi.
You are older than me.
By the way, congratulations.
Mandal was saying
you are going to have a baby.
When did I tell you?
-I did.
-Oh, yes.
-Yeah.
-Actually, even my friends call me Mandal.
Yeah, so...
But everyone's invited
to the baby's naming ceremony.
Tell Jeetu and Naveen
they are invited too.
I want all four friends there.
It's a family affair.
What was the name of
Naveen's cute girlfriend?
-Shreya.
-Shall we invite her too?
-Where is she nowadays?
-What are you saying, brother?
I told you...
You are going to be a father,
learn to behave.
But I am just another guy around you.
-Let's go booze.
-No, no...
I am not asking, I am telling you.
It's been a long time.
Your sister-in-law has made
this state a dry state.
Open the sunroof.
It's the moonroof at night, Yogi. Okay?
Mandal.
I really bonded with your brother today.
-That--
-He's a cool guy.
When you win after you've
lost is a 'Baazigar' (Player)!
What do you call a person
who's lost a winning game.
Founder.
No, no, no. Co-founder.
Yeah, co-founder.
Oh, God!
Yogi and Mandal's
house is being ransacked.
You?
What happened?
I still have a key.
PIVOT?
2.0?
Yes.
So that's what Pragati 2.0
is going to look like.
Seriously? Product change?
Isn't that a desperate move, guys?
Are you guys sure about it?
-Yeah. Absolutely.
-Yes.
Yeah...
We just need to figure out
little things. But mostly we are good.
Don't worry, Prachi.
From Nokia to Starbucks, all these
big companies were made by pivoting.
And according to a survey,
13% of startup
fails if they don't pivot
at the right time.
And according to that survey,
25% of startups shutdown
because of a pivot gone wrong.
You are trying to
convince us and yourself,
that we should do this.
But... I think it's right to say
that we don't have a choice.
Yes, but what's wrong with it?
Have you heard about Odeo?
The cream biscuit.
Odeo. ODEO.
It was a podcast-sharing website.
But they suffered a setback like us
when iTunes was launched.
And even they had to pivot.
Now we all have Odeo on our phones.
Called Twitter.
-Have you heard of Bourbon?
-The cream biscuit?
It was a check-in app,
which pivoted to a photo-sharing app.
That's the first thing
we check every morning we get up.
Instagram.
Everyone pivots.
Milkbikis.
Did they pivot too?
No. It's still a biscuit.
Guys.
Look, I think you want to
believe that I am naive,
but I am not.
I know what you guys are doing.
After the series-A was cancelled,
you guys reached a dead end.
You are trying to correct your course,
and I understand.
But if you're going to use my fuel,
to find yourself a different route,
get a driver first.
You guys want to pivot,
get a CTO first.
Yes.
Yes, I mean... yes.
Prachi, we don't have a tech head,
but we have a tech team.
-We will manage.
-You don't have to manage.
Every team needs a captain.
Name one company that pivoted
without a tech head.
Yes.
Yes...
I'm meeting with the
partners in three days.
Get yourself a CTO,
I will convince them
that we need to pivot.
Three days?
How will we find a
CTO in three days, Prachi?
Rohan, please tell them
how much runway they have?
About 90 days.
It's not three days,
it's 3.33 % of your entire battery life.
It is what it is guys.
I want to help you,
but you have to help yourself first.
Next meeting.
Shall we?
Thank you.
All the best, guys.
Okay.
Do you want to come for a smoke?
No.
Since when did you
start smoking so much.
I wasn't even a smoker.
Jeetu was.
He needed company.
He's gone, and now I am addicted.
It's been six months.
I think you should drop old habits,
and get yourself some new ones.
Hiring someone for a post like this,
is nothing short of a wedding.
Like we have to find a bride,
check if she suits you,
then arrange a meeting.
Then she has to like you.
Convince her to marry you.
And we've no clue who she is or where.
Hey... he sent a mail invite.
Meeting Pragati co-founders
with CTO in three days.
-Are you serious?
-Issue number 13.
Finding the CTO in three days.
Where was your list of issues when we
were discussing this the past two days?
I was posting it on the group, but
you guys weren't taking it seriously.
What else can we do, Mandal?
Shut down the company?
Did I say that?
I never said that. What is he saying?
Listen bro, either we go down,
or we change the company's direction.
It's very simple.
If you know a third way,
then speak now. We can try that.
-Oh, man...
-Let's do it, bro.
Change is the only constant.
Let's do it, okay.
Let's tell HR to put up
a post for walk-in interviews.
You keep making a list of issues,
and we'll execute Pragati 2.0.
Come on.
Let's not talk. Let's do it.
-Give me the bag.
-Here.
That's not what I said.
-You are always coming up with issues.
-What do you mean? What?
-Hello.
-'Appu, I've mailed you the job offer.'
Yeah, I got your mail.
Yes.
Just give me a second.
Yup!
Yes, please tell me.
'Appu, you know your situation
better than me.'
'Leave that sinking ship called Pragati,
and come join me.'
Can't say if it's
a sinking ship, but...
I feel very valued here.
You know, like I am a part
of every decision in the product.
'And here you'll make the product.
Lead programmer.'
-'Your salary--'
-Salary is not the issue, sir.
After all, it's CISCO, yeah.
-Appu, come on. Everyone's waiting.
-Yeah, one minute.
Yeah, sir. I will get back to you. Yeah.
So this is what Pragati 2.0
is going to look like, after the pivot.
I still have to finalise
a few more details.
I will prepare a product
road map in a couple of days,
and share it with everyone. Okay.
But, sir, this needs major changes.
You can't succeed
without changes, Sukhi.
-We'll do it.
-I mean cost,
execution...
It's going to be a tough job.
Say something, guys.
It does look tricky.
Well, cost was already on my list.
Number fourteen, execution.
Mandal.
I am still trying to compile this.
But we are taking a huge left turn.
It's a major change.
Don't be afraid of the change, Appu.
It's the only constant.
But, Yogi... we
We first locked a product vision,
and worked on it for a year.
Finally, it's stabilised now.
Why are we moving our goalpost,
just because Alpha1 has made a move?
No, we're not doing
anything because of Alpha1.
First of all, get this straight.
Our end goal hasn't changed.
Appu. We are only changing our route.
Guys, a pivot is not a failure.
It's a process.
Paypal pivoted five times in a year.
Before they landed on
their best and final version.
You guys know every
startup changes its product.
Drop all attachments
with the older version.
Let's burn the boat.
Let's jump out of a
parachute and build a plane.
What? What?
Let's jump out of a
plane and build a parachute.
Right.
In case the parachute doesn't open,
then what?
-It will open if we pull properly.
-Yes.
Naveen, Yogi,
product pivot is always interesting.
But challenging.
I mean we'll need a team for it,
also means extra workload.
Framework, architecture,
we'll have to redesign everything.
So, I am not sure how we can...
Number fifteen,
convince the team to pivot.
This will shock the entire backhand.
Web services, Deb ops...
Not to count the load on them.
The workload was always there.
But we did it, didn't we?
Back then we had...
I mean back then we had a CTO.
Naveen, I think we should
discuss this at length.
Aparajita,
I think that we'll discuss this.
We'll discuss it and let you know.
If you guys have any feedback to share.
I mean if you want to think about it,
then you should think
about how we fix this.
How do we make this happen?
You should give your
input in this direction.
Stop counting problems.
Yeah, got it?
-Yes.
-Makes sense.
Yes, sir.
Here we imagined we'll
be looking at half of Mumbai,
and here we're stuck
looking at uncle's underwear.
And he hasn't even
changed them for a year.
Cheetah print.
Shit.
Hey...
Naveen, I saw your plan.
We can do it.
We'll discuss the remaining
technical details with your tech head.
How can we do this
in three days, Prachi?
You know who we are trying to replace.
He wasn't just our CTO.
We have to do it, Naveen.
You'll have to put this behind you.
Look, sometimes what you need to do,
is more important
than what you want to do.
Have I told you,
how I found out about
Pragati in the first place?
From my brother.
He's been a user
of your app since day 1.
And you know, just like him,
Pragati has had many users,
and will have many users in the future.
So you have to remember that.
Whatever you do,
whatever you have done
and whatever you will do in future,
is not for yourself.
It's for others.
Whatever you are building,
has to be bigger than you,
me, or any of us.
But the builder is gone.
I don't know...
Sometimes I feel,
can I even handle this without him?
There are no permanent enemies
or permanent friends here.
And... especially not CTOs.
They are like startup butterflies.
Today here, tomorrow there.
They keep fluttering.
Today they are with one co-founder,
tomorrow they are with another.
But in the end,
the one who keeps standing will be you.
Because you started this alone.
And you will finish this.
Right?
Naveen, this is your journey.
No matter what happens,
you have to keep moving forward.
Finding a CTO in three
days is difficult, I get it.
Make it easy for yourself.
Just look for someone who is
willing to help you out at this point.
That's it.
Yeah, I think you are right.
Okay, all the best.
I... I want you to know that
I have faith in you.
I'll see you soon. Take care.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Ohh...
sorry, I didn't know.
No, no, Appu, please carry on.
Any update from HR?
How many CVs so far?
How much.
Not even one.
Message from Prachi.
What is she saying?
"Let's meet day after at lunch."
Fuck.
What do we do, Yogi?
The day is about to end.
Fuck walk-in,
we'll have to do walk-out interviews.
I'll scan from Hiranandini to Kurla.
We'll find some struggler coders.
And prepare a task sheet,
and ask everyone to write their problems
regarding pivot.
Sir... are we auditioning
for Roadies here?
-What? -Several people
are waiting in line outside.
What?
Don't you accept online payments?
No, sir.
Embrace technology.
It's necessary.
Thanks sir.
Is the OLA startup office here?
Yes, this is the one.
-Are you a coder?
-No. I am a salesman.
Joining in three days.
Even the notice period is three months.
No possible.
Your portfolio is quite impressive.
He's saying thank you.
Why isn't he saying it himself?
These genius coders are very introvert.
They don't speak for themselves,
their work does.
He's saying if you want to hire him,
you got to hire me as well.
I had a word with them.
I can join in a month.
Brother Yogi, doesn't matter
how many glasses you buy,
I cannot do it.
I can't do it.
I am married to my job.
I am not telling you to divorce her.
Just have an extra-marital on the side.
-No, no.
-Till the delivery of my baby.
-Bro...
No.
Kishore sir.
It's a surprise to
see a senior guy like you,
in a start-up circle.
Because everyone is a college dropout.
That is why I hate the startup culture.
Every startup wants to
move fast and break things.
But I am here to move
slow and build things.
This startup culture
needs to shut down, sir.
Shut down!
Coder.
-Excuse me, are you a coder?
-No.
-Bro... are you on the tech team?
Okay, let's seal the deal in 15 days.
Let me know if it's a yes.
Bro, watch my speed.
-Coder?
-Yeah.
Are you a lead coder?
-Excuse me, are you interested in.
-I said I don't want a credit card.
Yes.
We'll call you.
What is this?
CTO?
How much equity will I get?
What's your experience?
I don't code.
But I can get a coder for you.
What the fuck am I doing?
HR will let you know our decision ASAP.
See... just because she's your HR,
you are addressing her by her post.
But guess what, she is human first.
Human resources.
And she has a name.
Ma'am, what's your name?
Hina Rizwan.
But everyone calls me HR.
How is my second favourite
coder from college?
I quit coding after my MBA.
Now I am working at Indusverse.
Marketing manager.
If I have another beer,
I'll head straight to the office
with my resignation,
and throw it in my boss' face.
Have it.
Thank you.
What do you mean you
got sober on the way?
I bought an entire pitcher for you.
You should have fucking peed
after giving your resignation!
You can't even control 200 ml of pee,
bloody nincompoop.
I can join from tomorrow.
In fact, I've seen your app.
And I already have a few ideas.
Like we can use a few APIs
to make the transition smooth and...
That's KPI.
Sorry.
No, API.
You guys are interviewing for tech head,
and you don't know what is API?
Application programming interface.
Sixteen.
We need a tech person
to hire a tech person.
If you can't give a solution,
then stop counting the problems.
Please, please, Appu.
If knowing the definition of API
was in my KPI,
I would have never asked you.
But hiring a CTO isn't in my KPI either.
What if we hire some amateur?
The management will blame me.
Yes, I understand that.
Do you know what
'M' in 'CMO' stands for?
-Marketing.
-And Management.
Mr. Saurav Mandal,
I am also the chief management officer.
And the management...
See...
Is personally asking you
because it trusts your judgement.
See, Appu, after all,
you are the senior most
tech person we have here.
Okay, look.
Even I have some doubts regarding
this pivot like the rest of you.
But we'll discuss that.
But even for that, we need a tech head.
Come on.
Okay.
Yes.
But there are other ways to test coders,
than just asking questions.
Okay, yes.
I'll my boss just
the way my boss hired me.
Yeah... done.
Hi.
I am here for the interview.
The HR sent me.
Yeah, hi. Please, come in.
Come, come.
Shall I reduce the temperature?
No, thanks. I am fine.
Just a bit tired.
The staircase.
Yes.
You know, Naveen,
the perfect AC temperature
is supposed to be 24 degrees Celsius.
Aah... I didn't know that.
Well, nobody did.
So, I wrote an algorithm to prove it,
and put it on social media.
People needed time to accept it,
but now whenever you switch on
the air-conditioning,
the default temperature is
24 degree Celsius.
Wow, that's quite impressive.
As I said, nobody believed it initially,
but now they do.
So... you wanna talk a little
bit more about my past experiences.
Yeah, sure.
Seems like you're interviewing me,
not the other way.
You know, Naveen, how I look at it is,
it's important for a company
to choose the right candidate,
and equally important for a candidate
to choose the right company.
Yeah, correct.
Yes.
Mayank, your CV has pretty big names.
SwiftPay and IndoGames.
And we are just a growing company.
So...
I mean are you sure?
You're right.
I mean when I joined these startups,
they were small too.
It's my job to make them big.
Okay.
That's cool.
One second. Sorry.
Sorry.
So, Mayank, how did you
know about this opening?
Was that Prachi?
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't want any bias
to come in between, Naveen.
I don't want you to hire me
because your investor referred me.
I want you to hire me because,
you should feel I am
the right guy for the job.
So?
What do you feel?
I don't know.
I mean your CV is quite strong.
CV...
The thing about CVs is it's just a page.
You're looking at the entire book,
in flesh and blood.
Talking about the book,
let me narrate a chapter for you.
You know, when I was with SwiftPay,
the CEO Aman...
Great guy, lovely guy.
Great to work with, but...
his only problem was
he was a little myopic.
You know,
a little short sighted with working.
I mean when you have a guy
who can build a road to Mars,
why would you want to plan a trip
to the moon?
Isn't it?
Anyway, I prepared a version
according to his product brief,
but I also prepared my own version.
And even got more traction on it.
No points for guessing, which version
is currently getting widely used.
Naveen, I feel there are only two
kinds of people in this world.
The one who takes shit.
and the others who shit done.
I get shit done.
So, I've no doubts
that this pivot can help Pragati,
become a rocketship if you're lucky.
But if you have me,
you don't need luck.
Think about it
and let me know.
Or let Prachi know
right?
Thank you.
Pleasure.
What...
When did he do that?
We'll do it, right?
Listen, Mandal.
Pawan Putra's mom and dad
are coming to the office tomorrow.
To meet the CEO.
Pappi.
What happened?
Sir...
-I...
-What?
I drunk-dialled my dad.
You drunk-dialled your own dad?
Everyone was saying
the future of the company is uncertain.
I got a little nervous and...
Sir, please help me out.
I don't want to leave.
Yogi isn't in the office.
Naveen is busy.
You handle their parents.
Thank you, sir.
What?
Me?
Even me and my father are...
No, no.
And, didn't he want to meet the CEO?
But you're the Chief Management Officer.
I mean... this is a management issue.
Like managing Pappi's father.
And he's coming to Mumbai
with a form for the Bank PO.
Please convince him.
I know you can convince him, sir.
Please.
Why is my heartbeat racing?
Can I get you some water?
I think you can do it.
Please, sir.
Coming.
Who drunk dials his own father?
I've been looking since morning.
I think I found God, but not
one tech guy that suits the bill.
How are you handling it out there?
I am standing in front
of Vikroli's co-working space.
Yeah.
I'll let you know if I find anyone.
Okay.
So, HR, how is it going?
Good.
How is your health?
You taking care of your diet?
-Yeah-yeah, I am.
-Yaa.
One second.
Yeah.
I needed another approval.
Of course.
I'll sign it.
What the fuck? What is this?
It's a draft of a termination letter.
Who told you to do this?
Naveen, everyone's contract
has a three-month notice period.
And the company only has funds
for three months.
Who... told you this?
See.
These are our expenses,
and that's our account balance.
After punching in the entire data,
this is the result.
Three months.
Even I don't want to believe it.
But these numbers were entered by you.
And since it's tally,
it can't be wrong.
Does anyone else know about this?
No.
And I'll keep it that way.
See, Naveen,
I am just looking out for Pragati.
Some of the earlier startups,
faced major issues with employees.
I'll send you some links.
See for yourself.
Sometimes founders even go to jail
for such dues.
It's statutory compliance.
See, it's just a failsafe.
We should prep.
I really hope we never have to use this.
I'll take your leave.
You think about it.
Since I'm a Brahmin, I won't lie.
I thought since this is a startup,
you'd be working out of some garage.
But it...
looks like an office.
Yes.
Uncle, I am not a Brahmin,
yet I won't lie.
It's not that kind of start-up.
We don't know how many
'types' of startups exist.
Where we come from
the startup trend hasn't picked up.
I see.
What place is that?
'Ghatiya.'
Pappi, that's no way to talk.
Just because you live in a big city now,
doesn't mean you should
disrespect your hometown.
'Ghatiya' is the name of our town.
Yes.
Ohh...
We come from a family
of government employees.
Yes.
My father worked for 'BHEL',
and so do I.
His older brother wanted
to try something different,
so he joined CELL instead.
I said fine.
I got him in GAIL, but no.
He wanted to join a startup.
Here's my question,
if he doesn't finish his internship
who will offer him a job?
No, uncle.
This company and Pappi's internship
is absolutely safe.
Well, we had an important project
on our hands,
which didn't go too well. That's it.
It must have made him
anxious and called you.
Ups and downs are
common in any job, uncle.
Look, son.
Only share markets see ups and downs,
and we choose FD.
Yes.
If he wanted to join a private company,
he could have opted for TCS, Infosys,
which are the bigger
players in the market.
Your friends are there too.
In a 9-5 job.
What? What did you say?
What did you say?
I said I didn't want
a 9-5 job like them.
And you would rather work 9-9 here?
Uncle... Uncle...
Tell me one thing.
What are your office timings?
What are your working hours?
9 to...
9 to?
-Okay, fine.
-No, no...
-I get it. I get it. I get it.
-No, no.
See...
Nothing is certain in a startup.
Companies like this open
and shut down overnight.
Friends starting a company is one thing,
but keeping it afloat is different.
Rather than wasting
your education on a startup,
you should have opted for a job instead.
Secured our future and yours as well.
Pappi, your father
is just like my father.
Says you're his son,
but doesn't trust his decisions.
Uncle...
even I built this startup for friends.
But I know how to run my business.
Our entire family has been
running businesses for many years.
As a kid, I read more ledger books
than comic books.
Then I did my MBA... from IIM Indore.
Yes.
Education never goes to waste.
And we don't work here
staring at the clock.
Because what we do here
will change time.
Look, son.
You are the founder.
Yes.
If you succeed,
it will be your success alone.
Because Pappi is just an intern.
Who has benefitted from
working under so much pressure?
-Am I right?
-Right. Right.
How do you cook lentils?
Lentils?
In the pressure cooker.
Everyone uses the pressure cooker,
but you can make it
with any other utensil.
Well...we can make it
in a different utensil,
-but it will be time-consuming.
-Yes.
Cooks faster in a pressure cooker.
Yeah...
you are absolutely right.
Pressure.
Pappi may be working
under pressure here,
but he'll be hardboiled pretty soon.
I can understand.
Yes.
But I know Pappi better than you.
Pappi isn't ready
for such a daunting task.
Papa, you say I am your son,
but you don't trust him.
Shut up.
You talk about trust.
We've been to your flat.
There were no rations.
Just a satchel of green
leaves and a lighter.
I knew his room wouldn't be clean.
This is why his brother
booked an OYO room for us.
How is your room?
Excellent. Nice. Spic and span.
-They gave us a toothbrush and a comb.
-Yes.
Clean towels.
See aunty,
the startup trend reached
all the way to your house,
and you haven't realised it yet.
This place where you're staying,
was a startup like ours.
And the founder was younger than Pappi
when he started.
The company's initial job was online
listing of budget hotels in their area,
and it was called Oraville Stays.
Later he realised the problem
isn't about accommodation,
it was about a standard service.
Then he...
Pivoted...
I mean changed his business idea.
And within one year of the pivot,
Oraville Stays became OYO.
On Your Own.
Just like we are right now.
'On our Own.'
Why are you telling us all this?
I am not.
Bastard... is disagreeing your passion?
What? You're on the same page now?
You are changing the approach
of the entire company,
I can change my own.
#Parivartan (change).
What happened?
Couldn't find anyone?
Not even one. In this short notice.
Most of them are assholes.
And the decent ones are getting paid
double than Silicon Valley in Bangalore.
So who will work for us?
I think we are fucked.
Not yet.
There is a guy. Mayank Arora.
He's got experience,
and his CV looks good.
I am meeting him again today,
you guys should too.
Have you met him?
Do you think he fits the bill?
-Yes, I think he's okay.
-Great.
Tell Prachi we completed
the task before time.
Prachi sent him.
We should thank her.
-Okay...
-Wait a second.
-Prachi sent him?
-Yes, why?
Is he an investor hound?
What is that?
Fuck hostel four...
How are you dickhead?
At least stop ragging me now, Yogi.
How is my second favourite
coder from college?
I quit coding after my MBA.
Now I am working at Indusverse.
Marketing manager.
What are you saying?
What about your startup?
Didn't you see?
We were trending on Twitter last year.
#boycottfoodinthehood
Are you serious?
But your product was great.
You were getting affordable
food to half the slums in Mumbai.
Bro, nowadays people judge you
by your popularity, not your actions.
Some asshole put up a post.
The word 'hood' is
insulting to our users.
Thus began the trolling.
And do you know what the funny part is?
Most of our users don't
even know what hood means.
But until then we got
so much negative PR...
You had to shut down?
No, we had to change our name.
RobinFood.
Our new CMO's idea.
Investors sent him to change
the visual of the company.
But that asshole eventually
changed the entire vision.
-So, you had to shut down the company.
-No.
We don't get any orders
from Dharavi now, just Pali Hill.
I did not want to
be a part of that, so...
So did you shut down
the company, or what?
No. I quit.
But why didn't all the founders say no?
Why didn't you resist?
We were desperate.
And we didn't know the CMO will do this.
It's typical, brother Yogi.
When the company's screwed,
investors send their own guys.
Most of them are innocent and harmless.
Like puppies.
But some of them are hounds.
Investor's hound.
What the fuck is a hound?
They hunt vulnerable startups.
They come with a simple goal.
To make the startup successful,
and give the investors an early exit.
But that success comes at a cost.
Founders exit before the investors.
Meaning if Mayank Arora comes on board,
we could be out.
Honestly, even I thought
he was a control freak.
But we're out of options, Yogi.
That doesn't mean we'll hire a hound.
And you said he seemed
like a control freak.
-But we got to hire someone.
-Guys, I found someone.
The hackathon we arranged,
one guy killed it.
Perfect programming logic,
lovely code layout,
and exceptional handling
was exceptionally handled.
The best part was
he had his own algorithm.
Not copied from stack overflow.
Please explain in Hindi, English
or Bhojpuri. We don't speak Java.
It's been ages since I last saw a code.
Like... 30 years.
-Is he really good?
-He is amazing.
See it for yourself.
Let's go take a look.
Great.
What?
I don't know, dickhead. I am Ops.
I flunked C.
Are all the test cases clear?
Yes. Even the corner cases.
I always thought codes
look like The Matrix.
But this is just numbers and letters.
It's been around by
the numbers and letters.
I know. I know.
But with one wrong semi-colon,
it will give an error.
But that's how we were hired.
Jeetu sir put five bugs in a code
like this, and asked us to find it.
I had done the best. Four bugs.
-Fine.
-Great, Appu.
Appu...
Sir... his bug test is over.
How many? Did he match Appu's record?
-Did he find the fifth bug?
-No.
-Then how many did he find?
-Six bugs?
-What?
-Yeah.
There was already a
bug in Jeetu sir's code,
which even he missed I guess.
-He found it?
-And fixed it.
-Seems like some stud, man.
-Yeah.
-Where is he?
-Conference room.
Come.
He fixed all the bugs.
Chintu.
-Dungeon Master.
-Good evening, Naveen sir.
Good evening, Yogender sir.
Good evening, Saurabh sir.
And with all due respect,
there's an underscore
between dungeon and master.
Bloody--
Let's at least talk, Yogi.
Why do you become so rigid?
What else should we do?
-You want to hire Dungeon.
-But we'll have to hire someone.
Do you have another option?
Why are we considering him?
Okay, fine.
Let's relax and think about it.
Okay?
I know you have a problem with Dungeon,
but that can be solved.
Did you see how he was bullshitting us?
I've come back because I've
nothing but respect for you guys.
I could have taken up a job
in Silicon Valley, but...
I think you guys are the only
ones who deserve to be my bosses.
What bullshitting?
He was being so respectful.
He never even showed
respect to his father.
And I am his distant uncle.
Please think practically
and not emotionally.
We have to go meet Prachi.
I know you have problems with DM, but--
Great. You're giving him
nicknames already.
You guys might have forgotten,
but I didn't.
He was only 17 when that
dickhead personally attacked me.
I was 17.
I was just a college kid back then.
Now I am a college pass-out.
People change after college.
You keep saying change
is the only constant.
But this rule doesn't apply to morons.
Look at yourself.
Why are you getting mad at me?
I only get mad at people who are close.
Naveen, tell him.
Don't drag me into
your toxic relationship.
We are not in a toxic relationship.
We are in a complicated relationship.
We are fucking not in any relationship.
Why are you cussing now?
Okay, fine. Sorry. Sorry.
Guys, Prachi is arriving in two hours.
We got to decide now.
The decision is simple.
How can we hire Dungeon
after what he did?
I only did it because,
I knew the potential
of the product even back then.
I just want to be a part of it.
We cannot meet Prachi without a CTO,
and we're out of options
except for Dungeon.
Mayank Arora?
I don't want you to hire me,
because your investor referred me.
I want you to hire me because,
you should feel I am
the right guy for the job.
Seriously?
You were against him.
My opinion has changed.
I think we can take him.
Even my opinion has changed now.
I think Dungeon is better.
Jeetu literally kicked him out,
and now you want to offer him his seat.
You know,
I never wanted to replace Jeetu.
This is business.
Sometimes what we need to do,
is more important
than what we want to do.
Then let's replace
him with Mayank Arora.
Why do we need this idiot?
I mean when you have a guy,
who can build a road to Mars,
why would you want
to plan a trip to the moon?
I told you he'll want to run the show.
How can he?
He's alone, and we are three.
You can control a hound,
but not a 20-year kid.
Not every guy the investors
send would be a hound.
I don't have a problem
with Mayank Arora.
Fine, even I don't
have a problem with him.
Is it a yes or no?
It's always been a yes for me.
-For who?
-Who?
That...
Mayank.
Till now you were rooting for DM.
Why don't you ever take a stand in life?
How did Mayank get in now?
I haven't even met that Mayank.
How can I believe he's a control freak.
Think about it
and let me know.
Or let... Prachi know.
But I've met him.
I've been saying this too.
Mayank is a better choice than DM.
He isn't better. They both
have their own distinct problems.
You know what, let's order something.
There is no 'Dahipuri' here.
I ordered 'Sev puri'.
No one said 'dahipuri'.
I ordered 'Dahi puri'.
He did.
Tell him.
-He said 'Dahi puri'.
-He said.
You only said 'sev puri'.
Why wouldn't I order 'Dahi puri'?
I don't have any
enmity with 'Dahi puri'.
-He said it. -You said 'Sev
puri' and I ordered 'Sev puri'.
-Two guys are saying this.
-Yogi, both of us are saying this.
Eat it.
-This isn't fair.
-Two guys are saying this.
Next time write down your orders.
Give.
-Wouldn't I have ordered 'Dahi puri'?
-Guys...
-Don't eat it. Don't...
-What are you doing?
Mayank is on the way.
He just texted me.
He is asking when are we meeting Prachi.
We didn't even appoint him yet,
he thinks he's the CTO.
Typical like a hound.
Dungeon is better than him.
He is almost family.
But at least Prachi
is okay with this Mayank.
If she says no to Dungeon.
Then our pivot plan
will stay on the board.
Wait a minute, guys.
It will be our decision
who will be the CTO.
We just need someone so
that we can get her approval.
In that case,
we all know who is
the best man for this job.
I am the best man for this job.
Naveen, I feel there are
two kinds of people in this world.
Since the day I saw Pragati,
I've been an obsessed lover.
One, who takes shit.
And the others who get shit done.
Give the tech in my hands,
and I will always take care of her.
I get shit done.
Why can't you see it, Yogi?
Dungeon loves the product.
And Mayank loves power.
Fuck...
I forgot this argument.
Remember what Dungeon
said last time we met him.
He wants 30% equity
and final veto on the product.
So... who loves power now?
Prachi is reaching in 20 minutes.
Guys, let's make a decision.
No, seriously.
If they are both morons,
then let's take the experienced moron.
But he's also experienced in fuckups.
Juju.
-Shut up...
-No.
Then you guys decide.
You guys take a call.
Naveen,
you haven't taken a call for six months,
because you were not ready to move on.
Don't pressure us with
the decision at this crunch time.
He is right.
But let's not talk about this now.
-Leave it.
-I am sorry. I am sorry.
Okay, let's decide democratically.
Let's vote.
Write down your choices on paper.
And everyone will have
to accept the final verdict.
And we'll never discuss
who voted for whom.
-Okay.
-I don't want this conflict again.
Fine. Done.
Let's take five minutes
and think about it.
Appu, please help us
finish what you started.