Birthdays are so overrated.
What are we even celebrating here?
That we are growing up.
And the world's waiting
for us to arrive.
Birthday Bumps.
I'm turning 25,
and I feel like the world around me
is crashing and burning.
The question is,
"Can I walk through that fire?
"Will I make it through
to the other side?"
-How are you?
-Good.
-Quite a place.
-Yeah.
Hi.
Your dad and I
always wanted to come here together.
Hi, how are you? Varun!
But now we're here with Rajan. Right?
Come.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen!
And the beautiful little girl.
Let's begin the treasure hunt.
-All right!
-Yes!
When I blow the whistle, everyone go
and collect all the tiaras you can.
What's the prize?
-Here's the prize.
-Hi, everyone!
Hey!
Good to see you.
-Ciao, man. How are you?
-How are you?
Excuse me.
Partner selection time.
-Go!
-Yes!
Okay.
Rajan.
Sneha.
Mihir.
Sean.
You and I lost in Italy.
JEH
You were always the one.
-Damini was just an excuse?
-Yes.
And the treasure hunt starts now.
Grab your partner, basket, and cycle.
-Hey, Mihir, good luck.
-You too, uncle.
So you and my mom are friends?
Yup.
And what else?
Well, I'm very fond of your mother.
And the feeling is mutual.
We like each other's company.
How long has it been since your wife died?
Five years.
Yeah. Well, it hasn't been
that long for my mom.
I know that.
She needs time on her own.
To be alone or to be lonely?
There's a difference.
Look. She's vulnerable right now,
and I need to protect her.
I wouldn't expect any less.
I'm trying, Siddhi.
Could you also please try?
Sean?
You're really into her, aren't you?
Who?
Yeah.
-So tell her.
-Isn't she into women?
Umang falls in love with a person
and doesn't really care about gender.
But if she rejects you, it's not personal.
Sometimes two people
are right for each other,
but they can't make it work.
Right?
Let's get some tiaras.
I found one!
I found one, too!
All right! We are crushing this.
Let's look for more.
Go, go!
So, congrats! Moving in and all.
Yeah... That happened.
Wow, so much enthusiasm!
Was I ready?
I don't know. Any advice?
Boss, you're just moving in, right?
What advice do you want?
I got married, had kids, everything.
Without being ready.
Twice.
And now, I think the second one
will end in divorce too.
So yeah, man!
I'm the king of fucking things up!
Wait. You think I'm fucking it up
for myself?
Nah, man! You're a martyr.
You'd die for love
without so much as a whimper.
A martyr? Me?
Yeah, because you just told me
that you got forced into moving in.
-I wasn't forced.
-No?
I was bulldozed.
Wow. That's the harshest thing
I've ever heard coming out of your mouth.
Well, I'm learning from the best.
Me?
Her.
Umang?
You okay?
Mihir, has it ever happened to you
that someone loves you madly
but you just don't feel the same?
Nope.
The other way around.
To unrequited love.
That's a 20-year vintage Sangiovese.
Sanju who?
Bro, the poor thing has been
neglected for 20 years.
He needs our love!
The guest list is top brass, Dhananjay.
I got confirmations from everyone.
-Okay, stay in touch. Really excited.
-Dee?
Can't you go a day without work?
I also left my work behind.
It's only fair.
Phones off.
Fine.
Okay.
Damini, is this really so hard for you?
You wanted me to move in.
But since I moved in,
I don't know why you're unhappy.
I mean, you're in your own world
and I'm pulling you away from it.
Because no matter how hard I try, somehow,
I just don't fit in.
Not with you, not in your world.
Not with us.
Not in our world.
Jeh, you're overthinking this.
Really.
-Sangiovese!
As long as I have.
1920!
This place...
Anjana,
can I ask you something?
Yeah, of course.
How did you learn to be single again?
It's been so long.
I don't even know who I am without him.
You know, Sneha, in my case,
I chose to be single, right?
You didn't.
It's different.
Yeah, I know. It is different.
It takes time.
But maybe you should
take time to find yourself again.
Dada, I found that one.
-We're on the same team.
-Arya!
-No!
-Just put it in...
Arya, Varun, what's going on?
Damn it! Tiaras!
Why can't we all stay single?
Do we even need relationships?
So many expectations.
And even more disappointment.
I mean, look at me.
Samara. Meher. Pinky.
Before them, no problem.
Only happy.
And now, so many explanations!
But who needs explanations?
Everybody!
Speaking as an experienced jilted lover...
Siddhi explained twice
why she can't be with me.
But I still don't get it.
Maybe because I don't want to?
You want them to want to be with you.
And those are the only words
that'll ever work.
There's never any closure.
Is that why you're here?
Because I saw her stand-up.
And you saw how fucked up she is.
And because she asked me to come.
If there's any meaning in that...
I don't want to let that hope go.
Hey!
How are you?
Are you a masochist?
Yeah.
Why do you always act like a do-gooder?
-Don't you get tired?
-That's it?
Troll me a little more.
-You can do better.
-What does that mean?
Well, you're a comic.
An angry comic, apparently.
-So roast me.
-I could seriously punch you right now.
Then maybe I'll get a reaction from you.
You just stand there, listening.
Don't you ever get angry?
Just say something back to me!
Why do you love torturing yourself?
Because I still love you.
Love makes your brain stop working.
Just fuck off!
Shit!
You break my heart and my bones too?
Everything okay?
If Viju were here, he would've seen
his little girl become a woman.
Where did my life go?
Nowhere.
What's gone
is a story.
Your life is here.
Right here, right now.
There are so many memories, Rajan.
And wishes?
You have much to live for, Sneha.
Your story isn't over yet.
Mom?
Got you!
What?
Perfect.
Like the queen that you are.
Was that a pick-up line?
That's my life, man.
Using lines, writing lines.
Plus, I won you over with my words.
-Did you now?
-You know I did.
-Dada!
-Yeah?
I found one!
We're winning this. We're winning!
Come! Quick, my dear.
And the winners are...
Varun and Jeh!
And me!
-The little girl!
Thank you.
-Where's Siddhi?
-Isn't she with you?
Look here. There you go. Got it!
Thank you. All right!
Nice.
Drunk yoga.
Are you...
-What's up?
-Meher.
I understand where she's coming from.
It's hard
getting over you.
Meaning?
I'm crazy about you, Umang.
You're crazy!
You're just... Bro, are you nuts?
About you.
-You're crazy!
-About...
You're drunk!
Not at all.
Thanks for fucking up my head even more.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I'm sorry. I don't know
what came over me. I...
It's okay. I have narrow ear canals.
It affects me.
-You're wrong.
-Hey!
-An ENT diagnosed it.
-About still loving me.
You barely know me, Mihir.
What do you mean?
I've known you since childhood.
We aren't kids anymore!
You don't know this me.
Jeh.
Here.
Come.
It's okay. It's okay. Jeh.
The bed is right there, baba.
Wait, I'll get some water.
The only person I ever loved.
Jeh.
Maybe you don't love me anymore.
When did I say that?
You said nothing.
I'm left guessing.
Do you not see me, Damini?
Or am I not good enough for you?
Because you're a great intellectual,
and I'm a mere bartender.
I'm just a fucking bartender.
Happy birthday, Sids!
Happy birthday, Siddhi!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
This place is unbelievable.
You also cheer up, Sulk Smitha.
Sure.
In other news,
Sean says that he's crazy about me.
So?
I told him,
Italy is bringing out his inner Romeo.
Wow. And I thought I was rude.
How do you feel about him?
I don't know.
I mean,
he's a good guy.
Honest. And fit, too. But...
-But?
-I mean,
there's definitely something
I like about him.
But with men, it's like,
I've never had a meaningful relationship
with them outside of sex.
I don't know if I can be
in a relationship with a man, so...
But, Mangs, I think that's fine.
Sean is a close friend, not your lover.
And I guess that's why the confusion.
Just imagine being stuck with dick
for the rest of your life.
-Actually...
-What?
I don't mind being stuck with dick
for the rest of my life.
Of course.
Yeah! Cheers to that.
Where's your drink?
Hey, don't take mine.
Salud!
Hi!
Wow, amazing. How fantastic is this?
Partner!
Cheers!
-Eat!
-Yes.
-Want a top-up?
-Please.
Umang, do you want a top-up?
Everyone! Everyone!
Everyone!
It's my birthday, guys!
-Yeah!
-Yes, it is!
Okay, okay. Speech.
So, thank you all for coming out.
Really.
Okay, I know that for the last few days,
I've been a bit of a sulk-pot, but...
you guys are the best!
Okay, I promise
that from now on, I'll try my best
to be that cute,
bubbly, cuddly Siddhi again.
Sounds good to me.
Because, you guys,
we're in the country of love!
Love, yeah!
So, to...
To all the lovely couples out here,
Dee, Jeh?
You both look so hot.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so awkward?
-Not really.
-Shit. Still not doing it?
Okay, my Anj and Aru.
Hi! So cute!
Hey, what about me?
You're married.
Did you forget Kavya?
Anj, seriously. You have got
to stop snogging married men.
Siddhi, can you stop?
Mangs, I didn't forget you.
Mangs and Sean.
Guys! There are so many rooms here,
just go for it!
Siddhi, that's enough.
That's enough, darling.
Mom and your non-boyfriend.
That advice was not for you guys. Okay?
Just putting it out there.
And, Mihir.
My Mihu-Pihu.
No luck this time, buddy. Again!
Next time, let's try again
at an even more exotic location. Okay?
I promise.
So, a very happy birthday to me!
Happy birthday to you.
Yeah!
You really gotta get laid, man.
You need to get out of Anj's house, man.
I am happy where I am.
If you're doling out advice,
give some to Jeh.
He's the one
who got bulldozed into moving in.
-Varun.
-Excuse me?
Bro?
At least I'm not looking
for handouts from my partners.
What exactly have you achieved
in your life, anyway?
I made two smart, beautiful kids.
I swear!
My sperm is of the highest quality.
-I mean...
-It should be studied.
Speaking of kids,
Sids, you and Mihir
would make beautiful children.
But you're still a child,
so that'll never happen.
Go away, man!
Just go screw Sean. Go!
"Bubbly" is rude!
-Any problem?
-Yes, I do.
What? No more marriages to wreck?
Now it's a party, guys!
Yeah, let's go!
Happy birthday to me!
Bellissima, bellissima
You and me together make happiness
Hey, friends
Hello, amore
Greetings
I've been waiting for you
all my life, amore
Come hold my hand
and take me high, let's go fly
There's something about you
that makes me go crazy
When you move your hips,
my gosh!
You're right.
I know the childhood Siddhi.
I know you even today.
You bake the best red velvet cupcakes.
I know you'd do anything for your friends.
And by anything, I mean anything.
I know that you hide your vulnerability
behind your weird dark humor.
You're more instinctive
and introspective than you think.
I know that you're beautiful.
Inside and out.
And I know that
you're hurting inside right now because
you think life forced you
to suddenly grow up one day.
But I do know something else, too.
I know that growing up
comes with loss and pain
and sadness and heartache.
But it also comes with hope...
and love.
Cake! It's cake time! It's cake time!
Wow!
-Cake fight!
-No, no!
-This your room?
-That's it.
-Let me.
-Sorry...
Sids, let me...
Let me try. Let me.
Let me try.
I'm a bad person, right?
Nonsense.
Even more so with you.
For now.
You weren't always like this.
Mihir, please don't leave me, okay?
I just want to...
Varun, I'm really sorry
about what Siddhi said.
I don't think like that about you and...
-you should know that.
-Anj.
You don't owe me any explanations.
It's me.
And it's you.
Yeah.
And it's us.
Should I not have dropped that truth bomb?
No, it's...
You have the right
to express how you feel.
And you can feel awkward.
I'm not being awkward.
Then why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you.
You're kissing me back.
What are you thinking?
Sorry if I bulldozed you into moving in.
Damini?
You think you can do this with me?
Forever?
We should get married.
What?
Jeh...
I...
Just forget it.
Creative Supervisor: Dinesh Shakul