Previously on seasons one and two
Four More Shots Please!
When I hear you babbling,
I feel like I'm home.
That all's well with the world.
-Cheers.
They are feisty.
Women work twice as hard
to reach half as far.
They are flawed.
You've put on weight, Siddhi.
What is this?
They are judged.
Poor thing's a divorcee.
Four women,
who live,
love,
fall,
and continue being friends no matter what.
Meet Anjana Menon.
The best friend.
The perfect lawyer,
but the imperfect mother.
Pooky aunty is very nice.
You're the one who's moving on.
You also move on.
I'll show you what moving on is, asshole.
This is Damini Rizvi Roy.
A journalist...
They need to grow a pair of balls.
Writer,
OCD in life, messy in love.
I like you too much.
This is Umang Singh.
A Punjabi girl.
Queer and curious.
Hi.
Just keep a little faith,
it's gonna be absolutely...
You know who she is?
Bollywood Goddess Samara Kapoor.
And finally, meet Siddhi Patel.
Papa's favorite.
Hey, Siddhi-Piddhi.
But, can't deal with mom.
He chose men over you.
Shut up! Just shut up, Sneha!
And she's trying to love her body.
Vagina!
The four are always there for each other
but sometimes friendships
do get complicated.
We came here to discuss my problems.
But as usual,
you've made it about yourselves.
It's my first relationship with a woman.
I'm not sure if I'm...
"If I'm..." what?
I want to make this work.
Hi, I'm Myrah.
I'm taking Arya to the hospital.
Arya!
Sid, are you okay?
I and my heart are lonely.
Sids needs help.
It was time to leave
all the baggage behind and move on.
-Sids!
-Siddhi!
What are you doing here?
An SOS call is all it took
to bring them together again.
Friendship tied and sealed forever.
Oh, shit!
I miss you so much.
How did we end up here?
Do you still like me?
Not the right time for this.
You want us to do shows.
We're a hit pair.
From discovering hidden talents,
to making the world laugh.
You like shaking things
because you're shaken up,
or you're shaken up
because you shake things up?
Join me. As a senior partner, of course.
Seriously.
-Are you guys dating?
-Yes.
It was also time
to give love another chance.
-Will you marry me?
-Yes.
But what is love
without a bit of drama?
I'm pregnant and it's yours.
-You're pregnant?
-It's not yours.
You need to leave.
What the hell!
I believed you.
Had you known,
would you have done things differently?
I never really doubted
that it's not an open marriage.
I can't be with someone who always
puts me second to everything else.
Umang!
There's nowhere else I would rather be,
no one else I'd rather be with.
I love you guys so much.
Papa.
What?
He's gone.
Love makes your heart explode, but loss
makes it shatter into a million pieces.
Is there any way to protect your heart?
Maybe not.
Because you will always lose your love.
It's inevitable.
My papa is...
was a wonderful,
kind, warm and a funny man.
And I was his Siddhi-Piddhi.
He loved Kishore Kumar's songs,
drinking vodka with me,
and his morning walks here
with his friends.
Like he would always say,
"All you need on a tough day is vodka."
And he loves me and my mom
more than anything else in the world.
Loved.
It's really weird
talking about him in past tense.
It feels like any minute
he's gonna walk in and say,
"Siddhi-Piddhi, want to hear a joke?"
And I really miss his WhatsApp jokes.
Terrible as they were.
His favorite bad one was,
"What are your plans this weekend?"
"Income tax returns."
"Oh, when was part one released?"
"How do Emirati babies cry?"
"UAE, UAE."
Say the one about the pencil.
"Why shouldn't we use a broken pencil?"
"Because it's pointless."
But you know what?
Papa's jokes might have been terrible,
but his enthusiasm was so infectious
that you would have
no choice but to laugh.
I miss you, Papa.
And I hope you're making
everyone laugh wherever you are.
Morning, beautiful.
Do we have to
do this obstacle course every day?
Garlic breath.
Why did you order
garlic chicken yesterday?
Because I know how much you love it.
Really?
What else do I love?
Umang, this is the sixth complaint
I've received about you from a client.
Any more and management will get involved.
He was talking nonsense, okay? About...
He was being an asshole.
All male clients want you to train them
because they think you'll give them
some juicy details about you and Samara.
What about female clients?
Female clients think you're single now
and you might hit on them.
Right. Because I'm a sex maniac
apparently, right?
I might jump on anyone I see.
I only have two clients, Anusha.
I need to make a living.
What do I do?
I'm so big. Why is he so small?
You were small, too, baby.
No, I was always a big girl.
No wonder Miss Vee Vee gave up after that.
-Oh, my God!
-Hi.
Traffic jam outside and fam jam inside.
High on emotions, just like your mama.
Okay, so you know what time it is?
It's family selfie time.
-Yeah!
-Come on.
Three, two, one, say cheese!
Only one of my eyes is visible.
I look like a one-eyed witch.
That's true. Let's do another one.
Give it to Anj. It's easier.
What an idea!
Wow, it's the idea of the day.
Please do the honors.
Yeah, sure.
Ready!
Family!
Okay, that's your picture.
At least it has both my eyes.
We're a family!
-Oh, don't cry.
-Don't cry.
Mr. Patel was one of our
oldest and biggest clients.
-We can diversify the portfolio...
-A focused portfolio.
Reducing the risk of diversification.
Real estate is the only way.
Confused?
Count on us.
We're here for you.
We'll make sure
that you never miss Mr. Patel again.
They swoop down like vultures
on vulnerable women.
We can do this, darling.
Just the two of us.
Not like we have a choice.
It's literally just the two of us.
Who knows what tomorrow has in store.
You could find someone really special.
-So could you.
-Don't be ridiculous.
And anyway, who wants a 48-year-old?
Other 48-year-olds
or 80-year-olds or 30-year-olds.
Mom, age is just a number.
So, either I change diapers
or someone changes mine.
That's your plan?
Anyway,
you know there's no room
in my heart for anyone but you
and your papa.
Shit, man!
...22, 23, 24!
Welcome to the moon.
We are here before Chandrayaan-2.
Take a close-up, Madhav.
How many more potholes do I need to click?
As many as we find.
There are 24 potholes
in this 1.5-kilometer stretch.
Some of them as huge as this.
Someone on a bike or auto
might end up dead here.
Let's measure it.
Well, we can only submit one photograph.
With space for just four lines of text,
with the ads for constipation
larger than the article.
We owe it to our readers.
All five of them?
Moving on.
Twenty-two foot spans
is 203.5 inches.
What?
You know your foot size in inches?
Don't you?
-Okay.
-No, no.
First woman on the moon.
Disgusting.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
Ask for an injunction.
Defendant doesn't want
the plaintiff to take...
I've a 2:00 p.m. booking for this room.
The Gateway Tech meeting?
I should be here too, right?
No, I got this one.
Okay.
Aadil, let's go.
Negotiations take time, Mr. Sethi.
The other side is just playing hardball.
Give us some time.
I'll get you a better offer.
So, Shashank,
what do you think?
Ms. Menon knows best.
She always knows best.
Okay, then let's take this forward.
Sure, let's do that.
Thanks for coming. I'll see you out.
Thank you, Mr. Sethi.
Yes?
What was that?
What do you mean?
What you said to Mr. Sethi.
"Ms. Menon knows best.
She always knows best."
It's true, isn't it?
That's why I...
I mean, this firm hired you.
Anything else?
No.
Keshav, how many malaria cases were
reported in the first quarter this year?
Okay. Dengue? Chikungunya?
-Thank you.
-Hey!
You're Damini Rizvi Roy, right?
-Yeah.
-I've read your Bloody February.
Before it got banned, of course.
Technically, it was not banned,
it got pulled out because of protests.
I think the protest
did the world a huge favor.
It was a 400-page tome of lies
and now it lies in the tomb.
-Excuse me?
-That's what people like you deserve.
You deserve this.
This world has gone crazy, hasn't it?
When we go from "people like us"
to "people like you"?
These days, everyone gets
offended about everything.
If I said this a little louder,
people here will get offended.
And that Kulkarni won't even
let me do an op-ed.
For the last five months,
I've been covering dengue,
malaria, mosquitoes and potholes, Jeh.
And you know me, Jeh.
I'm doing that diligently, too.
But till when?
How long will I be punished?
Till when do I have to
keep proving myself?
By the way,
I'm surprised she survived.
How did she survive that look of yours?
Which look?
I don't do that.
You're confusing me with one of your exes.
Damini Rizvi Roy, you are a fighter.
So fight the good fight.
Yeah, this is Siddhi.
For a show? No, I quit stand-up.
Indefinitely.
Yeah, please don't call me.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Why are you upset?
-Telemarketers.
-God, I hate them all.
Say hello to little Miss Sex Maniac.
-What?
Coming up,
there are three types of people.
#LearnitfromMangs
First, the ones who are having sex.
Second, the ones who want to have sex.
And third, the ones who want to escape it.
And which one of these are you, Ms. Mangs?
All of these, at the same time.
Hugs and kisses!
So much love! I'm gonna cry.
We haven't met since morning.
-Oh, my God.
-You haven't met me either, Jeh.
Where's my kiss?
Aren't you my best friend?
Just to remind all of you,
I'm why you started coming here.
And if not for me,
you would've never hooked up with Dee.
So, where is my kiss?
-Kisses! Kisses!
-I have customers.
-Go upstairs.
-Drinks.
One more! One more!
Going, ta-da!
What is with girls and their papas?
They are our biggest heroes.
Varun is not just Arya's hero,
but her superhero.
Maybe because
they are the first man every girl loves.
But by that logic,
mothers should also be our heroes.
They're the first women we love.
I think for me,
both my parents were my heroes.
I just want to be like them.
Fierce, brave, have an independent voice.
Take a stand every single day
just like they did.
I had an okay relationship with my father.
Neither attached nor detached.
He got transferred
from one tea estate to another.
And I would see him
only during my boarding school holidays.
Just two different worlds.
I know what you mean.
You know you love them.
They love you, of course.
You have each other's backs.
But it's like a missing link. Isn't it?
My father
is big-hearted, hardworking, honest.
But he's stuck in his idea of being a man.
And I always fought for his attention.
I'd play hockey, and lift weights.
I won so many medals
in the hope of proving myself
a better son than my brother.
And he actually said to me that,
"You can never be a sportsman
"because 'sportsman' has 'man' in it
and you aren't one."
You've never had
an emotional relationship with him?
You know, on my 22nd birthday,
I was presented an album
from a marriage bureau.
And he was like, "Choose one of them.
"You have to get married."
Honestly, he couldn't care less
about me. That's how I felt.
God, that's hard.
This one time, he was like,
"I love you a lot
"but this is the obligation
of the relationship."
But, Mangs...
at least you still have him.
You'll just wake up one day,
and they'll be gone forever.
We're reaching in five minutes.
Story sent.
Don't bother Aunt Kavya and Dada, okay?
I'll play with Arav all weekend.
-Look, country cows!
-Sids, that's a buffalo.
Let's go back, please.
Mangs, you got this.
And we got you.
Let's go.
Ummi, my child.
Hello, Mom.
-Hello, Auntie.
-Who is it, Mom?
Ummi?
Hey, baby. Is your name Simrat?
-Are you Simrat?
-Who is that?
-Do you know Diljit Dosanjh?
Of course. He's Aunt Pummy's son.
-Can you take me to meet him?
-Why not?
Let's meet Diljit tomorrow.
Hey, can you smell the samosas?
I got hot samosas from Nathu Lal's shop.
Hello, Papa.
How dare she step foot in my house?
Don't shout, Umang is outside.
What if she hears you?
Let her hear!
She humiliated us!
We were finally happy
with the birth of Simrat.
She couldn't tolerate it
and had to come here today.
-Please, relax.
-How can I?
We shouldn't have come.
Let's go.
At least drink your tea, Ummi.
Simrat is just like you.
Everyone says that.
Are you happy, Pinky?
Yes, I am.
-Please don't lie.
-I'm not lying.
My priorities have just changed.
Now, Simrat comes first,
and the rest after her.
Being a happy mom
doesn't mean you are happily married.
What's the point in thinking about it now?
Does Vikram care for Simrat?
Yes, always.
He's after her all day.
I also love Vikramjeet now.
Not like I love you, but as a best friend.
Is that enough for you?
Why do you ask now?
Why didn't you ask me
when I came to Mumbai?
Ummi!
I'm not complaining.
I'm fine.
You also be fine now.
And listen, whether she says it or not,
your mom still misses you a lot.
She needs you.
The way you need her.
And even when we grow up
and become independent,
everyone needs their family.
And weren't you going to
start a family of your own?
With Samara?
I already knew.
He's asking for sugar.
Ummi.
How's work?
Do you have any new celeb clients?
Don't even mention
those shameless, worthless people.
They're the ones creating this nonsense.
Isn't that right?
Didn't she trick you
into becoming like her?
Papa, I was always like this.
You never tried to get to know me.
You lived in my house for 22 years.
And she says that I don't even know her.
Excellent.
Who am I?
What are my interests?
My goals? Have you ever asked me about it?
You always told me,
"Girls belong to another family."
Maybe that's why
you never showed me any affection.
Shut up!
You always made me shut up.
Is that a father-daughter relationship?
She must've taught you that too.
Arguing with your father?
I'm your father, Umang.
It's your duty to respect me.
What about your duty? What about that?
I've been dealing with so much
over the last few months.
It was in the papers!
You couldn't even call me.
To ask if I'm okay. If I'm alive or dead.
God forbid I ever received a call
about something happening to you.
I wouldn't be able to forgive myself.
But if you got similar phone call
about me, would it matter to you at all?
I shouldn't have come here.
Nothing is going to change.
It's not that I do not love you.
I do.
But this is the obligation
of the relationship.
I'm tired of this twisted love.
Papa, I also love you very much.
And that's the obligation
of our relationship.
Can't we change that?
It's too late now.
It's too late.
Now...
I have just one daughter.
And her name is Pinky.
Stop it!
Umang is my daughter even today.
And she always will be.
I have three children.
Do you hear?
Wow, that's Dee, eating some butter!
Nice.
-It's for your headache.
-I'm fine.
Mangu!
Hi!
Oh, shit! Incoming.
Please stop.
-Mangu?
-Hello, everyone.
-Hello.
-Hi, Neetu. Hi, Dolly.
You're in Ludhiana,
but no phone calls or status update.
God, you've changed so much.
And look, your entire arm
is covered with tattoos.
You are famous here.
And look at us.
We just got married and settled down.
And you are doing so well.
You built an amazing career.
And on your own terms.
Typical Umang style.
-Of course!
-We are so proud of you, Mangu!
Mama, I want to use the bathroom!
Why only when we are out?
Why didn't you use the bathroom
when I asked you to at home?
Come on, let's go.
-Okay, bye, Mangu.
-Bye!
-Let's go.
Wait, stop for a minute.
Mangu, listen to me. Come here.
This problem you have with Samara.
Don't worry, it'll get sorted.
After all, true love is true love.
Don't worry. See you later.
-Bye! Let's go.
-Bye.
Mangu?
Here, your true love awaits.
Also, we're very proud of you, too.
Hey, that's my school bus!
Girls, come on, let's go!
-Wait a minute.
-Guys, come!
-Wait a minute...
-You get the bus. Come.
It's a school bus, not a passenger bus.
Get off!
Mr. Teja Singh, it's me, Umang.
Umang!
Pain in the neck, school champion,
and my darling is all grown up now.
And you've become like Dharmendra,
more handsome than me.
-Where are you going?
-Same place you're going.
-School.
It was here where it all happened.
I finally discovered myself.
And right here,
I kissed Pinky for the first time.
I had strong feelings for her
from seventh standard.
And I just thought they were
extra strong feelings for a friend.
-Extra strong?
-I didn't know.
And you know how Vikramjeet
fell in love with Pinky?
Because of me.
Because Pinky would often come home
to see me.
And then,
Vikramjeet told Papa that
he wouldn't marry anyone but Pinky.
And Pinky chose
Vikramjeet
over me.
Forget it. It's fine. It's all good.
Okay, time for some old-fashioned
Punjabi therapy.
-Come on, let's go.
-Let's go!
Jump.
-Jump?
-What do you mean jump?
-Come on!
-No!
It'll be fun. Give it a try.
-Give it a try.
-Why should I go first?
You can do it. Come on.
Be the fearless journalist that you are.
-Yes! To the other side, let's go.
-Let's go.
-No!
-You can do it!
One, two, go...
Oh, my God!
All right!
Come on!
Where does this road go?
To Nathu Lal's for snacks
or Deluxe Cinema for a morning show.
Like Silky Youth?
Flirt under the Skirt?
You slut!
Hey, Punjabi ones are way better.
For example,
-Jungle Boy, Tarzan.
-Wow.
And my favorite,
Where Do I Put My Manji?
Manji meaning?
Manji means bed.
Where Do I Put My Manji?
Come on, let's go.
-"Where do you want to sleep tonight?"
-Let's go!
Oh, gosh.
That's it!
Nice one.
It's to chase the monkeys away, right?
Yes, today we'll use it
on some female monkeys.
One more.
Fuck expectations!
Fuck samosas!
Fuck helpless relationships!
All right, let's do this.
Fuck you, Shashank.
Fuck you, Varun! Fuck all you men!
Okay, not Arjun, actually.
-Here.
-Okay.
This is fun.
Come on.
Okay, fuck.
Fuck potholes!
Fuck mosquitoes!
Fuck all those coward editors
who won't hire me.
Fuck me because
I'm the biggest coward of them all.
I can't...
-You did good.
-It's okay.
-I can't. I... Sorry.
-Come on, Sids.
-Fuck you, universe!
Fuck you for taking my dad
way before it was his time!
Sids, use the gun.
Come on, you can do it.
You got this. Come on.
-Pick it up, come on.
-Come on, Sids.
Just aim and shoot.
-Oh, fuck!
-Sids!
-Are you okay?
-What are you doing?
-Are you hurt?
-Bro, say something.
-Sid!
Are you hurt? Are you all right?
-What's going on?
-Oh, fuck.
-What!
-No, she's fine.
Creative Supervisor: Dinesh Shakul