♪ Mmm, pacify ♪
♪ Clarify our love ♪
♪ Pacify, pacify ♪
♪ Pacify our love ♪
Dad, there's a phone call for ya!
Charlie!
Wait! Charlie!
Giddy-up, horsey! Giddy-up!
Dad, there's a phone call for ya.
Good boy. Good boy.
Well, you go back to the house,
and whoever's calling,
the operator will have their number,
and I'll call them back. Eh?
Oh, look, Charlie,
you must have violin practice.
It's Mrs Milligan. Go on.
Charlie. Charlie, you play loudly!
You might hear some bangs.
Go on.
Hi, Mr Shelby.
Maggie? Yeah, it's me.
-Yes, Mr Shelby.
-I just missed a call. Where was it from?
Er, Belfast.
Belfast.
Where in Belfast?
Er, I'm not sure.
Do you have the number?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
It's 0-8-24.
Yeah, can you put me through?
Tommy. Don't--
Mr Shelby.
My name is Captain Swing,
calling from the occupied six counties.
And there are some people
from the other side of our
neat little city that want you dead.
You should also know
that this boy,
this Michael, your kin,
was in his cabin aboard
the SS Monroe in Belfast dock,
making deals with the very men
who want you dead.
-Tommy, they're lying!
-Now, if you want,
we can put a bullet in his head,
here and now,
or we can send him home,
and you can deal with him.
Send him home.
Very well, Mr Shelby.
But be informed that this kin of yours
was talking to representatives from
the County Tyrone and Glasgow UVF
about how they'd divide up
the English racetracks
after they'd blown away your legs.
Tommy, they're lying!
And may I ask...
why you are doing me this favour?
Because, Mr Shelby, we've been informed
by people at the very highest level
that since your conversion to socialism,
you're now on the side of the angels.
And angels can be useful to us.
-Come.
Mr Shelby, the violin teacher
wants to know what all those bangs were.
Fireworks. I was trying 'em out
for Saturday.
You promised the doctor
not until after dark.
It's pretty dark, Frances.
Also, will Mrs Shelby and Ruby
be home for dinner tonight?
I don't know.
Dad?
I've learned something this morning.
Have ya?
So have I.
And what have you learned, my boy?
Let's get this over with.
I've got a train to catch.
Go get your train, Tom.
I can deal with this.
Hey!
Go home.
Come here, you.
Put this on.
There you go. Look at that.
Looks great on ya! Wrap up warm.
Wake up.
Rise and shine.
What are you doing here?
Wasting our fucking time on you.
Sit down, Finn.
Sit down.
What do I have to do...
to make you fucking listen to me?
You took a bullet.
You've been running around the streets
with a fucking gun in your hand.
Somebody has to.
Finn, we've got people
for that kind of work.
Soldiers. Captains and corporals.
Well, then, what am I?
"What am I?" Jesus Christ.
Yeah. What am I, Tom? Huh?
I'm the brother you never got around to.
You're a general, Finn.
You understand? You're a fucking Shelby,
so you're a general.
When did you last see a general
anywhere near the blood and the puke, eh?
He's fucking right.
That's what you are.
So, on your feet, soldier.
Come on, on your feet!
I thought you just said I was a general.
I did just say you were.
-So, get on your fucking feet--
-Arthur.
Finn. Finn. Look at this.
This is the bullet
that Aberama Gold cut from you.
First and last.
Don't lose it.
Go and clean up.
Put some clothes on. Nice suit.
I've got some trouble
that'll keep you out of trouble.
-Oh, and, er, Tom...
-Yeah?
While you're here, erm,
I've met this girl,
and I'd like to get married.
Fuck off. Go, get dressed.
Go on. Move.
Go!
Finn, this girl
you're trying to impress...
Tell me about her.
She likes the life.
She likes the life, eh?
Well, find one that hates it.
Look at him. That's what he did,
and now he's chairman of the board.
Go on. Hurry up.
Arthur? Lizzie and Ruby...
are they still at yours?
Yes, Tom, they're still there.
She's coming home today, she said, so...
She'll be home later.
Hmm. Has she been talking about me?
I mean, they talk a lot.
You know what women are like.
The kitchen and... You know?
Kids running around.
I don't pay 'em no mind, Tom.
-I don't listen to 'em half the time.
- Yeah.
Well, everything she says is true.
Well...
-You like the life, Tommy.
-I don't like the fucking life.
I don't like the fucking life.
I don't like that
Michael is coming back today.
Train arrives from Liverpool at 3:00.
Polly will be there. Take a weapon.
Tell Moss to clear the station of coppers,
you hear me?
Yes, sir.
Hey, Tom...
I heard 'em say one thing, though.
Just talking, you know?
They were saying that, er...
you don't sleep,
or something.
You can't sleep.
When I do sleep,
I dream.
And in my dream,
someone wants my crown.
Think it might be Michael.
Call me at 3:00.
Arthur, I'm gonna put that bullet
on a necklace and wear it as a reminder.
Arthur?
-I heard ya.
-You got trouble for me, then?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
Mr Shelby... Er... Er...
The police are here to see you.
Police aren't allowed in here.
Er... He's not in uniform
and said it's very unofficial.
Afternoon. Someone get you some tea?
No, I'm fine, Mr Shelby.
-This won't take long.
- Good.
You got five minutes.
Mr Shelby,
there was a shooting two days ago.
A man died.
It was a murder.
In Maida Vale,
of all places.
-His name was Levitt.
-Uh-huh.
He was a journalist.
The night before he was shot,
he came here to see you.
We found a Commons pass
and your name in his diary.
I was wondering
what his business here was.
And I'm wondering...
what your business here is.
According to his diary,
you knew him from Birmingham.
What's your name?
-Stacker.
-Stacker. Okay.
Mr Shelby, Mr Levitt was a queer.
Some may think
it was one of his queer friends.
Mr Stacker,
I get the feeling
that with a little provocation,
you could be very persistent.
Only within my remit.
Well, your Chief Constable Wyatt,
he has very clear views about persistence
which he has shared with me.
-Mr Shelby--
-He likes persistence,
as do I, and thoroughness.
But not frivolity.
A man who walks in the park with other men
dies in Maida Vale.
And you come to me?
As well as his diary,
-we have his notebook.
Your time's up, Mr Stacker.
Thank you.
♪ You have no idea what I'm capable of ♪
♪ You have never tasted
This kind of love ♪
♪ Underestimate me and see how it goes ♪
♪ Love you to death ♪
Hello, Mum!
This is Gina.
Gina Gray.
The captain married us on board.
She's my wife, Mum.
At least look at her.
Tommy said to ask you
to tell me the truth.
We've been travelling
for 15 days, Mrs Gray.
Maybe we could talk about this
at another time?
Yes. Let's go home and we can talk.
You have no home
until you tell me the truth.
-Here?
-Yeah.
Michael!
Hello, love.
Welcome to Birmingham, eh.
Michael.
Okay.
Our ship docked at Belfast.
-I was then taken off the ship by two men.
-At gunpoint--
I'm speaking to my son.
Fuck you.
Fuck you, too, Arthur!
This is my fucking wife.
I'm bringing her home, to this.
Come on, Gina.
Well, where are you going now, eh? Hmm?
Introduce me, at least.
-Excuse me.
-Look at this.
Look at this.
This is it, Gina.
This is my fuckin' people.
Do you wanna know the truth, Arthur?
Do you wanna know the truth, Mum?
I did not betray my fucking family!
Now, Mum,
I want to go home.
I've booked you a suite
at the Midland Hotel.
Was that Tommy's orders,
then, was it?
See, the Midland Hotel
is Tommy's little kingdom,
where all the porters keep an eye,
where all the telephone exchange girls
are reporting on my calls.
Yeah, well, why don't you
think of it like, er...
quarantine, Michael, eh?
We treat you like a fucking dog. Hmm?
Smelly one, stinking one,
until we know you're clean.
Hmm?
-Fuck you, Arthur.
Stand aside, Arthur.
No, Pol.
Come on, baby. Forget about it.
Go and phone Tommy.
Tell him,
"Polly says Michael's telling the truth."
It's all right. Forget about it.
All right, Pol.
Nice coat.
What are you, like, a camel, right?
Oh.
Welcome to the family, Gina Gray.
I applaud the attempt
in the Trevelyan Education Bill
to raise the school-leaving age to 15.
♪ All these folk
They think that I'm evil ♪
♪ Like I am the living devil himself ♪
♪ All these folk
They think that I'm evil ♪
♪ Like I am the living devil ♪
...as regards means
testing of any kind,
-we are the people.
We've had enough.
Hear, hear!
"We are the people and we've had enough."
I move in favour of the amendment.
Mr Shelby.
I must say,
you sing like a songbird in the House.
-And who is this pretty finch?
-My sister.
-Who's pregnant.
-And dangerous.
Oh, we adore dangerous.
Who's "we"?
It's a collective noun.
In this case, describing a group of people
who are impatient and young
and, as I have said, adore dangerous.
Mr Shelby, you had a horse of that name.
Whiskey, Irish.
Give him one from my bottle,
and one for myself.
In fact, bring the bottle.
And the lady?
Isn't thirsty.
How'd you know about the horse?
We have a mutual acquaintance.
May Carleton.
When I asked about you, she said,
"Oh, my goodness, where do I begin?"
And why were you asking after me?
Because, as I have said,
I adore dangerous.
And where did she begin?
You know, I was rather hoping
we might have this meeting alone.
My sister is my political advisor.
And my advice just now was,
"Don't meet Mr Mosley."
Because I am dangerous?
No.
What is it
you are impatient for, Mr Mosley?
I'm impatient for my fucking whiskey.
Bennet!
May Carleton spoke about you
the way I imagine one might
about a party they barely remember,
where you crash the car into the dovecote
and live on champagne and cocaine
for three whole days.
You know that kind of party?
Only three days?
My sister advised against meeting you
because it appears
you are moving away from the party...
in a different direction.
And which direction is that?
Towards fascism.
"We are the people
and we have had enough."
I thought that was excellent.
In which direction
are you heading, Mr Shelby?
I am my own revolution.
And you prefer Irish to Scotch.
As do I.
Like all things regarding Ireland,
it is complex, yes?
Oh.
Where do you stand
on the Irish Question, Mr Shelby?
Never been asked it.
Then perhaps it's time you were.
Tommy, I am the people,
and I have had enough.
We're looking for someone
to begin a dialogue
with certain elements in Belfast
with whom we don't officially
have any dealings.
I'll be too busy singing in the House.
It would involve a promotion.
Junior minister to the Duchy of Lancaster.
Birmingham is my concern.
Ireland bores me.
Thanks for the whiskey, Mr Mosley.
What the fuck was that about?
Ireland. It's been Ireland's day
all fucking day long.
What do you mean?
Ada, go home
and start calling anyone who had dealings
with Shelby Company Limited
while you were in Boston.
Ask 'em about Michael.
Ask them what about him?
Who he's been seeing,
who he's been meeting,
what deals he's made.
Why?
Ask 'em especially about people
he's met from Glasgow or Belfast.
Tommy, why don't you
come back with me, huh?
You can play chess with Karl.
I'll make some calls, you can listen in.
Drive home tomorrow--
Then that bastard
starts talking about Irish whiskey.
What the fuck does he know, eh?
More than me, Tommy.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about an empty chair, Ada.
My chair. My throne.
People think that I'm gonna fall.
They start behaving
in a different way around here.
Who thinks that?
They start to circle.
Who's gonna take the throne, eh?
Linda, she wants some for Arthur...
Aberama Gold,
people in the north, Michael...
Just go home, make some calls.
Protestants are coming, I think.
I need to get back to Birmingham.
Polly.
You armed?
Yeah.
Will you please consider
putting your weapons behind the bar,
in case feelings begin to run high?
Behind the bar, Pol, eh?
Behind my own bar, yeah?
I prefer it there.
Thomas.
Had a dream...
about a black cat last night, Pol.
A black cat dream
means there is a traitor close by.
It was you who taught me that.
Black cat can mean lots of things.
It can mean you're hurting yourself,
betraying yourself.
Are you seeing things, Thomas?
Yes, I am.
Yes, I am, very clearly.
Coming from every fucking direction.
Tommy.
I'd like to introduce you to my wife.
I would also like to, er, say something.
Sit down, Michael.
-I betrayed you.
-Michael.
But only in my heart.
There was a time, in America,
when there was
a lot of money in that bank.
And I wondered, I could...
I could leave, move to California.
Someone said I should invest in pictures.
-Hollywood.
But Gina stopped me.
-Gina said that--
-I told you to sit down, Michael.
Now tell me...
what happened on that ship...
in Belfast harbour.
On the journey back from New York,
we got married.
But we needed to find a witness, a purser.
He was from Belfast. We got friendly.
What happened when the ship docked?
This purser had friends
who ran a whiskey distillery
in County Tyrone.
They wanted a way
of getting their stuff into America.
So I said, "Okay, invite them aboard."
When they came in,
I realized that they didn't make whiskey.
They were Scottish, from Glasgow.
Couldn't understand
a fucking word they were saying.
They started swearing,
so I asked Gina to leave.
That was when they
started talking about you, Tom.
They said that Tommy Shelby
was a spent force.
That politics had got to him.
That he was spent in the head.
That now was a good time to move in,
and did I want to be part of it?
They knew about the money
we lost in America.
They said that you were going to blame me,
that you had a bullet with my name on it.
What did you say, Michael?
I didn't have time
to say anything.
Coppers came on board.
Well, I thought they were coppers.
They, er...
They were IRA.
Exactly.
And the first men, from Glasgow?
The IRA commander
said the men from Glasgow
were called Billy Boys.
Fucking Billy Boys.
I don't know who the fuck Billy Boys are.
They run every man
in every coal mine,
on every shipyard east of Glasgow.
Ties with Belfast, UVF.
Protestant razor gang.
They also dabble in politics.
You know, muscle for fascist rallies.
But you did no deal, Michael.
You didn't even know who they were?
I was too busy looking forward to
giving you the good news.
The reason Gina and I got married
on the ship was because Gina is pregnant.
You're going to be a grandmother.
Okay, Michael.
I believe you.
Welcome home.
Congratulations.
Just remember...
your unborn child
has witnessed what you said...
Thomas.
...and it will be born accordingly.
-You fuck!
-Where the fuck are you going?
Hmm?
Are you fucking mad? Hmm?
-You are free to fucking leave, Michael.
You fucking bastard.
But you're not free, Michael, are you?
You lost this company a lot of money.
I told you to sell,
but you held on.
And now, I want you
to pay me back what you owe me.
There is work you can do,
there are risks you can take.
We were close before.
Now, I want you closer still.
Michael, honey,
look at your cousin.
He's in trouble. Huh?
He needs you.
Come on, baby.
Let's go.
Fucking cheek of her, eh?
Mad Dog Jimmy...
coming south.
Not so mad anymore.
He's got friends
in high places these days.
A black cat dream is never wrong, brother.
♪ Hello, hello, we are the Billy Boys ♪
♪ We're up to our knees in Fenian blood ♪
♪ Surrender or you'll die ♪
♪ We are the Brigton Derry Billy Boys ♪
Drop the pea shooter, son.
A broken broom
stops all Gypsy curses, Mr Gold.
Who the fuck are you?
Did you not hear my song?
These gentlemen are the Billy Boys.
And me?
I'm Jimmy.
-No! Fuck.
Good. Mouth broke so you can't talk.
But you don't need to.
-Your body will be the lesson.
You work in a particular capacity
for Mr Thomas Shelby OBE, am I right?
I heard you're a fighter.
The best.
But your fighting days are over.
Because I need Mr Shelby to understand...
-...that his best...
- Fuck.
...is not...
good enough.
Bonnie.
Farewell, fighter boy.
You died well.
Bonnie.
Bonnie!
Tell Thomas Shelby
it's time to fucking share.
We'll take all the tracks south
as far as Nottingham.
We'll take Cheltenham as well.
Otherwise, it will be
Thomas Shelby who's crucified,
and there will be no resurrection.
Come on, boys.
♪ The sun comes shining through ♪
♪ But when you're crying
You bring out the rain ♪
♪ So stop your crying... ♪
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm just gonna
take a short break. Thank you.
Yeah.
Beautiful, Billy. Beautiful.
Really nice. Really nice.
Really meaningful,
you know, a heartfelt song.
I like it. I really do.
Boys...
this here is Billy Grade.
Man I was telling you about.
Billy, this here's my kid brother, Finn.
Hey.
Have a drink, Billy.
I can't, my voice is...
Drink, Bill.
Yeah.
You boys won't remember,
but I remember when Billy here
made a living on the football pitch.
Yeah, that was
a long time ago, Mr Shelby.
-Yeah. What a left foot, eh?
-Yeah.
And then what?
Manager, right?
-Hmm?
Well, yeah. And now I'm a singer.
Are ya?
Every football team in England...
knows Billy Grade,
and he knows a few people, too.
Didn't you, Bill, eh? Hmm?
One or two.
Useful.
Very useful.
But what do you do, Bill, eh? Hmm?
You're in here, singing,
or whatever the fuck you call it,
in shithole pubs in Birmingham.
That's no way to make a living, boys.
- Degrading.
- I love it.
I really do, I love it.
And thank you,
by the way, for inviting me here tonight.
I really appreciate it.
So, thank you very--
Don't thank me.
I didn't invite you here to sing.
I wanna listen to music,
I'll buy an Al Jolson record.
Hmm?
That's what I'd do.
Real singer, ya know?
Melody, tune.
So, what is it that you want, exactly?
Finn will explain
the nature of my proposition.
You'll listen to him, won't you, Bill, eh?
You'll be attentive, won't ya?
Yeah, of course. Of course.
'Cause Isiah here,
he'll show you the fucking consequences
if you don't.
All right.
I'll leave you with the bottle. Hmm?
What proposition?
Right. What I want from you, Billy,
is for you to write down
a name and a number
next to every one
of those football teams, yeah?
-Why?
People like to bet
on those kind of things these days.
-We're a gambling enterprise.
-I know who you are.
To fix a horse race,
you give the outsider a bit of cocaine.
-Jesus.
-To fix a football match,
you give the goalkeeper 20 pounds.
You're a Peaky Blinder now, Billy.
Hmm?
What have you got there?
I've written a letter.
Ah.
Who for?
For you.
And Lizzie's written one to Tommy.
Well...
can I read it?
It's not finished yet.
I'm getting rid of the parts I wrote
when I was drunk.
By the way, I stopped drinking.
And your bottles of snow
I poured down the lavatory.
When I was drunk, I was too hard on you.
It's not your fault.
So...
that letter's about me, is it?
Yeah.
Hmm.
And about me.
About the future, about the company.
Lizzie and I--
Sat here and made things worse
the last few hours, hmm?
Yeah.
And we've come up with a plan.
You've come up with a plan, huh?
Lizzie says Tommy won't live
two more years
if he carries on like this.
He's gone too far.
Is that was Lizzie says, hmm? Really, now?
Well, how far has he gone,
hmm, Linda? How far?
He's lost all the legitimate money
in America.
No. No, that was Michael.
He's fixing races, he's fixing football.
Following the financial crisis,
the Shelby Company Limited has to find
other sources of cash income.
Tommy went into Chinatown.
He's selling out the communists
to the British intelligence.
And all the time, every day,
he gets more and more famous.
But that's okay, because if anyone
puts two and two together...
That wasn't us.
It's not fucking us!
It's going to blow up, Arthur!
It can't sustain. You know it!
Oh, yeah? And what do you know?
You've worked it all out,
you and fuckin' Lizzie. Huh?
Got it all planned out, is that right?
Hmm?
I tell you, all you're gonna do
is you're gonna be a good fuckin' wife.
Yeah, like the perfect couple,
we'll go upstairs.
Hmm?
We'll go upstairs...
Yeah. And we'll make love. Hmm?
I spent my day writing two letters
and deciding which one to give.
Looks like I'll have to
give the other one.
What other one?
What fucking other one?
What did you do with my letter?
I burnt it.
So did Arthur.
-Did you read it first?
-Yes.
That's more than Arthur did.
Didn't help that you can't fucking spell.
I left school too early.
Did you read the bit about the lawyers?
Do you wanna fuck?
Didn't think so.
-You don't want to eat?
-No.
-You've got calls?
-Yeah.
It's Ruby's birthday today, Tommy.
Do you know why I took her to Arthur's?
Because she said she's scared of you.
When she knows you're not coming home,
she's a different kid.
But I've bought a cake,
and I want you there.
We're in the drawing room.
Lizzie.
I'm in a room,
and they're coming at me.
But it's okay. I want 'em to.
Last thing I want is silence.
Standing up there in silence,
and someone says...
"Sorry about all that noise.
Sorry about all that...
dust.
Sorry about all that mud
and all that fucking blood."
And you say, "Don't be sorry.
Don't be sorry. It's all I can do now."
You want me to write this down?
Do you want me to write you
a fucking letter?
Me and Arthur can't write it down...
'cause they haven't invented
the fucking words.
We don't have the fucking words.
And the worst thing is...
could've stayed at school,
but we volunteered.
Still don't have the fucking words.
Should you choose to depart, Tommy,
either by your own hand or someone else's,
the person who would
take your place is me.
Legally, financially, everything.
I need to know
there will be something left.
Well, you know, Lizzie, in my head,
I still pay you for it. So...
good luck with me.
I have business.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Yeah, I wanna ask you some questions
about the night you met Michael Gray.
Make a wish.
Yay!
Okay, kids, come on. Let's go to bed.
-Quickly.
-Why? Who's coming?
That's the thing, Charles.
We don't know. We never know.
Tommy!
-Out of the fucking car.
- Don't!
Get out of the fucking car now,
or I'll open fire!
You looking for traitors?
There's one,
-with his ribs mashed up!
The man's gone fucking mad, Tom!
You did this?
With one arm and a hammer,
and a mighty pain, and a mighty fury!
They killed him.
My son.
They shot him and they put him up
on a fucking cross,
and he's fucking dead!
Who did?
Only Johnny Dogs and his kin
knew where we were camped.
No, Tom.
-No, I swear to God, I never told...
-I'll fucking kill you!
- I never told a--
- Fucking shoot him!
-My only fucking son! My fucking only...
- Johnny! Johnny!
Fucking took him from me!
- My only son!
- It's shattered!
-Listen to me. Listen to me!
Your shoulder is shattered.
You don't get it fixed,
you'll lose your arm.
He's gone. They fucking killed him,
my only fucking son!
I'll fucking kill you!
Listen to me!
How can a one-armed man
avenge the death of his son, eh?
They crucified my son...
for you.
Get away from my house!
All of you!
Get away from my child!
This is my house.
And I don't want you back.
I don't want you back!
You wanna take on the Billy Boys?
You need me alive.
Everyone fucking needs me.
Call an ambulance
or a man will lose his arm.
Come on, Johnny!
Come on.
Tom.
I'm no black cat, Tom.
I know, Johnny. I know.
In all the world, of all of the people,
you alone I know I can trust.
♪ On a gathering storm
Comes a tall handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat
With a red right hand ♪
♪ A shadow is cast wherever he stands ♪