Man, we can't even get a goal
for an exhibition match.
Friendly.
Ain't nothing friendly
about what happened out here.
They call exhibition matches friendlies.
Man, this sport drives me nuts.
Rebecca. My apologies.
Now, you've come all the way to Amsterdam,
and we at Ajax have been such rude hosts.
Marjolein, you've been more than gracious.
Especially given the circumstances.
There we are.
Till next time.
Thank you.
Truly was an honor to play here
at the Johan Croyff Arena.
No. The honor is ours completely.
But it is pronounced Johan Cruijff.
Still.
God, this song's depressing.
Would you agree that
this has been
an extremely demoralizing result?
But, luckily our spirits
were already broken.
Yeah. And so, Roy Kent, don't you think
Richmond's objectively poor performance
is due to the fact that you're nothing
without Zava?
Who cares? It's a fucking friendly.
A friendly is a pretend match.
This is a pretend conversation.
You're a pretend person
with a pretend job.
And I'm having a really hard time
pretending to give a shit.
Wow.
Right.
Jan...
- Hi. Thanks.
- Hi. Love the pink.
Okay, a night out in Amsterdam it is.
Let's make the best of it.
What's the plan?
I'm spoken for, I'm afraid.
It's my first time in Amsterdam,
and I have a date with someone special
in the red-light district.
Nah.
- Just you and me then, kid.
- I'd love to...
- That's a quick cancellation.
- How'd you know I was gonna cancel?
Because there's a certain note
in your vocal range
that you only ever hit
when you're being preemptively apologetic.
- Come on. Out with it.
- All right.
Apparently,
tonight is the best aurora borealis ever.
Like, it's the aurora "boreal-iest."
In Norway.
And Jack and her plane are waiting
for me at the airport right now.
Subtle.
And amazing.
Go.
- I promise I'll make it up to you.
- Yes, you will.
Great job, Jan.
And, Roy, thank you again for doing this.
Yeah. Anytime.
- I love you.
- Where's she going?
- Somewhere that believes they deserve her.
Hey, there he is.
- Someone's in a mood.
- Yeah.
- Wait.
- Actually...
What do you think?
Think only you can get these guys out
of their pineapple percussions.
Doldrums. Nice.
Yeah, I'm gonna say something.
Hey, fellas.
I'm about to say three words no coach
ever says unless he dang well means it.
- "You're all shit."
- No.
- "Knowledge is power"?
- True, but no.
- "Live, laugh, love."
- No.
Correct answer is: "No curfew tonight."
- What?
- That's right.
I don't wanna see your pretty faces
until we get back on this bus
at what time, Coach?
10:00 a.m., baby!
You heard the man. 10:00 a.m.
All right, let's be careful out there.
Hill Street Blues.
Smart move, Coach.
Yeah. Well, you know, they need it.
Not as bad as you do.
No curfew in Amsterdam, boys!
Should we all take naps
so we can stay up later?
No. We push through,
and we all meet
in the lobby five o'clock sharp.
Yeah!
Tonight is gonna be mad, you know!
Not for you, Tartt!
Let's go.
You serious?
You're not on fucking holiday
from training.
What about my stuff?
Right.
Throw this away, please.
Let's go!
Great. Sick. You have fun.
Gonna see the sights. Training. Amsterdam.
- Don't actually throw that away, yeah?
- Okay.
Hey. Wait up, Coach!
Getting off the coach, Coach.
Run!
This is gonna be so good.
Hey. How about you roll with me tonight?
That'd be wonderful. Thank you.
Yeah. Great.
Our first stop: the red-light district.
Did you know Amsterdam's origins
date back to the 13th century?
That's mad, innit?
Coach, this way.
This is the world-famous Skinny Bridge!
Yeah?
As seen in major motion picture,
James Bond's Diamonds Are Forever.
Stop with all the fucking
sightseeing shit, you twat.
Right.
Next stop, Amsterdam's thinnest house.
It's gonna blow your mind, lad.
Come on. Get moving, lad.
Hello.
Stinky, what's wrong?
- Nothing. Why?
- Bullshit!
I felt warm in my belly,
so there must be a problem. Out with it.
Sass, you know,
you're actually wrong this time.
I am never wrong.
Jesus.
What are all those bells?
Are you in a casino?
No. I'm actually just out
having a stroll in Amsterdam on my own.
Completely unburdened.
I haven't even got my bag with me.
Oh, right. Amsterdam.
I forgot. Jealous.
Well, eat a space cake for me
and call me when you freak out.
- I love you.
- Buh-buh-bye.
- Yeah.
- Yes?
I saw you walking just there,
and I thought,
"I have to say something
to this beautiful woman."
Right. What exactly were you...
Oh, my God. Oh, my! Go...
Shit.
Oh, my God!
Are you hurt?
No. I'm okay.
- It's just very cold.
- Come on.
Sorry, did you see where my phone went?
Who cares? You're alive. Come on.
Yeah. Yes. Okay. It's my phone, so...
Fair enough.
Come. You need to get warm.
What is it that you wanted to tell me?
You're walking on the bike lane.
I mean,
how the fuck am I supposed to know that?
Stupid fucking place.
Come on.
Like, remember when Jordan
wouldn't wear Reebok in the '92 Olympics?
Of course.
'74 World Cup,
Cruyff refuses to wear Adidas,
they gotta make him a special
two-striped shirt. He was a badass.
But he was also a paragon of the '60s,
so he was bigger than Jordan, really.
He was like Jordan
and John Lennon combined.
That's cool.
- You pick a place to eat yet?
- Oh, shoot. No, I forgot.
On it.
Let's see.
Hey! This could be good.
Yankee Doodle Burger Barn.
"An authentic American dining experience
with American-sized portions."
You know, I could definitely go
for a little taste of home.
- How's that sound, Coach?
- What's it rated?
2.7.
Out of five.
Think we can beat that.
All right.
I don't know what's going
on with me, Coach.
It's like I'm feeling stuck
or something, you know?
I need to do something
to help me get me out of my head.
Like get punched in the face or
drink a couple of bottles of red wine
and yell at my mom.
You know, just...
I wanna try something new.
Help me get inspired.
I've been waiting for you
to say those words for a very long time.
We should have took a train
to Paris a long time ago.
Would any of you gentlemen care
for some drinks?
Leffe Blond.
- I'll have a beer and a shot of te...
- No!
We're about to head out, but thank you.
No worries.
Okay. Yeah. That's everyone.
So, what's the plan for the night then,
Captain?
I'm taking all your suggestions.
For me, the best option for a night
in Amsterdam is a train to Paris.
I told you...
I'm gonna say it again. I am not kidding.
You know, my father actually suggested
we take a boat tour through the canal.
- Yeah. Great way to see the city.
- We're near The Hague.
We can go
to the International Court of Justice.
Poke around. Ask some questions.
I would like to see a tulip.
- You mean tulip fields?
- No. Just one tulip.
An entire field
will be incredibly overwhelming.
Wait. Y'all are joking, right?
We gotta go to a live sex show.
Very cultural, Thierry.
Yo, Trent! What should we do?
Well,
the city has a wonderful museum culture.
In fact, tonight is what's known
as Museumnacht,
where they stay open till quite late.
I didn't come to Amsterdam
to learn things.
Yeah.
- Sorry, Trent.
- Great shot though.
I don't know. The city does seem lovely,
but maybe it would just be easier
if all of us stayed in
and enjoyed a nice team movie night.
Sam, come on.
Hey, boys. Have fun tonight.
Higgins. Where you going?
Tonight's the night young William here
becomes a man.
Cheers.
Nah.
Jan Maas, we're on your home turf.
What you got for us?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Good point. Let's go.
Okay, tourists, thank you for getting
all those terrible ideas out of the way.
Now listen, my cousin, Martin Garrix,
is deejaying
- at a private all-night party.
- I guess it's his cousin.
We're talking drinking,
dancing and women into the morning,
which is when they'll be serving
a hearty breakfast.
Hey, guys, I'm sorry. Sorry.
I think I need to bow out.
Yeah. I ate some pickled herring earlier,
and now my stomach's bothering me.
- You're gonna miss the live sex show, bro.
- You mean the party.
I cannot wait
to hear all the dirty details.
Good luck, gents.
- See you later.
- All right.
All right, broski.
Hydrate!
Right. So it seems like
this private party is the obvious answer?
- Yep.
- Okay, great.
We just gotta take the bus to Groningen,
which is only a two-hour drive.
Two hours?
- It breezes over.
- Two.
You will love it.
Hey, amigos. Why don't we just split up?
The tulips with me!
No! Overruled.
We pick one place, and we go as a team.
Excuse me.
I think we're gonna order them drinks now.
And can you bring me
a giant stack of napkins? Thanks.
Voting time.
- Dude, a sex show is funny.
- We're not going to a sex show.
I really want the tulip experience
that everyone talks about.
Actually surprisingly good water pressure
for a boat.
Hello?
Oh, shit.
Fuck me.
Right down there's the bench
from Fault in Our Stars!
The movie!
Tourist!
So, red-light district.
- That's right.
- Cool. Okay. Awesome.
- Is everything all right at home or...
- Here we are.
His name was Chet Baker.
American, gifted trumpeter,
unique singer and a heroin addict.
He was tortured by demons,
but they didn't stop him
from making beautiful music.
He's what got me into jazz
in the first place, you know.
You hear his story and you think,
"There's nothing more punk rock
than that."
Then, on the 13th of May, 1988,
he passed away on this very spot.
Wow. How was it he died?
He fell from that window up there.
But was it an accident?
Did he jump, or was he pushed?
And we're gonna solve
that mystery tonight.
No. We're just here
to pay our respects to a legend.
What led to his death?
We don't know, Will.
- We only know this: drugs are bad.
- Yes.
- No, they are.
- Yeah.
My man, Kenneth the bus driver,
hooked me up a couple of weeks ago.
Wait, so you travel with it?
I thought they had plenty
of that stuff here.
Well, I just don't like my medicine
to be taxed.
I don't know, Coach.
You know, I've always been more
of a beer man or Sour Patch Kids.
Sour Patch Kids don't form literal
new pathways in your brain.
Picture a sheet of fresh,
white snow covering all the footsteps
of all the paths that you've trod before,
forcing you...
Nay, encouraging you... to begin anew.
And how's it taste?
Disgusting, so most people put it
in peanut butter and jelly or yogurt.
Uh-huh. And which one we doing?
Neither. We're doing tea.
Oh, come on, man. Are you kidding me?
That's like hiding poop
inside a smoothie of barf.
I don't say this often enough
because I generally think it's implied,
but trust me.
This is how you change your mind.
I can't do it, Coach. I'm sorry.
Oh, boy.
Did you have any?
- Where we at?
- We have nine votes for sex show.
Nine votes for private party.
And one vote for tulip.
That leaves us with two.
Sex show versus private party.
And I think someone picked tulip, yes?
But who?
Dani, you wrote it in Spanish.
Someone wrote it in Spanish, yes.
Look, it doesn't matter what we choose.
This has to be unanimous. Discuss.
Okay, the idea of seeing a sex show
is one that makes me more uncomfortable
than aroused.
Right? Right.
Which is why I'm still in favor of,
you know, a nice, simple movie night.
But as I said earlier,
Jan's admittedly inconvenient plan
is an excellent second option.
Yeah? Yes? Okay.
Great. All right. Let's go.
Wh... No. Guys. Stick with me.
We're two hours away from that party.
But we're only ten minutes away
from watching some sex. Come on.
Things flying about...
Can you please tell my friend
that he is being a boring tourist?
- What is your name?
- Everybody calls me Van Damme.
Okay, Van Damme, would you prefer to pay
to watch two tired people have sex
or rather go to a party
where perhaps you could get some yourself?
They're tired?
Exhausted.
We can finally start our night
in Amsterdam!
In Groningen, yes!
No, wait. We need to eat first, right?
Yes. Definitely.
Okay. What do you want to eat?
- Ramen.
- Shawarma!
No way. We haven't eaten...
Some brownies with marijuana.
Or maybe some Mexican?
- Hello?
- It's me. Is it okay to come in?
Yeah, of course. It's your house... boat.
Hi.
You really didn't need to leave.
No, but taking a shower on a stranger's
boat is uncomfortable enough.
And you shouldn't be worried that
he's watching you through some peephole.
- Peephole?
- Yeah.
Someone's dated themselves.
Had you down as more of a webcam kind
of guy... Anyway, thank you, nonetheless.
You're bleeding.
- I'm what?
- You're bleeding.
What?
- Oh, God.
- Yeah, don't worry. Take a seat.
I don't even know how that happened.
I was in the military.
I trained for this.
And I don't want blood on my floor.
- Hey?
- Yep.
You got strong ankles.
Yes. I wear a lot of high heels for work.
All right. There you go.
Sorry. Force of habit.
It's all that military training.
And the tea was really lovely. Thank you.
Would it perhaps be more lovely
if we added some brandy?
No. I'm just going to wait
till my clothes have dried
and then I'll pop off.
In two hours and 40 minutes.
Okay.
If you don't wanna wait, I can call a cab
for you and your bag of wet clothes,
or I can make dinner.
Well, yes, I am quite hungry actually.
And wet clothes are rather heavy
in a bag, so... yes.
Fuck it. That'd be nice.
- Good! Gezellig?
- Yep.
Wait.
Feel free to change into one of these.
Should I be concerned that you've got
a giant Tupperware box of women's clothing
in your floating house?
These aren't trophies, are they?
No. It's my former partner.
She was tall, like you.
I'm sorry. Did she pass away?
Unfortunately, no.
Please help yourself.
I... Look, I don't really think I can
borrow your ex... God, this is lovely.
Please, change.
We'll eat, and then you'll go, all right?
Yeah. Sure.
And after dinner
I can give you a foot massage.
Absolutely not.
Are you sure? My technique is sound.
I'm sure it is, but I will pass.
Okay, then. Fine. Stand there
with tired feet, completely sober.
It does not affect me at all.
Fine. Come on, then. I'll have a bit.
Gezellig.
They put a dam on the river Amstel.
"Amsteldam."
Amsterdam. It's good, innit?
- Come on.
- Fucking stop for a fucking second!
Please.
God.
How do you know so much about here?
It's Amsterdam. How do you not?
Never been here in my life.
- What? Never?
- No.
- Not one stag party?
- Not one international match?
- No.
Not one emergency flight diverted here
because some EasyJet passenger
was being a prick?
- That never happens.
- It does.
It does happen, if you're being enough
of a prick. Which I was.
It just looks like
a Disney version of an old city.
It all looks so fucking fake.
It's not fake.
Come on. Windmills? Fake.
I ain't even from here, and I'm offended.
Windmills are real, man.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, I'll believe it when I see it.
We need bikes.
What? No.
- You know, Coach, if you wanna go...
- I'll see you in the morning.
Hey.
Hi. Can I help you?
Have you got vanilla vodka?
Dear God, no.
A beer, please. Thank you.
- There you go, sweetie.
- Thanks.
Hey, can I ask, do you know who I am?
Can I tell you a secret?
Tonight, you're whoever you want to be.
Yeah.
You should stick around for the party
later on. Thunderdong.
Good vibes, good place to make friends.
Sounds fun, I'm in.
Trent! Hey.
Can I get a drink
for my work acquaintance, please?
Sorry, did you say Thunderdong?
I think I'm in the wrong place.
My mistake. Cheers.
Happens all the time.
Yeah.
- Colin!
- Good to see you, Trent.
Colin. I already knew.
I've known for months.
I haven't said anything to anyone.
I must have a good reason for that,
mustn't I?
Right.
Your ex has wonderful taste.
Well, actually, she hated that one.
Yeah, of course she did.
I bought it for her.
Hey. Gezellig, right?
That smells wonderful.
It's almost ready.
Would you like a drink?
- I would love one.
- Please, help yourself.
So, should I be worried about some
giant Dutch woman wandering on here
and strangling me for wearing her clothes?
No.
Things are over between us, and have been
so for some time. So don't worry.
It's all right. I didn't mean to...
You don't need to tell me
any of the details.
She was unfaithful.
I loved her very much, so it wrecked me,
and I came dangerously
close to destroying our family on it.
But then, with time,
I realized that this thing didn't happen
to me, it happened for me. You know?
Cheers.
Proost.
- Proost. Prost.
- Proost.
Proust.
Wait, is this some Dutch bloke singing
"She Believes in Me" by Kenny Rogers?
Whoa.
This Dutch bloke is the great André Hazes,
and he's singing "Zij Gelooft in Mij,"
all right?
Okay.
And yes, the Gambling Man did it first.
But...
And who knows
Maybe on some special night
If my song is right
I will find a way
- The fuck are you doing?
- Just be patient.
Bicycle?
Thank you. Two, please.
I love a challenge. Hold this.
Mate. We've just made tonight amazing.
I don't wanna ride around
on a fucking bike.
Oh, come on. It'll be fun.
- Voilà. Sixty euros.
- Have a hundred.
Thank you.
- Here.
- Get it away from me.
- Oh, come on.
- No, I don't want it.
Mate,
we take the bikes, we find a windmill.
- No. I said no.
- Why the fuck not?
I don't know how to ride a bike!
No refunds.
Fucking hell, Roy.
Do you know how to tie your own laces?
Stop being a dick.
When I went to Sunderland,
my granddad told me he'd teach me how
to ride when I came back for Christmas,
and then he fucking died,
and I haven't been on a bike since.
And now I'm saying that out loud,
I realize that never learning was actually
a great disrespect to his memory
and now I feel ashamed.
So can we stop talking about it
and go back to me just taking out
my negative emotions on you,
even if you deserve it or not?
Go on, Roy. For Granddad.
Fuck.
Okay,
you're gonna sit up, look up and pedal.
Straight back up. Just straight back up.
Put your feet on the pedals.
That's it, good. Now pedal.
Put your foot on the ped...
All right. Okay. All right.
On the bike. Okay. There you go.
Pick it up but in an angry way, man.
Good lad. Pedal, pedal, pedal, pedal.
That's it. Hey!
Good lad, pedal it. You actually...
That's it, that's it!
That's good! That's good.
You did it for two seconds there, man.
That's an improvement.
Steady on, mate. Steady on.
Hey! What... You're doing well, man.
Calm down.
How's that gonna help anyone?
In there. There you go. Good.
- I can't turn the other way.
- Yes. All right. This way.
- It's right. Follow me.
- Try and hit me!
- I can't turn.
It's all about balance, man.
Just like dribbling.
If you can dribble, you can balance.
That's it.
Yeah, that's good. You do...
- All right, mate. It's good...
- I'm gonna kill you.
- You're doing it.
- I'm doing it.
Let's go find a fucking windmill!
For Granddad! All right, wait for me.
We're sitting here?
Well, yeah.
You know, you said pick good seats, so...
Yeah, but these are so exposed.
Oh, no. It's like the time I was
front and center at an improv comedy show.
Are they gonna make a song
about how I look like an altar boy?
It's okay. You did great.
- Here's your drink.
- Thank you.
Thank you for doing this, Will.
One pilgrim alone is merely a zealot,
but two pilgrims together,
that's a pilgrimage.
Cheers.
Here we go.
Welcome to Jazz Café Alto. My name is
Dante Charles, and we are the Kartel.
- Miles Davis once said that...
- Yeah.
Remember the night
And that was the second time
I came out to her.
This time, however, she believed me.
And now... we're closer than ever.
And your daughter?
Yeah. She's never been happier.
My point is,
it was really difficult
to hold on to that secret.
But I'm not a professional athlete.
How do you do it?
Well... my whole life is two lives really.
You got my work life.
Like, no one at the club knows.
I'd like to think they wouldn't care,
but it's just easier that way.
Then you got my dating life.
Some guys think it's hot.
Others say they don't care, but eventually
they get tired and they move on.
Then the club brought in Dr. Sharon...
and she helped me realize that I have...
an ache.
An ache for both my lives
to be my only life.
I don't want to be a spokesperson.
I don't want a bunch of apologies.
All I want is for when we win a match,
to be able to kiss my fella the same way
the guys get to kiss their girls.
And I know we can't fix
every ache inside of us.
But I shouldn't have
to pretend it's not there either.
How'd you know? About me?
Well, I used my Holmesian
powers of journalistic deduction.
Saw you kissing a guy
outside Sam's restaurant.
Yeah.
Those are the bells of the Westerkerk.
Anne Frank heard
those same bells every night.
She lived just there.
Right by this big, pink triangle?
Think that came a bit later.
Oh, yeah.
"One doesn't expect to get from life
what one has already learned
it cannot give,
rather, one begins to see
that life is a kind of sowing time...
and the harvest is not yet here."
He was just a humble preacher's son.
And yes, he had his demons, but they never
stopped him from searching for beauty.
Because when you find beauty,
you find inspiration.
If, that is,
you stay as determined as Vincent.
Never stop, no matter how many failures.
When you know you're doing
what you're meant to do, you have to try.
Where I'm from...
Kansas, my home...
This here, this is our state flower.
I want you to have this.
We close in three minutes.
Mercy buckets.
Yep.
We are in Holland!
We should try Dutch food!
- As a Frenchman, I would rather die!
- No!
Enough!
We are riven by this crossroads!
Is this it?
Should we huddle around the laptop
for a movie night?
How else do we proceed?
How doth we channel
this lack of compromise?
This dissension? This rage?
Captain.
Coach. I know that you have
my best interests at heart,
or the club's anyway.
Even though you're clearly upset
about something else
and you're taking it out on me.
What I'm trying to say is,
I'm sorry for being a dick earlier.
I've been to Amsterdam twice.
When I was 14, me dad
was trying to get back with me mum,
and he was acting like some kind of
fucking super dad or some shit,
and he brought me out here
for some father-son bonding time.
Anyway, he said it was
to watch a football match.
After the game, he took me to the
red-light district for my real present.
He took me to lose my virginity
to those ladies behind the windows.
Jesus. Must have been traumatizing.
No. She loved it.
For me... Sorry, me, you mean.
No.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Anyway, a couple of years later,
me mum brought me back here.
And we went to museums
and did all the tours,
and it's the first time I had stroopwafel.
Never forget that time.
Even though my dad weren't here, he was
still kinda there with us. You know?
I was a dick today too. I'm sorry.
I think Keeley's got a girlfriend.
Let's go find us some windmills, eh?
Yeah.
Bang.
Howdy, partner.
Hey there.
Welcome to Yankee Doodle Burger Barn.
Table for one?
Wh... Yes, please. Yeah.
Hey, where in the States you from?
Melbourne.
Plenty of room tonight,
where would you like to sit?
Windy City, Big Apple or Hollywood?
Oh, well. Tell Mama that Roxie Hart
is coming home. Lipschitz.
Chicago.
Windy City.
Great, mate. Giddyap.
Here you are. Your fancy hot dog.
Howdy.
- Can I get some ranch dressing?
- Absolutely, ma'am.
Hey, partner. Here all right?
Yeah.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Oh, no, you didn't.
- Yes.
Well, it actually happened.
Would you like some water?
Wise.
This is so cozy.
The food and the music, the boat and...
It really is...
Gezellig?
You keep saying that word.
Or are you just choking?
- Gezellig. That one?
- That's the one.
- Come on then. What does that mean?
- What...
I don't know. Gezellig.
There is no direct
English translation, I think.
It can mean cozy. Like a warm fire.
Gezellig.
But you can also keep your mind gezellig.
You know, your heart, your soul.
The people you're with. The places you go.
You know?
Even this, right now, here is...
Gezellig.
Exactly.
They feel pretty dry.
All right. Where were we?
Wine.
Here's your onion ring pyramid
and your freedom fries.
Thank you.
You enjoying the game?
Oh, yeah. Hey, you know what?
I bet you a thousand bucks
the Bulls will win 107 to 86.
I'm just kidding.
I remember watching this game
as a kid with my dad.
Yeah. I used to love
watching basketball with him.
Thank you for sharing.
And please feel free to choose
from our menu of 50 Nifty United Sauces.
And there's a lovely queso
from Puerto Rico.
You know what?
How about you just surprise me?
- Can do.
- Thanks.
And the Bulls drop
into their triangle offense,
creating constant movement
between the players.
It's been the key to their success
this season.
It opens up for Jordan. He shoots. Yes!
Pyramid ain't nothing but a triangle.
Actually, three triangles
all leaning on each other.
Howdy, Ted.
Hey. So, how does this one look?
Why'd you bring me this one?
It's the best one.
Well, this is mighty strange.
Hello?
Hello, Ted.
Hey, that's me. Who are you?
I am the True Spirit of Adventure.
I like that. Well, what's shaking, TSA?
Do you know where triangles come from,
Ted?
I don't know.
God dropped a square on the floor
and it broke in half long-ways
or something?
- Whoopsie.
- No, Ted.
It's debated that the triangle
was first defined by Pythagoras
as any shape with three sides
and three corners.
That's a good theorem.
But throughout history, many believe
that triangles have held special powers.
Oh, yeah.
From the Holy Trinity of Christianity
to the trikaya of Buddhism.
There's also that spooky eye thing
on the back of the one-dollar bill.
Oh, yeah.
In some Native American cultures,
the triangle symbolizes home.
I'm sorry Europeans kicked all
them folks out of their triangle.
But the concept of the triangle
reached its zenith in 1989
when a man called Tex Winter,
an assistant coach for your Chicago Bulls,
introduced his triangle offense.
The central component of which was
for a player to always have two available
teammates to whom he could pass the ball.
These three players formed...
A triangle.
Bingo, Ringo.
But that was never the only triangle
on the court.
For when the players moved,
they created more and more triangles.
Hey, you're right.
Actually, Ted, you're right.
Yes!
Howdy, partner.
Hey. Can I borrow a pen?
- Come on, boy!
- Thanks.
Yankee Doodle Burger Barn
Happy birthday
Happy birthday, Mel
World War II was won by America
But the West was liberated
Thanks to Canada
Hey!
Do you play?
Yes, he... Yes, he does.
He plays bass because Chet Baker...
Chet Ba... Do you know who Chet Baker is?
All right. Okay.
Players in.
Pillows ready.
Begin!
Let's get lost now.
Vanilla vodka.
- Oh, my God. He's still at it.
- Yeah. It's pretty amazing.
What the hell is he doing?
I don't know. But he's got my pen.
Derek's gonna make you buy a new one.
Fucking hate Derek.
Yeah.
Fuck!
Let's get lost
Good morning.
So...
Last night...
Did we...
Did we?
No.
Breakfast?
No. I have to go.
Of course.
But... thank you...
You're welcome...
I won't forget you.
Yeah, you might.
People get Alzheimer's.
Did we?
Oh, yes, we did.
I'm telling you, Amsterdam, amazing.
Like, yes, we lost the game,
but my boss played in a jazz band
and then...
Gerbrandt, Gijs, Gilles,
Brechje and Paul...
Okay, doei.
Doei!
- Hey, Will.
- You speak Dutch?
Don't tell Jan. Where's Ted?
- He's in the back.
- Thank you.
Mum? Sorry. Yes, no... What was I saying?
And then I met the most lovely couple,
and they invited me for a threesome.
Bonjour.
Coach.
Hey, Coach.
Wait, let me guess, Piggy Stardust.
- Rashers to rashers, oink to oinky.
- I love it.
Hey, sorry about last night.
No, that's okay. I'm sorry.
You know, I shouldn't have let you
wander around out there all alone
with a head full of tea, you know.
Good thing it was a dud batch.
What's that?
I wasn't feeling anything.
So I called Kenneth, he tried it,
couple hours later,
calls me up totally contrite.
Confirmed, dud batch.
It happens.
Let me ask you a question here.
Is this anything?
The way I see it,
we've been playing too rigid, you know?
Our guys need freedom.
Go wherever they wanna go.
Follow their guts, their hearts.
As long as they remember to fill
in the space that someone left behind.
They gotta have one another's backs,
that's for sure.
But, you know, it's just constant,
nonstop motion.
Just going from position to position
until positions don't really
even exist anymore.
It's fast, fluid, free.
With full support.
You come up with this yourself?
Yeah?
Congrats.
You should call it Total Football.
I like that.
Which was invented right here
in Holland in the '70s.
You think we should try it?
Yes, I do.
All right, cool. Total Football.
Room for one more?
Hey, boss.
So, 12 unanswered texts,
three un-haha'ed GIFs.
We good?
I'm sorry, Ted.
My phone is at the bottom of a canal.
Is that Keats?
Nope.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, Will, how we looking?
We're two short. Who's missing?
You lovely people!
Did you miss me?
Don't fucking ask.
Let's go.
We saw a windmill!
All right.
Hell yeah.
Come on!
I bet you the sex show was dope though.
- What?
- Leave it alone, man.
Everything okay, boss?
Don't worry, about a thing
'Cause every little thing's
Gonna be all right
Well, I appreciate it.
Singin', don't worry, about a thing
'Cause every little thing
Gonna be all right
Everybody!
Don't worry
About a thing
'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
One more time!
Singin', don't worry
About a thing
Don't worry about that thing now.
'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
Every one of them!
- Singin', don't worry
- Don't do it!
About a thing
'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right