Fucking hell.
All right, let's go.
It's 4:00 a.m.
Yeah. We start at 4:00 a.m.
I thought you were joking.
How is that a joke?
'Cause it's 4:00 a.m.
We start at 4:00, so you can do
three workouts a day instead of two.
Okay, but it's 4:00 a.m.
Do you wanna be better than Zava or not?
Well, how are we gonna see? It's dark out.
Fucking hell.
Now get dressed.
Or I start flicking your balls.
This is perverse.
Whoops.
There you go.
Good morning, Sassy Smurf.
Good morning, Marlboro Man.
You know, you snored all night.
I'm sorry about that.
That's all right.
It's actually very soothing.
Sounded like the sea.
Well, I'm glad
you didn't hear any boat horns,
given all the fried yams I ate last night.
Hey, I was thinking.
We have a good time together, yeah?
They're called simultaneous orgasms,
Ted, yes.
Yeah, well, but I mean
also all the talking and laughing
and all that stuff. Yeah?
Sure.
Well, apart from all your dreadful puns.
Right. Well, it's tough.
Sometimes I just see 'em there,
and I gotta take a swing at 'em, you know?
No, I... Well, what I'm getting at is...
Well, I was just thinking maybe...
we could go on an actual date sometime.
You know? You and me, together.
God, no.
Well, I appreciate you taking the time
to consider it.
Ted, we can't date.
Why not?
- You're a mess.
- I'm a mess?
Course you are.
I'm a mess too, but I'm a mess
three years further on than you,
so I'm more of a slight disarray.
More like a slight disarray of sunshine,
if you ask me.
Oh, God.
- Sorry.
- Ted, on the day my ex got remarried,
I drank a bottle of red wine
through a straw
and told my Uber driver
I was in love with him.
Then, when he dropped me home,
I puked so much,
my mouth was like an elevator
from the goddamn Shining.
Knocked my rating down to a 3.9.
3.9?
Fuck you. Why? What's yours?
Oh, God, you're a five, aren't you?
- Course you're a five. How the fuck are you a five?
I don't know. I'm tidy.
I say "Please" and "Thank you."
Sometimes I offer to drive
if they look tired.
You are such a mess.
Ted, I like our status.
Friends with benefits,
like Natalie Portman and Ashton Kutcher.
No.
I think you're thinking of 2011's other
good-friends-turned-casual-lovers
based rom-com.
No Strings Attached.
Friends with Benefits
was Mila Kunis and Justin Timberlake.
Wow. 2011, friends be fuckin'.
Yeah.
So, let's keep things 2011.
Cool and breezy.
Like an Arab Spring.
And good luck
against West Ham this weekend.
Fuck Rupert
and that shriveled raisin-pouch
he calls a nutsack.
Hello! Here for Flo?
- You can jump in, love.
- Lovely, thank you.
This is nice. Gray seats? Yes, please.
West Ham. This is the real opportunity
for the Wonder Kid
to become the Wonder Man...
101.
100.
Ninety-nine.
Why do you only sleep with a top on?
Because I get cold upstairs
and hot downstairs.
I get that.
Mornin'.
Listen to what Rupert said in this one.
"I truly look forward
to seeing my old club again.
Richmond are top-class."
- What a soggy, wet piece of shit.
- Thank you.
Right, I'm off to the training ground.
Thanks again for the opportunity.
Babe, you earned it.
Shandy came up with
this super fun Bantr promo.
It uses all the single players
on the team.
Yeah.
The anonymous man you're Bantr-ing with
could be a professional footballer.
That's great.
And that's all the single players,
you say?
So, it's, like,
Colin and Dani and Sam, et cetera?
Yeah, although I don't think
Sam's doing it anymore.
- No.
- So fun.
- Ms. Jones.
- Hello, Barbara.
- All right there, Barbs?
- It's "Barbara."
If possible, could I get two tickets
for the Richmond-West Ham match?
Jack might be coming to London
this weekend.
Of course.
Who's Jack?
Jack Danvers.
The head of the VC
that funded your company.
Our boss.
Yes. That Jack. Of course.
That's not a problem, Barbara.
I can let you have some seats in my suite.
Lovely.
Thank you so much, Rebecca.
That's so kind of you and so efficient.
Keeley.
Thanks, Barbara.
So, the one thing we cannot do
against West Ham is the False Nine.
- 'Cause that's Nate's shit.
- Exactly.
So, we decided to go with
our classic 4-4-2.
Which is exactly what
that prick expects us to do.
So, we do the opposite.
Five up front. Full-on attack.
But Nate knows we're gonna do that,
because Nate knows that we're trying to
outthink him by thinking like him.
Well, fuck Nate, fuck thinking
and fuck fucking Socrates.
So, we gotta stop thinking like Nate
and start thinking
like Nate would think we would think
if Nate were thinking like us,
and then do the last thing
that Nate thinking like us
thinking like Nate thinking like us
would ever expect us to do.
Have Zava drop back
and play Nate's False Nine.
Voi-fucking-là.
Brilliant.
- It's mostly Beard's idea.
- Nah, it was a group effort.
I do have one question.
- Of course.
- Who fucking cares?
Do you think Zava'll do it?
Fuck!
- Good mornin'.
- Hey.
- Uh-oh, what's wrong?
- Roy doesn't think we can beat Nate.
- Higgins doesn't think so either!
- Beard said it to me first.
- You throw me under the bus? How dare...
- You walked in here this morning...
- You're gonna sell me out?
- Whoa! Whoa.
Y'all pointin' more fingers
than Ganesha givin' directions.
Now look, you fellas need to calm down
and just kiss.
He's right.
Keep it simple, smartypants.
An answer will show up. Don't worry.
But until it does,
here's a question for y'all: Am I a mess?
Sassy ended up
spending the night last night and...
No, hush your butts.
That ain't the headline.
Well, I asked her out
on a proper date this morning.
She turned me down cold. She said I was...
And I quote... "a mess."
- Yeah.
- Sounds like a case for the Diamond Dogs!
Release the hounds.
Yeah, here we go! Let's do it.
- Fuck's sakes.
Yes.
- "Yes" what?
- Yes, you're a mess.
Okay. Expound.
We're playing Nate this week,
and you're acting like
it's not a big deal.
Nothing's different. He didn't hurt you.
Hey, look,
we ain't talking about Nate right now.
I'm asking you if you think I'm a mess.
All right?
Higgy pie, what do you think?
I think I don't understand
how you're not pissed off with Nate.
We have a saying
in Co-Dependents Anonymous.
- Y... What?
- Jane makes me go with her.
Yeah.
Pain is like carbon monoxide.
Expressing it to the person
who hurt you is like opening a vent,
but holding it in will poison you.
I like that.
But Nate didn't hurt me.
Bullshit!
Roy, did you wanna get in
on this Diamond Dog situation?
- Hey, Roy! Hey, Roy.
- Hey, Roy. Here, Roy.
Here, Roy. Come here, Roy.
La, la, la, la, la!
So, the match of the week
is clearly Richmond and West Ham.
Now, it's been a strong start
to the season for both of these teams,
but I think the Hammers are favorites,
going into the London derby,
based on the tactical acumen
of the Wonder Kid, Nathan Shelley.
Yeah, Shelley is brilliant,
there's no doubt about that,
but Zava, he is a genius.
I like the Greyhounds for this one.
That's my guy!
No, you can't have him. He's mine.
- Let's move on, shall we, to Sunday's...
- Hey, look. Guys, guys.
Who cares, right?
Now come on, we've got work to do.
Let's go.
He is correct.
We must ignore these talking faces.
Even when they are in our favor.
Thank you, "Zorro."
Exactly,
but it's actually pronounced "Zoreaux."
Why?
I don't know. Because that's how
my parents say it, I guess?
My friend, you can be
whoever you want to be.
I let all of my children name themselves
once they reach the age of seven.
That is why my eldest is called
"Smingus Dingus."
Dream big, and you may never wake up.
Thank you.
Jesus.
I can't believe I'm about to say this,
but hey, lads, I agree with Zava.
Yes, it's a big fucking game,
but we've just gotta focus, do what we do,
- do you know what I mean?
- Yeah. He's right.
And don't forget, yeah?
- Believe in "Believe."
- Yes.
What the...
What?
- Oh, shit.
- What?
- Why the fuck did you do that?
- I was just checking
if I acquired the ability
to chop things in half.
Yeah, and what if you had?
Sorry, bruv. I didn't think it through.
Fellas. Someone ripped this in half.
What the fuck? What?
What the fuck?
You're joking
Hello...
Jade.
Nathan.
Shelley.
Lovely to see you again.
Okay.
- Sorry I've not been around much.
You haven't?
No. No, I've been really busy
with my new job.
Big new job just keeping me very busy.
Sounds silly. Maybe you should quit
your big new busy job.
Anyway, just here to pick up my takeaway.
I bought lunch for my whole staff.
Apart from the trainers,
'cause they eat like cows.
Sorry, that sounds... No, they're love...
I mean, they're lovely people.
They're just vegetarians.
No way.
Look who's here. No fucking way!
- Do you know who this is?
- Jason Jelly.
- That's right.
- No, "Nathan Shelley."
That's right, Nathan Shelley,
manager of West Ham United,
in my restaurant!
- Big week, my guy.
- Yep.
Big fucking week.
I'm Derek. I'm the manager here.
- Anything you need, you got it.
- Okay.
- From one manager to another.
Yeah, well, it's not quite the same, but...
Facing your team this week.
That's gotta be hard-core, right?
I mean, you talked a lot of shit
about them in the press.
- Didn't ya? I loved it.
- Sorry, can I pay?
No.
This is on me, okay? On me. Understand?
This man's money is no good here.
Never charge. Except for booze.
Gotta charge for booze.
I didn't order any booze. It's 12:30.
Knock 'em dead. Go Hammers!
No way. Oi, do you know who this is?
All right, okay. Bye.
And cut!
Lovely, Colin. Thank you.
All right. Okay, Dani, you're up.
I'm very nervous.
No. Don't be nervous. Look, just sit here.
Look into the camera
and pretend you're talking
to an old friend.
My oldest friend is Javiar.
Great. How long have you known Javiar?
Only a couple of months,
but he turns 108 years old next week.
- Perfect.
- Yeah.
Final checks.
Thank you.
- Hello, Keeley.
- Hi.
Yeah.
Just scoot to your left a little bit.
Yeah, that's it. Okay, off you go, Dani.
You may not know who I am, but I think
the most beautiful parts of a woman
are her flaws.
And cut! Thank you, Dani. Next!
Okay.
- Brought you coffee.
- Yeah.
- How's it going?
- Oh, my God. This is great.
- Yeah?
- They're great.
I just... I love being the boss.
- Cheers to that. Yeah.
- Cheers to that.
You ready, Zoreaux?
Yeah,
but I actually go by "Van Damme" now.
Okay, great. Action, Van Damme.
You don't know who I am,
but I'm looking for someone
who likes short walks on the beach,
so we can spend more time, you know...
And cut.
Great, thanks, Van Damme. Next!
- Van Damme?
- Yeah. It's my new name.
Cool. Why?
Because I love Jean-Claude Van Damme,
and Zava told me
I should be whoever I wanna be.
- Okay, yeah. Cool.
- All right, Van Damme.
- All right, boys.
- Take it easy.
He's so fucking hot.
- What's his story?
- Jamie? He's so cocky.
But I guess you have to be at this level.
But he only thinks about himself.
At least, he used to.
Joking. No.
But he's not accountable for his actions
and what they do to others.
Except he is getting better
at making apologies.
Still, he only thinks with his dick.
And yet, I don't think
he's seen anyone in ages.
I just wanna know if I can bang him, babe.
I don't know.
You should probably ask him,
it's his dick.
Cool. Off you go, Jamie.
What are y'all still doing here?
Coach, you're gonna wanna watch this.
Is it one of them videos
of a military parent
coming home after a long tour?
'Cause if so, I'm gonna be eating tears
and snot for dinner.
Not quite.
Here we go.
Where'd this come from?
This fucking legend
thought to pull the security footage
when we told him about the sign.
When we told him about the sign.
I guess you can take the boy
out of journalism
but you can't take journalism
out of the boy.
Right, you fucking ruined it now.
The point is,
the answer we were looking for
has arrived.
What are you talking about?
A video like this could
motivate a team, perhaps.
Thank you for your help, Trent.
May a young Robert Redford
portray you in a film someday.
Probably Dustin Hoffman.
- Good night.
Go home, guys. Get some sleep.
Okay.
- Good night, Ted. Night, Beard.
- Good night.
Night, Coach.
Coach.
I was thinking about your Sassy situation.
Yeah.
Jane's sister is in town.
- No, thank you, Coach.
- That's the right answer.
Burning the midnight oil, I see.
Yeah. Sorry for the smell.
The oil burning.
So, you're feeling confident
about this weekend?
Yeah, no, I think so.
Yeah, no. Go... Yeah.
We're gonna destroy, right?
Good.
No, it's just, I...
I just haven't seen Ted since I left and...
We didn't leave on the best of terms and...
I feel like I owe him
an apology or something.
You did what was best for you.
What were you meant to do?
Hang around,
supporting Ted for the rest of your life?
I don't think so.
You've done nothing wrong, Nathan,
I promise you.
You earned this job.
Well, so what do I say when I see him?
You say nothing, apart from "hello."
You look him in the eye.
You shake his hand.
And then you beat him.
And then we go and celebrate.
Okay.
Good night, Nathan.
Good night, Rupert. Thank you.
Mr. Mannion.
Hey.
Working late? Or hardly working?
Well, I don't think
that's how the joke goes.
What joke?
Never mind. What's up?
I really want to win this one.
I know.
Everything okay?
Am I a mess?
Of course you are.
That's why we get along.
And I wish I could tell you
to ignore Sass, but she's usually right.
So, Sassy already told you
about the... Of course. Girl talk.
Girl talk.
So, is everything all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
Oklahoma?
I'm a work in "progmess."
Good night, Ted.
You already won, you know?
You got that turkey out of your life.
Beat them.
Good night, boss.
Oi, do I look all right?
Of course you do. Why?
Well, if Jack actually shows up,
I want him to think that I look
mysterious and powerful.
Dynamic, you know?
- All of that.
- You are mysterious, powerful and dynamic.
Shit, I'm nervous.
I think I need to go
and reapply my lip liner.
- I'll see you upstairs in the suite.
- Yep.
Hey, Rebecca!
- Rupert.
- Wonderful to see you.
- Bex. Love the new hair.
- Hi.
I haven't changed my hair.
Nor should you. It's perfection.
So, how's the little one?
Oh, yeah, Diane. She's already walking.
Can you believe that?
Yeah.
Drooling and pooing around the house.
Takes after her father.
Well. Hey, take it easy on us today.
No promises.
Oh, shit.
Excuse me.
I've got a bit of a situation here.
Thank you. But it's actually not that.
You're a lifesaver!
Usually I'm like clockwork,
but because I've been so stressed,
I've come on early.
I'm so happy that it's a super
and not a skinny.
Who are those even for?
It's not like my vagina is on a diet,
I'm on my fucking period.
Oi, thanks for helping me.
And I love your shoes!
- Yeah. Thanks. Pay it forward.
- Yeah.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Hi.
Boy, you're tall.
Is your dad a tree or something?
No, I'm screwing around.
Hey, speaking of trees,
who are y'all rooting for today?
West Ham.
Yeah, no, that makes sense. Yeah.
Go ahead. Yeah. Going down one more floor.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, of course.
Best of luck out there.
Hey, Nate. That you?
Hi. I didn't see you there.
- That's okay. How you been, man?
- Yeah, okay.
Yeah. Good.
Listen, Ted.
I just wanna say that the way I left...
Nathan. There you are.
Yeah.
Hey, Rupert.
- Ted.
- Nice to see you again.
Good luck.
- Keeley? Yeah.
- She's absolutely fantastic.
Here she is now.
- Hey. Yeah.
- Keeley? This is Jack Danvers.
Hello.
I believe you have something of mine.
Oh, fuck. You're Jack?
This is a bit embarrassing.
- No.
- Yeah. We all thought you were a man.
Yeah, that too.
It's like that old riddle.
- What riddle?
- You know, always a tricky one, this one.
A father and son are in a car wreck.
Dad dies instantly, the son is rushed
to an emergency room.
A surgeon walks in and says,
"I can't operate on this boy.
He's my son."
How is it possible?
- Because she's a woman.
- She's gay.
- Sperm donor.
- He lives in a simulation?
Right.
Yeah, I guess that's a bit dated now.
So, I assume "Jack" is short
for "Jacqueline," right?
No. It's short for my father wanted a boy.
I'm gonna go and sit
down now, outside. Now.
Jack, welcome.
We are not allowed to take drinks
to our seats.
So if you want to get plastered,
we should probably do that now.
Okay.
Well, after you.
You're so funny, Rebecca.
Barbara's obsessed with Rebecca.
I hope she doesn't try and kill her
and wear her skin as a suit.
What the fuck?
Cheers. It's gonna be a good day.
- All right, Baz.
- Oi!
This is a Richmond pub.
It's all right, Mae. He's with me.
Get the fuck out!
Come on, Richmond!
Come on, Richmond! Come on, Richmond!
It's a full house for today's battle
between West Ham United
and Zava's AFC Richmond.
A win would take either team
to the top spot in the table,
knocking mighty Manchester City
off number one.
Should be a tight match, Chris.
Any predictions?
I stopped making predictions, Arlo.
Because I was never wrong.
Got to the point I was worried
I was the one making things happen.
Well, that's interesting.
I knew you'd say that.
They fade and die
Fortune's always hiding
I've looked everywhere
I'm forever blowing bubbles
Pretty bubbles in the air
United! United!
Nate.
Let's have fun out there today, yeah?
West Ham are quite happy
to just soak up the pressure.
Not taking any risks at all
against Richmond,
of all teams, at home.
- A sign of how far Richmond have come.
- It's all right. We're okay.
What a threat Zava is.
Richmond! To the right!
Tight! Don't get scared.
And it stays nil-nil,
thanks to an amazing save by Zoreaux.
- Van Damme.
- Van Damme!
I hear he wants
to be called "Van Damme" now.
Why?
Well, we'd probably have to dive
into his childhood for that answer.
Richmond need the key pass
to unlock the Hammers' defense.
That could be the one.
- Tartt hits the woodwork.
- No!
- That was close.
- Zava was wide open.
For Zava!
- There'll be two more minutes in the first half of this scoreless,
But pulsating, London derby.
- Obisanya caught in possession.
- No.
And here come West Ham on the break.
Armando bearing down on goal.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
And it's there. Right under Van Damme.
The Canadian keeper apparently
not as unstoppable
as the Muscles from Brussels.
That's not fair, Arlo. Nobody is.
- We've been here before. Come on.
- Come on, lads.
The Hammers go up 1-nil
just before halftime.
Fuck it.
All right, guys. Come on, now.
Let's end this half strong!
Huddle.
What's this shit?
I don't know.
- Lower. Move it right. Five.
- Brilliant.
- Right now, come on. Five.
- Ref, just blow the fucking whistle.
West Ham pressing now.
- No.
- A new tactic from the Hammers
in the closing seconds of the first half.
In the closing seconds of the first half.
It's never too late to change, Arlo.
- No!
- Fuck! Fuck you! Fuck!
And it's 2-nil. Oh, deary me.
Excuse me.
How did that happen?
We go to halftime.
Richmond have dominated possession,
but out of absolutely nowhere,
it's 2-nil to the Hammers.
We don't deserve that.
What the fuck just happened?
I don't know.
Hey, fellas. I'll be right back. Okay?
The fuck are you going?
- I'll just be a minute or two, okay?
- What do we tell the team?
I don't know. Surprise me.
Hey, boss. What you doing down here?
I just wanted to tell you
that I believe in you, Ted.
Uh-huh?
And I know that I've been
putting an awful lot of pressure on you
to win today, but I just want you
to forget all about that.
Just be yourself and have fun.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay. Well, thank you.
I believe in you, Ted.
And it's intense.
- I better go. All right.
- Off you pop.
Remember, have fun!
Yes! This is so exciting!
No.
This is your surprise, huh?
A minute ago, they were catatonic.
Now look at them.
- They're killers. - Frankly, Ted, sometimes that's good.
Oh, my. Richmond coming out of the tunnel
with a palpable chip on their shoulder.
Wow. A real tension on the pitch.
I think we're in for an exciting half.
We begin the second half
with Richmond looking for a strong start.
- Come on, boys. Fucking kill 'em.
- Fucking kill 'em.
- Here we go!
- Kill!
That's an awful tackle.
- He would be fortunate to escape...
- Oh, fuck.
With just a yellow.
It's a deserved red, and Richmond
will play almost the entire second half
with ten men.
He's actually a very sweet young man.
Here come West Ham.
- And now Van Damme has been sent off.
- We're playing like Italians.
- I know.
It's awesome.
Oh, dear.
It's getting a touch spicy out there.
Spicy, Arlo? This is vintage vindaloo.
No.
Montlaur has lost his mind,
and Richmond have lost a third player.
Fucking come on.
- Richmond have completely lost the plot.
Zava must be wondering
what he's done to deserve this.
Yes!
And it's 4-1 to the Hammers.
It went from evenly matched
to unevenly matched
to light a match on fire
and put it into a can of petrol.
That second half should've come
with a trigger warning.
One extraordinary goal by Zava
did not make it any less tough to watch.
Richmond showed a side of themselves
we've never seen before.
They played angry, dirty and ugly.
Which are also the names
of Zava's three youngest kids.
Shit.
- Hey, it's okay.
- Shit.
Did you guys have fun?
Yeah.
The violence was quite entertaining,
wasn't it? In a way.
Sending off Van Damme was a mistake.
He played with passion.
"Passion" is a word we use
when we talk about love.
It is also a word we use
to describe a crime.
Sometimes it is also a fruit.
Oh, gosh. I'm so sorry.
- We fucked up.
- We overcorrected and played with hate.
- Be great if you yelled at us a bit.
- Please.
- Call us pieces of shit or something. - Now.
You can hit us.
Get it over with.
Tried something new. It didn't work.
Big whoop.
I will take that thumb drive
one of y'all's got.
Shake it off, fellas.
Lot of football left this season.
- What a fucking arsehole.
- I know.
You have to feel pretty good
about yourself after that win, yeah?
Well, yeah. Richmond were clearly rattled.
It was easier than I expected,
if I'm honest.
What about Ted?
Quite a snub not to shake his hand
at the end of the game.
Did I not? I didn't mean to.
I... Guess I just got caught up
in the excitement of it all. Yeah.
Excuse me a minute. I just...
Coach Shelley,
Mr. Mannion asked me to give you this.
He'll meet you there in an hour.
Thank...
- It's so good to see you, Rebecca.
- You too, Bex.
Oh, Rebecca, my dear.
- So sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
Come on, old man.
It's way past your bedtime.
Lovely to see you.
I saw you with your assistant.
Your daughter deserves better,
and so does Bex.
- Stop fucking around.
Here you go.
We are normally a lot better than that.
And nicer.
Well, it's never great when your team
gets more red cards than goals, is it?
No.
What a shit show.
Anyway, good news. Bantr's trending.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Pretty sure
the change to the bio line helped.
What are you talking about?
Who did this?
I did. This afternoon,
when I uploaded the vids.
You're welcome.
- Shandy.
- Yeah.
This is the opposite
of what Bantr is trying to do.
Are you joking? They're gonna love it.
I've literally tripled their subscribers
in an hour.
You need to change this back, now. Please.
Yeah.
It was really lovely to meet you.
- You too.
- Excuse me.
Hey. Here he is!
The Wonder Kid himself.
The man of the hour!
Thank you very much, Mr. Mannion.
Please, no. "Rupert."
Nathan.
Thanks, Ms. Kakes. That's...
And Nathan,
allow me to introduce Anastasia.
Huge fan.
Oh, my God. You're famous.
So are you.
Congratulations to your victory.
Yeah. Thank you.
Come on, Tartt! One more before dinner!
Let's go, Coach.
That was hard to watch.
Thierry, West Ham's domination today
saw Ted Lasso being totally exposed
by his former assistant Nate Shelley.
Gary, I love this quote
from a Chinese philosopher, Laozi,
"When the student is ready,
the teacher will appear.
When the student is truly ready,
the teacher will disappear."
The Greyhounds...
- Hi, Ted.
- Hey.
Sorry about the match.
No. That's all right. It was a tough one.
Henry's not here right now.
He's at a birthday party,
- but I'll...
- No, that's okay.
I was actually hoping just
to chat with you. You got a minute?
Sure. Is everything okay?
Yeah. Well... No. You know, I just...
I wanted to say something real quick.
Look, I...
I know that you and I aren't, you know,
together anymore.
And I respect that. Okay? I do.
But, Well, you know,
this whole thing with you and Dr. Jacob
really ticks me off.
And I'm upset that we didn't ever really
get to talk about it
before it all started.
Yeah.
And look,
I understand that me saying all this,
might be the wrong thing to do, but...
I just feel like not saying it...
isn't the...
Well, wouldn't be the right thing either.
'Cause we gotta raise
this little boy together, you know?
We're stuck with each other.
We're gonna share grandkids.
I love you, Michelle.
And I love Henry.
- And I love our family.
No matter what it looks like.
Okay?
Of course.
Well, I'll talk to y'all soon.
Have a good night. Tell Henry I love him.
Good night, Ted.