I had no idea.
I didn't know being pregnant
would be so tough.
So difficult.
As a man, I'd never even imagined
how it would change the rhythm of my life.
Congratulations!
Unexpected things happen in life.
When you're faced with that moment,
what would you do?
EPISODE 1
The best life hacks?
Prediction and preparation.
Here's your change and receipt.
Good morning, Mr. Hiyama.
-Morning. Drip coffee, please.
-Sure.
Take women, for example.
One drip coffee!
Hey, I had fun the other day.
-You'll ask me out again, right?
-Of course.
As long as…
Let me pay.
Yes, sorry.
…you don't drop the ball,
things will go as you intend.
Same with work.
It all comes down
to prediction and preparation.
-Morning!
-Morning.
There is nothing difficult about it.
She looks fantastic.
We really found a great girl for it.
Yeah, you said it.
It's surprisingly hard
to find an athlete like her.
We could even make a photo book.
-True!
-Good idea.
We'll take this to the client
for final checks.
-Perfect, Hiyama.
-Thank you.
-This will get attention.
-Right.
I mean, the girl's got big tits
and a great body.
-Hiyama, you filthy sod.
-That wasn't my intention.
You'll get in trouble
talking like that nowadays, Tanabe.
I'd never say it in public.
Frankly, what's important is results.
-That's right.
-I guess.
Men are attracted
to female athletes' bodies.
It's just a fact.
-Right?
-That's just you.
Speak for yourself.
Yeah, don't speak for all of us.
Give me a break, boss.
Tanabe, look at Miss Koga.
She's not laughing at all.
Oh, poor Koga.
Don't report me, okay?
I may have to disappoint you.
-Yikes!
-Report him.
Be honest. You'd be drawn to an ad
with a hot naked guy, too.
You're just digging yourself deeper.
-See, this is what I mean.
-Report him.
Alright, let's go ahead with this one.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Thanks, everyone.
All right.
-Hiyama.
-Yes?
-Tanabe.
Sawabe, you too.
You free for dinner tonight?
I'd like to discuss plans
for something else.
Is it about UNIVE?
Yes, and the in-house contest as well.
Try to make some time tonight.
-Understood.
-Right, thanks.
Thank you.
NATSUMI: SORRY FOR TALKING TO YOU
THIS MORNING!
I'M JUST WORRIED ABOUT
WHETHER YOU'RE THINKING OF ME.
AKI: THANKS
IT'LL BE LATE, BUT CAN I SEE YOU TONIGHT?
The client is chomping at the bit
for new branding.
Whether we win this deal or not
will make a difference.
You're right.
We can't lose,
for the sake of the whole company.
Exactly.
UNIVE is Japan's leading apparel company.
We need to power through,
whatever it takes.
Boss, excuse me.
I'm actually on child duty today
so I need to leave soon.
Oh, you do?
Forgive me. I appreciate the invitation.
What the hell?
The boss is giving us an opportunity.
It's fine.
Mr. Osugi isn't a man
who sweats over small matters.
Yeah, get home to your kid.
Yes, and please invite me again.
Thank you for tonight.
-See you.
-Good night.
-Night.
-Take care.
-Thanks, good night.
What a great dad!
Can you believe that?
Don't say that. Raising kids is tough.
Men shouldn't be
responsible for childcare.
It's just a matter of
controlling the household, right?
A front-line fighter
needs to get in the ring!
Come on, everyone's different.
Boss, let's get back to business.
Right, that's what's important.
Naturally, one of you two
will take the lead
at our next presentation meeting.
Make it work. I'm counting on you.
-Leave it to us.
-Yes.
-Thanks for tonight.
-Good night.
You're a crafty one, Hiyama.
What do you mean?
You play it cool,
but you're totally aiming for the top.
You know exactly how to handle our boss.
It's only natural.
I won't let you win this time.
It's time for you to step aside.
Okay, good night.
AKI: YEAH, FINE.
HIYAMA: I'M ON MY WAY NOW.
MOM: IT'S NEARLY YOUR BIRTHDAY!
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
STAY HEALTHY.
ALL I WANT NOW IS A GRANDKID!
Please, have a seat.
That's very kind, thanks.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sorry.
BABY ON BOARD
Been a while.
When you show up,
you're always late.
Sorry. I just got off work.
Get in here.
Thank you kindly.
You're so self-centered.
I'm in the middle of something.
Look, I'm sorry.
I wanted to ask you something about work.
-Work?
-Yeah.
Alright.
-Here.
-Thanks.
NATSUMI: WHY WON'T YOU REPLY?
Jeez, so needy.
ARE YOU AWAKE?
Why do younger girls
need everything spelled out?
Don't they get it?
-What's that?
-Nothing.
I prefer grown-up women, after all.
-Like you, Aki.
-What are you on about?
Come on.
It's true.
We're a good match, no?
How?
You know.
We're good together.
Ah, okay.
We're not bad.
Right? Come here.
-We're good at kissing.
-Not just kissing.
Here.
-What are you doing?
-I win!
Alright.
Bedtime for me, too.
What was that
about being good together?
-Good together?
-Not just kissing, right?
Something like this.
Like this, right?
Currently, around 40 cases
are reported annually in Japan
of cisgender male pregnancies.
At our hospital,
around one case is reported per month.
The first male pregnancy
was reported in the United States
around 50 years ago.
ALEX POWELL: WORLD'S FIRST
REPORTED PREGNANT MAN
His pregnancy made headlines
because he was not transgender.
Shortly thereafter,
across the globe,
reports of male pregnancy…
I can't even imagine it.
What?
A pregnant man.
Creeps me out a bit, to be honest.
But there's no one like that around you.
-Have you ever met someone like that?
-Never.
Anyway, having kids is pretty bold.
Doesn't matter if it's a man or a woman,
it just gets in the way of work.
I wonder…
-You writing something?
-Yeah.
I've got two deadlines
by tomorrow morning.
You're such an in-demand writer.
I'm just convenient for them.
It's pointless
unless I get commissioned by name.
I wish the youngsters
at my work could hear you.
There was a guy today
who went home early to look after his kid.
Sounds like a good thing
to be called a "doting father,"
but actually it means
he can't do important work.
Yeah.
I'm not averse to having children myself,
but I couldn't do my job well
while raising a kid.
Are you okay?
Maybe I drank too much.
Mind if I take a nap?
Go ahead. I'm still writing.
Sorry.
That's the gist of my plan.
Thank you for listening.
Thank you.
-Good job.
-Thanks.
-You're up.
Allow us to present our next proposal.
-Go on, Hiyama.
-Yes.
-Hello, everyone.
-Hello.
"Your own fashion."
My first thought about this
was what "your own" self means.
Although it previously seemed
too socially loaded,
this concept of "your own" self
is being reimagined across the globe
and we're entering an era
that celebrates individual diversity.
What's important going forward
is displaying our identities.
I see. Interesting idea.
But the risk of a flame war
is immeasurable.
Being bold is fine, but we'll be
the ones taking responsibility.
Yes, and to address that issue,
the project will set up funds
to support people of diverse identities,
at the same time demonstrating
how progressive the brand is.
This is a leading company,
which is exactly why
it should rally behind the slogan,
"Pride for All People."
These people are not just spectacles.
It's about living "your own" life.
There are no boundaries to that.
Let's go ahead with refining this one.
It seems like an exciting plan.
Thank you.
Does everyone have a drink?
Everyone ready?
Let's raise a toast
to celebrate Hiyama being selected
as Creative of the Year!
Cheers, everyone!
-Thank you.
-There's no stopping you!
I've still got a long way to go.
I just can't stand it.
He walked off with another deal today.
Poor Tanabe,
having to look up to Hiyama!
-He's a pain in the butt.
-Watch what you're saying!
-My little junior.
-Mayumi.
Don't you regret letting him go?
A little bit.
I never thought he'd be this successful.
You mean you didn't think I had talent?
That's not what I meant.
Okay, how about we get back together?
So calculating!
What will it be?
-Is it a yes?
-Absolutely not.
Oh?
Say what?
Could it be…
Is it?
It's a surprise cake!
Yeah, come on!
Give it up!
Yeah, Hiyama!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY HIYAMA
Congrats!
You can do it!
Alright, eat up.
Is it good?
You're not coming home again tonight?
Sorry, baby. It's work.
Look at this.
NATIONAL ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
ESSAY CONTEST
What's this?
I won an award at school
and got published in a newspaper.
Wow!
Make sure you find a proper job, okay?
Okay.
What a good kid.
Alright. Mom's gotta go.
-Kentaro?
-Huh?
-Are you listening?
-What?
Come on!
We want to go on a trip together
to celebrate.
A trip? Great idea.
-How about glamping?
-Nice.
Yay!
Would you like to join?
-Can I?
-Of course.
-Right?
-Yeah, come along!
-Really?
-Please.
Okay, I'll keep my schedule open.
It's decided.
Wow.
-I'm going to the bathroom.
-Sure.
-I've never been glamping before.
-Seriously?
-Leaving already, Aki?
-Yeah.
I need to write when I get home.
Stay for another drink.
There are people I want you to meet.
No, I'm okay.
Everyone's so fired up tonight.
It's a bit much for me.
You're already here. Just a bit longer.
I'm good, really.
Congrats on the award.
See you.
-Good night.
-Same to you.
-Hello.
-Kentaro?
Happy birthday.
Thanks, Ma.
You're already 37 now.
I'm so happy you're in good health.
How's work?
Same as before?
-Good night.
-Oh, night.
Look, Ma.
I'm earning a proper wage now.
You can quit driving taxis.
I'll send any money you need.
What are you talking about?
No way. I won't be a burden to my son.
Why not?
Well, you never know what might happen.
Anyway, you're doing so well now.
I don't want to hold you back.
What about my pride?
Don't waste your life
worrying about what other people think.
Look, I do it because I enjoy it.
Sorry, Ma. I've still got work to do.
You do? Okay, I'll let you go.
Happy birthday again.
Thanks. Good night.
Good night.
As you can see on the schedule,
we need to hurry and choose models
based on the key visuals
we showed UNIVE the other day.
Let me discuss the ideas
and backgrounds for the models later.
This is sensitive material,
so let's proceed carefully.
Okay.
Next, uh…
The event…
-Hiyama?
-Are you okay?
-Our campaign…
-How about some water?
Are you alright?
Hiyama?
-Sorry.
-You're sweating like mad.
-I'm sorry.
-Hiyama?
Excuse me.
Hiyama?
What's going on?
Mr. Hiyama, right?
We need to examine you further.
Could you read this and fill in the form?
I just filled in a medical sheet.
Yes, but we need you
to provide this separately.
-Separately?
-Yes.
Thanks for understanding.
This is quite far.
-We're almost there.
-Okay.
Please go in.
Thanks.
It's the room on the far right.
Here we go.
I'll cover your belly, too.
Um, so…
Please wait until the doctor comes.
He's ready, Doctor.
Huh?
Let me take a look at your stomach.
This will feel a little cool.
This thing checks for cancer, right?
Wait. Am I…
Yes. No doubt about it.
-What?
-Nine or ten weeks.
"Nine"?
Mr. Hiyama, please take a look.
It's actually almost two centimeters big.
This is the baby.
Baby?
What?
Please stay calm and listen.
Mr. Hiyama, you are pregnant.
Pregnant?
Me?
I get it. When men say "pregnant,"
it usually means someone else.
-What?
-Take your time to process it.
Hold on. No way. Me, pregnant?
-Mr. Hiyama, let me explain some details.
-"Pregnant"?
No, there's no need.
It's some kind of mistake.
-Mr. Hiyama.
-It's fine. Thank you.
-Mr. Hiyama!
-Excuse me.
PHARMACY
-No way!
-I know, right?
Yeah, it's wild.
-Hey…
-What?
Wait, isn't that…
Why does he have that?
-That's crazy.
-Don't stare!
FASTCHECK PREGNANCY TEST
Positive?
You're kidding me!
RESULT
-Yes?
-Hiyama, you finally picked up.
I told you to call
as soon as you left the hospital.
I'm sorry.
Now that UNIVE has accepted the plan,
there's no one who can replace you.
I'm fine.
You're fine health-wise?
Yes, I'm fine.
But you're panting. Are you okay?
No, I'm not panting.
-I'm totally fine.
-You're panting.
I'm telling you, I'm fine.
KENTARO HIYAMA
DUE IN 212 DAYS
I got pregnant.
Abortion consent form?
Hiyama.
I remember that time too.
I agree about not having the baby.
It's me who has to bear the risk.
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan