I think we need models
with a younger fan base,
like influencers maybe.
Yeah, that would be more relatable.
But if we're aiming for a global audience,
we should show diversity on a wider scale
instead of limiting ourselves to Japan.
Are you hungover?
You need a shave, man.
I did shave.
This isn't like you.
Last time, there were comments
about the female models being too samey.
Right. So I have an idea.
Take a look at this.
What is it?
When women breastfeed in public,
they cover up with a cape like this.
There's a sense of shame.
But overseas,
more people are saying
it's fine to do it openly.
But fashion and openly breastfeeding
are completely different concepts.
Breastfeeding out in the open
might not fly in Japan…
It has nothing to do with fashion.
What do you think, Hiyama?
What? Well…
It is eye-catching.
What happened to your shirt?
-Just a sec.
-Huh?
Sorry, sorry!
What the hell?
What?
HOW BREAST MILK WORKS
"Let-down reflex"?
"Stimuli such as
the sound of a baby crying
can lead to the secretion of oxytocin
and discharge of breast milk."
What the hell?
Gross.
EPISODE 2
Please take your time looking around.
Thank you.
Wow, so many people are here.
Congrats.
I worked myself to the bone
for a year for this.
I gave up my personal life,
so if it doesn't pay off, I'm screwed.
I hear you.
-Hello. My surname is Seto.
-Welcome.
Let me take that.
Take your time.
Smells great.
Eri?
Aki, you're here!
Is this your baby?
This is Waka.
My doppelgänger, right? It's uncanny.
-She's almost one year old.
-One?
I remember you used to say
you didn't want kids.
What?
You said even if you became
editor-in-chief,
you'd never have a kid
and go on maternity.
I guess I used to say that, huh?
But when I was approaching 40,
I thought it might be
my last chance to have a kid.
I knew I had to take the plunge
and do something new.
Eri?
-Do you have a minute?
-Oh, sorry.
Let's talk properly later.
Hey. Let's get drinks when this is over.
-What?
-I'm craving shochu and stingray fins.
You're on.
We wanted to create a system together
to address the causes of our fatigue.
VisuallyWorks is the result of that.
Right?
How great would it be
to have a platform
that analyzes and visualizes databases
in a clear fashion?
You're tired, in pain, worn out,
can't be bothered.
Take those negative feelings…
So, about the article…
-Could you finish it this week?
-What?
-You mean in three days?
-Yes.
I thought we had agreed on a week.
I'm juggling other work too.
It's too soon.
But you have three days to do it.
You told us we'd have an article out
before the launch.
That was before
the interviews got delayed.
If you can't do it,
we'll get someone else.
Can we make a clear decision on that?
Fine, I get it.
Thank you.
-Bye.
-See you.
So, you're not going ahead this time?
That's right.
I'd like an abortion as soon as possible.
When could we do it?
We'll do some checks before the procedure
so the earliest would be next Thursday.
Next Thursday…
Yes, let's do it.
-I'll book you in.
-Great.
This contains warnings and details
about what to bring to the clinic.
-Please read it thoroughly at home.
-Okay.
Please also fill this in
and bring it along
to the pre-examination.
"Abortion consent form"?
The other party needs to sign here.
The "other party"?
What if…
I don't know who they are?
If you don't know who it is…
Well, you're now ten weeks pregnant,
so it's probably someone
you were with around this period.
AKI
…You're tired, in pain,
worn out, can't be bothered.
Take those negative feelings
and share them with us…
Ms. Seto?
Ms. Aki Seto?
-Please come into the consultation room.
-Yes.
-Apologies.
-Thanks for waiting.
If your periods are really that tough,
maybe you could try going on the pill.
Okay.
I get such bad cramps.
Sometimes I can't even stand up.
It stops me from working.
I'll prescribe you a month's worth.
Give it a try.
Get in touch immediately
if it doesn't feel right.
There are loads of types,
so you can try out different ones.
It'll make your periods much easier.
It will?
Also, not to rush into things,
but surgery is another option.
Uterine fibroids can still grow back
even if they're removed,
so it's not a sure bet.
I'm not sure about surgery…
I'd have to be hospitalized
for about a week, right?
-Yes.
-I can't take that much time off work.
But if it gets worse,
it could make you infertile.
So if you think
you might want children later…
Could I have the pills for now?
I don't even have time to go to hospital
so having a kid just isn't realistic.
I don't have a partner, anyway.
Okay. Well, here's the prescription.
Right.
KENTARO HIYAMA: YOU FREE TONIGHT?
Not a chance.
ABORTION CONSENT FORM
AKI: CAN'T. I'M BUSY.
DEALING WITH MORNING SICKNESS
PRE-MAMA LAND HOMEPAGE
What's with this lame design?
"The cause of morning sickness is unclear.
No specific medical cure exists."
Seriously?
This is a joke.
Hello, Itofuji here.
Today we'll be doing
our popular Q&A segment.
Welcome to Mama Q!
We received
a lot of questions on our last video.
Here's one of them.
"Does pregnancy make nipples darker?"
Darker nipples?
People say so, don't they? Is it true?
Well,
pregnancy increases hormonal activity
causing body hair to thicken…
Hiyama.
Are you free today?
-Yes.
-Right.
See you later then.
Yes.
What's going on lately? You're slipping.
I've taken a bit of a hit
to my health. I'm sorry.
Maintaining your health
is part of your job too.
Find a wife and have her look after you.
Yes.
Without a wife at home
looking after things,
a man can't go out
and do proper work, can he?
Right, boss.
Look, here's what I want to say.
I put you in charge, not Tanabe.
Don't embarrass me.
I'm heading out.
Huh? What is it?
Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
You can't just turn up whenever!
I've got a deadline today, you know.
I'm not your girlfriend, Kentaro.
I feel awful.
You okay?
You feel ill?
I might have something
to settle your stomach…
I'm pregnant.
What? Who's pregnant?
I'm pregnant!
Me!
What?
What do you mean?
You mean, a cisgender male pregnancy?
Yep.
I thought I'd let you know.
Hold on.
Is it my kid? You see other girls, surely.
Based on the number of weeks,
I'm sure it's yours.
What should we do?
I'm not keeping it.
Oh, right.
Of course.
Write your name here.
"Abortion…"
Once this is filled in,
they book the procedure--
Oh, boy. Are you okay?
-Wait, oh!
-Ouch!
Take this.
Hold on. Stay there.
Let's get a towel…
You need a drink? Water?
Yeah, water…
Water. Don't you want it hot?
-Hot.
-Hot water, right.
-Any more?
-Uh…
-Isn't that crazy?
-Shh!
-Quiet!
-See you.
-Come here.
-Oh!
Don't tell anyone!
So some men really can get pregnant!
Keep it down.
Please, you can't tell anyone.
You always hear about it
on the news, right?
-Yeah, but I've never met one.
-Right.
Even if a man's belly sticks out,
I'd never think he could be pregnant.
Right.
Most of them have abortions, too.
-They do?
-Yeah.
When he told me he was pregnant,
I unintentionally asked
if it's really mine.
It's usually the man asking that.
But you know,
it's a pretty great time to be alive
where cisgender men can give birth.
-What?
-No?
I mean, being pregnant is tough.
Nausea and headaches for months.
People nagging you constantly
until it's born,
like, "Don't eat this,
move that, go for a walk."
You can't drink or eat raw stuff.
And to top it all off,
the hellish pain of labor
is waiting for you at the end.
If a man did all that for me,
I'd be over the moon.
Hey.
I know you're not interested in marriage.
But what about kids?
Don't you want him to have the baby?
What? I've never thought about it.
Okay, well.
Maybe think about it before deciding.
Because no matter who gives birth,
pregnancy is a freaking miracle.
Sorry I'm late.
No, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I was in such a state.
It's not your fault. You're pregnant.
Hello, here's some water.
-I'll bring a menu.
-Thanks.
I'll be right back.
All I can eat right now is sweet stuff.
I've lost two kilos this week.
Oh, yeah.
I got a new copy.
Go ahead.
ABORTION CONSENT FORM
Here.
But, you know…
think about this situation.
It's really a blessing.
For people who want kids, sure.
No, I mean for a man to get pregnant.
If you were willing to give birth,
I could have a kid
without having to give birth myself.
Plus, you're an ad man.
Being a pregnant man
could work to your advantage
and lead to new job opportunities.
When I think of it like that,
I start thinking that perhaps
this is actually a huge stroke of luck.
Look, Aki.
I'm actually pregnant.
-I get it.
-You don't.
I feel queasy all day.
My boss is watching me.
It's already destroying my life.
Don't joke with me.
Sorry.
I agree that we won't have the baby.
It's not just about agreeing.
Don't make it sound so easy.
I have to harm my body for an abortion.
Sure, but still.
You sound just like one of those guys.
Men who get girls pregnant
then say, "Oh, I understand,"
and sign the form
like it's none of their business.
But I'm the one who bears the risk
whether it's childbirth or an abortion.
Hurry up and sign it.
Yes.
Stamp it, too.
-Hello there.
-Hey.
We've got a UNIVE meeting at 3:00 p.m.
Is room A3 free?
The monitors are hard to see
in the usual room.
The meeting's already started.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
See you.
Sorry, I forgot to check
for any schedule changes.
It's fine. You're not feeling well.
-It was short notice.
-I'm sorry.
Given the circumstances,
I'd like to hand this project over
to Tanabe to manage.
What? But this plan was my idea.
The plan is a team effort.
You shouldn't have to
keep shouldering it all for the company.
-No, but--
-Hiyama.
Accept help when you're having trouble.
I'll work to the best of my abilities.
Wait, how do we tell the client?
This is a joint decision.
You turn up at the office poorly dressed.
Your mind's elsewhere,
you can't communicate properly.
I mean, where were you today?
We couldn't get a hold of you.
Seeing you like this lately,
we decided it would be best for the team.
Alright?
-Take care of it, Tanabe.
-Yes.
Right. Please tidy things up here.
Then read the minutes
and prepare the necessary materials
for next time.
Koga, you can leave.
KENTARO HIYAMA
DUE IN 206 DAYS
Dropped down the ranks, huh?
I'd like to do the procedure ASAP.
Are you pregnant?
-Boobs.
-I know!
It's not as easy as you think.
What do you think, Mr. Hiyama?
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan