Didn't your dad die?
That's what I thought.
Apparently he died right after I was born.
Is it okay for him to be in your home?
He knew my mom's name.
She's on her way here now.
Alright.
-She's here.
-Yeah.
Hey, where's that girl?
Sweetie, you there?
-Yes?
-Got any chopsticks?
He's here, right?
-Chopsticks?
-Yeah.
What for?
I've got this yakisoba sandwich…
Oh, it's Tomoko!
Long time no see.
What's with the sexy uniform?
Ouch!
You promised you'd never let him see you.
Why are you here?
You knocked out my crown!
Who cares about your teeth!
Okay?
-Mom.
-What the hell?
Calm down.
This jerk
abandoned us.
My crown's come out.
He abandoned us
when you were newborn.
He left!
-Because of that--
-My crown!
Shut up about your teeth!
You caused us so much pain!
Mom!
-Calm down.
-How can I be calm?
I said, my crown's come out!
Screw your crown!
EPISODE 6
Here's a change of clothes.
Cheers, pal.
Feel free to use the washing machine.
You'll wash my clothes for me?
So kind, thanks.
FEBRUARY 9, 1984
KENTARO
Man,
your mom sure was pissed.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
How many weeks now?
I've just entered my 21st week.
Oh, yes.
It gets stressful
because you can't sleep on your front.
-Your pee starts leaking too.
-Yes.
Still,
she's got energy.
To think, she used to complain
about back pain…
So…
was I really born from you?
Yep, that's right.
I know it's a bit rich saying this
after causing you so much trouble,
but I've been wanting
to meet you for so long.
Yeah.
I've left you a toothbrush and razor here,
-so feel free to use them.
-Cheers.
I'm so sorry you had to witness that
on our first meeting.
It's okay.
TOMOKO HIYAMA
CONDOR TAXIS
TO A HEALTHY BIRTH
Have you done this job for long?
For about 20 years.
My memory's vague
because I’ve done all sorts of things
since I moved here with Kentaro
after that man left us.
It's a pity, huh?
No, I…
I think it's incredible
that you raised him
by yourself like this.
You're incredible.
What?
When I got pregnant,
I kept myself out of sight.
But now,
we live in a world like this.
What about clinic visits?
I got ferried about
from one clinic to the next.
Some thought I might really be a woman.
All these big-shot doctors gathered around
and stroked my belly.
It was so humiliating.
People are somewhat more considerate now.
You can share info with others
via the online platform, too.
What's that?
It's a website on the internet.
This is it.
I created a space for pregnant men
to interact with each other.
MATERNITY SALON FOR MEN GIVING BIRTH
People post information on here.
-Wow.
-Yes.
-Very useful.
-Yeah.
You and I are similar after all.
I was also always thinking
about how pregnant men could be happy.
How they could keep their manhood
despite being pregnant.
Suits that hide your belly, for instance.
I thought it'd be so useful
to have a members-only maternity clinic.
I came up with all sorts.
I see.
But you know, Kentaro…
you must be pretty brave…
to have come this far.
I understand. I'm your dad.
Dad…
Yep.
Must've been tough all alone.
Well done.
Dad.
Now, now.
It's okay.
Here, what's wrong?
It's alright.
Alright! I've decided.
Here's what we'll do.
-Let's join forces.
-What?
See, I'm working on a project now.
Let's make it happen together.
With two pro pregnant daddies,
it'll be a sure success.
No doubt.
Alright!
No time to waste.
For the time being…
-let's live here together, okay?
-What?
If you're not eating, I'll have it.
No, I'm almost done.
You're always so pressured.
-Why don't you relax a bit?
-No way.
It's not easy to make a living
in this line of work.
-Right, sent it.
-Woo!
Nice one.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-No worries.
Hey.
Can you really raise a kid like this?
What?
In my case,
I live like this because I enjoy my work
and I've not had kids yet.
But in your case,
isn't it time you rethink
the way you handle work?
I forgot.
What now?
Kentaro's dad is supposed to be dead,
but he suddenly appeared yesterday.
-In a dream?
-No.
-No, I'll explain next time.
-Oh?
I've been asked to look after him
until Kentaro gets home today.
I can't finish this. Eat it if you like.
Sounds like a blast!
-Please wait a while.
-Sure.
Please stay positive.
Okay.
If your condition changes, let us know.
Right.
Well, take care.
-Thanks for your help.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
I don't want to be friends with someone
who only likes people who make them tea.
If that's your attitude, I'm out too!
What happened?
Listen, I asked this girl here--
Can you stop calling me "girl"?
I asked this fair lady here,
"Would you be so kind
as to serve me a cup of tea?"
That's all.
That's a lie.
You said, "Girl, tea!"
"Such fine green tea
must be cooled to 60 degrees."
So I said,
"This isn't a free hostess bar."
No, you said,
"If you want some tea
the vending machine downstairs
will be quicker."
Who says that?
But it would be quicker.
This woman will say
such cold-hearted things
to a harmless old man like me!
-"This woman"?
-Okay, stop it already.
If you want tea, I'll make some.
Honestly.
Look now!
Now, now.
-What?
-Look at this.
I spent today making a business plan.
What do you think?
"Maternity products for men"?
Sure, but a lot of companies
are already developing products.
"Underwear so you don't need
incontinence pads"?
Yes, it's underwear
made from absorbent material.
Wear a pair of them, and you don't need
one of those incontinence diaper pads.
True, it is annoying,
changing pads all the time at work.
-And I worry about people noticing.
-Yeah.
There's a lot of hype
around women's underwear
that removes the need for sanitary towels.
Maybe a male version could fly.
Right? It's a trend.
There's nothing for men. See?
-Exactly, not yet.
-Still, after all,
the most important thing
is how to promote it.
Aki, this is your area. Could you help us?
Alrighty.
Let's make our fair lady head of PR.
Glad you're on my team, son.
What?
You should start doing PR work now
for when you can't
make a living writing anymore.
-For when I can't make a living?
-I like it!
Yeah, that's right.
There are no men's sanitary undies yet.
I see.
Aki?
Aki, wait.
Wait. Aki!
I'm sorry.
Fair enough if you want
to get to know your dad,
but don't drag me into it.
Drag you into it?
I just asked for your help.
This project is my dad's dream.
I keep wondering,
why do women always have to
help men pursue their dreams?
Yet women chase their own dreams
by themselves.
It's not such a big deal as that.
Dad's just happy to have more family now.
Okay.
Who will you raise our kid with,
me or your dad?
"It's either your job or me," right?
No. I'm asking what your intentions are.
Well, my dad has a lot of time now,
so he can devote himself,
and he's experienced a lot,
-so I'm thinking of asking him.
-Right, got it.
Okay, I'll also work with that in mind.
-Wait…
-See you.
Go, Yuto!
Great! Go!
Go!
Here it is!
Alright, one more!
Mom.
See you later.
-See you.
-Bye.
Absolutely not.
You can't start a business with that man.
I've got a full-time job,
so it would just be a side hustle.
-Even so, no way.
-Really?
That man will never follow through.
He'll run away if anything happens.
That's…
Mom.
Why didn't you tell me about him?
How could I?
How could I tell you
that your father abandoned you?
Mr. Hiyama? Eiichi Hiyama?
Yes.
At the time,
pregnant men were still very rare.
So…
people would stare wherever he went.
Can you believe a man getting pregnant?
Seems like it's a real thing.
Maybe he'd just lost heart.
After giving birth to you,
he suddenly just quit his job
and did nothing but gamble.
You can stay for free in my room!
My father couldn't bear to see it,
so he had us look after
their inn back home.
Don't be such an idiot.
Have a shave too! We're serving customers.
I'm sorry.
But before long,
rumor spread that he'd been pregnant.
See you later.
Speak of the devil.
The baby's coming!
Don't be rude to the mother.
Daddy, give me a nipple too!
Stop it, that's gross.
That man and I planned to raise you well,
no matter how coldly
other people treated us.
It's pouring!
Look, it's raining.
It's your dad!
Welcome back.
Wait, where are you going?
He ended up running away.
He threw away everything.
Didn't you look for him after that?
No need to go looking.
He came to me begging for money.
I still don't think
he's such a bad person.
He's kept a photo of me
from when I was born.
That's just a con man's trick.
What?
Think of all the hardship
we've been through to get here.
You'll throw it all away for that man?
Wait, how come?
-Hello Hiyama.
-Hey.
When did you all connect?
You know this online platform?
It's very handy.
Everyone wanted to meet me
when I said I'd given birth.
He told us about when you were born.
What a trooper.
We have it so easy now compared to you.
Totally.
I was just telling everyone
about my business.
What?
This guy works at a design studio,
so he could make us some samples.
I wish we had underwear like this.
I always leak when I sneeze.
I hear you!
But I hate buying incontinence pads.
-Yeah.
-Right.
Breast milk pads, too.
Yeah.
Breast milk pads, incontinence pads…
Everything on the market is pink!
How dare they try emasculate us!
We have a right to live like men
even if we're pregnant.
Right?
-Can't argue with that.
-Alright!
Brilliant.
I'll speak with our designers tomorrow.
Let's start crowdfunding, too.
-Alright.
-Timing is crucial.
We could bring these two together.
-Yeah.
-I like it.
When's the baby being born, again?
The due date is in September.
Right.
But I'm so nervous
about whether we can do it.
With your husband?
He's not my husband.
We'd planned to raise
the kid together, that's all.
I guess I'm just not suited
to stuff like marriage.
So you're free now.
What?
Why don't you work for us in Singapore?
We're hosting an art festival next season.
We need an editor for the guidebook.
I'd like you to do it.
This looks so interesting!
-I'd love to do it.
-Nice!
I'd need to relocate, right?
Yeah, just for two years.
I know the baby's on the way,
but loads of men go away at that stage,
-for their career.
-Yeah.
Didn't you want
to build your career like this?
It's a good opportunity.
Hello?
Hello. Where are you now?
I just met with an old colleague
who offered me a job.
Really? That's great.
I'd have to go to Singapore for two years.
Singapore?
I've not answered yet.
He also knows we've got a baby on the way.
But I've not been
this excited about work in ages.
I've always wanted to do this kind of job.
Aki.
You'll say no, right?
Well, I told him I'd think about it.
If you go abroad now,
who will look after the kid?
Well…
I've got my job, too,
and this project with my dad
looks like it'll go ahead.
So I wanted you
to look after the kid for a while.
Sorry.
-I have to go, my train's here.
-Okay.
So…
Hello?
Hiyama?
It's Orita. Where are you?
What's happened?
It's bad. Come straight away.
TRENDSETTER KENTARO HIYAMA'S FATHER
SUSPECTED OF FRAUD!
HIYAMA'S DAD, THE SUSPECT,
WAS ALSO A PREGNANT MAN!
Surely not.
The father of Kentaro Hiyama,
the much-talked-about pregnant man,
is facing reports of alleged fraud.
-Crazy, right?
-Gross, pregnant men…
He was definitely gonna scam us.
We should've guessed.
Kentaro should be coming over.
Let's see what he says.
Sorry I'm late.
What is this?
I only just saw the news on my way here.
Where's Eiichi? I can't get hold of him.
He should be on his way.
-Are you part of this, too?
-Part of what?
We invested in Eiichi's project.
We put in 300,000 yen each
because you'd be the poster boy.
Can you give us an explanation, Hiyama?
-Hiyama.
-Say something.
Hiyama!
-Come on, speak.
-Hiyama…
KENTARO HIYAMA
DUE IN 54 DAYS
UNIVE wants to drop Hiyama?
The due date's approaching.
You're going off-topic, Hiyama.
You never know what might happen.
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan