You and I…
Aren't our ideas of family too different?
You're still not here?
It's fine. I think I'll make it.
The wedding day is scheduled
in ten-minute slots.
Don't mess it up.
I said I'm sorry.
This is why I told you
to stay over here last night.
No way. Spare me that, at least.
Hurry up!
-The whole family's waiting.
-I know, I know.
Why do you always cut it so close?
Your dad's all worked up
about you not being here yet.
I won't go near him so it's fine.
-Aki.
-What?
-No fights today, okay?
-Right.
Let him win, just for today.
-I got it.
-Okay.
-Aki's here, dear.
-Long time no see.
Oh.
Hello. I made it.
You're late.
Our two families are meeting
and my eldest daughter is missing.
What will the other parents think?
Stop embarrassing me.
Can't you just settle down?
Your younger sister beat you to marriage.
You should be embarrassed.
Are you still single, Aki?
Yeah.
Better hurry up.
Plenty of men in Tokyo, surely?
Plenty of women too, you know.
Make sure you get chosen.
Fat chance of that happening.
No one would choose this selfish brat.
It's not a matter of being chosen--
Don't quibble!
Come now, you two. Aki!
If she's of childbearing age,
surely someone will still have her.
You want kids too, don't you?
Sure, but…
-Without a partner--
-Hey!
What about that family's son
who got divorced recently?
Where does he work again?
-Yamaguchi Supermarket.
-Yes!
Couldn't we fix something?
EPISODE 5
ARE YOU OKAY, MIYAJI?
FOCUS ON YOUR HEALTH FOR NOW.
I'LL MANAGE THE PLATFORM.
SYMPTOMS TO PAY ATTENTION TO
BEWARE IF FETAL MOVEMENTS STOP
Really?
We can't identify the source of the pain,
but if I had to say,
we may expect a premature birth.
Since it's a male pregnancy
the baby won't come out early,
but surgery may be necessary.
Surgery?
Will I be okay on my own?
On your own?
I mean, after what happened to Miyaji,
I'm a little anxious.
It's a shame what happened to Miyaji.
But you know, Hiyama.
No pregnancy comes without risks.
You're birthing life, you see.
You're right.
The second round of our UNIVE campaign
went live today,
running simultaneously in magazines,
online, on billboards and such.
I saw a billboard
on the way to work this morning.
Hiyama's the only model now.
You're killing it!
Using this as momentum,
I'd like to give an overview
of future plans we’ve decided upon,
with Hiyama as
our company's main ambassador.
As you can see, we have plans set up
until the baby turns three.
A baby shower, a birth documentary,
workshops with other dads--
Wait, a birth documentary?
Pregnant men give birth by c-section
so you can't film it closely.
Rather than the actual birth itself,
we'll cover the family
pre- and post-birth,
and what it's like to live with the baby.
This is the first I've heard of it.
You can't make these plans
without asking me first.
Don't just decide without me.
Isn't it a bit late for that?
By having a long-term plan
from birth onward,
we'll get the entire nation
to watch the baby grow.
Yes, but this is quite--
You said you'd do anything.
That's why we're doing it.
You work in advertising, too.
Surely you get it.
We're on a tight schedule. Let's move on.
Right.
Okay, next.
They must be joking!
Saying what they like
because it's not their problem.
-What are you doing?
-Searching for something sweet.
You're scowling.
Indeed I am!
"Indeed"?
I don't know if it'll help, but here.
It's fugashi cake.
Thank you.
-Matsuno.
-Yes?
Thanks for everything.
What? You're quitting?
We just launched the second round today.
You do know how much trouble it'll cause
if we take down UNIVE's ads now, right?
Sorry, I've reached my limit.
I shouldn't have spoken like that
in this morning's meeting.
But don't quit suddenly because of that.
It's not just because of this morning.
I've thought it over. Here.
RESIGNATION LETTER
Wait, hold on.
Honestly, what's wrong with you?
Nothing. Here.
Put that away.
-Look…
-Message received.
Please take it.
-Give me some time, okay?
-No.
Thank you so much.
See you.
Friends from high school?
Yeah, we were good pals.
Nice to see you as always.
Thanks for today.
Thank you.
Brings back memories!
See you soon.
Is everything okay?
Maybe it's the pregnancy.
He seems unstable, in any case.
-Even the CEO is here.
-Hiyama.
You are essentially
the face of our company now.
Even if that's the case…
We'd suffer a great loss if you left us.
Hiyama.
Our CEO is always looking out for you.
You're hope for other pregnant men.
Think of your contribution
to society, okay?
Boss.
You really think that highly of me?
Of course I do.
Pioneers must struggle in any era.
Right?
Something's definitely up.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm fine,
it's just that
so much is happening at once
and I just can't control myself.
-Hiyama!
-Don't worry!
We'll control it together, okay?
That's what our company's for.
Yeah, you're right.
You're all here for me, right?
Yes! So you get it?
I understand.
I'll continue.
-Thank you!
-I'll continue.
I'm so glad to hear it!
Thank you, I'm so grateful.
Boss…
Wait, are you going out?
Yeah. To a reunion party.
No idea how many people
will be there though.
At least have dinner with us today.
Your dad's waiting in the living room.
There's a lot to talk about.
Sorry, I already said I'd go.
What's there to talk about?
Well…
I'm worried
you're pushing yourself too hard.
You can easily find work here.
Don't be so stubborn.
I'm not being stubborn.
I'm living my life doing work I love.
But we've all given up
on what we first wanted to do.
I had things I wanted to do
when I was younger
but I held back after you were born.
That's not the case for everyone.
It's standard for most people.
In the end, it's very difficult
for a woman to live as she likes.
Do as your father says
and get married soon--
Something's wrong with that thinking!
If there's something you want to do,
you should do it.
You can leave him, you know.
Sorry, but it seems like
you just do whatever he says.
Why don't you
care about yourself a bit more?
How old are you now?
I'm 35.
It's time to plant your feet
in the ground.
Stop living a life of disgrace.
Welcome!
Look!
It's Aki!
Long time no see!
How are you doing? It's been ages!
-You live in Tokyo, right?
-Yeah.
-Wow.
-Remember me?
Of course. Yuko, right?
-Long time!
-Didn't remember me, huh?
Excuse me! A beer, please.
You're so hyped up!
No, no.
-Brings back memories.
-Sure does!
You seen this?
-Yeah.
-You have?
-You know it?
-Yes!
-And?
-Huh…
-Really going for it, huh?
-No, not that bit.
So cute.
Super cute.
He's a handsome boy.
Yeah, he doesn't look like you.
How many kids do you have?
Me? Three daughters.
I'd like a daughter.
Sure, but three is tiring.
Don't you have a boyfriend, Aki?
Well, I suppose I do, but…
Marriage isn't on the cards.
What do you mean?
You don't think you'll marry?
Wow, Tokyo's another planet.
I guess so.
Aki lives for her work, see.
What kind of work do you do?
I'm a freelance writer.
I write about company projects online
and do posts for their social media.
That's amazing.
It's not amazing at all.
-Hey…
-Who's this old guy?
Men having babies?
-The guy on the news?
-Yeah.
They're mutants!
-Normally…
-You're drunk!
It's a woman's job to give birth.
Right, sure.
So, if a man gets pregnant…
-Right?
-So gross.
I'm not sure if it's gross,
but if my husband got pregnant,
I wouldn't be brave enough
to let him give birth.
-Right?
-Definitely.
I'd worry whether the baby would be okay.
It's actually scary.
Men who get pregnant
might have some genetic problem.
-What?
-Yeah.
It's been proven that medically speaking,
any man could become pregnant.
Really?
-So…
-You knew?
So, a man's baby probably wouldn't be
any different to a woman's.
But still!
I don't think it's very manly.
-Just speaking plainly.
-Sure.
I just think it's gross!
Too right.
His partner's still a woman.
I'd feel sorry for her.
True, if your man got pregnant,
-you could never tell people.
-Right.
You'd have to hide it forever.
It's just tragic.
Right?
What's tragic?
It's sad that she can't
fulfill her role as a woman.
-Yeah.
-Right.
"Role" as a woman?
Because of prejudice like that,
real pregnant men can't talk to anyone.
They get abandoned by their partners
and give up on their babies.
But if I got pregnant,
I'd be too shaken up
to happily announce it.
I'd find it too scary, for sure.
It's scary for women, too.
-True.
-Yeah.
What does it even mean
to be "manly" like you said?
Aki, are you okay? What's wrong?
Nothing.
You okay?
-Have you eaten something?
-Yeah.
Maybe I'll have another.
-Welcome back.
-Hello.
How was the reunion?
Find any good single men?
Why are you just standing there?
Have a seat.
What on earth is it?
I need to tell you something, Dad.
I have a boyfriend in Tokyo.
He and I
are having a baby.
Really?
Why didn't you tell us
something that important?
And?
Say it clearly.
If you're pregnant,
there's lots to discuss and get on with.
It's not me.
I'm not pregnant.
What?
He's pregnant.
It's a male pregnancy.
That can't be true.
He's been on the news.
Kentaro Hiyama.
You know him, right?
He's my boyfriend.
I'm the mother of his child.
No proper man would get pregnant!
I can never understand
people who say stuff like that.
If that's going to be your attitude,
I'll keep living in Tokyo.
I'll keep working
and become a mother there.
I won't bother you.
My life won't be a disgrace.
Hello?
It's me.
Are you free to talk?
Yeah.
I'm heading back to Tokyo now,
but I called because
there's something I want to say.
Where are you now?
The station in my hometown.
I'm on the platform waiting for the train.
What did you want to say?
It's about what you said the other day.
That you can't raise a kid with me.
Yeah.
I did say that.
No matter what you say,
I'd raise that kid properly, too.
We have a strange relationship.
It's not like we were ever dating.
That's right.
But I don't think it matters.
We can create
our own new kind of relationship
and raise our kid together.
We don't need to be trapped
by fixed ideas or values.
There are all these roles and expectations
but really, everyone's different.
What are you talking about?
I don't think prejudice is going anywhere.
But if it's with you,
I think we can create
a new way of doing things.
You do?
Got it.
My train's here.
Sorry, I have to go.
What's up with her?
Thanks for coming to pick me up.
I couldn't sit still
after hearing your voice.
Sorry for making you worry.
I've had some time to think since.
Listen, at one point,
I did say I couldn't raise a kid with you.
But honestly,
I've been a bundle of nerves since then.
I guess, after all,
it's tough going it alone.
That's clear from seeing
my own mother, too.
So I'm grateful for what you said
on the phone.
Thank you.
I was trying to sort out my own feelings,
so I just blurted it out.
Aki, after you hung up the phone,
I felt the baby move
for the first time in so long.
I think this kid
also knows you as the mother,
and needs your love.
That's why I think…
always being together is better.
Let's…
get married.
I never had a father.
But because of that,
I'll be a good husband and a good dad.
And a mother, I guess.
Father? Mother?
-Listen, Kentaro.
-Yeah?
Just to be clear.
I decided we'd raise this kid together.
Right.
But I think marriage is a different issue.
What? Hold on.
Are we going to raise the kid together?
-Yes, of course.
-Right? Okay.
What I want is to continue talking
about how we'll balance that.
We can consider marriage another time.
Oh, I see. That's what you meant.
I understand, I think.
-Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Take care.
-Okay.
So…
Let's have a fresh start tomorrow.
Let's keep talking and making decisions.
Yeah. Thanks.
Been a while, Kentaro.
Who are you?
What?
I'm your dad.
Oh, right.
Well…
I'm also your mom.
Nice to meet you.
She's a cutie.
KENTARO HIYAMA
DUE IN 131 DAYS
Is he okay in your house?
I've been waiting to meet you for so long.
You're throwing it all away for him?
Why do men chase their dreams,
while women play supporting roles?
Dad.
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan