My beard's grown so thick.
EPISODE 3
BABY ON BOARD
Please have a seat.
Thank you very much.
No worries.
Hiyama, I think Tanabe wants you
to sort the thing in his email
before this afternoon.
-Where is everyone?
-In the Seifudo meeting.
I see.
Wait, he wants all this done this morning?
Yeah, I think so.
What's that?
Freebie samples.
You told me to order them
in the meeting last week.
We're moving them
to an empty meeting room to clear space.
Give us a hand, Hiyama.
I have things to do now.
So do we. Right?
-Come on, swiftly does it.
-Alright.
These are heavy.
Well, it's soap.
You're the one
who wanted to use soap, Hiyama.
Think about
how we have to bag them all up, too.
You can say that again.
They're actually pretty cute.
They are!
Great job as always, Tanabe.
-It was all your doing, Osugi.
-Not at all.
I'll get the green light from sales
and show it to the client today.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Sort the agenda and send it over.
Yes, will do.
What are you doing, Hiyama?
Are you okay? You're sweating loads.
Yeah.
You finished
the stuff I emailed you, right?
-I will.
-You still haven't done it?
Please do it soon.
I'll get in trouble if it's late.
I can handle this. You go ahead.
-Thanks.
-Alright.
Yes. I'd like to do the procedure ASAP.
The consent form is ready.
Next week? Yes, let's book that.
Yes.
One week's paid leave?
I'm fully aware
that it's an unreasonable request
at such a critical time as this, but…
my mother is undergoing surgery,
and since she raised me single-handedly--
Sure, why not?
Sorry?
You're not handling anything crucial now.
Someone else can cover for you.
BOOKED THE ABORTION.
BEING ADMITTED NEXT THURSDAY.
OKAY. SHOULD I COME WITH YOU?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Seto.
No worries.
Here are the materials I borrowed.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for bringing them.
One more thing.
It's about the plan for the online exhibit
I've been proposing.
I gathered some ideas together.
About that… I'm really sorry.
I don't think we can do it.
What?
You know Nishi, the writer?
We've just been working
on a similar project
and they overlap.
But wait, the other day,
you said there was interest
because I had a good angle.
It's just bad timing.
If you're interested,
you could help with Nishi's idea.
No, I wanted to see my own plan through.
Sorry about that.
-I wanna play!
-Yes, at home.
-I wanna play more!
-At home. Let's go.
Let's play at home.
I wanna keep playing!
MAKE SURE YOU'RE THERE, BIG SIS! -NARUMI
This is the consent form.
Please read and sign it
and take it away with you.
That's what happens post-surgery
until you're discharged.
We're past 12 weeks for this abortion,
so it'll be treated as a stillbirth.
Please report
the stillbirth to the city office
and get permission for the fetus's burial.
-Burial?
-Yes.
Excuse me.
-Yes?
-Um…
are you pregnant, by chance?
What?
Oh…
Yep.
-My body hair's grown like crazy.
-Yeah.
My beard keeps growing
no matter how much I shave it,
so I just gave up.
You gave up?
Rather than body hair, what gets me is
-the boobs.
-I know!
Oozing from your nipples, right?
-Yes, and--
-Two beers for table two.
Coming right up.
-Sorry.
-No…
There's a strange sense of camaraderie
being in the same week of pregnancy.
Sure is.
By the way,
have you bought maternity wear yet?
No.
I looked up some plus-size makers
and picked out some stuff.
Like this for instance.
Looks so cool.
-Well, cute, maybe--
-Listen.
Miyaji, I…
-Actually, I…
-Go on.
I'm not keeping it.
What?
I'm not even married.
It's affecting my work too much.
How do I say this?
Right, I understand.
Sorry, I should've said so earlier.
No, I got ahead of myself.
Let me apologize.
No, I'm sorry.
Here's your bowl of edamame beans.
A whisky highball and one plum wine.
Whisky highball and plum wine, right?
-Yes please.
-I'll bring them to you.
Whisky highball and plum wine, please.
I do understand, though.
I was sure
I'd get rid of it at first, too.
What? Really?
Yeah, I mean…
To be honest, the idea of men
having babies grossed me out.
I thought, "Why me?"
I couldn't believe it.
-Right?
-Yeah.
But gradually I started to think
it might be better to keep it.
My wife got pregnant
straight away the first time,
but we had such a hard time
second time round.
I'm sorry, Hiyama.
How can you get drunk
on non-alcoholic beer?
I dunno, it's the atmosphere.
-Careful.
-Yeah.
There! That's my house.
-Miyaji!
-I'm back.
Oh, dear. What happened?
-This is Noriko.
-Okay.
-This is Hiyama.
-Hello, I'm Hiyama.
I'm so sorry about this.
-Thanks for bringing him back.
-Of course.
He didn't drink a drop of alcohol,
so no need to worry.
I reckon he was over the moon.
Finding another expecting father.
I see.
He's not smiled like this for ages.
Really?
Oh, thanks for the tea.
He shut himself away in shock for a while
after he found out about the pregnancy.
He's back working in the shop now,
but he seems stressed out.
Whoa.
We fight all the time.
It's triple the trouble
of when I was pregnant.
Hey, when's your baby coming?
What?
Let's see…
Dad's baby is being born in September.
It's meant to be September 8.
It is?
Hey, Dad!
Oh, Takuya.
September, right?
Dad! Get up!
-Have you done your homework?
-Get up!
Phew! Halfway there.
That's right.
We should outsource work like this.
Anyone can do it.
Anyone can do it, yes.
Surely that's why we're doing it.
Right?
Thanks.
Sorry, Matsuno.
We've got a UNIVE meeting at 2:00 p.m.
so we need to leave soon.
-Oh?
-Excuse us.
-Alright, see you later.
-Sure.
Wait, hold on.
Tanabe's handling it now, isn't he?
What are you two going to do there?
Even underlings have work to do.
"Underlings"?
Hiyama dropped a few ranks, huh?
I meant me. I'm the underling!
I know, I know.
The client's marketing folk
are joining today too, right?
Oh, shoot! We don't have enough handouts.
Hey, Hiyama?
Can you quickly go print some?
-I'll go ahead.
-But…
Look, us two can't be late.
Fine.
Thanks!
I reckon we could even make
the backgrounds the same.
By also using models
of various sexual identities
and models with prosthetic limbs,
as well as famous actresses
and influencers
who champion self-expression,
we aim to show
a diverse range of professions
and these five types of models--
Can I say something?
It's become a little… ordinary.
Sorry?
Last time, we said we wanted a freshness
that suited the current era.
But this feels less alive.
Of course, we agree.
Next up is our proposal with that in mind.
-Go on, Hiyama.
-Okay.
This version has pregnant women
who don't abandon their careers.
Keeping a work-life balance--
Hasn't this been done?
What do you think?
Seen it all before.
Our apologies.
From our standpoint,
we're making doubly sure
not to damage your brand image.
I'll say this again.
We're rebranding.
Impact is key.
Frankly, I'm concerned this material
will raise doubts within our company
about working with you.
What do you think, Hiyama?
When you first proposed this plan,
we sensed a great possibility in you.
You've not said a word yet.
Mr. Hiyama, you're pregnant.
Like, a  male pregnancy?
It's positive?
You can't communicate properly.
Hey, when's your baby coming?
Do it soon.
You're not handling anything crucial.
Dropped a few ranks, huh?
What happened to your shirt?
Don't waste your life
worrying about what other people think.
Get rid of it…
Being a pregnant man
could work to your advantage
and lead to new job opportunities.
Let's stick with pregnancy.
But what about male pregnancy?
It's become a hot topic lately,
but it hasn't yet appeared
in any advertising.
Wouldn't it get people talking
if we included a pregnant male model?
It's interesting, but is it realistic?
It's not possible.
No one would do it anyway.
I'll do it.
What?
You? What do you mean?
Actually, I…
I'm pregnant.
I'm currently in my 11th week.
I've been going to a clinic, too.
Seriously?
Here's an ultrasound.
What the…
Seriously? You're pregnant, Hiyama?
I'm battling with morning sickness
and my body is changing.
As a pregnant man,
I'm part of an underrepresented group.
If I were a model
and talked about the concept of this ad,
it could create a big movement.
It's certainly unique.
Stunning. No one can copy it either.
Right, we'll follow Hiyama's idea,
redo the plan and resubmit it
to you straight away.
Yes, please do.
What a surprise! Never expected it of you.
Look, what I said just now
about giving birth…
I'm not sure I can actually do it.
You'll be fine.
-See you.
-Bye.
Women get pregnant
and give birth all the time.
You'll nail it.
-Tanabe, hold on.
-Okay.
What? So…
you're going to keep it?
Yeah, that's right.
But don't worry. I'll raise it alone.
I won't trouble you, Aki.
In that case…
I'd like to raise the kid, too.
What?
Well, I've always been focused on work,
but lately I'm wondering
if it's about time.
Wait, you mean
we'll get married?
Let's think about that later.
-But--
-Thanks for waiting.
Here are two appetizers.
A fresh fish carpaccio
and a salad with cured ham
and cottage cheese.
Thanks.
-For now, let's have a toast.
-Yeah.
-Cheers.
Wish I could have a drink.
Yeah.
Let's try this.
-Wait.
-Huh?
Is cured ham okay when pregnant?
It's fine, surely.
-No, wait.
-Huh?
"Foods to avoid while pregnant…"
Yeah, you can't eat cured ham.
-No way.
-Yeah.
Also, unprocessed cheese
and raw fish.
-So I can't have any of this.
-Right.
-That's a shame.
-Man…
Look after your body from now on, okay?
Do moderate exercise.
Have a balanced diet.
Got it.
No more instant noodles.
I know.
-I'll contact you soon.
-Okay.
See you.
Sorry about the other day.
I was pretty tipsy
and got ahead of myself.
No, it's alright.
Actually, Miyaji…
Yeah?
I'm thinking of keeping the baby.
What, really?
Yes.
Man, that makes me so happy!
I'm so glad.
It's so reassuring
to be going through the same thing.
Thanks for saying that.
Thanks for telling me such great news.
How about a drink sometime?
Yeah, let's do that. A soft drink, okay?
Alright. See you soon.
Okay, see you.
Hello, Ma? It's me.
When did you find out?
Around two weeks ago.
I said nothing
because I'd planned to get rid of it.
Wait a minute.
What?
Being pregnant and giving birth
is not as easy as you think.
Are you telling me not to do it?
Well, I mean…
The birth is just the start.
If you're raising a kid,
you won't be able
to work like you do now.
Listen, it'll be fine.
Loads of people nowadays give birth
then go back and work their butts off.
But they're women.
It doesn't matter
if you're a man or a woman!
It absolutely does matter!
Ma, I told my company
and things are already in place.
You can still pull out of that stuff.
-Sorry, Ma.
-Huh?
I've made my decision.
Hello? Hello--
Even my own son…
Hiyama is here.
Please go ahead.
-Hello there.
-Go ahead, Hiyama.
Take his gown, please.
Excuse me.
Let's go.
Right, let's do some tests.
Okay, we'll do the tests.
Let us see your belly a bit more.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, good.
Turn your body sideways
to show your belly in profile.
Yep, that's it.
Once more with your hands down.
Good facial expression, too.
Yeah.
Okay, keep going.
Drop your hand a bit.
That's right. Good.
Hey, check this out.
Look how big his belly is!
Whoa, for real?
Wait, wait.
I've never seen it before.
I saw it on TV before!
KENTARO HIYAMA
DUE IN 145 DAYS
Hiyama, you're totally trending!
Let's make a space where we can mingle.
I'm the mother of the kid in his belly.
Some things can't be overcome
by applying logic alone!
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan