Here we are in front of
Kentaro Hiyama's house in Setagaya Ward.
As you can see,
a lot of reporters are here.
Hiyama has caught everyone's attention
as a pregnant man…
TANABE: THE PRESS IS AT OUR OFFICE
SO STAY HOME
INCOMING CALL: MIYAJI
Miyaji?
Sorry to call suddenly.
It's fine.
Are you okay?
What?
I passed your house on a delivery just now
and saw loads of press outside.
Yeah, I'm somewhat trapped now.
That's tough.
I'm nearby,
so if you need anything dropped off…
No, I…
Well…
If it's okay…
could you get me some nursing pads?
EPISODE 7
-Long time no see.
-Been a while.
Excuse me.
Thanks so much. It's a great help.
Not at all.
I was out doing deliveries anyway.
Do you have some time?
Sure.
We had the funeral the other day,
so I finally feel at peace.
Sorry for not being in contact.
No, I'm sorry myself.
You never know
what life's gonna throw at you.
I mean, look at you.
You suddenly found out
that you were born from your dad.
Yeah.
I never thought I had a father,
then he suddenly
called to me on the street.
Seriously?
I'd like to meet your dad too, Hiyama.
He was an awful person.
But…
it still gave me hope.
What?
That someone born from a man
could grow up to be as great as you.
Me? No…
Maybe your father was selfish…
but I understand where he was coming from.
If I were in his place,
I'd be glad to see you doing well
and I'd come to meet you.
I'm so sorry.
I told you that jerk would run away.
What a despicable man.
Well, he's probably gambling
at his usual pachinko parlor.
What?
He never changes.
Wait, are you really going?
Why?
I feel like you'll only keep suffering
if you get any more involved with him.
That's not the issue. He's my father.
I know, but…
he's already caused all this trouble.
The baby will be born soon, too.
-That should be your priority--
-Sorry, Aki.
This is my family's problem.
I'm sorry,
but this is none of your business.
You're not the one giving birth.
I'll be back.
I guess I'll get going then.
-Hey, Aki.
-Yes?
I'm sorry.
Um, I…
I'm sorry my son spoke so hurtfully.
No, it's fine.
I remember being told something similar.
"It's not like you're giving birth."
"It doesn't even matter to you."
Oh…
But what could I do?
It's not like it happened
because I wanted it to.
But still,
he'd look at me like I was forcing
the responsibility on him.
That's…
actually what it's like now.
I mean…
the pregnant man
isn't the only one who suffers.
Right?
I'm probably wrong, but are you pregnant?
Nope.
Right, sorry.
Would it be a problem if I were pregnant?
No, not a problem.
I just asked because I was curious.
My apologies.
So then I always cut
any mini sausages in his lunchbox
to look like little octopuses.
That's adorable.
But when he reached high school,
he said, "Quit the octopus thing already!"
He'd had enough.
I did it because I thought he liked it!
I'm craving those mini octo-sausages now.
I'll make some for you.
Still, in the end,
I was always conscious deep down
that I didn't give birth to him myself,
so I tried to be even more motherly
than anyone else.
I'd always pack lunches for him
and I joined his open classes
even after a night shift.
I poured everything into doing my duty,
and before I knew it, here I am today.
This is a life I chose myself,
so I'm satisfied.
Still, sometimes…
I do think there's more to life
than just being a mother.
Maybe things would be different nowadays.
-Can I say something?
-Sure.
Even you could suddenly become pregnant.
-See you.
-Yes, good night.
TAKAGI: LET ME KNOW ABOUT SINGAPORE
BEFORE NEXT WEEK.
Hey!
Don't hide, old man. Hey!
What are you doing?
Why did you run away?
I'm talking to you!
Hey!
-Here.
-I don't want that.
Answer me already.
-Answer me!
-Okay, okay.
Come on, don't yell at me like that.
I told you, my ticker's in bad shape.
-I'm very sensitive.
-Don't mess with me.
So? What is it?
I'm asking you why you ran away.
Twice!
Have you ever thought about
the people you leave behind?
No, I get it.
I really do.
I want to apologize
from the bottom of my heart.
Then don't run away.
Perhaps…
I've got into the habit of running away.
After I gave birth to you…
people around town were merciless.
Calling me gay or sick and shunning me.
Looking at it now,
I know they were all wrong.
But at the time…
I didn't know what to do,
so I ran away.
Pretty pathetic, huh?
Sorry.
Oh.
Alright.
Here's the money I gathered from everyone.
-Return it yourself.
-I've had enough.
I'll let you handle it.
But…
-Thanks.
-Hey, young man.
Let's leave it at that today.
He'll return the money when he has it.
He's an honest man.
It's not like that, Mat-chan.
-What?
-This is my son.
You've got a son, Chief?
-Yep.
-"Chief"?
I told you before.
I told you the pregnant guy
on TV ads lately is my son.
-Really?
-Yeah, this is him.
-That was real?
-Yes.
I thought you were just
making stuff up again.
You cheeky sod!
What a surprise.
I have seen you before.
Oh! Wait here.
I'll fetch everyone.
Don't do that, Mat-chan.
You don't need to fetch anyone.
Hey, you idiot!
-Hey!
-I'm leaving.
Okay, go.
Oh.
You are you. Live your own life.
I'm me. I'll manage.
Huh?
-You're still here.
-Yeah.
I need to talk with you.
Talk about what?
Listen, Kentaro.
I've given it a lot of thought.
I'm thinking…
I want to accept…
the Singapore offer.
Of course, I intend
to go back and forth often,
and this job is also well-paid,
so I can pay proper child support.
I've not changed my mind
about raising this kid with you.
Listen to me.
Like you said,
I'm not pregnant
and I won't be giving birth.
So that means…
I can't play the role of a regular mother.
So, what about me?
How should I behave?
When I thought about what sort of mother…
I wanted to become…
I realized something.
I want to make my child
proud of their mother.
who stays true to herself.
I see.
Don't worry.
Understood.
UNIVE wants to drop Hiyama?
We're in trouble if that happens.
All the other sponsors will pull out, too.
But he's always been estranged
from his father, right?
Yes, he didn't even know he was alive.
That part needs to be clearly explained.
He has no connection with his father
and is himself totally clean.
Let's have a press conference.
Agreed.
Good way to cool things down.
We're counting on you two.
Understood.
Hello? Did something happen?
No.
The press conference is soon, right?
Are you alright?
It'll work out.
You don't need to worry about me.
Go ahead.
You setting off soon?
Yeah, I'm at the airport now.
Take care. Do a good job out there.
Same to you.
-Thanks.
-Bye, then.
Is your pregnant boyfriend alright?
He's fine.
-But he's not my boyfriend.
-Sure, sure.
I just heard
from the coordinator over there.
They said they'll arrange dinner
for us tonight.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Thanks.
I would like to take this opportunity
to apologize for the trouble
my father caused in the past,
which has caused a great deal
of worry and inconvenience to many people.
I am truly sorry.
REVEALED: HYPOCRITE!
You were estranged
but recently started a business together?
JUST DISGUSTING
Were you actually quite close?
No, I met him
for the first time a few months ago.
Didn't your mother ever talk about him?
I was told he'd died.
You deny any responsibility
for the fraud committed by your father.
It's also true
that until the press covered it,
I had absolutely no idea
about my father's past money issues.
So Hiyama, going forward,
surely you'll carry out
your proper duty as a pregnant man
to make up for your father's misdeeds?
My "proper duty" as a pregnant man?
Yes, can you promise that?
Excuse me,
what's a pregnant man's "proper duty"?
What?
You mean,
behave as a pregnant man "should"?
What? Well…
What are “roles” anyway?
Being manly, womanly,
motherly, fatherly.
Why put people in boxes
like ideal father and ideal mother?
I found out I was pregnant six months ago.
I've had nothing
but very unmanly experiences since.
My nipples leak breast milk.
I've now got a formidable sweet tooth.
People give me strange looks.
I've had a hard time at work.
It's been such a mess.
I'm not making excuses for him,
but my father surely
went through this struggle, too.
Prejudice used to be worse back then.
You know,
unexpected things happen in life.
That goes for you.
You, you, and you too.
You never know
what position you'll be in tomorrow.
But the way you approach those situations
is what makes you who you are.
That's one of the great joys of life.
My father…
isn't someone people would admire.
But still…
the one thing he did show me,
as his son,
was how to live a life true to oneself.
Since I became pregnant…
I've met so many different people.
Everyone has their own hurdles
and their own ways of overcoming them.
Only after spending time with those people
have I finally realized that.
To everyone who helped me
make such an important realization…
Everyone…
I am extremely grateful.
Thank you so much.
You're going pretty off-topic.
Please answer the questions properly.
That's it from me.
-Mr. Hiyama!
-Excuse me.
-Are you running away?
-Wait!
Looks bad, pal.
Mr. Hiyama?
What happened?
Are you okay?
What a scoop!
Are you alright, Hiyama?
Sorry, I have to go.
What? Wait, Seto!
-Mr. Hiyama!
-Hiyama, are you okay?
-Hiyama?
-An ambulance!
Call an ambulance!
-Hiyama…
-Mr. Hiyama!
KENTARO HIYAMA
DUE IN -- DAYS
Can we get a comment?
Thank you.
How about quitting?
He's not quite there yet.
-I'm counting on you.
-Yes, sir.
We can't sacrifice ourselves.
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan