Hiyama has just been rushed to hospital
and will now be
taken into surgery immediately.
The hospital staff have said
that he was barely conscious,
and there is concern about his condition.
The conference was
broadcast live across the country…
Doctor!
Mr. Hiyama? Mr. Hiyama!
Hang in there. You're alright.
What are you doing?
Well, I saw the conference.
I'm going.
But there's, you know…
You saw the conference, right?
Yeah.
If you're still running away
after seeing that,
then go do as you please.
You're his father, aren't you?
Mr. Hiyama!
Have you been in contact with him?
-How is your son doing?
-Mr. Hiyama!
-Can we get a comment?
-How is your son?
Give us a comment!
Mr. Hiyama!
EPISODE 8
This might sting a little.
This will feel cold.
Kentaro Hiyama, 37 years old.
Let's start the caesarean section.
Yes, sir.
Let's do this, Mr. Hiyama.
Scalpel.
How long did it take with me?
I don't remember.
But…
it felt so long.
What a strange life.
Both my husband and my son giving birth.
I should be saying that.
Getting pregnant as a man.
"Unexpected things happen in life."
"The way you approach those situations
is what makes you who you are."
I ran away a lot.
Sorry.
Too late.
-Sorry I'm late.
-Aki.
Can I wait with you?
Of course, have a seat.
Thanks.
I caused a lot of trouble.
I'm really sorry.
I won't let him do things like this again,
so please go easy on him this time.
It's fine, please sit down.
Which of you are Mr. Hiyama's family?
Me.
Congratulations.
The baby is premature,
but we managed to deliver it safely.
Really?
Thank you.
The pediatrician is doing some checks.
Please wait here a while.
I'll call on you again.
-Wait--
-I…
Yes?
Is Kentaro okay?
Don't worry.
Both the father and the child are well.
Excuse me.
Mr. Hiyama, here's your baby.
-Could you move your arms?
-Yeah.
Now sit up slightly.
There you go.
So tiny.
Your family members are here.
Kentaro!
Ma?
Well done.
-Wow.
-Thank you.
Dad.
Aki.
It's our kid.
This baby's too cute.
Yep.
-Can I hold the baby?
-Sure.
-Momma's here!
-She's your mother.
I'm Aki.
Are you awake?
I'll come back later. Take your time.
Okay.
So cute.
Alright, alright.
Let's take a photo
of the kid and the parents.
Alright.
Here we go.
Alright, alright.
-Is that a smile?
-Or speaking?
-Shall I take one more?
-Yes, please.
Alright, Kentaro.
What are you doing?
Oh, right. Here goes.
-That was a smile!
-Really?
Say cheese.
BIRTH REGISTRATION FORM
How should we write the name?
Let's have a single phrase
expressed in one character.
-Birth registration?
-Yes.
KO "JOY" HIYAMA
I feel like there's more awareness lately.
Maternity goods for men are being made
and people see things with less prejudice.
I hope it keeps getting even better.
Thanks for that coverage.
Isn't it incredible?
Doesn't this show how much
Japanese society has progressed?
What do you think, Yamaki?
I think it's something to be celebrated.
They really say whatever they want.
They were so critical
at the press conference.
Yeah, but that's just how it is.
They just see what's popular at the time.
Right?
True.
Come to think of it, you're no different.
-Me? How?
-Yeah.
You said some pretty nice things
at the press conference
but you expected me to deliver
some dogmatic idea of femininity
and to play the motherly role.
-You said totally different things.
-No…
It was an updated version.
You were pretty pleased with yourself.
No, I wasn't being smug.
The words just naturally flowed out of me.
Right.
I was just repeating what you've said.
I've absorbed the things
you talk about a lot.
I'm easily influenced by you.
Oh?
Can we switch?
-What?
-Please.
-Here's your mom.
-Come here.
-Come here, Ko.
-Alright.
I'll get tendinitis doing this.
Now, let's go outside.
Can you look after Ko tomorrow afternoon?
I've got a meeting.
-In the afternoon?
-Yeah.
Okay…
Do you really need to work right now?
I need to get all of this done
within the hour you're helping out.
Can you keep on like this?
What?
You're going to Singapore in a few months.
That's right. They postponed it for me.
Not the best timing.
I couldn't help it.
I reacted before I had time to think.
You can't rely on your parents, huh?
I did send my sister a photo.
Can you feed the baby some milk?
-Sure.
-Here.
-Slowly.
-Slowly?
Like this?
It's in!
Is that tasty?
Lots of problems, huh?
Your poor mommy!
Huh?
Gross, Aki?
-Aki?
-What?
-What about this?
-What's "this"?
-Poop.
-Oh man, this is bad.
What is it? Poop?
Here, diapers. Go over there.
-No way.
-They're in here.
Thanks. Hello?
-Yes, within the next hour.
-Aki!
-That's right, yes.
-No…
Please kindly arrange a meeting
to discuss that matter next week.
So unhelpful!
The salon is getting so many more members!
Yeah.
TV coverage has been positive lately, too.
Seems promising.
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
We've been relying on Hiyama's brand,
but if we're able
to increase membership like this,
we could make it a business.
-You're right.
-Sorry.
What's wrong?
-Sorry, sorry.
-Alright.
-I'm sorry.
-Hey.
-Let me try.
-Okay.
-I'm taking this off.
-Thanks.
Come here, little Ko.
Alright, here we go.
Okay.
What?
-Here, here.
-How?
I'm the parent.
I guess I'm no good.
No, Hiyama.
Your baby strap might be too big.
With a newborn,
you're way better off with a strap
designed for younger babies.
I'll show you later.
Spoken like a true veteran.
You'll get used to it gradually.
We're all here for you.
Let's help each other.
So let's move quickly
to make the salon into a business.
You guys.
Thank you.
That's enough.
Come on, sit down.
-Have a seat.
-There you go.
-Wanna sit too, Ko?
-Sit down.
-Let's do that.
-Okay.
Alright.
There.
I'm so grateful that you stuck by me…
even after my dad caused all that trouble.
Thank you.
What are you saying?
We got our money back.
We're not fussed about it.
Yeah, we're all in the same boat.
Thank you.
We're home.
Aki?
Aki.
Huh?
-We're home.
-Welcome back.
Sorry, I fell asleep.
I'll clean up
as soon as I've sent an email.
-Tonight…
-Yeah?
Let's have my mom look after Ko
and us two go out for dinner.
-Can we?
-Yeah.
-Thanks for waiting.
-Thank you.
It's been so long since I ate hot food
-while it's still hot.
-Right?
Man…
-What a relief.
-I could look at this forever.
Another round.
-Two beers please!
-Coming up.
What's with this menu?
Everything looks so delicious.
-Still got room?
-Yeah.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Are these stir-fried sausages
those mini octopus-shaped ones?
-That's right.
-Really?
-I want it.
-And the simmered beef and tofu.
Got it.
-Ready?
-Okay.
-The suspense is killing me.
-Ready?
-Look!
-Whoa!
Such perfect skin!
-Wow…
-Stayed fast asleep.
-This would be a good wallpaper.
-Isn't it great?
-Sure would.
-It's great.
We've ended up looking at photos of Ko.
True, even though we came here to be free.
Yeah.
Thanks for asking me out.
I'll thank your mom later, too.
Sure.
It's totally different
from what I imagined before the birth.
Yep.
The reality is pretty tough.
Yeah.
Hey, Kentaro.
I've given it some thought.
Maybe Singapore would be too difficult.
What?
I have to give an answer next week.
I'm thinking of turning it down.
I'll keep working still.
But going abroad--
No, stop.
Then it'll be pointless, Aki.
-But realistically…
-Aki.
None of us should sacrifice ourselves.
Not you, me, nor Ko.
We should all be the priority.
Let's value everyone's life here.
So be true to yourself,
and go to Singapore.
That gives me courage.
Thank you so much.
We appreciate really it.
You're very welcome.
I'm happy to spend time with Ko, too.
Please ask me any time.
Thank you.
-See you, then.
-Yes.
Okay.
-I thanked her.
-Appreciate it.
Look at this message from my boss.
What is it?
What's it about?
Asking me to be the main ambassador again.
I guess the salon's getting a good rep
and public perception has changed.
What a smooth talker.
-Listen, Kentaro.
-Yeah?
Why don't you quit?
It's such a two-faced company.
No, that would be such a waste.
What's a waste?
First, I'll take proper parental leave
and get what I can.
Then, once my leave is finished,
I'll try to negotiate
so I can work shorter hours.
On top of that, I'll turn the salon
into a business and work hard on it.
Is the company really that understanding?
I'll make them understand.
I'm going to talk with them
about having a cot in the office
for when you're abroad
or when there's no one to look after Ko.
Very bold.
Companies and businesses
need to update, too, not just us.
There we go.
Lately, the updates
have increased in gigabytes.
-To the latest model?
-Yeah.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
It's a great help.
-It'll fly by.
-Sure.
Thanks.
-I'll see you out.
-You don't have to.
Let's go together.
I appreciate it.
Hiyama.
Hey Tanabe.
-Did you get the nursery documents?
-Yep.
Our company is surprisingly understanding.
Parental leave, huh?
You've changed, Hiyama.
Yeah.
I miss competing with you for promotions.
Tanabe, I'm tackling a new challenge now.
It's really fun and really tough.
If our promotion squabbles
were a marathon,
then now it's a triathlon.
-Well, hallelujah.
-Hey!
-See you later.
-Sure.
-Bye.
So, you're on leave.
I wish I could take a break, too.
I'll be focusing on raising my child.
It's not a break.
Honestly, I thought you'd quit.
But I don't dislike
your determination either.
Thanks for that.
I realized something.
Interrupting my career to have a kid
doesn't necessarily mean
lowering my sights.
I'm actually developing as a person,
so one day this experience
will surely be reflected in my work.
Yeah.
-Hiyama.
-Yes?
Don't be so pleased with yourself.
What?
It's always been like that for us.
Our "hero" is not quite there yet.
Honestly, men!
They're all bloody idiots.
Makes you laugh, doesn't it?
I suppose it's also a good thing.
-I've always thought so.
-Really?
Okay, this is enough.
-Here's fine.
-You sure? Okay.
-Thanks.
-Have a good one.
See you.
Unexpected things happen in life
one after the other.
I never expected dealing with them
would be so tough…
-Thanks.
-Yes, sir.
So complicated…
Hello!
Sorry I've been out of touch.
Can I feel?
Yet it's joyful…
and full of richness.
Is it salty?
It's sweet.
-Sweet?
-Yes.
Really?
Empty out your tray!
I never expected
that my priorities would change.
-The balls!
-Oh, right.
Thanks for looking after Ko.
I'll be back next week.
You should stay there
until you get a handle on things.
It's a big opportunity.
Right, Ko?
Huh? What?
What's wrong?
-Is everything okay?
-What's wrong, Ko?
I will be back next week, okay?
Thanks.
What's wrong all of a sudden?
-Hey, look.
-Huh?
Turn Ko to face me.
Look, Ko. Your mom has something.
It's Froggy!
-Are you gonna cry?
-Seems like it.
Maybe it's scary.
-Hasn't gone down well.
-Isn't it cute?
Such long legs!
That things legs are
so unnecessarily long.
Creepy, huh?
Look, that's a "too creepy" face.
Look, now.
Come on.
Look.
BABY ON BOARD
Are you okay?
You're pregnant, right?
Sorry I didn't realize earlier.
Go ahead.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Must be tough. How many months is it now?
I'm still only two months in.
There's so much I don't know yet.
Sorry, thanks.
It's fine.
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan