What's that?
Haven't you heard?
How cool.
Very fresh.
Seriously.
I can picture it.
It has a gender-neutral feel.
It's massive!
Amazing.
This is the person
everyone's talking about.
Kentaro Hiyama, a pregnant man.
In our studio today
we have Kentaro Hiyama
who has been attracting attention
with his pregnant man ads.
Until now,
the media hasn't taken much interest
in male pregnancy
like this.
Today on Buzz Check,
we look into the full story behind
the Hiyama craze sweeping the nation
and who this man really is.
EPISODE 4
I was driving on the highway,
and bam! You're on a billboard!
I almost crashed my car.
Social media's going crazy!
Hiyama, you're totally trending!
It just so happened.
Man, putting your whole body out there
to carve out a new era.
But still…
Isn't his body slightly too "out there"?
I had to choose between ending up
as an ordinary office worker
or exposing myself to boost my worth.
I just chose the latter.
Nice one, Kentaro!
Thanks for waiting.
Here's your rare steak.
I want to talk about life stuff today.
-Which would you lot pick?
-The latter!
Well, I wouldn't be here.
-You can't ask that.
-I can't say.
Rina?
Hiyama?
It's been a while.
You're actually pregnant.
Well, yeah.
We won't be able to see each other anymore
since you'll be busy with childcare.
But I'll be back to normal by next spring.
I'll get a babysitter.
I didn't mean that.
I could just about stomach
my lover being a dad,
but absolutely not a mother.
See you.
Cheers!
Yeah! Boy Meets Girl!
FLOWER SHOP MIYAJI
Miyaji.
Oh, Hiyama?
-Hello.
-Hi.
I'm at a baby shower one day,
some celebration the next.
Parties every day.
Honestly, I'm tired of it.
I understand.
Friendships change, right?
In my case,
these aren't people I'd call friends.
Actually, maybe I never had
a single friend
that I could talk to like this
without putting up a front.
-Sorry for talking about this.
-Not at all.
Take this if you like.
Are you sure?
-Thanks.
-Sure.
It's pretty.
Listen, for me,
if it weren't for you,
I might still be hiding away
with no one to talk to.
We're lucky chaps.
Could we offer a service like that?
A sort of online platform for pregnant men
to share information and such.
We could create a space
where we can mingle.
-What do you think?
-I like it.
I mean,
we have concerns that aren't
worth going to see a doctor about, right?
Sure.
Like when my belly gets even bigger,
-how am I gonna pee?
-So true!
I've worried about that, too.
-It's a good idea.
-Yes.
Hello?
Is that you, sis?
What is it? I'm working.
I can't talk much.
Are you actually going to come
to my wedding at the end of the month?
You're the only one
who hasn't replied to my invite yet.
I'll be there, probably.
"Probably"?
I know you don't get along with Dad,
but come to your
sister's wedding at least.
Alright, alright.
I've got something
I need to tell you, too.
What is it? New boyfriend?
I'm hanging up.
-Welcome.
-Sorry I'm late.
-Why, you little…
-Sorry!
-Long time no see.
-Been a while.
What do you want? I already ordered.
I'm leaving in 30 minutes.
What? Already?
I'm going to Singapore
for a month from next week.
I wish we'd had a drink
together with everyone.
-I'll be back soon.
-Excuse me.
-Some water.
-Thanks.
-Here's today's pasta dish.
-I'll have the same.
-Of course.
-I'll take this.
-Thanks.
So, how about you? How's work?
Me? Same as usual, really.
-It's going peacefully.
-Peacefully?
-What?
-Well…
you used to be
the keenest fighter of us all.
Well, actually,
I'm cooking up a big project, too.
What is it? Give me the elevator pitch.
You know Kentaro Hiyama,
the guy on TV all the time?
Yeah.
I'm the mother of that kid in his belly.
-Seriously?
-Yep.
What the hell?
-You interested now?
-Yes!
From what he says,
pregnant men still
aren't properly recognized,
so maybe if I wrote a series
to help people understand it a little--
Stop right there.
Who wants to read
something preachy like that?
You've got a great scoop.
Write about being
a pregnant man's partner.
No way. I'm not selling out
my life like that.
Sure.
I'm not saying you should bare everything.
But the old Seto used to win
no matter what.
Are you really satisfied
with living peacefully?
Excuse me. Here's your salad.
The world is keenly watching this man.
See you later.
Neither a showbiz celeb nor a model,
Hiyama is an advertising agent
and a pregnant  man.
FRONTLINE: KENTARO HIYAMA
How does Kentaro Hiyama live
as a pioneer of a new age?
Let's observe the cloud movement.
Clouds accompanying a front…
Sorry.
Bye.
Kentaro?
Oh?
Why didn't you use a pseudonym?
It's such a bother for your relatives.
There's only me and you.
Dad's dead and we're not
in touch with his side of the family.
I suppose so.
You hungry?
-Oh, thanks.
-Here.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Kentaro,
were you going to eat
all this by yourself?
It's true that you get a wild appetite
when pregnant, huh?
I've been holding back because I had
a checkup yesterday, so it's fine.
You're not allowed to get fat
when pregnant now, huh?
That's tough.
By the way,
what was Dad like?
What?
Why?
He was a great person.
So vague.
Why would you ask that?
I'm wondering what fathers
talk about with their kids
since mine will be out in a few months.
The media can’t get enough
of Kentaro Hiyama
who suddenly garnered attention
after appearing as a pregnant male model
in a UNIVE marketing campaign
starting this month.
Hiyama, your popularity is soaring
and you recently set up an online platform
which already has so many members.
Yes, I'm so grateful.
Currently we have over 10,000 members.
Ten thousand!
-Amazing.
-Yeah.
Incredible. It's free, too?
-It's free of charge.
-Free!
My aim is to create a space to support
other pregnant men and their families
which is why it's free of charge.
-I see. Very admirable.
-No, no.
WHY DO MATERNITY PRODUCTS
HAVE SUCH CHILDISH DESIGNS?
THE ONE WHO'S PREGNANT IS AN ADULT!
MAMI LIKED YOUR POST.
LIKO SHARED YOUR POST.
You're making waves
just by stating the obvious.
Who knew it was so easy
to get women on your side?
It shows how much women have been ignored.
If men say it, everyone listens.
Pregnancy turns you
into a feminist too, huh?
Tao Tsuchiya is here.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
Is that Mr. Hiyama?
Yes.
I always read your posts.
Really?
My agent, who I've always worked with,
-recently gave birth.
-I see.
I hear you've provided great comfort.
Wow, really?
I'm glad to be of help.
Good luck. I'm rooting for you.
Thank you.
-Ms. Tsuchiya, it's time.
-Okay.
-Keep up the good work.
-Thanks.
-See you.
-Hello.
-Go ahead.
-Hello, welcome.
This is the head.
This is the left arm.
So it's like this.
Have you felt any movement yet?
No, not yet.
Okay.
Is that not a good thing?
No, no.
A pregnant man has more muscle mass,
so he'll start to feel the baby moving
later than a woman would.
Oh, right.
Do you want to know the baby's sex?
-What should we do?
-Huh?
Let's find out.
What? But…
Don't you want to know?
Right.
Then I'll tell you, okay?
Most likely
it's a boy.
A boy?
Did you want a girl?
No, I just felt like it was a girl.
How?
-Which did you think?
-Boy.
Great instinct.
I just thought so, for some reason.
I'm beat.
Is it okay to move like this
while pregnant?
The doctor said to exercise.
I might get a taxi home.
That's not fair! You're calling a taxi?
Someone messaged the platform.
"Hello, I'm also a pregnant man."
"I don't know anyone I can talk to
so I feel anxious every day."
"Could we meet up somewhere?"
Is it a prank?
Could be a real pregnant dude.
The account was made ten years ago.
Their user pic is Robert Downey Jr.
So it is!
Why don't we arrange
an offline meetup for the platform users?
An offline meetup?
-It's probably similar.
-Yeah, true.
What do you do?
I wish there were
"Baby On Board" tags for men.
Yeah, there's the color too.
They're too cutesy.
-We need more…
-Hello.
Hello.
-Hi there.
Wow, you're big.
So many people came.
Where have they been hiding?
Um…
-Nice to meet you.
-Hi there.
It's me, Robert Downey Jr.
-Oh!
-Right.
I told my girlfriend I was pregnant,
but she said she wants
to get back with her ex.
Cruel, right? She was even
seeing us both for a while.
That's pretty cruel.
Unbelievable.
I badgered her about the baby,
but she insisted on splitting up.
So you're giving birth as a single parent?
I've always wanted a family.
So, even though I'm a bit worried,
meeting fellow comrades like this
has given me courage.
Same here.
Have you thought about nurseries
or where you'll raise your kid?
Not particularly.
So you haven't started hunting
for a nursery spot yet.
The process differs
depending on what area you live in.
You're talking about day care?
Yes, that's right.
You won't get a good place in Tokyo
unless you start soon.
Lots of moms have to quit work
when that happens.
Oh, I see.
That's amazing.
It's your second pregnancy?
We're both in our 19th week now.
So you'll be feeling the baby move soon.
I've already felt it for a while now.
I still haven't.
I mean, maybe I just haven't noticed it.
At first, it's just
a little bubbling sensation.
Maybe you wouldn't notice.
-Bubbling?
-Yeah.
Whereabouts? Lower down?
At first it was around here, lower down.
-Lower down?
-Yeah.
I feel like it wasn't there.
Where was it then?
It's hard to put it into words.
Come on, tell us.
I can't. I don't know how.
I clearly felt mine.
FLOWER SHOP MIYAJI
They were all pregnant men
but all so different.
Sure were.
We were the hosts,
but we were the ones getting advice.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
Hey, are you on TV?
A bit.
So that means it's not weird
that Dad's got a baby in his belly, right?
It's not weird.
I knew it. Yay!
Takuya, you're heavy!
Go to him.
Hush, calm down!
You don't need to get so upset.
Come here, Takuya.
Come on.
Don't run about in front of our guest.
Huh?
I think I felt the baby move.
What? A bubbling sensation?
Yeah, like bubbling up.
That's definitely the baby!
-Right?
-Yeah.
-I felt it.
-You did.
-Yep.
-Amazing.
So this is it.
Humbled, we must tell the gods
that Aki Seto,
grace be to the gods
of creation and fertility,
now carries a child,
thus we beseech you to bring her
quiet and peaceful days…
But I'm carrying the kid.
Please accept these gifts.
-May the baby be healthy.
-Um…
I'm the one giving birth.
-Oh, of course.
-Yeah.
To the expecting father…
I mean, mother…
I wish you a healthy child.
The priest totally did that on purpose.
Sure won't be the last time
that kind of thing happens.
"That kind of thing"?
I mean
not only are you a pregnant man
but we'll be raising a kid
out of wedlock.
Yeah, about that.
Are we really not getting married?
Normally people get married properly
then raise children.
You're really talking
about what's "normal"?
We've done everything under our own names.
Then suddenly we have to choose
one or the other.
The idea of changing my name…
I don't really get it.
It's not just my own problem.
It's about the world
this kid will be living in, too.
Sure, I get that.
But why?
How can you ask that?
Surely you just experienced
what it's like when roles get reversed
between men and women.
-That's not what I meant.
-Oh?
I meant, where did that idea come from?
Why…
Yes?
Noriko? Yes.
What?
Noriko.
Hiyama.
How's Miyaji?
The doctor said
there was a cytomegalovirus infection
which caused the contractions to start.
But…
at only 20 weeks old,
the baby couldn't survive
outside the womb, so…
So…
I would never say this to my husband…
but now that the baby won't be born,
a part of me feels relieved.
What?
Takuya is being bullied at school.
Kids say it's gross
that his dad's pregnant.
People have also treated me coldly.
This…
I know it's wrong.
I'm still so sad.
But somehow,
I also feel relieved.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it wrong to be bullied
because your dad's pregnant?
I feel so sorry for Takuya.
Noriko…
If she knew her son was being bullied,
wasn't there something she could do?
It's not her fault.
-She's suffered too.
-I know, but…
A child being bullied…
That could happen to our child, too.
You keep talking about your own situation.
Miyaji's baby dies,
but you're worrying about your own kid?
It's not like that.
I'm just saying
our choices could end up
interfering with our kid's life.
Sure, family can be a burden sometimes,
but we help each other out, too.
A parent protects their child
if something happens.
That's what I've always done with my mom.
Some things can't be handled
through logic alone, Aki.
Familial love, bonding…
Those things all sound good,
but they aren't necessarily
always helpful.
You and I…
Aren't our ideas of family too different?
What?
Maybe I can't raise
this kid with you, Aki.
KENTARO HIYAMA
DUE IN 137 DAYS
What's wrong?
Nothing. Here.
Stop being a disgrace.
Bloody mutants.
I won't be a disgrace.
Subtitle translation by: Helen O'Horan