Previously on This Is Us
I love our life. I love it right now.
And I'm so scared of changing it.
I'm not gonna stand for
anything changing between us.
(crying): I don't want
to be different from them.
Different from who?
Who, the kids at school?
If I get an "A," I'll get ice cream,
and Kate and Kevin won't,
and then they'll hate me.
KATE: I can't fall for
a fat person right now.
I guess I'll lose the weight then.
What did I do to deserve this?
You've done a lot of
really nice things for me,
so I wanted to return the favor.
By cutting up cardboard
into little squares
and putting it in a bowl? Yum.
Hey, so, Kevin, uh, it's
been a few days now, you know,
since you showed up.
- Without calling.
- Right.
I was just sort of wondering...
When you leaving?
Yeah.
♪
♪ (washing machine running)
♪ I listen to the wind ♪
♪ To the wind of my soul ♪
- (machine clatters)
- REBECCA: Washing machine
is officially cooked.
JACK: Ah, she's still got
some life in her, at least
- six more cycles.
- REBECCA: Jack, we have three infants.
We're gonna be doing six cycles by noon.
Jack? Yeah.
REBECCA: Uh, I need your help.
- It's leaking everywhere.
- (kids laughing)
- JACK: This is bail out!
- ♪ I've sat upon the setting sun ♪
REBECCA: Oh, my God.
This is the best washing
machine in the entire world.
I'm actually turned on
by this washing machine.
- JACK: I'm gonna show you turned on.
- (Rebecca chuckling)
- Oh, you are?
- I am.
♪ No, never, never, never ♪
- JACK: Big Three!
- KIDS: Big Three!
REBECCA: I just want to
do a small kitchen remodel.
Just some new cabinets,
maybe some new countertops.
YOUNG KEVIN: Give me those,
Randall, they're my bouncy balls.
YOUNG RANDALL: But Mom gave them to me.
YOUNG KEVIN: (chuckles) You said "butt."
YOUNG RANDALL: (chuckles)
You said "balls."
♪ Take me where my
heart wants to go. ♪
What the hell, Kevin?
Turn the lights out, man, it's 2:00 a.m.
Damn it, Kevin, you ruined it.
It's all ruined.
Hey, man, I'm...
I'm sorry, dude.
Don't.
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to help you.
Look, I'm sorry I touched
your precious woobie.
- That thing reeks by the way.
- It's the blanket I was left in, Kevin.
Well, it doesn't mean you
can't wash it once in awhile.
- What's your problem?
- What's my problem?
Yes, what's your problem?
What's my problem?
Dude, it's 2:00 a.m.
- and all the lights are still on!
- REBECCA: Hey, guys.
What in the name of
God could you possibly
be fighting about right now?
- He threw a football at my face.
- He keeps waking me up.
Shh.
And I need to get sleep because
I have a big game tomorrow.
Okay, Kevin, but Randall
has a lot of homework,
and now that he's on the football team,
- he has a lot less time do do it.
- And why does he suddenly
need to be on the football team?
What do I have to do with you guys?
Do I have to make you go
sleep in separate rooms?
- Yes, actually that'd be great.
- No, Mom...
Okay, that won't work
because the only empty room in the house
- is the basement.
- I want it.
Kevin...
(sighs)
- K... would you relax?
- Hey. Dude, come on.
You don't have to go into the basement.
I'll turn off my light,
and I'll do my homework in the kitchen.
That's a very nice offer.
Kevin, do you hear what
your brother's saying?
Yeah, I heard him.
♪ ♪
- Hi, Kevin!
- Ashley.
That baby teething?
- You know it.
- All right.
Ni hao, Mr. Hwa.
Keep working on that core.
- Hey.
- What's up?
Uh.
Morning, gentlemen.
- KEVIN: Hey.
- RANDALL: Good morning.
Look at this, I got six miles.
- Good for you, buddy.
- Yup.
I did eight.
(Kevin chuckles)
- Is William still asleep?
- Yeah.
I feel like yesterday's
chemo took a lot out of him.
Mm. Morning hugs!
- Give me my morning hug.
- No, gross!
Daddy, you're all sweaty.
BETH: All right, come on girls,
backpacks, lunches, car.
Let's go. I'll be right out.
RANDALL: Have a great day, beautifuls.
- Daddy loves you.
- Bye, Dad, love you.
Bye, kiddos.
- Hey, Kevin.
- Hmm?
Did you see a yellow legal pad
in my office?
You mean my bedroom?
Do I though?
All right, I am gonna grab a shower.
- Meet you at the office before dinner.
- Yeah.
Look, he and I are
having dinner tonight,
so you have a Kevin-free evening.
- Just the two of you?
- Mm-hmm.
- Alone?
- No, we're meeting our mother.
(chuckling): Oh, okay.
Why?
No, I just couldn't imagine
you and Kevin hanging out.
What do you... Well, the
guy lives in our house, Beth,
we hang out all the time.
Yeah, but you guys are never
in the same room alone together.
Uh, we just went for a run together.
- (ice clatters)
- Together?
Really?
So, what this mean, "Really?"
(chuckles)
It didn't end well for
Cain and Abel, baby,
that's all I'm saying.
- Well, we're not Cain and Abel.
- Hmm.
Well, they were much less repressed.
But if we were Cain and
Abel I'd be Cain, right?
'Cause he's the brother who won?
All right.
- I love you. (sniffs, clears throat)
- Love you.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
That was your fastest run yet.
Damn right it was.
Damn right.
♪ Ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
- (machine beeps)
- ♪ Woke up past 8:00 today ♪
♪ My neighbor paid my meter ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ My boss gave me a raise,
didn't even say the reason ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ There's kindness in the air ♪
♪ That takes me where I'm going ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I think I'm happy and I know it ♪
- ♪ Know it, ha ♪
- _
♪ Don't know why ♪
- ♪ But it keeps getting better ♪
- _
- ♪ 'Cause it's the best day ever ♪
♪ The best day ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ The best day ever. ♪
- KATE: I should pee.
- TOBY: You just peed.
- Every ounce counts.
- That's true.
And I'm crushing this weigh-in.
Get it!
All right, Kate, are you ready?
I am. All right. Let's do this.
- Oh, will you hold this for me?
- Yeah.
(scale beeping)
All right. Congratulations, lady.
You are down a pound and a quarter.
A pound?
Yeah, and a... and a quarter.
And a quarter.
Okay, I kill myself for
weeks, and I'm down a pound?
- And a quarter.
- Right. Yeah.
It's working, all right?
You got to keep going, though.
This is the tough
part, but you got this.
Yeah.
Good job.
Down. Down is great.
Thanks. Nice work, nice work.
- All right.
- All right, Toby, you ready?
- Yup.
- All right.
- (scale beeping)
- Okay. Oh, wow.
- You lost eight more pounds, mister.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- You know what that means?
Hey, guys, guess who
just met their month goal?
This guy!
(laughs)
Nice. Hey, yeah, Toby, do you
mind if we take a victory pic?
- Oh, no, no, that's not necessary.
- No, of course it is.
- No, it's no biggie.
- You hit your goal.
- It's no biggie.
- No. You are no biggie... anymore.
- Yeah.
- I'm proud of you, Toby.
Go, give 'em what they want.
Okay, all right.
Uh, I'll do the... I'll
do the victory photo.
WOMAN: Yes, let's do it.
All right, we're doing it.
WOMAN: All right,
guys, let's get in here.
- TOBY: Victory photo.
- WOMAN: Come on, circle it up.
- All right, one, two, three.
- TOBY: Ah!
- ALL: Cheese!
- TOBY: Cheese!
WOMAN: Super cute. Another one. Smile!
Yes! Beautiful!
-- Synced and corrected by ChrisKe --
-- www.addic7ed.com --
RANDALL: I want to make a big
push on rising temp futures.
Some of our clients don't
currently believe in science,
but we'll have 'em watch
an Al Gore documentary once
the cash starts rolling in.
Am I right, people?
Come on, guys, nothing? That was...
Is that the Manny?
Yup. That's the Manny.
- I'm early!
- Right.
I'll be right there. (clears his throat)
You guys look sharp.
(woman laughs)
I'll meet you in the...
meet you in the office.
Okay. Cool. Just chill
out in your office?
Yeah.
That is the Manny. It is. (laughing)
♪ Straighten up and fly right ♪
♪ Straighten up and stay right ♪
♪ Cool down, Papa, don't
you blow your top. ♪
Sounds good.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I don't remember the last
time I was this nervous.
Oh, it's just rehearsal, right?
Yeah, but it's my first
rehearsal in ten years.
You're gonna do great, babe.
- (clears throat)
- Hey, uh,
what are you planning on wearing
to the boy's game tonight?
Because I know we usually
wear Kevin's colors, but now
that Randall's playing
for another school...
The game. Crap.
Um, I'm meeting Bob Parrish tonight
to close the Doylestown deal.
- Doylestown?
- Yeah.
Really? So you got it?
I-I told you last week.
Well, I'm sure I would have
remembered if you said that.
- Oh, I know that I did.
- Okay, well,
is there any way that
you can move the meeting
because that coach is
coming to scout Kevin?
It's a really big game for him.
It's a big day for me,
too, and a big day for you.
And a big day for Kevin, so...
(sighs)
I'll see what I can do.
- Okay.
- Jack?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm all over the place.
- Have a good day.
- Have fun.
Thanks.
Yeah.
- RANDALL: No, of course.
- Hey.
I totally understand. We
can do dinner another time.
That was Mom? She's not
coming? What'd she say?
Yeah. Well, tell Miguel
I hope he feels better soon.
Let me talk to her. Is Miguel sick?
- Let me just talk to her real quick.
- Yeah, I'll tell Kevin.
Just give me the phone.
- Just put her on speaker.
- We can reschedule.
Just let me talk to her before you go.
Love you, too. Bye.
Before she... Let
me talk to her for...
Oh. It's Miguel's gout.
Really? I didn't know they
made gout anymore.
Yeah.
- So she's not coming then?
- No.
Not coming. Oh, okay.
(exhales)
- It's the two of us.
- Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, if you got
work to do though, I...
- we don't have to go.
- No!
- I'm, I'm okay.
- You're all right?
- Yeah.
- Uh, if you've got lines to learn
- or something, then we can...
- I'm good. I'm up to speed, so...
You and me.
You and I.
BETH: Hey, girls, wash up and come down.
So, Kevin and Randall are out tonight.
It'll just be you and us ladies.
Nothing for me, thanks.
(coughs)
You know, my dad had cancer.
Lung.
I didn't want to say
anything 'cause, you know,
it wasn't exactly a
happy ending for him.
Endings rarely are.
Weed helped.
With the appetite, you know? But...
I just figured with your history,
I didn't want to bring
that up because of...
No... Marijuana doesn't have
the same kind of trigger.
Even my doctor said.
Hmm.
Can't have you going out in the night
scoring drugs on my account.
What... what if I was to
tell you I had a little stash?
Then I'd say, woman, you surprise me.
And I'm not easily surprised.
How about I feed the girls, right?
Get their asses in bed,
and bake us up some special brownies.
- I like that plan.
- You like that?
- (chuckles)
- Yeah.
Right.
Hey! How are you?
(shouting): What do you think?
This place is great, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. The last time I was here,
I bro'ed out with Mario Lopez.
I don't know who that is.
Oh, okay. (laughs)
Oh, my God. We love you.
Yeah? All right, well, cool.
Let's, uh... do a selfie.
- Give it to me, I'll take it.
- No, no, it's a selfie.
- It's a thing.
- Right. Got it.
(indistinct chatter)
KEVIN: That's gonna turn out great.
- Thank you. (giggles)
- I'm suddenly getting
- why we came here.
- What'd you say?
I said I'm su...
- It's a great place!
- Yeah!
You're... Oh, you got to walk around.
Yeah, yeah!
Big table.
He's never been here.
- There he is!
- Hey!
Hey, everybody.
Hey, guys.
All right.
So, he's got a piece
of egg salad sandwich
dangling from his mustache,
riding me about how
- I don't take my job seriously.
- Yeah.
Eventually, I just had to
walk out while he was talking.
Jack.
I forgot to kiss Rebecca
good-bye this morning.
- (chuckling): Oh...
- First time in 15 years.
- Knock, knock.
- Hey, Heather.
Sabatino's?
(sighs) Best in the city.
Please, I can make a better meatball sub
than that, blindfolded.
- Is that an offer?
- Oh...
- I need you to sign off on these.
- Okay.
Do you have a...
- Here you go.
- Thanks. Thanks, Jack.
Here...
Mm-hmm.
- There you go.
- And... you missed one.
What would I do without you?
MIGUEL: There you go.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
What?
- I was playing...
- Are you...
So... Took your pen.
Oh.
Thanks.
Your wife should've got that.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Just...
♪ ♪
Hi. I'm so sorry I'm late.
(chuckling): Hey, no,
- you're not late.
- (groans)
Wow. Wow. (laughter)
Geez.
- Oh...
- Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my God.
It's been too long.
Guys, this is...
- Rebecca Malone.
- Um... it's Pearson now.
- Oh. Right. (snaps fingers)
- But, hi, hi, Rebecca.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Hi.
Thank you so much for thinking
of me for this. It really...
- it means a lot.
- Are you kidding?
Our manager decided we
needed a female vocalist
and I told him it's...
it's got to be the girl
- I used to play the keys for.
- Well, I guess
you forgot this girl
you used to play keys for
- got old.
- Not from where I'm standing.
- Really?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, what do you...
you want to jump in?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm ready. Okay.
One, two,
one, two, three.
(band begins playing)
♪ A buzzard took a monkey
for a ride in the air ♪
♪ Monkey thought that
everything was on the square ♪
♪ The buzzard tried to throw
the monkey off his back ♪
♪ The monkey grabbed his neck
and said, now, listen, Jack ♪
♪ Straighten up and fly right ♪
♪ Straighten up and stay right... ♪
Hey, you've reached Toby, I
can't take your call right now
'cause I'm out saving
the world from evil,
or it's Tuesday, and I'm bowling.
Toby out.
(beeps)
Hey, it's me.
Again.
I just...
wanted to apologize for ducking
out of the meeting. Again.
Well, not like I've ducked out
of previous meetings, I'm...
Please call me.
(knocking)
- Hi.
- Uh, hi.
Wow, uh, this is...
- not expected.
- I know you're mad at me,
and I get it. I should
have handled myself better.
No, no, no. No, it's fine,
it's fine. I literally
just saw that you called.
I've just, I've... I've been busy,
- is all.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
Can I come in?
Uh... uh, yep.
Yeah. Come on in.
Uh... it's the maid's day off. (laughs)
- You binged?
- No! What?
This is no big deal.
I just, I hit a goal and I celebrated
by eating some food that I
actually like the taste of.
You know, I don't... I
don't have an eating problem.
Yeah. Well, you didn't have a problem
- eating all this food.
- (laughs)
- All right, that's fair.
- Listen, Toby.
We can just get back on our program,
- like, right now.
- Here's the thing.
Depriving myself,
uh... makes me absolutely nuts.
So, I think I'm gonna need to
loosen the reins a little bit.
What does that mean, loosen the reins?
That means...
I'm done dieting, Kate.
But I still support you 100%.
(chuckling): Um... how?
Like, we were supposed
to do this together?
Or like, I agreed to go out with you
because you were gonna lose the weight
- for me. And...
- and I did.
I lost some of the weight. And if
I gain it back, I will lose it again.
All right? You are not alone in this.
When we are together,
I will eat the way that you eat.
I swear. I swear on
this bag of Cool Ranch...
which is...
way more disgusting than
I remembered, by the way.
I just don't know how
this is gonna work.
Then I'll show you. All right? Tonight.
We'll go to dinner.
We will eat sensibly, hmm?
We will talk as always.
We will laugh as always,
all right? We'll still be us, I promise.
Okay?
(rock song playing)
- Hey.
- Hey, congrats.
Heard you got your own room.
Yeah. (chuckles)
What's up with you?
- Nothing.
- Randall.
Why does he hate me so much?
Kevin doesn't hate you.
You guys are just so intense
with each other, you know?
Try lightening things up a little.
Joke around with him more.
You know Mom is gonna
kill you if she sees you
putting on all that makeup, right?
(chuckles)
Pop-Tarts
and Yoo-Hoo.
Breakfast of champions.
- What do you want?
- I just came to see your dungeon.
- I mean, your digs.
- I think it's cool.
Yeah... totally.
In a couple days you won't notice
that funky mildew, And the asbestos.
I'd give it at least a year
till it's imbedded in your lungs.
Randall, can you please
just get out of here, man?
Look, I came down here
to get away from you.
- Dude, I was just joking.
- Are you deaf?
I said get out.
(exhales) Get a life.
♪ ♪
♪ Comes easy to you ♪
(sighs)
- You feeling anything yet?
- Mm...
(laughs)
- I...
- ♪ I'm walking down ♪
... was I supposed to eat
a quarter of the brownie,
or a quarter of the pan?
Yes, definitely.
(laughs)
(laughing): What? What's so funny?
- That's not the answer.
- It's not...
You did it right.
- (laughs)
- You ate it.
Shh, don't laugh so loud.
I don't want to wake
up the girls, okay? Ah.
(footsteps)
I knew I smelled chocolate.
Why are you guys eating
brownies in the basement?
- Can I have one?
- No.
These are adult brownies.
- (laughs)
- These are work brownies.
(whispers): Shut up.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna make
you some kid's brownies, okay?
Okay.
All right. Go ahead back upstairs.
Go to bed.
And be gentle getting back
in that bed. I don't want you
- to wake up your sister, okay?
- All right.
- Okay.
- Good night.
- Night.
- (laughing): You...
- Was she walking
- or was she floating?
- (laughing)
(laughter)
Oh, I feel bad they have to
crowd themselves on my account.
I know Annie must be
wanting her room back.
You're not the one who's
cramping anybody's style
in this house.
Okay. My office used to be my haven.
Now, it's Kevin's hamper.
(laughs)
(both laughing)
Yes.
I wish he would leave.
(both laughing)
Compliments of the owner.
Thank you very much, appreciate that.
See? Don't I get the hookup or what?
I haven't done so bad for myself, right?
You're the mayor of free shrimp.
(chuckles)
(sighs)
- All right, so, how's the play going?
- Hmm?
- The play.
- Mm.
- It's good. Ha!
- See you still
- working it, Pearson.
- Hey!
Donny frickin' Watson.
What's up, man, how you doing?
- I'm good, I'm good.
- Yeah?
Oh, man, I can't stay.
I got to take my girl to see Cats.
She even played
Grizabella in high school.
It's a whole thing but... (chuckles)
let's connect soon, yeah?
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'd like that very much.
You're looking good.
Donny Watson.
How you guys know each other?
Funny.
(chuckles)
What, are you serious?
- Yeah.
- He...
played my best friend on The Manny.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
Out of context...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I must have missed that episode.
He was a series regular,
actually, on the show.
For four years, he was a series regular.
Have you ever seen... my show?
- Of course I have. Yeah.
- Yeah?
What was my, uh,
what was my character's name?
Don't tell him. What was my
character's name on the show?
(whispering): Wow.
(sighs)
(laughs) Okay.
- Kevin.
- No, no, man, it's all right.
- Just finish the dinner, man.
- It's all right, it's all right,
it's all right.
Good talk.
(Toby laughs)
And so this, uh, dog
just keeps getting reincarnated.
(laughs) And so,
and so, it's like he...
I think he's a schna...
like a schnauzer, like,
poodle mix and he's running around town
trying to solve crimes, but
he keeps getting hit by cars.
Yeah, yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
And did you see what happened here?
You had chicken.
I had the chicken.
We are in this together.
- Right?
- Thank you.
Would you two like to
see our dessert tray?
Uh, no, thank you.
Walk away, fine sir.
Hey, wait.
He'll have a look.
I will?
Dude, I know you want it,
and if you don't have it
here, you're gonna go home,
you're gonna stuff your face and
you're gonna lie to me about it.
(sighs)
You'll have a full-on
food mistress and I...
But I will never love her
(whispering): the way that I love you.
This is not a joke.
- I'm being serious.
- Okay, all right, okay, okay.
How are we gonna make
this relationship work
if we're gonna keep things
from each other? Hmmm?
I'll just have to handle it.
- All right.
- Okay.
(announcer speaks
indistinctly over speakers)
- Hold both at the same time.
- You made it.
- Hi.
(sighs)
What's with, uh, all the beige?
(chuckles)
I'm trying to remain neutral.
- Yeah?
- Okay. Yeah.
(chuckles)
Wait, where's Kevin?
Uh...
Oh, there he is.
- Twelve.
Down, set, hut.
Thank you.
ANNOUNCER: We'd like to welcome
tonight's visiting team, Hanes Academy.
Now, let's go, McKinley Wildcats.
Rehearsal?
Rehearsal was good?
- Oh, Jack, honestly, it was amazing.
- Yeah?
Yeah, just being on stage again,
and singing and I missed it.
Yeah.
The smell of the
microphone alone was...
- The microphone has a smell?
- Hey, Jack!
Hey.
Big game for Kevin, huh?
Yeah, and with your Bobby
opening up holes in the backfield,
Kevin's not gonna
have to do a whole lot.
ANNOUNCER: All right, folks,
McKinley Middle School has possession
with visiting Hanes Academy on defense.
You can finish telling
me the rest later.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
♪ Won't you please talk to me? ♪
MAN: No, no, send him down there.
♪ If you'd just ♪
♪ Talk to me... ♪
Set... hut!
♪ Come on, come talk to me ♪
(whistle blows)
MAN: Go! Go, go, go!
♪ Can imagine the moment ♪
♪ Breaking out through the silence ♪
♪ All the things that
we both might say ♪
♪ And the heart, it
will not be denied ♪
Blue 42! Blue 42!
♪ Till we're both on
the same damn side ♪
Get down, set!
- ♪ All the barriers ♪
- Hut!
♪ Blown away... ♪
- Go, go, go, go!
- REBECCA: Go, go, go, go, go!
♪ Talk to me ♪
♪ Won't you please... ♪
(whistle blows)
♪ Come talk to me... ♪
What are they doing?
(crowd groaning, shouting)
MAN: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
All right, all right.
Hey!
Boys!
(whistle blowing)
♪ Come talk to me... ♪
Hey. Hey, come on, Kev. Would you stop?
No, it's all right, Randall. I'm
just gonna go back to my hotel.
- Leave me alone, all right?
- Look, hey, I'll give you a
thousand dollars right now if you
can tell me what I do for a living.
Uh, you're a Wall
Street guy, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, but
what does that mean?
Uh, you know, you do the-the...
the... like,
The Big Short. You do
the Ponzu schemes.
Oh, dude, it's ponzu
sauce, Ponzi schemes.
Whatever.
Look, the point is, you don't
know what I do, and that's fine.
What difference does it make
if I didn't watch The Manny?
You hated the show! You were
so ashamed of it, you quit.
Not at first. At first, I was
proud of that show, Randall.
And I invited every single
one of you to tapings.
Kate's the only one that came.
Well, she had to. You were paying her.
Come on, dude. That was funny.
What are you... ?
(Randall laughs)
Now that... that is funny.
That's great.
Replaced by another black man.
What the hell did you just say?
No. "Replaced by another black man."
- Hey, you tell me what that means.
- Don't worry about it, Randall.
No. Please, Kevin. Let's hear it, right?
What are you harboring? 'Cause God knows
I would really love to hear this.
You always got special treatment.
Because I'm black?
No, because you're
black and you're adopted.
Oh, yeah, hit the jackpot
with that combination.
- Couldn't have had it any easier.
- In our house, you did.
- With our mother, you did.
- Oh, right.
- Okay, here we go.
- Why can't you just admit it, man?
Admit what?
Just admit that you were more
important to her, and that
she wanted to make sure that you
felt special every single minute
- of every single day so that
- Yeah.
You wouldn't feel like the odd man out.
Well, gee, Kevin, I wonder why
she was worried about
me feeling that way?
What the hell does that mean?
- Just go back to your hotel.
- No. No, hold on.
Randall, hold... No.
What does that mean?
It means you treated me like a dog.
And just like a dog, I kept
coming back again and again,
just hoping for a scrap from you,
like a crumb of affection
or kindness or respect.
- Respect? You wanted my respect?
- Yeah.
Yeah, okay. No, you wanted
to show me up, Randall.
Which is what you did
every single chance you got.
- No, I did not.
- You showed me up!
I'm done with this conversation.
- Done with this conversation?
- In any other family,
- I would have been the star!
- Yeah, you know what, bro?
You're no star. That is a star.
Get your hands off me.
You don't push my body.
Don't touch me, okay? Don't touch me.
What is wrong with you?
Oh, my God. Don't put
your hands on my body.
(indistinct grunting and mumbling)
(groaning)
Is that... is that the Manny?
Ow! My face...
Kevin? Hey, Kevin?
- You're all right, man?
- Hey, Seth.
Do you... want me to call someone?
- Oh. Oh, it's, uh...
- (camera shutter clicks)
No.
This is my brother.
Oh. Hey, man.
Hey, Seth Meyers.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
(distant siren wailing)
- No. You know what? Let's go.
- Yeah.
I'm still black. Come
on, let's go. Yup, yup.
(grunts) Let's get the hell out of here.
I'm sorry I couldn't help more
with moving the heavy stuff.
That's okay.
Did you know I grew up in a
house with 14 people in it?
Hmm.
My parents, four
siblings, aunts, cousins,
three bedrooms.
- How many bathrooms?
- One.
Oh, my gosh,
when I was young, all I did
was dream of living alone.
- Like some hippie life, you know?
- (chuckles)
Like in some artist loft downtown.
No husband.
Definitely no kids.
So what happened?
I met your damn son.
(laughs) One look in his eyes,
he ruined everything. (laughs)
Me, I pretty much always lived alone.
Hmm.
Now I have Randall.
And you.
And the girls
to fall asleep to, wake up to every day.
I hope that's a good thing.
Mostly.
Makes me feel sad to die.
I love it when there's
a new moon like this.
"Splendid against the
night, the searchlights...
BOTH: ... the tracers' arcs,
and the red flare of bombs."
How do you know that?
It's in this book of poems
that Randall's had since he was a baby.
(chuckling): Oh, yeah, that's right.
The one I gave Rebecca back in the day.
Oh.
What?
What'd you say? I'm
feeling a little tired,
Beth, I think I'll...
Oh, hell no, you ain't
cancering your way
out of this one, old man.
- (William stammering)
- You better talk.
(warning beeps)
(door chimes)
(alarm chirps)
(plastic bag rustling)
(rustling continues)
(sighs)
Get your asses in the car.
We're gonna talk big-time at home.
(engine starts)
You're right.
Mom did favor me.
She did.
Showered me with attention.
Took my side more often than not.
And I ate every bit of her love up.
Ate it up like Pac-Man.
(laughs softly)
You know why?
Because the one person
I wanted it from the mo...
You know, back there with those people,
it's the first time in 36 years
you've said the words,
"He's my brother."
- Come on, Randall, that can't be...
- Claiming me.
My brother.
Well, then, that really sucks.
Rebecca has known who you
were for Randall's entire life?
Yes, that's right.
And she never told him?
- I don't know, Beth.
- Lied to him,
when he asked. Huh.
I got to tell him.
No. No, no, no, no.
Beth, you can't do that.
Oh, "Beth you can't do that"?
This is my husband.
This is my marriage.
I know, but the closeness
he has with his mom,
you tell him this, it'll destroy it.
(door closes)
Whoa, someone's high.
Good night.
- Night.
- Good night.
Uh...
You and my wife got high together?
That's pretty cool.
(chuckles) Good for you.
All right, I'm gonna head up to bed.
Not that way; she moved you.
What do you mean, she moved
me? She moved me where?
(sighs) (laughs)
Oh, back in the basement.
- No, we'll move you back upstairs.
- No, come... hey, listen.
I should be getting out
of your hair soon anyway.
You know, until then, this is
actually a pretty sweet set-up.
There's no bathroom down here.
I can walk a flight of stairs.
(sighs) Well, uh... (clicks tongue)
- It's been a day.
- Yeah.
Night.
- Hey, uh, Randall.
- Hmm?
Uh, do you want to...
Do you want to hang out down
here for little bit with me?
We could, uh, turn
the TV on or something.
Uh-huh. For a little while.
- Yeah?
- Why not?
- Cool.
- Yeah.
Uh, Rebecca, this is Beth.
Yeah, um, so William just told
me something really interesting
about the two of you.
So, yeah, I'm gonna need
you to call me back, okay?
Right away.
As soon as you get this message.
Okay, bye.
KEVIN (on the TV): ♪ Manny's gonna
buy you a mockingbird. ♪
- You hate me, don't you?
- (TV audience laughter)
(Randall laughs)
I told you to heat the
bottle, not hit the bottle.
(TV audience laughter)
You want me to open up
that big bottle of wine
you've been saving for ten years.
Manny say, "What?!" (audience laughter)
♪ ♪
Hey, you never finished telling me
about your rehearsal.
It's okay; I'm tired.
We can talk about it tomorrow.
Okay.
Hey, can you turn the light out, babe?
I just realized we didn't
eat dinner tonight, Jack.
(sighs) I had a pretty big
lunch; I'm good.
Well, I'm gonna go make
myself something then.
The light, babe.
♪ ♪
♪ I listen to the wind ♪
♪ To the wind of my soul ♪
♪ Where I'll end up ♪
♪ Well, I think only
God really knows ♪
KEVIN: Mom!
♪ I've sat upon the setting sun ♪
What?
I can't turn the washing machine off.
I think it's possessed.
Kev, you know you can always
go back to your old room with Randall.
♪ But never, never, never ♪
♪ I listen to my words ♪
♪ But they fall far below ♪
♪ I let my music take me ♪
♪ Where my heart wants to go ♪
Oh, my God.
(laughing): This is the best
washing machine in the
whole world. Mm-hmm.
I'm actually,
I'm turned on by this washing machine.
- Well, I can show you turned on.
- (shrieks and laughs)
(calling): Jack, help.
- It's leaking everywhere!
- (kids exclaiming)
Kids, get the buckets.
- Okay.
- (kids screaming and squealing)
This is bail out!
(kids yelling)
JACK: Okay, kids.
Oh!
Washing machine
is officially cooked, baby.
Nah, she's still got some life in her.
At least six more cycles.
Jack, we have three infants.
We're going to be doing
six cycles by noon.
We can do it. You wash and I'll fold.
♪ I let my music take me ♪
♪ Where my heart wants to go ♪
♪ I swam upon the devil's lake ♪
Baby, one day, I'm gonna buy you
the best washing machine in the world.
(chuckles)
♪ I'll never make the same mistake ♪
♪ I'll never, never, never. ♪
-- Synced and corrected by ChrisKe --
-- www.addic7ed.com --