Previously on This Is Us...
- My water just broke.
- Yep.
- DOCTOR: First male is out.
- You hear that, babe?
- We got a boy.
- Something's... not right...
Your wife is in distress, Jack.
I found him. My father.
Randall Peasing. I'm
your biological son.
- Toby.
- Kate.
So, you want to be fat friends?
(laughs)
This show is so bad!
Everything's fake!
I quit.
We lost the third baby, Jack.
I'm very sorry.
I like to think that you took
the sourest lemon that life has to offer
and turned it into something
resembling lemonade.
♪
Guys, breakfast!
Let's go!
Mom, Webster told me to shut up.
- Shut up!
- REBECCA: Do not call him that.
KEVIN: Everyone else always does.
REBECCA: I don't care
what everybody else does.
Randall is your little brother;
you have to have his back.
No, sweetheart. No, no, no.
Your breakfast is over there, Kate.
Thank you.
Baby, we talked about this.
Morning.
REBECCA: Good morning.
Yuck.
REBECCA: Jack!
It's fine. It's fine.
- Did you get fruit?
- Yes.
Hey.
Do you need me to show
you where the coffee is?
Oh, I know where the coffee is.
Okay. Good.
RANDALL: Just give me...
Okay. Dad's off. Deep breaths.
And...
- First came...
- Me!
- And Dad said...
- Gee!
- And then came...
- Me!
- And Mom said...
- Whee!
- And then came...
- Me.
- And we said...
- That's three.
- Big Three?
- CHILDREN: Big Three!
(children chattering)
Do you need me to show
you where my mouth is?
No. I know where it is.
Oh. Good.
- Bye.
Kate, all the fruit, please.
♪ Both dirty, both mean ♪
♪ Yes, and the dream was just the same ♪
♪ And I dreamed your dream for you ♪
♪ And now your dream is real ♪
♪ How can you look at me ♪
♪ Good job. ♪
♪ As if I was just another
one of your deals? ♪
♪ When you can fall for... ♪
You know, I just did bi's,
tri's and left testicle.
I'm really starting to get
some definition on that guy.
- Not funny.
- It's fun... (laughs)
- It's not funny.
- Come on. Come on, can we go?
We've been here long enough.
- No...
- Kate. Come on, Kate...
Come on.
(sighs)
How are you losing weight and I'm not?
Can I be honest with you?
Yeah, please.
I think I'm just taking this
more seriously than you are.
(laughs)
Come on. Let's go. (laughing)
Worst place in the world!
♪
Baby?
Yeah.
I want to ask you something, but...
I'm not sure how to say it.
Since when do we censor
ourselves with each other?
No, I know, it's...
You know, Beth, we've been
together for 17 years.
That's almost half our lives.
I know your face,
your hands, your soul
better than I know my own.
You don't have to censor yourself.
Ever. Not with me.
What was your question?
How long is your crack-addict
biological daddy
gonna be sleeping in our
six-year-old daughter's bedroom?
- Damn.
- I know, right?
You need to censor yourself, woman.
- It's just got real.
- (exhales)
(chuckles)
But Randall, he's been
here for three days.
And the girls still think he's
your 70-year-old co-worker
who likes sleepovers.
(exhales) What's our endgame here?
Beth, the man has Stage
4 stomach cancer.
I'm just trying to get him to
his first doctor's appointment,
make sure he's gonna
make it past Thursday.
Then we can take the rest from there.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
And he's a former crack
addict, by the way.
Oh, well, then he can stay forever.
- See? You didn't even think about that.
- (giggling)
- ♪
- So now Rebecca's all worked up
because the kids at school
are calling him "Webster."
You know, the black kid the white
family adopts on that show?
- I love that show.
- Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know, Miguel, it's just...
It's hard to see the woman I
married sometimes, you know?
♪
What?
- Nothing.
Nothing. You... I'm your, I'm
your best friend. You're venting.
Best friends let best friends
vent without judgment.
I'm not even gonna say
anything about it being 5:03
and that being your second bourbon.
- I appreciate that.
- The thing is...
your wife is, like, the
gold standard of wives.
- I know, Miguel.
- I mean, she's smart,
funny, beautiful,
- great personality, greater ass...
- Easy.
She's raising not one, not
two, but three eight-year-olds
while you sit here
drinking not one, not two,
but soon to be three bourbons by 5:05.
I know all this, Miguel.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Because as your loyal best friend,
it is my duty to remind you
of what you've got there.
You married way, way above your station.
I'd be careful not to give
her a reason to notice.
Oh, my father, he
wasn't a very nice man.
He wasn't like your father.
Why not?
Well, your father, he's good.
He doesn't have vices.
You know what a vice is?
A vice is like a bad habit,
like bitin' your nails, but worse.
- Like drugs?
- Yeah, that's right.
That was my vice.
Where would you get drugs?
Well, that's an interesting
question, Tess.
Let's see...
- Well, the cocaine I used to...
- That's good. - Okay, kids.
Let's get ready for school, okay?
Come on.
Hey, so I got good news.
I got you an appointment with
an immunotherapy specialist.
- Oh, that's not necessary.
- No, it was nothing.
Guy at my firm had an in.
This guy is doing some really
ground-breaking stuff.
Thank you; that's very kind.
You got it.
Oh, hey, come on, baby.
I need you to take one big,
deep breath for me, okay?
(inhales)
Oh, that's good.
All right.
My vice is asthma.
(Randall chuckles)
His is cocaine.
All right, so let's get our jackets.
- Okay.
- Go and get your coat.
BETH: Honey, here, take your lunch.
Okay.
(exhales) Here you go.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I know they're too young
to talk about cocaine.
I just...
I feel like six is a hair
young for cocaine...
Yeah, but seven... We let
them try it at seven.
(chuckles) BETH: Um, so...
what are you up to today, William?
Oh, nothing much. The usual.
I've really enjoyed being here.
Being around those girls...
it fills me in a way...
In a way I surely don't deserve, so...
I hope you'll let me know when
I've overstayed my welcome.
You know, don't be silly.
We're happy to have you.
Uh...
I was wondering if I could be so forward
as to ask you for a few
dollars for the bus.
Oh, sure. Sure.
Where you going?
Oh, you know, just around.
(sighs)
♪ Now because I'm so fly,
they just get to know why ♪
♪ Got to stick to what I do
best, I'm like "Oh, hi" ♪
♪ We've been trying to do soft
tens with aloha, aloha... ♪
(sighs)
Victor. My man.
How you been?
- I've been Hector.
- Right on. Yeah.
Yeah, and I'm sorry. I
got a lot on my mind.
I don't know if you heard the news.
I left the show.
Yeah. I'm gonna meet
with the team today.
You know, we're gonna
strategize, talk next steps.
Lots to figure out, lots to talk about.
It's exciting. Exciting times
for everyone involved.
(phone ringing in the distance)
LANIE: Kevin,
do you remember where you
were when I found you?
Yeah, sure. I was, uh, in
an improv comedy troupe.
That's right.
And when I saw your first show,
do you know what I thought
to myself, Kevin?
- No, I-I...
- I thought
to myself... I've done it.
I have found
the least funny person
on the entire planet.
Okay.
But I saw something there,
so I took you on.
And I got you the commercials,
got you the soaps,
eventually got you a job paying you
almost three million dollars a year,
making you so famous that
you could wear a ski cap
when it is 80 degrees outside,
and no one would say a damn thing.
Okay, Lanie...
Take off that hat.
Okay.
What's done is done, right?
I mean, you know, can't we just...
move on?
Brian... speak.
You're contractually bound to
the show for another two years.
Okay.
All right, and if I refuse?
Listen to me very carefully, Kevin.
The network owns you.
They can sue you for damages.
They could bankrupt you.
And even if someone slipped a chill pill
into their collective drink,
you would still be
legally unable to work
for the next two years.
That's for any studio, any network.
Television or film.
So...
that's the good news.
Now here's the part
you're not gonna like.
KEVIN: She's throwing this big...
Hollywood party at her
house tonight, right?
The network president's
gonna be there, everyone.
I'm supposed to show up, get
down on my hands and knees
and beg to be the Manny again.
Yeah.
They own me, Sis.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Well, I do, and you did it already.
Do you need me to show you
the video on YouTube?
No.
Kevin, I've known you your whole life.
Well, except for those two
minutes at the beginning.
You've succeed at everything
you've ever tried.
So here's what's gonna happen.
Okay? You're gonna go to that party,
and you're gonna march
up to that network guy,
and you're gonna tell him, "Manny out!"
- Mm-hmm.
- Manny out?
Manny out. Manny out!
Well, you're not supposed
to say the... Okay.
Manny out! That's good.
(both laughing)
- Let me ask you a question.
- Mm.
What did I ever do those first
two minutes without you?
Oh, you cried, and you crapped a lot.
- (muffled laugh)
- Sounds about right. Yeah.
So you're coming to the party,
though, tonight with me, right?
- The fancy Hollywood party?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah.
Kevin, I... Okay, f...
- I don't even have anything to wear.
- Kate.
I need you there, okay?
It's gonna be fun.
- Is it? Is-is...?
- It's gonna be a blast.
Yes, it's gonna be a blast. Manny out.
- Kevin, here... here's the...
- Manny out.
Or maybe Manny out!
Whatever... whatever works.
♪
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
- Nothing can live...
- (Randall sighs)
All right, little mamas,
five-minute warning
- till teeth brushing.
- But...
It's not open for discussion.
Rain, the source of all...
- Hey, William.
- William!
Hi, everybody.
You're home late. Everything okay?
Yeah, yes. I'm fine.
Just a long day.
I think I may just go lay myself down
for the night.
Well... night.
Night.
From the ashes rises the phoenix...
Okay, monsters, these teeth
aren't gonna brush themselves.
(groans)
Oh, God. Hey, girl,
what you been eating?
Ice cream.
You scream? I'm gonna scream
if I got to carry you up these stairs.
(groans)
You're too heavy.
MARSHA: Guess the thing I really need
to say out loud to everyone is, well...
I'm down three pounds in one week.
(laughs, screams)
(applause)
Oh, guys, come on. Stop.
Stop. You don't...
Well, okay, fine, keep going.
I'm-I'm so happy. I'm... (laughs)
Well, I had a crap day at work,
so I stopped at Wendy's.
And I was about to eat in the car,
which is... all you know is my thing.
The second I left the
drive-through, I threw
ten dollars' worth of Wendy's
out of my moving car,
and I went home, and I had a salad.
(laughs)
WOMAN: I know I'm ridiculous. I
know I'm a joke to you guys.
I know I have body distortion
issues or whatever it's called,
but it's real.
It's brutal.
I wish I could show you guys what I
see when I look in the mirror...
Oh, for God's sake.
Madison, you weigh 105 pounds.
If you feel like a fat girl
when you look in the mirror,
why don't you step a damn scale?
And when the scale reads
"One, zero, five,"
you know that you're not fat.
And Laurie,
that Wendy's story, okay.
I'm sorry, but you're just a litterer.
You're just a littering damn litterer.
Uh...
well, that feels like a
good place for a break.
(indistinct chatter)
You hulked out on a bunch of fatties.
You're not going to make me laugh, Toby.
What's up, kid?
My brother is making me go to
this nightmare Hollywood party
at his agent's house tonight.
Yeah, I went to buy a dress,
and nothing fit, literally nothing.
Everything looks terrible.
I'm not losing weight.
I'm starving.
I don't know.
That's what's up, I guess.
Okay.
Hey, your brother's agent
is Lanie Shultz, right?
Yeah.
Kate, Lanie Shultz
is one of the most powerful agents
in what I like to call... show business.
I heard
that Deadpool was her idea.
Or maybe it was Hamilton.
I get those two confused. Anyway,
Kate, you are so taking
me to that party.
- Uh-uh.
- Mm-hmm.
No. I don't want you to see me there.
Like, I am at my worst at those things.
Kate, you are at your worst
when you are eviscerating
the anorexic lady,
and I am still standing here.
- (sighs)
- Look,
we have had three lunches
and four dinner dates.
We have made out seven times
and heavy-petted twice.
Our plane is rapidly approaching
the boyfriend-girlfriend zone,
and, I, for one, am preparing
myself for landing.
But I need to know that everything
isn't gonna always be about our weight.
All right? We need to be able
to cut loose at parties.
We need to get really dressed
up, we need to have sex.
I just slipped that in
there very casually
because I think that's something
that we should start doing very soon.
So, Kate, I am asking you,
please, for the love of God,
can we spend one fat-free night
at the house of the lady
who came up with the idea
for Deadpool and/or Hamilton?
Is that a... is that a smile?
(laughs)
Is that...? Yes, that's
a yes and a smile.
All right, hey, guys,
Bruce Banner's back.
Everything's fine. The Hulk is gone.
Let the healing continue.
Sorry about that.
Are you comfy?
Okay, sweetness.
Good night. I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Mom?
Yeah, babe?
I only ate fruit today.
(sighs)
You know I just want you
to be healthy, right?
And I want you to be happy.
Are you happy?
For the most part.
Well, then, I'm happy, too.
Tell you what. How about
you and I find a healthy
balance together?
How does that sound?
- All right.
- RANDALL: Shut up!
- KEVIN: You shut up, Webster.
- RANDALL: Stop calling me names!
Goodnight. Boys?
Uh-uh. Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, stop. To your beds right now.
- (boys groan)
- Now.
Okay, who am I yelling at first?
(sighs)
Kev, bud, what is the deal? Why
are you always so hard on him?
Everybody thinks it's weird
that we're brothers.
You know it doesn't
matter what people think.
He is your little brother, Kevin.
You have to be there for one another.
Do you hear me?
(sighs)
Yes.
I love you.
(sighs)
Can you force him be nice?
I'll see what I can do.
Hey.
Promise me you'll always be good.
I'll see what I can do.
(soft chuckle)
I love you.
Now get some sleep, please.
No more fighting.
Don't make me come back in here.
Good night, I love you.
(sighs)
- Hi, baby.
Did I miss putting them down?
Just by an hour.
Well, I was...
I was... oh, shopping.
I was shopping.
I know...
(clears throat)
I know we haven't been
on the same page lately.
That we just got to get
back on track, baby.
So...
consider this a... way-too-expensive
peace offering.
I think we've been more than off track.
Hey, how do you think
we're doing so far?
At parenting?
- I...
- 'Cause I think we're at a six.
On a sliding scale, one through ten,
I think we're at a six and I
think I'm being generous.
- Bec...
- Seven, fine,
but only because there
are three of them.
- Baby, I...
- And the thing is,
I'm trying really hard
to get us to a nine.
Because they are cute kids, and
they deserve nine-parents.
And, the thing is, I feel
like I'm there, Jack.
I feel like I'm operating at a nine.
Because I do individualized lunches
and I do individualized
tuck-ins for each kid
so nobody feels gypped.
And...
(scoffs)
When you're home, and you're you,
you're way better than I am.
You're a ten when you're you, Jack.
But you're getting home later and later
- and when you do come home, you're...
- Bec, what are you saying?
The drinking has to stop.
You have to reign it in, baby,
because I won't have it in my house.
You won't have it in your house.
- I won't.
So if it's a problem, fix it.
Be a man, and fix it.
Because I'm done letting
you lower our score.
Damn.
- Yeah?
- (chuckling): Yeah.
Hell to the yeah.
- Thanks.
- (chuckling)
You look dapper.
Ah, show business.
Oh, great, you're, uh...
We got to go, you know?
- 'Cause we're gonna be late.
- Okay.
You're wearing that?
Yeah.
That's great.
- You look awesome.
- Oh, is the hat too much?
The hat is everything.
Yeah, that's a real peacock feather.
(chuckles) Come on, show business!
(people talking
indistinctly and laughing)
♪ Stuck to the wall ♪
♪ You think you really
know where we wanna go ♪
Hey, go, okay? And I'm
right here if you need me.
Okay?
- Manny out.
- TOBY: Go get 'em.
You and I are crushing that dance floor.
Let's go. Come on, let's go.
♪ Groovin' ♪
♪ My record's spinning with the DJ ♪
♪ He lets my song play ♪
♪ From night until day ♪
(giggling)
(laughing): Oh, no!
Come on! Come on.
(music and people's voices fade)
(somber music plays)
TOBY (echoes): Kate.
Kate.
- (party music resumes)
- Kate.
All right, come on, come on,
we're getting you drunk.
- Come on, yup. Time to get drunk.
- Let's just go.
- (phone rings, then machine beeps)
- Jack, It's Miguel.
It's late, so I'm leaving
you a message at the office
in case I miss you in the morning.
Feel like I overstepped before.
Um, you know I love you,
you know I love you guys.
Hell... (chuckles)
I'm jealous of your
relationship, if anything.
Uh, I shouldn't have said
anything at the bar.
Now I'm just overdoing it.
Uh...
Okay. Bye.
BETH: Hey.
You need to get some sleep, it's late.
You've been up since,
like, 4:00 this morning.
No, I know. Just five more minutes.
(machine beeps)
- (treadmill slows to a stop)
- Hey.
Shower. Sleep.
Now.
You shower quick, you can work off that
last five minutes a different way.
(panting)
I am so happy that we
could all get together.
You know, work through, and...
(stammers): and... Kevin
just feels awful...
I'm so sorry, this is whole
thing, Lanie, is ridiculous.
I mean...
Mr. Manning.
I'm truly grateful for everything
that your network has done for me, I am.
But please let me go with God, sir.
The way I handled myself,
I mean, that was wrong, I'll be
the first one to admit that.
That-that was wrong.
But can't we all, at this point,
just, sort of, you know...
sort of move on, right?
You're a good kid, Kevin.
- I appreciate your honesty.
- Thank you.
The show, it's a solid performer, but
it's not the biggest thing on my network.
Without Lanie telling me,
would I have known you
from one of these waiters
passing around the chicken skewers?
- Probably not.
- Really?
I really don't care what
happens behind the scenes
on my third-rated sitcom.
You know what I do care about?
KEVIN: Mm-mm.
St. Maarten, Kevin.
I'm building a home in St. Maarten
and in two years I'm going to retire,
and my favorite wife and I
are going to move there.
Until then,
I plan on just drifting
through these two years
as painlessly and
drama-free as possible.
Like I'm on morphine, Kevin,
that's how I'll be drifting
through those years.
Okay.
That's... great, you know?
Go with God.
You know, the thing is...
excuse me darling.
(Lanie chuckles)
Recasting the lead on a hit sitcom,
isn't exactly drifting on
morphine, now is it, Kevin?
So unfortunately, my boy, you're
not gonna be leaving the show.
If you do, I'll be forced to
Nagasaki your life and career.
Hey, have you ever heard of the
actor, uh, Taylor Jennings?
I'm not familiar with the name.
I Nagasaki'd him.
So take the money, kid.
Ride out the next couple
years, all right?
Otherwise, I'll make you
a bigger laughingstock
than you already are.
Deal?
I'm sorry, I'm j... I'm gonna go, uh...
my sister's here, I'm
gonna go check on her.
It's his twin sister.
Big girl.
♪ Yeah, we're all about a good time ♪
♪ Yeah, we're all about a good life ♪
(Toby laughs, glass splashes in pool)
(giggles)
- You love drunk Kate.
- I love drunk Kate.
Wait, what?
- Woo!
- Hey.
Hey!
How'd it go? I'm wasted.
Not good.
Good? Oh, my God, that's great.
No, no, no, no, not good.
It did not... I don't
know what I'm gonna do.
- (imitates fishing reel)
- Uh-oh!
- Gone fishing.
- You caught a whopper!
Uh-oh. (grunting)
Come reel me in, got to reel me in.
(grunts) It's my first time fishing.
- Won't be his last.
- Well...
♪ Yeah, we're all about a good time ♪
- ♪ Yeah, we're all about a good life. ♪
- Kev!
Which little monster's
standing at my door?
It's okay, I'm way too old
to be scared of monsters.
I think it's time you and I had a talk.
(indistinct conversations)
(bus door opens,
children chatter, laugh)
I can't wait until the
next day of school starts.
Hey, everyone, it's Webster!
(children laughing and taunting)
BULLY: Kev,
come on, Kevin, ditch Webster.
Let's go.
Come on.
(phone vibrating)
(phone beeps)
Hey.
Hey, uh... is it too late out there?
I know you're usually up late, right?
- No, I was just, uh...
- (clears throat)
catching up on some paperwork.
Sweet, uh...
Hey, listen, I-I know I've
owed you a phone call
since everything went down,
it's been crazy out here, just...
you know.
No, it's all good.
Kate's kept me up to speed.
Good.
They said they're not gonna
let me out of the show, man.
And I...
I don't know what I'm gonna do, like...
they locked me in for two
more years, maybe more.
Damn.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I was kind of hoping you'd tell me.
Oh, because you care what I think?
Because I care what
everyone thinks, man.
You know that.
I was not a very good
brother to you, was I?
No, you weren't.
But you've still got time.
KATE (giggling): Hey!
Yeah, uh...
Anyway, look, it's getting
late, man, I, you know...
I probably should go.
It's, uh... Kate's here, it's Randall.
- Oh, hey, Randall!
- Hey.
Anyway, yeah, I-I should probably, uh...
I got to go back inside and
sell my soul to the network,
like the whore that I am.
Hey, Kev.
Deep breath, okay?
Come on, man. First came...
Me.
And Dad said...
"Gee."
- And then came...
- Me!
And Mom said...
- "Whee!"
- And then came...
- Me.
- And they said...
"That's three."
- Big Three!
- ALL: Big Three!
KATE (laughing): Yeah.
You good?
Uh... yeah.
Yeah, I'm good, I'm good.
- Kevin?
- Yeah?
Mom and Dad didn't raise no whores.
Except briefly, during
Kate's eyeliner phase.
(chuckles)
(sniffs) Yeah.
Night, little brother.
Night, big brother.
(phone beeps)
Hon?
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Can I cut to the chase?
It's your meeting.
(chuckles)
Eight years ago, I was, um,
pregnant for the first time.
And Randall was vying for
partner at his firm.
We'd just bought this house on faith,
even though it needed a lot of work,
even though we couldn't
afford it whatsoever.
Then Randall made partner.
He did all the work
on the house himself,
so we didn't have to spend a penny.
And he made sure I didn't lift
a finger during my pregnancy.
He's a good man.
No, he's not good.
He's perfect.
Problem is, he stopped sleeping.
And then one morning, I
was in the bathroom,
and he called out to me.
And he was confused, you know?
He was confused because he...
couldn't see anything.
My husband... my mountain of a man...
could literally no longer see
things through his eyes.
It was as if 28 years
of being that perfect
had all caught up to him that morning.
And he, um...
he pulled himself out of it.
He self-corrected,
'cause that's what my man does.
Randall is not free of vice, William.
His vice is his goodness.
It's his compulsive drive
to be perfect.
It's why I love him...
but it's also why I have to
protect him sometimes, you know?
So now, I'm gonna have to
ask you a couple questions,
questions he would probably
be too polite to ask himself.
Ask away.
(inhales sharply) The money you borrow.
You use it for the bus?
Yes.
Where do you go?
You're gone all day, every day.
My place in Philadelphia,
it's a long ride.
Why?
Are you using drugs?
- Are you getting drugs?
- Mm-mm. No.
Are you really sick?
Yes, I am.
Beth, I said it before,
and I really meant it:
if I'm overstaying my welcome,
I wish you would just say it.
William, you are overstaying...
RANDALL: Beth.
What are you doing?
Somebody has to ask the
questions here, baby...
It's a cat.
I have a cat.
It's all I really have.
His name's Clooney.
One of those ironic names,
'cause he's a pretty ugly cat.
I go back and forth to feed him.
Three hours on the bus each day.
Why wouldn't you just
tell us you had a cat?
Nah.
The little one has asthma
and I knew if I brought up the cat,
you'd tell me to bring it,
that would cause problems.
And I don't want to cause any problems,
'cause if I cause problems,
I'd have to leave.
And... and I don't want to leave.
Six months ago, some doctor
told me I had three to live.
But for some reason, I
don't feel so bad lately.
Maybe to do with this house.
I don't know.
Truth is, I'd never thought I'd
have anything to care about again
besides an ugly cat, so...
Well, now I feel like a bitch.
(Randall laughs)
(William chuckles)
It's not funny. It's not.
(chuckling) It's not funny.
(laughing continues)
I'm about...
****
Mm.
Are you gonna hold my hair for me, Toby?
No. I-I'm still gonna be at this party,
trying to bang a Gilmore Girl.
(laughs)
Well, go for both.
Gil-more the Gil-merrier.
It's always gonna be about
the weight for me, Toby.
(sniffs)
It's been my story ever
since I was a little girl.
And every moment that I'm
not thinking about it,
I'm thinking about it.
Like...
will this chair hold me?
Will this dress fit me?
And if I ever get pregnant, would...
will anyone ever notice?
It's just at the core of who
I am, it's just deep inside,
and eight tequila shots can only
mask that for a couple hours.
- So...
- I know.
And it was ten tequila shots,
but I... I get it. I know.
And just for the record,
um, this dress is fitting you
in all the right places.
(purring)
- This old thing?
- Uh-huh.
I mean, I-I just threw it on.
Oh, you just threw it on? Mm-hmm.
I didn't even think about it.
(chuckles)
(sighs)
There he is.
I told 'em to go screw themselves.
And what'd they say?
A lot of mean, scary things.
I'm gonna do theater.
You know?
I'm moving to New York.
(whispering): Show business.
(sighs) What are you doing out here?
I don't like sleeping far away from you.
No more drinking.
- You can't just stop...
- I can.
For you, I can.
I will.
(sighs)
You know, when I was a little boy,
I didn't know what I wanted
to be when I grew up.
(inhales, exhales deeply)
Adults always ask little kids that.
You know?
I never had a good answer.
Not until... not until I was 28.
Till the day that I met you.
That's when I knew exactly what
I wanted to be when I grew up:
I wanted to be the man
that made you happy.
(sighs)
You make me happy.
Not always.
(scoffs) Not lately.
From here on out, I'm gonna
be an 11 for you, baby.
No...
Screw that.
I'm gonna be a 12 for
you, from here out.
I'll be an 11 for the kids,
but you get a 12.
Do you forgive me?
You slept outside our bedroom
door like a Labrador.
Of course I forgive you.
Can I still give you my gift?
If you insist.
♪ Come down off your throne ♪
Do you like it?
♪ And leave your body alone ♪
I got a moon because of... Our song.
Yeah.
♪ Somebody must change ♪
I'm never gonna take it off.
♪ You are reason I've
been waiting so long ♪
♪ Somebody holds the key ♪
Do you like it?
Does it look good?
- ♪ But I'm near the end ♪
- It's beautiful.
Thank you.
♪ I just ain't got the time ♪
Mm.
♪ And I'm wasted ♪
How much time we have
till the kids get up?
I don't care about the kids.
(moaning) Pile drive!
- (yelling)
- (laughing)
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Come down on your own ♪
♪ And leave your body alone ♪
♪ Somebody must change ♪
(laughing): Daddy, stop! Daddy, stop!
If you want to sleep in, you
have to pay the tickle tax!
WILLIAM (laughing): Tickle tax.
(Randall sighs)
- (timer dings)
- Oh. All right, come on, honey.
- It's time to take care of...
- WILLIAM: Here you go.
♪ But I'm near the end ♪
- (inhaler puffs)
- WILLIAM: Good.
Big breath.
- Good.
- (doorbell rings)
You expecting somebody?
- ♪ And I'm wasted ♪
- No.
♪ And I can't find my way home ♪
TESS: Grandma and Grandpa are here!
I'll be in my room.
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
- ♪ But I can't find my way home ♪
- Hey, Mom.
Hey, Miguel.
♪ But I can't find my way home. ♪
Hey.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -