CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(murmuring voices)
Where’s Reverend Lovejoy?
He’s never been late
for Christmas service.
Maybe he’s cheating on us
with the Episcopalians.
Look at ’em, with their
bright, airy narthex
and light, flaky Eucharist.
I wouldn’t mind dipping
my hand in their font.
("Jingle Bell Rock"
ring tone plays)
Christ is born;
who’s on my horn?
Bad news, Ned.
There’s been
a horrible train wreck.
So many little plastic
Christmases ruined.
(gasps)
You want me to deliver
the Christmas sermon?
Oh! I feel like I’m
born again again!
(fanfare plays)
Ooh!
Now, don’t be nervous, Ned.
You’ve practiced this so many
times in the shower.
Aah! Paper cut!
Ooh...
Now there’s no one
to deliver the sermon.
Did anyone order a hero?
(humming nonchalantly)
Mmm!
(clears throat)
Okay, Christmas... Christmas...
You know how your paper boy
always sends you
a Christmas card
with his home address on it?
What’s up with that?
PAPER BOY: I wanted you
to tip me!
No tip till they bring back
Hagar the Horrible.
That’s not
my decision.
Oh, it’s never
anybody’s decision.
Anyhoo...
I’d like to tell you all
a little story I call
"The First Christmas."
(murmuring)
I, for one,
am dying to hear it.
A carpenter named Joseph
was about to get some frankly
preposterous news.
Uh, Joseph,
you know I have never
lain with a man.
(scoffs)
Tell me about it.
And yet, I am with child.
A pregnant virgin?!
That’s every man’s
worst nightmare.
(angelic choir chants)
Hail Mary, full of grace.
That’s not all she’s full of.
Quiet, you.
Mary, you carry in your womb
the Son of God,
who will grow up to become
King of the Jews.
So, not a doctor...
Well, he will be able
to heal the sick.
But nothing to hang on the wall.
(groans)
King Herod, we three
Wise Men come bearing gifts
for the King of the Jews.
We bring gold...
Frankincense...
And myrrh,
which I am re-gifting,
’cause who needs myrrh?
Here’s the tag.
Thank you.
Which one should I open first?
ALL:
Hmm...
(chuckles)
This is awkward.
Uh... the King of the Jews
we seek is, uh, a newborn child.
Find this pretender to my throne
and bring him to me.
Uh, now you wouldn’t hurt
the little boychik.
Of course not.
Kings don’t hurt babies.
Giant pointy swords hurt babies.
(stammering)
Good King Herod!
Except you don’t really
have the "good," so...
what do you have,
really, then?
("Away in a Manger" playing)
INNKEEPER:
Now, don’t you worry.
I got plenty of rooms
at my inn.
All with brand-new carpeting.
I think my water
just broke!
You can have the barn.
Now feel free to come
by the main house
for breakfast.
There won’t be any.
(sharp, rhythmic breaths)
(cattle lows)
Just keep pushing, sweetie.
The doctor will be
here any second.
Shalom, everybody.
(laughing)
I’ve got some
very good news.
Caesar just invented
the cesarean.
Get him out of here!
("Silent Night" playing)
I knew I’d like him, but I
never dreamed I’d adore him.
I’ve got the Messiah’s nose.
Give it back.
He’ll kill us all!
(chuckles)
He looks just
like his dad.
Not you!
Oh! I’m not the father,
I’m not a Wise Man, I’m nothing.
This is the worst
Christmas ever.
Hmm... maybe a little toot
off the old wine skin’ll
cheer me up.
(boinging)
Oh! My wine turned into water!
Who could have performed
such a cruel miracle?
(chuckling)
Why, you little...!
(thunder rumbling)
Joseph, no!
He has to stay alive
till he’s 33,
when he’ll be renounced
by his friends
and crucified.
Huh?!
Sorry, kid.
(baby crying)
Oh! Anytime anyone
suffers in the world,
he starts crying again.
Can you do something?
Me? But I’m watching
the Orange Bowl.
Now!
(crying)
Oh!
(chuckling)
-(bleating)
-Oh!
(chuckling continues)
Hmm... you like
physical comedy, eh?
Nyuk, nyuk, nyuk, nyuk...
A... wise man, eh?
Pick two!
-(boinging)
-Oh!
(laughing)
Why, I oughta...
Hmm... hmm... hmm...
Now, hold still.
(groans)
(muttering)
(laughs, then yawns)
Oh... I think
this nontraditional household
just might make it.
(sighs)
Jesus, Mary and Joseph--
we got a great family.
Now, let’s get some sleep.
Herod is coming
for the child.
Manger danger!
(loud grunting)
The kid you’re looking
for is in there.
The other tenants
have been complaining
about the incessant swaddling--
all hours, day and night.
Uh, gee, Chief, I feel pretty
bad-- trying to take out a baby.
Oh, don’t worry, boys.
No one will ever speak
or write of this again.
What a boffo beginning
for my book!
(loud grunt)
There they are.
I see his head dealy.
Follow that glow!
(shouting)
(quacking)
They put his halo
on a duck.
The oldest trick in the book.
What the hell
are you doing?
Well, he does have a halo.
Hail, Quackie!
-(thunderous rumbling)
-(honks)
That ought
to spruce things up.
(all yelling)
(honking)
(gasping)
What a beautiful Hanukkah bush!
I say we call it
a "Christmas tree."
ALL: Aw...
A Christmas tree...
what a great name.
Makes you feel
all warm and fuzzy.
(moaning and groaning)
And did you know...
that little baby Jesus
grew up to be... Jesus?
(gasping and murmuring)
I know.
It’s weird, isn’t it?
("Deck the Halls" playing)
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Coming up next:
the Energizer Bunny
Christmas Special.
Ah, I don’t know
why I’m so run down.
I must be low on
Christmas spirit.
It’s ’cause
you’re using
regular batteries.
You forgot about
Energizer Ultra!
Now let me crawl inside you.
(screams)
Cold... so cold.
(clattering)
(gasps)
It’s Santa!
(screaming)
(grunts)
Grampa?!
What are you doing
in the chimney?
Trying to kill Santa.
What’s it to ya?!
What do you have
against Santa?
He screwed me over
back in WWII!
I was a Navy pilot
in the Pacific.
Oh, Bart, why’d you ask him
a follow-up question?
It just slipped out!
Yep, I was a Navy pilot
in the Pacific,
along with my
big brother Cyrus.
Cyrus? You never
mentioned him before.
And I’ll never
mention him again,
but I loved him all the same.
Okay, Abe,
let’s win this war quick,
so we can go home and slowly
give black folks more rights.
(siren blares)
Kamikazes at two o’clock!
Well, I don’t usually drink
after lunch, but... oh, my God!
The sky is full of
that kind of plane
that crashes into the boat!
Cyrus, you be careful up there.
Nah, I’m not worried,
not as long as I have
my good luck charm.
("American Patrol"
by Glenn Miller playing)
(machine gun firing)
Good thing I stole two of these
off dead soldiers.
Lieutenant, radio my brother
and tell him to watch his tail!
Quiet, you.
I’m talking to my best gal.
I miss you, too, Bernadette.
You hang up first.
No... you hang up first.
No.
You hang up first.
No!
(murmurs angrily)
Cyrus!
You’ll pay for that,
you haiku-spouting savages!
GRAMPA:
I wish I tried reefer!
(grunts)
Quit lollygagging
and build a fire!
I don’t have to listen to you.
On this island,
military rank means nothing.
We’re in a state
of nature
where the strong of
will control the weak.
(spits)
How dare you drown the
King of New Burns Island!
(spits)
How’d you like to be the
archduke in charge of coconuts?
No! I give up!
I give up!
GRAMPA:
Days turned to weeks.
Weeks turned to months.
Months turned back to days.
Even Burns was starting
to look good to me.
Hey, sailor,
my eyes are up here.
By Christmas Eve, our hopes
of rescue were fading.
You know, Simpson,
we’ve had our dustups,
so I’ve made you a
little peace offering.
A shaving kit?
Is this pomade?
Oh, it’s nothing really, just
seagull brains and snail goo.
Thanks, Lieutenant.
Merry Christmas.
-(jet roars)
-Incoming!
Is it one of ours?
Who cares? It’s Christmas.
I want to shoot
something.
What in the name of the
Tennessee Valley Authority?
Donder! Blitzen!
He’s German.
That’s good eatin’.
You useless waste
of socks!
That ain’t no Kraut!
We just shot down
Santa Claus!
Oh, thank you, boys.
I guess I must have run
into a sudden storm.
Yes, yes.
Everything happens to you.
My sleigh! It’s ruined!
Well, we’ll get
you up and running
or my name ain’t
Young Grampa Simpson!
("Sing, Sing, Sing"
by Benny Goodman plays)
Boys, I’m almost ready.
I’m just missing Prancer...
and Rudolph.
(hisses and rattles)
And now to bring joy to boys
and girls around the world.
Ho! Ho! Ha... ow!
Damn it!
Sorry, Chuckles,
change of plan.
This sleigh is my ticket
off this hellhole.
And I’m keeping
all the toys for myself!
Because, at heart,
I’m just a very wicked child.
Yah!
You backstabber!
And I let you spoon me.
(exhaling)
Let’s go, you flying hat rack!
(screams)
(sleigh bells jingling)
Hmm?
(sputtering engine noises)
-(roar of diving plane)
-Come on, baby!
(growls)
-Ow! Ow!
-(toy mallet squeaks)
(grunts)
Somebody should have beat you
with a tricycle years ago!
(screams)
Thanks for everything, Abe.
And now I’m off.
I’ll be back in a few days
to take you ho-ho-home!
Well, that’s the craziest thing
I’ll ever see.
(screams)
Except for that!
GRAMPA:
I waited and waited.
But Santa never came back.
If I hadn’t invented
a jet ski made of coconuts,
I’d have never gotten home.
And then when I did,
the war was over
and the nurses
were all kissed out.
That’s quite a tale, Grampa.
(stutters angrily)
You little...
It’s true, I tells ya!
(clattering,
sleigh bells ringing)
It’s Santa!
I got an old score to settle.
Doggone it!
I missed him again!
("American Patrol"
by Glenn Miller playing)
My brother’s lucky watch!
Santa must have left it.
Cyrus, I miss you every day.
SANTA:
He misses you, too.
(stutters excitedly)
Wait! He, what, who?!
Your brother didn’t die
in the war, Abe.
He crashed into Tahiti.
And he liked it so much,
he never left.
And now, if you like,
I’ll take you to him.
Will we be back for
the Tournament of Roses Parade?
Probably not.
Good, I hate that crap.
Yeah, me, too.
Santa, one thing’s
still bugging me.
Why didn’t you ever
come back to pick me up?
I kept putting it off and then
I was just too embarrassed.
Sorry I never called, Abe.
I was too busy with
my 15 native wives.
(women giggling)
15! Whoa, that sounds
like a lot of sex!
I said "wives,"
not "girlfriends."
(women giggling)
WOMEN:
No poko-miku for Cyrus!
("Dance of the Sugarplum
Fairies" plays)
(cymbals crash)
Oh my God, it’s over.
We’re free!
It’s not over.
It’s just intermission.
I said we’re free!
(audience chattering)
We’re still doing Act Two.
I’ll be the audience.
Boo! This is terrible!
Ugh. I hope I never hear
that god-awful
Nutcracker music again.
I don’t know, Dad.
This time of year,
everybody does it,
’cause you don’t have to pay
for the music rights.
Really?
(to Nutcracker melody):
♪ I’ve still gotta bake
my Christmas pie ♪
♪ I’ve gotta get Dad
a lousy tie ♪
♪ Christmas crowds
is what I hate ♪
♪ No time left
to procrastinate ♪
-♪ So move your ass ♪
-♪ And let me pass ♪
♪ ’Cause Christmas Eve
is here ♪
BOTH: Ow!
♪ Er, why is this Santa suit
so snug? ♪
♪ Grr, why should I care?
It’s all humbug ♪
♪ I’ve jacked my prices up
so high ♪
♪ But there’s no junk
these saps won’t buy ♪
♪ Last year’s eggnog,
a green hot dog... ♪
♪ ’Cause Christmas Eve
is here! ♪
(instrumental interlude)
(explosion)
♪ These holiday cookies
swell my fat ♪
(singing gibberish)
♪ Cat ♪
♪ Even though we’re not gentile,
we’ll get together for a while ♪
-♪ To shoot the breeze ♪
-♪ And eat Chinese ♪
♪ ’Cause Christmas Eve is here ♪
Oy!
(instrumental interlude)
♪ Christmas is
a family day ♪
♪ I told Grampa we’d be away ♪
♪ He’s at the door,
let’s hit the floor ♪
♪ ’Cause Christmas Eve
is here ♪
Fine. I’ll spend Christmas Eve
with the raccoons.
(groaning)
(chittering)
You got me a gift?
Rancid lard?!
Aw, you shouldn’t have.
Every year at this time,
I show what’s probably
my most requested clip.
Roll it, Freddie.
♪ It’s the most wonderful time
of the year... ♪
(groaning)
Ow! Ow!
(moaning)
"Give the audience snowballs,"
they said.
"It’ll be cute," they said. Oh!
(both laughing)
(chuckling)
Okay, time for my annual
holiday tradition:
attempting to kill myself.
(sobs)
("The Mirlitons" from
The Nutcracker plays)
(grunting)
(horns honking,
indistinct shouts)
(sighs)
What’s it say?
Hey, Barn, as a special gift
to me this year,
will you kill me?
But I already got you
a wool hat.
Maybe next year, huh?
Merry Christmas, Homie.
I think you’re really
gonna like this.
(laughs):
That’s great.
Now I’ll just get
my present for you,
which is... right
outside the door.
Oh, my God, I forgot
to get Marge a present!
(tires squealing)
(to "Russian Dance"
from The Nutcracker):
♪ I need a present for my wife ♪
♪ Or I’ll have no sex for life ♪
♪ Diamond ring, a vase by Ming ♪
♪ Some kinda useful
kitchen thing ♪
♪ I need a store
I can break into ♪
♪ Or a place run by a Hindu ♪
♪ The Christmas rush
has cleaned me out ♪
♪ I just have jerky
made of trout. ♪
(song ends)
Ow!
("Pas De Deux" from
The Nutcracker plays)
I knew you’d forget,
so my gift to you
is a gift for you
to give me.
Oh, it’s just
what I wanted.
Here, Marge,
this is for you.
Oh!
(truck horn honking)
MOE: Ah! Eighteen wheels,
and they all missed me!
♪♪
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem