CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(screaming)
Oh.
(screams)
(chews loudly)
(whimpering)
Oh...
(chuckles nervously)
(screams)
(sighs)
Hmm?
(screams)
(circus music plays)
I’m so glad we came
to Paradise Pier.
Ever since
I was a little girl,
I’ve wanted to ride
that Ferris wheel.
(explosions)
(screams)
They’re tearing down
the Pier!
But what will junkies
do drugs under?
They’ll bounce back, son.
They’re a strong people.
(hammering)
(giggling)
Ooh, ooh, I want to ride
the bumper cars!
Whoa, sir, we’re
dismantling this ride.
-It’s not safe.
-I call the red one!
(giggling)
(grunting)
(laughing)
Homie, no!
It’s not street-legal!
Don’t worry, ma’am.
He’s not connected to the power
supply, so he can’t go far.
(chuckles)
Gulp.
(laughing)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(screams)
(giggles)
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Oh, he’s got us
in a corner.
I hate this ride!
Mom, can we buy
a magnesium vapor soak tub?
For the last time, no!
Oh...
But how will I increase
my vitality?
(groans)
Uh, he’s just faking loss
of vitality, Reverend.
Mm-hmm.
I believe you.
A strongman?
Are you for sale?
’Cause I need someone to throw
a birdbath at my neighbor.
Robusto is not for sale!
But would you like to buy
my last dumbbell?
Hmm... I suppose
I could use a little toning.
(quivering):
I’ll give you $5 for it.
Sold.
(gasps)
A bicycle built for two!
And I could be one of those two!
Homie, if I buy
a bicycle built for two,
will you ride with me?
Marge, I don’t hate
your mother.
I just won’t be sad
when she dies.
47, 48...
I was asking for something.
Yeah, sure, whatever you want.
95, 96, 13, 64, banana...
I’ll take it!
I can’t believe
I own a tandem bike.
Mm-mm.
You want me to ride
a what-cycle built for who?
A tandem bicycle!
When I bought it,
you said you’d ride with me.
But I’m watching television!
A lot of people
worked hard on this show.
(sighs)
I was really
looking forward to it.
Bart, how’d you
like to go
on a tandem bike ride
with your mom?
Mom, please!
I’m playing a video game.
Ooh, small hill.
Pedal, pedal, pedal!
Now enjoy scenery.
Enjoy! Enjoy! Enjoy!
(sighs)
Maggie, would you
like to ride with me?
(groans)
("Bicycle Built for Two"
music plays)
Bart, why is your mom riding
a two-person bike by herself?
Ha ha!
She’s lonely.
Moms don’t get lonely.
Hmm...
306...
(yawns)
307...
(faint bell rings)
(confused grunting)
(bell rings)
Hey, Mom,
want to go for a ride?
I’d love to!
I’ll be right...
Wait, are you sure
you’re not just trying
to get me to make pizza
for breakfast?
HOMER:
Woo-hoo! Pizza
for breakfast!
Mom, I mean it.
I want to ride
with you.
Oh...
I’ll be right down.
Hello, Domino’s?
What do you mean
you’re not open?
No, you call me back
during business hours!
I’ll show you
who’s a recorded message!
(birds chirping)
Puddle.
(laughing)
I’m glad I could share
in their fun.
("Sweet Home Alabama"
intro plays)
♪ Well, I heard Neil Young
sing about her ♪
♪ I heard ol’ Neil
put her down ♪
In the name of the Father...
-Hey!
-Hi. Hi.
♪ Well, I hope
Neil Young will remember ♪
(grunting, coughs)
♪ This Southern man don’t
need him ’round, anyhow. ♪
Mom, who’s Neil Young?
He was a singer in the ’60s,
like The Archies
and The Banana Splits.
(birds screeching and cawing)
(owl hooting)
I’m a little worried.
This part of the county
is unincorporated.
Just to be safe, I’m going
to dial "9-1" on my cell phone.
(classical music plays)
A teahouse?
Want to go inside?
I don’t know.
Think they have
video games?
No.
-Batting cage?
-No.
-Rock climbing wall?
-No!
-Robot musical revue?
-No.
-Zumanity
by Cirque de Soleil?
-No.
-Bathroom?
-Yes.
Well, that’s really
what I need the most.
Let’s go.
Mmm. Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Wow, Mom, I love tea.
You haven’t
had any tea.
(gulps)
Yeah, well, I still
love this place.
(British accent):
Good afternoon, madam.
Ooh, and who’s your handsome
gentleman friend?
(giggles)
Oh, you.
(humming)
(strained grunting)
No, dude, uh,
no, that hurts.
-Careful, careful.
-(groans)
Hey, what’s the big idea
getting trapped
under that thing?
Uh, long story.
Uh, we were trying
to impress some girls
and things kinda
got away from us.
Just for the record,
I regret nothing.
(grunting)
Homer, how’d your right arm
get so strong?
Just lifting this dumbbell.
49,999...
50,000.
(laughs)
I’m pretty happy with this baby.
Now it’s lefty’s turn.
Oh, no, you don’t.
I just got an idea.
-Listen...
-Wha...?
(whispering)
Uhh...
(laughs)
Hey, you...!
-(whispering)
-Uh? What?!
Hey, you’ve...! Oh...
-(whispering)
-Why, you...!
Ah... Yeah.
Mom, all we have is carrot
sticks and fresh fruit.
Well, we could bike to
the tea shop and have some cake.
All right.
Pedal to the kettle.
Hey, Bart,
they’re testing me for lazy eye.
Wanna come with?
Hmm?
Sorry, Milhouse,
I’ve got plans.
(disappointed):
Okay.
I’ll bring you back
an eye care pamphlet.
Okay, here comes our victim.
Let’s bash his head in.
Hey, Moe, I thought
you were just going
to hustle him.
Oh, right. I was thinking
of another thing I’ve got going.
Gimme a bottle of bourbon.
I got a new liver,
and I’m breakin’ it in.
(slight lisp):
Excuse me,
Mr. Bartender, sir.
May I have a sugar-free
ginger ale?
And, uh, make it flat.
The bubbles burn my buds.
Goldarnit, son.
What the hell kinda
sissy are you?
Hey, are you callin’
my life partner a sissy?
’Cause a hundred bucks says he
could whup you in arm wrestling.
A "Texas penny" it is.
Yee-haw!
Goldangit!
I’ve been played like
a dimwit’s kazoo.
(grunts)
Oh...!
Yes!
Homer, we make
a dynamite team, huh?
With your arm,
and my head-gunk,
we’re goin’
right to the top.
-(hammers clicking)
-Whoa.
This is one Texan who don’t like
when he’s made out to be a fool.
Well,
what do you like?
I dunno, a good book,
long walk on the beach.
So, we, uh, we kinda
evened things up here?
Not yet.
I wanna play some Frisbee.
You know, honey,
I’ve really started
to look forward
to our little bike rides.
Me, too, Mother.
Ooh, such respect.
You could grow up
to be a doorman.
BRITISH WOMAN:
"Loyal customers,
we have been forced
to close forever.
It seems our cakes were filled
with rat droppings.
It’s not
that we’re bad people.
We just weren’t paying
close attention.
Ta-ta."
What did it say?
Uh... she died.
Hmm?
Well, Bart,
I guess that’s it.
We’ll have to go back
to our separate things.
Hey, we could have tea
in my tree house.
You invited me
to your tree house?
Wow!
That’s like Bruce Wayne letting
his mother into the Bat Club.
(slurping)
(groans)
So... is that standing water?
-Yeah.
-(buzzing)
You know, that puddle started
life as a bowl of cereal.
(nervously):
Oh...
Hmm. Hmm.
I think I might be able to turn
this tree house into a teahouse.
Mom, this is great.
It makes our real house
look like a pile of crap.
And I threw out
all your old comics.
Mom!
(laughing)
Just kidding.
Today’s mom knows
to seal them in Mylar
so you can never
read them again.
Never, ever again.
Where are you two going?
I’m joining the professional
arm-wrestling circuit.
Uh-huh.
And how will this affect
your job at the power plant?
Negatively, I assume.
Oh. Well, we’re off
to buy a new tea set.
Have fun.
(car doors closing)
Gee, she didn’t seem angry
or anything.
Maybe she doesn’t care anymore.
Forget about it, Homer.
She’s dead to you now.
O...kay.
Now, if we get bored
on the bus,
I got a book
of brain teasers here.
Let’s see, uh...
Oh, "Brothers and sisters
have I none,
but this man’s father
is my father’s son."
Huh...
Ah, screw you,
you stupid thing.
"He is my son."
That blows.
I can’t wait to use our new
Krusty the Clown tea service!
Me, neither.
Oh, my God.
I took
the salesman’s pen.
I’ll be right back.
KRUSTY’S VOICE:
Green Tea? What’s that?
Mr. T’s Irish brother?
(laughs)
Earl Grey?
I’d rather have
Linda Gray.
Is she still alive?
What’s next?
What the hell?
I’m not doing that one.
(laughs)
-BOY: Hey, Simpson!
-Huh?
What are you gonna do
with that teapot?
Gay out?
I’ll answer
for you: yes.
What? Um, uh...
I just shoplifted this bad boy.
Housewares never
knew what hit ’em.
Why didn’t you steal
something cool?
Uh... because I’m gonna
bring it back
to the store for store credit.
How you gonna get credit
without a gift receipt, ass?
Um, well...
We’ve seen you hanging out
with your mom, Simpson.
Word on the street is...
you’re a mama’s boy.
Hey, there is no way that
Bart Simpson is a mama’s boy.
MARGE (sing-songy):
Oh, Bart!
Aren’t they jazzy?
They match the new curtains
we hung in your treehouse!
Here, try
yours on.
I got you
a child’s large
because your tummy’s
getting kind of bloopy
from all the cakes
we’ve been having.
Somebody here likes
princess cakes.
Princess cake?
Bart, you just got yourself
a nickname for life.
Hey, Princess Cake!
Want some princess cake?
-(laughing)
-Bart, are you
having a fight
with your
boyfriends?
Shut up!
I don’t want
your stupid sweatshirt!
(gasps)
Or your tea set!
(grunts)
Smashing voids my warranty.
Have a good life.
Mom, I only hung out
with you
because I felt sorry
for you.
That was weird.
Will you teach us
how to smoke?
No!
(Bart grunting)
I can’t believe she suckered me
into being a mama’s boy.
I got to make this place
mine again.
(grunting)
(sobbing)
It’s gonna take me weeks
to get the booger wall back up.
Bart?
You’re not
allowed in here!
Can’t you
read the sign?
You mean this?
BART:
Ay, caramba!
Yah!
I’m worried about Mom.
She’s been
sitting there
just petting the
dog for two hours.
(yelps)
(whimpers)
(sad music plays)
Hey, Mom.
Hello, Bart.
Just so you know,
I sold our bike.
(laughing):
Faster! Faster!
BOTH:
Whoa!
(all shouting)
But we had so much fun
on that bike!
(yelling)
Mom, I really did
like hanging out with you.
(whines)
You know, there’s a karaoke
night at school tomorrow.
Some of the little kids
are bringing their parents.
Do you want to go?
Really?
Could we do a duet?
Sure. Why not?
(chuckles)
It’ll be fun.
It’s still happening!
Oh, I can’t believe
Marge hasn’t called me.
Maybe I should
go home.
Oh, Marge called you.
She said, uh,
that she loves you
and she hopes
you break the guy’s arm so hard
that it pokes through his skin.
Did she say anything else?
Yeah, she said to shut up,
stop asking questions,
and listen to Moe.
Oh, Marge,
I love her so much.
Now, Homer, you got
to keep your head
in the game,
all right?
Your first opponent
is Lefty "The Righty"
Leftwright.
Oh, he looks tough.
Yeah, he only
lost once:
in his fight
against illiteracy.
I can relate.
I fought that foe
and lost many times.
(phone ringing)
(whiny):
Oh, Marge isn’t home.
Homer, focus.
Moe, I’m starting to have
grave doubts about this thing
I barely liked
in the first place.
Come on, Homer.
We can make it all the way
to the quarterfinals
for the Eastern Division,
Class B,
over-35, Amateur grouping!
-Sorry, Moe.
-(grunts)
The place for my arm
is around my wife.
-(crackling)
-(yells)
Homer, come back.
You got my teeth-whitening
system in your suitcase!
Let’s see...
what would be a good duet?
Hmm.
"Just the Two of Us,"
"You and Me Against the World,"
"Ebony And Ivory"?
"Ebony and Ivory"?
(chuckling):
I’m afraid that
song’s taken.
by me and my mother.
You know, people say when
we’re on stage,
it’s more
like scary-oke.
Uh, scary talented,
I assume.
I’m singing a song
with Bart tonight.
Capital. My mother and I have
been performing together
since I was in fourth grade, and
it’s really brought us closer.
Seymour,
where were you?
A brightly-colored car
hurt my eyes.
Don’t worry, Mother,
I have your eye balm
in my man-purse
right here.
Good boy.
You can push your crib
into mommy’s room tonight.
It’s not a crib.
It’s a cot.
If it has rails,
it’s a crib!
(groans softly)
(music playing)
♪ Where is my John Wayne? ♪
♪ Where is my prairie sun? ♪
♪ Where is my happy ending? ♪
♪ Where have
all the cowboys gone? ♪
♪ Do-do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Do-do-do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Do-do-do, do-do... ♪
Whew.
You know, Mother,
I wasn’t sure
about tonight.
But seeing us dressed
the same really feels right.
Well, now I’m not so sure
about the bells
on the painter’s pants.
Are you kidding?
I love my tinklies.
(bells jingling)
(murmurs softly)
Next up on the Springfield
Elementary Karaoke Showcase
is... Skinner!
And Mrs... Skinner!
(scattered applause)
♪ Ebony and ivory ♪
♪ Live together
in perfect harmony ♪
-♪ Side by side on my piano ♪
-(gasps)
♪ Keyboard ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, why don’t we? ♪
No!
Stop the showcase!
(music stops)
Mrs. Simpson, please.
Hush up, Seymour.
She’s just saying
what we’re all thinking.
Mother,
what are you doing?
Don’t call me Mother.
My name is Mom.
And my son
is no mama’s boy!
(all gasping)
Bart, you are
a wild heck-raiser,
and I don’t want to see you
turn into that.
What, a wall?
Mom, I thought this
was what you wanted.
Your job isn’t
to worry about me.
It’s to give me things
to worry about.
Hmm.
Hey, losers, I’m gonna do to you
what you did to these songs.
Interpret them
artistically?
Die! Die! Die!
(all yelling)
We were gonna sing
"My Sharona"!
(laughing)
(country music playing)
♪ Sweet home Alabama ♪
♪ Where the skies are so blue ♪
HOMER:
♪ Sweet home Alabama ♪
(gasps)
♪ Lord, I’m coming
home to you ♪
Alabama!
Marge, spending
time with you
is more
important to me
than all the pie-eating
contests in the world.
I thought it was
arm wrestling.
I was in a pie-eating
contest on the way home.
Now, let’s go to bed.
(a cappella):
♪ Oh, my little pretty one,
my pretty one ♪
♪ When you gonna give me
some time, Sharona? ♪
♪ Ooh, you make my motor run,
my motor run ♪
♪ Got it comin’ off
of the line, Sharona ♪
♪ Never gonna stop, give it up ♪
♪ Such a dirty mind ♪
♪ I always get it up for
the touch of the younger kind ♪
♪ My, my, my, aye-aye, whoo! ♪
(all gasp)
HOMER:
That song
is a pop music footnote!
I didn’t say stop!
♪ M-M-M-My Sharona. ♪
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem