CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Welcome to the Mayor's Easter
egg hunt.
And now, my rarely-seen wife
would like to say a few words.
-(microphone feedback)
-Thank you, Joe.
In just a few moments,
the hunt will be opened
by our own "wascally weferee,"
Hugs Bunny.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sorry, kid.
Legally, I’m not allowed
to hug you.
Now, begin the hunt.
WOMAN:
Joe!
You said your wife
was dead.
And you said you graduated
from typing school.
I have trouble
with the space bar.
(children shouting happily)
Nelson, those don’t count
as Easter Eggs.
Yeah, but they count
as breakfast.
(grunts, crunching)
(birds screeching,
Nelson yelling)
It was worth it.
Yay!
Ralph, there’s a
hole in your basket.
You’re Lisa’s brother.
(Maggie squeaks)
Hey. Nobody pushes around
my precious bundle of joy.
Whoops, wrong one.
I’ll take that.
Too slow, Drooly Joe.
Peek-a-boo, I steal from you.
(giggles)
(whistle blowing)
Sir, you want to
set the baby down?
Don’t worry,
I just want to talk.
(yells)
(both grunting)
-Silly wabbit,
kicks are for ribs!
-(pained grunt)
(both grunting)
(growling grunts)
This house
has such beautiful wainscoting.
(laughs):
Well, Marge,
I didn’t know
you were into wainscoting.
I read an article about
it at the tire store.
Did you know
it’s not named
after someone
named Wayne Scott?
-Oh!
That’s very
interesting.
(Bunny yelling)
You are now
in the Mayor’s office.
This is the switch
the Mayor uses
to call his Chief of Staff.
(mechanical whirring)
("Music to Watch Girls By"
playing)
(sighs heavily)
(music stops)
That concludes our tour.
(disappointed moans)
But I’d love it
if you’d all join me
for tea in the parlor.
Tea? In the parlor?
You’re like all
Easter Bunnies--
can’t take a punch
to the crotch!
Maybe next time
you’ll think twice before you
(mockingly):
"volunteer to help children."
Oh, hey, Marge.
(weakly):
This is my husband, Homer.
(nervous chuckling)
Ladies.
Marge, is there a small
rip in my pants?
(shocked gasping)
Homer, please.
We’re about to have tea.
No tea.
Security.
("Music to Watch Girls By"
playing)
Ah. Everyone, just go.
Way to blow
our tea, Marge.
That’s the last
refrigerator magnet calendar
you get from me.
We throw those
out anyway.
You lie.
Stop lying.
Hey, good-looking.
Wanna snuggle
with "Tyrannosaurus Sex"?
(lusty growling and chomping)
No, I don’t.
I’m still upset about
what happened today.
I don’t have many friends,
and when I finally start
to make some, you ruin it.
Oh, come on, honey,
you have lots of friends.
There’s, uh...
Lisa and... the stove.
(irate growl)
Ah, that poor woman.
I am going to find her a friend.
Someone cute, athletic,
with a nice laugh.
(chittering happily)
(gasps):
My husband...
and my best friend.
(chitters)
(grunts)
It’s a risk I’ll have to take.
Whatcha lookin’ for,
Lisa?
Summer opportunities.
We’re going to Twin Camp.
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
Spend a summer in Rome.
Rome?
Founded by twins,
by the way.
Hey, where’d she go?
Oh, well, let’s talk
in our secret twin language.
(nonsensical gobbledygook)
Okay, Lisa, to study in Rome,
an applicant needs
outstanding grades-- check.
Uh-oh. Lisa, it says you
have to speak fluent Italian.
Uh... check.
You speak Italian?
Of course I do.
Why would I say it if I didn’t?
(nervous chuckle)
Flawless logic.
But I am going to have to ask
you to speak a few phrases
to verify your fluency.
-(nervous gasp)
-Though not now,
because I have a series
of important meetings.
-(relieved sigh)
-But how’s tomorrow for you?
-(nervous gasp)
-Because it’s
terrible for me.
But I’ll get back to you. Soon.
(moans anxiously)
Son, I need to find a new friend
for your mother.
So you’re gonna have to finish
the shopping yourself.
We’re on food stamps?
I wish.
I made these at work.
(Homer chuckles)
Hmm.
I bet she’d be a good friend
for Marge.
She looks defeated, too.
(wheels squeaking)
Psst. Psst.
(squeaking quickens)
Why does every woman
I try to talk to run into cans?
MAN (on tape):
Voglio affittare
una barca piccola.
"I want to rent a small boat."
Voglio affittare
una barca piccola.
Progetto di scaricare questo
corpo nell’oceano.
"I plan to dump this body
in the ocean."
Huh?
(shocked gasp)
(angrily):
Questo e quello che prendi
per Sare domande.
"This is what you get
for asking questions."
(gunshots)
(shutters)
Arrivederci, ignorance.
Marge, I did it.
I found a woman
to be your new friend.
She’s waiting
in the living room.
(crazed ravings)
(cat screeches)
(angry grunt)
I’m going out for some air.
I bet you can’t throw
a cat over the house.
Oh, yeah? (raving)
-(crazed ravings)
-(cat screeches)
Huh. I was wrong.
♪ Everybody hurts... ♪
♪ Sometimes... ♪
(sighs heavily)
I guess I’m not meant
to have friends.
WOMAN:
Stop that hat!
(laughs)
Whoo!
How about this wind, huh?
I don’t know how you
keep your hair so perfect.
Johnson’s Water Seal.
(tinny clangs)
(laughing)
My name’s Tammy.
And these are my friends,
the Cheery Red Tomatoes.
(gasps)
The nationwide
social organization
for women of a certain age?
Yeah, but we don’t sit around
watching television
and eating bonbons.
Except on TV Bonbon Night,
which is every Tuesday
and Thursday.
What are you doing today?
We’re gonna have margaritas and
poke gentle fun at our husbands.
Would you like to join us?
Would I?!
Now, let’s see.
Homer cut up my wedding dress
to make a badminton net,
which he never uses.
He spent my last three birthdays
in jail,
called out his bowling ball’s
name during sex...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, honey!
Save it
for Johnny Fiesta’s.
And now, we return
to the Vic Tayback Motel and
Casino in downtown Las Vegas
for Has-Been Celebrity Poker.
As always, all our celebrities
are playing for charity.
What?! I am so
out of here.
Wow, Mom, great red dress!
For your information,
I am now a junior member
of the Cheery
Red Tomatoes.
Marge? In a gang?
(laughs)
What’re you gonna do,
shoot me with a frosting gun?
Seriously, I would love that.
(all laughing)
Oh, you guys
make everything fun.
(gasps):
That’s my Italian tutor!
Oh, hey, Milhouse.
I think Bart’s upstairs.
I’m not here for Bart.
I’m here to teach you Italian!
Oh, sure, I get it.
Bart told you
I was taking lessons,
so you thought
you’d come over and...
Prego si fermi
ed ascoltare.
That means, "Please
stop and listen."
I’m the tutor
the company sent over.
I’m here to teach you
la lingua di arte e la musica.
You really speak Italian?!
Si. My grandmother,
Nana Sophie, lives in Tuscany.
Since I was a baby, I’ve spent
two weeks there every summer.
Nana hated English,
because in World War II,
a GI left her with child,
my uncle Bastardo.
Nana only spoke Italian to me.
I love you, Nana!
Whoa!
Idiota!
MILHOUSE:
Every time I spoke English,
she hit me.
Ow! That hurt!
Idiota!
I’m sorry I’m so stupid!
Milhouse Mussolini
Van Houten,
parla Italiano, idiota!
(Milhouse yelling)
That’s how I learned Italian
and started wetting my bed.
Anyway, what
do you say?
Can I be your
insegnante?
Okay, if that means,
"Teacher."
It means masculine teacher.
Bye, ladies.
You can text-message me
any time.
We already did!
(gasps)
Ooh!
(tires screeching)
Oh, how cute.
(snoring)
He tried to stay up,
but he just couldn’t make it.
(doorbell rings)
Buon giorno, Milhouse.
Ah, perfetto.
(giggles)
Thank you.
I’ve been studying.
I even made flash cards.
(gasps)
My efforts.
Oh, Lisa, you don’t
learn Italian,
you live Italian.
Come, we ride to Little Italy.
But first, I take care of
some classroom business.
Lisa Simpson?
-Present.
-Let’s go.
(Italian music playing)
MAN:
Milhouse, che cosa di nuova?
Ciao, Milhouse!
Come stai?
(blowing kisses)
Un gelato per la bella ragazza.
"One gelato for..."
Oh... "the pretty girl."
Ah, Mister Milhouse,
thank-a goodness.
Could you translate and-a help
me buy cheese for my lasagna?
But, Luigi, surely
you speak Italian.
(sighs)
No, I don’t.
I only speak-a, how you say...
fractured English.
That’s what my parents spoke
at home.
I had a wonderful
time today.
Grazie, grazie mill-eh.
(laughs)
I’m the luckiest boy
in the world!
Don’t be in
love, stupid!
(groans)
Tammy, I’d never have
the courage to skydive
if it weren’t
for you girls.
Thanks, Marge.
And, you know, when we land,
we’ve got a little surprise
for you.
Ooh! Well, now I really hope
my chute opens!
MOE:
Goodbye, cruel world!
Ladies.
Marge Simpson,
we hereby induct you
as a full member
of the Cheery Red Tomatoes.
(applause)
I feel a happiness
I’ve never felt.
I not only have friends,
I have a hat to prove it.
Now, Marge, as
a full member,
you get to share
in all our secrets.
Like our recipe
for mock apple pie.
The secret is,
it’s got apples in it.
And now we can tell you the
secret plans for our fundraiser.
This year, we’re going to steal
one million dollars
from Mr. Burns.
(gasps)
You’re joking.
You’ve got to be joking.
You’re not joking.
Oh. Any other surprises?
I’m not a natural redhead.
Whoa...
I’m sorry, I can’t steal
Not even from Mr. Burns.
Mr. Burns promised
a million dollars
to the Springfield
Children’s Hospital.
And then...
Instead of donating
this money,
I’m going to use it to extend
my own life another ten minutes.
Smithers.
(pen squeaking)
And the register.
(booing)
Release the hounds!
(dogs barking,
people screaming)
Why would you bring attack
dogs to a charity event?
I was taking them
to the groomer’s.
Oh, who’s a stinky dog?
You are.
Michelle’s going
to work on you today.
Yes, he is.
There are 12 Faberge eggs
in his vault,
each worth a small fortune.
We can get them,
but we need your special skills.
When I joined, I never thought
we’d be robbing people.
You said you wanted friends.
And the one thing about friends
is that they stick together,
especially when they’re trying
to pull off
a million-dollar
heist.
Maybe we were
a little too quick
to give you that hat.
Take back the hat!
She deserves bare hair!
ALL:
Bare hair! Bare hair!
Okay, okay, okay, I’m in!
You ladies
doing okay down there?
Sorry to wake
you, Stanley.
Don’t let us down,
newbie.
Welcome back to Fox Sports West
II Classic Fox Sports Fox.
Hey, Marge,
where you going?
Oh, uh, well, I, um...
bird-watching.
Wait a minute.
If she’s going bird-watching,
why did she leave our
Peterson’s Field Guide to
Birds on the kitchen counter?
(gasps)
Roadrunners are real!
♪ Milhouse is teaching me ♪
♪ To speak so prettily ♪
♪ I’ll quip so wittily ♪
♪ When I’m in Italy ♪
(sighs)
(gasps)
Milhouse!
Just what is going on?
Run along,
Angelica.
But not-a
too fast, eh?
(playfully growls)
Lisa, Lisa.
She is the appetizer,
but you are
the main course.
Sono cosi matto a lei!
Ho pensato abbiamo
avuto qualcosa andando,
e poi la prendo con
questa sgualdrina!
Lei me fa malato!
(normal voice):
Lisa, you’re speaking
perfect Italian!
Grazie.
Idiota!
-Idiota! Idiota! Idiota!
-Ow! Ow! Ow!
Now, let’s see
what Marge is up to.
"Recipes, dress patterns,
toaster
undercoating agreement...
Heist plans"?!
(gasps):
Burns’ Mansion?!
That’s Mr. Burns’ mansion!
Remind me, Smithers,
while we’re out.
I need to get my eyes
re-balled
and my brain
flushed out with vinegar.
Yes, sir.
Oh, and your knees will be
back from the shop tomorrow.
Excellent.
Okay, Marge.
You’re the only one of us
skinny enough
to squeeze through this vent.
That’s my special skill?
Well, what’d you think?
You’re a master of disguise?
Not with that do.
I thought you liked my hair.
It’s all right.
(gate squeaks)
I gotta stop Marge
from doing something reckless
and irresponsible.
(screaming)
Lou, we’d better
go after him.
Eddie,
you direct traffic.
You’re the graceful one.
You got it, Chief.
WIGGUM:
Look at him tease
that Subaru.
And that guy can’t
find a girlfriend.
I’ll never
figure it out.
I got the combination from Burns
after I let him feel me up
during the Depression.
Zero to the right...
zero to the left...
back to zero.
(sirens approaching)
Marge, I wanted
to save you from the cops,
but the cops followed me.
Game over, man!
Game over!
So, are you gonna
introduce me to your friends?
Don’t worry, Mr. Burns.
We’ll get to the bottom of this.
Excuse me, Lou.
I’m supposed to say that.
Acting like the chief
doesn’t make you the chief.
If I was acting
like the chief,
I’d need size 58 pants.
Oh, here we go
with the fat jokes.
You know, I just wish you
could hit the easy targets
on the firing range so well.
Oh, Lou, why do we
hurt each other so?
Because sometimes
it’s easier to be cruel
than to say what
you really feel.
Permission to hug,
Chief?
Permission...
(chokes up)
granted.
Granted, Lou.
Thank you, Chief.
Ooh, enough!
While you morons are canoodling,
someone’s burgling
my miscellania!
(booming gunshot)
Try to take my eggs, will you?
Well, this rooster has a beak.
A beak which calls out
death-a-doodle-doo.
Why... you’re all women.
I’m not.
I suppose,
but you’re certainly
buxom and flirty.
Oh, well, I try
to have a good time.
All I wanted to do
was join a group of women
who wore the same outfits.
(sobbing)
(all sobbing)
(sighs)
Oh, no jury on earth
will convict
a bunch of moist-eyed
mothers.
I’ll tell you what, ladies.
Give me my eggs back
and I’ll let you go.
(sobbing)
And tell me I’m not fat.
(disgusted groan)
Well, I guess our fundraiser
was a failure.
Don’t be so sure.
Ah, Marge, I love you.
But to be safe, sweetie,
I don’t think we can ever
see each other again.
I’ll really miss you guys.
I’ll never forget
the three activities
we did together.
(sniffling)
Listen, Marge.
No matter where
you go in this life,
you’ll always
have one friend
who loves you
body and soul.
And Marge,
there are certain things
I can do for you
that no other friend can.
Special things.
(chuckling)
Wow, this is special.
(thud)
I can’t believe
this happened to me twice.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem