CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(erie music plays)
♪ Tis season should be jolly ♪
Mid-June?
(chattering)
Kids,
this is the holiest
night of the year.
Tomorrow
is Father’s Day,
and that makes tonight
Father’s Day Eve.
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ A father’s born ♪
♪ Let me receive great gifts. ♪
Dad, there’s no such thing
as Father’s Day Eve.
No Father’s Day Eve?
Does this mean there’s no such
thing as... Daddy Claus?
Fine, there’s
a Daddy Claus.
Is there a Super Bowl Bunny?
Sure, why not?
(gleeful giggling)
Bart, Lisa.
We’ve got to get to the mall
before it closes.
Oh, can I come with you?
I know I can’t.
(giggling)
Hey, Mom, can I
have some money
to buy Dad a present?
If I give you money,
how is the gift really from you?
Where do you get your money?
Here’s a ten.
Make your own card.
(gleeful giggling)
Now, Ralphie, let me
explain it to you again.
I give you $5 and
you buy Daddy a present.
Okeydokey.
Hey, hey, give
me that. Eww...
Whoa, this is a 50.
This kid’s
finally paying off.
All right, Ralphie, let’s see
what you can do with a hundred.
Come on, Ralphie.
Big money. Big
money, Ralphie.
Big money.
("Thus Spake Zarathustra"
playing)
Cool.
That’s what I’m getting.
How ’bout you?
I’m afraid the best thing
I could find is this.
Ay caramba.
You know,
this mass-produced junk doesn’t
express how I feel about Dad.
I am making him a present
that comes from the heart.
Hello. I’m looking for something
in a pipe cleaner,
extra bendy,
with medium fuzz.
Mm-hmm. This just
came in from Zanzibar.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
HOMER:
What a great Father’s Day!
Here you go, Dad.
I hope you like it.
I’ve forgotten what it is.
(gasps)
A Leather Buddy.
There’s no limit
to what I can do with this.
Fear not, m’lady,
Captain Dash Superstud
is here
with his small tool.
(all yelling)
(grunting)
Arr. This is the worst
Father’s Day ever.
(groans)
Oh, Captain,
you’re so handy.
Bart, this is the greatest
present I ever received.
To open another gift now
would be like following
the London Philharmonic
with Jessica Simpson.
What you got, Lisa?
What the hell is this?
Mm.
The unicorns
are you and me, Dad.
I drew it myself.
LISA:
What do you think? Huh? Huh?
Pretty heartfelt, huh? Huh?!
Oh, it’s heartfelt.
There’s no escaping that.
(chuckles):
Thanks, honey.
You didn’t like it, did you?
No, no, no,
it’s great.
I’m done with it now.
Lisa, sweetie,
I think your father
would like to put your
book up on the fridge
where everyone can
see how nice it is.
Aw, isn’t that cute?
Oh, Dad...
how could you?
Well, it’s not my fault.
Lousy magnet!
(sobbing):
Oh, no, no.
What the...
"Happy Birthday, Dad!
From Lisa."
D'oh!
(groans)
I still don’t
understand
how her feelings
can be hurt.
It’s my day.
She’s not going
to get over this quickly.
I know women.
Yeah, but I know
how to win women back.
I even won you back after I lost
our wedding album in a bar bet.
You what?
I mean, I will win you back.
(to melody
of "Wedding March"):
♪ Here comes the Moe ♪
♪ With a pretty girl ♪
♪ ’Cause these are things
that happened in real life. ♪
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Moe, can we
get a drink?
Aw, shut up and hand me
more Moe heads.
(grumbling)
(humming ditty)
Hmm?
Cool, I’m a street.
Hey, Simpson,
are you gonna steal the sign?
Yeah, if a sign’s
got your name on it,
you can take it,
and the cops can’t
do nothing about it.
It’s like the Sixth Amendment
or something.
Well, that sign would look good
hidden under my bed.
Whoa. Can we dish out
the peer pressure, or what?
-Huh!
-Hey, Milhouse!
Cool kids ride bikes
with their eyes closed.
MILHOUSE:
I’m cool!
(train horn honks, bells ding)
(thud)
I’m out of here.
I’ve got
Hebrew school.
Baruch atah
adonai eloheem.
Melech h’olom...
I’m sorry
I made you feel bad, honey.
But I’m gonna show you just how
much I care about your feelings.
One adult
and one baby, please.
I’m not a baby.
A baby is zero to two.
Her first words.
Play along.
It’s 50 cents less for babies.
I’d rather not go than lie.
How you doing?
So... is that your jacket
on the back of that chair?
Check it out.
I stole the sign.
We stole "The Scream."
Put that away.
It creeps me out.
(muttering)
Stupid Dad doesn’t care
about my feelings.
Oh Lisa, may I borrow
one of your colored pencils?
Sure, that’s all you men do,
is take, and take, and take
without regard to feelings
or unicorns.
(grunts)
Here, take my lunch, too.
Just take my whole backpack!
(grunts)
Which of you boys
hurled Lisa Simpson’s backpack
through my window?
Oh, it had to be a boy, did it?
You think a girl can’t flip out?
Well, you’re wrong!
(Lisa grunting)
My flexi-cast.
Yah!
(whinnies excitedly)
Lisa...
I hold in my hand a sticker
with a frowny face on it.
Don’t make me affix it
to your file.
(mockingly):
Don’t make me affix it
to your file.
I’m peeling off the back.
Don’t make me do this.
May God forgive me.
(dramatic music)
(electricity surging)
Willie, we’ve got rats chewing
through the wiring again.
Leave me alone.
I’m making me Ramen noodles.
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
I’m afraid we have
a real problem with Lisa.
(glass shatters)
Your daughter broke a window,
upended an ashcan,
and hurled a Thermos-brand
thermos onto the street!
Does it still keep hot drinks
hot and cold drinks cold?
I’m afraid it doesn’t keep
any drinks anything.
(gasps)
I’ve asked the school
psychologist to shed some light
on your daughter’s sudden burst
of inappropriateness.
I’m afraid Lisa’s rage
stems from extraordinary
disillusionment
with a parental figure.
In this case, her father.
Oh, sure, it’s easy
to point out my faults.
It’s a little harder
to shut up.
Looking at
your daughter’s essays,
this isn’t a new trend.
"Daddy’s Face-Down
Thanksgiving."
"Left at the Grand Canyon."
"The Day a Policeman Came
to My Soccer Game."
Mr. Simpson,
Lisa is at a crucial juncture.
If she doesn’t
see her father
as a positive role model,
she could hate men
for the rest of her life.
Oh, I know!
But how can I undo
eight years of jerkiness
in two easy sessions,
at no cost to me?
If, uh, I may
make a suggestion?
The school is looking
for a new "Safety Salamander."
When Lisa sees you
teaching children
to avoid downed power lines,
it could restore her faith
in you and the male gender.
Oh, I don’t know.
What happened to the last
Safety Salamander?
Um, he fell asleep
in the suit and suffocated.
I can do that!
Okay, Lisa, time for
Daddy’s big surprise!
(Homer growls; Lisa screams)
(laughing)
Sometimes it’s scary
when your dreams come true,
isn’t it, sweetie?
I guess.
Yeah.
Now, I’m off to bring safety
to Springfield Elementary
and win back your love!
Whoa!
-Ugh!
-What’s that, honey?
I can’t hear you very well.
(gurgling)
Salamander away!
(crashing)
(cat yowls)
Sorry, Bart!
HOMER:
The first rule of bus safety is
always wear
your seatbelt.
School buses
don’t have seatbelts.
Then what protects you
if we crash?
A metal bar at tooth level.
Stop this bus!
(tires screeching;
metal clanking)
(kids groaning)
MILHOUSE:
My teeth!
Look, Lisa--
I made safety
happen.
(groans)
HOMER:
Safety tip 99:
always double-bolt your easel.
-(snapping)
-Ow! Son of...
(panting)
Uh... questions? Comments?
Are you a girl?
Cause I don’t see
a sala-wiener.
(laughing)
Did I hear
"Where are the fireworks?"
’Cause here they are!
(audience "oohing")
(screaming)
(Homer joins screaming)
Every man for himself!
Trample if you must!
(panicked screams)
(fire alarm blaring;
Homer panicking)
(kids straining)
(Homer sobbing)
Safety! Safety!
Die for safety!
(groaning sobs)
(siren wails)
So, sweetie,
am I your hero again?
Janey’s father just takes her
to the zoo once a month.
Couldn’t you be
that kind of dad?
Now, honey, you know
Daddy’s not allowed
in the zoo anymore.
Oh, yeah.
But I’ll never
stop trying
to redeem myself
in your eyes.
How did you do that?
I don’t know.
I said, turn left
on Bart Boulevard!
I’m tellin’ you there
t’ain’t no Bart Boulevard!
Forget it.
Baby’s already out.
Just get out
your huntin’ knife
and cut
the "umbrellical" cord.
Yes’m.
(tires screeching; crashing)
Hey!
Watch it!
Ow!
This is Kent Brockman,
live at the scene
of the worst accident
in Springfield history.
But not to worry,
the city’s emergency services
are on the way.
(sirens wailing)
(crashing)
(crashing and screaming)
Can we all agree not to get
our insurance involved?
Come on, people. Be cool.
Springfield needs a hero,
and it needs one now!
This looks like a job
for a dad trying to win back
his daughter’s love!
I’m forever indebted to you...
and my many creditors.
We were car pooling--
and that’s it!
My mother’s still
in the car!
No, she’s not.
Ha-ha!
Three cheers for
our new hero!
Only three?
Okay, six!
That’s more like it!
Hip-hip hurray!
Oh, please,
you’re embarrassing me.
I hereby award you
Springfield’s highest honor:
the key card to the city.
Now, any new business?
Mr. Mayor,
your administration has been
one fiasco after another!
Who the hell are you?
Your press secretary.
I knew I should have hired
my nephew.
I am your nephew.
Okay, so I stink.
Tough Toblerone.
Read the charter, people:
I cannot be removed from office.
Except by a simple
recall election...
Err, uh, disregard
that last part.
ALL (chanting):
Recall! Recall! Recall!
PARROTS: (squawking):
Mayor Diamond Joe Quimby
has survived
12 reelection campaigns,
countless accusations of
infidelity, bribery, extortion,
and his bizarre attempt
to hijack a 747.
Take this plane anywhere
girls are going wild.
But the Mayor may have
a tougher time
getting past next month’s
special recall election.
Over 200 candidates have filed,
including yours truly,
Kent Brockman.
In other news, a common
household fabric can kill you!
Find out which one when you vote
for Kent Brockman.
Dear God, every wacko, nutcase
and Disco Stu in this town
is gonna run against me.
Just imagine--
me, the mayor!
Then nobody would laugh
at my singin’!
♪ I’m proud
to be an American... ♪
I am so screwed.
Vote Luigi!
I make-a the good government,
just the way you like.
Vote for me,
a steroid-abusing,
pot-smoking,
woman-groping, son-of-a-Nazi,
washed-up, has-been movie star!
(cheering)
Oh, also, I believe
we should keep an open mind
towards stem cell research.
(crowd booing)
(Wolfcastle groans,
loud, angry chattering)
This election is
out of control.
Someone terrible
could win!
If you’re lame enough to vote,
vote for me.
ANNOUNCER:
Jimbo: Tough on nerds,
tougher on dorks.
Dad, we got to
do something.
What can I do?
I’m only one man.
Lincoln was only one man.
Are you sure there wasn’t
a midget in his hat?
I read an e-mail
that said there was.
Look, as the Safety
Salamander,
you are beloved
by all.
And if you were the Mayor,
we could make sure
that only good people,
like me, tell you what to do.
Hmm.
I will run for mayor!
And I will be
your campaign manager!
And I’ll find out
what a mayor does!
Expand my brain, learning juice!
Oh, I hate
press conferences.
Homie, you might
score more points
if you didn’t wear
that salamander suit.
You look like
the mascot
for some horrible
Southern college.
Marge, without this outfit,
I’m just Homer Simpson,
multiple felon.
With it,
I’m a costumed hero,
like George Washington
or Dame Edna.
(cheering, fanfare plays)
Today marks a new dawn
for Springfield.
This salamander is sitting
on eggs labeled "elder care,"
"flex-time,"
and "downtown pedestrian mall."
And those eggs
are ready to hatch!
(cheering)
Now, I will take your questions.
Uh, what special powers
would a salamander bring
to the office of mayor?
Well, there’s my X-ray vision,
my fire breath,
and I can get big laughs
with tennis balls.
Bloop, bloop, bloop.
(laughter)
Wow! l didn’t know
salamanders could do
all those things.
And to think, for
all these years, I’ve
been a gecko man.
Take a hike, jerk.
Mr. Simpson, what about
those photos of you
strangling your child?
Why should we let this election
be influenced
by a photo taken hours ago?
(cheering)
Now, restaurant matchbooks
for everyone!
CROWD ( chanting ):
Sala-mander!
Sala-mander! Sal...
Homer, you’re doin’ great.
You’re way ahead in the polls.
Even those negative campaign ads
aren’t hurting you.
Simpson barely even comes
into work anymore.
He pays a homeless man
to do it for him.
I, um...
I don’t feel so good, Blue.
(laughs)
Hey, people may not
love Homer Simpson,
but they love this suit.
(chuckles)
Just like they love their stupid
American flag.
(loud gulping)
Oh, what’s that smell?
It’s the smell
of impending victory.
-(retching)
-Did you just vomit in that
suit?
A little.
Oh!
Have you cleaned that suit once
since you got it?
No, but I swam in it.
Ugh! I’d better wash that thing.
It’s hard to know
where the suit ends
and you begin.
Yeah.
But aren’t you gonna
have fun finding out?
No!
(clucking)
That’s weird.
Started off as an egg.
KENT BROCKMAN:
Our next question goes
to Eleanor Abernathy,
also known
as the Crazy Cat Lady.
Uh, Cat Lady,
how would you boost the
city’s commercial tax base?
(speaking gibberish)
Small business incentives...
(gibberish continues)
Corporate accountability.
(speaking gibberish)
Cats in everyone’s pants!
All right, thank you, Cat Lady.
See you in the spin room.
(mumbling):
Okay, okeydokey... yeah.
Our next question is
for the Safety Salamander.
(cheering)
Sir, how would you restore our
city’s crumbling infrastructure?
That’s an excellent question,
Kent.
First of all...
What the...?
It must have shrunk
when my wife washed it!
Why without his costume,
he’s naught but a man!
Hey, screw this.
I’m not gonna let any human
tell me what to do.
That’s right. I am a man.
The man who dressed
like a salamander
to win back his daughter’s love.
Let’s meet her now.
Uh, well, my son is here, too.
Let’s meet him now.
BART:
Here’s... Bart!
Whassup?
(sing-songy):
Boring!
We’re sick of you
and your hatchlings!
(all booing)
Please, stop throwing fruit!
Oh!
(woozy whimper)
(thudding)
KENT BROCKMAN:
Our exit polls show
no candidate attained the
five percent necessary to win,
and Mayor Joe Quimby
will keep his job,
which I didn’t want anyway.
Your loss, jackasses.
(groaning)
Well, Dad, you tried
to make this town
a better place,
and no matter what,
that makes you my hero.
Aw, thanks.
Now how about a dance
with your daddy?
(Blue Danube Waltz plays)
I can’t believe I lost
after Ben Affleck campaigned
day and night for me.
LISA:
Yeah, I warned
you about that.
Oop! Be careful of my tail.
You don’t have a tail anymore.
I know. I... I still feel it.
Ooh!
It’s so itchy!
(Homer groaning and mumbling)
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem