CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
♪♪
(hammering)
-(sawing)
-(groans)
(jackhammer pounding)
(mumbling to beat
of hammering)
Homer! Do something
about the noise!
(mumbling funk melody
to construction sounds)
It’s 7:00 a.m.
What are they cock-a-doodily
doing?
Flanders, I can’t listen
to your crap before my coffee.
Okily-dokily,
here’s some French roast.
Now, I’ll go make toast.
Stupid best friend Flanders.
BART: A stamp museum?
(groans)
Oh! Stamps?
Those are for snail mail!
Stamps rule!
I mean suck!
Well, they can’t just start
building in our neighborhood
without asking us.
What ever happened to "please"
and "thank you"?
I think they killed
each other.
You know, one of those
murder-suicide deals.
We have to stop all this
construction.
The noise is jiggling my grapes
to the bottom of the Jell-O.
What man would want you now?
(chanting):
Two, four, six, eight,
I hate stamps,
They aren’t great!
Okay, how about this?
Seven, four, three, one...
Oh, wait,
that’s my PIN number.
Everyone forget that.
♪ Tell me over and over
and over again my friend ♪
♪ Ah, you don’t’ believe ♪
-♪ We’re on the eve
of destruction ♪
-Again! Again!
Again.
That’s enough.
-Whoa!
-♪ Don’t you understand
what I’m trying to say? ♪
♪ And can’t you feel the fears
I’m feeling today? ♪
♪ If the button is pushed... ♪
"Come home from Iraq,"
my wife says.
"Fallujah’s too dangerous,"
(whistles and cat calls)
♪ And you tell me over and over
and over again my friend ♪
-♪ You don’t believe we’re on
the eve of destruction... ♪
-(screams)
All right, Homer!
You beat those stamp Nazis
with good old-fashioned
American complaining.
Homer, if it weren’t for
you, we’d be at the mercy of
weekend philatelists.
You know, why didn’t you just
say "stamp collectors"?
’Cause I’m tired of dumbing
myself down for you.
The Postal Service is sending
a change of address card...
to itself.
The stamp museum will now be
built on the site
of the Springfield Cemetery.
The cemetery will be moved right
here, next to the Simpsons.
Oh, instead
of a stamp museum,
we’ll be next door
to a graveyard?
Look at the bright side,
Marge.
When I die, you can mourn me
from the bathroom.
That’s multitasking.
(groans)
This is a little too
spooky for me.
I don’t even like watching
the Count on Sesame Street.
One coconut, two coconuts,
three coconuts...
(ghoulish laugh)
Go back to your own country!
(bird squawks)
(door creaks)
-♪♪
-(owl hooting)
This stinks.
My room is the only one
that faces that cemetery.
Then the zombies
will eat you first,
and you won’t have
to watch them eat us.
Thanks for making me
feel better.
Well, thanks for making me
feel better,
knowing that your screams
when the zombies chomp
your brains
will warn me
so I can get away.
There’s no such thing
as zombies!
Oh, glad to hear you say that,
because the person
who doesn’t believe
in zombies
is always the first
to get feasted upon.
(grunts)
(snickering)
Stop scaring me!
(screams)
Bart, don’t you have
homework to do?
Yeah, and I could
really use your help.
(nervously): I believe in
science and reality,
not ghosts and monsters.
(meows)
(screams)
Can I sleep with you guys
tonight?
Oh, sure you can,
sweetie.
Just don’t make
a habit of it.
Okay, just let me
clear some space.
-Off you go.
-(loud clanking)
You, too.
Uh!
Hmm, so that’s why I’ve been
smelling margaritas at 3:00 a.m.
Hey, I love waking up
drunk in the morning.
(mutters restlessly)
(yells)
(groans): Oh...
Lisa, honey, I know
last night was tough,
but all our kids
sleep by themselves.
We don’t even hear Maggie
cry at night anymore.
Oh.
Wait a minute, there’s
no batteries in this thing.
I, uh, needed them
for my remote-control
helicopter.
Tonight, I want you
to really try to sleep
in your own bed,
because...
Homer, stop that!
There’s a little plastic man
in your hair,
and I’m trying to rescue him.
No soldier left behind.
Oh! Homer, can you help me
out here?
Lisa, honey, if you sleep
in your own bed tomorrow,
we’ll do something special
just for you.
Well, I heard they finished
the stamp museum.
That could be fun.
I can’t believe it took us
40 minutes to get here!
Why can’t they build
a stamp museum
closer to our house?
Dad, you fought tooth
and nail
to get it away
from our house.
Lisa,
when you’ve sustained
as many blows to the head
as I have,
consistency is something,
something that something...
I love you, Bart.
Isn’t this Lenny’s house?
Hey, Simpsons.
That’ll be 40 bucks.
Oh, I thought it was 20!
(chuckles): Yeah,
that’s per axle.
Park over there in Carl Four.
No early outs.
I can’t believe you’re making
money off this.
Oh-ho, yeah!
Living next to the stamp museum
is making me a mint!
I bought a diamond
for my belly button!
You guys need water?
No one’s gonna pay a buck
to drink water from your hose,
so... D'oh!
Pay the man, Homer.
Wow! Look at all these
worthy Americans.
My name is Frederick Ives.
I invented the halftone
printing process.
Thanks to me,
Katherine Blodgett,
-we have nonreflecting glass.
-Yeesh! Butter face.
And I’m Alexander Graham Bell,
inventor of the telephone.
You stole it from me,
Elisha Gray.
Read the patent number,
bitch!
The Land
of the Wild Beasts?
That’s the first book
I read all the way through.
You read a book all the way
through? Why?
Milton Burkhart’s work
has touched
on every genre from books
to films to advertising.
All right! Commercials!
NARRATOR: Once upon a time,
a bad boy was sent to bed
without any dinner.
But then,
something magical happened.
Huh? (gasps)
Is this the Land of
the Wild Beasts?
No, this is the
Land of the Wild Feasts!
The Hillside Wrangler Steak
House!
I’m a $4.99 steak.
I’m all-you-can-eat
salad bar!
Yo, and I’m Sneeze Guard.
Put it on
the glass, dawgs.
(pounding steps)
And I’m Jumbo Shrimp!
Maximum two servings!
That’s bull (bleep),
man!
♪♪
I love you,
Hillside Wrangler!
(applause)
Tell us, Mr. Burkhart,
what led you
to the magical world of
children’s books?
I wanted to be
a children’s book illustrator
ever since Playboy wouldn’t
publish my cartoons
because they were
too filthy.
♪♪
(thunder crashing)
Groundskeeper Willie?
No, I’m his cousin,
Gravedigger Billy.
I’ve been digging graves
for 30 years,
and I’ve never buried
anyone alive.
If I did,
they’d ring this bell.
Well, that’s just the wind.
Oh, that’s just
a tree branch,
with a nice watch on it!
(grunting)
(thunder crashes)
Ah!
MARGE:
What a lousy party!
I don’t care
what Apu was in a past life,
In this life,
he’s a blabbermouth!
Oh, and that Dr. Hibbert
was so boring.
"Homer, we’ve got to get
that lump checked out."
"Homer, we must discuss
your test results."
"Homer, we’ve got
to find you a donor."
Blah, blah, blah.
LISA: I thought
those people were
your friends.
(groans):
Look who’s sleeping
in our bed again.
I didn’t know grownups said
bad things about other grownups.
You see, sweetie,
when a mommy and daddy
are married for years
and have nothing
new to talk about,
they bad-mouth their closest
friends.
But I thought it was wrong
to talk about people
behind their backs.
I spy with my little eye
a girl who’s not sleeping
in her room like she promised.
I know. I’m sorry.
Oh, and I spy with
my little eye
something with four legs
that can’t run.
Homer, we’re not
really playing.
-Oh!
-Is it the chair?
Exactly! Now, what has two ears
but can’t hear?
-Grandpa!
-Tragically, yes.
What if we show Lisa
we can sleep in her room
without being frightened,
hm?
Okay, Marge.
But don’t be surprised
if a snuggle monster shows up.
Well, I hope
he’s accompanied
by the "How Was Your Day"
monster
and the "Foot Rub" monster,
and the "Let Me Just..."
Don’t worry,
he’s not showing up.
(scratching)
(frightened gasps)
Boy, Lisa’s room
really is scary.
Now, Willie, the pot of gold
I saw is right down there.
All I see is an empty grave.
Why don’t you fill it,
you lazy bastard!
Finally! Back in the only
safe bedroom in the house.
What about Bart’s bedroom?
You know that race car bed
I made him?
-Yeah.
-The brakes are shot.
Ow.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Lisa, honey, any chance
you could stop reading soon?
Okay, I’ll watch TV.
ANNOUNCER: Now, RerunLand takes
you back to 1965 with Bonanza.
See here, Cartwright,
your boys have been
eating my apples.
That doesn’t sound like
my boys.
I’ll thank you to keep
a civil tongue.
(Bonanza theme plays)
Oh, Lisa, do you really
want to watch this?
Mom, I think there’s
a danger this time
they might lose
the Ponderosa.
(crash) Ow.
Learn to drive, boy!
(sighs): We need
professional help.
As a young child, did Lisa
receive a lot of nurturing?
Frankly, no.
Lisa kind of took care
of herself.
Our oldest, Bart,
was such a handful.
Did you bring those home movies
of your daughter I asked for?
Uh...
this is all I could find.
HOMER:
Why you very little...!
-(grunting)
-(choking)
Homer, stop that!
Oh?
Who was filming that scene?
Stationary camera.
I see.
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
to overcome her neglect,
Lisa had to suppress her
childhood fears.
My ten-week program can help
her learn to be a kid again.
Well worth the $4,000.
$4,000?
Now, Marge, when our
little girl’s happiness
is at stake... (gasps)
Run, Marge! Start the car!
(loud grunts)
I’m not chasing you,
Mr. Simpson.
And you won’t!
Unless you can leap
through fire!
I can’t keep sleeping
in Mom and Dad’s room.
Yeah, if Dad rolls over,
you’re dead.
Mom showed me how to make
a retaining wall
out of pillows.
But I’m going to conquer
my fears... tonight.
(gate creaks)
(clangs)
(owl hoots)
(gasping)
(grunting)
(jingling)
(yells)
I changed my mind!
Can you please
open the gate?
Hmm?
Oh, I don’t work here.
I was just visiting another
security guard that died.
Bye, now.
(keys jingling)
(wolf howls in distance)
(whimpers)
If I can just spend
the night here,
I’ll never be scared again.
And, boy, you’re free to go
home whenever you want.
(gasps)
Hi, Dr. Nick.
Hi, everybody!
I mean, uh,
I’m not Dr. Nick.
I’m... Dr. Octopus.
Ha!
I’m going to get you,
Spidey.
Then I will have upside-down
kiss with Mary Jane.
Bye, Dr. Nick.
Bye, Lisa.
And remember, you have
a checkup next Thursday.
We don’t go
to you anymore.
We have a better doctor.
Oh, congratulations!
Boys, that grave robber
could be anywhere.
The most vital thing
is that we stick together.
Wait.
Where did everybody go?
Okay, this is it, Clancy.
No squad car, no backup,
legs cramping in fear,
sweat in my eyes
and groin...
Oh, I’d better get out
of this damn cop uniform
before someone
takes a shot at me.
There we go.
Oh, hey, there’s my Walkman.
(music playing)
You know, I actually
got into law school,
but I just couldn’t
afford it.
Quiet, I hear something.
Yeah, that’s my life
slipping away.
(guns cock)
Okay, got to keep calm.
If Scooby Doo
has taught me anything,
it’s that the only thing
to fear
are crooked
real estate developers.
(snaps)
(owl hoots)
(screams)
Whoa...
(grunts)
(groans)
Where’s Lisa, boy?
This book’s going to solve
all her problems.
Well, if you’re looking
for Lisa,
she said she was going
to spend the night
in the bone yard out back.
The cemetery?
And you’re just
sitting here?
I figured the best thing
I could do
is monitor the news
for any reports.
You’re watching
cartoons!
Hmm! Just the show for me!
Tim-Tom Tabby
is a curious cat.
Went to see the queen
in a velveteen hat.
(moans)
This is so boring!
Shh!
(laughing)
Hey, Mom, can we have
fried chicken for dinner?
HOMER/MARGE: Lisa!
BOTH: Lisa! Lisa!
Don’t worry,
we’re not evil spirits!
Although,
if we were evil spirits,
we’d probably assume
the shape of your parents.
Homer!
Marge, we owe her
the truth.
(screaming)
(grunts)
There, there, dear.
Grandma will protect you.
But I ain’t grandma!
(screaming)
Oh, whoa-whoa-whoa!
(gasps)
Lisa, meet
your new husband.
(chuckles)
I made us a dream house
out of slime!
I don’t know
how I reproduce,
but we’ll have a great time
figuring it out.
(screams)
(grunts)
(groans)
Where am I?
(growling and roaring)
(screaming)
Welcome to the Land of
Wild Beasts, little girl.
(growling and roaring)
(whimpers)
Not scared. Not scared.
For God’s sake, girl,
you’re eight years old.
It’s natural for you
to feel scared sometime.
But I’m too smart
to get scared.
Lisa, everybody
gets scared,
no matter how old
or how smart they are.
In fact,
I’m scared of her.
No, you’re afraid
of intimacy.
That’s because I know
after we mate,
you’ll eat me.
Your brother
didn’t seem to mind.
You know,
you monsters seem scary,
but when you get
a little closer...
(chuckles):
You’re just funny.
(grunting approval)
But wait.
How am I supposed to sleep
with that spooky cemetery
outside my window?
You could just draw the blinds,
you silly goose.
Or get a night-light.
My dad says
they’re too expensive.
(grumbling disapproval)
For God’s sake,
they’re four bucks apiece.
I could slime your dad,
just like I slimed us
a Paris honeymoon.
I think I’ll be
okay by myself.
What is it about slime
that chicks don’t dig?
Bye, guys.
You’ve really
helped me a lot.
-Bye-bye, Lisa.
-Bye, Lisa!
See you soon!
We’re always
just a concussion away!
Lisa, honey,
please wake up.
If you do,
I’ll get you a new pony.
New pony?
Uh... this is still
part of your dream.
(singsongy):
Dreaming... dreaming...
Now you’re awake.
Oh. Mmm!
Sweetie, we’re going
to get you home
and straighten out
all these fears you have.
I think I’m going
to be fine.
Let’s get
some breakfast.
Uh, Chief, it’s light out.
You can open your eyes
and come down.
I don’t want to, Lou!
I’ve got a pizza bagel
for you.
Let’s roll.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem.