CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Children, we have
a special treat today.
Willie?
(cheering)
(groaning)
(gasping)
NARRATOR (on TV):
Welcome to Diversity Tales.
(moaning)
Enjoy your
multicultural hooey.
(laughing)
MALE NARRATOR (on TV):
It was the Feast of the
Sea Lion Who Would Not Share.
Come, brother Titi,
let us collect
cha-cha sticks.
I will make a headdress
for the wedding of
Earth Turtle and Moon Mongoose.
You don’t need a headdress.
Your most beautiful costume
is your self-esteem.
NARRATOR (on TV): Pause here
to discuss tolerance.
What is this crap?
This is worse than
"Wheelchair-nocchio."
Yeah, well,
if you don’t like the movie,
feel free to stare
out the window. Ha.
(car sputtering)
Hey, Crypt Keeper,
I like your
Dodge Scare-a-van.
(laughter)
How dare you mock
my mobile-a-mobile?
It was the first car
to outrun a man.
A caveman.
(laughter)
I thought of that ’cause
I slept in a cave last night.
Of all the...
I will not be lampooned
by schoolchildren.
Kill them, Smithers.
Uh, you could just
buy a new car, sir.
Well... whatever’s easier.
A new car?
May I suggest
an Oldsmobile?
Mr. Burns sucks!
(laughter)
Ooh, I won’t forget
who mocked me.
I’m taking your picture.
Now, hold perfectly still
for 78 minutes.
(Mr. Burns snoring)
HOMER:
Bomp, bomp, bomp, bomp,
bomp, bomp, bomp, bomp.
Bomp, bomp, bomp, bomp.
(imitating "Charge" anthem)
-Simpson?
-Charge!
I mean, "Yes, sir?"
I just bought
a new car.
A nice foreign number.
The Lamborgotti Fasterossa.
A Lamborgotti
Fasterossa?
That’s the car
I think about
when I make love
to my wife.
Yes. I need you
to pick up my car
at the factory in Italy,
and ship it
directly back to me.
I’ll save thousands
in taxes.
You’re sending me to Italy?
Yes.
-Can I take my family?
-Sure.
Do I have to hang out with them?
It would be nice.
(screaming)
(groaning)
Hey, that guy in first class is
taking a TV out of his armrest.
What’s in you?
Oh, a bunch of stupid cables.
(thunderous crash)
Hey, Brandine?
The kids just got
a new playhouse!
Cletus, you are the most
wonderful husband--
and son-- I ever had.
What’s with
the Canadian flag
on your backpack?
Well, some people in Europe
have the impression
that America has made
some stupid choices
in the past, oh, five years.
So, for the next week,
I’m from Canada.
Uh, I think Dad
may blow your cover.
That flag is mine!
Don’t mess with Texas!
Shock and awe, losers!
Shock and awe!
(with Italian accent):
Your car, she’s a-coming
off the assembly line.
This car is
the ultimate marriage
of design and technology.
Ooh, marriage.
Now we have to drive it
straight to Rome,
where it’ll be shipped
to Mr. Burns in Springfield.
Gee, I wish
we could explore
a little
more of Italy.
Marge, are you encouraging me
to be irresponsible?
Why don’t you encourage him
to get us some health insurance?
Why you little...
(Bart choking;
Homer groaning)
So, first time in Italy?
(tires squealing)
HOMER:
Wow, I’ve seen photos of this,
but you can’t really
experience it until you’re here:
a McDonald’s
where you can get booze!
But, Dad, don’t you want
to turn around
and see the tower?
Eh, there’s a picture of it
on my cup.
When Mount Vesuvius
erupted,
people were overcome
by volcanic ash so fast
that they were frozen
in whatever position
they were in
at the moment
of their death.
Savages.
MARGE: We’ve passed
the Pontevecchio bridge
three times.
I think we’re lost.
Let me check
the navigation system.
It says here we should turn left
at a fat chick in a tutu
being fed by a midget.
That’s a DVD
of a Fellini movie.
I get it.
The midget represents dwarves.
Dad, cheese truck!
(tires screeching)
(screaming)
Mozzarella!
Parmigiano!
Provolone!
Pecorino!
Gorgonzola!
Fontina!
Taleggio!
Bocconcini!
(splattering)
(screams)
LISA:
Mortadella!
(crashing)
Don’t worry.
We got the cheese insurance.
It doesn’t cover
mortadella.
No!
(all straining)
Stupid Italy.
Wish you’d never
been unified
by Victor Emmanuel II.
If only you’d stayed
a loose confederation
of city-states,
trading with each other
and occasionally warring.
LISA:
Maybe there’s a mechanic
in this Tuscan village.
Hey, do you know anything
about fixing sports cars?
Scusi?
(louder):
It’s a Lamborgotti
Fasterosa XT 550
with ABS Sport
Tech package.
(groans)
Americano?
What the hell
could that mean?
Why can’t you people learn
to speak my language?
I learned to eat
your food.
Il Mayore
capice Inglese.
Hey, she says
the mayor speaks English.
I honor you
and your country.
(shrieks)
"Kentucky?!"
In Italia,
this a-means "whore"!
Excuse me?
Mister Mayor?
They say
you speak English?
Indeed I do.
ALL:
Sideshow Bob!
The Simpsons!
(all scream)
BART:
Sideshow Bob?
Of all the regioni
and all the villaggi
in all of Italia,
you had to be
il mayore of this one!
I assure you, I’m as sorry to
see you as you are to see me.
How’d you wind up here?
Yes,
tell us your story.
But it better have a beginning,
a middle and an end.
And you’d better make us
root for the protagonist.
My tale begins after I had once
again attempted to murder Bart.
Okay, so far
I’m rooting for you.
I needed a fresh start.
But where?
Not in this lifetime!
Damn it!
Never!
Now cut that out.
Ah, Tuscany.
Fortune is finally
smiling upon me.
(mutters angrily)
I left my past behind
and moved to the small village
of Salsiccia.
Acceptance came slowly.
It’s pronounced "buon giorno."
Your mouth is getting lazy
on the second syllable.
Here, let me guide you.
But that all changed
when the grape harvest began.
(people groaning)
(all gasp)
♪ These feet are made
for stomping ♪
♪ And that’s just
what they’ll do ♪
♪ One of these days
these feet will make ♪
♪ Chianti out of you ♪
Ready, feet?
Start stomping.
(hums lively tune)
(cheers)
It was the biggest
harvest ever.
Never had I felt
such acceptance.
The next spring, the contadini
elected me their mayor.
But I won more than
the love of a town.
WOMAN:
Roberto...
Amore.
This is my bride Francesca
and my son Gino.
Holy moley!
I always thought you were,
you know, out loud and proud.
Well, I experimented
in college, as one does.
Yeah.
I never went to college.
Stop the presses.
Hello, I’m Marge.
This is my husband Homer,
my daughters Lisa and Maggie,
and my son Bart Simpson.
Bart Simpson?
The name Roberto cries
when he has the bad dream.
Bart Simpson! Bart Simpson!
Bart Simpson!
I make like my daddy!
(stabbing noises)
(chuckles)
Yes.
Bart and I used
to go fly-fishing together.
Die, Bart! Die, Bart!
(groans)
You shall all stay for dinner
and tell me more
about my wonderful Roberto.
(sighs)
He makes love like a man
who just got out of jail.
(chuckles)
Yes, yes.
You crave my skillful touch.
Now go, take the boy,
and shut the door.
I’ll rock your world anon.
Simpsons, I beg of you.
Please don’t destroy
the new life I’ve created here.
Surely, even the most
heinous criminal
deserves a seventh chance.
Bob, you haven’t told your wife
about all the terrible things
you’ve done?
Yeah, I tell Marge everything.
Not necessarily in words,
but in body language.
You know, sneaking around
and such.
Bob, your family
will find out the truth.
Sooner or later,
you’ll try to kill me again.
Watch, I’ll prove it.
Come on, Bob, slice,
dice and serve on rice.
You little scamp.
(laughs)
You know, you’ll make some
murderer very happy one day,
but it shan’t be me.
Bart, Bob is
a family man now.
You can’t be a bad person
if you have a family.
And literature is filled
with tales of redemption
from Jean Valjean to the voice
of Buzz Lightyear, Tim Allen.
All right, Bob, we won’t tell
your beautiful new family
that you’re a homicidal
psychopath
if you fix up our car.
Grazie.
Now I can’t undo the past,
but I can try
to make it up to you.
My humble little town
is at your service.
Loro sono miei amici,
le Simpsons!
(cheering)
Dad, don’t act
like Mussolini.
Ooh, I thought I was
doing Donald Trump.
Here’s a cute fact.
This sausage shop
has been grinding
the same family of pigs
for 600 years.
Prego?
Si, si.
(muffled noises)
And he kisses you
with that mouth.
I love you, Marge.
(kissing noises)
(Sideshow Bob laughing
and speaking Italian)
(kids laugh)
He is so wonderful.
They must miss him
in America.
Uh, well...
Eat justice, Sideshow Bob!
Chief, I tried to warn you.
Sideshow Bob hasn’t
lived here for months.
Oh, God, am I sorry.
(chuckles)
Oh, hey, is that
a Penn State banner?
’Cause my cousin went there.
Did you know him?
Mark Wiggum, fat kid,
played a lot of Tetris.
(tapping on glass)
Mi amici, we are here to honor
my old friends, the Simpsons.
Tomorrow, they return
to America,
taking with them my gratitude,
my friendship
and my heartfelt wish
that they never return.
And now... mangiata!
No wine for her.
She’s only eight.
Marge, don’t be
so Olive Garden.
Yeah, this is Italy.
Look, the town drunk
is two years old.
♪ Hey, mambo ♪
♪ Mambo Italiano ♪
(burps)
(Italian music plays)
Bob, your
generosity and...
abbondanza have
touched our hearts.
(cheering and applause)
Bra-Bravo!
Bravissimo!
Whoopsie.
I’ll just get it out
with more wine.
See? It’s fine.
Go on, go on with the thing.
(groans)
It’s obvious
why Bob is a vaunted pillar
of your community.
Yeah, but he’s a wanted killer
in our community.
(laughs)
(squeaks)
He deserves to be hailed
at this wingding.
More like jailed
at Sing Sing.
Time for bed, now.
-(laughs)
-(groaning)
Drunken children
tell the ugliest lies.
(chuckling)
(giggling)
(groaning)
(yells)
(all gasping)
(screams):
Sideshow Bob!
Sideshow Bob?
Il fuggitivo?
BOTH: Hmm?
Roberto.
Is this true? You try
to make the murder?
But darling, the boy
drove me to murder
by exonerating
a harlequin
who I framed for robbery
at the Kwik-E-Mart.
Oh, it all sounds so stupid.
You have brought shame
upon our humble,
Mafia-controlled village.
You are welcome in
Salsiccia no more.
(grunts)
(bleating)
(sinister grumbling)
Uh-oh. He’s getting
that stabby look.
Simpson family,
I hereby swear a...
(Italian accent):
vendetta.
"Vendetta" means...
"vendetta"!
(all scream)
Boy, that Sideshow Bob
goes from zero
to murder awfully fast.
At least this time it was Lisa
who ruined Bob’s life.
Oh, I feel so sick.
(laughs)
It’s called
a hangover, sweetie.
And it’s an unavoidable
part of life.
BURNS:
Simpson? Simpson!
Where is my
roadster?
You were due back
a month ago.
Mr. Burns, we may be
experiencing
some technical difficulties.
(both groaning)
(laughing)
Sideshow Bob!
(tires screeching,
engine revving)
Oh, Dad, you’re driving
on an ancient Roman aqueduct.
What am I supposed
to use it for--
transporting water
to distant urban centers?!
(engine revving)
Uh-oh.
Lazy Romans.
(engine whining)
(screaming)
(loud, rumbling thud)
Hmm?
HOMER:
Everyone, remember
where we parked.
(engine stopping)
(Homer and Marge whimpering)
(loud, anguished cry)
Why do I keep trying
to kill them?
Roberto!
Francesca,
you’ve come to me.
Well, you caught me
at the right time
because I swear never
to raise this hand
in vengeance again.
No, Roberto.
If the Simpsons
have dishonored you,
they have dishonored our family,
and we shall take revenge
as a family.
Vendetta! Vendetta!
Vendetta for mi papa!
(whipping air)
(clink)
Ah, revenge is a dish
best served
family-style.
(laughing)
(sinister laugh)
(cries)
We’re in a foreign city
with no car,
being stalked by a killer.
I feel like
I’m the Bourne Identity.
(tires squeaking)
Hey, Krusty’s
in an opera here in Rome.
He can save our lives.
Come on. Let’s go.
Oh! Opera?
They have that here, too?
Ugh!
Let’s see. Uh...
Oh, I ain’t doin’ that.
Oh, that’s not funny.
Here we’ll change
"wealthy merchant"
to "nudist with big rack."
This needs punching up.
That’s comin’ out.
Two acts?!
Krusty, you gotta help us.
I don’t do gotta.
Sideshow Bob has sworn
a vendetta against us.
Vendetta? What’s that,
an Italian vending machine?
(screams)
That’s my opening joke.
And my closer.
And my saver.
And my topper.
(cries)
Please help us, Krusty.
We don’t want to be
the first Christians
to die at the
Colosseum.
I’ll tell ya what.
Put on these costumes,
go on the stage
and mix in
with the crowd scenes.
He won’t kill ya in front
of all those witnesses.
Can I be the Phantom
of the Opera?
Dad, the Phantom isn’t in this.
But I do a great impression
of him.
Um, I am the gayest
super villain ever.
Beware my
scented candles.
Ooh, scented.
(to tune of aria):
♪ No more Rice Krispies ♪
♪ We are out
of Rice Krispies... ♪
(laughing and sobbing)
(all gasping)
Hey, don’t blame me.
I didn’t write this crap.
I can’t believe
what that clown
is doing to Leoncavallo.
And they call me a murderer.
Vendetta. Vendetta! Vendetta...!
I don’t wish to brag,
but he’s evil
at an eighth grade level.
Vendetta!
Let’s see, what else
we got here? Uh...
So, I had this beautiful
tour guide, right?
And I tell her,
I want to see her Naples.
She slapped me.
(slight chuckle)
We call it Napoli.
Yeah, well, it sounds like
you’re all taking a "napoli."
I know you’re out there.
I can hear you being greasy.
(grunts)
♪ Ridi, Pagliaccio ♪
♪ Sul tuo amore infranto... ♪
(cheering and applause)
It’s so beautiful.
That’s Sideshow Bob!
I know, and he’s magic.
(orchestra plays)
This is no act.
They’re actually trying
to kill us!
(all gasping)
♪ Ridi del duol ♪
♪ Che t’avvelena il cor...! ♪
(satisfied sighs)
La commedia è finita.
(laughs)
Quick, get in!
(tires squealing)
Krusty,
you saved us!
Well, I need someone
to help me smuggle antiquities
to America.
Everyone, break off a piece
and hide it on your person.
Hide it well.
Vendetta! Vendetta! Vendetta!
Farfalla.
Farfalla vendetta!
Oh, Homie, isn’t
Venice romantic?
This gondola ride
was a wonderful idea.
♪ When a wife looks like that
and her husband’s so fat ♪
♪ That’s immoral ♪
♪ When she kisses that jerk
while I do all the work ♪
♪ That’s imm... ♪
Hey, knock it off.
Excusi. No speaka English.
♪ When a big tub of lard... ♪
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem