CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(alarm beeps)
-(alarm beeps)
-Oh.
(rapid beeping)
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
We got a real nail-biter here
at Mile High Stadium.
The Broncos down by one,
and 30 seconds left
on the clock.
Come on, Broncos,
you can do it.
And I’m joined
in the broadcast booth
by the stars of ABC’s
latest reality show,
Billionaire Versus Bear.
Let’s review the easy-to-follow
rules of your show.
Each of you thought
you were in a race
to plant the Taco Bell flag
at the North Pole.
What you didn’t know is,
the race was a chase,
spiced up by the presence
of the Betrayer.
(groaning)
Well, now, the bear
has a surprise for you.
He’s not really a bear,
he’s a tiger!
Ho! Lookie there!
Denver just won the ballgame!
Oh, the Broncos won?
Why didn’t I bet on them
like Professor Pigskin
told me to?
Who’s Professor Pigskin?
He’s a pig who can predict
football winners
in advance!
How is that possible?
Because he’s got something
no gambler’s ever had:
a system!
I’ve gotten the pamphlet
four weeks in a row,
and every time,
the pick-of-the-week
has been right on the money.
Ah... I get it.
Every week,
they send out two pamphlets,
half picking one team and half
picking the other.
Eventually,
there’s a small group of people
who only receive
the correct predictions
and think Professor Pigskin
is always right.
That’s when they ask
for your money.
(gasps): I have money!
Dad, it’s a scam!
A scam?! Not according
to Eddie F. from Tucson,
or Football Millionaire
in Beloit, Michigan.
Look, all I’m saying is,
you really should think
twice before...
Expiration date: 06/08.
Oh, Professor Pigskin told me
to bet on the Raiders,
but they look awful!
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
And with 37 starting players
out with the flu,
the Oakland Raiders
have turned to drunks
conscripted from local bars.
Spare some change,
football dude?
Aah!
Now, you have a good day.
Dad, how much money
did you bet?
Hey, I didn’t bet
any of our money.
I just borrowed
some from him.
Don’t worry,
we can hammer out
a payment plan.
Ow! Ow! It’s not my fault
the Raiders lost!
It’s Professor Pigskin’s!
If he mentions
that pig again, use two hammers.
But the pig... Ow! Ow!
Now, I do have a way
we could settle this debt.
We would like to use your home
to shoot an adult film.
Yeah, it’s called
Lemony Lick-it:
A Series of Horny Events.
(gasps):
Marge would kill me!
Please! There’s got to be
something else I can do.
Like mow your lawn
every week for two weeks.
I can’t do it next week.
Ow-ha-ow! All right!
You can shoot your gay
adult film at my house.
I didn’t say anything
about gay.
I thought you guys
were the Gay Mafia.
Ow!
HOMER:
Oh, they’re shooting
an adult film
at my house tomorrow.
How am I gonna get rid
of Marge and the kids?
Well, I got these
free tickets to Santa’s Village.
I know a guy
who turns the dead
sleigh horses into jerky
and sells it to bars.
Ew...
Thanks, Moe!
Why would we want
to go to Santa’s Village?
It’s August.
I want to see Santa--
he can explain
why he gave me
a PlayStation box
with nothing inside
but a coloring book.
It got your hopes up,
didn’t it?
Uh, Homer,
before I take the kids,
I want you to swear
you’re not up to something.
-I swear.
-And I’d also
like to know
why your hand
is in that cast.
Because you look
even more beautiful now
than the day I married you.
Oh...
-(flies buzzing)
-Welcome to Santa’s Village,
where it’s Christmas
every day.
Closed on Christmas.
Those reindeer look
really uncomfortable.
That’s because they don’t
thrive in this environment!
Watcha reading, Santa?
Tom Clancy’s Op-Center.
You don’t seem
very jolly.
Well, Santa
got some bad medical news.
Okay... okay...
And... action!
We’ve been on this spaceship
for a hundred years.
When will we ever
get to Planet Satisfaction?
Hey, Homer, we...
Whoa!
Angela Dare!
Sultry Stevens!
Yeah, what is this,
a reunion of Fahrenheit 9 on 1?
Guys! Get out of here!
Homer, how’d you ever get Marge
to go along with this?
Look, if you promise
never to tell her,
I’ll let you be in the movie.
We just came over
to borrow a board game,
but okay.
I’ve always dreamed
of working in
an adult film.
I’ll run the sound board!
And I’ll perform
in the sex scenes!
Merry Christmas!
I’m your old pal
Frosty the Snowman!
In your dreams.
Frosty!
Where’s your magic top hat?
Oh, God, please don’t tell Mr.
Roselli I lost my hat again!
(whistling)
My Christmas present
to myself this year
was leaving
that place early.
Mom...
I got a rash
where the reindeer licked me.
Hah?
When they put Santa
in the ambulance,
why’d they pull the blanket
all the way up over his head?
Now, look, I know this
wasn’t the greatest outing,
but your father meant well,
so don’t let him know
that we didn’t... Aah!
Are you guys
almost done?
Listen, uh, I got
a tattoo of Foghorn Leghorn
on my right thigh.
Are we gonna get into
any trademark or copyright
issues here?
’Cause we could put
a Band-Aid on it
and say my character
just got stabbed.
Relax, three guys’ll put their
hands on it, okay?
Now, everybody
is very much in love.
And... action!
Homer! Is this
a snuggle film?
Uh... You’re in
the wrong house, lady!
How could you allow this,
in the room where we do
puzzles!
(groans)
Honey, please, just listen
to what I have to say.
All right.
I owed the Mafia money.
Oh!
Where are you going?
Away from you.
-When will you be back?
-I don’t know.
-Who’s going
to watch the kids?
-You are.
Me? But I’m the father!
(tires squeal)
Boy, Homer, I’ve never
see Mom this mad.
Honey, come back!
You didn’t say
bye to the kids!
Bye, Bart.
I love you, Lisa.
Sleep tight, Maggie.
Today’s the last day
you can eat the yogurt
in the fridge.
Well, we better go eat
that yogurt.
Kids, I’m sure your mother
will be back soon.
She should be back now.
It’s dinnertime.
Look, we’ve been down
this road before.
I do something stupid,
your mom leaves,
we eat waffles.
We’re out of waffles.
All we got is ketchup.
You mean Homer’s
famous marinara sauce?
No, I mean ketchup.
Where’s your sense
of magic and wonder?!
Come on, Marge.
When are you going to call?
(phone rings)
Huh? Let it ring,
play hard to get.
That’s hard enough!
Oh, my darling, I love you!
Please forgive me!
MOE: Hey, Homer.
Moe, what are you
calling me for?
You told me to call.
You wanted to see
if your phone was working.
But what if Marge tries to call
while I’m talking to you?
Ain’t you got call waiting?
Of course, I have call waiting,
you idiot!
I just never learned
how to use it!
Uh-oh, I might have
broken the phone.
I better call Moe.
Oh, hey, Homer.
Moe, will you get off
the line?!
(sighs)
(gasps)
(resignedly):
I guess I better tell them
I’m coming home.
-(snoring)
-(phone rings)
Uh, oh, Marge,
what a pleasant surprise.
I’m at a rest stop
south of Springfield.
I know. You’re sorry now.
Then you’ll buy me
some Quickie Mart flowers,
maybe a box of candy,
where half the pieces
mysteriously have testing bites,
and a week later you’ll be back
to your old thoughtless self.
No, no, it’s not going
to be like that, I swear.
Ew, lemon cream.
You’re going
in the Marge pile.
I mean, I love you so much.
Yeah, I love you, too.
(loud banging)
Hold on.
I’ll be off in a minute.
(guttural honking)
Listen, buster, I had to buy
a club soda I didn’t want
to get change for this phone.
(gasps)
An oogly-boogly!
(roaring)
Be still.
Don’t give it the phone.
Settle down, Sugar Plum.
Look what Daddy’s
got in his pocket.
Yummy, yummy kelp.
Good girl, yes, yes.
This animal
means you no harm.
She’s a sweet old Florida
manatee,
also known
as a sea cow or dugong.
Hello, Marge,
where do we keep the socks
that don’t smell like feet?
I’ll call you back.
I’m Dr. Caleb Thorn,
and I would do anything
to protect a manatee
except harm
another manatee.
What if by harming
a manatee
you could save
two manatees?
But before you answer,
consider this:
the manatee you have
to harm is pregnant.
Those are the questions
that keep me up at night.
(groaning)
I see a manatee
that needs a hug.
Ooh...
Hello, Marge?
Does the pizza guy
take a check?
If so, where do
we keep the checks?
And lastly, how do you
write a check?
Oh!
I think the worst part
was when I realized
that Homer lied to me.
From what you’ve told me,
it sounds like
what your husband
did is nothing new.
Exactly.
I have a saying
which goes,
"You can’t teach a manatee
any tricks."
Maybe you could just
put a hat on him
and say it’s a trick.
My point is Homer is the exact
same man you married,
and if there’s a problem here,
it’s that you keep
expecting him to change.
Huh.
He cares so much
about those doggone dugongs.
I wish I felt
that kind of passion.
Maybe I should join him
on his mission.
Hey, lady blue,
while you’re sitting
there staring at the ceiling,
you boyfriend’s
in the parking lot
with his hands
in a walrus.
Yeah, that’ll be good
for business.
Got to find your mom.
BART: Dad, I promise
I’ll be good.
Can I get out
of the dog carrier?
It was hard enough
getting you in there.
I’m not letting you out.
Yeah, she came through here.
I believe she was looking
to rekindle her
passion for life.
Ain’t that right, Victor?
Oh, yes.
Señora left for the coast
with a rugged,
yet sensitive man of science.
Rugged?
Is that the same as handsome?
Oh, no, no.
"Handsome" means
he look at himself
in the mirror all day.
"Rugged"
means you look at him.
Oh...!
Okay, water monsters,
be friendly...
but not too friendly.
What do I do?
Talk to it!
Let it know
you’re not a threat.
Oh, okay. You know, up close
you’re kinda cute.
(retching)
Oh, you’re a good thing.
I know it.
Let me clean out
your ears.
(soft groaning)
I’ve bonded with him!
(laughs)
Whoa!
Where is he taking me?
To his underwater palace.
Just kidding.
It’s a lagoon
full of bugs.
(Marge screaming)
Dad, I don’t think
we’re going to find Mom today.
And I’m sick of eating
at restaurant chains
I’ve never even heard of like
Skobo’s and Dim Willie’s.
(Bart groans)
Okay, kids,
we’ll stop for the day.
I have cousins near here.
We’ll stay with them.
Country cousins?
Are they rubes?
’Cause I don’t cotton
to rubes.
Oh, the rubiest.
Ooh, look,
a new restaurant chain.
Whoo-hoo!
Can we say it’s my birthday
and get free stuff?
We’ll say it’s all our
birthdays.
(muttering):
I cannot believe it.
Cousin Homer,
how are you?
And this must be
Bart and Lisa.
Well, aren’t you
nice-looking kids.
Hey, do you folks
want to see a quilt
that’s been in our family
for five generations?
I warned you
he was an idiot.
(country drawl):
Well, all I need
is some moonshine
and someone playing
the harmonicky
and I’m as happy
as a pig in plop.
We’re having lasagna
and Caesar salad.
Don’t laugh.
They’re doing
the best they can.
(sighs)
So, Homer, how are you?
Oh, just great.
Things couldn’t be better.
And how is our
lovely Marge?
She, uh, was killed by
a falling air conditioner.
But that’s terrible!
It wasn’t all bad.
As part of the settlement,
her funeral was air conditioned.
Now if you’ll
excuse me,
I have to use
the outhouse again.
Well, we don’t have
an outhouse.
My recording studio!
So how are we related again?
Our dogs are brothers.
BART: Oh, yeah.
I see Mom!
(laughing)
I’ve got my groove back!
We’ve got to tell Dad!
Where is he?
(clucking)
Oh! You lost
that first game to hustle me!
(clucking)
I can’t believe how many
manatees we saved today.
And the ones we can’t save,
we put to good use.
(moaning)
What am I supposed to do,
bury them at Arlington?
HOMER: Marge?
Homer?
These are for you.
Ooh...
Listen, I thought about
what I did.
And it was really,
really wrong.
I’m sorry.
Homie, I accept your apology.
I love you, Marge.
But I’m not coming
back yet.
Wha...?!
I’ve found a place
where I’m needed.
You’re needed at home!
And treated like
I deserve.
You’re needed at home!
I’m sorry, Homie.
I just can’t find it
in my heart to come back
right now.
Well,
that’s very reasonable.
You stole my wife!
I’ll kill you!
Homer, I have no interest
in stealing your wife,
but Marge is getting something
from her work with me.
Something a strong,
passionate woman like her needs:
a purpose.
Wow.
I can see
why she loves you.
She doesn’t love me.
She’s just trying
to find herself.
(sighing):
You know everything.
I don’t know everything.
I’m just a man.
And what a man!
Okay, the key to this
thing is the manatees.
Is Marge saving them
or killing them?
Saving!
Okay. To save the manatees,
I guess I could donate my time
and money
and help build them a...
eh, screw that.
Dad!
Those jet skiers are headed
right for a herd of manatees!
Check out those gentle,
exotic sea creatures.
Let’s whomp ’em!
(thuds)
(men laughing)
Oh, man, I just wish
we could see their tears.
(panting)
Why don’t you pick
on someone your own size?
They are roughly our size.
In fact,
they’re bigger than us.
Look, if it were up to me,
I’d be harassing them
with you.
If anything, I’d be the guy
who took it too far.
But I love my wife
and I want to win her back!
You’re a brave man.
And we respect
two things: bravery
and tattoos
that look like barbed wire.
Let’s go.
(laughing)
Rubes!
What did you call us?
Catch me if you can!
(moans)
Manatees-- defend!
(yelling and groaning)
(gasps)
(Homer sobbing)
Attention jet skiers.
I have a court order here
requiring you
to vacate these waters.
No court order’s gonna
tell me what to do.
Oh, man--it’s notarized!
Let’s boogie!
Homer, are you okay?
How many fingers
am I holding up?
Poor dumb country mouse.
Can’t even count.
(groans)
(groaning)
Oh, my sweet,
sweet Homie!
You sacrificed yourself
for the manatees.
(moans)
Rubes...
So many rubes...
pounding me
with their jet skis...
Rubes.
Please, no, rubes.
(groaning)
I’m gonna take you home
and fix you up,
’cause you’re the real
endangered species--
a devoted husband.
Marge, I’m always
amazed you chose me.
And I always will.
Woo-hoo!
(sighs)
I’m starting to think
I should find a woman.
-(barking)
-Yeah, Miranda was nice,
but I’m not driving
to Corpus Christi
every time she needs
a light bulb changed.
-(sad barking)
-Amen.
Hey, since we got
the kids with us,
why don’t we all take
a few days
of much-needed R & R?
-Don’t you have to be
back at work?
-Yes.
But I’ve got a friend
who owes me a solid.
Smithers, who is this
barrel-chested go-getter?
I believe it’s a manatee
posing as Homer Simpson, sir.
Oh, that’s cute.
I think this is the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
Actually, sir,
I believe he’s about
to die of dehydration.
Good heavens!
Grab a sponge, man!
(disco music plays)
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You might
not ever get rich ♪
♪ But let me tell ya,
it’s better than
diggin’ a ditch ♪
♪ There ain’t no tellin’
who you might meet ♪
♪ A movie star or maybe
even an Indian chief ♪
♪ Workin’ at the car wash... ♪
♪ ...Car wash ♪
♪ Get with
the feelin’, y’all ♪
♪ Car washer ♪
♪ Come summer the work
gets kind of hard ♪
♪ And this ain’t no place to be
if you planned on being a star
♪ Let me tell you
it’s always cool ♪
♪ And the boss don’t mind
sometimes if you act the fool ♪
♪ At the car wash ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Talkin’ about
the car washer ♪
♪ Come on ya’ll
and sing it for me ♪
♪ Car wash ♪
♪ Whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Car washer... ♪
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem