ANNOUNCER: We’re here
at Game 6 of the World Series.
The highlight so far--
a cloud shaped like a giraffe
that floated by during
the rain delay.
Oh, would you look at that,
the batter just called
time-out again.
Now, let’s look in the stands
at the players’ wives.
Well, whaddaya know,
they’re talkin’ on cell phones.
No doubt complaining
about the good life.
This is the most boring game
in all the universe.
And with all the steroids
they take,
the players look like freaks.
-Freaks! Freaks!
Freaks! Freaks!
Freaks!
And next week on Fox,
catch the new O.C.
spinoff, Pomona.
It’s even hotter away
from the beach.
Mmm-mmm.
If we don’t
speed up this game,
The Simpsons Halloween
Special won’t air
until Administrative
Professionals’ Day.
Speaking of which,
we must remember
to get Dorothy something.
-(chuckling lasciviously)
-Oh, yeah.
The boredom is excruciating.
Fire the Accele-Ray!
ANNOUNCER: Rodriguez
pops it to right field
as some sort of Accele-Ray
bathes the stadium
in an eerie green glow.
Oh, who would’ve thunk it?
It’s still boring.
Faster!
But the fabric of the universe
itself my shatter.
Good. Only then could
the Cubs finally win.
( Accele-Ray hums )
(pop)
KODOS: Smooth move,
Space-lax!
You’ve destroyed
the totality of existence!
KANG: It’ll be fine.
I’ll just leave a note.
Patty, is it you or me
who likes grape jelly?
For 35 cents off, I love it!
Hey, Lis, I bet I could jump
in the swimming pool from here.
Bart, that would be
the stupidest thing
you ever did.
No. The stupidest thing
would be doing it backwards.
(grunts)
Cowa... (thud)
(gasps)
Uh, Mom?
Remember how you wished
we would never grow up?
I’m afraid your son
is in a deep, deep coma
from which he will
never emerge.
I guess we should
count our blessings
he’s not dead.
Don’t I know it-- this way,
I get to keep billing you.
(laughs)
Bart, wake up!
I got that bike
you wanted!
(ringing bell)
(weeps)
Now, Marge,
if you miss your boy
that much, you could
replace him with one of these.
A robot?
Wow. A robot kid would be
a blast.
We can confuse him
and make his head explode.
(affecting robot voice):
This statement is a lie.
But if it’s a lie,
then it must be true.
But if it’s true,
then it must be--
whoop, whoop, whoop! Kaboom!
And a robot
would take your mind off
your dead son.
I thought he was in a coma!
They’re pretty much
the same thing.
except this way,
I get to keep billing you.
You already said that.
Well, you didn’t laugh
the first time.
Okay. Your robot son
is good to go.
You want me
to boot him up?
Okay.
Yah!
Ow! Mom, that hurt!
Oh.
He knows how to push
all my buttons.
And here’s
how to push his.
Now, I’m a man who likes
to strangle his kids.
Do you think I could...
Sure,
let him have it.
Why you metal...
(grunting)
Wow! The windpipe
is incredibly responsive.
( gagging )
Yeah, that’s
the oh-sixes for you.
MARGE:
David is so helpful.
And he’s great
with the neighbors.
Hi-diddly-ho!
There’s no bot
like a robot!
(laughs)
(grunts)
Ow! My Flander-doodles.
Having a robot
brother troubles me.
The ethical implications
are really tensing me up.
Oh...
Goodbye, implications.
(heart monitor beeping)
...bunga!
What the...
More waffles, Father?
Nice and hot-o,
Mr. Robot-o!
David, you’re by far
the best son I’ve ever had.
Uh-oh.
Did you replace me
with this Tinkertoy?
Replace is
such an ugly word.
We upgraded.
Bart, we can be
friends.
Eat my shorts.
I will comply.
(mechanical whirring)
(bell dings)
(squeals delightedly)
Here, make me a kitty!
Oh!
♪ Johnny come lately ♪
♪ The new kid in town ♪
♪ Everybody loves you ♪
♪ So don’t let them down ♪
♪ You look in her eyes,
the music ♪
♪ Begins to play ♪
♪ Hopeless romantics ♪
♪ Here we go again ♪
♪ But after a while,
you’re looking the other way ♪
(elephant trumpeting)
(chittering)
I hate going to the zoo.
I feel so sorry
for the animals.
Lisa, the zoo opens
up a whole new world
for the animals.
In the wild, they would
never experience boredom,
obesity, loss of purpose...
you know,
the American dream.
Time to get rid
of the competition.
(Bart grunts)
(groans)
(cawing)
(sighs)
Thank God I landed
in a bunch of fruity birds.
(cawing)
(hissing)
(yells)
This is where stem cell
research led us?
David and Bart
just aren’t working out.
We have to do something.
Hmm...
HOMER: I’m really sorry,
but our family just
can’t handle both of you boys.
I hope that somewhere
deep in your databanks,
you process fond
memories of us.
The sad part is,
there were times
when I actually
had feelings for you.
I almost felt
I was your father.
What are you
talking about?
David feels-- and your mother
will agree when I tell her--
that it’s best for our family
if you’re no longer in it.
(tires screech)
-(grunts)
-Uh!
We’re still going
to the toy store, right?
And I can pick out
as many toys as I want?
No toys!
(thunder cracking)
(crow caws)
(mumbling glumly)
There should be a law against
abandoning your child.
-(screams)
-Don’t fear us.
We’re gentle robots who were
cast off, just like you.
I’m not a robot, I’m human.
(surprised murmuring)
Tell me, young man.
What is it like to have...
feelings?
I said I’m a human,
not a girl.
(playing Herbie Hancock’s
"Rockit")
Uh, I think it’s about time
we all power down
for the night.
(whirring and clicking)
Can I stay
with you guys tonight?
Of course.
And, maybe someday,
you will teach us...
to love.
Yeah, maybe.
What did you used to do?
I was a lawnmower.
I could cut grass
at three different heights--
but I could not love.
I get it, I get it.
Sucks to be you.
Good night.
(whirring)
(yawns)
What the F-prompt?
(electrical static)
Our parts are gone!
We’ve been harvested!
My servos are gone.
That boy screwed us over.
(robotically):
He peed on me!
You are a Urinal-bot.
"Lava-tron."
(laughing)
-(doorbell rings)
-Huh?
Hey, hey!
It’s Bart!
Super.
(all screaming)
(menacingly):
I’m home!
You told me he was
at culinary school.
You wanted
to believe the lie!
Time to destroy the one
who did this to me.
(whirring)
To get me...
you’ll have to go through
your fa...
Oh, those were
my good pants!
(slurping)
Well,
the important thing is
we’re a family again.
This stinks!
I got stubby little robot legs,
and an ass that’s not equipped
for an adult diet.
(rivets popping)
(thudding)
Oh...
LISA: Dad?
Dad, wake up!
You’re not a robot!
You’re just possessed
by the devil.
The power of Christ
compels thee!
(spouting demonic gibberish)
Mm...
I’ll call work and tell
them he can’t make it.
Whoo-hoo!
(laughs)
Suckers.
( shotgun cocks )
-(screaming)
-(footsteps)
(gunshot; glass shatters)
"Dear Homer Simpson,
Mr. Burns invites you
to a hunting party
at his private estate."
Parenthesis, "Sinister Laugh,"
close parenthesis.
Please don’t accept
this invitation, Dad,
hunting is cruel.
Honey,
animals don’t feel death.
That was proved
by the scientists
at Black Angus.
No fair--Dad gets to kill
wild animals,
but I shoot one bird
and I have to go
to a psychiatrist.
(groans)
He still thinks
that hobo was a bird.
(thunder cracking)
CARL: This is a pretty sweet
deal,
Burns inviting us over.
What kind of motive
do you think he has?
Ulterior.
Mmm.
(door hinges creaking)
Welcome, all!
Now, to explain
why I summoned you here.
Oh, God, here it comes:
time-share pitch.
Well, I got bad credit,
so the joke’s on you!
(slurping)
You’re here
to participate in a hunt
for the world’s
most dangerous game.
"The most dangerous game?"
What could it be?
Hmm...
Hmm... Hmm...
Hmm.
The game I am hunting...
is all of you.
Now,
because I am too kind,
I will give you all
a five-minute head start.
You may commence running!
Five minutes of running?
Shoot me now.
(gunshot; thudding)
Well, that broke the ice.
Now, any man who lives
till noon tomorrow
shall win his freedom.
Excuse me,
what gives you
the legal right
to do this?
You tell me,
you’re my lawyer.
Well, I guess you are
zoned for hunting,
and you have
previously claimed,
killing people
is part of your religion...
I think I can draw
something up.
(keys clacking)
(typewriter dings)
There,
this should hold up
in just about
any courtroom.
Excellent.
(shrieks)
(all screaming)
(engine racing)
The game is afoot.
(sniffs)
I smell fear...
mixed with curry.
APU: Uh-oh.
Ah!
You got me.
But I shall be reincarnated!
(groans)
Ha, ha!
You can’t kill a Hindu!
(screams)
Help me, Jesus!
-(gunshots)
-(panting and shrieking)
TV ANNOUNCER:
You’re watching
The World Series
Of Manslaughter,
the most violent TV spectacle
since the Hip Hop Image Awards.
Mom, Mr. Burns
is going to kill Dad!
I should’ve known
something was wrong
when we got this week’s
TV Guide.
(Lisa gasps)
Now for his take on tonight’s
bloodthirsty action,
here’s guest analyst
Terry Bradshaw.
Terry?
Well, conventional wisdom
says good fleeing
will always beat
good chasing.
But the stats say,
"Put your money
on the guy with the gun!"
(screaming)
-(gunshot)
-(groans)
Dying is just like golfing,
except in golf...
(gunshots)
Ah!
You hate to see that.
That’s the kind
of showboating
that’ll turn people
off this sport.
MOE: Hey, hey, Homer!
Burns is coming, climb up!
(straining)
( wood cracking )
MOE: Oh, you fat ass!
(screaming grows louder)
(gunshots; thudding)
Nyah, nyah--
you missed me!
(groans)
Well, before I die,
I’ll just scratch
that lottery ticket
I got in my pocket.
"Instant Jackpot,
one million dollars!"
If I make it out alive,
I could...
Ooh!
Homer, Burns has only been
chasing us for six hours,
and you’ve already
resorted to cannibalism.
And there’s bananas
in that tree up there.
Oh, they look a little green.
(all shrieking)
Carl, I see Heaven!
(gasps):
What does it look like?
Uh...
ALL: Hurry up, Lenny.
We’ll be late for work
at the plant.
(sighs)
(gags)
You can’t escape me,
Simpson.
You’re not smart enough!
HOMER: Yes, I am!
I mean...
(squawking like a bird)
Oh, no!
I’ve been killed!
(groans)
Outfoxed ’em with
the corpse of my best friend.
Hee-hee!
(shrieks)
(shouts)
(gun clicks)
Is there room
in the head bag, Smithers?
I can make room.
Excellent.
(clanging)
Done and done!
Marge!
You saved me.
(shouts): D-ohh!
What was that for?
Staying out 18 hours
and not calling home once.
Aw, I can’t stay mad at you
when that pan smells
like sausage and onions.
And I am glad you’re okay.
(both moaning)
All right,
and there you have it!
Terry Bradshaw, your thoughts
on what just transpired?
Well,
it’s a disgrace, Roger.
This network will show
a dozen gruesome murders,
but I bet they cut
to commercial
before these two begin
the tender act of love.
(moaning)
I spoke too soon, huh?
There they go!
Whoa!
That’s goin’ in my playbook!
Oh, everyone’s wearing
such an interesting costume.
Look! Grandpa’s a gorilla,
Sideshow Mel is Spider-man,
and Nelson’s a raccoon.
I’m not a raccoon.
I’m the Lone Ranger.
I’m too poor
to afford the hat.
That’s not even a mask.
It’s axle grease.
Don’t listen to him,
Silver.
(imitates horse whinnying
and hooves clopping)
And now the finalists
for Best Costume.
First, we have Blackula.
Oh, because I’m black
and I’m Dracula,
that makes me Blackula?
(sputters lips):
My wife said don’t go
as Dracula,
but I said, "Bernice,
we live in the 21st century..."
Send him the standard
racist remark apology.
They’re in the middle drawer.
Our other finalist
is this hideous witch.
(cackling)
(crowd cheering)
Congratulations.
You have won this $25
Kwik-E-Mart certificate.
Sucker! 25 bucks won’t buy
you half a Balance Bar.
I exaggerate, but really,
my prices are very high.
Thank you!
Wait! Before you leave,
we’d all like to know
which of our beloved regulars
you are under that costume.
Lindsay Naegle?
Helen Lovejoy?
Old Jewish Man?
No, I’m right here,
dressed as my brother Irving.
(sighs):
Every day, I miss him.
(chuckles)
Uh, this is
a little awkward,
because I’m not wearing
a costume.
I’m a real witch.
(crowd gasps)
Wait a minute.
That’s cheating!
Burn her...
gift certificate!
Since you are not
technically in costume,
you cannot
win this award.
Rescind my award,
will you?!
You’re all going to pay!
Taint of newt
and scum of pond,
thou shalt become
the guise thou donned.
-(puzzled murmuring)
-Speak English, moron.
I’m turning you
into your costumes.
Well, are you going
to talk about it,
or are you going
to do it?
(groans)
(gasps)
(whinnying)
I’m not a raccoon!
I’m the Lone Ranger!
(groans)
Disco Stu wishes
he’d gone as Marilyn McCoo.
Ooh! Whoo!
Ooh, whoo!
Good luck getting your deposits
back on those costumes!
(horrified gasps)
Seymour, I told you
not to go as G.I. Joe!
Mother, I’m fine.
I... Uh-oh.
Oh, this isn’t fair.
I wasn’t wearing a costume.
Look at me! I’m a young,
strapping gorilla!
-(thuds)
-(groans)
My hip! It’s shattered!
Somebody help me!
Off we go
to the gorilla hospital.
That’s it,
suck out the poison.
Wait a minute.
(Grandpa screaming)
(howling)
(dogs growling)
I am not a happy meal
right now!
I’m telling you,
I’m Oberon,
King of the Fairies.
You’re a big fat bug,
and you’re goin’ down!
(scratching noises)
(grunts)
My spine is not
a scratching post!
(Snowball II yowls)
(with German accent):
Oh, there must be some way
out of this
verdammten spell.
Lisa, do you think
you could check
on your father?
Oh, that’s an excellent
use of a genius brain:
to look after
an idiot head.
(slurps)
(groans)
Oh!
(slurps)
No!
Damn it!
(gasps):
That’s the answer!
Maggie’s a real witch now!
She can reverse
the spell!
(growls)
I don’t want
to reverse the spell.
I can howl at the moon
and eat rats.
(howling)
I don’t want to change,
either.
Now I can pull horses
out of the mud.
Then girls will like me!
And I’m Jared
from the Subway ads.
I’m only a little overweight
and sexually ambiguous.
Don’t listen to them,
Maggie.
Maggie?
Please change me back!
This bumblebee has developed
an unhealthy obsession with me.
I don’t want flowers.
I am a flower!
As for Apu-D2,
I could go either way.
(making beeping
and clicking noises)
(discordant pleas shouted
over each other)
( Bewitched
theme music playing)
Oh, well.
This still beats being Moe.
Okay, this concludes
this year’s Halloween show.
We hope you had as much fun
watching our show
as the Koreans
did animating it.
But there’s one group
for whom every day
is Halloween.
I’m talking about
adult illiterates.
For them, trying to read
the morning newspaper
is more terrifying
than any goblin, ghoul,
spook or spirit.
So won’t you please donate
a children’s book or something?
Together, we can make
reading a slam dunk.
Dennis Rodman?
What are you doing here?
Working off
a speeding ticket.
Happy Halloween,
everybody!
(screams)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem