CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(beeps)
(pipe organ playing
gentle melody)
Ha-ha!
And now,
let us bow our heads
in silent prayer...
(loud scratching)
Maggie, that’s not
what you do with a hymnal.
Homer!
What? I forgot to floss
this morning.
Something’s wrong
with Maggie.
We should get her
to Dr. Hibbert.
But I don’t see him anywhere.
The Hibberts now attend a more
"boisterous" house of worship.
(clearing throat)
-(lively gospel music playing)
-♪ Shine on ♪
-♪ Let the light... ♪
-♪ Shine on... ♪
-♪ From the lighthouse ♪
-♪ Shine on ♪
-♪ Shine on me ♪
-♪ Shine on me... ♪
-♪ Shine on... ♪
-♪ Shine on me ♪
-♪ Shine on ♪
-♪ In the morning... ♪
-This is awesome!
Black God rules.
-♪ In the noonday ♪
-♪ Shine on ♪
♪ Oh, let it shine on... ♪
(chuckling)
-Dr. Hibbert?
-Mm-hmm?
Uh, I hate to interrupt
while you’re rejoicing,
but Maggie
is terribly itchy.
Mm-hmm!
Oh, this looks to be
the initial stages
of chicken pox.
Say "Amen"!
Amen!
Coat Maggie with this
Calamine lotion
and the scabbing will heal.
The scabbing will heal!
ALL: The scabbing
will heal!
Heal my scabs, Lord!
Praise the Lord!
I can walk again!
Hmm...
What? My foot fell asleep.
Sweetie,
I know it itches,
but you’ve got
to stop scratching.
No!
(gasps): No!
Here, here, play
with your teddy bear.
Oh, sugar-booger!
Aw, poor Maggie.
Homer, don’t touch her!
You’ve never had chicken pox.
I know, and you did,
and you’re great.
Oh, I’m just saying
it’s very dangerous
if you get it
as an adult.
It could leave
you sterile...
down there.
Oh, you always got to work blue,
don’t ya, Marge?
You’re better than that.
Can’t even go in
my own kitchen...
I bet Bart’s in there
right now
licking frosting off
my eggbeaters.
Mm.
Don’t worry, Dad.
I’m saving one for you.
I’ll just leave it here
in the dog’s mouth.
No! (stammers)
Bart!
That’s a really
bad storage area.
Hey Homer,
why the sour puss?
Did ya chugalug
a skunky Snapple?
I don’t know, maybe.
Plus my wife
won’t let me inside
because the baby’s
got chicken pox.
Really? Do you mind
if I bring my boys over
so she can infect
Rod and Todd?
Then there’ll be a pox
on both our houses.
Why would you do that?
Are you a bad parent?
Au contraire,
man with no hair.
You see, Rod and Todd
can only get
the chicken pox once,
and childhood’s
the safest time.
So you want Maggie
to infect your kids?
You betcha.
In fact, some parents have been
known to hold "pox parties,"
so other kids
in the neighborhood
can get the disease
when they please.
And would they pay handsomely
for the privilege?
Well, they might.
But you’d have to be awfully
money-grubbing
to charge your friends
and neighbors...
HOMER: $15 to infect
your kids.
Now featuring the Pox Box.
Pox Box not recommended
for pregnant or nursing women.
As with any disease box,
results may vary.
Pox Box.
Welcome to our pox party.
Save room for punch--
Maggie’s bathing in the bowl.
(doorbell ringing)
Uh, hi.
Luann will pick up Milhouse
when the party’s over.
I’ll just read in the car
till then.
(chuckles)
Oh, Kirk, come join
the parents in the kitchen.
We’re having
alcohol drinks,
and dishing on the parents
who aren’t here.
Ordinarily,
I’m not one to laugh
at a man’s urinary blockage,
but, you should
have seen it...
Oh, there he is.
(chuckles)
Ladies and gentlemen,
presenting the sister
with the blisters...
the tot with all the spots...
Maggie!
(coughing)
I feel like
a chicken already.
I just made an egg
in my pants.
Hey, Marge.
Hit me with a little bit
more of that, uh, silly slush.
Chief, don’t you think
you’ve had enough?
I’m fine.
Watch, I can even touch
my gun to my nose.
(both gasping)
Oh, don’t worry,
I’m the Pief of Cholice.
I mean, I’m, uh,
the beef with no cheese.
(sobbing):
Why doesn’t Lou like me?
Why?
Knock, knock.
Luann, what are you
doing here?
I thought you were just
dropping Milhouse off.
I could get some coffee
and come back...
No, no, no, you stay.
I’ll just drive home.
Uh, who’s going
to let me siphon?
Look, why don’t you
both stay
and have one of
my Marge-aritas?
All right!
I never drank one of these
without a cigarette in it.
Now, kids,
in lieu of one of those
inflatable jumping things,
please welcome
Mr. Krusty the Clown.
(cheering)
Hey, hey, kids!
(laughing)
This putz only paid
for 20 seconds,
so listen fast.
(sing-song voice):
Moishe caught the chicken pox,
he scratched all night and day.
He asked the rabbi
what to do, and he said...
-(watch beeps)
-Time. I’m out of here.
(laughs)
(tires squealing)
Kirk, you look good.
Have you been working out?
Well, dogs have been
chasing me...
No one’s been
chasing me lately.
What happened
to your last boyfriend?
The one who’d always
go to the gym
after visiting you,
then have lunch
at that place downtown?
You know,
his taillight’s broken.
I’m not seeing him anymore.
Well, does that mean
that there might be
a chance for me?
Almost anyone’s
got a chance now.
(children coughing)
Goodbye, thanks for coming.
If my party made you sick,
tell your friends.
(sighing)
Sweet Lizzie McGuire!
You think
that’s traumatic?
Mr. Stomach, are you hungry?
(deep voice):
I’m always hungry.
So make with the pizza,
Fatso.
You’re the stomach.
(slurping and sloshing)
I have to do this for work.
So Milhouse
walks into the bedroom,
and there’s his
mom and dad going...
(sensual moaning)
(high-pitched):
Oh, Mr. Van Houten,
I love when you kiss me!
(deep-voiced):
Yeah, yeah, kissing ladies
is the best.
(high-pitched):
Oh, baby, kiss my mouth.
(deep-voiced): Mm, kiss me
like we’re in a fancy hotel.
All right, we get it!
(horrified gasps)
Marge,
what’s happening to me?
Oh, Homie,
you got chicken pox.
But how?
I don’t know. I kept away
from Maggie all day.
Ooh! I’m so itchy!
(Bart and Lisa grunting)
Ah. Oh, yeah!
KIRK: Son, we want
to talk to you
about what you saw
in the Simpsons’ house.
Well, I didn’t see anything
to get my hopes up,
if that’s what you mean.
Well, maybe you should
get your hopes up a little.
They’re already up!
They’re sky-high!
Your father and I
are going through
what’s called
a "trial un-separation."
And, son, I want to make
one thing clear.
Unlike the breakup,
this is not your fault.
I can’t believe it!
Our family might
get back together again!
♪ Our house ♪
♪ Is a very, very,
very fine house ♪
♪ With two cats in the yard ♪
♪ Life used to be so hard ♪
♪ Now everything is easy ♪
♪ ’Cause of you ♪
♪ And now... ♪
♪ La, la, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la,
la-la-la, la-la... ♪
(sighs)
I haven’t daydreamed
in color in so long.
Oh, thank God.
We were afraid
we lost you, son.
You sit in this
oatmeal awhile
and it’ll send
your itchies packing.
Homer!
Mmm... Homer-oats.
Stop eating the oatmeal!
That’s the third tub
you’ve eaten.
(phone ringing)
Y’ello?
No, I’m not coming
in to work.
I have chicken pox.
I know I said that last month,
but I was lying.
Sheesh.
Right. Right.
Right. Right. Okay.
Right. I love you. Bye.
I just got fired.
Better check the "Want Ads."
Ooh, truck driver
needed in Iraq.
Trucks are like big cars.
Oh...
Okay, Luann.
For honesty’s sake,
we should probably
talk about everyone we dated
while we were separated.
Well, the Sea Captain
and I...
Yeah, okay,
I don’t wanna know.
I don’t wanna know!
So what are we going
to do as a family today?
Mini-golf? Pedal boats?
Indoor rock wall?
Um, Milly...
Botanical garden?
Build-A-Bear Workshop?
Arena Football with
the Springfield Stun?
Not today, big guy.
Your dad and I need
more time
to get... reacquainted.
-(chuckling)
Why are you laughing?
Tell me!
Private jokes are rude.
Uh, son, here’s ten bucks.
Why don’t you go
to the bowling alley
and throw some solo balls?
But it’s league night!
(Milhouse groaning)
This trial un-separation
stinks.
My parents used
to compete for my love,
and I’d cash in
every time.
And I always got
the spillover.
Drive-in movies,
two Christmases,
soda with dinner...
(sighs)
We lived like kings.
Remember when you told my dad
to go to bed, and he did?
That was some New Years.
Now, listen.
I think we should
consider
breaking
your parents up again.
I don’t know, Bart.
I’ve wanted them
back together for so long.
Look, you know
they’re gonna separate again.
Why don’t we just
speed up the process?
You know, Bart,
my imaginary friend
never made me do things
I thought were wrong.
That’s why he had
to go away forever.
I thought you were gonna
let him come back.
I’m afraid he has
to spend another year
searching for his brain.
(groans)
(grunting)
Luann, I’m moving
my stuff back in!
Uh, Dad...
Mom says you’re stinky
and gross.
Your mother said that?
This is so great.
I mean, she used to keep her
criticisms all bottled up,
until they destroyed
our marriage.
(sniffs)
And I guess
I am a little funky.
Well, this is what cologne
samples are for.
(humming)
(sighs)
Mom, I don’t wanna
get Dad in trouble, but...
he just let me
drink a beer!
Hmm. Looks like
we have a problem here.
The problem being that you are
addicted to fibbing.
I am drunk! I’ll prove it!
Watch me...kiss this
picture of Nana.
(shuddering)
Oh, I can’t do it.
She’s so mean to me.
She wouldn’t let me
eat Fruit Loops!
MILHOUSE:
Maybe my Mom and Dad
are meant to be together,
Bart.
You better hope not,
’cause you know
what comes next?
Your worst nightmare--
a baby sister.
Hi, Bart.
I baked you some cookies.
Skanks for nothing,
Lame-er-ella.
If you two don’t mind,
I’d like to watch
that cool Fox show about
teenagers in Orange County.
Austin!
I was looking
for my belly ring
in your recording studio,
and I found this!
Does this or does this not
belong to Feather?
Sorry, Jade.
That’s how we light it up
in the O.C.
You cheated on me!
Our mixed-race
fling is so over!
Whatever.
Let’s score some jam
at Knott’s Berry Farm.
For sure, dawg.
We’ll be kickin’ it old-school
at Bigfoot Rapids.
Gonna get my flume on...
log style!
♪ We’ve been on the run,
drivin’ in the sun ♪
♪ Lookin’ out
for number one ♪
♪ California,
here we come ♪
♪ Right back
where we started from ♪
♪ Hustlers, grab your guns,
your shadow weighs a ton ♪
♪ Driving down the 101 ♪
♪ California, here we come ♪
♪ Right back
where we started from ♪
-♪ California... ♪
♪ Here we come... ♪
I bet that bra was planted
-by Sterling to break them up.
-(TV clicks off)
That’s a brilliant idea.
Those TV writers
are geniuses!
Whatever they’re paid,
it’s not enough.
This bra is really
gonna lift and separate--
lift your mother’s suspicions
and separate your parents.
LUANN: Milhouse!
I need slender fingers
to get me a pickle!
This isn’t mine.
(stifled giggles)
I have a message
for your wife--
stop sleeping
with my husband!
Okey-doke.
(muttering):
"...with my husband..."
And you are...?
The wife of your wife’s lover.
Will she know
what this is regarding?
Oh, you moron!
Marge is having
an affair with Kirk!
(scoffs):
That’s ridiculous!
No woman would want to have
sex with that loser!
Oh, I...
And, uh, congratulations
on snagging him back.
Good stuff.
Just answer me
one question.
How did your wife’s bra
end up in my husband’s bed?
(grunts)
(gasps)
This is Marge’s bra.
I bought it for her boobs!
Of all the people
for Marge to cheat on,
why did it have to be me?
Oh, boy, am I beat.
If you wanna return
a melon to the grocery store,
clear your day.
Well, that answers the mystery
of the missing melon,
but I have
one more question--
did you sleep
with Kirk Van Houten?
(gasps):
How could you ask me that?
I repeat--
did you sleep with Kirk?
Homer, you’re crazy!
You’re not saying "no."
Fine... No!
I’m still
not hearing "no."
No! No! No!
Well, methinks the lady
doth protest too much!
You don’t trust me?
After I salved every chicken
pock on your ungrateful body!
How dare you!
I’m still waiting
for that "no."
Get out of this house!
Gladly.
(grunting)
(grunting continues)
We tried to break up
your parents,
and we broke up mine.
Wanna call my therapist
and tell her how you feel?
Hello, Dr. Wexler?
WEXLER: Stop calling me!
I’m on my honeymoon!
Yeah,
it’s that weird kid again.
-LISA: Dad?
-(gasps)
I thought Mom kicked
you out of the house.
I came to get my mail.
Resident... occupant...
(sadly):
I can’t open these.
Ooh, a traffic ticket!
(sobbing)
I’d do anything
to get your mother
and that donut back.
Okay, look, you and Mom
can fix this.
What exactly happened
between the two of you?
Lisa, we don’t
need to know how.
It’s a natural thing
that happens,
like a hurricane
or going to war.
Hmm...
Well, I’d better go.
Where are you staying?
You know
the Four Seasons?
Well, I’m experiencing them
firsthand,
because I’m living
in the park.
Bart, I think
you’re behind this whole thing.
Yeah, I can see
how you’d think that.
But on the other hand...
(grunts)
Ha! I can read
you like a book.
Ha-ha, you read books.
If you don’t tell Mom
what you did, I will.
Oh, come on.
Wouldn’t it be easier
if our parents divorced
and you compensated by
marrying much older men?
Meanwhile, I’ll be
one of those weird guys
who’s 35 and shows up
at high school
basketball games.
(sighs)
(groaning)
Why did I marry
that selfish jerk?
I’ve asked him
to flip the mattress
a thousand times,
and he never does.
(grunting)
Uh, Mom?
Hi, sweetie.
Uh, you know that bra
that broke up our family?
Uh-hmm.
Well, I looked into it,
and it turns out
I was responsible.
Really?
Well, just for that
I’m gonna erase
all the saved games
on your PlayStation.
What?! How do you know
about things like that?
I learned about it in here.
Hmm!
But Dad can come home,
right?
-No.
-But he’s innocent.
Innocent?
After all I do for your father,
he still doesn’t trust me.
I’m finished with him.
Does this mean
you and Dad might get
a D-A-V-U-R-S?
Young man, you go work
on your spelling,
or I’ll delete all the custom
ringtones from your cell phone.
No!
Our reverse
parent trap
just made
everything worse.
Maybe we should use a different
movie as our guide.
Like Oklahoma.
♪ Oh, the farmer and the cowman
should be friends ♪
♪ One man likes
to push a plow ♪
♪ The other likes
to chase a cow ♪
♪ But that’ s no reason
why they can’t be friends. ♪
(gunfire)
What do you think, Bart?
A hoedown could solve
all our problems.
I just need your chap size.
It’s two more than
your pant size.
How many times
do I have to tell you--
no Rodgers
and Hammerstein!
Rodgers and Hart?
No!
Well, what will
trick your parents
into getting back together?
LISA: Enough
with the tricks!
Stupid movie schemes
do not work in real life.
Mom and Dad have
a marriage on the rocks,
and they need to work
through it in therapy
to make sure it
doesn’t shatter.
Rocks... shatter...
jagged cliff...
Lis, you’ve just given me
an idea for the most insane,
hair-brained,
fool-proof scheme ever!
(exasperated groan)
Okay, when my mom and dad
see this dummy fall
in the river,
they’ll think it’s me,
and they’ll realize
what really matters--
each other.
Do you like
the dummy, Bart?
I even made it
smell like you.
Now, to make sure
Homer and Marge are in proper
viewing position...
So, I got your note
saying you wanted
to meet here to apologize.
Well, I got your note
saying you were gonna
bring me
a bucket of potato salad.
Where’s my apology?
Where’s my bucket?
Now, I’ll get
Mom and Dad’s attention,
and you shove the dummy
in the water.
Any questions?
Yeah, what are you going
as for Halloween?
Pile of dog doo.
Let’s roll.
Mom! Dad!
I’m playing
on a dangerous cliff...
because you’re too busy
arguing
to pay attention to me!
(gasps)
Bart! We’re all disappointed
there’s no potato salad,
but for God’s sake,
don’t jump!
(loud whisper):
Now.
I can’t tell which is which.
Oh, no!
I’m already running!
(groans)
Whoa!
I did it, Bart!
Bart?
(screaming)
(grunting)
I’m a-comin’, boy!
(yells)
(screaming)
(Homer humming nonchalantly)
(groans)
(both whimpering)
This is all my fault!
I planted Mom’s bra
in Milhouse’s parents’ bed!
Why you little...
(grunting)
Homer!
I can save you both!
Just let go of the rock!
(whimpering)
Just do it! Trust me!
Okay.
(yelling)
(all moaning)
(panting)
Mom, Dad...
I’d give a kajillion dollars
for you to get back together.
Make it two kajillion.
Homer!
We’ll lose the
first kajillion to taxes.
Well, I guess you showed
you do trust me, after all.
Of course I do.
The only thing
I can’t believe
is that a woman
as great as you would be
married to me.
Oh, Homie...
-(both sighing)
-Oh... Marge.
MILHOUSE: I don’t want
to live
in a world without Bart!
(gasps)
Can he swim?
What do you think?
♪ California ♪
♪ Here we come ♪
♪ Here we come. ♪
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem