You guys look amazing.
Stanley, I thought
you hated halloween.
He wears it
so he can sleep at his desk.
- Who are you?
- Carrie Bradshaw from Sex and the City.
- I like your shoes.
- Thank you.
- Will you help walk me to the fax?
- Sure.
I got her, I got her,
I can help you.
- You look amazing.
- Inappropriate. Thank you.
- Who are you, Larry King?
- Gordon Gekko.
- From the insurance commercials.
- Yeah...
Awesome.
Let's put a smile on that face.
Damn it, Creed!
I've been up since 4:00!
Sweet'stume, dude.
Who are you supposed to be?
Cool.
You are...
a cat.
We were looking for kitten.
Give me one second.
Jim Halpert.
- Hey, New York. Happy Halloween.
- Thanks.
My costume's getting
a lot of attention.
So apparently no one
dresses up for Halloween here.
I wish I had known that before I used
grease paint for my moustache.
And I can't even take off my hat
because then I'm Hitler.
Wanna see a magic trick?
I'm gonna make a pencil disa...
Disappear.
OK, I think we are set.
We have puzzles,
string for cat's cradles.
Burned this last night.
A little road trip CD.
Puppets.
Look at all this stuff.
It's only 7 hours.
When corporate found out
that we were dating,
they decided
they were gonna transfer Holly
back to her old branch
in Nashua, New Hampshire.
Michael's taking a personal day
to move me up.
Road trip!
Right?
Breaker one-nine, copy...
Copy that, breaker.
Those Duke boys are at it again.
Do not... touch my radio.
- Kidding.
- We're not doing anything.
It's been a weird week
since we found out I had to transfer.
Michael wanted me to quit
and get some job here in Scranton,
I said "why don't you quit
and get some job in Nashua?"
He said "I asked you first."
I said "first"
at the same time he did.
And then I said "jinx."
And then we never...
talked about it again,
and haven't been back
to the conversation, so...
All right, everybody,
I am out of here.
- Jim, you are in charge.
- I'll walk you out.
You're quite a gentleman.
You can let people go
a couple of min early if you want.
All right, we'll see.
No.
I'm off to New York.
My brother Pete from Boston
and my brother Tom from New Jersey
are taking Pam and I out for lunch
to celebrate the engagement.
Or maybe to beat me up.
I can never tell with those two.
Good morning, temp.
Good morning.
Good morning, Dwight.
Thought I'd go casual today.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Hello.
How are you, Phyllis?
That's funny.
Take that sweatshirt off!
- Hey, buddy.
- Andy.
Remember when I jokingly yelled at you
to take your sweatshirt off?
Totally joking.
But you should know
those colors are sacred.
Not that I care.
But if you're not a Cornell man.
- You probably shouldn't wear them.
- No, I get it.
I totally understand.
And I just want to assure you
that I mean no disrespect.
You see, I'm applying.
Come on, you think
you could get into Cornell?
Well, if someone who barely
out-sells Phyllis can get in,
I should be fine.
- I'm sitting right here, Dwight.
- I meant that as a compliment to you.
As well as a slight to Andy.
Cornell is a good school.
And I want to better myself
through higher education.
If it makes Andy angry, so be it.
I have to unpack this weekend, but maybe
next weekend we go to the outlets!
Mike, you driving every weekend?
We're gonna switch
back and forth, the driving.
Sometimes we'll just meet
in the middle.
It'll be fun. Wait a sec.
I love this song.
Life is a highway
I wanna ride it all night long
If you're going my way
I wanna drive you all night long
Hey there.
So, how do you think we're gonna do
against Penn this year?
Nathan Ford's arm
looks pretty strong.
Well, he's had
a pretty good season so far...
Stop saying "we."
You did not go to Cornell.
You're just doing this
to screw with me.
Not so.
Cornell is an excellent school.
Without its agricultural program,
we probably wouldn't have cabbage.
At least not modern cabbage.
I know it's an excellent school, Dwight.
I went there.
My blood runs big red.
Someday we'll both get together
in Comstock Hall
and just laugh about all of this.
Hey, future baby sis!
How are you, Tom?
Nice to see you.
I asked Tom and Pete to come early
so we could play
a prank on Jim at lunch.
Pretty awesome, right?
I think they're into the idea.
They're probably thinking,
"that Pam Beesly,"
"she's the coolest
sister-in-law on the planet."
"She's the best."
"The absolute best."
OK, so, here's what I'm thinking.
I'm gonna say that before ceramics class
I took off my ring.
And then when I changed
back out of my smock,
it wasn't in my pocket
anymore, and I lost it.
That's perfect.
You know what'd be
even more hilarious?
Remember that thing we did when Jim
was in high school with his girlfriend?
That would be hilarious.
We should totally dog her
about being an artist,
- never making any money.
- That's awesome.
Like she basically
has a hobby for a job.
So, not the ring, then?
Not doing the ring, then.
I think this is better.
This is nice. It's fun.
He hates it when
we pick on his girlfriends.
They came up
with that idea really fast.
- This trip is longer than I thought.
- Yeah, it did look shorter...
I was having a nightmare.
You were sleeping?
- You were talking before.
- Was I? Really?
- Was I saying anything interesting?
- Not really.
All right, what's the scoop?
How far?
Four hours.
Almost halfway there.
- We're only halfway?
- Halfway! You know what I want to do?
I want to pull over and
find a little bed and breakfast
for when we meet in the middle.
Emphasis on the bed.
And the breakfast.
Next exit isn't for five miles.
Let's check there.
- Hey, guys.
- How are ya?
Good to see you.
Nice to see you again, Pam.
Pam, I haven't seen you
in so, so long.
All right.
So now we can sit...
and get comfortable.
There's nothing out here, man.
I don't know. I just...
imagined a hotel right here.
A pool over here.
Little breakfast place...
With really good bacon. Just...
Here we go.
Fourth time's a charm.
Life's like a road where you just...
One thing here and the next day back
Sometimes you deal with it
then you don't
Sometimes you do what you want
It's out there...
- Are you crying?
- No.
- Allergies?
- Did Darryl touch you?
- What!
No, Darryl did not touch me.
Can we just keep going, please?
- What's the matter?
- It's not gonna work.
- Sure it is.
- There's too much distance.
It's gonna work.
It'll be fine.
We've only been dating
each other for a few weeks.
Listen to me.
- I like you so much.
- I like you too.
- And I've dated almost 4 women last...
- I've dated 4 guys last year too.
No. In like, the last 10 years.
I've dated almost 4 women.
And you are so far
above them it is stupid.
Michael, don't. Don't.
Don't make it harder
than it has to be.
That's what she said.
Holly thinks
that this relationship is over.
Well, you know what,
I am not gonna give up that easy.
I'm going to make this way harder
than it needs to be.
Take that down.
- Excuse me?
- Take...
that down!
I once dated a couple of guys
from Cornell.
They were really nice,
gave me a ride home.
I seriously doubt
anyone from Cornell dated you.
It's pronounced "colonel."
Highest rank in the military.
It's pronounced Cornell!
It's the highest rank
in the Ivy league.
Andy, let's just talk about this
man to man
- after work. What do you say?
- Fine. Good.
- Good.
- Can we...
That's big red bear!
That's a bobble big red bear!
God!
If you leave on friday by 5:00,
you'll be rolling in
at midnight at best.
And then sleep in saturday.
That only leaves us less than 24 hours
before you have to go back again.
I will talk to you
on the bluetooth the entire trip.
So we're talking constantly
all the way.
I'll tell you everything that I see.
Everything that I pass by.
Things that I witness on the road.
Maybe I'll see an accident
one weekend.
How long could we keep that up?
- Years.
- Years?
Years of just a few hours
every weekend?
Here's my wish.
I want you to meet a great guy,
and I want you to be happy.
- Thank you.
- My wish has come true, incidentally.
Because you've met me
and you are happy.
Clever, Mike.
So Pam, how much money does an artist
make after they leave art school?
Not a lot of money
in the arts, right?
That's not really true.
There's a lot to do
with an art degree, actually.
Maybe Pam should pay the check by...
drawing a picture on this napkin.
That's... a little rude.
What's your deal?
- Just having fun, Jimmy.
- Right, Pam?
You know what,
I think we're a great couple.
I think we're a classic couple.
I think we're like Romeo and Juliet.
I think we....
go together so well.
We're like peanut butter and jelly.
- Don't you think?
- I do.
Then, don't do it.
Please don't do this.
What's up?
I just thought I'd try you.
I'm thinking about that story
where you ran into the girl
you used to babysit.
- I don't know what I'm gonna do!
- Please call me back.
- I'm not gonna be OK.
- You will.
No, I won't. I'm not strong.
I'll go back to Jan, and I hate Jan.
Oh, god!
- You might be interested...
- What?
Dwight
Andy, I've been meaning to ask you,
which a cappella group
should I join?
The Harmoniacs or the Do-Re-Migos?
Assuming you had the voice
to be in any of them,
it's irrelevant.
Because I called admissions,
and it looks like I...
will be conducting
your university interview.
- That's a conflict of interest.
- Yeah. Big one.
So should I not let you in now,
or do you want to do the interview,
and then I won't let you in?
- Interview.
- Excellent.
When the hourglass strikes 3:00,
then in the room
whence employees confer.
- What?
- The conference room.
Who are your role models?
If I had to put Dwight's chances
into a percentage,
I would say he has
none-percent chance.
So...
Dane Cook.
Jack...
Bauer.
And Eli Whitney.
You're doing great.
Life is a highway
I wanna ride it all night...
This is my niece, Vanessa.
She's a trumpeter.
- And... look at her.
- Cute.
It must be really fun
for you and Marcy.
She only knows how to play
When the saints go marching in.
- I love that one.
- Yeah, but...
She doesn't think she's gonna be,
like, a career musician, right?
Here we go again.
What's your deal today?
Just saying, how many famous trumpeters
can you name, besides Louis Armstrong?
- Miles Davis.
- One.
- Chet something.
- Half.
- The point is that there are jobs...
- Dizzy Gillespie.
Also good.
and hobbies. I love baseball
more than anything,
but you don't see me
trying to get on the Mets.
Pete, you couldn't make the Mets.
She's at Pratt.
You play JV baseball.
Will you lighten up a little bit?
Just calling it like I see it.
I don't know if I'm going
to make any money with art.
I mean,
it's a very competitive field.
But I've a professor who says
that I've a lot of promise.
And if I don't try now,
I never will, so...
Guys, what is going on?
We pranked you.
It was Pam's idea.
Pam was the mastermind.
Got you.
That was killer.
I was so close to blowing it.
Let's see how well you know
your big red history.
Bring it.
Who was Cornell's 8th president?
- Dale Raymond Corson.
- I'm sorry, that's incorrect.
Cornell's 7th president
was, in fact, James A. Perkins.
Comprehension skills sub-par.
Interviewing skills... sub-par.
What are you writing? You can't even
give Cornell your full attention.
On the contrary, I'm helping Cornell
by evaluating their interviewers.
Nobody wants that... to happen.
Well, when they get my evaluation,
we'll see if they're interested.
Applicant is attempting
to blackmail interviewer,
showing low moral character.
Interviewer is threatening applicant
with an arbitrary review process.
Applicant is wasting everyone's time
with stupid and inane accusations.
Interviewer has suspect motives.
Applicant has a head
shaped like a trapezoid.
Interviewer has turned off
applicant's interest in Cornell,
and they are going to go
to the vastly superior Dartmouth.
Ever heard of it?
I think I have everything I need.
You will be hearing from
the Cornell Application Department.
And you will not be pleased
with the result.
And your affiliation with Cornell
will end completely!
... will end completely.
That is all, sir.
You may go.
There's another dolly
in the truck, Mike.
You could take more than a lamp.
For the record, I wanted
to go another direction.
Which was way better.
Well, I'll be the judge of that.
What do you got?
I lost my engagement ring
in ceramics class.
Left it in my smock.
I had this whole thing
where I go back to class,
wrongly accuse another girl.
Look, I even used makeup
to put a ring around my finger.
- You can hardly see, it's very subtle.
- That is good.
Thank you.
Truthfully, anything
would have been better than that prank.
Text message from my brother.
"Pam cool. Welcome to the family."
How about at Thanksgiving
we prank Tom about being bald?
- This is the last of it.
- That's mine, actually.
- Maybe put it back in the truck.
- You're not staying?
You know, I have some things
I need to do this weekend.
I just remembered, so...
I'll just ride back with you.
- But you want me to put it back.
- I'll be down in just a second.
So...
I think I'm gonna go back
with Darryl.
- Bye.
- OK, bye.
I know it's hard, Mike.
Break-ups hurt.
We didn't break up.
Looked like it.
Sometimes when I'm down like this,
it helps to sing the blues.
That's a really pretty song.
No, no, check it out. Look.
Wanna do that?
That's when you hit me
with what's getting you down.
No, wait, you...
You supposed to...
Never mind.
I thought I'd come in casual today.
Man, I'm hungry.
Anyone else feel like a beet?
- Where did you get those?
- What, these?
Bernard Farms.
Best beets in the state.
I see what you are doing.
But I do not know
where you are going with this.
You will.
As soon as you visit
my new beet farm.
You're supposed to cook these,
aren't you?
Cornell.