- Well, I should go.
- All right,
I'll tell everybody here
that you say hi.
No, don't. I'm mad at them.
Why? What happened?
Not one of them called
to congratulate me on our engagement.
That they might be off the hook for,
because I didn't tell them.
What? Why not?
I just didn't, you know,
want to deal...
Come on, it won't be that bad.
You know what? Here we go.
Everybody, just wanted
to make an announcement.
Pam and I are engaged.
Hi, everyone!
- I thought you were already engaged.
- Nope.
That was Roy.
She was engaged to Roy.
- Thank you, Angela.
- I got a gift for Pam and Roy.
- Do I have to get another one?
- Yes.
A little close
to my engagement there, Tuna.
- What's your game here?
- To get married.
She's not a virgin, you know.
- What's going on?
- No, nothing. Nothing, Michael.
Just saying hi.
The tall guy got engaged.
- To be married?
- Yep.
Sorry.
Subtitles: - Feygnasse Team -
Synch: Collioure
The Office 5x02
- Business Ethics -
Pencils down!
Just kidding. Take your time.
Today is ethics day.
After they finish the quiz,
I'm gonna run my first meeting here.
It's gonna be in-sane!
No, it's not.
I have to read from the binder.
I got it. I got it.
I took you to an intimate restaurant
Then to a suggestive movie
There's nothing left to talk about
Unless it's horizontally
Let's get ethical,
ethical
I wanna get ethical
Let's get into ethics
Let me hear Dunder Mifflin talk
Your body talk
Let me hear your body talk
Why are you helping her?
You're not even dating.
She's my friend, and...
ultimately my strategy
is to sort of...
merge this into a relationship
without her even knowing.
OK, let's give it up for Miss...
Holly Flax!
Thanks, Michael.
Today we're gonna have
a business ethics seminar,
because recently,
without mentioning any names,
there has been
some misconduct at corporate.
And we have a very strict
ethics policy,
- and that employee has been fired.
- Come on!
He's right there.
He was hired.
- Check it out... Hired guy.
- Nice.
OK, elephant in the room.
Let's talk about it.
Do I regret what I did?
Of course I do.
Even though it was an amazing ride,
and I'll give you an example.
Anyone see Survivor, season 6?
Anyone know Joanna on that show?
In New York city,
I hooked up with a girl
who looked exactly like that...
Indistinguishable, so...
OK. Well done. Good speech, Ryan.
You're a good guy.
Let's start discussing
those questionnaires
that you filled in this morning.
"It is wrong to make personal calls
during work hours?"
Now some of you marked
that you very strongly agree.
But ideally you would've selected
"totally agree."
I thought "very strongly agree"
sounded stronger than "totally agree."
Corporate would like to emphasize
that ideally you would all
totally agree with that statement.
Well, I think
we can all totally agree
that Holly is totally fantastic.
Thank you.
"In fact, spending a half hour
at the watercooler
"during work hours
is a form of stealing."
- What?
- Yes, it's called time theft,
and it's the same as taking money
from the company.
Can anyone think
of examples of things
that are over-the-line
time-wasters?
This meeting.
Can't set them up like that.
Why is it OK for smokers
to take breaks all the time?
If I want to go outside
and hang out once an hour,
I'll just take up smoking.
I'll do it. Don't care.
I'll smoke with you.
I got a bag of cigars in my purse.
Stealing office supplies
is another big ethical area
that there seems to be
some confusion about.
Can we have a moment?
Can I talk to you for a second?
A lot of good stuff, and
you look... you look...
- fantastic.
- Michael.
What should we be working on
while you guys are talking?
Do some... do some work.
People expect a lot
from these meetings...
Laughter, sudden twists,
surprise endings.
You need to be Robin Williams
and M. Night Shyamalan.
You need to be Robin Shyamalan.
Well, I just have to get
through the binder.
- Just... you're kind of losing them.
- I am?
Don't think about the stakes.
- It'll freak you out.
- OK.
Well, Michael makes
a really good point. So...
let's just open this up
a little bit.
Say my name is Lauren, and...
here I am shopping
in a supermarket,
and I steal a pencil.
That's not right.
Lauren, enough with the pencils.
I have to go over pencils
and office supplies.
- It's part of the ethics thing.
- That isn't ethics.
Ethics is a real discussion
of competing conceptions of the good.
This is just the corporate
anti-shoplifting rules.
I'll drop an ethics bomb on you.
Would you steal bread
to feed your family?
Exactly, Andy.
I took intro to philosophy...
twice, no big deal.
It's a trick question.
The bread is poisoned.
Also, it's not your real family.
You've been cuckolded
by a stronger, smarter male.
No, that's not how it works.
I would not...
steal the bread.
And I would not
let my family go hungry.
OK, but we should
get back to business.
Have any of you ever faced
any ethical dilemmas
in the workplace?
Anybody?
This is a chance for you to say
something without any repercussions.
Stanley?
- Oscar, come on.
- Pass.
I will go first.
When I discovered Youtube,
I didn't work for five days.
I did nothing.
I viewed Cookie Monster
sings Chocolate Rain
about 1,000 times.
What was the dilemma?
To tell you or not,
and I'm glad I did.
I feel very, very good
and "catharctic."
I promise you that you are not
going to get into trouble.
You can say anything you want
with total and complete immunity.
Come on. Anybody?
Let it fly.
Once in a while,
I'll take a long lunch.
- A siesta.
- Time thief. Time thief... Fire him.
You've really never stolen
any company time?
Never.
You are a thief of joy.
Anybody else?
Sometimes I download pirated music
onto my work computer.
Who hasn't? Good. Good!
- What else?
- No, I'd like to hear more about that.
I once reported oscar to the I.N.S.
Turns out he's clean,
but I'm glad I did it.
- Well, let's keep this party moving on.
- I'll go.
Have you guys ever met Bruce Myers,
the Scranton rep for Hammermill?
Well, for the past six years,
I've been sleeping with him
in exchange for discounts
on our supplies
and outback steakhouse
gift certificates.
Jackpot.
Meredith, that is serious.
I mean, not only is that
a conflict of interest,
but there's also
an exchange of goods.
Exchange of steak.
Have you ever had
sirloin steak, honey?
That's crazy.
That's crazy talk.
The "Merenator",
sleeping with suppliers.
What time we got?
You know what?
That's a good place
to end it, right there.
This, I think,
was a great ethics seminar.
She has given us a lot
of wonderful things to think about.
Right,
what is wrong...
Who's to say, really, in the end?
I mean, because it is unknowable,
but let's give her a round of applause.
Holly, everybody.
Get back to work.
Great job.
I am truly impressed.
That... You really pulled that one out.
Classic, classic meeting.
We should celebrate.
There are some serious
issues with Meredith.
I mean, all of you have done things
I wouldn't have done myself,
but Meredith's actions
are really over the line.
What you gonna do?
So, regarding the supplier,
approximately how many liaisons
have there been?
Liaisons? You mean meet-ups?
I don't know.
Once a month for six years,
something like that.
Meredith, why don't you tell Holly
it's not what she thinks,
nothing unethical happened,
and that you just
like to sleep around.
Am I in trouble here or something?
No. This is just
a stupid formality.
No, it's not a formality.
Now, were these...
meet-ups,
just personal,
unrelated to business?
No. I wouldn't have done it
if it wasn't for the discount paper.
There's not a lot of fruit
in those looms.
For the love of god, we're trying
to help you, you stupid bag.
What I don't understand is...
why the steak coupons,
I mean, if you were already
getting the discounted paper?
Well, it's funny.
Maybe it's a girl thing, but...
after we did it,
when he would give me
those coupons,
I just felt good about myself.
What's going on here?
I thought I had immunity.
Well, unfortunately, immunity,
or something being off the record
does not really exist
in the workplace.
I've never heard of anyone
who kept their job
after something like this.
Well, I'm not quitting.
Yawn... Four seconds.
What are you doing?
You had said that you don't do anything
personal during work time, so...
I'm just making sure.
Wait a minute. So you're gonna time me
every time I yawn?
That's absurd. Really?
Hey, look, monkey knows
how to use a stopwatch, everybody.
He's ti...
Personal conversation...
17 seconds.
There is no way that that was...
One second.
Holly-lujah.
It's a miracle.
You're at your desk.
It's mike-raculous.
Reaching!
You'll get there.
Anyway,
I was giving it some thought,
and there's no reason
that two attractive,
good-looking...
intelligent, funny,
attractive people can't,
you know, just sit down
and work this whole Meredith thing out.
Sounds good.
Good.
Would you care
to bang it out over lunch?
I already bought this.
Your food...
is no good here, my lady.
Sorry.
You know what? Let's go out,
Dunder Mifflin's treat.
Actually, you're not a client, so...
we'll just split it?
Ethical.
- So I've gone over corporate policy.
- What do you think?
What do you think of this place?
- It's very nice.
- Isn't it?
It's kind of business/romantic.
So you're from Des Moines?
That sounds so...
warm.
In summer.
Here too. You know
what my favorite season is?
Maybe we should talk
about Meredith first.
Yes. Get the boring stuff
out of the way.
Autumn was what I was gonna say.
When the leaves change.
It's just... I think it's the most
contemplative of seasons.
OK, so I've gone over this,
and I've thought about it,
and I just don't think
there's any way I can write a report
that doesn't end
with her being terminated.
Terminator.
I'm from the future.
Hey, Andy.
By any chance, did you see
Battlestar Galactica last night?
No, I did not.
Is that any good?
Actually not. It is really so-so.
I mean, I like
all the crazy monsters and stuff,
you know, like Klingons
and Wookies and...
all that, but...
Sorry, was there something
you wanted to add, Dwight?
Is that anything like
the original Battlestar Galactica?
You know, it's weird.
It's practically
a shot-for-shot remake.
Really?
That's cool.
Story's kind of bland.
It's about this guy
named Dumbledore Calrissian,
Who needs to return the ring
back to Mordor.
It's really...
That doesn't sound right.
I just don't want my employees
thinking that their jobs
depend on performance.
I mean...
What sort of place is that
to call home?
And Meredith needs this job.
This is her main source of money.
That's very sweet,
but we have to follow the protocol.
Those are the rules.
New idea. We don't report at all.
We just punish her.
We punish her?
Tell her, can't have sex
for 6 months.
I don't think
we could enforce that.
I don't know. I saw this thing...
- Like a belt with a key.
- A chastity belt.
Yeah, it's more of a...
Underwear garment
that has little spikes,
like, made of... I think sometimes
they're made of metal.
You know what I'm talking about.
You unlock a little door that...
Down...
Where you... Where you put...
Where you put the...
He has not stopped working
for a second.
At 12:45, he sneezed
while keeping his eyes open,
which I always thought
was impossible.
At 1:32, he peed,
and I know that because he did it
in an open soda bottle
under the desk
while filling out expense reports.
And on the flip side,
I've been so busy watching him
that I haven't even started work.
It's exhausting
being this vigilant.
I'll probably have
to go home early today.
I am just saying
that I don't think that
you understand what I am saying.
No, you are saying that
we should sweep it under the carpet,
accept the discount on supplies,
not fire Meredith,
and pretend like the whole thing
never happened.
Yes.
- What am I saying?
- Well...
Busted. I don't...
I'm saying that her behavior
is unethical and a little icky,
and I don't think I want to work
in an environment
where that sort of conduct
is tolerated.
You have to tolerate a lot
when you're part of a family.
It's not a family.
It's a workplace.
I will be honest with you,
that car ride
did not go well.
And that was not my fault.
The only reason I am standing
out here right now
is because I don't want to take
the elevator with her.
And I am holding on
to her leftovers.
19 minutes and 48 seconds.
What were we doing
for 19 minutes and 48 seconds?
None of your business.
So I guess I can assume that was...
personal.
Fine.
So maybe you're not
completely ethical after all.
Yes...
Maybe I'm not.
It's been a little tense.
People are suspicious of me,
and my best friend in the office
won't even talk to me.
Turns out being the morality police
does not make you popular.
I should know, because in middle school,
I was the hall monitor,
and the kids used to stuff
egg salad in my locker.
I was just hoping
middle school was over.
Kendall from corporate H.R. is on line 1
and Holly's on her way too.
What's the only thing worse
than one H.R. Rep?
Two H.R. Reps.
You get me.
Can I sit?
I don't know. Can you?
Kendall, my main man.
Listen, Holly, Michael,
I just got the report that your branch
submitted, and there's a lot of stuff
about a relationship
Meredith is having...
Yes, that came out
during the ethics seminar.
And let the record show that it was
during the immunity part of the seminar.
I'm not sure these circumstances
warrant any action.
I think it's pretty clear
it was unethical.
From what I can gather,
it seems like a gray area.
Look, to be honest,
the company's getting a discount
at a tough time in our balance sheet,
I don't know that the right
thing to do for the company
is to turn our noses up at that.
Kendall, I understand that the discount
is good for the company,
but I'm just not happy
about the way we're getting it.
I thought it was
clear with you, Holly.
Your task was to get signatures
from the employees
showing that
they completed the training.
I understand...
Cause every other branch
has managed to get those.
If it's not something you can handle,
then that's a different discussion.
- No, I can do it.
- Good.
How do you tell somebody
that you care about deeply,
"I told you so"?
Gently? With a rose?
In a funny way,
like it's a hilarious joke?
Or do you just let it go
because saying it
would just make things worse?
Probably the funny way.
Can I have everyone's attention?
Excuse me! May I have
everyone's attention, please?
We need to finish
the ethics seminar.
- No way, lady.
- It's a trap.
Everyone, please,
I just need your signatures
to show corporate
I gave you the training.
- Don't sign anything.
- OK, everybody listen up.
If you are not in that
conference room in 2 minutes,
I'm going to kill you.
It's a quarter to 5:00,
and I have started to gather my things.
Get in there right now,
or I'm gonna lose it!
- Am I getting fired?
- Now is really not the time, Meredith.
In this next section,
we examine the difference
between sick days
and personal days.
Sick days are only to be used
when an illness precludes you
from doing your job
or can spread to your coworkers.
Personal days, on the other hand,
are much more flexible.
Thank you, Meredith.
This was delicious.
Where's the steak sauce?
I think we're out.
I got some in my minivan somewhere.
Wait a second.
How does the steak factor in again?
I think she got it as a tip,
but I don't know
why she didn't just take cash.
I don't care what she's doing.
I hope she just keeps doing it.
Amen, just keep the ribs coming.