- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- I LOVE YOU.
- FOR US.
- MORE THAN WORDS CAN SAY.
- YOU MAKE ME
FEEL SO COMFORTABLE.
- I'’M PREGGERS.
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THERE'’S GONNA BE
TWO OF YOU ON THIS EARTH.
- I KNOW.
- THE HOUSE RIGHT NEXT DOOR
TO ME IS UP FOR RENT.
- MOVE THERE FOR THE SUMMER?
- NEXT DOOR PREGNANT.
- I'’M DOWN.
- SO HOW'’S THE BABY DOING?
- SHE'’S KICKING.
- HEARTBEAT'’S RIGHT THERE.
THESE ARE THE RIB SHADOWS,
RIGHT THERE.
- WE HAVE A CHUBBY MONKEY
ON OUR HANDS, SO...
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- WELL, LET'’S JUST HOPE
THAT THERE'’S NO HOSPITAL LIMIT
TO BAGS...
'’CAUSE THAT WOULD BE A PROBLEM.
I'’M NINE MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND I'’M FREAKING OUT
BECAUSE I HAVE TO PACK
ALL MY HOSPITAL BAGS,
BUT I DON'’T KNOW WHAT TO BRING.
THIS IS MY LIFE.
AND I HAVE, LIKE, 17 BAGS.
I DON'’T HAVE ENOUGH.
YOU SHOULD SEE ALL THE EYELASHES
I BROUGHT TOO.
NIPPLE CREAM.
THAT'’S NICE.
HEADBAND,
IF SHE DOESN'’T HAVE A OVAL HEAD.
DO THEY NEED BIBS IN HOSPITALS?
I DON'’T KNOW,
BUT I'’M BRINGING '’EM IN CASE.
I DON'’T KNOW
IF SHE'’S GONNA BE COLD.
IF SHE'’S GONNA BE HOT.
I DON'’T KNOW
IF SHE'’S GONNA SPIT UP.
IF SHE'’S GONNA NEED BIBS.
I DON'’T KNOW WHY I NEED SO MUCH,
BUT I DO.
WHAT ARE THESE?
I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT SHE'’S GONNA NEED,
SO I'’D RATHER BRING IT ALL.
THIS IS, LIKE, A PUMP BRA.
THIS IS OVERWHELMING.
HOW DO YOU DO THIS?
UGH.
OH, THIS IS SEXY.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'’S GONNA WORK.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'’M TRYING TO PACK HER BAG.
- THIS IS FOR THE HOSPITAL?
- THIS IS HER STUFF, RIGHT HERE.
- DEFINITELY PREPARED MORE
THAN I AM.
I HAVEN'’T PACKED ANYTHING.
- WELL, YOU NEED--
- CAN I JUST SHARE A LITTLE BIT
OF YOUR SPACE
AND MAYBE PUT A TOOTHBRUSH
AND A PAIR OF UNDERWEAR
AND SWEATPANTS IN IT?
- WELL, LET ME JUST--
I DON'’T THINK I HAVE ANY ROOM.
- WE HAVE PLENTY OF STUFF.
WE'’RE--EVERYBODY
IS IN GOOD SHAPE.
- I WONDER WHAT
THE HOSPITAL'’S GONNA SAY.
"HEY, WE'’RE MOVING IN."
- WHAT IS THAT?
- AN ENEMA.
- AN ENEMA?
- AN ENEMA, SO I CAN POOP.
- YOU'’RE GONNA GIVE YOURSELF
AN ENEMA IN THE HOSPITAL?
- OR HERE; DEPENDS ON HOW FAST
THE CONTRACTIONS START.
- IF YOUR WATER BREAKS,
YOU'’RE GOING TO SHOVE SOMETHING
UP YOUR ASS?
- YEAH.
LISTEN, I'’M NOT HOLDING BACK.
- ALL RIGHT.
- IT STINKS IN HERE.
- SHE BETTER HAVE CREAMER.
- WHO'’S THIS [bleep] GIRL?
[sighs] HEY, POOP.
LORENZO THREW UP IN THE CAR.
- EW.
- YEAH, AND HIS CAR SEAT.
- WHEN?
THIS MORNING?
- MM-HMM.
- I WAS COMING OVER TO ASK
IF YOU HAD CREAMER OR MILK.
- YEAH.
IT'’S ALL HIS MILK THROW UP,
SO IT LOOKS LIKE DRIED YOGURT.
- OH, I CAN'’T WAIT FOR THAT.
- YEAH.
I THINK JENNI'’S GONNA HANDLE
THE BABY POOP
AND VOMIT PHENOMENALLY.
- UGH.
- BECAUSE SHE HAD
TO CLEAN UP MINE ALL THE TIME.
YOU WANT ANYTHING?
- NO, I'’M OKAY.
I GOT UP A LITTLE LATE TODAY.
I HAD TO TAKE A SHOWER.
YOU EVER WAKE UP BURNING
WHILE BEING PREGNANT?
LIKE, WHEN YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU'’RE IN THE DESERT?
- OH, YEAH.
- THAT'’S, LIKE, PRE-LABOR,
ROGER WAS TELLING ME.
FLU SYMPTOMS.
AND NOW I'’M GETTING,
LIKE, REALLY SCARED.
IT'’S LIKE I'’M STUCK IN PURGATORY
RIGHT NOW.
- OH, THE WORST.
- IT'’S JUST THE CONSTANT
SAME THING OVER AND OVER.
BACK PAIN AND THE CRAMPS,
BACK PAIN--
AND NOTHING CHANGES.
IT'’S LIKE GROUNDHOGS DAYFOR ME.
- REMEMBER HOW I ALWAYS WANTED
TO DO PRENATAL YOGA WITH YOU?
- YEAH.
I'’M STIFF AS A BOARD.
- WELL, IT'’D BE GOOD, THEN.
YOU COULD STRETCH OUT
YOUR LIGAMENTS, YOUR VAGINA.
- I NEED A VISE GRIP.
I MIGHT AS WELL, '’CAUSE
THE CRAMPS ARE KILLING ME.
EVERYTHING HURTS.
- LIKE, WE SHOULD DO IT TODAY.
- I WOULD LOVE TO DO YOGA.
- I HAVE NOTHING TO DO TODAY.
- I HAVE NOTHING TO DO,
AND IT'’S SO HOT OUT.
I DON'’T WANT TO BE OUTSIDE.
- DO YOU WANT TO HELP ME HOSE
OFF MY CAR SEAT?
- HIT IT WITH DISH SOAP.
- OH, YEAH.
- DISINFECT THAT [bleep].
- [burps]
- I'’M GONNA TURN IT ON.
- WHOA.
JENNI.
[screams]
OH, MY GOD, IT'’S A PENIS.
THIS HOSE IS THE DEVIL.
IT IS POSSESSED.
[screams]
AND THEN IT, LIKE, MOVES LIKE
A CRAZY PENIS.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
- IT WAS LITERALLY
LIKE FIGHTING A SNAKE.
- THIS ISN'’T A HOSE.
THIS IS SOMETHING ELSE.
- THE ANACONDA OF HOSES.
- IT'’S FRICKING WEIRD.
THERE'’S STILL THROW-UP.
- UGH.
- IT IS WHAT IT IS.
WHATEVER.
- MAKE JIONNI CLEAN IT.
- ALL RIGHT, I'’LL PICK YOU UP.
- THANK YOU FOR THE MILK TOO.
- LOVE YOU.
- [gags]
- HMM.
NO TRAFFIC.
THAT'’S GOOD.
[horn blaring]
- I LOVE THE FACT THAT NICOLE
WANTS TO GO DO PRENATAL YOGA
TO MEDITATE,
BUT SHE'’S LAYING ON HER HORN
RIGHT NOW LIKE A CRAZY MADWOMAN.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'’S NOT VERY NAMASTE.
- [burps]
- OH, THAT WAS NICE.
- YOU READY?
OH.
OH, THERE.
[bleep].
[gentle harmonium music]
♪
LOOKS LIKE A FUNERAL.
- SHE'’S PLAYING,
LIKE, THIS HARMONICA THING.
I DON'’T KNOW WHAT THE HELL
IT IS, BUT THERE'’S CANDLES LIT.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE
A FUNERAL NOISE.
SOMEBODY PASSED AWAY,
AND WE'’RE GOING
TO SHOW OUR RESPECTS.
- HELLO, LADIES.
- WE'’RE HERE FOR YOGA.
- ARE WE LATE?
- YEAH.
THERE'’S TWO YOGA MATS
RIGHT THERE.
YOU GOT IT?
- I REALLY HOPE THAT JENNI
DOESN'’T POP IN CLASS,
BECAUSE SHE'’S SO CLOSE
TO GIVING BIRTH,
BUT I KIND OF WANT TO HELP
A GIRL OUT
AND JUST GET
HER LIGAMENTS READY.
♪
- LET'’S BRING OUR HANDS UP
TOWARD OUR HEART CENTER.
♪ AH
- AT FIRST, IT'’S LIKE,
"HUM,"
AND YOU WANT TO BE LIKE,
"WHAT THE [bleep] ARE WE DOING?"
I'’M SO IMMATURE.
all:
♪ AH
BUT THEN AS THE CLASS WENT ON,
YOU ACTUALLY
GOT INTO THE HUMMING,
AND IT WAS RELAXING.
BUT AT FIRST IT'’S LIKE,
"THIS IS WEIRD."
- SO WE'’LL KIND
OF DO A TABLE TOP.
SPREAD THE FINGERS APART.
INHALE, LOOK UP, TAILBONE UP.
- OH, MY GOD.
- EXHALE AROUND
THROUGH THE SPINE.
- I FEEL LIKE A COW.
- DROP OUR BUTT BACK
A LITTLE BIT.
BRING THE HANDS FORWARD,
SO FINGERS FORWARD MORE.
- SHE'’S GONNA POP OUT THAT BABY.
- DON'’T GIVE BIRTH.
- SEPARATE THE FEET.
TAKE A REALLY DEEP, LOW SQUAT.
- I HAD TO POOP THE WHOLE WAY
TO THIS DAMN CLASS.
I GOT TO LET LOOSE.
- LITERALLY.
- I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
- AWESOME.
- IN HERE?
- YES, RIGHT TO THE LEFT.
- SHE HAS TO POOP.
DON'’T WANT TO LET
LOOSE ON THE FLOOR.
- NO.
[toilet flushes]
OVERALL, THE YOGA EXPERIENCE,
MY BODY DEFINITELY HURTS.
- YOGA WAS THE WORST EXPERIENCE
OF MY LIFE.
- YOGA MADE ME FEEL
LIKE A FAT WHALE.
- YEAH.
- NAMASTE, BITCH.
- SOON AS I'’M DONE WITH THIS,
WE'’RE GONNA GO BACK
TO TAKE A NAP, OKAY?
YOU WANT TO TAKE A NAP?
HERE, GIVE ME THE--
OW.
THAT'’S IT.
THAT--THAT'’S IT.
HEH!
- NO!
- PUTTING LORENZO DOWN
FOR A NAP'’S PRETTY TOUGH.
I FEEL LIKE INSTEAD OF SLEEPING,
LORENZO WOULD RATHER
JUST PLAY WITH ME.
BUT I'’M GONNA TRY HARD
TO PUT HIM IN HIS OWN ROOM.
thud!
- DADDY. DADDY.
DA!
WANT BA.
- YOU GOT TO TAKE A NAP.
- NO!
- YOU HAVE TO. YOU HAVE TO.
- SHH.
LORENZO,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE A NAP.
I'’M TRYING
TO PUT HIM IN THE CRIB.
I DON'’T KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT HE'’S NOT REALLY COOPERATING.
- [wailing]
- COME ON.
WHEN IT COMES TO NAPPING,
LORENZO'’S DEFINITELY THE BOSS.
I HAVE NO CONTROL
WHEN HE WANTS TO SLEEP.
TAKE A NAP.
JUST ME AND YOU.
THERE YOU GO, BUB.
- BA-BA.
- LET'’S TAKE A NAP.
AFTER TRYING TO GIVE LORENZO FOR
A NAP, IT'’S JUST NOT WORKING.
NOW I JUST WANT TO GO TO SLEEP.
YOU WANT TO GO IN THE CRIB?
FORGET IT.
HE'’S NOT GOING TO SLEEP.
THE TERRIBLE TWOS
ARE KICKING IN.
HERE WE GO.
[laughs]
OH, MY GOD.
- ♪ OH, OH
♪ YOU'’RE TAKING ME ♪
♪ A DARK AND HAUNTED
♪ MYSTERY
- LOOKIT. WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT AN INTRODUCTION OUTFIT?
- I THINK YOU HAVE MORE THAN
ENOUGH, JUST IN THAT BAG,
FOR A WEEK IN THE HOSPITAL.
- I'’M A LITTLE ANXIOUS
AND NERVOUS
ABOUT WHAT I HAVE TO DO
BEFORE WE GO INTO LABOR
BECAUSE I DON'’T WANT
TO FORGET ANYTHING.
[sighs]
IT IS JUST SO MUCH.
I ACTUALLY REALLY
GOT WINDED RIGHT THERE,
SO I WAS LIKE,
"JUST ROLL WITH IT."
I CAN'’T TALK LONG.
DO WE EVEN KNOW HOW LONG
IT'’S GONNA TAKE
TO GET TO THE HOSPITAL
FROM HERE?
- I'’M ESTIMATING 20 MINUTES,
TOPS.
- I'’D FEEL MORE COMFORTABLE
IF I COULD DO A TEST RUN.
- [sighs]
IF THAT MAKES YOU FEEL BETTER,
TO DO A TEST RUN,
WE'’LL DO A TEST RUN.
- SO ARE WE TIMING IT FROM
WHEN WE LEAVE, OR WHEN WE START?
- AT THIS POINT, I THINK I'’M
GONNA JUST YES JENNI TO DEATH
TO PRETTY MUCH ANYTHING SHE
SAYS AND JUST MAKE HER HAPPY.
IF SHE WANTED TO GO STRAWBERRY
PICKING TODAY, I WOULD GO.
I WOULD DO BASICALLY ANYTHING
SHE SAID JUST TO MAKE THIS ROAD
A LITTLE BIT EASIER FOR HER.
THE MOMENT YOU KNOW IT'’S ON,
WE'’LL HEAD OUT THE DOOR.
SO LET'’S PLAY IT LIKE THAT.
- IT'’S TIME.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'’S GO.
I KNOW WHERE EVERYTHING
IS THAT NEEDS TO GO IN THE CAR.
I START GRABBING SUITCASES.
I START GRABBING BABY SEATS.
I REALLY HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
JENNI'’S DOING AT THIS POINT.
- I NEED YOU GUYS TO RALLY.
COME ON.
IT'’S ALREADY TAKING TOO LONG.
AND GO.
LET'’S GO.
- I'’M GETTING THE STUFF.
- OH, YOU ARE?
WELL, WHERE ARE THE DOGS
GONNA FIT, THEN?
BABE?
- YOU KNOW THAT THE DAY
THAT THIS HAPPENS,
DOGS CAN'’T COME, CORRECT?
- I GUESS.
- I THOUGHT THE IDEA, THOUGH,
WAS WE'’RE REPLICATING WHAT IT
WOULD BE LIKE TO RUSH OUT,
AND OBVIOUSLY AND CLEARLY,
WE'’RE NOT BRINGING THE DOGS
WHEN THAT ACTUALLY HAPPENS.
SO WHY DID I EVEN BOTHER
PUTTING THE SEAT IN THERE?
THAT MAKES NO SENSE.
- THAT'’S WHAT I WAS TRYING
TO TELL YOU.
- THAT, TO ME, WOULD BE ABSURD.
- THEY'’RE OUR CHILDREN.
- THEY ARE NOT OUR--
THEY'’RE YOUR CHILDREN.
THEY'’RE NOT. THEY'’RE DOGS.
I TREAT THEM AS SUCH.
I LOVE THEM,
BUT THEY'’RE [bleep] DOGS.
- OOH, DROPPING THE F-BOMB.
- YEAH, WELL,
YOU DROP IT 9,000 TIMES A DAY.
CHALK ONE UP FOR ME.
OH, GOD.
- CAN YOU JUST TURN THE CAR ON?
IT'’S REALLY HOT BACK HERE.
SHE JUST SNUCK OUT OF HER THING.
YOU JUST MADE ME FAIL, OKAY?
- NO, YOU--YOU FAILED
ON YOUR OWN BY BRINGING THEM.
- ROGER'’S A LITTLE WEIRDED OUT,
THE FACT
THAT I'’M BRINGING THE DOGS,
BUT THEY'’RE MY BABIES.
[dogs barking]
HEY. HEY.
SHH.
THEY'’RE COMING FOR THE RIDE.
IT'’S A FREE COUNTRY.
[dog barking]
STOP IT!
STOP THE FIGHTING!
HEY, YOU GET ON YOUR SEAT BELT.
SIT. RELAX.
WHO THE [bleep] IS DRIVING
IN FRONT OF US?
THEY'’RE GOING, LIKE, MISS DAISY.
- I AGREE, BUT WE--WE'’RE--
THIS IS A TEST RUN, AND THEY--
IT COULD BE WORSE THAN THIS
WHEN WE'’RE GOING.
SO LET'’S JUST RELAX.
I'’M USUALLY THAT VOICE
OF REASON,
AND TODAY ESPECIALLY,
I HAVE TO BE THAT GUY.
WE'’RE PREPARED FOR THIS.
I'’M JUST TRYING
TO CALM HER DOWN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, YOU [bleep]?
[horn blares]
- OH, BABE.
DEATH BY HORN.
- EVERYTHING'’S GONNA BE FINE.
[dogs barking]
- HEY, HEY.
I SHOULD START BETTING MONEY.
- I'’M HAPPY.
I MEAN, WE DID GOOD.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- SO...
- I THINK OUR DRY RUN
WENT PRETTY GOOD.
25 MINUTES.
- MM-HMM.
- NOT BAD.
- YEAH.
- MAMA NEEDS SOME FRO-YO
IN HER LIFE.
- I WOULD NOT HAVE
BROUGHT THE DOGS.
ABSURD.
I'’LL BUY YOU SOME FROZEN YOGURT.
[dogs barking]
- RELAX!
- LORENZO,
YOU WANT TO HELP ME COOK?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OVER THERE?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE HELPING.
THE FIRST NIGHT
WE GOT DOWN TO THE SHORE,
JENNI AND ROGER
MADE US A NICE DINNER.
NOW NICOLE AND I
WANT TO RETURN THE FAVOR.
SCRAMBLE, SCRAMBLE, SCRAMBLE,
SCRAMBLE, SCRAMBLE.
WANT TO DO IT?
I LOVE TO COOK,
MY MOM LOVES TO COOK,
AND MY GRANDMA LOVES TO COOK.
IT KIND OF RUNS IN THE FAMILY.
SCRAMBLE, SCRAMBLE, SCRAMBLE,
SCRAMBLE.
I KNEW YOU COULD HELP.
I'’M HOPING
LORENZO TAKES AFTER US.
- [sneezes]
- BLESS YOU.
I HOPE NO ONE GETS THAT
IN THEIR MOUTH.
- ♪ SHE'’S MY QUEEN ♪
- THIS IS CUTE, RIGHT?
- YES, VERY NICE.
IS YOUR MOTHER IN TOWN?
- WHY?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- STOP.
THEY'’RE HIGH-WAISTED.
- CAN WE MAKE THE WORLD'’S
LARGEST QUILT OUT OF THOSE?
- STOP.
THOSE ARE CLASSY UNDERWEAR.
AND THEY HOLD IN OUR DAUGHTER.
- THEY'’RE BLOOMERS.
- SHAPEWEAR.
NO, THEY'’RE SHAPEWEAR.
- DO YOU STILL NEED TO WEAR
THOSE AFTER SHE'’S HERE?
- YES.
- YOU DO? HONESTLY?
- I--THIS DOESN'’T GO BACK
TO NORMAL RIGHT AWAY.
THEY KEEP MY TUMMY IN SO IT
DOESN'’T FEEL LIKE IT'’S SO HEAVY.
- [laughs]
WHATEVER WORKS, BABY.
GRANNY PANTIES IT IS.
- YOU ENJOY YOURSELF WITH YOUR
FASCINATION OF MY UNDERWEAR.
- IT WASN'’T THE FASCINATION
OF THE UNDERWEAR.
IT WAS THE FASCINATION
OF THE SIZE OF THE UNDERWEAR.
- SHUT UP.
- [gasps]
DID WE GET DORITOS?
- YES, I GOT EVERYTHING FOR YOU.
- OKAY.
I AM GONNA MAKE
MY INFAMOUS DORITO TACO SALAD.
THAT'’S BASICALLY THE ONLY
GOOD THING THAT I CAN COOK.
I JUST HOPE I DON'’T
BURN THE HOUSE DOWN.
HOW DO YOU TURN THIS ON?
WHOA.
WHICH ONE'’S WHICH?
THERE'’S TEN OF THEM.
- THIS DORITO SALAD
IS NICOLE'’S SIGNATURE SALAD.
SHE MAKES IT EVERY TIME
SHE SAYS SHE WANTS TO COOK.
LIKE, THIS IS HER MEAL.
THAT'’S IT.
IF SHE SAYS, "I'’M COOKING,"
THEY'’RE GETTING DORITO SALAD.
- THIS LOOKS SO GROSS,
BUT IT TASTES SO GOOD.
- HELLO?
- HOLA.
- HI.
- YUMMY.
- FOOD'’S READY.
- I SEE THAT.
- THE FIRST NIGHT
WHEN JIONNI AND NICOLE
GOT HERE AND WERE SETTLING IN,
WE BARBECUED FOR THEM,
SO I THINK IT'’S, YOU KNOW,
VERY FITTING
THAT THEY'’RE INVITING US OVER
TONIGHT FOR A DINE-IN NIGHT.
I'’M STARVING.
- TACOS AND CHICKEN PARM.
- TACOS?
- TACO SALAD.
- OH.
- HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
WE WENT TO YOGA.
- JENNI SAID SHE WANTS YOU
TO STRETCH HER EVERY NIGHT NOW.
- I DON'’T MIND.
I'’LL DO WHATEVER.
- I KNOW GOOD MASSAGE TECHNIQUES
AND POSITIONS IF YOU GUYS EVER--
- OH, MY GOD.
DID YOU TELL NICOLE
WHAT WE DID, OR WHAT WE--
- KIND OF.
- NOT REALLY.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT'’D YOU DO?
- I--I PENETRATED YOUR MAN.
PROBABLY THE EASIEST WAY
TO SAY IT.
- [groans]
[laughs]
- BAD MORNING TO TAKE A VIAGRA.
- OH, GOOD LORD.
- TELL ME.
- THIS GUY TOLD ME
IT WAS A DADDY DAY CARE,
OR DADDY BOOT CAMP, RATHER.
IT--IT WAS ANYTHING BUT.
IT WAS RUBBING HIS BACK,
HIS FOREHEAD,
THE BACK OF HIS NECK,
HIS FEET,
WITH HOT OILS.
- IT WOULD HAVE MADE
GAY JOEY FEEL COMFORTABLE.
- A LITTLE BIT OF JEAL--
I'’M KIND OF JEALOUS.
- I'’M A LITTLE BIT OF JEALOUS.
PREGNANCY BRAIN.
- I'’M A LITTLE JEALOUS OF JIONNI
GETTING RUBBED DOWN BY MY MAN.
- ME TOO.
WELL, I WANT JIONNI
TO DO THAT TO ME.
I DON'’T WANT ROGER
THAT'’S WEIRD.
I WOULD HAVE LOVED THAT CLASS.
- RIGHT?
WE WALKED IN, THEY GO, "WHO'’S
THE WOMAN? WHO'’S THE MAN?"
HE GOES, "YOU'’RE THE WOMAN."
- OW.
- I WAS LITERALLY HUMPING
IN THE AIR ON ALL FOURS,
INTO HIS BRASCIOLE.
- THANK YOU FOR DINNER.
- I'’M DONE.
- I AM SO FULL RIGHT NOW.
- YES, THANK YOU BOTH.
- WELCOME, GUYS.
- I LITERALLY INHALED
17 PORTIONS.
- LORENZO, ARE YOU
GONNA HELP DADDY CLEAN UP?
- LORENZO, YOU ARE A MAN
OF THIS HOUSE,
SO YOU NEED TO HELP.
- FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
- BYE-BYE.
- BYE.
- I WAS REALLY NERVOUS
WITH LORENZO,
'’CAUSE I WAS LIKE, "OH, I HOPE I
DON'’T HAVE, LIKE, A UGLY BABY."
- I'’M PETRIFIED.
- LIKE, PLEASE BE CUTE.
PLEASE BE CUTE.
- A LOT OF WEIRD THINGS
GO ON WITH NEWBORNS.
- THEY COULD LOOK WEIRD
AT FIRST, BUT THEN CHANGE.
- YEAH.
LIKE, WITH--
- SO DON'’T BE UPSET
IF IT'’S A LITTLE WEIRD AT FIRST.
- BECAUSE SHE'’S SO BIG, LIKE,
I'’M GUARANTEEING A CONE HEAD.
SHE'’S GONNA PEAK AT HER HEAD.
- LIKE, DO YOU EVER NOTICE,
LIKE,
TWO REALLY GOOD-LOOKING PEOPLE
MAKE AN UGLY-ASS BABY?
OR, LIKE, UGLY PEOPLE MAKE--
- YOU AND JIONNI DIDN'’T.
- WE GOT LUCKY.
- YEAH.
- LORENZO GOT ALL MY GENES.
[laughter]
- ♪ YOU WEAR YOUR SECRETS
SO WELL ♪
♪ THEY CANNOT TELL
[dog barking]
- SHUT UP!
THIS IS A WICKER BASKET,
OR SOMETHING.
- WHAT'’S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A WICKER BASKET
AND A WICKER BOX?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- A WICKER BASKET
WAS WHAT LITTLE RED RIDING HOOD
WAS CARRYING
TO HER GRANDMOTHER'’S HOUSE.
A WICKER BOX WAS WHAT ELMER FUDD
WAS GONNA DO TO HER
WHEN HE GOT THERE.
- THAT'’S A HORRIBLE JOKE.
[dog barking]
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO ABOUT THAT?
- I NEED STUFF.
- [shouting] WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO ABOUT THAT?
- OH, THE BARKING?
- YEAH.
- YOU'’RE THE ONE THAT CLAIMS
THAT THEY DON'’T HAVE AN ISSUE.
- SHUT UP!
- I'’M SCARED THE DOGS ARE GONNA
CONSTANTLY WAKE UP OUR DAUGHTER,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WHEN SHE--WHEN SHE'’S SLEEPING,
I WANT HER TO BE ABLE TO SLEEP,
AND THE DOGS ARE LOUD.
I MEAN, LET'’S BE HONEST.
THEY BARK NONSTOP.
EVERYTHING WE'’VE TRIED THUS FAR,
JENNI JUST QUITS, RIGHT?
I CAN NAME NUMEROUS THINGS.
- I WANT TO SOUNDPROOF HER ROOM.
HEY, SHUT UP!
- IF I COULD AT LEAST
SOUNDPROOF THAT WALL.
- I WANT TO SOUNDPROOF THE ROOM.
WHY NOT?
IT'’S A THEORY.
HYPOTHETICALLY SPEAKING,
IT SHOULD WORK.
I HOPE IT WORKS.
I HOPE WHEN OUR DAUGHTER'’S HERE,
THAT SHE WON'’T HEAR THE DOGS.
SHUT UP!
- SO I GOT SOME PLANS TODAY.
SINCE JENNI'’S STRESSED OUT ABOUT
BEING A MOM, DELIVERING,
I JUST FEEL LIKE SHE NEEDS TO
GET HER MIND OFF OF IT A LITTLE.
SO I WANT TO THROW HER
A LITTLE BABY SHOWER.
- REALLY?
- AND INVITE A FEW
OF HER FRIENDS.
- DOES SHE KNOW?
- NO.
IT'’LL BE, LIKE,
A LITTLE SURPRISE.
I THINK JENNI'’S GETTING
STRESSED OUT BECAUSE HER LIFE
IS TOTALLY GONNA CHANGE.
SO I REALLY WANT TO THROW JENNI
A SURPRISE BABY SHOWER
BEFORE THE BABY COMES OUT
AND RIPS HER VAGINA OPEN.
AND I WANT TO MAKE
HER THIS CAKE.
- OH, YEAH?
- BUT IT'’S NOT LIKE
YOUR AVERAGE BABY SHOWER CAKE.
IT'’S SO GROSS.
- EW.
THIS IS, LIKE, DISTURBING.
[dog barking]
- NOEL, SHUT UP!
I'’M SORRY I'’M NO HELP.
I'’M TRYING TO GET MY WATER
TO BREAK OVER HERE.
I HOPE THAT WORKS.
- I KNEW THAT WASN'’T GONNA WORK.
- SOUNDPROOFING
ISN'’T GOING SO WELL.
- WE CAN'’T USE ADHESIVE SPRAY,
BECAUSE I DON'’T FEEL SAFE
SPRAYING IT IN THE BABY'’S ROOM.
SO WE'’RE USING
DOUBLE-SIDED TAPE,
WHICH ISN'’T WORKING SO WELL.
I'’M TRYING IT ONE MORE TIME.
NOPE.
- WE NEED BETTER TAPE.
- BE BACK.
I'’M GONNA GO SEE
HOW AUNT JENNI'’S DOING.
BYE.
GOD.
OOH!
[dogs barking]
HEY, GUYS.
- SHUT UP!
- HELLO?
- HEY, BOO!
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- SHUT UP!
- HEY, GUYS.
- HI.
- I HAVEN'’T HEARD
FROM YOU ALL DAY.
- YOU'’RE CUTE.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- WE'’RE--WE'’RE DOING A LITTLE--
A LITTLE BIT OF SOUNDPROOFING.
DID YOU HEAR THAT NOISE
WHEN YOU WALKED INTO THE HOUSE?
- YES.
- WE'’RE--WE'’RE TRYING
TO SAVE OUR DAUGHTER FROM THAT.
- WELL, IF YOU SOUNDPROOF
THE ROOM,
HOW ARE YOU GONNA HEAR HER CRY?
THEN AGAIN,
YOU WANT TO HEAR HER CRY TOO.
- YOU PICKING--
YOU PICKING THIS APART?
- NO.
- TRY IT OUT.
I'’LL SHUT THE DOOR.
YOU YELL INTO IT.
- SO YOU WANT ME
TO YELL OUT HERE?
- BARK LIKE A DOG.
BARK LIKE A DOG.
GO.
- [barking]
[dogs barking]
[laughter]
- IT DOESN'’T WORK AT ALL.
AT ALL.
- I BLAME IT ON THE PREGNANCY.
- LISTEN, YOU HAVE GOOD IDEAS.
IT JUST--
YOU GOT TO THINK ABOUT IT.
- THAT'’S...
[laughs] COMING FROM YOU.
- I'’M GONNA GO ON RECORD NOW
AND SAY YOU'’RE A GENIUS.
- WHAT'’D I DO?
- [laughing]
I'’M ACTUALLY SHOCKED THAT
NICOLE ACTUALLY KNOWS SOMETHING.
- YEAH.
- OW.
- "A" FOR EFFORT.
YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
JUST WAIT FOR THAT MUCUS PLUG.
- OH, WE'’VE ALREADY--SUPPOSEDLY,
JENNI'’S ALREADY SEEN
SOME SIGNS OF THAT.
- THAT MEANS SHE'’S COMING.
- HURRY UP.
- IT MEANS SHE'’S GONNA
BE HERE VERY SOON.
- YOU MIGHT BE IN LABOR 27 HOURS
LIKE I WAS.
- CAN YOU IMAGINE?
- IT HONESTLY WASN'’T THAT BAD.
ONCE I GOT THE EPIDURAL,
I DIDN'’T FEEL ANYTHING.
- YOU HAD AN EPIDURAL,
SO HOW MUCH--WERE YOU FEELING
ANY PAIN, OR NO?
- NO PAIN.
JUST A LOT OF PRESSURE.
WITH THE EPIDURAL, THANK GOD
I DIDN'’T FEEL THAT,
BUT HE WAS, LIKE,
ELBOW-DEEP IN [bleep] VAGINA.
- A LOT OF PRESSURE?
- LIKE, I FELT--
- LIKE YOU HAD TO POOP?
- A WATERMELON COME OUT. YEAH.
- THAT'’S WEIRD.
- YEAH, LIKE--
- YOU GET [bleep].
- [bleep] DEEP BY YOUR DOCTOR.
YEAH.
- WHAT IF THEY HAVE BIG HANDS?
- OH, AND ONCE THAT LAST PUSH
AND THE BABY'’S OUT,
DOES THAT ALL SUBSIDE?
THAT ALL GOES AWAY? NO PAIN?
- BUT THEN YOU GOT TO PUSH
THE PLACENTA OUT.
SO YOU GIVE BIRTH TWICE.
- OH, GOD. ALL RIGHT.
I'’M SORRY I ASKED.
ALL RIGHT. THAT'’S GOOD.
- THEN IT ALL JUST FLOPS OUT.
[gabbles]
AND THEN YOU GET STITCHED UP.
I'’M SCARING YOU.
I'’M GONNA GO NOW.
- YEAH.
LEARNED A LOT, HERE. THANK YOU.
- SEE YOU LATER.
- THANK YOU.
- BYE, LOVE YOU.
[dog barking]
- FOR THE 45TH TIME,
CAN YOU JUST YELL AT THOSE DOGS?
- SHUT UP!
- I HAVE A LOT TO DO
FOR JENNI'’S BABY SHOWER.
I HAVE TO GO
TO THE GROCERY STORE
TO GET ALL THE FOOD
AND YUMMY STUFF.
CHEESE.
FRUIT.
WHOA, THOSE ARE THE BIGGEST
BALLS I'’VE EVER SEEN.
OH, GRANDMA UNDERWEAR.
COOL.
[bleep].
I KIND OF WANT TO DO TWO CAKES.
WHAT IF ONE CAKE
LOOKS LIKE [bleep]?
THEN I HAVE ANOTHER CAKE
TO SHOW EVERYBODY.
I'’M GONNA POOP MY PANTS.
UM, I DON'’T THINK
I CAN REACH THAT.
IT'’S, LIKE, PUSH CAKE, LIKE,
YOU KNOW, GET READY TO PUSH
THE BABY OUT OF YOUR VAG.
- THOSE ARE ALL THE ONES
THAT WE HAVE.
- OKAY.
CAN YOU REACH?
OH, YOUR ARM'’S BROKEN.
- WHICH ONE?
- THE PINK.
SHE'’S HAVING A GIRL.
IT'’S HER FAVORITE COLORS,
PINK AND BLACK.
I HAVE A QUESTION.
- WHAT?
- I'’M TRYING TO MAKE HER
A REALLY VULGAR CAKE,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE A VAGINA.
- JUST SLICE IT AND THEN JUST
PUT ALL YOUR STUFF IN THERE.
WHEN YOU PUT THE ICING ON,
JUST KIND OF RAISE THE ICING
UP A LITTLE BIT
IN THE CORNER WHERE YOU CUT IT,
SO IT'’LL LOOK JUST LIKE THAT.
- AND IT LOOKS LIKE A VAGINA?
- IT'’LL LOOK JUST LIKE THAT.
- OKAY. COOL.
THAT'’S ALL I NEED.
WE'’RE GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU'’RE WELCOME, HONEY.
- THANK YOU, GUYS.
I FEEL LIKE I GOT ENOUGH STUFF
FOR THE PARTY
WITH THE FOOD, THE CHIPS,
THE DESSERT, THE CAKES.
NOW I JUST
NEED TO SET IT ALL UP.
OH, HI, BABY.
- HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
- I NEED HELP.
- WITH?
- I BOUGHT ALL THESE BALLOONS
AND DECORATIONS FOR THE PARTY,
BUT I DON'’T WANT JENNI
TO SEE IT WHEN I BRING IT IN.
- OKAY.
- SO WE GOT TO BE,
LIKE, SECRET AGENTS
AND SNEAK INTO THE HOUSE.
- RIGHT NOW?
- YEAH.
IF THERE WAS ONE DREAM JOB
I COULD HAVE,
I'’D WANT TO BE A SECRET AGENT,
LIKE SCARLETT JOHANSSON.
AND JIONNI WOULD LIKE THAT
BECAUSE HE LOVES ME.
SO I HAVE TO GO
SECRET-AGENT STYLE
AND MAKE SURE
THAT JENNI'’S NOT LOOKING.
[grunts]
OH, MAN.
I JUST TINKLED IN MY PANTS.
I CAN'’T BREATHE.
CLEAR.
I'’M GONNA GIVE BIRTH.
- NICOLE WOULD NOT MAKE
A GREAT SPY.
SHE'’S TOO LOUD TO BE A SPY.
- COME ON. COME ON.
BALLOONS, COME ON.
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON, BABY.
- I GET EVERYTHING
INTO OUR HOUSE,
AND I REALLY, REALLY HOPE
SHE DIDN'’T SEE ME
BRING ALL THIS STUFF IN.
- I DON'’T KNOW WHAT I'’M DOING.
- DON'’T MESS IT UP.
- WELL, I DON'’T KNOW
HOW TO DO IT.
- YOU JUST POUR IT IN
AND SWIRL IT.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
- WELL, GO AHEAD,
AUNT JEMIMA, DO IT.
- WHO'’S AUNT JEMIMA?
WHO IS AUNT JEMIMA?
- ISN'’T SHE THE LADY ON
THE--COOKER? I DON'’T KNOW.
SHE HAS TO DO SOMETHING
WITH COOKING.
- I NEVER HEARD OF AUNT JEMIMA
IN MY LIFE.
- SHE MIGHT BE ON THE--
I FORGOT THE BOX.
- MARTHA STEWART?
- NO.
I DON'’T THINK
THIS IS THE RIGHT SIZE PAN.
- NO ONE SAID WE WERE BAKERS.
- BEST I CAN DO.
WHAT'’S THIS?
- IT'’S GONNA BE THE BABY.
[laughs]
- WAIT A SECOND.
YOU'’RE GONNA PUT PAINT
ON THE CAKE?
- YEAH.
- YOU KNOW IT'’S NOT EDIBLE?
- I KNOW, JIONNI.
IT'’S JUST FOR SHOW.
CHEAP BARBIE.
- ALL RIGHT. GOOD LUCK.
- I WANT TO MAKE
THIS BARBIE LOOK LIKE JENNI,
SO SHE KNOWS IT'’S HER CAKE.
JENNI HAS A DRAGON.
I'’M PUTTING HER TATTOOS ON HER.
A CAT HERE.
SHE HAS ONE ON HER ANKLE.
DOES SHE HAVE ANY OTHER TATTOOS?
- SHE HAS ONE ON HER BUTT CHEEK.
- SHE HAS ONE ON HER BUTT CHEEK?
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
I'’M GONNA PUT PASTIES
ON HER BOOB.
SHE LIKES PASTIES.
I BASICALLY JUST
HAVE TO PUT THE BARBIE ON
WITH THE LITTLE SCARY HEAD
COMING OUT OF THE VAGINA,
LIKE SHE'’S GIVING BIRTH.
SHE GOT A TAN BABY
WITH EYELASHES COMING OUT.
WHAT A BEAUTY.
AND THEN I HAVE TO WRITE
"PUSH, JENNI, PUSH."
SO I FEEL LIKE THAT CAKE
IS THE EASY CAKE.
OH, [bleep].
IT'’S STUCK.
WHOA.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
VICTORY.
JUST A LITTLE STICKAGE.
IT'’S NOT BAD.
AND I HAVE TO CUT OUT,
LIKE, A--WHAT'’S THIS SHAPE?
- VAGINA?
- NO--WHY YOU SAY IT LIKE THAT?
"VAGINA."
EW.
THE CHERRIES RESEMBLE
THE PLACENTA AND THE BLOOD
WHEN THE BABY COMES OUT.
- THAT'’S NASTY.
- IT'’S LIKE A PERIOD.
EW, A VAGINA.
- YOU'’RE SICK.
- AND THEN ADD THE SPRINKLES
FOR LITTLE PUBES.
[both chuckle]
I NEED A BUTTHOLE.
AND THEN SOME SPRINKLES
ON THE BUTTHOLE,
'’CAUSE I DON'’T KNOW
IF HER BUTT'’S HAIRY.
HOW DO YOU POP THE HEAD OFF?
BABE, I'’M SCARED.
[laughs]
BABE, STOP.
AWW.
THAT'’S CREEPY.
THAT IS CREEPY.
- [moans]
- OH, STOP!
THAT--THAT LOOKS PHENOMENAL.
- GROSS.
- ALL RIGHT, MY JOB
IS DONE FOR THE DAY.
I'’M CHECKING OUT.
- WHO'’S GONNA HELP MAMA?
- ME.
- THERE YOU GO.
- COME ON. WE GOT TO GET
JENNI'’S SHOWER READY.
I'’VE NEVER PLANNED A BABY SHOWER
BEFORE, AND I'’M REALLY NERVOUS.
- LET'’S WORK DOUBLE TIME.
- CROWN.
- I NEED TAPE.
- HOW WOULD I DO THIS?
BABY.
NOW IT LOOKS LIKE A TURD.
I DEFINITELY WANT TO GET
EVERYTHING DONE
BEFORE JENNI'’S FRIENDS
COME OVER,
SO I JUST FEEL LIKE WE'’RE
RACING THE TIME RIGHT NOW.
THE STREAMERS ARE RUINED.
DID YOU EVER PLAY
THE DIRTY DIAPER GAME?
- NO. HOW DOES THAT WORK?
- YOU GOT TO GUESS...
- EW!
- WHICH CHOCOLATE
IS IN THE THE DIAPIE.
JUST TO MAKE
IT FUN AND INTERESTING,
I HAVE GAMES
TO PLAY AT THE BABY SHOWER.
ONE IS THE POOP GAME
IN THE DIAPER.
SO YOU GET CHOCOLATES,
AND THEN YOU MELT THE CHOCOLATES
IN THE DIAPER, AND THEN YOU SEE
WHAT KIND OF CHOCOLATE IT IS.
EW.
[gags]
AND A LOT OF OTHER STUFF.
I JUST WANT THE PARTY
TO BE NICE AND FUN AND CUTE,
AND NOT, LIKE, BORING,
LIKE WE'’RE JUST SITTING THERE.
ALL RIGHT, THE GIRLS
ARE GONNA BE HERE SOON.
- I ACTUALLY GOT TO GO
HELP ROGER, ANYWAY.
- WHILE I'’M THROWING JENNI
THE BABY SHOWER, YOU AND ROGER--
- I'’LL BE HELPING ROGER
WITH THE NURSERY.
- BECAUSE I WANT
TO SURPRISE JENNI
AND SHOW HER
MEILANI'’S FINISHED NURSERY.
YOU KNOW, JUST SO EVERYTHING
IS GOOD FOR THE BABY
WHEN SHE GIVES BIRTH.
[doorbell rings]
[bleep] GRANNY PANTIES.
OH, I CAN'’T.
HURRY, HURRY, HURRY.
THE GIRLS ARE HERE,
BUT I'’M LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,
GET IN THE HOUSE
SO JENNI DOESN'’T SEE YOU GUYS,"
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE SHE CAN JUST
LOOK OUT HER WINDOW
AND EVERYTHING WILL BE RUINED.
- OH, MY GOD.
- OH, YEAH, THE CAKES.
- OH, MY--
- DID YOU MAKE THESE?
- YEAH. I MADE THEM.
- THIS IS HYSTERICAL.
- YEAH.
- OH, MY GOD, AN ACTUAL VAGINA?
- MM-HMM. I GOOGLED.
- THAT'’S AMAZING.
- ALL RIGHT,
SO NOW THAT YOU GUYS ARE HERE,
I'’M GONNA CALL HER.
- HELLO?
- HI, BOO.
- HI.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- PISSING OFF MY DOGS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- DO YOU WANT TO COME HANG OUT?
BECAUSE JIONNI BROUGHT LORENZO
TO THE PARK, AND I'’M BORED.
- YEAH, SURE.
- ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU SOON.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
- CAN YOU NOT LICK YOURSELF
ON MY BED?
- ALL RIGHT. COME IN HERE.
[mumbles softly]
- GET LOW.
SHE'’S COMING.
- CIAO, CIAO.
OH, MY GOD.
all: SURPRISE!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- HI.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
NO WAY.
I HATE SURPRISES.
EVERYONE THAT KNOWS ME
KNOWS I DON'’T DO SURPRISES.
- COME IN.
COME SEE OUR DECORATIONS.
- IF I DID, I WOULDN'’T HAVE
SHOWED UP IN COWBOY BOOTS
AND A GREEN SWEATER.
OH, MY GOD, WHO MADE THAT?
- I MADE THESE CAKES
THIS MORNING.
- YOU DID?
- YEAH. DO YOU LOVE THEM?
- EW!
OH, THAT'’S A BUTTHOLE.
- EVEN THOUGH THIS CAKE
LOOKS VULGAR AND DISGUSTING,
THE CAKE
IS ACTUALLY REALLY GOOD.
- NOT BAD.
- VULGAR?
YOU PUT A HEMORRHOID ON IT.
- NO, THAT WAS--OH, YEAH,
A BUTTHOLE WITH A HEMORRHOID.
THAT'’S '’CAUSE YOU HAVE ONE.
- THANKS.
HERE'’S YOUR BUTTHOLE.
[laughter]
- ♪ HEY, I'’LL DO IT
ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ HEY, HEY
♪ I'’LL DO IT
ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ GET YOURSELF TOGETHER
♪ AND I'’LL GET MINE ♪
- ROGER?
- I'’M UP HERE, LITTLE BUDDY.
- WHAT'’S GOING ON?
- GOT TO FINISH PAINTING
THIS ROOM.
- I HAD TO GET
OUT OF THAT HOUSE.
- TOO MUCH ESTROGEN OVER THERE?
- HELL, YEAH.
- TOO MANY LEAKING NIPPLES?
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- I DON'’T KNOW IF JIONNI
WILL BE A BIG HELP,
BUT MY SUSPICION
IS HE'’LL BE A LITTLE HELP.
THAT'’S TEAMWORK, RIGHT THERE.
I AM HIS LADDER.
SO GIVE ME THE RUNDOWN
ON WHAT TO EXPECT.
- YOU JUST GOT TO, YOU KNOW,
STAY CALM, STAY POSITIVE.
EVEN THOUGH HER VAGINA'’S
NOT GONNA LOOK GOOD,
JUST SAY IT DOES.
STAY POSITIVE.
DON'’T LOOK AT HER VAGINA.
PLEASE, MAN,
DON'’T LOOK AT THE VAGINA.
JUST DON'’T--DON'’T DO IT.
- IT'’S LIKE LOOKING
AT THE SURFACE OF THE SUN?
- YEAH, PLEASE DON'’T.
DON'’T.
STAY BEHIND HER.
OH, MY GOD.
SHE'’S GONNA BE FARTING.
IT'’S GONNA STINK.
SHE'’S NOT GONNA KNOW.
I'’M NOT KIDDING.
SHE GOT THE--
- EPIDURAL?
- EPIDURAL.
YOU DON'’T FEEL ANYTHING
FROM YOUR VAGINA DOWN,
AND SHE WAS JUST BLOWING ASS
THE ENTIRE TIME.
- WHAT ABOUT THIS MIRACLE
OF LIFE I KEEP HEARING ABOUT
AND WHAT A BEAUTIFUL MOMENT
IT IS?
EVERYTHING
YOU'’VE DESCRIBED IS HORRIBLE.
- YOU'’LL GET THERE.
YOU'’LL GET THERE.
IT JUST--
RIGHT BEFORE MEILANI COMES OUT,
IT SMELLS LIKE ASS, OKAY?
IT--JENNI'’S GONNA BE YELLING.
YOU KNOW, JUST TELL HER
HOW BEAUTIFUL SHE LOOKS.
JUST STAY POSITIVE, BECAUSE
IF YOU FOLD AND SHE FOLDS?
- IT'’S BAD.
- YOU [bleep] ASS[bleep].
- WHAT?
- I LIKE THESE SHORTS.
- YOU KNOW THE DIAPER GAME?
- MM-HMM.
- WELL,
YOU LOOK INTO THE DIAPER.
YOU GOT TO EXAMINE IT, SMELL IT,
MAYBE TASTE IT TO SEE
WHAT KIND OF CANDY IT IS.
- THAT'’S REALLY DISGUSTING.
- DOESN'’T IT LOOK REAL?
- IT'’S DEFINITELY A TYPE
OF CANDY?
- YEAH, THEY'’RE ALL CANDY.
JUST TELL ME
WHAT YOU THINK IT IS.
- EW.
THAT'’S A PAYDAY.
- TOTAL BUTTERFINGER.
- OH, IT'’S A BABY RUTH.
- SNICKERS AND CARAMEL,
NOU--SOME NOUGAT.
- YEAH.
- WHAT'’S A NOUGAT?
- NOUGAT.
NOUGAT IS THIS GUY RIGHT HERE.
- EW.
WHAT'’S A NOUGAT?
- IT'’S PART OF THE CHOCOLATE.
- LIKE A NUGGET?
- BUT IT'’S NOUGAT.
- HOLD ON,
LET ME--LET ME MAKE SURE.
- EW.
- MM, THAT'’S NOUGAT.
[laughs]
- NASTY.
- [laughing]
- WE CAN MAKE A DIAPER.
READY. SET.
GO.
- OW!
- GOD.
[laughter]
- THIS LOOKS GREAT.
I'’M ALREADY WINNING,
I CAN TELL.
- WINNER!
- HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK.
- WHOA. THERE IT IS.
- STIMULATE YOUR NIPPLES
WHILE BOUNCING ON THE BALL.
IT'’S TO HELP YOU GIVE BIRTH.
- COME ON, NOW.
RUB THE NIPPLES.
- EW!
- JENNI IS GONNA BE HAPPY.
OH, THAT'’S NICE.
- YEAH, A LITTLE BALLERINA.
JIONNI AND I SHOULD OPEN
OUR OWN PAINTING COMPANY.
I MEAN, WE CRUSHED IT.
- I'’M PRETTY IMPRESSED.
WE DID GOOD.
- YEAH.
NOW COME SIT ON DADDY'’S LAP.
THANKS, BUDDY.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING.
- OF COURSE.
- THE SHOWER
WAS ABSOLUTELY PERFECT,
AND I WAS GENUINELY SURPRISED.
- I'’M DOUBLY HAPPY
I PULLED THIS OFF
BECAUSE I LITERALLY HAD A DAY.
I MEAN, IT WAS DEFINITELY A
LITTLE STRESSFUL, BUT IT WORKED.
- YEAH, I CAN'’T BELIEVE
ONE OF MY [bleep] FRIENDS
DIDN'’T TELL ME.
- I'’M SURPRISED
I DIDN'’T TELL YOU.
- YEAH.
YOU'’RE ONE OF THEM.
- OH, SOMETHING'’S LEAKING
OUT OF ME.
I SWEAR TO GOD.
- STOP.
- I SAID I HAD TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
I WASN'’T KIDDING.
- IS IT PEE,
OR DID YOUR WATER BREAK?
- IT LOOKED LIKE SNOT.
- THAT'’S YOUR MUCUS PLUG.
- I THINK IT IS.
- YOU'’RE GOING INTO LABOR.
- WHAT'’S COMING OUT OF ME?
- THIS EPISODE
OF SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- CONTINUES NOW.
- IT'’S JUST MUCUSY.
- SHOW ME. IT MIGHT BE
YOUR DAMN MUCUS PLUG.
- I'’M NOT SHOWING YOU
WHAT'’S COMING OUT OF ME!
- OH, MY GOD, WE'’RE BOTH GIRLS.
GET OVER IT.
IS SHE HAVING A BABY?
DID THE BABY FALL OUT?
WHAT'’S GOING ON?
- I'’M NOT SHOWING YOU
A BOOGER RAG.
THERE ARE SOME THINGS
FRIENDS SHOULD NOT SHARE,
AND ONE OF THEM IS
MY MUCUS PLUG.
YEAH.
NOW I GOT TO GET HOME
'’CAUSE I GOT TO CHANGE
MY UNDERWEAR.
BABE?
- I'’M IN HERE.
BE QUIET.
THE BABY'’S SLEEPING.
- [gasps] OH, MY GOD.
- THE BABY'’S SLEEPING.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BE QUIET.
♪ HUSH, LITTLE BABY,
DON'’T YOU CRY ♪
- OF COURSE,
ROGER'’S CRADLING JIONNI.
- THEY'’RE SO WEIRD.
- THEY REALLY ARE.
- THEY DID IT.
- WE DID IT.
HE'’S A BIG BABY.
- GOOD JOB, GUYS.
I THINK JENNI'’S PLUG
JUST FELL OUT.
SHE RAN TO THE BATHROOM.
SOMETHING LEAKED OUT.
- I WAS GETTING OUT THE DOOR.
WE WERE WALKING OUT, AND IT JUST
FELT LIKE A HOT, WARM FEELING.
- THAT'’S LIKE THE THIRD TIME
THAT'’S HAPPENED.
- PACK YOUR BAGS.
- SHE'’S GOING TO THE DOCTOR'’S
RIGHT NOW, THANK GOD.
- I'’M GOING
TO THE DOCTOR'’S REGARDLESS.
I'’M GONNA CHANGE, ANYWAYS.
- GOOD THING WE GOT THIS DONE.
- YEAH.
SO I WAS JUST STANDING
AT THE DOOR TODAY,
AND I JUST FELT, LIKE,
THIS WARM, GOOEY--
AND I RAN INTO THE BATHROOM.
BUT I FELT IT, LIKE,
TWO OTHER TIMES AROUND ROGER.
I WAS JUST LIKE,
"EW, WHAT IS THIS?"
- YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU BREAK YOUR WATER,
IT'’S JUST GONNA CONTINUE.
- DID MINE ALREADY?
- YOURS HAS NOT, NO.
- OKAY.
IT COULD MEAN
I COULD GO TOMORROW.
I COULD GO IN A MONTH.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
- ANY PROBLEMS, CALL ME.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I'’LL PUT THESE UP ON TOP,
OR ON BOTTOM?
- BABE?
- WHAT?
- DO YOU WANT TO CALL HER
AND SAY THE DOCTOR
BROKE MY WATER BY ACCIDENT?
SO I WANTED TO TELL NICOLE
ABOUT OUR DOCTOR'’S APPOINTMENT,
BUT I ALSO WANTED TO GET
HER BACK FOR PULLING A PRANK
ON US SAYING THAT HER WATER
BROKE WHEN IT DIDN'’T.
- NICOLE'’S WATER JUST BROKE!
WHAT DO WE DO?
ROGER, WHAT DO I DO?
- HELP!
- YOU'’RE THE WORST [bleep] LIARS
KNOWN IN THE HUMAN MANKIND.
- YOU SHOULD PLAY IT OFF LIKE,
NOT A SENSE OF EMERGENCY.
IT'’LL MAKE IT MORE BELIEVABLE.
- SO I'’M GONNA TELL HER
THAT MY WATER BROKE.
- BUT WE'’RE JUST GONNA
BE A LITTLE BIT
MORE BELIEVABLE ABOUT IT.
- ACADEMY AWARD STATUS.
[phone line trilling]
- YOLO.
HOW WAS THE DOCTORS?
- I'’M GONNA NEED YOUR HELP.
MY WATER DID BREAK.
- I TOLD YOU!
JIONNI, HER WATER BROKE!
OH, MY GOD, I'’M CRYING.
SHE'’S GONNA HAVE A BABY!
- [softly]
NOW I FEEL BAD.
- WHEN?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- CAN YOU STOP CRYING?
SHE'’S NOT EVEN CRYING.
- I'’M VERY EMOTIONAL RIGHT NOW.
- WE'’RE GETTING OUR BAGS
INTO THE CAR,
AND THEN WE'’RE GONNA HEAD
TO THE HOSPITAL.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
- NOTHING,
'’CAUSE I'’M AN ASS[bleep].
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- SHE'’S LYING.
- YOU'’RE LYING?
- OH, MY GOD.
- NOW I FEEL BAD
'’CAUSE YOU CRIED.
- I'’M CRYING.
I HAD MY UGLY CRY FACE ON
AND EVERYTHING.
- CAN I SEE IT?
- NO.
IT WAS LIKE--
[laughter]
- I HAD TO GET YOU BACK
FOR [bleep] DOING IT TO ME.
- YOU'’RE AN ASS[bleep].
I JUST RUINED MY MAKEUP.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
- '’CAUSE I LOVE YOU.
- WELL, I DON'’T LOVE YOU.
WHO DOES THAT?
YOU'’RE HONESTLY THE WORST FRIEND
I'’VE EVER HAD.
- YOU DID IT TO US!
ROGER TOLD ME
TO SAY IT THAT WAY TOO.
- TYPICAL.
- YEAH.
- THANKS FOR BEING A JERK
AND SAYING YOU WENT INTO LABOR
AND MADE ME CRY.
THAT'’S SO RUDE.
- JUST '’CAUSE
WE DID IT BETTER THAN YOU.
- BYE.
- BYE, NOW.
HIGH FIVE FOR ACTUALLY
MAKING IT BELIEVABLE.
- OH [bleep].
- NEXT TIME ON SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
YAY!
YOU SMELL LIKE BALLS.
[laughter]
- MY DAUGHTER'’S
COMING IN MINUTES.
MY DOCTOR'’S NOT HERE,
AND I AM JUST IN THE--
THE WORST PAIN
I'’VE EVER FELT IN MY LIFE.
- YOU'’RE DILATING VERY RAPIDLY.
- I'’M SCARED.
OH, MY GOD,
I THINK MY WATER JUST BROKE.