- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- AW.
- BYE, MEILANI.
- BYE.
IT WAS FREAKING AWESOME
TO BE PREGNANT
WITH MY BEST FRIEND.
NOW SHE'’S A MOM.
- I JUST WANT TO HELP HER NOW
WITH HER WEDDING
AND GIOVANNA.
I FEEL LIKE A NEW WOMAN.
I'’M OBSESSED WITH MY NEW HAIR.
I DEFINITELY NEEDED TO FIND
MY SEXY BACK.
- WE'’RE HOME.
- BACK IN THE BASEMENT.
WE'’RE ACTUALLY MOVING OUT,
AND WE'’RE NOT GONNA BE
LIVING IN THE BASEMENT ANYMORE.
IT'’S SAD.
LET'’S JUST STAY HERE.
- ARE YOU OUT
OF YOUR [bleep] MIND?
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- ♪ I SEE RIGHT
TO YOUR GUIDING LIGHT ♪
♪ EVEN DESPITE
YOU HIDING THE LIFE YOU... ♪
- YOUR HANDS ARE COLD.
- TODAY'’S INSPECTION.
- MY BELLY HURTS.
- LAST DAY IN THE BASEMENT.
- YOU SAY THAT EVERY MORNING.
- NICOLE AND I ARE WAITING
FOR OUR C.O. TO MOVE IN A HOUSE.
A CERTIFICATE OF OCCUPANCY
IS WHERE AN INSPECTION COMES
AND WE GET THE GREEN LIGHT
TO MOVE IN
AND EVERYTHING'’S SAFE
AND READY TO GO FOR US.
- OW.
- WHOA.
- THE BABY COULD BE HERE
IN A WEEK, TWO WEEKS.
SO I DEFINITELY JUST WANT TO GET
OUT OF THE BASEMENT
AND BE IN THE HOUSE
BEFORE I HAVE THIS NEW BABY
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
IT'’S GONNA BE VERY DIFFICULT TO
HAVE TWO KIDS IN THE BASEMENT.
RUB MY TUMMY.
- YOU'’RE ONE CENTIMETER DILATED?
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'’RE CROWNING?
- NO, WHEN YOU'’RE CROWNING,
THE BABY COMES OUT, I FEEL.
I'’M NINE MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND I'’M STARTING TO DILATE,
SO I'’M ONE CENTIMETER.
- WHEN YOU'’RE ONE CENTIMETER
DILATED,
IT MEANS THE BABY'’S COMING OUT
A CENTIMETER OF YOUR VAGINA?
- IT REALLY HURTS.
- WHERE DOES IT HURT?
- IT JUST HURTS.
IT JUST MEANS YOUR CERVIX
IS GETTING SOFTER
AND IT'’S GETTING BIGGER
FOR THE BABY TO COME OUT.
- IS YOUR CERVIX YOUR VAGINA?
- WHY--WHY DO YOU SAY "VERGINA"?
IT'’S "VAGINA."
- SHOULD I STOP RUBBING?
- NO.
THE CERVIX IS--
IT'’S IN YOUR VAGINA, YEAH,
BUT IT'’S NOT A VAGINA.
IT'’S A CERVIX.
IT'’S COMPLICATED DOWN THERE.
- YOUR VAGINA'’S DILATED.
YOU HAVE TO RELAX.
- MY CERVIX.
- [laughs]
HE'’S LIKE LITTLE JUMPING BEAN.
- HE LOVES THAT THING.
WAYS TO INDUCE LABOR NATURALLY.
APPLYING FINGER PRESSURE.
APPLY PRESSURE IN YOUR WEBBING.
IT HURTS.
I GOOGLED SOME TIPS
ON HOW TO INDUCE LABOR.
I JUST WANT TO GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD.
I CANNOT BE PREGNANT ANYMORE.
BANANAS, NIPPLE STIMULATION,
POLE DANCING.
- POLE DANCING?
- YEAH.
- WHERE YOU GONNA DO THAT?
DO YOU HAVE A POLE DOWNSTAIRS?
- YOU GOT A POLE SOMEWHERE.
- NO, I DON'’T.
YOU HAVE A BROOMSTICK.
- THAT'’S NOT POLE DANCING.
- JOE,
WHERE'’S THOSE HOT PEPPERS?
WE'’LL WAIT ANOTHER WEEK.
THEN WE CAN START PUSHING
AND WALKING AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
- I TOLD YOU THE HOT PEPPERS,
FRESH FROM THE GARDEN.
- I KNOW. I'’M SCARED.
- THEY BURN GOING IN.
THEY BURN COMING OUT.
- YUMMY, YUMMY.
- I'’M NOT GOOD WITH SPICE.
JANIS IS CUTTING ME UP THIS
GREEN PEPPER FROM THE GARDEN.
IT'’S CRAZY,
BECAUSE I HATE SPICY FOOD.
THAT JUST SHOWS THAT I REALLY
WANT MY BABY OUT.
- SEE?
OH, YEAH.
OOH.
GO AHEAD.
WHOO.
- NO.
- GO AHEAD, SMARTY.
- I'’M SCARED.
- FRESH FROM THE GARDEN.
- JANIS EATS IT,
AND SHE'’S CHOKING.
I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE I'’M GONNA
DIE EATING THIS PEPPER.
I'’M REALLY NERVOUS,
BUT I THINK IT MIGHT WORK.
[laughs]
- YOU GOT TO TOUCH IT.
OH, WAIT. NOW WAIT.
- THAT'’S HOT.
- OH, YOU DIDN'’T EVEN CHEW IT.
- I DID.
IT'’S BURNING MY TONGUE.
- OH, YOU'’RE SUCH A BABY.
IT DID NOT.
- [groans]
ALL RIGHT, CAN YOU DO
A COUNTDOWN?
- THREE, TWO, ONE, GO.
- OH, MY GOD.
OH. OH, MY GOD!
I'’M NOT KIDDING. OW!
[laughter]
- I HOPE YOUR TONGUE
DOESN'’T SWELL UP.
'’CAUSE THAT COULD HAPPEN.
- [burps]
- YOUR TONGUE COULD SWELL UP,
AND THEN YOU CAN'’T TALK.
- JUST CHEW ON--
- I CAN'’T BREATHE.
- JUST CHEW ON THE BREAD.
- YOU CAN BREATHE.
EAT A PIECE OF BREAD.
- ♪ TAKE ME BACK
TO THE SEPTEMBER RAIN ♪
♪ BEFORE YOU LOST
YOURSELF TO... ♪
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
LISTEN, I WAS GONNA
GIVE HELEN A CALL.
YOU KNOW THAT SPRINKLE
I WANTED TO DO?
I WANT TO GET THAT DONE.
I'’M GONNA ASK HER
IF IT'’S ALL RIGHT
IF WE HAVE SOMETHING HERE,
REALLY SMALL.
AND WE'’LL JUST HAVE, LIKE,
A LITTLE SPRINKLE.
- A SPRINKLE PARTY
IS A PARTY
FOR YOUR SECOND BABY,
I GUESS.
IS IT A SURPRISE?
- YES.
- NICOLE DOESN'’T LOVE SURPRISES,
BUT SHE'’S GONNA GET ONE.
- MAYBE JUST JENNI, HELEN,
MARY, AND STEPH?
- OKAY.
- PUT IT ON SPEAKER.
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
GO LIKE THAT.
THEN YOU GO LIKE THAT.
[line rings]
OKAY.
- YOU'’RE SILLY.
[cell phone ringing]
POOPING?
JANIS IS CALLING.
HEY, JANIS.
- HI, JENNI, HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
WELL, THE REASON
I WAS CALLING IS,
I WANT TO HAVE A LITTLE
SPRINKLE SHOWER FOR NICOLE.
- OH.
- I WAS THINKING
OF NEXT SATURDAY,
MAYBE, LIKE, 1:00,
JUST, LIKE, A LUNCH.
HOPEFULLY I'’LL GET HER
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
- OKAY, GREAT. I CAN'’T WAIT.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, TELL ROGER I SAID HI.
KISS THE BABY FOR ME.
- I WILL.
- ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
- YAY.
NICOLE'’S AN ONLY CHILD,
SO I KNOW THE ONLY THING
THAT CAN MAKE AN ONLY CHILD
HAPPY IS GIFTS.
SO I'’M GONNA GO SHOPPING
FOR ANYTHING CUTE AND PINK.
SOME THINGS IN LIFE ARE EASIER.
I DON'’T THINK
I'’D HAVE IT ANY OTHER WAY.
YOU'’RE TOO DAMN CUTE.
ME AND YOU HAVE MATCHING SHOES.
- ♪ OOH-OOH, I GET THIS FEELING
IN MY HEART SOME DAYS ♪
♪ WHOA-OH-OH-OH-OH
- ALMOST THERE, BUTTERCUP.
OKAY.
[groans]
OOH, THIS PLACE LOOKS SNAZZY.
LOOK HOW PRETTY.
I CAN'’T TAKE IT.
CAN I LEAVE MY STROLLER
RIGHT HERE?
I AM JUST DYING OVER THIS.
THIS IS FANCY.
IS THIS JUST PAJAMAS?
I'’VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING SO NICE.
NOW I KNOW WHY.
THAT IS NOT CHEAP.
I'’M AFRAID TO TOUCH THIS STUFF,
HONEYBUN.
THIS STORE IS VERY HIGH-END.
YEAH, ALL BOURGIE.
BUT I WILL BUY ONE NICE THING
FOR GIOVANNA.
I WILL.
[mumbling]
MY GOD.
MAN, THIS IS GONNA HURT.
I'’D RATHER GET HER THIS.
NINE MONTHS.
- WOULD YOU LIKE IT WRAPPED?
- YES, PLEASE.
- SURE.
[baby crying]
YOU'’RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE PERFECT BABY.
WHAT'’S GOING ON?
WHAT'’S WRONG?
WHAT'’S WRONG, STINKBUTT?
OOH, YOU TOOTING?
YOU TOOTING?
DO YOU HAVE A GARBAGE,
BY ANY CHANCE,
I COULD THROW OUT A DIAPER?
I KNOW WHAT'’S GOING ON.
I KNOW--OOP!
I KNOW WHY YOU'’RE FUSSING.
MEILANI HAS NEVER ACTED OUT,
EVER.
BUT MEILANI'’S TOTALLY
BEING A BRAT RIGHT NOW.
SHE'’S ACTING LIKE A REAL BABY,
AND I FEEL LIKE
SHE'’S JUST JEALOUS
THAT I'’M SHOPPING FOR GIOVANNA.
I'’LL BE RIGHT BACK
IN ABOUT FIVE MINUTES.
- OKAY.
- I GOT A CRYING BABY.
I NEED XANAX.
THIS BENCH ACTUALLY MIGHT BREAK,
BUT IT'’S ALL RIGHT
AS LONG AS YOU'’RE OKAY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- CALLING JOE.
- CROSS YOUR FINGERS.
[line rings]
- WHAT'’S GOING ON?
- TALK TO ME.
- THE FIRE INSPECTION IS GOOD.
ALL THE INSPECTIONS ARE GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT. WE'’RE COMING IN.
WE'’RE MOVING IN TONIGHT, RIGHT?
WE'’RE SLEEPING THERE?
- NO, NOT YET.
NOT TILL WE GET THE C.O.
- COME ON.
- HOW LONG'’S THAT TAKE?
- TWO WEEKS AWAY MAX,
YOU GUYS WILL BE IN.
- IS THERE ANY WAY
IT COULD BE SOONER, LONGER?
- IT'’S OUT OF OUR HANDS NOW.
- WHAT IF I WROTE A LETTER
TO THE STATE
SAYING MY FIANCEE'’S
ONE CENTIMETER DILATED?
- ANYTHING THAT CAN HELP,
I'’M ALL FOR IT.
- LET'’S CALL THEM.
- ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- I'’LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
- BYE.
WE PASSED INSPECTION.
EVERYTHING'’S LIVABLE.
EVERYTHING'’S OKAY.
NOW WE HAVE TO WAIT FOR
THE CERTIFICATE OF OCCUPANCY,
THIS C.O. THING.
TWO MORE WEEKS.
- WE'’RE GONNA HAVE THE BABY
HERE.
- TWO MORE FRICKING WEEKS.
- I'’M GONNA HAVE
TO STERILIZE STUFF.
- I CAN'’T LIVE LIKE--
I CAN'’T DO THIS.
- CALL YOUR MOM.
WE GOT TO TELL HER
ANOTHER TWO WEEKS.
SHE'’S GONNA FREAK OUT.
- MA!
- WHAT IF IT'’S JUST
NOT MEANT TO BE...
- MA!
- AND WE'’RE GONNA
LIVE HERE FOREVER?
- WHAT?
- WE JUST TALKED TO JOE,
AND HE SAID ANOTHER TWO WEEKS.
- NO, HE DID NOT.
- YEAH.
- YES, HE DID.
- FOR--FOR THE PAPERS.
- YOU HAVE EVERYTHING ROLLED UP
AND PACKED AND EVERYTHING.
DID HE REALLY SAY THAT?
- YEAH.
- HE SAID TWO WEEKS.
TWO WEEKS FOR THE PAPERS.
- I CAN'’T BELIEVE
YOU'’RE STILL GONNA BE HERE.
- YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT.
- YOU'’RE GONNA STAY
IN THE BASEMENT.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
TWO MORE WEEKS.
- ♪ IT'’S EASY ♪
♪ IT'’S SO EASY ♪
- WHAT?
- WHY IS IT SO SMALL?
- IT'’S SUPPOSED TO BE BIGGER?
- CAN YOUR ASS FIT ON THAT?
SO I WAS REALLY EXCITED FOR THIS
COUCH THAT I ORDERED ONLINE,
AND IT LOOKED
LIKE A FRICKING DOG COUCH.
THE LITTLE PEG LEGS.
- OH, MY GOD, NICOLE.
- WHAT IS THIS COUCH FOR?
- OH, MY GOD.
- I'’M DROOLING.
WHO IS THIS FOR?
IS THIS FOR CHILDREN?
- NICOLE, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- SOMETIMES WHEN I ORDER THINGS,
I DON'’T REALLY LOOK
AT THE SIZES.
- IT'’S LESS THAN A FOOT
OFF THE GROUND.
- JUST PUT THE LEG--OH, MY GOD.
- LORENZO COULD LITERALLY
JUST STEP ON THIS.
- COULD WE PUT IT
IN YOUR MAN CAVE?
- ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
- I GOT TO SHOW YOU THE PICTURE.
IT WAS, LIKE, IN A LIVING ROOM.
IT LOOKED SO CLASSY.
- OH, MY GOD.
- DOESN'’T THAT LOOK SO GRAND?
- "THE COUCH IN THE PICTURE
IS WAY SMALLER
THAN YOU MIGHT THINK IT IS."
- WHO SAID THAT?
- SOME GUY.
"VERY NICE BUT VERY SMALL.
IT'’S BARELY BIG ENOUGH
FOR A CHILD."
OH, MY GOD.
DO YOU READ THE REVIEWS?
- I THINK I PURCHASED THIS AT,
LIKE, 2:00 IN THE MORNING.
- "SMALLER THAN I THOUGHT.
VERY DISAPPOINTED."
- SO EVERYBODY'’S REACTION
IS THE SAME.
- "WHEN MY HUSBAND
FINISHED PUTTING THIS TOGETHER,
"WE WERE BOTH VERY--
EXTREMELY SURPRISED
IN THE SIZE."
- I'’M GONNA GIVE IT
TO NOEL AND BELLA.
- THE DOGS?
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU, MAN?
SO FAR, YOUR MIRRORS ARE TOO BIG
AND YOUR COUCHES ARE TOO SMALL.
- [laughing]
STOP. IT HURTS.
I'’M REALLY UPSET
THAT THIS ISN'’T A BIG COUCH,
BECAUSE I LOVED THE STYLE OF IT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL.
AND HONESTLY,
IF IT WAS, LIKE, ADULT SIZE,
IT WOULD BE
A NICE-LOOKING LOVE SEAT.
COME HERE.
- I'’M NOT SITTING
ON THAT WITH YOU.
- BABE, SIT ON IT.
- NO.
- BABE. COME ON.
IT'’S A LOVE SEAT.
[laughing]
IT'’S PERFECT.
- YEAH, FOR A DOG.
- ♪ ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR
♪ OH, OH-OH, OH-OH
- TODAY IS NICOLE'’S
SPRINKLE SHOWER.
I HAVE TO MAKE IT UP TO JANIS'’
TO SURPRISE NICOLE,
TO GET NICOLE OUT OF THE HOUSE
SO JANIS CAN SET UP THE HOUSE
FOR NICOLE'’S SPRINKLE.
[knocking]
- HI.
OH, MY GOD, YOU LOOK SO GREAT.
- GOOD MORNING.
- HEY, SQUIRREL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I WANTED TO SURPRISE YOU
'’CAUSE YOU HAVEN'’T
BEEN FEELING WELL.
OH, MY GOSH.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- I MISSED YOU.
WE'’RE GOING TO THE HOUSE.
- CAN I COME?
- YES.
- YEAH?
- YOUR BOOBS GOT BIGGER.
I'’M FEELING LIKE [bleep] TODAY.
I MEAN,
I'’M NINE MONTHS PREGNANT.
IF I HAD A CHOICE,
I WOULD LAY IN BED ALL DAY
AND I WOULD EAT ICE CREAM
AND I WOULDN'’T DO [bleep].
I JUST--
I'’M NOT FEELING IT TODAY.
- COME ON, LORENZO.
NANA'’S GOT SO MUCH WORK TO DO.
THEY FINALLY LEFT. COME ON.
- SO EXCITED TO SEE
WHAT NICOLE AND JIONNI
HAVE DONE WITH THE PLACE.
I'’VE NEVER BEEN HERE, SO I JUST
WANT TO TAKE IT ALL IN.
WHOO-HOO.
- WELCOME.
- I LOVE IT.
- THERE'’S SO MUCH [bleep] TO DO.
I FEEL LIKE THIS HOUSE,
THIS STYLE DEFINITELY FITS
WHO I AM NOW AS A MOM.
BUT, LIKE, THINKING OF ME,
LIKE, FOUR YEARS AGO?
- CAN YOU IMAGINE THE HOUSE
YOU WOULD HAVE BUILT?
- IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
A LEOPARD PALACE.
I DEFINITELY THINK I STILL
HAVE LEOPARD PRINT IN ME,
BUT I'’M GONNA SAVE THAT
FOR MY LITTLE GIRL.
I MEAN, YOU NEVER FULLY
GET RID OF THE LEOPARD.
- NO, YOU JUST PASS IT ON.
- YOU JUST DIAL IT DOWN
A LITTLE BIT.
- YOU PASS IT ON TO YOUR KIDS.
- YUP. MM-HMM.
- WANT TO HELP NANA?
- NO.
- YEAH, COME ON.
I'’LL SHOW YOU THE DECORATIONS.
COME ON.
DON'’T. ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT TOOK ME
TO PUT THIS STUPID THING
TOGETHER?
LET GO. LET GO.
- JIONNI?
- YO.
- ARE THESE GOLDFISH OKAY?
- YEAH.
- DID YOUR BACK HURT?
LIKE, RIGHT
WHERE MY BUTT CRACK STARTS.
- I HAD, LIKE, A NERVE PAIN.
I DID ALL CRAZY [bleep]
TO GET HER OUT.
DID YOU TRY THE BOUNCING BALL
YET, A BIRTHING BALL?
- YEAH, THAT [bleep]
DOESN'’T WORK.
- I KNOW. DID YOU TRY--
- I TRIED SPICY FOOD.
MY FARTS STUNG AFTER.
THAT'’S THE ONLY THING IT DID.
- DID YOU TRY
RUBBING YOUR NIPPLES?
- I'’M LIKE,
"WHY AM I DOING THIS?"
NO, I WAS LIKE THIS.
[laughter]
NOTHING HAPPENED.
I DID IT FOR, LIKE, TEN MINUTES.
I'’M GONNA TRY
AND HAVE SEX TONIGHT.
- YOU SHOULD.
- WE DID THE OTHER DAY,
BUT NOTHING HAPPENED.
I READ ONLINE THAT IF YOU GO
UP IN THERE AND TRY
AND TOUCH THE BABY'’S HEAD OR,
YOU KNOW, JUST GO DEEP UP THERE,
YOU COULD ACTUALLY START
SOMETHING, SO I TRIED--
- I WAS WORRIED ABOUT MY NAILS.
- I TRIED TO GET UP THERE,
BUT MY FINGER'’S TOO SHORT.
- YOU DO HAVE A TINY--
- IT'’S A LITTLE SAUSAGE FINGER.
IT DIDN'’T EVEN MAKE IT UP THERE.
THEN I FELT LIKE I WAS,
LIKE, BEING A PERVERT.
- PUT YOUR FINGER NEXT TO MINE.
- I AM HAVING SEX.
- GIRL.
LIKE, TWICE.
DISGUSTING.
- YOU GOT IT GOOD RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN HAVE
SAFE SEXUAL INTERCOURSE.
- I WAS, LIKE,
RUBBING MY MAKEUP OFF
FROM A LONG-ASS DAY,
AND HE COMES IN THERE.
- LITERALLY.
- HE WASN'’T TAKING NO
FOR AN ANSWER.
IN THE BATHROOM, OF ALL PLACES.
IT'’S PROBABLY THE ONLY TIME
IN MY LIFE I ACTUALLY SCREAMED.
- ARE YOU ON BIRTH CONTROL?
- NO.
- AND YOU'’RE HAVING SEX?
- KIND OF.
- YOU'’RE GONNA GET PREGNANT.
- NO.
- NO?
- I WOULD KILL HIM.
- YOU'’RE VERY FERTILE
AFTER YOU GIVE BIRTH.
- TELL ROGER THAT.
- YOU'’RE NOT ON BIRTH CONTROL,
AND YOU'’RE NOT USING CONDOMS,
SO HI.
THAT'’S HOW YOU GET PREGNANT.
- TRY TO TELL HIM.
- SO WHY'’D YOU COME
AND SEE ME TODAY?
- '’CAUSE I LOVE YOU,
AND I JUST WANTED TO SAY HI.
- ARE [bleep] PREGNANT?
- YES,
THAT'’S WHY I SURPRISED YOU.
HI, YOU'’RE GONNA BE A GODMOMMY
AGAIN.
- NO, ARE YOU KIDDING?
- I MEAN, I'’M NOT SURE
BECAUSE I HAVEN'’T HAD MY PERIOD,
BUT...
- YOU'’RE PREGNANT.
- I AM NOT [bleep] PREGNANT.
- YOU ARE.
- I WOULD BE CRYING RIGHT NOW.
- JENNI'’S GONNA GET PREGNANT
AGAIN.
- NO, I AM NOT GONNA
GET PREGNANT.
- SHE'’S NOT ON BIRTH CONTROL
AND THEY'’RE DOING IT.
- I WILL NOT BE PREGNANT AGAIN,
'’CAUSE I WOULD JUMP
OFF THE [bleep] BROOKLYN BRIDGE.
- WHY BROOKLYN?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
IT SEEMS HIGH.
- SO MY MOM JUST CALLED.
THEY'’RE READY FOR LUNCH,
IF YOU WANT.
- YEAH, I CAN EAT AGAIN.
- I THINK SHE MADE BEET SALAD.
- ANYTHING JANIS MAKES
IS AMAZING.
- COME ON, LET'’S GO.
- LET'’S GO.
- SHE'’S HERE. SHE'’S HERE.
SHE'’S JUST PULLING IN.
- [groans]
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'’M NOT FEELING SO GOOD.
- SHH, SHH, SHH.
- MY TUMMY HURTS.
- WHAT IS SHE DOING?
- SHH.
all: SURPRISE!
- OH, MY GOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT IS THIS?
- YOUR SPRINKLE.
- OH, I GOT TO [bleep].
[laughter]
- THANKS, GUYS.
HI, NANNY.
I SEE LITERALLY,
LIKE, 20 PEOPLE.
I SEE STEPH. I SEE MY MOM.
I SEE MY SISTER-IN-LAWS.
I SEE EVERYBODY, BALLOONS,
A CANDY BAR.
IT TOOK ME A MINUTE
TO COMPREHEND WHAT WAS GOING ON,
AND I'’M PISSED THAT I DIDN'’T
GO INTO LABOR BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, THEY SCARED ME.
BUT, I MEAN, OVERALL,
I'’M JUST REALLY, REALLY HAPPY
THAT, YOU KNOW,
THEY DECIDED TO THROW ME
A LITTLE SPRINKLE PARTY.
- I TOOK A HALF A DAY YESTERDAY
TO DO EVERYTHING,
AND THEN YOU END UP
STAYING HOME ALL DAY.
- I HAVE NO IDEA HOW I DIDN'’T
KNOW ANY OF THIS WAS GOING ON.
I JUST FEEL LIKE I'’VE BEEN
SO WRAPPED UP IN BEING PREGNANT
AND BEING MISERABLE THAT
I PROBABLY MISSED ALL THE SIGNS
THAT EVERYBODY
WAS THROWING AT ME.
I'’M JUST SO GRATEFUL
TO HAVE THEM IN MY LIFE,
AND NOW IT'’S TIME
TO OPEN PRESENTS,
AND, I MEAN,
WHO DOESN'’T LOVE PRESENTS?
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
DID YOU MAKE THIS?
YOU MADE THIS?
- YOU MADE THAT?
- OH, MY GOD, I LOVE IT.
- IT'’S PRETTY.
- I'’M GETTING SUCH CUTE GIFTS
RIGHT NOW,
AND I'’M JUST NOT USED TO SEEING,
LIKE, ALL THIS PINK
AND LEOPARD AND BOWS
THAT, YOU KNOW,
IT'’S, LIKE, HITTING ME
THAT I'’M GONNA HAVE
A LITTLE GIRL
AND I CAN DRESS HER UP
IN GIRLY THINGS.
OH, MY GOD.
- SHE'’LL BE A LITTLE OLDER
IN IT.
- OH, HOW PRETTY IS THAT?
- THAT'’S GORGEOUS.
- YOU LIKE IT?
- THANK YOU.
- SO PRETTY, SO SOFT.
- YEAH.
- IT'’S BEAUTIFUL.
- I FELL IN LOVE WITH IT.
LORENZO LOOKS LIKE MOMMY NOW.
- CAN I SEE?
- LORENZO LOOKS LIKE MOM.
- THIS SPRINKLE IS DEFINITELY
TAKING MY MIND
OFF OF EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW,
WITH THE HOUSE AND THE WEDDING,
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE RIGHT NOW,
I'’M JUST IN ANOTHER PLACE,
A HAPPY PLACE,
AND I'’M NOT STRESSED OUT
RIGHT NOW.
- AFTER THIS WEEK,
YOU CAN HAVE IT NOW.
- OH, OKAY.
I'’M GOOD NOW.
- WE WERE JUST HOLDING--WE
WERE JUST HOLDING OUT FOR TODAY.
WE DON'’T CARE WHAT YOU DO NOW.
- I TRIED THE SWINGS.
- SHE TRIED GALLOPING.
- GALLOPING.
- CAN YOU SHOW ME THIS?
- I'’VE BEEN DOING EVERYTHING TO
TRY AND GET MYSELF INTO LABOR.
I MEAN, SOMETHING
HAS GOT TO WORK,
AND NOTHING HAS HAPPENED.
- THIS IS HOW WE DO IT.
- AND THEN THERE'’S ANOTHER ONE.
YOU GET ON ALL FOURS,
AND THEN YOU...
THAT DOESN'’T WORK.
- I THINK ALL THAT HELPS
WHEN YOU'’RE ACTUALLY IN LABOR,
TO, LIKE, PUSH THE LABOR ALONG.
- YEAH, WELL...
- LIKE, GALLOP IN THE HOSPITAL.
- THAT [bleep] DOESN'’T WORK.
- NOTHING WORKS.
EAT ALL THE [bleep]
PINEAPPLE IN THE WORLD,
RUB YOUR NIPPLES ALL DAY
IF YOU WANT,
IT AIN'’T GONNA
STIMULATE [bleep].
- NOPE.
- YOU'’RE GONNA HAVE SOME
NICE BOOBS FOR YOUR WEDDING.
- BIG BOOBS.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT YOUR BOOBS?
- WELL, I WANT IT TIGHTER,
LIKE, ALL AROUND.
- ARE YOU GETTING YOUR BOOBS
DONE BEFORE THE WEDDING?
- I WAS THINKING THAT.
- YOUR BOOBS ARE ALREADY SO HUGE
TO BEGIN WITH.
- WHEN I WAS BREAST-FEEDING--
- YOU'’RE GONNA BE
WALKING AROUND,
AND YOUR BOOBS WILL ENTER
THE ROOM BEFORE YOU DO.
- [bleep] YES.
I WANT THEM THE WAY THEY LOOKED
WHEN I WAS BREAST-FEEDING.
- OH.
- DID YOU EVER--
WHEN THEY, LIKE, GET REALLY--
- YES.
- I WAS LIKE, "COME ON."
I TOOK A PICTURE,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"I WANT THAT, PLEASE."
- IT'’S PROBABLY LIKE THIS.
[laughter]
- I AM SO HAPPY
THAT THE DAY WENT FLAWLESS,
AND IT WAS PERFECT, AND I LOVE
YOUR FAMILY AND FRIENDS.
- I'’M REALLY HAPPY
THAT YOU CAME UP.
- YEAH. OF COURSE.
ANYTHING FOR YOU.
- '’CAUSE IF IT WERE MY CHOICE,
I PROBABLY WOULDN'’T SEE YOU
UNTIL AFTER I GAVE BIRTH.
I'’M SUCH A MISERABLE BITCH
RIGHT NOW THAT I'’M, LIKE--
- YOU HAD A GOOD TIME
THOUGH, NO?
- YEAH.
NO, I DID.
I JUST WANT THIS BABY OUT.
THAT'’S ALL I'’M THINKING ABOUT.
- WERE YOU REALLY SURPRISED?
- YES.
- YEAH?
- I HAD NO IDEA.
- DID YOU WANT, LIKE,
A LITTLE SHOWER?
- A LITTLE SPRINKLE? YEAH.
- SPRINKLE.
- WAS IT YOUR IDEA?
- YUP.
- NO.
YOUR MOM SAID IT WAS HER IDEA.
I HEARD IT WAS JANELLE'’S IDEA.
- WELL, IT WAS EVERYBODY.
YOUR MOM TALKED ABOUT IT,
JANELLE.
- BOOP!
- EVEN THOUGH NICOLE
WASN'’T FEELING WELL
AND, YOU KNOW,
SHE'’S BEEN IN PAIN,
I THINK
IT REALLY HELPED, YOU KNOW,
SEEING HER FRIENDS, HER FAMILY,
AND, YOU KNOW,
SHE NEEDED SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
- YOU HAVE FUN AT THE PARTY
TODAY?
I WALKED IN.
HE WENT, "SURPRISE."
- LORENZO SAID, "SURPRISE."
- LORENZO, WHAT'’D YOU DO
WHEN I WALKED IN THE HOUSE?
- '’PRISE!
- YOU SAID, "SURPRISE"?
- YOU'’RE SO CUTE.
YOU SAID, "SURPRISE, MAMA,"
RIGHT?
WHAT'’D YOU SAY?
- '’PRISE.
- YOU'’RE A GOOD KID, LORENZO.
- YOU'’RE GOOD.
SMART TOO.
I LOVE YOU.
- YOUR DAD TAUGHT YOU WELL.
- '’PRISE.
- ♪ IS THIS LOVE
I'’VE FOUND AGAIN ♪
♪ OR IS THIS LOVE
FOR THE FIRST TIME ♪
- NICOLE, DO YOU HAVE
GOOD HAIR SPRAY?
- YEAH,
ALL THREE OF THOSE ARE GOOD.
- NONE OF THEM ARE HARD.
- THE PINK.
THAT'’S WHAT SHE SAID.
- THAT'’S WHAT SHE SAID.
- TONIGHT WE ARE GOING OUT
TO DINNER WITH JENNI AND ROGER
BECAUSE WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE WANT TO PUT
ON OUR MENU FOR THE WEDDING.
SO IT'’S A LITTLE WEDDING
TASTING DINNER.
WHAT IF I EAT A LOT AND THEN
I GIVE--I GO INTO LABOR?
I'’M GONNA POOP EVERYWHERE.
[laughs]
YOU BETTER BE CAREFUL
IN THOSE HEELS HOLDING HER.
- I KNOW, BUT SHE HAS TO BURP.
- YOU HAVE SIX-INCH HEELS ON.
- NICOLE AND I DEFINITELY
HAVEN'’T SPENT ENOUGH TIME
ON THE WEDDING AND WHAT WE
WANT TO EAT AND THE MENU.
SO THIS IS DEFINITELY A GOOD
IDEA FOR US TO GO OUT TONIGHT
AND TRY DIFFERENT VARIETIES
OF FOOD
AND JUST GET, YOU KNOW,
A GENERAL IDEA,
AND IT'’S REALLY GOOD HAVING
JENNI AND ROGER WITH US TO,
YOU KNOW, GIVE US THEIR OPINION.
- WHY IS THERE
SO MUCH SILVERWARE?
WHAT ARE THESE FOR, LORENZO?
THERE'’S LITTLE SILVERWARES,
AND THEN THERE'’S, LIKE,
THREE FORKS,
THREE SPOONS, THREE KNIVES,
A MILLION GLASSES WITH
WINE GLASSES AND REGULAR CUPS.
IT'’S CONFUSING.
- THIS IS A CHARDONNAY.
- I COULD SMELL THEM.
- I FORGOT WHICH ONE'’S WHAT.
- THAT'’S A CHARDONNAY, YOU SAID?
- THIS IS A ROSE.
- OH, A ROSE.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
LIKE, TAKE SHOTS?
- I JUST TOOK A SIP
OF EVERYTHING.
- OOP, ALREADY DRUNK.
- ARE YOU--
- ONE OF THE MUST BE A MERLOT.
- ARE YOU A BIG WINE DRINKER?
- NOT AT ALL.
- THAT SMELLS GOOD.
A LITTLE--A LITTLE SWEET.
- YOU TAKING NOTES?
- OKAY, THIS IS THE CHARDONNAY.
I DON'’T KNOW
HOW TO SPELL "CHARDONNAY."
- I MEAN,
NONE OF US AT THE TABLE
ARE AWESOME SPELLING BEE
STUDENTS,
BUT I MEAN,
AS LONG AS IT TASTES GOOD,
WHO CARES HOW IT'’S SPELLED?
- THE BURRATA MOZZARELLE.
IT'’S A BURRATA STUFFED
WITH A CREAMY CENTER,
WRAPPED IN PROSCIUTTO DI PARMA
AND HOMEMADE ROASTED PEPPERS.
THIS IS OUR SPRING SALAD.
IT'’S A MIXED BABY GREEN
SERVED WITH CANDIED PECANS,
GOAT CHEESE, TOMATO, ONION,
AND GOLDEN RAISINS.
- OH, MY GOD.
- EVERYBODY WRITE DOWN...
- WHAT YOU LIKE?
- WHICH OUT--WHICH OUTFITS.
WHICH FOODS YOU LOVE THE BEST.
I LOVE THIS MOZZARELLE THING.
- THAT MOZZARELLA BALL?
BUT THIS ONE'’S REALLY GOOD,
WITH THE PECANS.
- YEAH.
- THAT WAS PROSCIUTTE
AND MOZZARELLE, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- WRITE THAT DOWN, BABE.
- HOW THE HELL
DO YOU SPELL "PROSCIUTTE"?
- HOW DO YOU SPELL "PROSCIUTTE"?
- P-R-U--
- "PRUH-ZHOOT."
- ANY SELF-RESPECTING ITALIAN
WOULD KNOW HOW TO SPELL
"PROSCIUTTE."
I'’M NOT ITALIAN.
HOW DO YOU SPELL IT?
- B-R--
- U.
- S.
- I GOT THAT FAR.
- J.
- I THINK IT'’S A S, ACTUALLY.
I DON'’T THINK IT'’S--
- IS IT "BROSCUITTE"
OR "PROSCIUTTO"?
- IT'’S B.
B-R-U-S-J.
- NO.
IT'’S PRONOUNCED
WITH, LIKE, A B,
LIKE, "BROSCIUTTE."
- YEAH, I ALWAYS THOUGHT
IT WAS PRONOUNCED "BROSCIUTTE."
- BUT IT LOOKS
LIKE "PRAH-SCOOT-OH"
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
B-R-U-S-H-E-T-T-I.
- THAT'’S IT?
- "BRUSCHETTA."
- "BRUSCHUTE."
- IT'’S "BRUSCHETTA."
IT'’S NOT "BRUSCHUTE" RIGHT?
- I DON'’T HAVE A CLUE.
I DON'’T CARE HOW TO SPELL,
BECAUSE I JUST LIKE EATING IT.
I CAN SAY IT.
- WE HAVE OUR CAJUN CALAMARI.
IT'’S A SPICY BALSAMIC.
- OH, WOW, HERE WE GO.
- CAN YOU TELL ME
HOW SPICY IT IS?
- OH, MY GOD,
THE SHRIMP'’S SPICY.
MM!
[laughter]
- HOT?
- IT'’S TOO HOT FOR ME.
- THAT WAS PRETTY AWESOME.
- [coughs]
[laughter]
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- THAT BAD?
IT'’S A SPICY MEATBALL-A.
THAT'’S AMORE.
- OH, GOD.
WHO AM I WITH?
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WE HAVE SOME PASTA FOR YOU.
- OH.
- THREE DIFFERENT KINDS.
- I CAN'’T EAT ANY MORE.
REALLY GOOD.
- YEAH, LINGUINE, I LOVE.
- IS THIS SPICY?
I'’M SO FULL.
- UH-OH, HERE COMES THE DESSERT.
- OH, I CAN'’T. DESSERT? OH.
- A LITTLE PALATE CLEANSER.
- OH, PALATE CLEANSER?
THAT MEANS THERE'’S MORE TO COME.
- WAIT.
WHAT'’S A PALATE CLEANSER?
- IT MAKES YOU GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
- IT MAKES YOU GO POOPS?
[laughter]
I THINK YOU USE
THE LITTLE SPOON.
- YEAH.
- THAT'’S OUR CHILEAN SEA BASS.
IT'’S OVER A SAUTEED SPINACH
TOPPED WITH A SWEET
MASHED POTATO CRUST.
- CHILEAN SEA BASS?
I'’M CHILEAN.
- IF YOU DON'’T HAVE A FISH
PICKED,
THIS IS, LIKE, MY FAVORITE ONE.
IT DOESN'’T EVEN TASTE LIKE FISH.
- THAT'’S WHAT SHE SAID.
- IT MELTS IN YOUR MOUTH.
- I DON'’T LIKE FISH.
- IT DOESN'’T TASTE LIKE FISH.
- IS IT GOOD?
- IT TASTES LIKE FISH.
YOU SAID
IT DIDN'’T TASTE LIKE FISH,
AND I'’M EATING IT;
IT TASTES LIKE FISH.
- IT DOESN'’T HAVE
A GAMY FISH TASTE.
- I DON'’T LIKE FISH.
- AND IT'’S FROM CHILE.
- OKAY.
DOESN'’T MEAN I HAVE TO EAT IT.
NO.
- I DON'’T ACTUALLY KNOW
IF IT'’S FROM CHILE.
- BUT IT'’S CHILEAN SEA BASS.
THAT'’S GOT TO BE FROM CHILE.
WELL, FRENCH FRIES
ARE FROM FRANCE.
- ARE THEY?
- I THINK.
- I'’M GONNA THROW UP.
- I'’M READY FOR BED.
- I'’M DEFINITELY IN A FOOD COMA
RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'’T BREATHE,
AND JUST TRYING A LITTLE BIT
OF EVERYTHING KILLED ME.
- I'’M STUFFED.
- AND SOMEONE'’S GONNA HAVE
TO ROLL ME OUT OF HERE.
- ENJOY EVERYTHING, GUYS?
- EVERYTHING WAS AMAZING.
- VEAL WAS MY FAVORITE.
HE LIKED THE SEA BASS.
- AH, THE CHILEAN SEA BASS
WAS TO DIE FOR.
- YOU GONNA USE ANYTHING
FOR THE WEDDING?
- WE MADE A LIST.
- YOU GOT A LIST?
- SO WE'’RE GOOD.
- I'’M GLAD I COULD HELP, AND
I HOPE YOU HAVE THE BABY SOON.
- TONIGHT WE'’RE GONNA DO IT.
- POOR THING.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
- THANK YOU.
- I CAN'’T MOVE.
DO THEY HAVE A WHEELCHAIR?
- GOING TO MARRA'’S WAS
DEFINITELY A SUCCESS TONIGHT.
WE GOT GREAT IDEAS.
WE TASTED DIFFERENT VARIETIES
OF SALADS, FISHES, MEATS,
AND, YOU KNOW,
IT WAS A SUCCESS TONIGHT.
- OH, MY GOD.
[farts]
- I HEARD THAT.
- HEARD WHAT?
- YOU FARTED.
[laughs]
- ♪ '’CAUSE I'’M READY ♪
♪ OH, I'’M READY ♪
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- UGH, I GOT TO PUMP.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I'’M GETTING REALLY BAD
CONTRACTIONS.
I DEFINITELY WANT TO DO THINGS
TO HELP THE PROCESS
AND MOVE IT ALONG.
SO I'’M GRABBING MY BREAST PUMP,
AND I'’M GONNA GO IN THE BATHROOM
AND JUST START PUMPING,
BECAUSE ONCE YOU PUMP, THEN,
YOU KNOW, YOUR UTERUS CONTRACTS,
AND I FEEL LIKE THAT
CAN JUMP-START THE PROCESS.
TA-DA.
- EW.
HOW'’D YOU DO?
- WELL, I GOT SOME MILK
OUT OF IT, WHICH IS GOOD.
- WHY IS IT SO YELLOW?
- IT'’S COLOSTRUM,
BEFORE THE MILK ACTUALLY COMES.
- I JUST DRY HEAVED.
- COLOSTRUM IS THE YELLOW STUFF,
SO IT'’S BASICALLY, LIKE,
THE PRE-MILK
BEFORE YOUR MILK COMES OUT.
SHE'’D PROBABLY CHUG THIS
RIGHT AWAY.
- I DON'’T WANT TO LOOK AT IT.
- IT'’S ONE OUNCE.
- LISTEN, NICOLE.
YOU WANT TO GO TO THE HOUSE?
- YEAH.
WHY YOU MAKING THAT STINKFACE?
- CAUSE I DON'’T--
I DON'’T KNOW WHY.
I GOT, LIKE, A GROSS FEELING.
COLOSTRUM LOOKS PRETTY NASTY.
- IT'’S PRETTY GROSS.
JIONNI, IT'’S MILK.
- IT'’S REALLY YELLOW.
- IT'’S COLOSTRUM.
- REMINDS ME OF THE MUCUS PLUG.
- HOPEFULLY WE'’LL SEE THAT
TODAY.
I HONESTLY FEEL LIKE GIOVANNA'’S
GONNA COME TONIGHT.
I MEAN, THIS PAIN,
I HAVEN'’T REALLY FELT YET,
AND I FEEL LIKE IT JUST
GETS WORSE AND WORSE.
SO I FEEL LIKE, YOU KNOW,
IT'’S GONNA HAPPEN.
- MAY THE PUMPING
BE IN YOUR FAVOR.
- IT'’S THE LAST THING.
THEN I'’M GONNA GET
SOME CHAMOMILE TEA.
I HEARD THAT WORKS TOO.
- YOU WANT SOME NIP STIM?
- I JUST DID MY NIP STIM.
- OH.
- THEY WERE BEING YANKED ON.
- THAT'’S WHAT SHE SAID.
- ALL RIGHT. YOU'’RE GROSS.
- I THOUGHT THAT WAS MY JOB,
TO YANK YOUR NIPPLE.
- NO.
- TODAY'’S GONNA BE
ANOTHER BUSY DAY AT THE HOUSE.
WE HAVE A LOT OF UNPACKING,
A LOT OF BUILDING
AND PUTTING STUFF TOGETHER.
NICOLE AND I ARE GONNA
BE BUSY AGAIN TODAY.
- SHE NEEDS TO BE OUT OF HERE.
I'’M DOING EVERYTHING,
AND SHE'’S NOT COMING OUT.
I'’M GONNA DRINK AS MUCH
CHAMOMILE TEA AS I CAN TODAY.
LET'’S STERILIZE SOME BOTTLES
JUST IN CASE.
I'’M NOT FEELING SO HOT.
- WELL, SO RELAX.
- NO, I AM.
I JUST FEEL LIKE SHE'’S DOWN.
- NICOLE IS JUST
TRYING EVERYTHING POSSIBLE,
AND WITH ALL THESE MYTHS,
I FEEL LIKE
SHE JUST KEEPS TRYING TO INDUCE
HERSELF AND INDUCE HERSELF,
BUT AT THIS POINT,
I GUESS IF SHE'’S
IN THAT BAD OF PAIN,
SHE NEEDS IT.
SO, YOU KNOW,
I'’M THERE FOR HER IF SHE NEEDS--
WHATEVER SHE NEEDS.
I JUST WANT HER TO FEEL BETTER
IF SHE'’S IN PAIN.
- I DON'’T FEEL GOOD.
I KEEP GETTING THIS PAIN.
- DON'’T DRINK TOO MUCH TEA.
- I'’M HAVING SEVERE CRAMPS
RIGHT NOW.
- I WISH SHE DIDN'’T FEEL
LIKE THIS,
AND I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW SHE'’S FEELING,
AND I JUST WANT HER TO RELAX
AND TAKE IT EASY.
- BABE, CAN YOU GO GET
MY BOUNCY BALL IN THE BACKSEAT?
- WHAT'’S IT FOR?
- SO I CAN BOUNCE ON IT.
I FEEL LIKE BOUNCING ON THE BALL
HELPS YOUR CERVIX OPEN
AND YOUR HIPS OPEN.
[laughing]
THIS IS PERVERTED.
SO RIGHT NOW, I'’M TRYING
TO BLOW UP THIS BOUNCY BALL
WITH THE LITTLE HOSE,
AND IT'’S A LITTLE AWKWARD
BECAUSE IT'’S KIND OF SEXUAL.
BABE, LOOK.
NEVER MIND, DON'’T LOOK.
- WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
- IT WAS A PUMP,
SO I HAD TO, LIKE,
HOLD THE PUMP,
AND IT WAS LIKE THIS.
BUT I WAS TRYING TO DO IT, LIKE,
FAST TO GET THE BALL GOING.
AND I WAS LIKE--
- THAT'’S USUALLY WHAT YOU DO.
- EW. [laughs]
EW, YOU'’RE SICK.
- THAT WAS SUCH A FAKE LAUGH.
- [laughing]
THIS IS IT?
IT'’S THE SMALLEST BALL
I'’VE EVER SEEN.
- THAT'’S WHAT SHE SAID.
- [laughs]
WELL, I WAS EXPECTING
THIS BALL TO BE WAY BIGGER,
BUT IT'’LL DO THE JOB.
YOUR BUTT LOOKS NICE.
- SHUT UP.
- LITTLE BUBBLE BUTT.
IS THIS WHAT I'’M SUPPOSED TO DO?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- IT HURTS SO BAD.
HOW VIOLENT SHOULD I BOUNCE?
I FEEL PRESSURE IN MY VAGINA.
WHERE ARE YOU?
- HOW'’S SHE DOING?
- LOOK.
- OH, MY GOD.
SEE, I TOLD YOU, SHE'’S TEETHING.
SHE BITES THE BOTTLE.
- SHE'’S LIKE A BABY COW.
- [laughs]
- OH, THEM EYES
ARE GETTING HEAVY, SO, SO HEAVY.
- SHE'’S BEEN UP
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
- SHE'’S SLEEPING.
WE COULD GO UPSTAIRS
AND MAKE LOVE.
- I HAVE MY PERIOD.
- IN 4 1/2 YEARS,
JENNI HAS INITIATED
TWO SEXUAL ACTS, TWO.
THAT'’S THE TRUTH,
AND SHE CAN'’T ARGUE IT.
- BECAUSE YOU ASK
45 TIMES A DAY.
WHAT'’S THE POINT
OF ME INITIATING IT?
- TWICE. 4 1/2 YEARS.
AND IF YOU DIDN'’T HAVE
YOUR PERIOD?
- I HAVE A HEADACHE.
- AND IF YOU DIDN'’T HAVE
A HEADACHE?
- I BROKE A TOE.
- AND IF YOU DIDN'’T BREAK A TOE?
- I STABBED MYSELF IN THE EYE
WITH A FORK.
- AND THIS IS THE TRUTH.
YOUR IDEA
OF INITIATING A SEXUAL ACT,
IS IT OR IS IT NOT
LAYING FLAT ON YOUR BACK
AND SAYING TO ME,
"DO YOU WANT TO HAVE SEX?"
THAT IS YOUR IDEA
OF INITIATING A SEXUAL ACT.
AND THEN I'’LL SAY, "SURE!"
AND I'’LL BE LIKE, "OKAY,
"I'’LL WAIT HERE
UNTIL SHE DOES SOMETHING.
WE'’LL HAVE A STALEMATE HERE."
I WOULD BE LAYING THERE
FOR A [bleep] WEEK.
SO I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
[laughs]
THIS IS THE HELL
THAT YOUR DADDY LIVES.
HE REALLY MUST LOVE YOU.
HE MUST REALLY LOVE YOUR MOMMY.
- I'’M GETTING
REALLY BAD CONTRACTIONS.
- HI, GUYS.
- AND HERE'’S ANOTHER ONE.
- I JUST HUNG A MIRROR.
- YOU JUST HUNG A MIRROR
BY YOURSELF?
- MM-HMM.
- OH, MY GOD. IT'’S SO PERFECT.
- JANIS?
- WHOA. YES?
I BROUGHT JACKIE.
- I'’M HAVING THE BABY.
- WE CAME TO EMPTY THE POD.
I FEEL SO BAD.
AND--
- IF I DON'’T GO TONIGHT,
I'’M GONNA HANG MYSELF.
- SHE'’S POOPING.
- OH, I THOUGHT
SHE WAS IN HERE--
- HI, JACKS.
- IN THIS ROOM.
- I PUMPED TODAY.
- YOU WHAT?
I GOT AN OUNCE OUT.
- ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO DO THAT?
- I'’M SO EXHAUSTED.
I'’M IN PAIN.
IT REALLY HURTS.
AND IT'’S REALLY BAD.
I'’M SO OVER IT.
- YOU HAVE TO REST.
- NO.
IF I MOVE,
IT MIGHT INDUCE LABOR.
I'’M JUST WAITING FOR IT.
IT'’S TORTURE.
I'’M GETTING THIS SHARP PAIN,
LIKE, EVERY 12, 13 MINUTES.
LORENZO, PULL.
- PULL IT, LORENZO.
- LORENZO, PULL.
I LOVE WHEN YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
WE GET [bleep] DONE.
STRONG LADIES.
I THINK I'’M GONNA GIVE BIRTH.
- JUST DO IT. IT'’S OKAY.
- REALLY?
- I'’M TRYING. I KEEP PUSHING.
- DON'’T BE PUSHING RIGHT NOW.
- [yells]
- YOU'’RE ALL SWEATY AND [bleep].
- NO, I'’M NOT KIDDING.
I'’M PUSHING.
- DON'’T.
YOU MAKE ME SO NERVOUS.
- CUTE PUSHING FACE.
- OOH, YOU SHOULD SEE IT
WHEN I REALLY PUSH.
I GO LIKE THIS.
[laughter]
- LET ME SEE?
- THIS EPISODE
OF SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- CONTINUES NOW.
- IT'’S SO BAD.
I WOULDN'’T WISH THIS ON ANYONE.
- EMBRACE IT. EMBRACE THE PAIN.
- WHY DON'’T YOU EMBRACE IT?
YOU WOULDN'’T LAST
ONE CONTRACTION.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- I'’M TEN MINUTES APART.
- DO YOU THINK
YOU'’RE GONNA GO TONIGHT?
- PROBABLY.
- DID YOU EAT?
WANT TO EAT SOMETHING?
- I DON'’T KNOW WHAT I WANT.
- WELL,
YOU HAVE TO EAT SOMETHING.
I'’LL MAKE YOU A SALAD
WITH SOME GRILLED CHICKEN?
- NO.
- MOZZARELLE STICKS?
- A BIG MAC?
- NO.
I'’LL POOP EVERYWHERE
IF I GIVE BIRTH.
- COME ON, YOU HAVE TO EAT
SOMETHING; WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- OKAY, I'’LL HAVE
GRILLED CHEESE.
- YOU'’LL HAVE GRILLED CHEESE?
- JANIS IS ASKING A MILLION
QUESTIONS, AND AS OF RIGHT NOW,
IT'’S SO HARD
FOR ME TO HAVE A CONVERSATION.
I'’M JUST TRYING TO DEAL
WITH THE PAIN, AND I JUST--
I DON'’T WANT TO FEEL THIS WAY
ANYMORE BECAUSE IT HURTS SO BAD.
[sneezing]
I JUST PEED.
DAMN IT.
- SO WHAT'’S THE PLAN?
- I'’LL JUST WAIT TILL MY WATER
BREAKS, OR I'’LL JUST DIE IN BED.
[laughter]
- ALL RIGHT, CALM DOWN.
- WE COULD DELIVER THE BABY
IN BED.
- NO, I DON'’T WANT TO FEEL IT.
- OH.
- THAT'’S WHAT SHE'’S SCARED MOST
IS NOT BEING ABLE
TO HAVE THE EPIDURAL.
- YEAH.
I'’M DEFINITELY NERVOUS
RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE EVERYONE'’S TELLING ME
THAT THE SECOND ONE
COMES SO MUCH QUICKER
AND YOU WON'’T HAVE TIME
FOR THE EPIDURAL.
SO OBVIOUSLY,
I'’M FREAKING OUT ABOUT THAT.
I GOT TO GO THE BATHROOM.
- GO AHEAD.
- DON'’T TALK [bleep] ABOUT ME.
I KNOW I'’M CRAZY.
JUST DEAL WITH IT RIGHT NOW.
THESE CONTRACTIONS ARE LITERALLY
TAKING MY BREATH AWAY,
AND ANYWHERE THAT I'’M SITTING,
IF I'’M SITTING,
IF I'’M LAYING DOWN,
IF I'’M WALKING, IT JUST--
NOTHING HELPS THE PAIN.
SO HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DEAL
WITH THIS PAIN FOR--
EVERY TEN MINUTES FOR FOUR DAYS?
IT'’S VERY IRRITATING.
- EXPLAIN THE PAIN.
LET ME HEAR WHAT IT FEELS LIKE,
WHAT YOU'’RE FEELING.
- LIKE A KNIFE.
BUT IT'’S LIKE A ROLLER COASTER,
AND THEN IT GOES--
IT GOES, LIKE, FARTS.
- SHE'’S THE WRONG PERSON
TO TALK TO.
- I KNOW, '’CAUSE SHE LIKES PAIN.
IF JIONNI PINCHES ME, I CRY.
I JUST CAN'’T DEAL WITH PAIN.
SO AS OF RIGHT NOW, I'’M DYING.
OW. SEE, THAT HURTS.
IT GOES UP,
AND THEN OUCHY, OUCHY, OUCHY,
OUCHY, OUCHY, OUCHY, AND THEN--
- THAT'’S A CONTRACTION.
- I KNOW.
IT'’S LIKE A ROLLER COASTER RIDE
OF PAIN.
- I NEED A PILL FOR MY NERVES.
- HAVE A DRINK.
- COME ON,
GIVE ME A KISS GOOD NIGHT.
- WE'’LL CALL YOU
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS.
- OKAY.
- THANK YOU.
- IF I DON'’T HEAR, WAKE ME UP.
- I DON'’T WANT TO COME.
- YOU REALLY THINK
I'’M NOT GONNA GO TONIGHT?
THAT'’LL SUCK.
- BABE, I DON'’T KNOW.
- I'’M JUST PRAYING
THAT I HAVE THIS BABY TONIGHT,
BECAUSE I'’VE BEEN
FEELING CONTRACTIONS ALL DAY,
10 TO 12 MINUTES APART,
AND NOW BEFORE GOING TO BED,
THEY'’RE 7 MINUTES APART,
SO I MEAN,
ONCE THEY'’RE 5 MINUTES APART,
THAT'’S TIME
TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL,
AND IT'’S TIME
TO PUSH THE BABY OUT.
SO IT'’S GOT TO BE TONIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- OW.
I FEEL REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE
RIGHT NOW.
BABE?
- HMM.
- FEELS LIKE IT'’S COMING
OUT OF MY BUTTHOLE.
I WANT TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
- RIGHT NOW? FOR REAL?
- YES.
IT HURTS.
I CAN'’T SLEEP AT ALL.
WAIT. I'’M CRAMPING.
- ALL RIGHT, TAKE YOUR TIME.
- OW.
AND I'’M TIMING MY CONTRACTIONS,
AND THEY'’RE FIVE,
SIX MINUTES APART.
AND THEY FEEL LIKE DEATH.
I FEEL LIKE THERE'’S A KNIFE
IN MY UTERUS TWISTING
AND IN MY VAGINA,
AND THIS PAIN, I'’VE NEVER FELT
THIS PAIN IN MY LIFE.
I CAN'’T BREATHE.
I CAN'’T MOVE.
AND THIS PAIN IS NOT GOING AWAY.
SO I FEEL LIKE THIS
IS THE REAL DEAL.
I'’M IN LABOR, AND I NEED TO BE
AT THE HOSPITAL RIGHT NOW.
IT HURTS.
BABE, IT REALLY HURTS.
- COME ON.
TAKE IT EASY.
- OH, I CAN'’T DO IT.
OUCH.
BABE, I DON'’T THINK
I CAN GET UP THE STAIRS.
- GO SLOW.
- I DON'’T WANT TO. OW.
- AS SOON AS WE GET THERE,
YOU GET YOUR--YOUR MEDS.
- I'’M SCARED [bleep].
I'’M NERVOUS. I'’M TERRIFIED.
I JUST--I'’M NOT GOOD WITH PAIN,
AND I JUST REALLY, REALLY
WANT TO GET THE EPIDURAL
SO I DON'’T FEEL ANYTHING.
SO THAT'’S JUST IN THE BACK
OF MY MIND RIGHT NOW
IS TO GET TO THE HOSPITAL
ON TIME TO GET THE EPIDURAL.
BECAUSE IF I DON'’T GET
THE EPIDURAL, I'’M DYING.
OW.
- TAKE IT EASY.
- BABE, I CAN'’T EVEN SIT.
- WELL, TAKE IT EASY.
JUST RELAX.
- NO, IT HURTS.
YOU DON'’T GET IT.
- WE'’RE ALMOST THERE.
WE'’RE ALMOST THERE.
- NO.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BABE, BABE.
- JIONNI, I CAN'’T.
- NICOLE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THIS IS THE ONLY COMFORTABLE
POSITION I CAN DO RIGHT NOW.
- JUST CALM DOWN.
- THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
I NEED THE EPIDURAL,
LIKE, RIGHT NOW.
- WE'’RE ALMOST THERE.
- NO, I CAN'’T DO THIS.
- JUST BREATHE.
WE'’RE--YOU'’RE OKAY.
- I CAN'’T BREATHE.
I'’M NEVER DOING THIS AGAIN.
- BABE, WE'’RE PULLING IN.
WE'’RE PULLING IN.
- I GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
OH.
YOU GOT MY PILLOW?
AH!
- COME ON.
- NO.
NO. AH. OW!
I CAN'’T MOVE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I CAN'’T MOVE.
- IT'’S ALMOST OVER.
I CAN'’T MOVE.
- ALL RIGHT, JUST SIT.
I'’LL TAKE YOU FROM HERE.
- I'’M LITERALLY CRYING,
I'’M IN SO MUCH PAIN.
I JUST--I CAN'’T MOVE.
I CAN'’T EVEN SIT RIGHT
IN THE CHAIR RIGHT NOW,
AND MY VAGINA REALLY HURTS,
AND MY UTERUS REALLY HURTS,
AND EVERYTHING REALLY HURTS,
AND THIS IS HELL.
OH, I CAN'’T DO IT.
HONESTLY, I JUST WANT
MY MOMMY.
OW.
- ALL RIGHT, ALMOST THERE.
- AH!
I FEEL HER HEAD
COMING DOWN MY VAGINA,
AND SHE'’S JUST GONNA POP OUT.
[crying]
OW, OW, OW.
- I'’M ASSUMING YOU WANT YOUR
EPIDURAL AS SOON AS YOU CAN?
YOUR LITTLE GIRL'’S COMING.
I'’M JUST PREPARING MYSELF,
YOU KNOW,
GOD FORBID THE EPIDURAL
DOESN'’T KICK IN IN TIME.
I SERIOUSLY NEED TO GET
MENTALLY FOCUSED
TO ACTUALLY GIVE BIRTH
AND FEEL EVERYTHING.
AND I'’M SCARED THAT I'’M NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO DO THIS.
[moaning]
OW.
THEY GOT TO GET OUT. GET OUT.
AH! NO. NO.
[sobbing]
- YOU'’RE DOING GREAT.
IT'’S GONNA BE CLOSE.
- WHOA, WHOA, PLEASE HELP ME.
SOMETHING'’S NOT RIGHT.
- NEXT TIME ON SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- I THINK I'’M GONNA POOP
'’CAUSE I ATE.
- UH-OH.
[baby cries]
- HERE SHE IS.
- I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE MY KIDS.
- I GOT SOME GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
- AFTER 27 YEARS, THIS IS
THE DAY I ACTUALLY MOVE OUT.
ONLY ONE THING LEFT TO DO.
- GET MARRIED.