- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
[dog barking]
OKAY, OKAY.
[screams]
EW, JIONNI. JIONNI, PLEASE!
- YEE!
- [screams]
THE JOEYS NEED ETIQUETTE CLASS.
- YOU DON'’T THINK WE DO?
- YEAH, WE DO.
- HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
I'’M MAKING BREAKFAST FOR YOU.
- WAS IT ACTUALLY YOUR IDEA,
THOUGH?
- IT ABSOLUTELY WAS MY IDEA.
- JUST ASKING.
- ALL RIGHT.
- BUT I APOLOGIZE
FOR THAT COMMENT.
JUST ME AND YOU, NOW.
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- OH, MY GOD.
IS THAT REAL?
MA, COME HERE.
- OH, IT'’S A...
- CATERPILLAR?
I MEAN, A GRASSHOPPER?
- YEAH. I DON'’T THINK
YOU COULD KILL IT.
IT'’S ILLEGAL.
- THAT BUG?
- WHAT IS THAT?
SAY, "HI, BUGGY."
- BYE, BYE.
- WHAT IS THIS HOUSE?
THIS HOUSE IS DEFINITELY
INFESTED WITH INSECTS.
THERE'’S ALL TYPES OF SPIDERS,
BEETLES, COCKROACHES.
LIKE, I'’M GETTING GROSSED OUT.
- WHY?
- IT'’S A BUG.
THAT IS A BIG BUG.
- I--
I TOUCH.
- WE'’RE NOT TOUCHING IT, NO.
NO. YOU CAN GIVE IT
TO YOUR MOMMY.
WANT TO GIVE IT TO MOMMY?
- I DON'’T KNOW WHAT THESE BUGS
ARE IN THIS HOUSE,
BUT THIS IS DEFINITELY
THE PERFECT TIME TO,
YOU KNOW, SET NICOLE UP.
- THAT SMELLS DELICIOUS.
- NICOLE, COULD I HAVE A HUG?
COULD I HAVE A HUG?
- WHY ARE YOU ACTING LIKE ME?
- TIRED.
[sighs and groans]
[baby giggles]
- BABE, I'’M HUNGRY.
- WHO'’D YOU WATCH A MOVIE
WITH LAST NIGHT?
- CARLY.
- WAS YOUR OTHER FRIEND HERE?
- WHO?
- YOUR OTHER FRIEND
WATCHED A MOVIE WITH YOU.
- WHO'’S MY OTHER FRIEND?
[screams]
WHAT IS THAT?
JIONNI? JIONNI!
- I DIDN'’T PUT IT THERE.
- I JUST--
I DON'’T LIKE CREATURES.
I DON'’T LIKE BUGS.
AND THIS IS WHY JIONNI
WANTED A HUG.
JUST TO SCARE ME.
IT WASN'’T GENUINE.
WHAT IF IT JUMPED ON ME?
- I WOULD PROBABLY HAVE PEED
IN MY PANTS.
- GET IT OUT OF HERE.
- THIS HOUSE IS FULL
OF CRITTERS, CRAWLERS,
AND CREEPERS.
WE MIGHT AS WELL USE IT TO--
- IT'’S CREEPY CRAWLERS,
NOT CRITTERS.
- I WAS JUST MAKING THINGS UP.
- I DON'’T WANT
TO HURT IT THOUGH.
IT'’S A GRASSHOPPER.
- IT'’S A CRICKET.
- WAIT, IT'’S LOOKING AT ME.
[screams]
DON'’T DO THAT. I'’M NOT DOING IT.
LET'’S WATCH IT HOP AWAY.
BYE, CRICKET!
I'’M FEELING BUGS.
IT'’S MY HAIR.
Lorenzo: BYE-BYE.
- BYE, BUGGY.
NO BUGGIES IN THIS HOUSE.
COME ON.
MOMMY'’S GOING TO EAT.
- BYE, BYE.
- I WONDER HOW MEILANI'’S DOING.
I WANT TO BABYSIT HER.
I'’VE BEEN TELLING JENNI
TO GO OUT,
GO DO SOMETHING, SO I COULD
JUST HAVE HER TO MYSELF.
- ISN'’T TODAY THEIR ANNIVERSARY?
- IT IS?
- YEAH.
- WHEN IT'’S THEIR ANNIVERSARY,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
GO SOMEWHERE AND DO SOMETHING.
I'’M GOING TO CALL JENNI.
I GOT TO TELL HER
I LEFT LASAGNA IN HER FRIDGE.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO.
- HI, BOO.
- OH, HEY.
- HOW'’S MY BABY?
- SHE GOT REALLY SICK
THIS MORNING.
SHE, LIKE, SPIT UP EVERYWHERE.
- I MEAN, IT'’S NORMAL
FOR BABIES TO SPIT UP.
- I JUST GOT HER BACK
TO SLEEP RIGHT NOW.
- IT IS YOUR ANNIVERSARY TODAY,
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
DID YOU FORGET?
- NO, IT'’S JUST--
IT'’S ON THE BACK BURNER.
WE'’RE BOTH ON EDGE.
ROGER LEFT TO COOL DOWN
BECAUSE WE GOT IN,
LIKE, AN ARGUMENT
AFTER SHE SPIT UP.
HE'’S JUST ANNOYED
THAT I TOOK TOO LONG
TO GET READY
WHEN HE MADE BREAKFAST.
- OH, I HAVE TO COME OVER.
I DON'’T KNOW
IF YOU HEARD ME LAST NIGHT.
I'’D FEEL AWFUL
IF I WOKE MEILANI UP.
ME AND JANIS SNUCK IN,
AND WE PUT LASAGNA
IN YOUR FRIDGE,
'’CAUSE WE DIDN'’T HAVE ANY ROOM.
AND I TOTALLY FORGOT THE DOGS
WERE IN THE OTHER ROOM.
- THAT'’S WHY THEY WERE BARKING?
- YEAH, I'’M SORRY.
- NO, IT'’S ALL RIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL. I'’M GONNA
COME OVER AND GET MY LASAGNA.
- ALL RIGHT, I'’LL BE UPSTAIRS
IF YOU WANT TO SEE ME.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
- BYE, NANO.
- I DON'’T THINK
SHE WANTS TO GO OUT.
DAMN IT, I'’M NEVER GOING
TO WATCH THIS KID.
JENNI AND ROGER
USED TO FIGHT A LOT.
THE FACT THAT IT'’S HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW SUCKS.
SO, I'’M SAD
THAT JENNI'’S UPSET ABOUT THAT.
[dogs barking]
SHH. SHH.
HOW'’S MY BABY?
IS SHE SICK?
- MM, YOU SMELL GOOD.
[baby coughs]
- OH.
- AH.
- HANDS UP. HANDS UP.
- SO BIG.
[baby coughs]
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- HE LEFT '’CAUSE HE WAS UPSET.
- BUT WHY? '’CAUSE
YOU WERE LATE FOR BREAKFAST?
- TO ME THAT, I'’M LIKE,
THAT'’S EXPECTED AS NEW PARENTS.
- YEAH.
- THERE'’S NO MORE SITTING DOWN,
AND HAVING NICE BREAKFASTS.
THERE'’S NO MORE WARM BREAKFAST
BEING READY AT THE TABLE.
AND I DON'’T THINK
HE GRASPED THAT YET.
BUT I THINK HE'’S JUST--
- STRESSED OUT?
- YEAH, I THINK HE'’S
JUST LOST HIS DAMN MIND
BECAUSE HE'’S TIRED.
I FEEL BAD, BUT I APOLOGIZED.
I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT ELSE I COULD DO.
- YOU HAVE A BEAUTIFUL
BABY GIRL.
THAT DRAMA IS NONSENSE.
- MY GOD, I AM LIKE,
I JUST DON'’T EVEN CARE.
I'’M LIKE,
I JUST LET IT GO AT THIS POINT.
- DO YOU KNOW IF YOU'’RE GOING
TO GO OUT TONIGHT OR TODAY?
- I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
IF I WANT TO.
I DEFINITELY KNOW ROGER
AND I ARE GOING TO FIGHT AGAIN.
I MEAN, ALL COUPLES FIGHT.
IT'’S THE WAY YOU HANDLE
THE FIGHT
THAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
SO, I HOPE WE HANDLE
OUR NEXT FIGHT DIFFERENTLY,
ESPECIALLY
NOW THAT WE'’RE NEW PARENTS.
- CALL ME. LET ME KNOW
IF YOU WANT ME TO BABYSIT.
- THANK YOU.
- BYE, BABY.
- BYE.
- I'’M GONNA GRAB MY LASAGNA.
- ENJOY.
- [laughs]
- SHH.
OH, MY GOD.
ROGER'’S BREAKFAST
LOOKS SO AMAZING RIGHT NOW.
I REALLY WANT TO DIG
INTO THE PANCAKES,
BUT I CAN'’T RUIN
THEIR BREAKFAST.
IT'’S THEIR ANNIVERSARY.
IT'’S FOR THEM GOING FOR DINNER.
WHY AM I SNOOPING?
THIS IS VERY RUDE.
OH, MY GOD. IS THAT A CINNABON?
MM.
I WANT THAT CINNABON.
- JENNI AND I DID HAVE A FIGHT,
BUT IT WASN'’T RIGHT TO LEAVE.
IT'’S TIME
TO MAKE THE WRONG RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE MY FAILURES
AND I HAVE MY DEMONS,
AND SO DOES JENNI,
BUT THE IMPORTANT PART
IS THAT WE WORK THROUGH THEM
AND STAY TOGETHER.
AND IT'’S--
IT'’S IMPORTANT NOW TO WORK
ON THOSE COMMUNICATION SKILLS
MORE THAN EVER
'’CAUSE WE'’RE PARENTS.
Jenni: I KNOW.
- HEY.
- HELLO.
- HOW IS SHE?
- FUSSY.
- CAN DADDY SEE HER
FOR A MINUTE?
- YEAH, WE'’RE ABOUT TO TAKE
A NAP, ACTUALLY.
WANT TO GO TO YOUR DADDY?
[baby coos]
- OKAY.
SO, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
SO, ARE WE OKAY?
- YEAH, WE'’RE FINE.
WE'’RE JUST TIRED NEW PARENTS.
- I THINK THAT DOESN'’T GIVE ME
THE RIGHT TO STORM OUT
AND LEAVE.
BUT SOMETIMES I THINK
THAT'’S THE LESSER OF TWO EVILS,
AND I JUST DIDN'’T WANT TO ARGUE
IN FRONT OF HER, REALLY.
THAT'’S ALL IT WAS,
AND I PROBABLY MADE
A WORSE DECISION BY LEAVING.
- WELL, YOU WORK ON THAT,
AND I'’LL WORK
ON MY SNAPPY COMMENTS.
- OKAY, THAT'’S FAIR.
- I'’M GLAD YOU'’RE BACK
'’CAUSE I NEED A BREAK.
- DON'’T EVER WANT TO BE
AWAY FROM MY ANGEL BABY.
- I APPRECIATE ROGER,
YOU KNOW, SAYING HE'’S SORRY.
YOU KNOW, WE'’RE LEARNING,
WE'’RE GROWING AS A COUPLE,
AND I'’M GLAD
BECAUSE I'’M TOTALLY OVER IT,
AND I JUST WANT TO MOVE ON
AT THIS POINT.
THANK YOU.
- WANT TO GO DOWNSTAIRS
WITH DADDY?
DADDY PUT YOU IN YOUR SWING?
- [yawning] HAVE FUN.
- TAKE A NAP.
OKAY?
- UH-HUH.
- SPREAD IT ALL AROUND.
- LASAGNA'’S HERE.
- WHERE DO YOU WANT TO EAT?
- MY BROTHER, JAMES,
IS COMING OVER SOON.
WE ALL PREP FOR DINNER.
WE'’RE GETTING READY
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
WE'’RE HAVING ALL FAMILY NIGHT.
THAT THING REALLY
SMELLS LIKE IT'’S BURNING.
DAD, OPEN THAT. OPEN THAT UP,
SOMETHING'’S BURNING.
- WHOA, LASAGNA ON FIRE.
OH, GOD.
- THIS OVEN SUCKS.
- THE FLOUR.
- OH, YOU SMELL IT?
P.U.
P.U., IT'’S STINKY.
- YOU HAVE TO GET THAT DRIP.
- I'’M NOT GOING TO GET IT WET
AND CLEAN THAT.
[smoke detector goes off]
- OH, HERE YOU GO.
- LOOK WHAT YOU DID. THERE'’S 10
OF THEM GOING OFF, NOW.
- OH, MY GOD.
- BRING HIM OUTSIDE.
- COME ON. OH, THE FIREFIGHTERS
ARE GOING TO COME.
- REALLY?
- YEAH,
I THOUGHT YOU KNEW HOW TO COOK.
- IT'’S YOUR OVEN.
- NO.
IT WAS DIRTY.
NO, YOU'’RE NOT GOING
IN THERE, PREGNANT.
DON'’T GO IN THERE.
- WHY?
- WHAT'’S THAT NOISE?
OH, PYOO. PYOO.
- I FEEL LIKE THIS IS SOMETHING
I WOULD DO, BECAUSE I DON'’T KNOW
HOW TO COOK, REALLY.
BUT JANIS DOING IT, IT'’S LIKE,
I THOUGHT YOU COULD COOK.
- KEEP GOING.
- I DID IT!
- YOU DID IT. KEEP DOING IT.
[laughs]
- NOW WE HAVE
SOME BRAGGING RIGHTS.
- EPIC FAIL.
- LOOK WHO ALMOST
BURNED OUR HOUSE DOWN.
- NANA'’S BURNED
THE LASAGNA.
- YOU BURNED THE HOUSE DOWN.
- HERE GOES DINNER.
HERE GOES THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
- MAMA.
- WHAT?
LORENZO, HOLD ON.
- MAMA.
- HOLD ON.
[doorbell ringing]
UH-OH.
- SOMEBODY'’S AT THE DOOR.
- WHO'’S THAT?
- LORENZO, SOMEBODY'’S HERE.
LORENZO, OPEN IT.
- HEY.
- HEY, GUYS.
- HI.
- LORENZO, WHO'’S THAT?
JAMES AND AMY, JIONNI'’S BROTHER
AND SISTER-IN-LAW
FINALLY GET HERE
SO WE CAN DIG IN,
AND I REALLY HOPE EVERYONE
ENJOYS MY LASAGNA,
BECAUSE JANIS TAUGHT ME
HOW TO MAKE IT.
I DID IT ALL BY MYSELF,
AND I FEEL LIKE IT'’S GOING
TO TASTE REALLY GOOD.
HERE'’S MY LASAGNA I MADE.
- SHE MADE
THE WHOLE THING HERSELF.
- EVERYBODY HAS TO TRY.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'’M NERVOUS, BUT OKAY.
OH, IT'’S DELICIOUS.
IT'’S REALLY GOOD.
- I DID GOOD?
- YEAH, YOU DID REALLY GOOD.
I'’M IMPRESSED.
- WHOO-HOO.
- WHEN NICOLE
AND I MOVE INTO OUR HOUSE
WE DEFINITELY
WANT TO HAVE DINNERS LIKE THIS.
TAKING SUNDAY
OVER FROM MY MOTHER PROBABLY
WON'’T HAPPEN EVERY SUNDAY,
BUT WE DEFINITELY WANT
TO TAKE OVER A LITTLE BIT.
- LORENZO MADE THE PIZZA.
- [giggling]
- MM.
- LORENZO, YOU WANT
TO TRY THE LASAGNA?
- NO!
- LORENZO, TRY.
- IT'’S LIKE--IT'’S MACARONI.
- REALLY NICE.
- THERE YOU GO, GOOD BOY!
- GOOD JOB, LORENZO.
- YAY, LORENZO.
- PASTA, BABY.
- OKAY, WHO WANTS
SOME LOBSTER?
- YOU SHOULD'’VE SEEN
HOW SHE KILLED IT.
THEY WERE ALIVE,
AND SHE STABBED THE HEART.
- REALLY?
- AND THE TAIL WAS FLAPPING.
I DON'’T WANT TO TRY THE LOBSTER
JUST BECAUSE I SAW
THAT LOBSTER BEING KILLED.
AS AN ANIMAL LOVER,
IT DOESN'’T SEEM HUMANE TO ME.
IT'’S MURDER.
- MY GOD.
- THAT'’S DISGUSTING.
- THAT LOOKS AWESOME, NICOLE.
HOW DOES THAT NOT LOOK SO GOOD?
- IT SMELLS
LIKE THE OCEAN WATER.
LIKE, STRAIGHT UP OCEAN WATER.
I MEAN, IF YOU PAID ME $100,
YEAH, I'’LL TAKE A LITTLE BITE.
- 100 BUCKS? THAT'’S IT?
- ALL RIGHT, $1,000.
- DO I HAVE LOBSTER ON MY FACE?
- MM-MM.
I'’M SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
I ATE TOO MUCH.
AH, I'’M READY FOR BED.
- ♪ RAISE
♪ YOUR SAILS AND ROWS
♪
- [grunts]
[gasps]
HOW FANCY.
OH, MY GOSH.
I'’M SO EXCITED, BECAUSE
OUR VICTORIAN OUTFITS CAME IN,
AND I WAS HOPING
THAT THIS WOULD HAPPEN
BECAUSE TODAY I HAVE
NICOLE'’S BRIDAL LUNCHEON.
- HOPE YOU HAVE
A GOOD BRIDAL LUNCHEON.
- [smacking lips]
IS THAT ANNOYING?
- WHAT?
- JUST CHEWING, LIKE.
- YEAH.
WORK ON CHEWING--
- WHEN I COME BACK
I'’LL BE A NEW WOMAN.
- CHEW WITH YOUR MOUTH CLOSED.
- I'’M GOING TO BE A NEW WOMAN.
YOU'’RE NOT EVEN
GOING TO RECOGNIZE ME.
HELLO?
- UPSTAIRS.
SO, TODAY WE'’RE GOING
TO GO TO THE BRIDAL LUNCHEON
THAT I SET UP WITH NICOLE,
WITH THE JOEYS
AND LEARN PROPER ETIQUETTE,
AND HAVE HIGH TEA.
- [gasps] PRETTY.
AGH, IT SMELLS LIKE OLD PEOPLE.
IS SHE SLEEPING?
- I TRIED TO YELL, BUT COULDN'’T.
I HOPE THE PINK ONE FITS.
IT LOOKS A LITTLE THIN.
- SMELL THEM.
- OLD PERSON.
- SMELLS LIKE A CASKET.
- AGH.
- THESE DRESSES
SMELL LIKE A DEAD PERSON.
THEY JUST SMELL,
LIKE MOTH BALLS.
WE'’RE GOING TO GET NAKED
AND PUT THESE ON?
MIGHT GET A HERPE.
THIS IS NOT GOING TO FIT.
- DO YOU WANT TO TRY MINE ON?
- DOESN'’T ZIP UP.
COME ON.
DOESN'’T FIT, DOES IT?
- NO.
HOW ABOUT WE JUST WEAR
THE HATS AND PUT A SUN DRESS ON?
- NO, I'’M WEARING THIS.
I LOOK SO OLD.
- WELL, WE'’RE
IN VICTORIAN TIME OUTFITS.
I DON'’T KNOW
WHEN THE VICTORIAN ERA IS.
DON'’T ASK ME THESE QUESTIONS.
I LOOK [bleep].
I NEED TO GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
IT'’S, LIKE, ARE YOU SMARTER
THAN A FIFTH GRADER?
I JUST FAILED.
- I HAVE NO IDEA
WHEN THE VICTORIAN ERA WAS.
I'’LL GUESS 1800s.
SOMETIME BACK IN THE DAY.
EW. I'’M A FAT BRIDE.
- A SOUTHERN BRIDE?
- JENNI LOOKS BEAUTIFUL
IN HER DRESS.
- THANK YOU.
THEY'’RE A LITTLE UNCOMFORTABLE,
AND I CAN'’T BELIEVE
THESE BITCHES WORE [bleep]
LIKE THIS BACK IN THE DAY,
'’CAUSE I WOULD DIE.
- SERIOUSLY.
NOW, WE HAVE TO WEAR
THIS IN THE CAR?
- YEAH, RIGHT?
[truck horn honking]
- TOODLES.
- WHOO.
- I DON'’T THINK
I NEED TO LEARN ANYTHING
IN THIS ETIQUETTE CLASS.
I MEAN, I DON'’T WANT TO BE ONE
OF THOSE PINKY UP PEOPLE
'’CAUSE THAT'’S TOTALLY NOT ME.
BUT JUST TO GO
FOR THE EXPERIENCE.
I THINK IT'’S GOING TO BE FUN.
BUT TO ACTUALLY LEARN SOMETHING,
I'’M FINE.
THIS DRESS KIND OF SMELLS.
- OLD?
- LIKE AN OLD, DYING PERSON.
- VICTORIAN TEA ROOM, DARLING.
- YOU CAN'’T DO A BRITISH ACCENT?
- NO.
- HELLO, MATE.
- THAT'’S NOT BRITISH.
- THAT'’S AUSTRALIAN.
WHATEVER, IT'’S EUROPEAN.
- HUH?
- IT'’S EUROPEAN.
- AUSTRALIAN IS EUROPEAN?
- YEAH, IT'’S OVER THERE
IN EUROPE SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
THIS HOUSE IS SO HAUNTED.
- [burps]
- THAT'’S PROBABLY NOT.
I'’M GOING TO SWING HERE.
- WONDER IF THE JOEYS ARE HERE.
I KNOW WHERE ANTARCTICA IS.
THAT'’S DOWN THERE
AND IT'’S ITS OWN THING.
- IT'’S DOWN THERE,
RIGHT BY HERE?
- NO, IT'’S ITS OWN--IT'’S LONG.
IT'’S THE ONLY THING I KNOW.
[classical music]
♪
- OH, HOW FANCY.
- YEAH, THIS IS NICE.
- OH, CRYSTAL.
- I'’M GLAD I WORE UNDERWEAR.
[sigh]
- [groans]
- OH, GIRLS, THIS CHAMPAGNE'’S
LOVELY BUT I CAME PREPARED.
- OH, MY GOD.
- OOP, OH, MY GOD.
- [bleep] DRESSES.
YOU LOOK LIKE AN ASS[bleep].
- AND SO DO YOU.
- AMEN TO THAT.
- SO, THIS IS A SPECIAL DRINK
I'’M MAKING.
CHEERS.
- CHEERS.
- NOW, THIS'’LL GET A PIECE
OF HAIR ON YOUR [bleep].
I'’M SO SORRY, LADIES.
[doorbell ringing]
- I'’VE GOT IT.
HELLO.
- HELLO.
- COME ON IN.
- OH, YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- THANK YOU.
- SO DO YOU.
- I LOVE THE UMBRELLAS.
- OH, IT'’S BEAUTIFUL IN HERE.
ARE WE ALLOWED TO USE THEM
IN THE HOUSE
OR IS THAT NOT PROPER?
- IS THAT NOT ETIQUETTE?
- BAD ETIQUETTE.
AND IT'’S BAD LUCK.
- OKAY.
- VERY BAD LUCK.
- OH [bleep], OW.
- I APOLOGIZE.
HEY, GIRL.
- HEY, GIRL.
- LOOK AT YOU.
both: MUAH.
- HI, OH, LOOK AT...
- CUTE.
- LITTLE HOES ON THE PRAIRIE.
Jenni: SO, ALL OUR JOEYS
ARE DRUNK AND I DON'’T THINK
WE WOULD HAVE IT ANY OTHER WAY.
- IF THEY WERE SOBER,
IT WOULD BE A PROBLEM.
- YEAH.
- SO, WHAT ARE WE CELEBRATING
TONIGHT?
- I WASN'’T ABLE TO ATTEND
BERTHA'’S BRIDAL SHOWER
DUE TO THE FACT
THAT I JUST HAD A BABY.
SO, JUST WANT TO,
YOU KNOW, CELEBRATE
IN A OLD FASHIONED WAY.
ALSO LEARN
PROPER ETIQUETTE '’CAUSE WE--
- WE DON'’T HAVE THAT.
- YEAH, WE'’RE TERRIBLE AT THAT.
- YEAH, WE'’RE
AWFUL HUMAN BEINGS.
- YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE
A SELECTION OF SANDWICHES,
YOU'’RE GOING TO HAVE SOUP.
IT'’S GOING TO BE DELICIOUS.
- MM.
- AND WE'’RE GOING TO BE WATCHING
YOU TO SEE IF YOU DO IT NEATLY.
- OH.
- OH, [bleep].
- SEE HOW YOU DO [bleep].
- I HAVE TERRIBLE ETIQUETTE.
- I FEEL LIKE BOTH OF US SUCK,
BUT JENNI IS WORSE.
- YEAH.
- JUST A LITTLE BIT WORSE.
CHEERS.
- CHEERS, BITCHES.
- NOT PROPER TEA TALK.
- NO?
- [slurps noisily]
- OH, EXCUSE ME, NO SLURPING.
- OH, I'’M SORRY.
MY TEA IS LOVELY, BUT I THINK
IT NEEDS A LITTLE SOMETHING.
- LOOK, OOH, THE TAMPON.
- ARE TAMPONS ALLOWED
AT THIS TABLE?
- OOH.
- NO, TAMPONS ARE NOT ALLOWED
AT THE TABLE.
- PUT THAT AWAY.
- IT'’S NOT A REAL TAMPON.
IT'’S LIKE A FLASK.
- OH, OKAY. THAT'’S DIFFERENT.
- JOEY HAS FAKE TAMPONS
FILLED WITH SCOTCH,
WHICH IS A GENIUS INVENTION,
'’CAUSE IF YOU'’RE A GIRL
THAT'’S BROKE
AND YOU DON'’T WANT TO SPEND $10
A DRINK AT THE BAR,
YOU BRING IN, LIKE,
SEVEN OR EIGHT TAMPONS
AND YOU'’RE GOOD TO GO.
- IT'’S DISCREET.
- OH, YOU'’RE INSANE.
- IT'’S DELICIOUS.
- OOH, OUR SOUP'’S HERE.
MM, IT SMELLS
LIKE MARINARA SAUCE.
- WHAT DOES THIS SMELL LIKE?
- A MUSHROOM.
- IT SMELLS LIKE [bleep].
- OH, IT DOES.
TELL THE WHOLE TABLE
WHAT YOUR MUSHROOM SMELLS LIKE.
- [bleep]
[all laugh]
- NOT PROPER TEA TALK.
- PARDON.
- YOUR SOUP SPOON, UP THERE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- WHEN YOU USE YOUR SPOON,
TRY NOT TO CLANK THE SPOON
ON THE SIDES
OF THE CUP OR THE BOWL.
- [bleep]. I MEAN, PARDON.
- TRY TO AVOID PROFANITIES OR--
- OH.
- THAT'’S HARD FOR US.
- INAPPROPRIATE TOPICS.
- LIKE WHAT?
- LIKE POLITICS AND RELIGION?
- YOU PEE TOWN VIDEO.
- CAN I SEE?
- I HAVEN'’T SEEN.
- I DIDN'’T.
- OH. [laughs]
- OH.
- GIVE IT UP.
JOEY DECIDED TO SHOW US A VIDEO
OF HIM POUTING ON A COUCH
LIKE THIS,
WHILE AN ORGY'’S
GOING ON BEHIND HIM.
Nicole: I'’M DYING.
- DON'’T TOUCH ANYTHING.
- HE WENT TO BEAR WEEK.
AND OF COURSE EVERYBODY
HAS SEX WITH EACH OTHER.
- MY GOD, THAT ONE PART.
- I KNOW.
LIKE, WENT IN.
- YEAH.
- THAT'’S NOT PROPER TEA TALK.
NOT PROPER TEA TALK.
- I'’M SWEATING. SWEATING.
- I THINK WE SHOULD PUT--
- AND HE'’S DONE.
- IT AWAY.
- WE'’RE GETTING YELLED AT AGAIN.
- I'’M ACTUALLY A LITTLE
CONCERNED THAT WE'’RE GOING
TO GET KICKED OUT OF HERE
BECAUSE WE ARE
FAR FROM PROPER
AND WE'’RE ASS[bleep].
- OH, I'’M JUST A LITTLE HOT.
Jenni: MM-HMM.
- WHOO!
- THERE YOU GO, GIRL.
- COME ON, YOU'’RE RUINING
THE WHOLE SCENARIO.
- I GOT TO AIR IT OUT
A LITTLE BIT.
WHOO-HOO.
- I THINK YOU BEST
PUT IT BACK ON.
PUT IT BACK UP.
- COVER YOUR BOSOMS.
- YES.
- OH.
- BRING IT UP, THAT'’S IT.
- COVER YOUR BREASTICLES.
- HAVE YOU BEEN TO A TEA BEFORE?
- WE'’VE BEEN
TO A TEA DANCE BEFORE.
THAT'’S A LITTLE BIT
DIFFERENT IN OUR CULTURE.
A TEA DANCE IS AN AFTERNOON
DANCE PARTY
WITH LOTS OF ALCOHOL
AND SHIRTLESS MEN.
- I THOUGHT
YOU MEANT TEA BAGGING.
- NO, I'’VE HAD THAT AS WELL,
BUT THAT'’S IN THE EVENING.
- THAT'’S SOMETHING
MUCH DIFFERENT.
- WHAT'’S THAT, AGAIN?
WHERE DO YOU PUT THEM?
- ON YOUR FACE.
- THAT'’S NOT PROPER TEA TALK.
NOT PROPER TEA TALK.
- THIS IS A LITTLE GAME WE LIKE
TO PLAY IN THE GAY COMMUNITY.
OKAY, GIRL, ASSUME THE POSITION.
PUT IT IN YOUR MOUTH.
CHEW IT, NOW SWALLOW.
SEE?
- WE'’LL HAVE TO ASK YOU
TO RETURN TO YOUR SEAT.
- SLUTS.
- YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
- PLEASE, DON'’T DO
ANY MORE OF THOSE.
- I'’M SORRY.
- WE WOULD NOT FIT IN,
IN THE VICTORIAN SOCIETY.
I FEEL LIKE WE WOULD BE
THE DRUNK, AND THE WHORE.
- I WAS GOING TO SAY
THE SAME THING.
WHO'’S THE DRUNK
AND WHO'’S THE WHORE?
- I'’M THE DRUNK,
YOU'’RE THE WHORE.
- OH, COOL.
- YOU GOT FAKE BOOBS, SO.
- THIS IS A LOT OF WORK.
- WHAT?
- BEING PROPER.
- I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO POOP.
- NOT PROPER TEA TALK.
- I HAVE AN IDEA
WHAT WE COULD DO TODAY.
- WHAT?
- I WAS THINKING,
FOR OUR NEW HOUSE,
SINCE WE WANT TO DO GARDENS
AND STUFF...
- YEAH.
- WHY DON'’T WE PRACTICE HERE?
AND IF WE MESS UP,
WE MESS UP AND IT'’S HERE.
- THE ONLY BAD THING ABOUT
A GARDEN IS MAINTAINING IT.
YOU'’VE NEVER SLAVED IN THERE.
I'’VE DONE IT FOR YEARS.
- I USED TO GARDEN WITH MY MOM.
IT'’S GARDEN WARS.
- LET'’S START THIS [bleep]
- LET'’S GO GET OUR GARDEN ON.
- OKAY.
NICOLE AND I ARE GOING
TO MAKE TWO SEPARATE GARDENS.
WE'’RE GOING TO HAVE
A LITTLE GARDEN WAR.
- GARDEN WARS,
2014.
- AND WE'’RE GOING TO SEE
WHOSE GARDEN IS BETTER.
- IT'’S A COMPETITION.
WE'’RE NOT FRIENDS.
- AT GARDEN WARS, YOU
DON'’T TALK ABOUT GARDEN WARS.
- YEAH, AND AT GARDEN WARS,
WE HAVE TO KISS EACH OTHER.
- HOPE YOUR EYELASHES DON'’T
FALL OFF WHILE WE'’RE DIGGING.
- YOU'’RE SO ANNOYING.
- HELLO.
HEY.
- CARLY'’S HERE!
BABE, YOU READY?
WE'’RE GOING TO GO GET
SOME FLOWERS AND VEGETABLES.
- OKAY.
Jionni: GARDEN WARS.
- IT'’S ON LIKE DONKEY KONG.
I'’M DOING FRUIT, YOU DO VEGGIES.
- DON'’T COME LOOKING FOR ME--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- DON'’T COME LOOKING FOR YOU?
- WHY DID YOU JUST DO THAT
WHILE I WAS TALKING?
- '’CAUSE YOU, LIKE, STUTTERED.
- NO, I DIDN'’T.
DON'’T FOLLOW ME AND SAY, "OH,
LET ME SEE WHAT HE'’S GETTING."
- I DON'’T WANT TO FOLLOW YOU.
WE'’RE NOT FRIENDS RIGHT NOW.
OH, I REALLY HAVE TO POOP.
SHOULD I HOLD IT?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- OOH, I'’M GOING TO USE THIS.
- WHY DO YOU GET THE BIG ONE?
- YOU WANT THE BIG ONE?
- YEAH.
- ACTUALLY, NO. IT'’S A WAR.
- SEE YOU, LOSER.
- I THINK I'’M GOING TO WIN.
NICOLE'’S PREGNANT,
SHE'’S SLACKING, AND...
- THAT'’S SO RUDE.
- I THINK I'’M GOING TO TAKE...
- LIKE, THAT'’S YOUR BABY.
- THE W.
- WHAT YOU JUST SAID
SOUNDED VERY RUDE.
- OH, '’CAUSE IT'’S GARDEN WARS.
- A BUTTERFLY.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I THINK THERE'’S SPIDERS.
STAY ON YOUR SIDE.
- WHAT?
- THIS IS MY SIDE.
- COME ON.
- TWO, FOUR, WHAT'’S THE BLACK?
- OH!
- I SHOULD BE A GARDENIST.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- SQUIRREL!
- ARE THESE GOOD FLOWERS
FOR A GARDEN?
- NO CHEATING.
JIONNI'’S CHEATING.
HE'’S ASKING THIS GIRL...
- I'’M ASKING
THE PROFESSIONAL GARDENER...
- WHAT FLOWERS ARE BETTER
IN THE SUN.
- I'’M ASKING
THE PROFESSIONAL GARDENER.
- YEAH, BUT ON THE WAY THERE
I SAID YOU CAN'’T ASK
THE FLORIST.
- FROM WHAT I SEE YOU HAVE--
YOU DEFINITELY
SHOULD BE ASKING QUESTIONS.
I'’M READY.
- YOU DON'’T REALLY HAVE A THEME.
WHAT'’S YOUR THEME?
- HOW DO I NOT HAVE A THEME?
THE THEME IS THIS.
- THE COLORS. I LIKE--
- THIS IS CALLED PANDORA.
- YOU'’RE NOT FROM AVATAR.
- THIS IS FOR AVATARS.
THIS IS AN ALIEN GARDEN.
- OKAY, WELL YOU DO YOUR GARDEN,
I'’LL DO MINE.
- OKAY.
I FEEL LIKE I...
- I DEFINITELY PICKED OUT...
both: THE BETTER FLOWERS--
- YOU HAD--
THEY WEREN'’T EVEN FLOWERS.
- THEY'’RE FLOWERS.
- THEY WERE LEAVES.
- THEY WERE FLOWERS.
- OKAY.
LET'’S SEE HOW GOOD
YOU MAKE A GARDEN.
- OKAY, I'’M NOT SCARED.
- YOU SHOULD BE SCARED.
WHAT DID I GET?
- THOSE ARE MINE.
JUST CARRY YOURS.
- THOSE ARE NOT.
- THOSE ARE MINE.
- NOPE.
- DON'’T MESS WITH ME.
both: I'’M GOING
TO WIN GARDEN WARS.
- I'’M GOING TO WIN GARDEN WARS.
- I KNOW I'’M GOING TO WIN
GARDEN WARS.
SO, I DON'’T GOT TO KEEP
SHOUTING IT TO MYSELF.
- I'’M GOING TO WIN GARDEN WARS!
- KILLED IT.
- NO, I DIDN'’T.
- YEAH, YOU DID.
DO YOU WANT THEM RIGHT NEXT
TO EACH OTHER OR SPREAD OUT?
- SPREAD OUT.
I DON'’T WANT MY FLOWERS TOUCHING
YOUR UGLY FLOWERS.
WHAT?
- THIS IS GOING TO BE
A TOUGH COMPETITION.
I CAN FEEL IT ALREADY.
- I HAVE A DISADVANTAGE HERE,
I'’M PREGNANT.
LOSER.
[laughs]
- I SAW THAT.
YOU CHEATED.
- I DIDN'’T TOUCH YOUR PLANTS.
- OH, NO?
I WATCHED YOU GO TO MY PLANT
AND KNOCK IT OVER.
- OH, WHEN IT WAS
OUT OF THE CAR, YEAH. I DID.
- WHY DID YOU--
MAYBE NEXT YEAR, LOSER.
- YOU'’RE NOT A VERY NICE PERSON.
- THIS IS GARDEN WARS.
I'’M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE NICE.
THANKS.
- CAN'’T DO GARDEN WARS
WITHOUT A HAT.
BLOCK THE SUN.
[blows raspberry]
- [burps]
- WHOO!
SET FOR FAILURE.
- NEED HELP?
- NO.
I'’M NOT GOOD WITH DIRECTIONS,
BUT I'’M GOOD WHEN I COPY.
THAT'’S HOW I PASSED HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, THIS IS TOO MUCH WORK.
- DON'’T CRY OVER IT,
YOU LITTLE BABY.
THIS IS GARDEN WARS.
WE DON'’T GET BREAKS.
- YOU LOOK LIKE MY GRANDPA.
- YEAH, THAT A GIRL.
- DOES THIS TURN YOU ON?
- EW.
- SEE, MAMA CAN GARDEN.
- YOUR CRACK IS SWEATING.
- MY CRACK'’S SWEATING?
- YEAH.
- I'’M PREGNANT.
- EW.
- IT'’S JUST CRAZY TO THINK,
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
A FEW YEARS AGO
WE WERE DOWN AT THE SHORE
WITH OUR ROOMIES,
GETTING WASTED
AND GOING CRAZY...
[dance music]
♪
TO NOW, MAKING A GARDEN.
IT'’S JUST--IT'’S WEIRD,
BUT I LOVE IT.
- ALL MY FLOWER HEADS DIED.
- MAKE IT WORK.
- I GOT TOO HIGH OF PLANTS.
- NOT MY PROBLEM.
- BUT I'’M WORKING WITH IT.
NEED TO START
WATERING THESE GUYS.
- OH, NO!
- WELCOME TO MY WORLD.
DRINK UP, LADIES.
ALL RIGHT, I THINK I LIKE THAT.
THINK WE GOT A WINNER,
CHICKEN DINNER.
- YOU'’RE NOT A WINNER.
- THANKS, THAT WAS NICE,
JACKASS.
- FABULOUS, ABSOLUTELY FABULOUS.
WE HAVE TWO
TOTALLY DIFFERENT GARDENS.
I'’M REALLY HAPPY WITH MY GARDEN.
IT LOOKS LIKE
A PANDORA ALIEN GARDEN.
AND I HAVE A SQUIRREL
AND A DUCK-DUCK.
- MINE LOOKS LIKE AN AWESOME...
- GRANDPA.
- FLOWER GARDEN,
AND MY GRANDMOTHER
WOULD BE VERY PROUD OF ME.
- ALIENS WOULD BE PROUD OF ME.
- YEAH, '’CAUSE IT'’S UGLY.
- IT'’S VERY CLUTTERED.
- SHUT UP!
- GARDEN WARS!
- LORENZO, ME AND DADDY
ARE DOING A GARDEN CONTEST.
GARDEN WARS.
- FOR FLOWERS.
- FOR FLOWERS, GO,
YOU KNOW, FLOWERS?
I DEFINITELY WANT LORENZO
TO JUDGE THE GARDEN WARS
BECAUSE LAST SUMMER
HE JUDGED OUR PIRATE DRAWING
AND HE PICKED JIONNI.
THIS IS MOMMY'’S.
- YOU GO ON THAT SIDE.
- NO.
- SEE WHO HE GOES TO.
- THIS IS MOMMY'’S.
THAT'’S DADDY'’S.
- WHO'’S DO YOU WANT FOR PIN
THE PATCH ON THE PIRATE?
- WHOSE DO YOU LIKE?
- MINE OR MOMMY'’S?
- LORENZO, LOOK,
YOU'’RE NOT EVEN LOOKING.
- MINE OR MOMMY'’S.
- COME HERE, COME HERE.
DON'’T GO OVER THERE.
- COME ON.
YES! YES! YES!
- YOU DON'’T LIKE MOMMY'’S?
- YES!
- YOU HAVE TO BE A JUDGE.
- I WANT TO JUDGE.
- YOU'’RE GOING TO STAND
IN THE MIDDLE,
AND WE'’RE GOING TO SAY,
"WHOSE DO YOU LIKE BETTER,
MAMA'’S OR DADA'’S?"
- MM, MAMA.
- LORENZO, WE'’RE GOING TO SAY,
"WHOSE DO YOU LIKE BETTER?"
MAMA'’S OR DADA'’S?
- MM, DADA.
- IT'’S 50-50, HE'’LL SAY ANYBODY.
- YOU GETTING NERVOUS?
YOU'’RE ALL OF THE SUDDEN
GETTING NERVOUS.
- OKAY, I'’M GOING
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
- LORENZO, YOU GOT TO LISTEN,
OKAY?
WHEN I SAY,
"WHOSE FLOWERS DO YOU LIKE,
MAMA'’S OR DADA'’S?"
YOU GOT TO COME TO DADA, OKAY?
DON'’T TELL MOM I SAID THAT.
AND IF YOU DO THAT
YOU GET AN ICE POP.
- YOU GET AN ICE POP.
- OKAY?
PINKY SWEAR?
GOOD JOB.
WHO'’S GOING TO WIN THE CONTEST?
- DADA.
- YES.
- THERE YOU GO.
- YES. THE GARDEN WAR RULES?
THERE ARE NO RULES.
I CAN'’T LOSE.
SOMEONE'’S LISTENING.
- ALL RIGHT, LORENZO.
IT'’S TIME TO JUDGE.
- REMEMBER WHAT I TOLD YOU.
- LORENZO.
- LORENZO, WHOSE FLOWERS
DO YOU LIKE BETTER?
MAMA'’S OR DADA'’S?
COME TO WHOSE YOU LIKE BETTER.
- COME HERE, BABY.
COME ON! COME ON!
- LORENZO, LORENZO.
LOOK, LOOK AT THE COOL COLORS.
LOOK AT THE FOOTBALL.
- LORENZO, THE SQUIRREL.
LORENZO, THE DUCK.
- THE FOOTBALL, COME HERE,
LORENZO.
- QUACK, QUACK. COME ON LORENZO,
LET'’S DO BUBBLES.
- COME ON, WANT AN ICE POP?
- LET'’S DO BUBBLES.
- YOU WANT AN ICE POP?
- LORENZO, LET'’S DO BUBBLES.
- LORENZO, WANT AN ICE POP?
WANT AN ICE POP? COME HERE.
- LORENZO, BUBBLES.
- COME HERE.
- LORENZO, SQUIRREL.
- ICE POP, ICE POP.
[screams]
LORENZO, ICE POP.
NO!
- YAY, DADA!
LORENZO PICKED MOMMY.
- IF I HAD A BIG SQUIRREL TOO,
I THINK I WOULD'’VE WON.
- I WIN.
GOOD JOB, DADA,
YOU PICKED THE RIGHT CHOICE.
- GOOD EFFORT.
[makes raspberry]
- [laughs] YOU'’RE A SORE LOSER.
THAT'’S SAD.
OH, WELL.
- WHAT? NOW YOU LIKE MINE?
WHERE WERE YOU A MINUTE AGO?
[Going to the Sun'’s
Alone in the Same Room]
- ♪ HAVE I TURNED A BLIND EYE,
MAYBE A DEAF EAR ♪
- GUESS WHAT I'’M DOING TODAY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- BRIDESMAID SHOPPING!
- REALLY?
- UH-HUH.
TODAY I'’M GOING TO DINNER
WITH MY BRIDESMAIDS
AND THEN WE'’RE GOING TO GO
TRY ON BRIDESMAID DRESSES.
JENNI'’S GOING TO COME WITH ME.
- OH, REALLY?
WELL, WHILE YOU'’RE DOING THAT--
- I'’M GOING TO MAKE HER WEAR
REALLY UGLY DRESSES.
- LIKE FOOTBALL PADDED?
- UH-HUH.
A DRESS THAT MAKES HER LOOK FAT,
'’CAUSE SHE'’S SO SKINNY.
I DEFINITELY WANT TO PLAY
A LITTLE JOKE ON MY GIRLS,
AND PUT THEM IN HIDEOUS,
DISGUSTING DRESSES
SO THEY CAN LOOK GROSS,
AND I CAN FEEL BETTER
ABOUT MYSELF.
MY FOOD.
CAN'’T EVEN FIT BEHIND YOU.
I'’M SO FAT!
[phone ringing]
- GOOD AFTERNOON,
BRIDAL REFLECTIONS.
THIS IS JESSICA,
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- HI, IT'’S NICOLE POLIZZI.
- HEY, NICOLE, HOW ARE YOU?
- I'’M CALLING BRIDAL REFLECTIONS
SO THEY KNOW EXACTLY WHAT I WANT
TO DO FOR THE BRIDAL FITTING.
OBVIOUSLY TRY ON THE REAL DRESS
THAT I GOT FOR THE BRIDESMAIDS,
BUT I ALSO WANT
TO PRANK THEM AND PUT THEM
IN REALLY, REALLY UGLY DRESSES.
- I'’LL PICK OUT,
LIKE, THE UGLIEST ONES
I THINK THAT WE HAVE
AND THEN I'’LL LET YOU UH,
HAVE THE DECIDING UH, FACTOR
AND WORD ON THAT, OKAY?
- OKAY, PERFECT.
- I'’M REALLY EXCITED
TO SEE THE GIRLS,
AND I'’M REALLY EXCITED
TO TRY ON A DRESS.
BUT YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE
I EAT LIGHT, BECAUSE--
- YOU'’LL BE FINE.
EAT WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU SHOULD GET A MARGARITA,
LIKE YOU'’VE BEEN CRAVING.
YOU'’VE BEEN CRAVING A MARGARITA
THIS WHOLE TIME.
- [burps] NO, JUST TEQUILA.
- THEN GET TEQUILA.
- IT'’S NOT LIKE I WOULD DRINK
LIKE THE OLD DAYS, ANYWAYS.
- IF I COULD DRINK, I WOULD HAVE
A NICE GLASS OF RED WINE.
- MM, RIGHT, LIKE HEY!
- RED GETS ME CHILL DRUNK.
- YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT PASSING OUT...
- AND HORNY.
- I AM PETRIFIED OF HAVING SEX.
- OH, YEAH.
I DIDN'’T HAVE SEX '’TILL,
LIKE, TWO, THREE MONTHS AFTER.
SEX AFTER GIVING BIRTH HURTS.
AND IT'’S REALLY NEVER
THE SAME AGAIN.
- NO.
- YEAH.
- AND NOT IN A GOOD WAY.
- NOT IN A GOOD WAY.
WHOO!
- [laughs]
HELLO, LADIES.
ALL: HI.
- HEY, GIRL.
- JENNI, YOU LOOK PHENOMENAL.
- THANK YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I'’M GLAD A MAJORITY
OF THE SWELLING WENT DOWN.
- RIGHT HERE?
WE GET TO CITY CELLAR
AND AMY, DEENA,
AND SAM ARE ALREADY HERE.
- I'’M JUST STUPID EXCITED
THAT I CAN HAVE A DRINK.
- GET YOUR MARGARITA.
- MM.
I'’VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS MARGARITA
FOR, LIKE, A YEAR.
- OH, YOU CAN DRINK NOW.
- YEAH.
I'’M GOING TO HAVE
THE ULTIMATE MARGARITA.
- YEAH!
- LOOKS GOOD.
- I'’M DRIVING.
- I WAITED TEN MONTHS FOR THIS.
IT'’S NOT EVEN
THAT I MISS GETTING DRUNK.
I JUST MISS THE FACT THAT,
LIKE--
I JUST DON'’T LIKE WHEN SOMEONE
SAYS YOU CAN'’T DO SOMETHING.
- OH.
- THAT LOOKS SO GOOD.
- THANK YOU.
- THAT'’S WHAT PISSES ME OFF.
- THEN YOU WANT TO DO IT, YEAH.
- SO, CHEERS.
all: CHEERS.
- TO WEDDINGS.
- BABIES AND WEDDINGS!
- BABIES AND WEDDINGS.
- YAY.
CHEERS TO JENNI'’S DRINK.
- CHEERS TO JENNI.
- COOL.
MY FIRST MARGARITA
IS REALLY STRONG.
AND REALLY SALTY.
- WINE IS SO MUCH MORE SMOOTH.
- HUH?
- YOU SHOULD'’VE JUST WENT
WITH, LIKE, WINE.
- I'’M HAVING LIKE FOUR SIPS
AND I'’M ALREADY DRUNK.
- AND YOU'’RE BOMBED.
- YEAH.
- DRINK.
[laughs]
- ARE YOU GOING TO DO
THAT EVERY SIP?
- IT'’S BEEN A WHILE.
ONE MORE.
- OH, SHE'’S GOING TO GET BOMBED.
- SHE'’S GOING TO BE ROLLING
AROUND IN THE DRESS PLACE.
- JELLY.
- MY EYES ARE [bleep] CROSSING.
- SHOW ME ALL THE PICTURES.
SHOW ME ALL THE PICTURES,
JENNI.
- HERE'’S A COUPLE.
- AW.
- WAIT, SHE WAS SLEEPING
ON THE SIDE OF HER?
- SHE'’S SUCH A LITTLE,
LIKE, A LITTLE PEA.
- SHE KIND OF LOOKS LIKE YOU,
HERE.
- I KNOW, SHE'’S GETTING
TO LOOK LIKE ME.
- STARTING TO.
- HOW WAS IT?
- IT'’S NOT THAT BAD.
LOOK, IT'’S ALREADY OVER WITH.
- YOU SAID IT WASN'’T BAD.
DID YOU GET THE DRUGS?
- MY LABOR WAS
[bleep] GOD AWFUL.
I FELT EVERYTHING.
- THE DRUGS DIDN'’T WORK?
- SHE FELT HER VAGINA RIP.
- OH, MY GOD.
BUT THAT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
- HER HEAD WAS OUT, LIKE,
POKING WHEN MY DOCTOR WALKED IN.
RIPPED RIGHT THROUGH,
LIKE SHE CAME OUT,
LIKE A [bleep],
LIKE, WATERSLIDE PARK RIDE.
LIKE, JUST FLEW OUT OF ME.
I'’M DRUNK.
I AM DRUNK. I'’M HONESTLY
REALLY DRUNK RIGHT NOW.
I'’M, LIKE, DIZZY.
- ARE YOU DRUNK?
- YEAH.
- LET'’S DO THE WHOLE THING.
LET'’S GET DRUNK TONIGHT.
- WOW, I NEED TO EAT
'’CAUSE THE ROOM'’S SPINNING.
I THOUGHT ABOUT GETTING
THE QUINOA.
- I'’M GETTING THAT ONE, TOO.
- YEAH, THAT'’S WHAT I'’M GETTING.
- WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT IS IT CALLED?
- QUINOA.
- QUINOA?
- YEAH.
- OH, WAIT.
IS THAT LIKE ASIAN FUSION?
- NO, IT'’S LIKE RICE.
- OH, OKAY.
OH, NO. NO, NO, NO,
I DON'’T WANT THAT.
"KENNY?" WHAT IS IT CALLED?
- SHE GOES,
"IS IT ASIAN FUSION?"
'’CAUSE WE'’RE LIKE, QUINOA.
- OH.
IT'’S LIKE COUSCOUS.
- OH, I DON'’T EAT THAT.
- RIGHT, IT LOOKS LIKE THAT.
IT'’S LIKE A PROTEIN, YEAH.
OH, ASIAN FUSION?
- BUT DOESN'’T IT SOUND IT?
- ASIAN FUSION IS--I DON'’T KNOW.
YOU FUSE
A LOT OF ASIANS TOGETHER.
I DON'’T [bleep] KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU?
QUINOA?
- I'’M GOING TO ASK
IF I CAN GET THAT WITH LETTUCE.
- OH, MY GOD.
- ONLY YOU.
FINALLY.
- WE MADE IT!
- HI.
- YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- SO DO YOU.
- HI.
- HELLO.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- I'’M GLAD YOU MADE IT.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU LOOK FABULOUS.
- WHY, THANK YOU.
- LIKE MY BOOBS?
- THEY'’RE HUGE.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU GUYS
THINK THESE DRESSES LOOK LIKE?
- THEY'’RE GATSBYISH.
- GATSBYISH? OKAY.
- WHAT COLOR?
- I'’M NOT TELLING.
I'’M DOING SOMETHING CUTE.
I CAN'’T WAIT FOR THE BRIDESMAIDS
TO SEE THE DRESSES,
BECAUSE I'’M GOING TO PUT THEM
IN HIDEOUS ONES,
AND THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THEY'’RE IN FOR.
ARE YOU GUYS
READY TO TRY ON DRESSES?
- YES!
- LET'’S GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
THAT WAS SO FUN.
WHY ARE YOU WALKING LIKE THAT?
- BECAUSE I'’M ABOUT
TO FALL OVER.
- ARE YOU DRUNK?
- LITTLE BIT.
- YOU SHOULD PUT
YOUR BALLET FLATS ON.
- [bleep] YOU. WHAT, AM I REALLY
WALKING THAT BAD?
- YEAH.
- IT'’S BEEN A YEAR,
AND I'’M EXTREMELY--
- YOU'’RE BOMBED.
- I'’M A LITTLE DRUNK.
- THIS EPISODE
OF SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- CONTINUES NOW.
- THIS IS IT, KIDS.
SO WE WALK
INTO BRIDAL REFLECTIONS,
AND I'’M REALLY EXCITED
TO SHOW THE GIRLS THE DRESSES.
LOOK AT ALL THE NICE DRESSES.
SO PRETTY.
- NICOLE, YOU WANT
TO COME WITH ME?
- OH, YEAH.
- WITH--THERE'’S POOP STAIN.
- IT'’S BROWNIES.
JESSICA'’S BRINGING ME
IN THE BACK
TO SHOW ME THE UGLY DRESSES
THAT SHE GOT
FOR THE BRIDESMAIDS.
OH, MY GOD. THIS IS HIDEOUS.
ABSOLUTELY [bleep] DISGUSTING
- AND THEN THERE'’S
THIS REALLY BIG, TACKY ONE.
- OH, THAT'’S LIKE A PROM.
I DEFINITELY WANT JENNI
TO TRY THIS ON.
THE DRESSES LOOK GREAT.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO LOVE THEM.
ALL RIGHT, I HAVE
YOUR DRESS HERE. GO TRY IT ON.
COME ON, TRY THIS BAD BOY ON.
- WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- JUST, PLEASE?
OKAY? IT'’S GORGEOUS.
- IT'’S MORGEOUS.
- I GOT A LINEUP OVER HERE.
- I CAN'’T GET IT OVER MY ASS.
WHOA.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- [laughs]
- TRY THEM ON.
- IT DOESN'’T EVEN FIT.
- EW, NICOLE.
THIS IS MORE LIKE DEENA.
CAN WE TRADE?
- HOW BAD ARE YOURS?
- I FEEL LIKE I LOOK
LIKE AN APRON.
- THIS IS HORRIBLE.
- GOD, I STINK.
- I LOOK LIKE AN OLD LADY.
- OKAY, RUNWAY SHOW!
OH, MY GOD.
- HOW DO YOU--
HOW DO YOU WORK IT IN THIS?
- YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
- I FEEL SO DUMPY RIGHT NOW.
NICOLE PUT ME IN A [bleep]
FRUMPY ASS DRESS RIGHT NOW.
I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT GAME SHE'’S PLAYING,
BUT I LOOK LIKE A LESBIAN
THAT HASN'’T COME OUT
OF THE CLOSET YET
THAT'’S AT PROM.
- YOU LOOK GREAT.
[all laugh]
OKAY, FRANKIE!
- OOH!
[imitate retching]
THAT'’S A THROW UP DRESS.
COME ON, DEENA!
WHOA!
[all laugh]
- THIS IS NOT GATSBY.
THIS IS TRASHY.
- OKAY, SAMMY!
- SAMMY LOOKS LIKE
A [bleep] BALLERINA.
IT'’S GROSS.
- OOH!
- AND MAID OF HONOR STEPHANIE.
YAY! YAY! YAY!
WHICH ONE WOULD YOU GUYS
LOVE TO WEAR AT MY WEDDING?
- HOW ABOUT THIS?
- I DEFINITELY THINK THE GIRLS
ARE A LITTLE DISAPPOINTED
WITH THE BRIDESMAID'’S DRESSES.
- I FEEL LIKE THESE DRESSES
DON'’T FEEL VERY GATSBY.
THEY FEEL LIKE PROM NIGHT
DUMPSTER BABY.
- ALL THESE DRESSES ARE REALLY,
REALLY CUTE, I THINK.
- ARE THEY?
- THEY'’RE ALL ADORABLE.
BUT I ACTUALLY
HAVE YOUR REAL DRESSES HERE.
- OH, YOU DO?
- YES.
- THANK GOD.
- [clapping] YAY!
DO YOU GUYS LOVE IT?
- I LOVE IT.
- ISN'’T IT FLATTERING?
- IT'’S VERY FLATTERING.
- I LOVE IT.
I LOVE THAT DRESS, RIGHT?
AND IT JUST MAKES YOU
LOOK LIKE--
- TIGHT.
- SO MUCH BETTER
THAN MY MUSTARD.
- THE GOWN IS STUNNING.
- IT LOOKS GOOD ON ANYBODY,
IT'’S JUST...
- IT'’S VERY GATSBY.
- IT'’S SWEETHEART CUT,
IT'’S TIGHT
TO SHOW EVERYBODY'’S CURVES,
'’CAUSE EVERYBODY'’S DIFFERENT.
AND THEN IT COMES OUT,
KIND OF LIKE A MERMAID DRESS,
ESPECIALLY WITH THE BOW.
- MM-HMM.
- ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU, GUYS,
FOR COMING. I LOVE YOU ALL.
- THANK YOU.
- GROUP HUG.
- BYE.
- THANK YOU.
- I CAN'’T WAIT TO GET MARRIED.
- YAY!
- WHOO!
- I'’M SO GLAD
ALL MY GIRLS CAME OUT,
AND THEY APPROVED OF THE DRESS,
AND NOW WE HAVE ANOTHER THING
OFF OF OUR WEDDING LIST.
WE'’RE ONE STEP CLOSER,
AND I AM READY
TO BE MRS. LAVALLE.
all: GO, GATSBY WEDDING!
- [laughs]
- YAY!
- ARE YOU EXCITED, NOW?
- NEXT TIME ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- I'’VE NEVER SEEN A BABY
EAT THAT MUCH EVER.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR MAYBE YOU.
[laughter]
- I HAD ROLLS.
- LIKE A LITTLE SUMO WRESTLER.
- WE GOT TO LEAVE TONIGHT.
IT WAS AN AWESOME SUMMER.
NOW IT'’S TIME TO GO BACK
TO THE BASEMENT.
MUAH.
all: AW.
- GOT A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
♪ BABY JESUS
- OH, MY GOD.