[JWOWW]
Previously on...
[Snooki]
Snooki &amp; JWOWW.
[Jionni]
All right, we'’re coming in.
We'’re moving in tonight, right?
[Jionni]
We'’re sleeping there?
[man on phone]
No, not yet.
[bleep] CO.
How long'’s that take?
[man on phone]
Two weeks away,
max, you guys'’ll be in.
[Snooki]
I'’m in labor, and I need to be
at the hospital right now.
I can'’t move.
- All right.
- I can'’t move.
- It'’s almost over.
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I don'’t care ♪
♪ I love it
♪ I don'’t care ♪
I love it ♪
♪I don'’t care ♪
♪ I love it
♪
♪ I don'’t care ♪
- Ow.
- I need to start your IV
right away if you'’re gonna
want your epidural.
Ow.
They got to get out.
Get out.
- Come on.
- Ow.
[Snooki moans]
[nurse]
When did these contractions
start getting really bad,
Nicole?
[Jionni]
At least an hour of this.
[Snooki crying]
- Where'’s the epidural?
- It'’s coming.
[Snooki]
I can'’t do this much longer.
[nurse]
I know Dr. Russo'’s
on his way in.
[Snooki]
Oh!
Ow.
[Snooki moans]
[Snooki]
I can'’t do this.
[nurse]
Yes, you can.
[Snooki]
No more kids.
- Okay.
- I'’m not kidding.
[Jionni]
All right.
[Snooki]
I'’m not doing this again.
[nurse]
Don'’t start.
They'’re here, the anesthetists.
[Jionni]
There you go.
- Save me.
- Hello.
Thank [bleep] God, you know,
somebody'’s gonna save me
from this pain.
[nurse]
You'’re getting meds
now continuously,
okay, until you deliver.
- Yes.
- Hit this button here.
[nurse]
You can hit this
as often as you like for extra.
- Thank you.
- If you need it.
[button beeping]
Hey.
Once Nicole got the epidural,
she was feeling so much better,
and she just--she looks better.
[Jionni]
She'’s not in that horrible pain.
How you feeling?
[Snooki]
It'’s getting there,
but I still feel things.
- Do you feel that?
- Yes.
Yes.
[button beeping]
Nicole'’s definitely overdosing
on the button here.
[beeps]
I don'’t know if
she realizes that at one point,
it kind of just stops, because
if that was the case,
people would
probably not wake up.
Yeah.
Have you been
using your button?
Yeah.
Yeah, she keeps pressing it.
[beeping]
[Jionni]
Does it mean it'’s coming in?
[nurse]
No.
It times out after a while.
- But mentally, that helps me.
- But mentally, yes.
Well, you can press away.
[Snooki]
Exactly.
One more for good luck.
[beeps]
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
You'’re welcome.
Would you adopt?
Why you asking me that
right now?
I don'’t know
if I can do this again.
[Snooki]
The pain was a good eight, nine.
Maybe I'’ll do one more.
[Jionni]
No, this is it.
I'’m done.
I'’m tying my knots.
[Jionni]
I want to have two kids first,
and--
You said at least three.
All right, we'’ll go with--
let'’s have our second child
first,
and then we'’ll think about two.
But we have all these rooms
in our new house.
We have to fill them up.
Guests.
"Guests?"
Shut--
I feel like I'’m gonna poop.
That'’s a good thing.
No, like, when I push.
I think I'’m gonna poop,
'’cause I ate a lot.
What'’d you eat?
Like, two grilled cheeses.
[Jionni]
Oh, boy.
Uh-oh.
Ooh.
- I'’m so sorry if I poop.
- We'’re in trouble.
[Jionni]
We'’re in trouble.
Two grilled cheese sandwiches.
Grilled cheeses.
And with cheese, I--you know,
you figure you'’re gonna poop.
What if you see it?
[Jionni]
I'’ll be back here.
What if it, like, touches her?
- Touches who?
- The baby.
They--they wash her off.
My [bleep] gross.
- You know it.
- That'’s true.
I have to flush five times.
[Snooki]
Can you just hold my hand?
I'’m nervous, and I'’m scared.
[woman]
All right.
[Snooki]
What are you doing here?
I couldn'’t stay away.
[Snooki]
Janis comes, and I feel bad
because it'’s, like,
2:00, 3:00 in the morning.
How you doing?
- Good.
- Better?
I got the...epidural,
so I feel a lot better.
Okay, you'’re happier now.
I was seven centimeters.
Get--
Seven?
Oh, my god.
I'’ll probably have her in,
like, an hour.
Okay, good.
Why didn'’t you go back to bed?
How was I gonna
go back to bed?
- You got to be kidding.
- Are you a nervous wreck?
I'’m a nervous wreck, yeah.
[Snooki]
It'’s nice to see Janis
because, you know,
kind of makes me more calm,
just seeing people I know.
All right,
I'’ll just be out here,
waiting for your mom and dad.
[Janis]
They'’re on their way, okay?
Stop.
That'’s how I know
I'’m getting nervous.
I know, stop.
[Snooki]
How far'’s my mom?
Um...
Want me to ask her?
Yeah.
I want my mommy.
You don'’t know what to expect.
You don'’t know
what'’s gonna happen.
You'’re scared
something bad'’s gonna happen.
You don'’t know the pain
that you'’re gonna feel.
It'’s a very scary feeling.
So right now,
I just want my mommy.
Uh-oh, I'’m not ready.
I'’m just--let me just examine,
see how--
how far down the baby is,
and we'’ll see.
Okay.
'’Cause maybe
if you don'’t feel him,
we can do it without, you know,
feeling any pain.
[nurse]
Oh, my god,
your baby'’s head is right there.
[Snooki]
I'’m not ready to push, though.
[nurse]
You are ready.
[Snooki]
I don'’t feel it.
[nurse]
You don'’t have to.
It'’s time, guys.
[Snooki]
And I'’m basically there,
ten centimeters,
and it'’s time to push.
[Janis]
They'’re waiting for you.
- This one?
- Yeah.
Nicole?
- Mommy.
- Hi.
[Snooki]
And once my mom
got into the room,
it was time to push.
Thank God that I could have
my mom again by my side.
[Snooki]
Ohh.
I can'’t.
- You'’re okay.
- I can'’t.
[nurse]
So you just
finished a contraction.
[nurse]
Wait for the next contraction,
Nicole.
- Did you just look?
- No, I didn'’t look.
[laughter]
[Snooki]
Did you see her?
[Jionni]
I didn'’t look.
[nurse]
She'’s got dark hair!
[Snooki]
I feel something moving.
[nurse]
Keep coming.
I do my first push,
and I feel her head
just coming out,
and I just feel my vagina,
like, expand and I'’m like,
"Oh, my God, ew."
[nurse]
Okay, good, three, four,
here we go.
- [moans]
- Stop pushing now.
[Dr. Russo]
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Baby'’s head'’s out.
I push again, and Giovanna'’s,
like, butt comes out,
and then I push one more time,
and Giovanna'’s out.
[baby crying]
There she is.
- There she is.
Congratulations.
Yeah, same here.
- Oh.
- You did fantastic.
[nurse]
She'’s too much.
[Dr. Russo]
A lot of hair.
- Yes.
- A lot of hair.
And I'’m like, "Yay."
And I'’m so [bleep] happy.
I love my baby.
I love my kids.
I'’m happy.
I love you.
Mm.
You'’re so pretty.
Giovanna'’s here, and it'’s just--
it makes our family
even more complete,
and she was the missing piece
of the puzzle,
and we just have
an awesome, awesome family.
- Aw.
- Can you see?
- She came out okay?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah?
- Three pushes, boom.
- Really?
- And that'’s it.
- Wow.
- Congratulations.
- [laughs]
- Congratulations to you.
- She'’s beautiful.
- She looks like Lorenzo.
- Right?
Yeah.
You know, the excitement
of seeing your daughter
kind of just
overtakes everything.
It just, as soon as you see her,
you'’re just, like,
you know, it'’s awesome.
- Mm-hmm.
- It'’s, like, you know--
it'’s that feeling,
nothing else matters.
Like, everything you--the house,
I forgot about
we'’re building a house.
I forgot about, you know,
us having a wedding.
Like, it was just her.
Yeah, screw the wedding.
We got a little baby.
[Jionni]
So everything else kind of
was second to us,
and she was just, you know,
first.
Now I have two girls
to take care of.
Two princesses.
And a beast.
Make sure no boys
pick you up in the nursery.
- Da.
- What?
I want Mama at the house.
[Jionni]
Do you want to go see mama?
- And--
- You want to see your sister?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Come on, buddy.
Go see your sister.
[Jionni]
I'’m taking Lorenzo back
to the hospital.
Our family'’s gonna
be together for the first time,
and he'’s wearing
his big brother shirt,
and I want Nicole to see Lorenzo
'’cause she definitely
misses him.
[gasps]
I hear Da-Da.
Lorenzo'’s gonna meet his sister
for the first time,
and I'’m a little nervous.
[Snooki]
It'’s like, I don'’t want
to hurt his feelings
because he was my first kid.
[sniffles]
Lorenzo, it'’s mama.
- Come on.
- I just don'’t want to
neglect him.
That'’s--that'’s what I'’m worried
about, honestly,
as a parent of two.
Like, I don'’t know how
I'’m gonna,
like, divvy up my time.
[Snooki]
Lorenzo?
Lorenzo, it'’s Mommy.
[Snooki]
Hi.
Are you a big brother?
- Aww.
- Baby, come here, I missed you.
- Come see Mama.
- He picked you out flowers.
[woman]
Check it out, bud.
[gasps]
Thank you, baby.
[laughs]
- Lorenzo.
- Lorenzo, where'’s sissy?
- Your sister.
- Yeah, that'’s sissy.
- Aww, yeah.
You want to give your sister
a kiss right here?
- Lorenzo, this is sissy.
- Give your sister a kiss.
- Aww, good job, buddy.
- Aww.
This is definitely a moment
I want to cherish forever.
This is your sister.
[Snooki]
I'’m gonna call Jenni.
I haven'’t told her
we gave birth yet.
[phone ringing]
Can you answer that?
It'’s Nicole.
Oh, she'’s Facetiming.
Ooh, I look like [bleep].
Hello.
I'’m so tired.
[JWOWW]
Why?
I just gave birth.
You'’re lying.
Do you want to see her?
[JWOWW]
Yes.
Come over here.
She'’s sleeping right now.
Let me flip this around.
Oh, my god, she really is.
[Roger]
No way.
- Congratulations.
- Do you guys see her?
Congratulations.
[JWOWW]
Oh, my god,
I love that headpiece.
She'’s perfect.
- Right?
- She is.
[JWOWW]
She'’s sleeping nice and snug?
Oh, my God,
look at Jionni sleeping.
[Snooki]
Sorry I didn'’t tell you.
It happened last night, so I'’ve
literally been up for 24 hours,
and I feel insane,
and my butthole hurts.
[laughs]
Roger just made her a tutu.
Oh, a tutu?
Is that Meilani'’s?
[JWOWW]
We actually made that tutu
for Meilani,
and it'’s way too small, so
we'’re gonna give it to Giovanna.
All right, we'’ll take it.
I love you.
I'’m so proud of you.
I'’ll see you guys tomorrow?
[Roger]
Congratulations.
Get some sleep.
[JWOWW]
Congratulations.
All right, love you.
Love you, I can'’t wait
to see you tomorrow.
Okay, bye.
[JWOWW]
Bye.
[Roger]
How'’s our little peanut?
Doing good?
Yeah.
Oh, my god, they'’re gonna--
she'’s gonna look
like a beast next to her.
Our baby'’s gonna
try to eat their baby.
Oh, my God, stop.
Good night, baby.
Good night, baby girl.
Good night.
Good work today.
Thanks, babe.
I'’m proud of you.
You sure you don'’t want
to sleep in bed with me?
God bless you.
Let'’s make another baby
right now.
I'’m not touching
your swollen vagina.
You'’re bleeding.
There'’s blood on your bed.
[laughs]
That'’s gross.
You'’re so rude.
[sighs]
Oh, my stomach'’s going down.
I can fit in that wedding dress.
Oh, god.
Here we go.
[baby cooing]
Yeah.
[knocking]
both: Hi.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- It'’s like deja vu.
[Snooki]
Jenni and Roger are
visiting today,
and I'’m really, really excited
because she'’s gonna
meet Giovanna,
and I feel like
she'’s gonna fall in love.
Do you want to hold her?
Hi, baby.
- I'’m nervous.
- Do you remember?
- Look at her little feet.
- Oh, my God.
You look just like your mommy.
My nipples hurt so bad.
[JWOWW]
Babe, you got to take pictures.
Seeing Giovanna
for the first time is honestly,
it, like,
makes your heart skip a beat
'’cause she'’s so beautiful.
She looks like Lorenzo.
She'’s tanner than me--
[Snooki]
And she has
better hair than you.
I know.
She'’s, like, she'’s perfect.
Look at that knee.
The vagina'’s not that bad
like I thought it would be.
- Ew.
- Ew, I know.
- I think about that sometimes.
- [laughs]
- You get used to it.
- Yeah.
[Snooki]
I have to get used
to Giovanna'’s vagina
because obviously
I'’m used to a wiener.
An outie?
[Snooki]
With a vagina, you have to,
like, get into the creases.
You have to wipe a certain way.
[Snooki]
With Lorenzo'’s wiener,
you could just wipe whatever,
and, you know, that'’s it.
So, I feel like with the vagina,
it'’s definitely
more complicated.
Did you change a diaper yet?
Yeah,
but there wasn'’t any poop.
[Jionni]
I just pulled out a guck.
[JWOWW]
Oh, yeah, the vernix will be
stuck in there for a while.
[JWOWW]
It'’s actually a good protector.
Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- We just pulled it out.
- The whole thing?
- No, no, it shot back in.
[Snooki]
There'’s still more in it.
Were we not supposed to
pull it out?
[JWOWW]
Vernix is what
the baby comes out in.
[JWOWW]
It'’s supposed to be, like,
the cream of all creams.
- It'’s that white, gooey stuff.
- That white stuff.
[JWOWW]
It'’s like,
if they were to bottle it up,
it'’s, like,
$20,000 per, like, a small jar.
Like, that'’s how good
it is for nutrients.
[Roger]
The old-school nurses say
it'’s, like, great for your skin.
[Roger]
Like, if you have an injury
or psoriasis or anything.
- Yeah.
- That guck?
You'’re lying.
You just want us
to put it on our face.
[laughter]
Why didn'’t I take it off of her
and put it on my face?
- Oh, I did.
- I wish I knew that,
because when they put
Giovanna on me,
I didn'’t want to touch her
because I thought
it was, like, gross.
I still didn'’t poop.
[laughs]
I held off.
It wasn'’t that bad, though.
When'’d you poop after?
[JWOWW]
In the hospital.
They made me.
[Snooki]
I don'’t know why I'’m
not pooping, '’cause I'’m eating.
[JWOWW]
It'’s cause of the painkillers.
I'’m not sure
why it'’s important to poop
after you give birth,
but if I don'’t poop on my own,
I'’m gonna have to have
a nurse go up there and,
like, put her finger in there
and, like, move the poop around.
[makes fart noise]
[hiccups]
I'’ll try.
It'’s gonna be
like rabbit [bleep].
[Snooki]
Stop.
- Little pebbles.
- No.
[Jionni]
I'’ll go poop first
and tell them it was you.
[laughter]
You'’re sick.
You'’re gonna
blow up the bathroom?
I'’m gonna go play golf today.
[gasps]
Lorenzo.
[Janis]
Hold your sign up.
[Snooki]
Welcome home, sissy.
[Janis]
Who'’s that?
[Snooki]
We'’re home as a family.
I'’m with my two kids.
[Snooki]
We have Lorenzo and Giovanna and
now we can just live our lives.
I feel like this is
where I need to be.
[Jionni]
It'’s awesome coming home to,
you know, such a great family.
- Look at the baby.
- Lorenzo, who'’s this?
- Go ahead.
- Hi, baby.
Say hi, sissy.
[laughter]
That fact that I just
feel comfortable and relaxed,
this is what I needed
for the past couple days.
[Snooki]
I got to feed her.
- Ready?
- We'’ll head out.
[Snooki]
Thanks guys for coming.
- Sure.
- Love you.
Let me kiss her.
- Bye, Ji.
- Bye.
- Love you.
- I'’ll see you soon.
Thank you.
Nicole and I are very lucky.
We--we have a great family.
We come from a great family,
and we'’re all really close,
and, you know,
we can'’t ask for anything more.
Lorenzo.
- See you, boys.
- Want to watch King Kong?
See you, kids.
Good night, babe.
Good night.
Okay.
First night home
with sissy.
Whoa.
I almost dropped my ice cream.
- Nicole?
- Yeah.
Joe'’s calling.
[Snooki]
All right, answer.
[Jionni]
Joe, what'’s up?
[Joe]
What'’s going on?
[Jionni]
Nothing, just hanging.
We'’re about to go to the house.
What are you doing?
[Joe]
I got some good news for you.
Uh-oh, let'’s hear it.
[Joe]
We got the temporary CO.
You can start moving stuff in,
and tomorrow is the big day.
[Joe]
You can sleep there.
Whoa.
Yeah.
- We can move into our house.
- All right.
[Jionni]
And then tomorrow
we can sleep there?
[Joe]
You can sleep there.
Big day tomorrow.
- I appreciate it.
- No problem.
- See you there.
- All right, buddy, thanks.
[Jionni]
I'’ll see you.
Come on.
Last day in the basement.
[Jionni]
See you, Nonna.
We just got news that we can
move into our house tomorrow,
so I was thinking
you and Roger--
[JWOWW]
You got your CO?
Well, we'’re gonna get
a temporary one for tomorrow.
No, that'’s--
it'’s completely wrong.
Oh.
We--we got our CO,
so we'’re gonna move in tomorrow.
No, that'’s still wrong.
What is it?
We have our temporary CO.
We can move our clothes.
Tomorrow is the official.
- I just said that.
- No, you didn'’t.
Kind of hard
to believe after 27 years,
this is the day
I actually move out,
and I couldn'’t be any happier.
[Snooki]
Yeah, we have two kids now, so
we'’re definitely
ready to move out
and start our life together.
[JWOWW]
That'’s awesome.
Congratulations.
[Jionni]
So Nicole wanted to know
if you guys want to come up,
have lunch, and maybe
help us move some stuff.
- Today?
- Yeah.
[JWOWW]
We'’d love to.
I can'’t really do anything
because I just gave birth, so.
- Oh, great.
- It'’s all you.
[Snooki]
It'’s so nice in here.
I forgot what it looks like.
Are you down to, like, moving
stuff upstairs...
- [shouting]
- Today, babe?
Well, I want to do
some of my clothes first.
I feel like now
that we'’re finally in the house
and we'’re settled in,
now we'’re gonna have time
to actually work on our wedding
and make sure
everything gets done
because that'’s right around
the corner.
[Jionni]
The two biggest things
got checked off our list.
[Snooki]
Moving into the house,
and having a baby.
[Jionni]
Only one thing left to do.
Get married.
Look what mama got.
No food on here, okay?
No food in this room.
All right,
put it down on the floor.
- Put it right here.
- No!
I don'’t want it
on my brand-new loveseat.
Loveseat?
What do you do, make love in it?
Yep.
We'’re gonna conceive
our third child on this baby.
Not with me.
- Okay.
- Go find him.
He'’s somewhere out there.
Hi.
- She'’s out.
- Oh, my God.
[JWOWW]
She'’s huge.
She eats every two hours.
She'’s getting enormous.
She looks like you as a baby.
Yeah, '’cause she'’s getting
fat, and I was a fat baby.
You were so fat.
- I know.
- I can'’t even.
Chubby, chubby.
Mommy'’s chubby,
my daddy'’s chubby, we'’re chubby.
[laughs]
Stop.
[Snooki]
She'’s a monster.
Can we take a picture?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Get her away.
- My kid'’s gonna eat her.
- Is that normal?
- That'’s like us.
- I know.
[JWOWW laughs]
[Roger]
My kid may eat your kid,
really.
She might just sneak
a hand over
and palm her face and--aah.
[Snooki]
That'’s literally us.
[JWOWW]
Can I please have
that picture?
- Yeah.
- I'’m dying.
- That'’s us, but babies.
- I know.
[JWOWW]
I'’m such a ham.
It'’s--it'’s literally scary.
- Like, they look like us.
- Yeah.
[Snooki]
Like, you'’re the tall one,
and I'’m, like,
the little, short [bleep].
- That'’s--
- Like, that'’s what
they look like right now.
- Yeah.
- And it'’s adorable.
It'’s so freaking cute.
I can'’t.
I could stare at this
all day.
Mm-hmm.
- Thank you for the tour.
- Thanks for coming.
- The house is beautiful.
- Ooh, hold on.
I got to fix my hair.
I like you brunette better.
[Snooki]
I think you look beautiful
in any color.
If you were pink, purple, green,
but my JWOWW is a brunette.
Honestly, I'’ll have to admit
that you might be right
on this one.
And you'’re over it already.
A little bit.
What do you think
of that blonde hair?
She literally spent
50 hours
turning her hair blonde.
- And she hates it.
- I knew--I knew she was gonna.
- Literally.
- I also broke out in hives.
[JWOWW]
Like, I had, like,
a reaction to it.
- Allergic to blonde.
- Are those Roger'’s shoes?
[Snooki]
'’Cause you'’re not supposed
to be a blonde.
My whole chest,
like, became red and inflamed.
Yeah, God was telling you
this isn'’t right.
[laughs]
[JWOWW]
Blondes have more fun,
but I always say
brunettes get the job done.
[JWOWW]
So I need to be
a brunette again.
'’Cause I'’m not a [bleep] flake.
When are you getting
your hair did?
Tonight.
[Snooki]
I'’m getting my girl back.
I'’ll see you soon, okay?
- Bye.
- Bye, guys. Bye, Meilani.
[Roger]
Beautiful house.
If you want to get your hair
done late, now, that'’s cool,
but we'’re not gonna be home
until late now.
It'’s only gonna take
an hour and a half, two hours.
[JWOWW]
Honestly,
I need to find my sexy back,
because right now
I just feel like
a normal blonde from Michigan.
And I'’m not from Michigan.
[JWOWW]
You two have fun.
Don'’t cause too much trouble.
[JWOWW]
I really just want
to go dark again,
but, like, no highlights.
- Just all dark.
- Okay.
[JWOWW]
And I actually want to do
what I'’ve been wanting
to do for years, now.
[woman]
What?
- Do your shave?
- Yeah.
For, I would say
almost three years,
I'’ve always wanted
to take the left side
and shave half my head.
So you'’re going from mommy
to punk rocker?
I definitely want to be
a MILF,
so I'’m gonna
take it to a whole new extreme.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
It'’s gonna grow back,
if anything.
- In 20 years?
- 20 years?
Like, five.
I'’m kidding.
- Oh, my gosh. Really?
Are you?
Oh, my god, stop.
I'’m kidding.
[woman]
Don'’t stop.
[laughter]
[woman]
Oh, my god.
Just do it.
Do--close your eyes, everybody.
[JWOWW]
I'’m [bleep] myself
because I'’m like,
you can'’t go back
from that [bleep].
[JWOWW]
You can'’t go back
from that [bleep].
[JWOWW]
I'’m done. You can'’t go back
from this [bleep].
I'’m definitely nervous
right now.
Now I need a drink.
That feels good, actually.
[woman]
Aww, you'’re not blonde anymore.
Yay.
If you shaved your whole head,
I feel like
you would look pretty.
- I love it. I [bleep] love it.
- Calm down. Calm down.
It definitely
is better than the blonde,
and it fits my personality,
but I'’m definitely concerned
if Roger'’s gonna attack me
when he sees me
with my new hair.
Now it'’s like you'’re home.
I am. I'’m home.
Aww.
[woman]
Bye, sweet cheeks.
[JWOWW]
Babe?
[Roger]
Hi.
Hey.
How was your day?
[sighs]
[JWOWW]
What do you think?
I really like it, actually.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I think it looks amazing.
Like Christy Mack, actually.
Oh, your favorite porn star.
- That'’s great.
- [laughs]
Well, don'’t expect me
to act like her.
Jenni definitely has a certain
porn star quality to her now,
for sure.
Not that it'’s gonna probably
change anything in our bedroom.
- No.
- But...
Did you see
how quick she says no?
Before I can even say it.
"No."
Hi.
I really like it.
It looks really good.
Do you recognize your mommy?
[JWOWW]
I don'’t think Meilani
recognizes me right now.
She'’s looking a little upset.
- [baby crying]
- Oh.
Does she scare you?
Who'’s that strange lady?
"Daddy, why is there a porn star
in my house?
Daddy, daddy."
Stop.
Don'’t make--I'’m gonna cry.
Shut up.
You'’re disgusting.
Let'’s go to bed
with your new porn star mother.
Did you shave downstairs too?
[JWOWW]
Shut up.
[Roger laughs]
[Jionni]
Lorenzo?
You ready to start
moving into our house?
Yeah.
[Snooki]
This morning is the last
morning at Janis'’s house.
Like, this is for real.
[Snooki]
Today'’s the day.
Let'’s get the hell out of here.
[Jionni]
Oh, my God.
We'’ve got all these boxes too.
Ugh!
[grunts]
Oh, I can lift again.
Bye, basement.
[grunts]
Mama.
Mommy'’s nipples are burning.
I'’ve never owned
my own place before.
[Snooki]
I moved from my mom'’s house
to the Shore,
back to my mom'’s house,
to Jionni'’s basement,
and now here.
So, this is definitely,
like, a huge, adult,
parent moment for me.
Mom.
[doorbell rings]
Are you kidding?
You guys locked the door?
Who'’s that?
Carly.
No, Carly'’s not here.
Babe?
They locked the door
already on me.
Stay here.
I'’m scared.
[Snooki whimpers]
Are they kidding?
You guys locked the door?
Oh.
[sighs]
[Jionni]
It'’s the first day
in our new house.
My mom'’s here already.
It'’s only been a few hours,
and she'’s already crashing it.
I was scared.
I just thought you were
a Terminator or something.
Oh, my god.
I'’m here to help.
Thank you.
[Janis]
You'’re welcome.
Hi, Nonna.
So Janis comes over,
and I'’m just relieved
because I know she'’s gonna
help me put everything away.
[Janis]
But don'’t do too much.
[Snooki]
But I had no idea
she was gonna be
Speedy Gonzales with everything.
Where do you want me to
put everything?
Oh, there you are.
Do you want me to bring
these boxes outside?
Yeah.
Thank you.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
Big game tonight.
Your Nonna'’s a madwoman.
Okay, here we go.
Do we have cleanser?
This stuff'’s good.
Let'’s start doing the pantry.
Just put it anywhere?
This doesn'’t go here.
[Janis]
Whoa, look at this
we'’ve got to fix.
Whoa.
More pillowcases.
What do you want me to do?
Mop the floor.
I'’m not mopping the floor.
[Jionni]
Having my mom
at the house is awesome.
[Snooki]
She'’s literally
running back and forth,
putting things away.
- She was a monster.
- It'’s how she--
that'’s just what--
that'’s just what she does.
Yeah, but she was, like,
on crack.
Like zing, zing, zing.
My mom doesn'’t do crack.
I'’m not saying she does.
It'’s a expression, Jionni.
Oh, my God.
[Janis]
What?
Her bacon strip fell off.
Her what?
Her bacon strip.
Ew.
Isn'’t it called
a belly button?
All right.
Jionni!
What?
Her bacon strip fell off!
Already?
Your mama'’s cuckoo.
- I hate to tell you.
- Oh.
[Snooki]
I want to save it
with Lorenzo'’s.
Good job, baby.
[Snooki]
Can you just look at it?
This just makes me
really nervous
because her bacon strip
already fell off,
and now I'’m thinking, you know,
when she'’s gonna
go on her first date
and when she goes to prom,
when she gets married--
We'’re not there yet.
I'’m just--she'’s growing up
too quick on--on me.
- I can'’t.
- She'’s not going to prom.
Bugs on your food.
You'’re gonna make him
knock over the drink.
Oh, sorry.
You just jinxed me.
[Jionni]
Well, time to go, Ma.
It was a really long day
for Nicole and I
with all the moving
and the unpacking.
We want to enjoy
our new house tonight.
I feel bad I didn'’t finish.
You did so much, though.
Mom, thank you so much.
Make sure you
lock the front door!
[Jionni]
Okay.
Come back tomorrow.
[JWOWW]
We'’re here.
- Morning, Squirrel.
- Good morning.
Lorenzo, say, "Hi, Aunt Jenni."
Hi.
Say, "Hi, Meilani."
Oh, she'’s sleeping.
Did you get good sleep?
No.
So it'’s trying time.
Meh. But, I mean,
he takes on both kids
when I need him,
like if I have to go shower
or I want to take a quick nap,
he'’s--I'’m like,
"Can you watch both kids?"
He'’s like,
"Yeah, no problem," so...
- He'’s, like, the best dad ever.
- Yeah, this morning Roger was,
like, bouncing her around
when I'’m like...
[snores]
[JWOWW]
So...
We have good guys.
Yeah, no doubt.
They definitely deserve
something.
[huffing]
No, they are really
good dads.
Even though we'’re
awesome moms.
We'’re fabulous moms.
Yeah.
I honestly think
we'’re really blessed
to have Jionni and Roger
in our lives.
[JWOWW]
They'’re so awesome,
just as dads alone.
As fiances, I mean, yeah,
I seriously want to kick
his ass all the time,
but he'’s--they'’re great.
[Snooki]
Well, maybe we could do
something for them,
like, it'’s Dad Appreciation Day.
"Thank you, dads."
What are we gonna do
for them?
The obvious thing is probably
cook something for them.
I was gonna say
send them away.
[laughing]
I could get Carly to come
over here and watch the kids,
and then the boys,
obviously we don'’t want
them here when we'’re cooking.
We should get them a limo.
I like that.
And that gives us enough time
to, like, prep the dinner.
[Snooki]
Mm-hmm.
- That'’s hopefully edible.
- I always cook Italian.
No Italian. Chinese.
- Roger doesn'’t like Chinese.
- Okay.
He likes Japanese.
He likes, like, sushi.
- You want to try sushi?
- Yeah, you can put, like,
a Dorito in a sushi roll
if you wanted to.
Mmm.
Then we can also, like,
give them massages.
Aww.
- My hands cramp up.
- I feel like Roger would
be like, "Lower, lower."
[laughs]
I definitely want the boys
to have fun, so get them a limo.
- Yeah.
- And get the massage stuff
ready so when they get
back to the house,
we can all have a nice dinner,
And we can give them massages
and happy endings.
Rubs the lotion--what?
I'’m kidding.
We'’re moms.
We don'’t do that.
No.
How to make sushi.
Hi.
[Snooki]
It can'’t be that hard.
It looks really easy,
actually.
I'’ll make a grocery list.
I think the guys
are gonna be dumbfounded.
They'’re gonna be like,
"What did you do?"
Or they'’re gonna be like--yeah,
"Who'’d you hook up with? "
Yeah.
They'’re gonna think
we did something wrong.
Yeah.
[doorbell rings]
[Snooki gasps]
- Carly'’s here.
Carly'’s here.
- Hi, Carly.
- Hi.
What are you doing?
Say hi.
Me and Jenni are doing
a lot today
because we'’ve got to
go to the store
and get our sushi stuff,
get massage stuff,
and then set everything up
at the house.
I'’ll get a cart.
Okay.
I personally have never been
to an Asian market before.
Me neither.
I honestly feel like we'’re
transporting into, like, Japan.
I don'’t know what this says.
And everything is in Asian.
I don'’t understand anything.
Yan-Yan.
What the [bleep] is this?
What the [bleep]
are these?
That looks like fingers.
That looks like
[bleep] fingers.
- Clams.
- That looks like cow tongue.
Ew, this looks like dried bugs.
Oh.
What the hell is this?
That'’s a Big--
it'’s called a Big Squish.
How much to eat this?
No.
Couldn'’t pay me.
We don'’t necessarily have to
read the labels.
We just have to, like, scan
the aisles for the actual item.
Rice?
Oh, that'’s breadcrumbs.
Oh.
I feel like this is
the sushi aisle.
Oh, here we go.
Oh.
A bunch of seaweed.
Seaweed rolls.
Looks like tissue paper.
I don'’t know
how the [bleep] to make sushi.
I know it'’s, like, sticky rice.
Oh, my god, miso soup.
Miso horny.
It'’s sticky rice...
both: Seaweed.
And then you just roll it
with whatever you want.
Whatever you want.
Let your imagination create.
- How are you?
- Oh, you'’re the fish expert.
We'’re trying to make sushi.
What do you like?
Salmon.
We have salmon,
tuna, or shellfish.
Is this fish eggs?
Fish eggs.
Salmon.
Hoo.
- What'’s a fish egg?
- Oh, my God.
They'’re little babies.
We all know I don'’t like fish.
I just don'’t like
the smell of it.
[Snooki]
I think it'’s gross.
I think of Nemo.
Like, I think of all
these cute little characters,
and now they'’re all dead.
Did you ever see Finding Nemo?
[laughs]
Stop.
Oh, my God!
Oh, stop. Jenni.
[JWOWW]
I'’ll buy this one too.
Oh, my God.
What are they?
Sea bass or carp.
Sea bass?
Bass or a carp.
- 12 carp?
- Yes.
Whoa.
Aah!
That was--I thought
it was my earring!
[laughs]
I mean, if you'’re gonna
throw a shrimp at me,
I'’m gonna put it on you.
Don'’t [bleep] with me.
[laughs]
Oh, my God.
[Snooki]
Is this a slaughterhouse?
[JWOWW]
When it comes to thousands
of little fishies underneath,
and it'’s like your own--
you get to pick
and slaughter them, and--
[Snooki]
They'’re staring at you saying,
"Help me."
- That'’s terrible.
- Yeah.
Who'’s down there?
No.
[screaming]
[JWOWW]
Nope, I'’m good.
Let it free.
[Snooki]
Oh, my God.
I can'’t.
I'’m gonna have
nightmares of this place.
- Maybe.
- Now we have to go to Buddy'’s.
Help wanted, sales associate.
That'’s my next job.
And Buddy'’s is where we'’re gonna
get all of the stuff
that we need
for our massage experience.
- Yeah.
- Oils to lube up their backs.
Ooh, these are rub-a-dubs.
Personal massager.
How many of these?
Do we need a bunch of these?
Yes.
What about vibrators?
But usually
when you get a massage,
sometimes
they use a back massager.
- Like a vibrator.
- Which we call a vibrator.
Over two-hour run time.
Oh, that'’s a good run time.
[Snooki]
Oh, my God.
That'’s crazy.
[JWOWW]
We'’ll buy a couple vibrators.
I think we'’ll get one of those.
I think we'’ll get two.
[JWOWW]
I'’m bringing this vibrator home
with me, yes.
I'’m glad that we
bought three different types.
Mm-hmm.
I'’m gonna use it on my back.
Mm.
My nipples are leaking.
We like your massagers.
[cashier]
Oh, I'’m glad to see it.
And of course we have
the Shiney Hiney back here.
[JWOWW]
What'’s a Shiney Hiney?
- Oh, my God.
- Bring sexy back in the back.
A butt cleaner.
Mm-hmm.
A nice butt cleaner.
I don'’t even know--like,
a toothbrush for the butt.
- Never even knew that existed.
- Nope.
[cashier]
But it is going to actually
have a whitening cream
as well as three flavors
of cleansing creams.
And you [bleep] up your butt?
And you just--yup,
right there.
So, like, after, like,
a crazy poop or a crazy workout.
- You can clean your butt.
- You go in the shower,
and you just, like,
toothbrush your butthole.
Yeah.
You just kind of--your butthole.
So it'’s nice and clean.
- Bye.
- Thanks for my Shiney Hiney.
- Thanks for the ass cleaner.
- Use it well.
[Snooki]
This episode of
Snooki &amp;JWOWW...
[JWOWW]
Continues now.
[doors close]
[JWOWW]
Yummy.
Ooh.
You got that rice?
I hope this turns out
to be edible.
[Snooki]
Me and Jenni don'’t know when
the boys are gonna get back,
so we want to get
everything done
before they get to the house.
We'’re literally just
rushing to get everything done
so when the boys get here,
they'’re gonna be surprised.
Press like this.
[Snooki]
Oh, it definitely
feels like sushi.
We know how to make sushi now.
Hey.
[Snooki]
I think the boys
are gonna be surprised.
I mean, they have no idea
what we'’re doing.
I hope I spelled
"appreciation" right.
Yeah, that looks right.
But they know
we'’re doing something.
I think we did
a pretty frigging amazing job.
I don'’t know whether to be
nervous or excited,
because this is rare,
for the girls to send a limo
to pick us up from work, right?
It is pretty random.
Something--something'’s up.
What do you think?
Maybe they'’re guilty
about something?
Maybe they did something?
Maybe they'’re trying
to make it up
before we find out
what it is?
[Jionni]
I can'’t figure out
why the girls did this for us.
Usually when the girls
do something nice for us,
there'’s--there'’s a reason.
There'’s something behind it.
Where you taking us?
Nervous.
"This is not your child,
but here'’s a limo."
[laughter]
Is it possible
we'’re going to your house?
- I don'’t know.
- They can'’t cook.
If they are cooking, should we
call for pizza just in case?
Absolutely.
I think we'’re ready.
Everything looks phenomenal.
[Snooki]
I mean, the massage stuff
looks great.
[Snooki]
The table is set.
So hopefully,
they'’re gonna be surprised.
Jenni, I think
the boys are here.
Yeah, they'’re here.
[JWOWW]
Are they?
Oh, my God.
Hide.
[JWOWW]
I'’m just really happy
that we'’re able
to do this for the boys
because I can'’t remember
the last time
I did something nice for Roger.
- Seriously.
- And especially, like,
him being a new dad,
he needs to know that
I appreciate everything he does.
Agreed.
- Oh, it'’s not--
- Locked out of my own house.
[doorbell rings]
[Snooki]
Damn it.
Got to open the door.
[bleep].
Say surprise when I open it.
[JWOWW] Okay.
both: One, two, three.
- [yawns]
both: Surprise!
Hi.
- Hi.
- Hello.
[Roger]
Surprise?
Happy Daddy Day.
[Roger]
As soon as
we walked through the door,
it was Dad Appreciation Day,
which I never expected.
We have more for you.
- Yeah.
- More?
- Let'’s go.
- Come on.
We have more surprises.
[Snooki]
Welcome to the massage parlor.
- No way.
- Oh.
[Roger]
So the girls have this entire
kind of, like, spa setup there.
- Put your robes on.
- Yes.
Vibrators and some
odd-looking stuff,
but hey, whatever, I'’m game.
- I don'’t want the--
- If it only happens once,
it'’s not gay.
[Snooki]
I don'’t really have
a plan here.
- Um...
- Let'’s just start off
with these?
Just to get it nice and--
How do you give a massage?
Can you just lay down?
- Okay, ready?
- [sighs]
[Snooki]
I'’m not really sure
what you do with these.
But I feel like this is it.
Does that feel nice, sir?
Yeah, keep going.
The girls had a massage set up.
They--we--we put our robes on.
Oh, yeah, baby.
That'’s what I'’m talking about.
What are you doing?
I have, like,
a vibrator thing for your back.
Oh.
Can you work that
on the front side
a little bit there, mama?
Stop.
What'’s wrong with you?
I'’m massaging your butt.
Why would you stick that
in my butthole?
I didn'’t put it
in your butthole.
[laughs]
That'’s stupid.
[Jionni]
I thought this was
Dad Appreciation Day,
and I don'’t appreciate being
violated right now, so let'’s--
let'’s move on.
You guys hungry?
- You guys hungry?
- Mmm.
- We did this all by ourselves.
- Yeah.
I'’m definitely a little
suspicious of Jenni and Nicole.
I'’m scared.
You guys are scaring us.
[Roger]
I don'’t know.
I don'’t--if Meilani comes
walking around the corner
with a cast on her leg,
I'’m gonna be really pissed.
- Ta-da.
- Surprise.
- We made you sushi.
- We made sushi.
- Babe, this is yours.
- Oh, my God.
You did make us sushi.
- We really made this.
They made us sushi rolls.
[Roger]
I'’m a little nervous
because sushi, you know,
that'’s a delicate craft.
You'’ve really got to know
what you'’re doing.
But they look amazing.
I'’m hoping that they taste
as good as they look.
How often do these
Dad Appreciation Days happen?
[Snooki]
Once in a blue moon.
Wow.
This is good sushi.
I put them up there
with any good sushi restaurant
I'’ve been to.
High five.
Thank you.
We also made you cards.
[Jionni]
Thank you.
Here'’s your card...
[muffled]
And your card.
[Roger]
Mine says, "To daddy,"
and it'’s got
some stickers on it.
[laughs]
[Roger]
"Thank you so much for being
"the best dad
anyone could have asked for,
Meilani and Jenni."
Aww.
[Roger]
[Jionni]
"Jionni...
"We love you.
"Thank you for being
the best dad and fiance ever.
I couldn'’t be more happier.
You make my life--"
Wait a minute.
Does it say "more happier?"
[laughter]
[Roger]
Does it really say
"more happier?"
Why?
Does that not make sense?
- No.
- Who wrote this, Lorenzo?
It just means
I'’m really happy.
She'’s extra happy.
[Jionni]
I understand what it meant,
and I appreciate it.
I'’m more happier too.
Honestly, for me,
and I think same for you,
to me, every day
is Dad Appreciation Day
that I get to spend
with my little girl,
you know what I mean?
[all]
Aww.
No, I really mean that.
I'’m actually getting choked up.
[all]
Aww.
Always been an emotional guy,
always have,
but I'’ve never been a guy
that wore that
on his sleeve,
you know what I mean?
I cry all the time now,
just tears of happiness,
'’cause my kid is
that important,
and affects me emotionally
that much, and I don'’t care.
I could care less
what people think.
- [bleep] "yous."
- Yeah, [bleep] "yous."
Jionni?
[both laughing]
How can I top that?
[JWOWW]
Next time, on Snooki &amp; JWOWW...
We'’re going to Miami
for my bachelorette party.
[all cheering]
I look up, there'’s
a "Rest In Peace Jionni" sign
bannered on the wall.
- Who played that sick joke?
- [laughs]
Did you get a lap dance
from anyone?
Jionni!