- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
JENNI JUST HAD HER BABY.
- ARE YOU HUNGRY?
JUST, LIKE, GIVE ME THE BOOBS.
- I AM IN LOVE.
- WE WERE SCARED
YOU WERE GONNA BE UGLY.
SO ME AND JIONNI WANT TO DO
SOMETHING REALLY SPECIAL
FOR JENNI AND ROGER WHEN THEY
COME HOME WITH THE BABY.
- YOU GOT A MARIACHI BAND?
[band playing Rock-a-Bye Baby]
- I'’M GONNA KILL THEM.
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- ♪ OH,
MAYBE THERE'’S STILL HOPE ♪
♪ MAYBE THERE'’S STILL ♪
♪ HO-OH-OH-OH-OH-OH-OH
♪ OH-OH-OH-OH-OH-OH
- THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
- YOU'’RE WELCOME.
- THERE'’S FOOD IN THERE.
- IS THERE? I'’M STARVING.
- YEAH.
- GO IN THE DINING ROOM.
- GO EAT.
- SO BRINGING MEILANI HOME
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
AND JIONNI AND NICOLE
HAD REALLY GONE OUT OF THEIR WAY
TO MAKE IT SPECIAL FOR US.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
YOU CAN GO EAT.
WE CAN LOOK AT HER.
THEY NEVER STOP STARING AT HER.
- WE LOVE EVERYTHING
THAT THEY DID.
EVEN THOUGH WE'’RE EXHAUSTED
AND TIRED,
IT WAS A WELCOME HOME
FOR US AND FOR MEILANI
THAT WE NEVER EXPECTED.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
THAT'’S WHAT MAKES THEM
SUCH EXCEPTIONAL FRIENDS.
- SO NOW WHAT?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- YOU'’RE PARENTS.
- I'’M STILL TRYING
TO FIGURE THAT PART OUT.
I GOT 72,000 MANUALS,
AND I STILL DON'’T KNOW
WHAT THE [bleep] I'’M DOING.
- MM.
- AND THIS ONE...
THE CRAZY DOTING DAD.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN
SOMEONE SO HARD GO SO SOFT
IN A MATTER OF 24 HOURS.
LIKE, ROGER
HAS NO STREET CRED LEFT.
- SHE'’S GOOD.
SHE'’S SLEEPING.
- SO ME AND NICOLE WERE--
HAD BEEN NERVOUS--
- NERVOUS WITH WHAT?
- WHEN YOU GUYS PULLED UP,
WE WERE LIKE,
"I HOPE THEY WANT PEOPLE HERE.
IMAGINE IF THEY WANT TO JUST
GO HOME AND RELAX."
- YEAH.
- YEAH, WELL, OF COURSE
WE WANT TO GO HOME AND RELAX,
BUT THIS IS RELAXING.
IT'’S YOU GUYS.
- EXCEPT THE MARIACHI BAND.
- I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
WHAT A MARIACHI BAND IS.
- [laughs]
[knock at door]
- HELLO.
- SO OUR VERY GOOD FRIENDS,
DIONNE, AIMEE,
AND KELLI,
WHO ARE ALL MOTHERS, YOU KNOW,
THEY JUST STOPPED BY
TO SEE MEILANI,
AND IT'’S SO GREAT TO SEE THEM.
- LOOK AT HER.
SHE'’S A LITTLE PEANUT.
[all cooing]
- LET'’S TALK ABOUT THE GIRLS
ROGER USED TO PULL WITH--
WHEN HE HAD THE LIGHTNING BOLT.
- ARE YOU MAKING FUN OF ROGER?
I WANT TO HEAR IT.
- ANY PERSON OFF THE STREET.
- HEY, ROG, WHAT'’S UP
FOR THE WEEKEND?
"WELL, FIRST I GOTTA GO
GET MY EDGE UP.
AFTER I GET MY EDGE UP--"
- I STILL GET AN EDGE UP
EVERY FRIDAY.
- IT'’S STILL THE SAME THING.
- KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING.
I NEED MORE INFO.
WAS HE A FULL-BLOWN GUIDO?
WORSE THAN HE IS NOW?
- HE WAS TRYING.
IT WASN'’T QUITE WORKING OUT
FOR HIM.
- IT WASN'’T REALLY GUIDO.
- OH, MY GOD.
- THIS WAS PROBABLY ONE
OF MY BEST NIGHTS OF MY LIFE.
I'’M DEFINITELY GONNA USE
SOME OF THIS AS AMMO.
THE GIRLS SAID SOME GOOD STUFF.
YOU KNOW, KARMA DAYS,
BAMBOO DAYS, SO I'’M GONNA
KEEP IT STORED JUST IN CASE
ROGER WANTS TO BUST CHOPS.
- DEFINITELY.
THIS IS A GREAT CONVERSATION
TO HAVE WITH JENNI.
- HE'’S VERY NICE.
- THE GIRLS THAT I USED TO PULL.
GREAT CONVERSATION TO HAVE.
- ALL RIGHT, POOH,
I'’M GONNA GO SEE LORENZO.
- OKAY.
- LOVE YOU.
- BYE, BABY.
I WANTED TO LEAVE JENNI'’S
JUST BECAUSE I FELT LIKE IF I
LEFT MAYBE EVERYONE WOULD LEAVE.
'’CAUSE YOU KNOW WHEN
THAT ONE PERSON LEAVES
AND IT'’S LIKE, "ALL RIGHT,
I'’M GONNA GET OUTTA HERE."
IT DIDN'’T WORK.
- NO, IT DIDN'’T.
- '’CAUSE I COULD TELL
YOU WERE GETTING TIRED.
- MM-HMM.
- AND--
- MY FRIENDS ARE DICKS.
- YEAH, IT DIDN'’T WORK.
- JENNI, ARE YOU IN THERE
CLEANING UP AFTER US?
- [sighs]
- [laughs]
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
I HAVE TO GO WRAP UP MY LAPTOP,
'’CAUSE--
- I HAVE TO--I HAVE TO--
- I'’M WORKING TOO.
- SO EVERYONE STARTS TO LEAVE.
THANK GOD,
'’CAUSE I WOULD LOVE TO RELAX
AND JUST LOOK AT MY DAUGHTER
AND CHERISH HER,
'’CAUSE HONESTLY, SINCE HER BIRTH
I HAVEN'’T BEEN ABLE TO
'’CAUSE OF MY RECOVERY.
YEAH, SO IT'’S OUR TIME NOW.
- ABSOLUTELY.
I'’M GONNA GIVE HER TO YOU, BABE,
AND RUN TO THE PHARMACY
FOR YOU IN A MINUTE.
I DON'’T WANT TO GIVE HER UP,
THOUGH.
- I FEEL LIKE WHAT I'’M DOING
IS, LIKE, WHAT EVERY SINGLE MOM
OR, LIKE, ITALIAN MOM DOES ONCE
THEY GET HOME FROM THE HOSPITAL.
HAS, LIKE, A PARTY
AND THEN CLEANS UP.
I KNOW ROGER'’S IN LA-LA LAND
WITH OUR DAUGHTER RIGHT NOW,
BUT LIKE, SERIOUSLY,
I JUST HAD A BABY,
AND I WOULD REALLY LOVE
IF HE KIND OF,
LIKE, STAYED IN TUNE WITH ME,
SO HE CAN HEAR ME IN THE BACK
BITCHING THAT I COULD USE
HIS HELP CLEANING UP THIS HOUSE.
I'’M GONNA [bleep] HEMORRHAGE,
I SWEAR TO GOD.
- WHY?
- I'’M JUST DOING TOO MUCH.
- JENNI!
- I GOTTA--I NEED MY MEDICINE.
- JENNI, STOP FOR TWO SECONDS.
- YEAH, RELAX.
- TWO SECONDS, AND LOOK AT ME,
AS YOUR FIANCE,
AND EXPLAIN TO ME
WHAT I CAN DO TO HELP,
AND IF YOU'’RE MAD AT ME, '’CAUSE
I FEEL LIKE YOU'’RE MAD AT ME.
- I'’M ANNOYED AT YOU
A LITTLE BIT, YEAH.
- OKAY, CAN YOU EXPLAIN WHY?
- BECAUSE SHE'’S SLEEPING,
AND YOU CAN GET UP,
AND YOU COULD HAVE HELPED CLEAN,
OR YOU COULD HAVE HELPED
DO SOMETHING.
- YES, I COULD HAVE.
AND YOU COULD HAVE SAT
AND TAKEN HER FROM ME.
NOBODY SAID YOU HAD TO CLEAN.
JIONNI WAS HANDLING IT ALL.
- JENNI, I THREW THE PARTY.
I WAS CLEANING.
- YOU TOOK THAT UPON YOU...
- NO, IT'’S FINE.
- JUST FOR A REASON
TO GET AGGRAVATED AT ME.
- NO.
- AND WHY ARE WE DOING
THIS AGAIN?
BECAUSE YOU WANTED
TO HAVE PEOPLE BACK HERE.
WHO THOUGHT THAT
THAT WAS A BAD IDEA?
OF THE TWO OF US,
WHO THOUGHT THAT WAS A BAD IDEA?
- JENNI AND ROGER
DEFINITELY BOTH,
YOU KNOW, OVERTIRED,
AND THEY START BICKERING,
AND I JUST--I FAKED
I HAD TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
I HAD TO LEAVE.
I JUST FELT UNCOMFORTABLE.
- DO ME A FAVOR AND SPEAK ON IT
RATHER THAN GET ANNOYED,
'’CAUSE I WOULD MUCH RATHER
YOU SIT WITH HER AND HOLD HER
AND I WOULD CLEAN,
AND IT DOESN'’T BOTHER ME AT ALL.
BUT YOU DON'’T SAY ANYTHING.
- RIGHT.
- YOU JUST TAKE THE INITIATIVE,
YOU GO DO IT,
AND THEN--AND THEN YOU ACT
ALL P.O.'’D AT ME,
AND I THINK THAT'’S RIDICULOUS.
- I KNOW I'’M BEING
SHORT-TEMPERED WITH ROGER
ONLY BECAUSE I'’M TIRED.
I WANTED TODAY EVEN THOUGH
HE SAID WE SHOULDN'’T DO TODAY
AND HAVE FRIENDS OVER.
I WANTED IT.
AND I JUST FELT LIKE I
DESERVED A LITTLE PAMPERING TOO,
AND I HAD A--
YOU KNOW, A TEMPER TANTRUM.
- I LOVE YOU.
LET'’S NOT FIGHT, ESPECIALLY NOW.
- NO, I AGREE.
DO YOU WANT TO BRING HER
OVER HERE?
- SURE.
I'’LL BRING THAT LITTLE GIRL
RIGHT OVER.
I GOTTA GO TO THE PHARMACY
AND GET YOU SOME MEDICATION.
- ♪ YOU'’RE A DREAM OF MINE ♪
♪ OH, YOU'’RE A DREAM OF MINE ♪
♪ SUMMERTIME DAYDREAM
ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ OH, YOU'’RE A DREAM OF MINE ♪
- I AM SO [bleep] DELIRIOUS
THAT I COULD ACTUALLY
SEE A PINK ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM
AND BELIEVE IT'’S THERE.
LIKE, I WOULD HAVE
A CONVERSATION WITH IT.
[gentle music playing]
♪
- YOU KNOW,
IT'’S OUR FIRST NIGHT HOME.
I JUST--I'’M SO--I'’M SO BLESSED
AND SO HAPPY TO BE A DAD.
YOU KNOW?
I'’M SO PROUD OF JENNI.
GOOD NIGHT, BABY.
- NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT, MY LITTLE BABY.
- GOOD NIGHT, BABE.
LOVE YOU.
[Meilani crying]
I DEFINITELY WOKE UP A BUNCH
LAST NIGHT.
MY POOR DAUGHTER.
LIKE, SHE'’S UNCOMFORTABLE.
I'’M UNCOMFORTABLE.
ROGER'’S UNCOMFORTABLE.
SHE LOVES FORMULA.
SHE'’S DRINKING IT
EVERY TWO HOURS,
AND THEN SHE NEEDS A DIAPER
CHANGE EVERY TWO HOURS.
THEN SHE NEEDS TO BE BURPED.
THEN WE HAVE TO WAIT
FOR HER POOPS,
'’CAUSE THEY EXPLODE ABOUT
30 MINUTES AFTER HER FEEDING.
- [crying]
- I'’M SO TIRED.
YOU KNOW, THAT'’S LIFE.
- TELL LORENZO
WHAT HE'’S DOING TODAY.
- LORENZO, GUESS WHO
YOU'’RE GOING TO SEE TODAY.
POP-POP.
- YOU GONNA HANG OUT
WITH POP-POP?
WITH POP-POP TODAY?
- YOU MISS POP-POP?
- WE'’RE DROPPING YOU OFF,
SO MOM
CAN GO PICK OUT HER FLOWERS.
- FOR...
- FOR OUR WEDDING.
WE HAVE A LOT TO DO BEFORE WE
GET MARRIED IN A COUPLE MONTHS,
SO WE ARE GOING
TO SEE OUR FLORIST TODAY,
AND THIS WEEK
IS MY BRIDAL SHOWER,
SO I GOT A LOT
OF [bleep] GOING ON.
I NEED TO GO BUY GRANNY PANTIES.
- THAT'’S EMBARRASSING.
WANT ME TO ASK MY GRANDMA?
- YEAH.
THE UNDERWEARS HAVE TO COME UP
TO HERE.
- THERE'’S ONLY ONE PAIR.
"UNDERWEAR."
- UNDERWEAR.
- YOU WANNA GO TO THE FLORIST?
- YEAH.
I'’M EIGHT MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND I'’M SO UNCOMFORTABLE,
I'’M FREAKING OUT.
I'’M EXHAUSTED, I CAN'’T MOVE,
AND I'’M JUST
REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
- I WAS UP AT 4:00
AGAIN, RIGHT?
- I KNOW.
WE CUDDLED.
- WHY DO YOU THINK
I CAN'’T SLEEP?
- MAYBE YOU'’RE POSSESSED.
DON'’T KILL YOUR FAMILY.
- WHAT IF YOU HAD TO KILL ME?
TO SAVE YOUR AND LORENZO'’S LIFE?
WHAT WOULD--HOW WOULD YOU DO IT?
- I WOULDN'’T.
- YOU HAD TO.
- I'’M NOT GONNA KILL YOU.
UNLESS YOU HAVE YOUR SPERM
STORAGED
FOR MORE KIDS.
- YOU WANT ME TO DO THAT
JUST IN CASE I PASS AWAY?
- YES.
BUT ONLY FOR ME.
IF SOME OTHER CHICK GETS IT,
I'’M GONNA BE REALLY PISSED.
YOU SHOULD JUST DO IT AT HOME.
- I'’M NOT FREEZING SPERM
IN MY FREEZER.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
PUT IT IN A JAR?
- YEAH, A CLOSED JAR.
AN AIR-SEALED, TIGHT JAR.
AND THEN IT'’S THERE.
- YOU'’RE SICK.
WHERE DO YOU COME UP
WITH THIS [bleep]?
- I ALMOST PEED.
- SO I JUST FEEL LIKE I'’VE BEEN
AROUND BABIES AND ESTROGEN
AND ANGRY FIANCEES
A LITTLE BIT TOO MUCH LATELY.
I NEED TO GET OUT,
GO TO THE BARBERSHOP,
AND JUST, YOU KNOW,
TALK TO THE FELLAS
ABOUT SPORTS AND CARS
AND JUST KIND OF HAVE,
YOU KNOW, GUY TIME.
- HOW WAS
YOUR FIRST DIAPER CHANGING?
[phone rings]
- NOT BAD, MAN.
I JUST CHANGED ONE,
JUST BEFORE I CAME IN.
I MEAN,
WE'’RE ONLY ON DAY THREE NOW,
AND I'’M ALREADY CHANGING DIAPERS
LIKE A CHAMP.
- WE HAD A C-SECTION.
LISTEN TO ME, BRO.
THEIR GUTS ARE, LIKE, HANGING,
SITTING NEXT TO '’EM
WHEN YOU HAVE A C-SECTION.
- OH, FOR THE C-SECTION.
C-SECTION'’S WORSE, BRO.
CONVERSATIONS DEFINITELY
HAVE CHANGED AT THE BARBERSHOP.
I THINK SHE LOOKS LIKE ME
AS A BABY.
- SHE BREAST-FEEDING OR BOTTLE?
- YEAH, WELL,
SHE TRIED IN THE HOSPITAL,
AND THE BABY'’S GETTING SOME,
BUT IT HASN'’T COME IN FULLY,
SO IT'’S MORE SUPPLEMENTING
TILL IT COMES IN FULLY.
- LOOK AT THAT.
I'’M PROUD OF YOU, ROG.
YOU'’RE LEARNING ALL THIS STUFF.
- TODAY THE BARBERSHOP
FEELS LIKE--MORE LIKE A SALON.
I DON'’T KNOW, I'’M JUST GONNA
HAVE TO LEARN TO LIVE WITH THAT.
I GUESS THAT'’S HOW
IT'’S GONNA BE FROM NOW ON.
- YOU KNOW THE MENTAL PICTURE
I JUST HAD OF ROGER?
- BABIES EVERYWHERE.
- PICTURED HIM IN AN APRON,
A BIG SPATULA, A DIAPER,
AND THE BABY IN THE LEFT HAND,
AS HE'’S FLIPPING BURGERS.
- A YEAR FROM NOW,
BIG BEER BELLY.
- NOW YOU'’RE OFFICIALLY PART
OF THE CLUB.
- YEAH, MAN.
- WHAT KIND OF FLOWERS
DO YOU WANT?
- I DON'’T CARE
WHAT KIND OF FLOWERS WE GET.
- I MIGHT WANT CALLA LILIES
IN MY BOUQUET.
- WHO?
- CALLA LILIES.
- WHAT THE FREAK'’S
A CALLA LILLY?
PELLINIS.
PANINIS.
DID YOU EVER
HEAR OF THAT FLOWER?
- JIONNI THINKS THE PANINI
IS A FLOWER.
- I DO NOT.
- BUT A PANINI IS A SANDWICH.
- I DO NOT THINK THAT.
- I DON'’T WANT A PANINI.
- PANLILLIES. PANINI.
- OH, I WOULD LOVE A PANINI
RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT'’S THE FLOWER CALLED?
PANINE?
- PENIS.
PEONIES.
- SEE? PEONY.
I DON'’T EVEN KNOW HOW TO SAY IT.
PANINI.
SO MUCH TO DO, SO LITTLE TIME.
- WE'’LL GET IT DONE.
DID YOU SHOWER?
- NO.
- EW.
HI.
- HEY, NICOLE! HOW YOU DOING?
- GOOD.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- JIONNI, WHAT'’S UP?
- HOW YOU BEEN?
- HOW'’S IT GOING? ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- SO YOU'’RE HERE TO TALK
ABOUT WEDDING FLOWERS, HUH?
- YEAH.
WE GOTTA GET THIS DONE.
- WHEN'’S THE BIG DAY?
- NOVEMBER 29TH.
- WHAT KIND OF THEME
ARE YOU GONNA CARRY THROUGH
WITH THE WEDDING?
- WE'’RE DOING
A GREAT GATSBYTHEME.
- OH, COOL.
- I'’M GATSBY.
- NO, YOU'’RE NOT.
- THEN WHO AM I?
- [laughs]
JUST KIDDING.
YOU'’RE HOTTER THAN THE GATSBY.
LEONARDO DICAPIO.
- I'’M GATSBY.
- [laughs]
- LEONARDO DICAPPIE.
- SO THE COLORS--
- BLACK AND GOLD.
- YEAH, VINTAGE.
AND, LIKE,
IVORIES AND CHAMPAGNES.
- OKAY. THE CENTERPIECES,
WHAT DO YOU THINK--
- HUGE.
- HUGE CHANDELIERS, FEATHERS,
AND THEN REALLY,
REALLY GORGEOUS FLOWERS.
- LIKE THE GATSBY.
- AND THEN I ACTUALLY BOUGHT
PEARLS THAT I WANT
TO DRAPE ON THE CHANDELIERS.
- YOU CAN DO THAT--
- I WANT IT ALL HIGH.
- YOU WANT IT ALL HIGH.
SO YOU WANT ALL HIGH, ALL BIG,
ALL OUT THERE.
- YEAH, SO WHEN PEOPLE WALK IN,
THEY'’RE LIKE, "WOW."
- OKAY.
SO I'’LL PUT SOME FLOWERS
AND SOME VASES OUT,
AND THEN YOU CAN GO BACK THERE,
AND YOU CAN SHOW ME
WHAT YOU'’RE THINKING.
- I DON'’T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT FLOWERS, BUT--
- NEITHER DO I, SO IT'’S OKAY.
[laughter]
- LET'’S START THIS [bleep].
- COME ON, MAN,
YOU GOTTA STEP IT UP, MAN.
SHE'’S BEATING YOU HERE.
COME ON.
- IT'’S ALL ABOUT
HOW IT LOOKS AT THE END.
- THAT'’S RIGHT.
HE'’S GOT EXPERIENCE HERE.
I CAN TELL.
- IT'’S THE COMPETITION.
WE'’RE NOT FRIENDS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET OUTTA HERE.
- YOU TOOK ALL OF '’EM.
OH.
I REALLY DON'’T CARE WHAT
JIONNI'’S DOING WITH HIS FLOWERS,
BECAUSE I HAVE AN ORIGINAL,
REALLY, REALLY GOOD IDEA,
AND JUST PEEKING OVER
AND LOOKING AT HIS FLOWERS,
NONE OF THEM MATCH,
AND HE'’S JUST PICKING
RANDOM FLOWERS. SO...
- YOURS IS UGLY.
I ALREADY WON,
JUST LOOKING AT
WHAT YOU'’VE BEEN PICKING OUT.
- DONE.
- COOL.
- SO WHICH ONE
LOOKS MORE GATSBY?
MY BOUQUET IS THE MORE GATSBY
THAN JIONNI'’S.
- I WASN'’T TRYING
TO MAKE IT LIKE THE WEDDING--
- WHITE FLOWERS.
- OBVIOUSLY.
- NOW YOU'’RE JUST SAYING THAT
'’CAUSE YOU LOST AND I WON.
- [scoffs]
- MINE ARE MORE GATSBY.
- I WASN'’T TRYING
TO MAKE THEM GATSBY.
- YOU'’RE A SORE LOSER.
IT'’S OKAY.
- SHUT UP.
- JIONNI, LET'’S NOT SLEEP.
COME ON.
LET'’S GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- SURE YOU STILL WANT TO DO IT?
- UH-HUH.
WE SHOULD'’VE JUST ELOPED.
SO MUCH EASIER.
- I WAS ASKING YOU THAT
FOR TWO YEARS NOW.
- YOU HAVE TO GET YOUR TUXES.
- WHAT ELSE?
THE BAND.
- WE HAVE TO CALL OUR BAND.
I HAVE TO DO MY MAKEUP
AND HAIR TRIALS WITH MY GIRLS.
I'’M GOING THROUGH
MY WEDDING BINDER.
YOU KNOW, THERE'’S A LOT
OF [bleep] TO DO.
JIONNI!
- OOH, IT'’S AN ANGEL BABY.
YOU ARE A LITTLE EATING MACHINE,
GIRL.
HOW MANY OUNCES IS THIS? 2?
- YEAH.
SHE'’S UP TO, LIKE, 3.
CAN'’T BELIEVE
THAT WAS A WEEK AGO.
MY VAGINA STILL
SAYS IT WAS YESTERDAY.
HOW DO YOU WANT
TO DRESS HER TODAY?
- CUTE.
SHE'’S GONNA BE AN ANGEL BABY.
- ANGEL BABY?
HE JUST LIKES TO SAY "ANGEL
BABY" A THOUSAND TIMES A DAY.
I'’VE NEVER HEARD SOMETHING SO,
LIKE--IT'’S LIKE A BROKEN RECORD.
"ANGEL BABY, ANGEL BAB--
MY ANGEL BABY."
- WHAT ARE WE DOING, ANGEL BABY?
HI, ANGEL BABY.
DADDY'’S ANGEL BABY RIGHT THERE.
DADDY'’S LITTLE ANGEL BABY.
ANGEL BABY.
HI, ANGEL BABY.
MY BABY'’S AN ANGEL BABY.
- DADDY'’S GONNA
CHANGE YOUR NAME.
WE SHOULD'’VE JUST
NAMED HER ANGEL.
HE'’S SO NUTS.
UGH.
SORRY, MY BOOBS HURT.
[laughs]
- WE COULD PUT A BURLAP BAG
ON YOU,
AND YOU'’D STILL BE
A LITTLE ANGEL BABY.
- [chuckles]
- I WANT TO GO SEE JENNI.
- CHECK IN ON THEM?
- ACTUALLY, I DON'’T EVEN
WANT TO GO SEE JENNI.
I WANT TO SEE MEILANI.
[scoffs]
JESUS.
HELLO.
- HELLO.
LOOK AT YOU.
- IT'’S FROM JANIS.
- OH, MY GOD, I LOVE HER.
- YEAH.
WHY ARE YOU SKINNY AGAIN?
YOU'’RE SUCH A WHORE.
I HATE YOU.
- [laughs]
- HI, BABY.
- YOU'’RE GONNA BE
THE SAME EXACT WAY.
- I BETTER.
I HAVE A WEDDING DRESS
TO FIT IN.
- I KNOW.
- OH, DO YOU WANT TO GO
GET YOUR NAILS DONE?
- I NEED TO.
- I NEED TO GET A PEDICURE.
- MY BRIDAL SHOWER IS TOMORROW.
- I DON'’T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I'’M REALLY BUMMED THAT I CAN'’T
MAKE IT TO NICOLE'’S BRIDAL
SHOWER, BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I JUST HAD A BABY.
BUT EVEN THOUGH NICOLE
IS VERY UNDERSTANDING,
I STILL FEEL
A LITTLE DEBBIE DOWNER-ISH.
- IT'’S LIFE.
- WILL YOU GET HER DRESSED
WHILE I GET DRESSED?
- OH, YEAH.
EVEN IF SHE'’S SLEEPING?
- IT'’S EASIER.
- OKAY.
- AND IF SHE FUSSES,
JUST USE THIS.
THAT'’S WHAT ROGER SAYS.
- OH, I FORGOT HOW TO DO THIS,
BUT SHE'’S IN GOOD HANDS.
YOU'’VE GOT BIG NIP-NIPS.
SO HOW IS IT? TOUGH?
NO SLEEP?
- YEAH, IT'’S NOT EASY.
I'’M NOT GONNA LIE.
WE DON'’T GET MUCH SLEEP, BUT I
WOULDN'’T TRADE IT FOR THE WORLD.
YOU WANT ME
TO TAKE THESE DOWNSTAIRS?
- OH, YEAH.
- THANK YOU.
- JANIS MADE THEM FOR YOU GUYS.
- OH, DID SHE REALLY?
- YEAH.
- NO WAY.
- IS THIS ALL RIGHT?
'’CAUSE I DON'’T HAVE
NON-MATERNAL CLOTHES HERE.
- YOU LOOK AMAZING.
YOU DON'’T EVEN LOOK
LIKE YOU HAD A BABY.
- SERIOUSLY, SHE'’S NOT FAT.
WHO DOES THAT?
- IT'’S A WEEK.
IT'’S BEEN A WEEK.
READY TO GO.
I'’LL JUST GET THE BOTTLES.
- WILL YOU WATCH HER WHILE ME
AND NICOLE GO GET NAILS?
- MM-HMM.
SURE.
- I'’M GONNA PISS MY PANTS.
WHITE?
- WHITE. OKAY.
- IT'’S REALLY NICE TO GET
MY NAILS DONE WITH JENNI TODAY,
JUST BECAUSE I REALLY,
REALLY NEED IT.
I WANT TO LOOK PRETTY
FOR MY BRIDAL SHOWER,
AND PLUS I WANT
TO SPEND SOME TIME WITH BOO.
- I'’M PROBABLY GONNA CRY
TOMORROW.
- SERIOUSLY?
- I'’M SERIOUS.
- IT'’S NOT LIKE YOU'’RE MISSING
THE BACHELORETTE PARTY.
I GOT A LOT OF [bleep] GOING ON.
- I CAN'’T IMAGINE.
- WHEN IT'’S ALL OVER,
I'’M GONNA BE SO RELIEVED.
- RIGHT.
- WHEN WE'’RE DONE
I CAN JUST LIVE MY LIFE.
THEN WE CAN PLAN OUR VEGAS TRIP.
- SERIOUSLY.
- I REALLY HOPE WE'’RE
THOSE MOMS THAT, LIKE,
WHEN OUR GIRLS ARE 18 OR, LIKE,
21, THEY GO TO VEGAS TOGETHER
AND THEY WANT US TO COME.
- I AM SO EXCITED FOR OUR
DAUGHTERS TO BE BEST FRIENDS.
- MM-HMM. THEY'’RE GONNA
BE INSANE TOGETHER.
- YEAH.
- THEY'’RE GONNA BE LIKE US.
- MM-HMM.
- THAT'’S SCARY.
- THAT I'’M NOT LOOKING
FORWARD TO.
- COCKTAILS, PLEASE.
- I AM NOT CHASING MY DAUGHTER
DOWN IN KARMA.
- OH, IT'’S SCARY.
ALL THE [bleep] THAT I DID,
OH, MY GOD.
- TEEN NIGHT?
TEEN NIGHT!
- OH, THEY'’RE GONNA BE AWFUL.
I'’LL BE NEEDING MIMOSAS
JUST TO FUNCTION.
I CAN'’T MOVE.
[laughter]
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF MEILANI HAD A SEX TAPE?
- THAT WOULD NEVER HAPPEN.
- KILL HER.
- EXACTLY.
MY DAUGHTER WILL NOT BE
GOING OUT AND DOING SOME BAD.
DID YOU SEE HER FATHER?
MY GOD.
I FEEL--
- EXACTLY WHY SHE'’S GONNA
GO AND DO SOMETHING BAD.
- NO.
- MY BABY'’S GONNA
BE IN THE CHOIR.
SHE'’S GONNA BE AN ALTAR GIRL.
- OH, YEAH?
- SHE'’S GONNA BE
AN HONORS STUDENT.
I'’D RATHER HAVE A SMART GIRL.
- ME TOO.
- WHAT IF SHE'’S BUTT-UGLY
BUT REALLY SMART?
- I KNOW A GOOD PLASTIC SURGEON.
- OH, GOD.
THANK YOU.
BYE.
- HOW'’D YOUR NAILS COME?
OOH.
- MY EYEBROWS.
- IT'’S ABOUT TIME.
- I GOT MY NAILS DONE.
I GOT MY TOES DONE.
SO I HAVE TO GET READY RIGHT NOW
FOR THE BRIDAL SHOWER,
SO EVERYTHING
IS READY FOR TOMORROW.
I'’M ALREADY RUNNING
AN HOUR LATE,
AND I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING GETS DONE.
I DON'’T WANT
TO BE STRESSED OUT ABOUT THIS.
BABE?
- YEAH?
WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
- I'’LL SHOW YOU
A SNEAK PEEK,
WHAT I'’M GONNA LOOK LIKE
ON OUR WEDDING DAY.
- OH, GOD.
- [humming Chopin'’s
Funeral March]
WAIT, HOW DOES
THE WEDDING SONG GO?
I KEEP GOING...
- ♪ DUN DUN DA DA
- LOOK AT ME.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT ME
IN THE EYES THE WHOLE TIME.
- I KNOW SHE WANTS
TO LOOK BEAUTIFUL,
AND THAT'’S REALLY IMPORTANT
TO HER,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I ACCEPT HER RIGHT LIKE THIS.
- [laughs]
- DEARLY BELOVED...
- WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY...
- TO WITNESS THIS SACRIMONY.
- "SACRIMONY"?
WHAT'’S A SACRIMONY?
STAND UP.
GONNA BE LIKE THIS.
- YOU'’RE GONNA HAVE
THAT SMILE THE WHOLE TIME?
- YEAH.
WHY ARE YOU SQUEEZING MY HAND
SO HARD?
'’CAUSE THAT'’S WHAT
WE'’RE GONNA DO.
WE HAVE TO STARE AT EACH OTHER
FOR, LIKE, 20 MINUTES.
- AWKWARD.
- IT'’S NOT AWKWARD.
WE LOVE EACH OTHER.
- ARE YOU GONNA CRY?
- MM-HMM.
- OH, GOD.
IF I FLIP THAT THING UP
AND AN EYELASH FALLS OFF,
I'’M GONNA BE REAL PISSED.
- [laughs]
- I MIGHT WALK AWAY.
- YOU READY
FOR YOUR BRIDAL SHOWER?
- I'’M PACKING NOW.
- YOU'’VE BEEN PUMPED
FOR THIS FOR...
- WANNA SEE MY OPTIONS?
- TWO YEARS.
- COME HERE.
- I LIKE THAT A LOT.
WOW.
- I DIDN'’T TRY IT ON YET.
- HERE'’S WHY I DON'’T
SEE YOUR OPTIONS,
'’CAUSE YOU NEVER GO
WITH WHAT I LIKE.
- I'’M NOT ASKING
FOR YOUR OPINION.
I'’M JUST SHOWING YOU.
- WELL, THAT'’S EVEN MORE RUDE.
- I'’M JUST REALLY,
REALLY ANXIOUS AND EXCITED.
I'’M EXCITED TO SEE ALL MY FAMILY
AND FRIENDS AND GET PRESENTS.
- [laughs]
- AND WE CAN GET MARRIED.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
- WHAT GOES ON
AT BRIDAL SHOWERS?
- STRIPPERS.
WE GET WASTED.
YOU KNOW.
- HOW COME I'’M NOT ALLOWED
TO GO?
- I DON'’T KNOW ANY GUYS THAT GO
TO THEIR WOMAN'’S BRIDAL SHOWER.
AND I DON'’T REALLY WANT
HIM THERE, NO OFFENSE.
IT'’S JUST FOR GIRLS.
IT'’S FOR ME AND MY FRIENDS.
- NONE TAKEN.
- CAN YOU BRING THIS DOWNSTAIRS?
COME ON, HELP ME PACK.
I GOTTA GO.
I'’M ALREADY RUNNING LATE.
I GOTTA GET CHANGED.
- LORENZO,
YOU GONNA GO SEE NANA?
COME ON.
YOU'’RE GONNA GO FOR A RIDE
IN THE CAR.
FREEDOM!
- WHY WOULD YOU--THAT'’S SO RUDE.
WHAT, LIKE YOU'’RE IN JAIL
WITH ME AND LORENZO?
- UH...
NOT LORENZO.
- OKAY. LOVE YOU, BABE.
- BYE.
CAREFUL DRIVING.
- OKAY.
I LOVE YOU.
- [whistles]
[burps loudly]
MM. LET'’S SEE IF MOMMY NOTICES
IF WE PUT A LITTLE BIT OF BREAST
MILK CREAMER IN HER COFFEE.
[laughs]
IT'’S REALLY HOT, SO BE CAREFUL.
I ALMOST STARTED FEELING BAD.
ALMOST.
- [coughs]
DID YOU PUT A SUGAR IN THAT?
- ONE STEVIA
AND AN IRISH CREAMER.
[Meilani laughing]
ARE YOU L--WAS THAT A LAUGH?
- OHH!
I DON'’T KNOW WHAT THAT WAS.
- I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT THAT WAS EITHER.
- IF YOU COME BACK UP, WILL YOU
BRING UP SOME MORE CREAMER?
- OKAY.
[laughs]
HOW IS DADDY GONNA
PULL THIS ONE OFF?
I'’M LOOKING AT THIS FULL THING
OF CREAMER.
LIKE, AM I GONNA
DUMP ALL THIS CREAMER OUT
JUST TO PUT A LITTLE TINY BIT
OF BREAST MILK IN THERE?
NO, NO, CAME UP WITH A WHOLE
TINFOIL INGENUITY THING.
I'’M A [bleep]DAMN GENIUS.
HOW MUCH?
A LITTLE BIT?
- A LITTLE WHITER.
AWW.
- IT'’S EXTREMELY HARD
NOT TO LAUGH.
[chuckles]
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER,
I PULLED IT OFF
AND GOT AWAY WITH IT,
SO IT'’S EVEN FUNNIER TO ME.
- MMM, IT'’S GOOD.
- [laughs]
- SO I PICK UP CARLY,
AND I HAVE TO DRIVE
TO MY MOM'’S HOUSE
TO DO A LITTLE SLEEPOVER
WITH LORENZO AND CARLY,
SO WE CAN GET EVERYTHING READY
FOR THE SHOWER TOMORROW.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, DOUCHE BAG?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
- [bleep] HICK.
I DEFINITELY HAVE ROAD RAGE,
AND I HAVE WORSE ROAD RAGE
NOW THAT I'’M PREGNANT.
[bleep] WHORE!
DON'’T SAY THAT, LORENZO.
DON'’T EVER SAY THAT.
- PEE-PEE!
- PEE-PEE?
YEAH, SAY THAT.
- SAY THAT ONE.
- SAY PEE-PEE.
I JUST HATE EVERYONE
ON THE ROAD.
I FEEL LIKE
THEY'’RE ALL OUT TO GET ME.
- ♪ EVERYONE IS--
- DOUCHE!
PEOPLE DRIVE CRAZY.
THEY'’RE [bleep] MORONS.
DRIVE LIKE AN ASS[bleep],
GET AWAY FROM ME.
[bleep].
DON'’T SAY THAT, LORENZO.
- HOW WAS YOUR TIME?
- GOOD.
- HOW WAS SHE?
- SHE'’S GOOD.
- YOUR BEST FRIEND FOREVER?
- MM-HMM.
♪ AN ANGEL BABY
- OH.
EVEN THOUGH, YOU KNOW,
WE HAVE A BABY AND EVERYTHING,
IT HAS BEEN ALMOST A WEEK,
I FEEL,
SO I WANT THE DOGS
TO MEET MEILANI TODAY.
- I'’D FORGOTTEN WE EVEN HAD '’EM.
- REALLY?
- NO.
[barks]
- HEY.
KNOCK IT OFF.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'’S ALL YOU.
YOU HOLD HER.
YOU'’LL CONTROL THE SITUATION.
I'’M LETTING YOU DO IT ALL. COOL?
- YUP.
THE DOGS DON'’T BEHAVE
FOR ANYBODY,
SO I'’M EXTREMELY NERVOUS
BECAUSE DIESEL LIKES TO JUMP.
HE'’S GOT SHARP NAILS.
I JUST DON'’T WANT
TO SEE ANYTHING BAD HAPPEN.
SO I'’M GONNA DO IT, YOU KNOW,
KIND OF LEISURELY.
[chittering]
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT GOING DOWNSTAIRS
AND MEETING THE DOGGIES?
IF THEY BOTHER YOU AT ALL,
DADDY WILL PEN THEM UP
IMMEDIATELY.
- THE ONLY THING
I'’M WORRIED ABOUT WITH MY DOGS
IS ROGER.
I'’M NOT CONCERNED WITH THEM.
IT'’S ROGER THAT'’S CONCERNED
WITH HOW THEY'’RE GONNA REACT
AROUND MEILANI,
SO WE HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE.
- OH, YOU SMELL THE BABY?
[dog sneezes]
OH.
NO SNEEZING ON THE BABY.
NO, YOU CAN S--
YOU CAN SMELL,
BUT YOU CAN'’T JUMP UP HERE.
IT'’S A BABY.
LOOK AT BELLA.
YOU CAN SMELL.
- WAS SHE GIVING HER KISSES?
- YEAH.
- OH, SHE GAVE HER KISSES.
- YOU CAN SMELL.
- AW.
- IT'’S A BABY.
IT'’S A BABY, BELLA.
THE DOGS ACTUALLY DID
EXCEPTIONALLY WELL
WHEN THEY MET MEILANI.
YOU KNOW, NONE OF THEM
JUMPED ON HER,
NONE OF THEM WERE BARKING,
NONE OF THEM WERE BEING,
YOU KNOW, TOO CRAZY.
THEY WERE ALL REALLY GOOD.
- AW, THEY'’RE BEING GOOD,
THOUGH.
- MM-HMM.
- THEY ARE BEING GOOD.
I'’M IMPRESSED.
- HOW'’S YOUR COFFEE, BABE?
GOOD?
- IT'’S GOOD.
WHY, WHAT'’D YOU DO TO IT?
- NOTHING.
I'’M JUST SAYING.
OH, SHE JUST LAUGHED.
SHE JUST LAUGHED.
- YEAH, '’CAUSE SHE KNOWS
DADDY'’S A PRANKSTER.
- [laughs]
- DAD--DADDY MADE IT WITH LOVE.
MOMMY SAW DADDY MAKE IT.
- MAKE ME ANOTHER ONE.
- OPEN THAT DOOR.
NO, DON'’T JUMP.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'’S GO.
- LET'’S GO, ANGEL BABY.
- COME ON, GUYS.
- LINDSAY'’S GOTTA
GO AND LIVE HER LIFE.
OH, YEAH, GOT YOUR CHECK.
DON'’T MIND.
- [laughs]
- THAT WOULD HAVE
REALLY SUCKED
IF I WOULD'’VE GOT BREAST MILK
ON THAT.
I WOULD--
I FORGOT IT WAS IN THERE.
- I LOVE MEETING THE BABY.
- YEAH.
- SEE YOU GUYS.
- BYE.
- SEE YOU TOMORROW, LINDS.
- WHAT?
YOU DID PUNK ME,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
- I PULLED THAT OFF FLAWLESSLY.
- YOU'’RE RUDE.
YOU MADE ME DRINK
MY OWN COLOSTRUM.
- BEST CREAMER YOU EVER HAD.
- YOU'’RE AN ASS.
- WHY'’S THERE SO MANY CARS?
WHO THE [bleep] IS HERE?
HELLO.
- HI.
- THE BRIDE'’S HERE.
- YAY.
- RIGHT WHEN I GET TO MY MOM'’S,
I SEE ALL MY GIRLS,
AND I'’M JUST SO HAPPY
TO SEE THEM,
AND I FEEL LIKE
THEY'’RE VERY, VERY EXCITED
FOR THIS BRIDAL SHOWER.
SO WE'’RE GONNA GET [bleep] DONE
TONIGHT.
LET'’S GET GOING, BITCHES.
- TIME TO WORK.
- YEAH, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
- DO THE GOODY BAGS FIRST,
'’CAUSE THAT'’S GONNA
TAKE THE LONGEST.
GOODY BAGS.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO, NIC?
LIKE, ONE THING IN EACH BAGGIE?
- ONE OF EACH
AND THEN CONCEALER,
LIP BALM, AND THAT'’S IT.
- AND THE FANS.
- OH, THE FANS WE'’RE GONNA PUT
ON THE TABLE, WE DECIDED.
I HAVE TO MAKE THE FAVOR BAGS
FOR ALL OF THE GUESTS,
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO DO,
LIKE, 200 BAGS.
I DEFINITELY APPRECIATE
ALL MY FRIENDS'’ HELP.
I LOVE MY FRIENDS TO DEATH.
I WILL DO ANYTHING FOR THEM.
SO, YOU KNOW,
THEY DO THE SAME FOR ME.
MOM, CAN YOU FEED ME?
- I CAN FEED YOU.
- TAKE THE CONCEALER--
- ARE THEY
THE LITTLE BLACK PACKAGES?
- YEAH, ONE.
ONE LIP GLOSS.
- ONE OF EACH
OR JUST ONE LIP GLOSS?
- I'’M JUST GONNA BRING
THIS WHOLE BOX IN HERE.
- AIM, YOU'’RE DOING LOTION?
OR YOU'’RE DOING LOTION?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
WE DIDN'’T DISCUSS ANYTHING.
- YEAH, WE'’LL JUST, LIKE,
ROTATE THE TABLE.
- THIS IS BODY POLISH,
AND THAT'’S BODY WASH.
- WELL, DO WE WANT
TO DO THE TISSUE PAPER FIRST?
- THIS THING TOO?
- ONE OF EACH.
- OKAY.
- DO WE HAVE ENOUGH?
- OH, MY GOD.
- DO WE HAVE THESE LITTLE ONES
OVER THERE?
IS ANYBODY DOING THOSE?
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- TURMOIL.
- ARE THESE GOOD?
- THESE FEEL A LITTLE LIGHT.
- WE FORGOT ABOUT THOSE.
- YOU KNOW,
I'’M A VERY NICE PERSON,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
THIS IS THE ONLY TIME
WHERE I CAN BE A BITCH
AND BOSS PEOPLE AROUND.
- THESE ARE DONE.
- LIKE A BUNCH OF MONKEYS.
IT'’S MY DAY,
AND WHATEVER I SAY GOES.
ARE YOU COUNTING?
- I WASN'’T, NO.
- WAS ANYONE COUNTING?
all: NO.
- YOU GUYS SUCK.
ANIMALS.
[laughs]
- WANNA EAT?
- DO YOU WANT SUSHI?
- OOH!
GOOD CALL.
- GET OUTTA THERE.
- WHAT?
I ALWAYS LIKE
TO SQUEEZE YOUR HEINIE.
THEN I FORGET
THERE'’S A DIAPER ON THERE.
- DADDY'’S MEAN.
I'’M SO EXCITED
TO HAVE OUR FIRST FAMILY DINNER
AND THE SIX OF US.
NOT THE THREE OF US,
THE SIX OF US.
- THREE PEOPLE, THREE DOGS,
JUST SO WE'’RE CLEAR.
SHE SPIT UP ALL OVER HERSELF AND
THE PILLOW THAT WAS DOWN THERE.
- AW.
- I'’M NOT WORRIED ABOUT IT.
- I GOT THIS CUTE OUTFIT
FOR HER.
ACTUALLY, FOR THE FUR BABIES
TOO.
- OH, YEAH?
CAN WE CHANGE THAT TO
"I AM YOUR OWNER"?
- STOP.
- THAT'’S WHAT SHE IS.
THEY'’RE DOGGIES.
YOU'’RE HUMAN.
- HELLO.
- I ALMOST CAN'’T BELIEVE
WHAT I SEE.
JENNI, I FEEL, IS
BEING A LITTLE RIDICULOUS.
DADDY DRESSED THE BABY.
GUESS WHAT MOMMY GETS TO DRESS.
SHE GETS TO DRESS THE IDIOTS.
SHE DOES TREAT HER DOGS--
OUR DOGS--LIKE HUMANS,
EVEN THOUGH IT DRIVES ME
A LITTLE NUTS.
- COME ON, GUYS.
PUT THESE ON.
UH-OH.
- THAT'’S TIGHT ON THAT BIG BOY.
- I DON'’T KNOW
IF IT'’S GONNA FIT YOU, BUBBY.
COME HERE, BUBBY.
AH, THERE WE GO.
I THINK MAMA GOT THE WRONG SIZE.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU BELONG
IN THE '’80s.
- DO YOU FEEL STUPID, DIESEL?
AND DON'’T YOU LOOK FOOLISH.
- MOMMY'’S SORRY.
[laughs]
MOMMY'’S SORRY.
SO THE ONESIES
KIND OF, YEAH, THEY DON'’T WORK
FOR THE DOGS THAT MUCH.
DIESEL'’S AND BELLA'’S IS
A LITTLE SNUG, BUT WE'’RE GONNA
MAKE THE BEST EFFORT,
SO WE CAN HAVE A FAMILY DINNER
TOGETHER AND EVERYONE
WEAR THEIR CUTE OUTFITS.
FIRST FAMILY MEAL.
TO OUR FAMILY.
- TO OUR VERY UNRESTED YET...
- PERFECT.
- PERFECT FAMILY.
DIESEL, YOU STINK, MAN.
- OH.
ONE BIG, HAPPY FAMILY?
[dog barks]
BE ANGELS!
- WHAT IS THIS?
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT?
- THIS ONE DOESN'’T
HAVE CONDITIONER.
- WHAT?
- DID YOU GUYS [bleep] UP?
MOM, THEY'’RE CHAOTIC.
WHAT DID YOU FORGET TO DO?
- NOTHING.
- WHAT'’D YOU FORGET
TO PUT IN THE BAGS?
- SHE DOESN'’T WANT TO BE BLAMED.
- NOTHING!
SOME ARE SHAMPOO,
AND SOME ARE CONDITIONER.
- NO, EVERY BAG HAS--
- SOME GOT SHAMPOO.
SOME GOT CONDITIONER.
- SUPPOSED TO DO BOTH.
- WHOOPSIE.
- WE'’LL GO BACK IN
AND PUT ONE IN EACH.
BUT THEN THEY MIGHT GET TWO
CONDITIONERS AND ONE SHAMPOO.
THIS IS LIKE--
- YOU GUYS ARE MORONS.
- STUFFING BAGS WITH [bleep]--
- MY FRIENDS ARE ASS[bleep],
SO I'’M NOT SURPRISED
THAT MY FRIENDS,
YOU KNOW, MESSED UP MY BAGS
FOR ALL OF MY GUESTS.
BUT I MEAN,
AS LONG AS THEY GET SOMETHING,
THAT'’S ALL THAT MATTERS.
- ALL THE ONES
I SAW I SWEAR SAID CONDITIONER.
- YOU WERE THE ONE
THAT DID THAT.
- I WAS THINKING, IN MY HEAD,
WHY ARE THEY ALL CONDITIONER?
- AND YOU'’RE THE MAID OF HONOR.
- I THINK THAT MEANS
STEPHANIE'’S DEMOTED.
IF ANYONE AGREES.
- YOU CAN HAVE MY JOB, TRUST ME.
- STEPHANIE JUST FELL
OUT OF FIRST PLACE,
AND I'’M COMING IN HOT.
- [bleep] IDIOTS.
YOU'’RE ALL FIRED.
[phone rings]
- WHY ARE YOU CALLING ME?
- I GOT SOME STOGIES.
NO KID HERE. NO GIRL HERE.
I FIGURED WE'’D HAVE
SOME STOGIES.
- OKAY. YOU WANT ME
TO COME OVER THERE, THEN.
- YEAH, COME HERE.
NO ONE'’S HERE. WE CAN GET WILD.
- OKAY. COOL, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, I'’LL BE RIGHT THERE.
SO I'’M NOT MUCH
OF A CIGAR SMOKER.
JIONNI CLEARLY IS,
'’CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
CIGARS HAVE BEEN LINKED
TO STUNTING YOUR GROWTH.
SO...
- BRO, WHAT'’S UP?
- THE TRUTH HURTS SOMETIMES,
MY FRIEND.
- MY DAD SMOKES CIGARS, OKAY?
HE'’S 5'’2".
- I REST MY CASE.
- MY GRANDFATHER SMOKES CIGARS.
HE'’S 5'’3".
- THERE YOU GO.
- SO HOW'’S IT GOING?
- SO IT IS THE GREATEST THING
THAT HAS EVER HAPPENED TO ME
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE,
HANDS DOWN, BAR NONE.
- YEAH?
- LITERALLY.
I'’M SO OBSESSED WITH HER
YOU CAN'’T IMAGINE.
I DON'’T WANT TO BE AWAY FROM HER
FOR MORE THAN AN HOUR.
IT'’S CRAZY. I'’M SO IN LOVE
WITH THAT LITTLE GIRL.
- GOOD FEELING.
- I LOVE CLEANING HER POOP.
THAT'’S HOW MUCH I LOVE HER.
WELL, SHE'’S A GIRL, SO
SOMETIMES IT GETS ON HER--HER--
- CHOCHA?
- CHOCHA.
- YOU WIPE UP OR DOWN?
- YOU HAVE TO WIPE AWAY.
YOU CAN'’T WIPE TOWARDS IT. YEAH.
- WIPE DOWN?
LORENZO GETS POOP ALL OVER
HIS WIENER AND BELLY BUTTON.
- [laughs]
- YOU'’RE--
[laughter in background]
WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
- CREEPY-ASS DOLL BEHIND YOU.
WHY IS THAT THERE?
- WHY DID THAT JUST GO OFF?
ARE YOU [bleep] WITH ME?
- YEAH, I GOT A REMOTE CONTROL
IN MY CIGAR.
THIS CREEPY DOLL LITERALLY
SHOWED UP OUT OF NOWHERE.
IT WASN'’T THERE WHEN I SAT DOWN,
I'’M ALMOST POSITIVE.
- DO YOU KNOW I'’M SLEEPING
BY MYSELF TONIGHT?
- I DIDN'’T EVEN SEE IT
WHEN I GOT OUT HERE.
- ME NEITHER. THAT WASN'’T THERE
THE WHOLE TIME?
- I DIDN'’T SEE IT.
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
HAVE YOU--
HAD YOU SEEN IT PRIOR TO THAT?
- NO.
- SO WEIRD.
- I'’M TELLING YOU,
THERE'’S THINGS AMONG US.
- [laughs]
WHERE DID IT COME FROM,
AND WHY IS IT MAKING NOISES?
- ONE OF THE GAY JOEYS
PROBABLY BROUGHT IT.
[doll laughs]
- SHOULD HAVE LEFT
MY HAIR DIRTY.
IT WOULD'’VE CURLED BETTER.
I KNEW IT.
- MAMA.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HUH?
LET ME SEE
YOUR WRESTLING STANCE.
YEAH!
- I'’M GONNA LEAVE NOW,
ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- AND I'’LL MEET YOU OVER THERE.
HOPEFULLY, SHORTLY.
- WHERE'’S LORENZO?
- HE'’S RIGHT HERE.
- I GOTTA GET A Q-TIP.
- GOOD MORNING, GOOD MORNING.
- LORENZO.
YOU GOTTA GET READY.
- NO.
- HAPPY BRIDAL SHOWER DAY!
- CAN YOU GET HIM READY?
GET IT TOGETHER, LORENZO.
LET'’S GO.
- NO.
- YES.
YOU'’RE NOT GONNA MAKE ME LATE
FOR MOMMY'’S BRIDAL SHOWER.
I DEFINITELY JUST GIVE UP
WITH LORENZO SOMETIMES.
HE'’S BEEN A LITTLE BRAT LATELY,
SO YOU BASICALLY
JUST HAVE TO LET HIM GO
AND DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
I MEAN, HE'’S A TODDLER NOW,
SO IT'’S DEFINITELY HARDER.
- [wails]
- COME ON, LORENZO.
- [sighs]
- YOU'’RE NOT GONNA MAKE THIS
EASY, ARE YOU?
- I'’M SO EXCITED
JUST TO GET TO MY BRIDAL SHOWER,
FIRST, BECAUSE I JUST
WANT TO MAKE SURE
ALL THE DECORATIONS LOOK GOOD,
EVERYTHING LOOKS SET
BEFORE EVERYBODY GETS THERE.
SO I JUST HOPE
ALL MY BRIDESMAIDS ARE THERE
BECAUSE THEY HAVE WORK TO DO.
READY, KIDS?
- READY.
- LET'’S GET THIS PARTY STARTED.
- YEAH.
[indistinct chatter]
- WE'’RE GOOD.
COME ON, WE'’RE GONNA GO INSIDE.
GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- YOU MIGHT WANNA--
- MAYBE ON THE NAPKINS BETTER.
- I HAVE TO POOP.
SO RIGHT WHEN I GET
TO MY BRIDAL SHOWER,
EVERYTHING LOOKS
REALLY, REALLY NICE.
I MEAN, IT JUST LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
THIS IS MORE
THAN I EXPECTED IT WOULD LOOK.
AND I WAS SCARED IT WAS GONNA
LOOK A LITTLE CHEESY,
BUT IT LITERALLY LOOKS AMAZING.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'’S GET THIS PARTY STARTED.
- OH, THAT'’S A CUTE IDEA
FOR EACH BAG.
- LORENZO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HERE, START--START STUFFING.
LORENZO!
- I WANT TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'’M YOUR MAITRE D'’ FOR TODAY.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- THIS IS VANESSA,
YOUR HEAD SERVER.
- HI. WHAT'’S A MAITRE D'’?
- HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- I'’M YOUR BANQUET MANAGER.
- SO LIKE MY BITCH.
- KIND OF, YEAH.
IF YOU WANT ME TO BE,
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- I GOT A BITCH FOR THE DAY.
MMM, I'’M STARVING.
- ALL RIGHT, HONEY, I'’M GONNA
PUT THIS IN THE FRIDGE.
- BITCH FOR THE DAY.
I LOVE IT.
I DESIGNED THIS,
LIKE, REALLY GOOD.
- I KNOW.
- YOU DID.
- I SHOULD BE AN EVENT PLANNER.
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
- HI.
- WHORES!
- IT WAS, LIKE, THREE HOURS.
- I LOVE THAT.
- YEAH, FROM THE SHORE.
I'’VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU [bleep].
HI, GUYS.
- HI, MUFFIN.
- MWAH.
- I LOVE IT.
- SQUIRREL.
- HI, SQUIRREL.
YOU LOOK SO GOOD.
- THANK YOU.
DO I LOOK GATSBY?
- YES.
- YOU LOOK PRETTY.
- YOU LOOK AWESOME.
DID YOU GET LAID?
- I GOT LAID THE VERY LAST DAY.
- REALLY?
- HE'’S SO HOT, THOUGH, YEAH.
AND I [bleep] HIM.
- ARE YOU GONNA
BE HIS BOYFRIEND?
- I WANT HIM TO BE MY BOYFRIEND.
HE WAS SO CUTE, RIGHT?
- HE'’S HOT.
- THANK GOD.
- AND WHAT GAVE YOU THIS IDEA?
- WELL, ME AND JIONNI
WATCHED THE GREAT GATSBYMOVIE,
AND WE WERE THINKING
ABOUT A THEME FOR THE WEDDING.
AND I WAS LIKE,
THE GREAT GATSBY.
- I PARTY WITH JAY GATSBY.
- OH, MY GOD, I LOVE IT.
GATSBY.
- YOU DID.
- SO GATSBY.
HI, GRAM.
LOOK AT THESE.
GATSBY.
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'’RE GONNA NAME HER YET?
- GATSBY.
STOP IT. IT'’S SO GATSBY.
GATSBY.
ALL YOU NEED IS PEARLS.
SO GATSBY.
YOU GUYS LOOK SO GATSBY.
YOU LOOK SO GATSBY.
SO GATSBY.
GATSBY.
both: YES.
- GATSBY.
SO GATSBY.
VERY GATSBY.
GATSBY. GATSBY.
GATSBY.
SO GATSBY.
GIVE ME SOME GOOD SEX STUFF.
- GOOD SE--
OH, I CAN DO IT, BABY.
- WE'’RE GETTING BORED.
- OKAY.
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
- WHAT'’S YOUR IDEA?
YOU WANT TO GO ROB A BOAT?
- GO STEAL A BOAT.
I DARE YOU.
- DARE YOU TO STEAL A BOAT.
- I DARE YOU TO STEAL A BOAT.
STEAL THE RAINBOW BOAT.
IT'’S PERFECT.
- RIGHT?
- HE'’LL GET THAT BOAT.
SO OF COURSE THE JOEYS
WANT TO DO SOMETHING CRAZY,
AND SINCE WE'’RE BY THE RIVER,
THEY WANT TO GO
AND STEAL A BOAT.
AND I'’M TOTALLY DOWN FOR THAT.
I FEEL LIKE
IT'’S GONNA BE A [bleep] SHOW.
- OKAY, GIRLS.
I'’M A MARINE BIOLOGIST.
I'’M JUST HERE DOING A STUDY.
[gasps]
- I'’M NOT INTERESTED
IN GETTING ARRESTED TODAY.
- NO, WE'’RE NOT BREAKING
AND ENTERING.
OUR FRIENDS LIVE HERE.
- WE'’RE GONNA GET IN TROUBLE.
- HOW ARE WE GONNA GET
IN TROUBLE?
- ARE WE GONNA GET ARRESTED?
- IT'’S HOT IN HERE.
COME ON, GIRLS.
WHAT ARE YOU SO SCARED OF?
- I DON'’T WANT TO GO
ON A BOAT RIDE.
I ONLY CAME DOWN
'’CAUSE JOEY DRAGGED ME.
- WELL, HOW DO WE GET OFF NOW?
HELP HER ASS OUT.
THE SEAS ARE GETTING ROUGH NOW.
- EVERY TIME WE GO OUT,
BAD STUFF HAPPENS.
LIKE WE GET ARRESTED.
- HE'’S A MANIAC.
- HE'’S MY FAVORITE PERSON
IN THE WORLD.
- THIS EPISODE
OF SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- CONTINUES NOW.
- DID YOU STEAL A BOAT?
- YEAH.
I TRIED TO BREAK INTO THE BOAT,
SO I TRIED TO--
- I LOVE THESE.
I CAN SEE.
- AND I WENT--
- THIS IS LIKE HD.
- YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
- THANK YOU.
THIS IS HD.
- THANKS, FELICIA.
- SO THE BRIDESMAIDS MADE SURE
THERE WERE SOME GAMES
TO PLAY AT THE PARTY,
WHICH WAS SO COOL.
YOU GUYS BETTER KNOW
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THESE.
- OH, THE THREE-LEGGED ANIMAL.
YOUR CAT.
- YOU DON'’T KNOW MY CAT'’S NAME?
- JUST GIVE ME THAT.
- YOU GUYS SUCK.
- WHAT IS NICOLE'’S
FAVORITE THING ABOUT JIONNI?
HIS SENSE OF HUMOR.
- AND HIS WIENER.
[laughs]
JANIS TOLD ME TO KEEP IT PG.
[laughter]
OOH, LOOK AT ALL MY PRESENTS.
KITCHEN.
- OH, WAIT,
YOU DIDN'’T OPEN THIS EITHER.
I BOUGHT YOU YOUR LINGERIE
FOR YOUR HONEYMOON.
- THE ONE WEIRD THING
THAT JANIS GOT ME WAS LINGERIE.
A LITTLE WEIRD.
WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
I'’M GONNA GET PREGNANT AGAIN.
- THAT'’S OKAY.
- OOH. IT'’S FOR MY NURSERY.
I REGISTERED FOR THAT.
- ♪ KEEPING IT TRUE
♪ THROUGH A DARK DEBUT
♪ I'’M SHEDDING LIGHT
ON SOMETHING NEW ♪
♪ GOTTA BEND BEFORE YOU MOVE
- [laughs]
GOD!
- STOP, I JUST PEED.
- OH!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LOVE YOU.
- GOOD SEEING YOU.
SEE YOU AGAIN SOON.
- THANK YOU GUYS FOR COMING.
WE LOOK LIKE ASS[bleep]
TOGETHER.
LORENZO, STOP.
OW! YOU'’RE SQUISHING IT.
I WANTED EVERYTHING TO BE GOOD
AND PERFECT, AND IT WAS,
AND I'’VE LITERALLY BEEN PLANNING
THIS WEDDING FOR TWO YEARS,
AND I JUST CAN'’T WAIT
FOR THE DAY.
YOU KNOW, OBVIOUSLY ENJOY IT,
HAVE THE BEST DAY OF MY LIFE,
SO I CAN SAY
THAT JIONNI'’S MY HUSBAND.
YOU'’RE BEING BAD.
MM, I LOVE YOU.
- NEXT TIME
ON SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
MY NAME IS ESTHER,
AND I WAS WONDERING
ABOUT ETIQUETTE CLASSES.
- DO YOU HAVE A LAST NAME,
ESTHER?
- M-C-F-A-R-L-E-Y.
- [laughing] ESTHER MCFARLEY.
- OKAY.
- I'’VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU, JENNI.
- OH, GOOD LORD.
I DON'’T EVEN UNDERSTAND WHAT
THE HELL HE'’S SO UPSET ABOUT.
JUST ME AND YOU NOW.