- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- BRING THE HANDS FORWARD.
- I FEEL LIKE THIS COULD
ACTUALLY BRING ON LABOR.
- IT'S GONNA POP OUT
THAT BABY.
I WANT TO DO
THE TELEPHONES.
WITH STRING.
- THAT DOES NOT WORK.
- SOMETHING'S LEAKING
OUT OF ME.
- IS IT PEE,
OR DID YOUR WATER BREAK?
- IT LOOKED
LIKE SNOT.
- THAT'S YOUR
MUCOUS PLUG.
- I THINK IT IS.
- YOU'RE GOING
INTO LABOR.
- * I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
[pop music playing]
- ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA GO SEE AUNT JENNI.
AND WE'RE GONNA
MAKE TELEPHONES.
WHAT DO YOU DO
WITH A TELEPHONE?
HELLO.
BLUH-BLUH-BLUH-BLUH.
SO TODAY, I'M GONNA TAKE LORENZO
OVER TO JENNI'S HOUSE
AND HANG OUT,
AND JENNI IS, YOU KNOW,
NINE MONTHS PREGNANT.
HER LIFE
IS COMPLETELY CHANGING,
AND SHE JUST HAS
NO IDEA YET,
SO WHY NOT HANG OUT WITH HER
EVERY SINGLE DAY?
CAN YOU SAY "JENNI"?
- NO.
- WHY?
SUCH A BRAT.
THAT'S YOUR GODMOMMY.
IF I DIE,
SHE'S YOUR NEW MOMMY.
- [laughs]
- THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
I'M GONNA DIE.
REMEMBER WE TALKED
ABOUT MAKING A PHONE?
- OH, YEAH.
- I BOUGHT STRING.
- I HAVE CANS.
- WE CAN TIE THEM TOGETHER
AND THEN SEE IF THEY WORK.
- I BROUGHT STRING
OVER TO JENNI'S,
BECAUSE I WANT TO TRY
AND MAKE THESE TELEPHONE CANS.
AND I ALWAYS FEEL LIKE NEIGHBORS
DO THESE KINDS OF THINGS.
LIKE, THE KIDS.
- YEAH.
- LIKE WHEN THEY WANT TO, LIKE,
TALK TO EACH OTHER,
AND IT'S, LIKE,
TOO LATE.
YOU KNOW, THEY WANT TO BE LIKE,
"HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?"
LIKE, I WANT TO BE LIKE THAT,
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE ADULTS.
- WITH CELL PHONES.
TO BE LIKE,
"HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?"
WE GOT TO MAKE THIS WORK.
ROGER DOESN'T THINK
IT'S GONNA WORK.
AND I HAVE TO PROVE
HIM WRONG LIKE ALWAYS.
- WE'LL PROVE HIM WRONG.
JIONNI SAID
IT WORKS, SO...
WHAT, YOU DON'T
BELIEVE MY MAN?
YOU'RE RUDE.
- I WOULD LOVE FOR IT TO, LIKE,
REALLY, REALLY WORK,
ENOUGH FOR ROGER
TO, LIKE, NOT DENY IT,
'CAUSE I HATE
WHEN HE'S RIGHT.
SO ANNOYING.
- 'CAUSE HE THINKS
EVERYTHING IS...
- LOGIC, AND HIS WAY, AND...
- 'CAUSE SOMETIMES
EVERYTHING CAN BE MAGICAL.
[harp playing]
AND THIS IS MAGICAL.
- [laughs]
WHAT THE [bleep]?
OH, MY GOD.
"MAGICAL."
- I DON'T KNOW.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
- EW. IT SMELLS LIKE FISH.
- [laughs]
- YOUR ARMPITS SMELL.
- WHAT THE [bleep]?
- WHAT?
YOU HEARD IT?
- CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- [screams]
I HEAR YOU!
VAGINA HOLE.
- VAGINA HOLE.
- I HEAR YOU!
IT WORKS!
- I HAD NO IDEA.
- WE'RE GENIUSES.
WE SHOULD SELL
THIS [bleep].
I CAN HEAR JENNI
IN THE FRICKIN' CAN.
- IT'S CREEPY.
- IT'S SO WEIRD.
- YEAH.
WE'RE FANCY NOW.
WE INVENTED IT.
- YEAH.
WE'RE, LIKE, REALLY SMART.
- WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH STRING.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA ADD, THEN?
- I HAVE, LIKE, RIBBON.
WE DID IT, BUT WE
HAVE TO CONNECT HOUSES.
- AND THEN WE CAN SEE
IF THE [bleep] WORKS.
HOW ARE YOU GONNA
GET IT TO ME?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T FIGURED
THAT PART OUT YET.
- TIE IT ON A BROOM,
AND THEN LIFT THE BROOM UP.
MACGYVER THAT [bleep].
- DO YOU HAVE
A 25-FOOT BROOM?
OH, [bleep].
- WHAT?
[screams]
WHOA!
- ALL RIGHT.
both:
YEAH!
- I JUST WENT
INTO LABOR.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
HELLO?
- HELLO.
- OH!
HEY, I CAN HEAR YOU.
WE PROVED ROGER WRONG.
- MM-HMM.
- AND I CAN'T WAIT
FOR HIM TO LISTEN.
- HE'S GONNA FREAK OUT.
- MM-HMM.
HE'S GONNA TRY AND DENY IT.
- HE'LL BE LIKE, "NO,
I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING."
- YEAH.
[laughs]
- WHAT'S UP?
- NOTHING MUCH.
WHAT YOU DOING?
- I HAVE TO GO POOP.
- DO NOT TAKE THIS
IN THE BATHROOM WITH YOU.
- OKAY.
- I CAN HEAR YOU RIGHT THERE.
WE COULD JUST YELL
OUT THE WINDOW.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
ALL RIGHT.
SHE CLOSED THE WINDOW.
BYE.
- BYE.
- * OUTSIDE
* ON THE BACK PORCH
- FIGHT NIGHT!
- WE LEFT LORENZO HOME.
IT'S BEDTIME.
HE'S WITH A BABYSITTER.
ADULT NIGHT.
- LET'S GET WASTED.
- WHOO!
- BABE.
- YEAH.
- I HAD AN ACCIDENT AGAIN.
- YOU PEED?
[laughs]
- YOU PEED YOUR PANTS?
- GO CHANGE
YOUR PANTS.
- WHEN'D YOU PEE YOUR PANTS?
- I TRIED TO HOLD MY SNEEZE
GOING UP THE STAIRS.
- HAH.
- DID YOU GO RIGHT THROUGH YOUR
GREAT BIG, GIANT GRANNY PANTIES?
- I PEED THE FLOOR
A LITTLE BIT.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T.
- YOU PEED ON THE FLOOR?
- OH, MY GOOD LORD.
WHY DO YOU THINK NICOLE
DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
WHEN SHE FLUSHED HER UNDERWEAR
DOWN THE TOILET
IN THE JERSEY SHORE HOUSE,
AND PLUGGED THE TOILET UP?
- WHAT DID SHE DO?
- I WAS DRUNK AND I
LEFT MY PERIOD UNDIES.
- EW.
- 'CAUSE I DID IT
ON PURPOSE, JIONNI.
YOU'RE SO MEAN!
- YOU DO IT EVERY
OTHER MONTH AT OUR HOUSE.
- YOU'RE SO MEAN.
- I SEE UNDERWEAR
WITH BROWN, RED, YELLOW...
- IT WAS MY SHORTS.
IT WAS MY SLEEP SHORTS.
EVERYBODY POOPS,
AND SOMETIMES THINGS HAPPEN.
I'M PREGNANT.
IT'S SOMETIMES HARD
TO GET BACK THERE.
- I SAW A PAIR OF SHORTS
WITH POOP STAINS.
I'M LIKE, "NICOLE."
I GO, "YOUR UNDERWEAR
DISGUSTS--"
SHE GOES,
"THEY'RE MY SHORTS."
- IT WAS MY SLEEP SHORTS.
- IT'S JUST THE SHORTS.
GREAT.
THAT'S OKAY.
[bleep] IN YOUR SLEEP SHORTS.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- OW. OW.
- THAT'S FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THEY'RE SLEEP SHORTS.
- IT MUST HAVE BEEN
A FART OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
DIESEL, THEY'RE
MAKING FUN OF ME.
- ROGER SHARTED TOO, ONCE,
AND HE HAD TO THROW HIS
UNDERWEAR OUT.
- EXACTLY.
IT HAPPENED AT WORK TWICE,
AND I'LL READILY ADMIT IT.
- I'M DEFINITELY EMOTIONAL--
I'M A ROLLERCOASTER--
SO YOU NEVER KNOW.
IF JIONNI SAYS SOMETHING,
I CAN EITHER LAUGH,
I CAN CRY,
OR I CAN PUNCH HIM
IN THE FACE.
- I WOULD LOVE TO SEE YOU
PUNCH HIM IN THE FACE.
- NO, I CAN'T.
BUT I WANT TO.
IS THAT CHANNING TATUM?
- THIS IS--YEAH.
- HE'S JACKED.
- [bleep] IS IS NAME?
EVERYBODY HAS A FREE PASS?
- WHO'S YOURS?
- MINE OR HERS?
- YOURS.
I KNOW HERS.
- WHO'S HERS?
- TOM HARDY.
- YEAH, TOM HARDY.
- I HAVE A NEW ONE THAT I LIKE.
- WHO?
WHO?
- THAT GIRL, UH--
I HAVE A FEW, ACTUALLY.
- OH, WAIT, THE BLONDE
THAT TURNS INTO THE--
- JENNIFER LAWRENCE?
- SCARLETT JOHANSSON.
- OH, YEAH,
I LIKE JENNIFER LAWRENCE.
- I DON'T LIKE HER ANYMORE.
THANKS A LOT.
YOU'RE SO STUPID.
WHY DO YOU HAVE A FEW NOW?
- WHY ARE YOU
CHECKING OUT OTHER GIRLS
LIKE I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH?
- J.LO, SCARLETT JOHANSSON,
JENNIFER LAWRENCE.
IF WE WERE IN THE WILDERNESS,
SHE'D PROTECT ME.
- I WOULDN'T?
- SHE'D HAVE A CROSSBOW
AND KILL THINGS,
AND WE COULD EAT TOGETHER.
- JIONNI, IT'S A MOVIE.
- YOU'RE AFRAID OF SPIDERS.
- SHE'S ACTING. SHE'S ACTING.
IT'S NOT REAL.
- I BET YOU--I GUARANTEE YOU SHE
COULD SHOOT A BOW AND ARROW.
- GO BE WITH HER, THEN.
- YOU HATE SPIDERS.
IF WE WERE IN THE WILDERNESS,
JENNIFER LAWRENCE
WOULD BE GOOD TO BE WITH.
- SO YOU WOULD LEAVE ME
SO YOU CAN SURVIVE?
YOU HAVE A FEW NOW?
- OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU FOR REAL?
- I DON'T LIKE YOU.
[bleep].
- STOP. I'M KIDDING.
- NO, YOU'RE NOT.
- IT'S JUST J.LO.
IT'S JUST J.LO.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
I DON'T EVEN LOOK
AT OTHER GUYS AND SAY,
"OOH, I WANT TO HAVE
SEX WITH HIM."
- I SAID ONE.
- YOUR ASS IS HAIRY.
YOU SMELL LIKE BALLS.
ALL THE TIME.
- SHUT--
- I'M GONNA GIVE BIRTH.
- HERE, LET'S CALL AUNT JENNI.
- OVER THERE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THIS IS NOT
HOW YOU DO THROW PILLOWS.
- HERE.
I DON'T DO THROW PILLOWS.
- JENNI!
IS THIS HOW IT WORKS?
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT IS SHE DOING?
- CAN YOU LISTEN?
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
- SO NICOLE'S YELLING AT ME TO
TELL ME TO PICK UP MY PHONE CAN,
AND I'M DYING FOR MR. ROGER
TO COME CHECK IT OUT.
BABE, THE THING DOESN'T HAVE
A RINGER ON IT.
IT'S NOT LIKE I KNOW
SHE'S CALLING ME
RIGHT NOW
FROM THE TELEPHONE.
- YOU JUST HAD A CONVERSATION
THROUGH THIS WINDOW,
AND NOW YOU'RE GONNA GO
OVER TO THE TELEPHONE WINDOW,
AND YOU'RE GONNA HOLD
THE THING UP TO YOUR EAR.
YOU COULD HEAR HER FINE
THROUGH THIS WINDOW,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA ACT
LIKE IT MAGICALLY
IS COMING THROUGH THAT.
RIGHT.
I DEFINITELY DO NOT THINK, BY
ANY STRETCH OF THE IMAGINATION,
THAT THE CAN PHONE'S
GONNA WORK.
NO WAY.
THESE TWO WACKOS,
THEY'RE JUST KIND OF SCREAMING
BACK AND FORTH AT EACH OTHER...
- ALL RIGHT,
TIGHTEN IT!
- PULL IT!
- AND, YOU KNOW, TOTALLY
DEFEATING THE PURPOSE
OF THIS CAN PHONE DESIGN
THAT THEY CAME UP WITH.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- [gasps]
SEE?
[bleep] LISTEN.
- WHAT'D SHE SAY?
- LISTEN.
- WHAT DID SHE SAY?
- LISTEN!
- I DON'T WANT TO LISTEN.
I DON'T WANT TO LISTEN.
- THEY'RE ARGUING.
[laughs]
- YOU CAN'T TELL ME
WHAT SHE JUST SAID.
- YEAH, BUT WHY CAN'T YOU
LISTEN FOR YOURSELF?
ROGER'S GONNA TALK TO--
LISTEN!
MAKE SURE IT'S TIGHT.
- ROGER.
- YOU HEAR HIM TALKING IN THERE.
- I CAN ACTUALLY HEAR SOMETHING.
- I TOLD YOU!
- ROGER, DO YOU GUYS
WANT TO GO TO THE PARK?
- HOW THE [bleep]
IS THAT POSSIBLE?
- [laughing]
- HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
- I TOLD YOU!
- I CAN ACTUALLY
HEAR HIM THROUGH THERE.
HE JUST SAID, "ROGER, DO YOU
WANT TO GO TO THE PARK?"
- SEE?
- HOW THE [bleep] IS THAT--
AND I'M THE IDIOT.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M DONE SECOND-GUESSING YOU.
IF YOU TELL ME BELLA
CAN FLY TOMORROW,
I'M GONNA JUST BELIEVE IT.
- YAY.
- WHO'S THE IDIOT NOW, ROGER?
- I'M--I CONCEDE.
I'M AN IDIOT.
WHY DON'T WE
HAVE STRINGS
RUNNING ALL ACROSS
THE UNITED STATES, THEN?
- WE DO.
TELEPHONE POLES.
- IT'S NOT--
IT'S DIFFERENT.
- THEY DIDN'T
ANSWER THE QUESTION.
- WHY'D THEY HANG UP?
ARE YOU GUYS
STILL THERE?
ARE YOU STILL THERE?
- HOW ANNOYING.
THEY'RE STRAINING TO HEAR US,
BUT NO ONE'S TALKING BACK.
- THEY HUNG UP.
[whimsical pop music playing]
*
- WHAT IF OUR GIRL
IS NOT PRETTY?
WHAT DO WE DO?
I DON'T THINK YOU
WOULD ADMIT IT
IF WE HAD A LITTLE BIT
OF A HOMELY BABY.
I WOULD ADMIT IT.
- I WOULD JUST BE DOING
A LOT OF NICE THINGS FOR HER.
- A LOT OF BOWS,
A LOT OF ACCESSORIES?
- A LOT OF BOWS, A LOT
OF ACCESSORIES.
FIX THE EYEBROWS.
PUT A LITTLE ROUGE
ON THE CHEEKS.
- I REALLY DON'T THINK
SHE'S GOING TO BE.
- I WOULD REALLY
DO THAT, THOUGH.
- I KNOW.
- BEING CUTE--
- NOBODY WANTS AN UGLY BABY.
- BEING CUTE IS GONNA
MAKE HER LIFE EASIER.
THAT'S JUST THE FACT
OF THE MATTER.
YOU WOULD BE WHERE YOU WERE
IF YOU WEREN'T PRETTY,
AND [bleep]
A LOT OF [bleep].
- WE ALL KNOW
I DON'T DO THAT.
- TRUE.
SAW MY BUDDY SCOTT
AT THE GYM TODAY.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT--
I WAS LIKE,
"I'M GONNA BE A DADDY TODAY,
I'M SUPER EXCITED,"
AND HE WAS LIKE, "OH,
IT'S THE GREATEST THING,"
BUT HE SAYS,
"I GOT TO TELL YOU"--
HE SAID, "YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE GONNA BE HUMBLED."
HE SAID, "YOU'RE GONNA
ASK A LOT OF QUESTIONS,
"'CAUSE EVERY GUY
THAT COMES IN THAT ROOM
STICKS A FINGER
IN YOUR WIFE."
HE GOES, "I SWEAR, THE SECURITY
GUY, THE GUY DELIVERING LUNCH,
"STUCK A FINGER
IN MY WIFE AND WAS LIKE,
'OH, YEAH,
THREE CENTIMETERS DILATED.'"
AND HE'S LIKE,
"EVERYBODY'S"--
- NOBODY'S GOING UP THERE
UNLESS HE'S DR. REZAI.
- THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
HE SAID, "EVERYBODY THAT COMES
IN IS JUST, 'PFFT.'"
- EW!
NO TOUCHY.
- OH, HEY.
[dogs barking]
JENNI'S ASKED ME
TO COME OVER
BECAUSE SHE WANTS TO EXPLAIN
TO ME HOW TO WATCH HER DOGS
WHEN SHE'S GIVING BIRTH.
AHH!
OH, MY GOD.
DIESEL, PLEASE.
- GET YOUR BALL.
THERE YOU GO.
AS LONG AS I'VE
KNOWN THIS BITCH,
SHE'S OBSESSED
WITH HER DOGS.
IT'S GONNA BE EASY
TAKING CARE OF THE DOGS.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS FEED THEM,
LOVE THEM, AND WALK THEM.
THEY'RE DOGS.
- THEY'RE MY DOGS, THOUGH.
- YOU'RE CRAZY.
BELLA, PLEASE.
- SO, THE DOGGIE TO-DO LIST.
MAKE SURE YOU HAVE WATER OUT OF
THE FILTRATION SYSTEM FOR THEM.
DIESEL LIKES FIVE ICE CUBES.
AND THEN I HAVE GROUND TURKEY,
AND IF YOU COULD JUST SAUTEE
THAT UP INTO SMALL BITES,
THEY LIKE THAT FOR DINNER.
BRUSH THEIR TEETH DAILY.
DIESEL NEEDS
HIS AROMATHERAPY BATH.
- IS THAT A JOKE?
- NO.
- SERIOUSLY?
- SERIOUSLY.
- SHE'S CRAZY.
THESE DOGS ARE VERY
HIGH-MAINTENANCE.
I FEEL LIKE THEY DON'T
EVEN THINK THEY'RE DOGS.
THEY THINK THEY'RE PEOPLE.
- DIESEL LOVES
HIS LEGS MASSAGED.
THREE WALKS A DAY.
- [groans]
- GIRLS NEED A MANI.
BELLA LOVES PINK,
NOEL LOVES PURPLE.
BELLA'S A DIVA.
SHE LOVES HER NAILS PAINTED.
SHE LOVES DRESS-UP.
- I CAN'T.
- THEY LOVE MASSAGES.
I DON'T SEE
WHAT THE BIG DEAL IS.
AND THAT'S REALLY IT.
I MEAN,
IT'S NOTHING MUCH.
- YOU'RE A PSYCHO.
- I'M NOT A PSYCHO.
- YOU'RE A CRAZY DOG LADY.
I WANT TO SHOOT MYSELF
IN THE HEAD.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
- WELCOME TO MY HELL.
- ONE, TWO,
THREE.
- I GOT LORENZO A LITTLE BOUNCE
HOUSE FOR THE BACK YARD.
AT HOME, HE LOVED
THE TRAMPOLINE,
SO I THINK, YOU KNOW,
SETTING IT UP,
YOU KNOW, BLOWING IT UP--
HE'LL LOVE IT.
- WHOA!
A BOUNCE HOUSE!
WHAT?
WANT TO COME IN REAL QUICK?
- NO.
- WHY?
ARE YOU SCARED?
- BRING HIM IN WITH YOU.
- COME HERE, BABY.
- NO.
- JUST TAKE HIM!
- I'M TRYING.
- [whines]
- HE DOESN'T WANT TO.
- IF HE GOES IN WITH YOU,
HE'LL HAVE FUN.
- NO!
MAMA.
- HE'S TERRIFIED.
- [crying]
- JUST TRY IT.
JUST TRY IT WITH MOM.
GO IN WITH HIM.
HURRY.
- THERE YOU GO.
GO, NICOLE.
- MOMMY'S COMING.
MOMMY'S COMING.
WHEE!
- MAMA!
- CAN YOU GIVE ME THE BALL?
- LORENZO, GO GET THE BALL.
- THAT'S SUCH A FAKE CRY.
- I JUST FEEL LIKE HE NEEDS
TO GET USED TO THINGS,
AND GET,
YOU KNOW, ACCLIMATED.
MY MOM TAUGHT ME
THAT WORD.
- ALL RIGHT.
COME ON.
- HEY, GO DOWN THE SLIDE.
- NO!
I DON'T WANT TO.
- WHOA!
- WHEE!
both:
YAY!
- LORENZO?
- IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
YOU DON'T LIKE IT.
IT'S OKAY.
WHEE!
- NO.
- HOW YOU DOING, BABE?
- SHE'S GONNA FALL OUT.
- ROGER AND I ARE
AT THE DOCTOR'S TODAY
TO GET OUR LAST ULTRASOUND,
AND IF SHE'S BIG ENOUGH,
WE'RE GONNA SCHEDULE
AN INDUCTION.
- ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S BABY'S HEAD.
GOOD-SIZED HEAD.
LET'S GET AN IDEA APPROXIMATELY
WHAT SIZE THIS BABY IS.
THIS WAY WE CAN TELL DR. REZAI
AND SEE HOW IT ALL TURNS OUT.
APPROXIMATELY EIGHT POUNDS,
TWO OUNCES RIGHT NOW,
GIVE OR TAKE
ABOUT A POUND.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO THE HEART,
'CAUSE THERE'S THE HEART.
YOU SEE IT BEATING RIGHT THERE?
- YEAH.
- WE MADE THAT
LITTLE HEARTBEAT.
- I KNOW.
- 144 BEATS PER MINUTE.
- OH, SHE'S SO PERFECT.
- SO EVERYTHING
LOOKS GREAT.
I THINK WE'RE PRETTY CLOSE.
I'LL GO TALK
TO DR. REZAI,
AND I'LL BE BACK
IN JUST A COUPLE MINUTES.
- OKAY, GREAT.
- THANK YOU.
- THANK YOU AGAIN.
- IT'S VERY SURREAL RIGHT NOW
TO THINK THAT NOW WE'RE
GONNA BE A FAMILY OF THREE.
IT'S SO CRAZY
THAT THERE'S GONNA BE
A COMBO OF
US IN THIS WORLD,
AND IN THIS HOUSE,
IN, LIKE, DAYS.
- REZAI'S ON THE PHONE.
- HI.
- HE WANTS TO TALK TO YOU.
- SURE.
UH, SATURDAY?
YEAH.
WHAT TIME WOULD THAT BE AROUND?
LIKE, UH--
OKAY.
7:00, 8:00 P.M.?
OKAY, GREAT.
OKAY.
AWESOME.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
BYE.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
- YES.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED, RIGHT?
SATURDAY?
- THANK GOD.
GET HER OUT.
I'M SCARED.
I'LL BE HONEST.
LIKE, I'M SUPER EXCITED.
I JUST WANT
MY DAUGHTER HERE.
- THAT IS REALLY GOOD NEWS,
LET ME TELL YOU.
I'M SUPER EXCITED.
- BUT REALITY SET IN,
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS
LABOR'S GONNA HAPPEN.
WHAT IF I'M NOT A GOOD MOM,
OR WHAT IF I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO DO SOMETHING?
LIKE, IT'S JUST ALL THOSE
BILLION QUESTIONS
THAT RUN THROUGH YOUR HEAD ARE
STARTING TO RUN THROUGH MINE.
I'M SCARED TO DEATH.
[dogs barking]
[line ringing]
- SHUT UP!
HEY!
NONE OF THAT.
- HELLO?
- GOD.
HI.
- HEY, BOO.
- SORRY.
I HAVE FIGHTING DOGS, PER USUAL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST EATING STRAWBERRIES.
- I JUST GOT
SOME REALLY GOOD NEWS.
I GOT AN INDUCTION DAY.
SATURDAY NIGHT
AT 8:00 P.M.
- MM-HMM.
- OH, I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
A LITTLE MORE EXCITED THAN THAT.
- OH. WHEE!
- YOU'RE THE MOM.
IF YOU WANT
TO HELP ME RUN THROUGH
AND SEE IF I'M MISSING ANYTHING,
OR IF YOU SUGGEST ANYTHING.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'LL COME OVER RIGHT NOW
AND WE'LL SET IT UP.
- THANK YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
OH! YEAH.
I DO HAVE ONE.
- THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S A STERILIZER?
BRR.
BRR, IT'S COLD IN HERE.
FREEZING.
- THE [bleep]?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT WORKS.
WELL, THERE'S THIS STERILIZER
THAT YOU CAN USE
FOR THE BOTTLES--
- DOES IT GET TIRING?
- UM, YEAH.
- LORENZO'S STILL
ON THE BOTTLE, NO?
- SHUT UP!
- WHAT?
BUT I'M SAYING, LIKE--
I STILL DON'T STERILIZE IT.
HE CAN EAT HIS OWN BOOGERS.
I DON'T CARE.
- OH.
WHAT ELSE
DO I NEED?
- I DON'T REMEMBER.
I'M PREGNANT.
- SO AM I.
YOU'RE PREGNANT
WITH SATAN.
- YOU'RE PREGNANT
WITH A STRIPPER.
WHAT'S A HEMORRHOID FEEL LIKE?
- ITCHY.
LIKE, ANNOYING.
- OH.
- IT DOESN'T HURT, REALLY.
IT'S NOT EVEN ITCHY.
IT FEELS LIKE--
- MY BUTTHOLE HURTS.
- YEAH.
- BUT THERE'S NOTHING THERE.
THERE'S NO, LIKE, BUMPS.
- SO MAYBE YOU'RE JUST--
- MADE IT SORE.
- FROM STRAINING?
I DIDN'T DO
ANY BUTT SEX.
- NO, I'M JUST SAYING,
FROM STRAINING.
I DON'T STRAIN.
I TAKE THESE GREAT PRENATALS
THAT DON'T MAKE ME
HAVE THAT ISSUE.
THIS IS PREGNANCY PROBLEMS
NOBODY TELLS YOU ABOUT.
- YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
- I DON'T SPEAK SPANISH.
- WHY'S THIS IN SPANISH?
- YOURS TOO?
- AY-YI-YI.
- I'M SO HAPPY THAT NICOLE'S
HELPING ME WITH THE BABY
AND GETTING EVERYTHING READY.
- IS THIS THE TOP?
- I THINK IT GOES LIKE THAT.
- YOU SURE?
- NO.
- I FEEL LIKE THIS
IS VERY COMPLICATED.
- SOME OF THESE ARE.
THIS LOOKS
LIKE A UFO.
- I'M CONFUSED.
THIS ONE'S WAY
TOO COMPLICATED FOR ME.
- I GUESS SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT THE HELL TO DO,
AND I'M JUST LIKE,
MY POOR DAUGHTER.
HER FIRST WEEK OF LIFE
IS GONNA BE HELL.
- THIS IS A GOOD ONE.
- YEAH.
I HAVE IT IN PINK, TOO.
- DID YOU TRY IT ON?
- YEAH.
- YOU'LL SEE, LIKE--
YOUR BREAST MILK SMELLS BAD.
- OH, IT'S TERRIBLE.
- LIKE, IT STAINS.
IT SMELLS LIKE
COTTAGE CHEESE.
- EVERYTHING TO YOU
SMELLS LIKE COTTAGE CHEESE.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
YEAST INFECTIONS...
- WELL, I THINK
COTTAGE CHEESE SMELLS BAD.
THAT'S WHY I SAY IT.
I'M LIKE, EW.
- MM-HMM.
- BREAST MILK
DOES NOT SMELL GOOD.
- MY BUTTHOLE HURTS.
- SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
- MAYBE 'CAUSE I'M CONSTIPATED.
- I'M TAKING ROGER TO GET HIM
SOME VICTORY CIGARS
FOR WHEN MEILANI'S BORN.
WE COULD GO OUT BACK,
YOU KNOW,
WE COULD GO
AT THE HOSPITAL.
- DO YOU REALLY CONSIDER IT
A VICTORY HAVING A BABY,
OR IS IT
A CELEBRATORY CIGAR?
- BOTH.
- IT'S A VICTORY?
- VICTORY.
CELEBRATORY.
- [laughs]
"CELIBATORY?"
- EITHER WAY, I'M GONNA
GET SOME ROGER CIGARS.
WE'RE GONNA SMOKE THEM
AFTER MEILANI'S BORN.
- I WOULD LIKE TO BUY
SOME CELEBRATORY CIGARS,
'CAUSE I'M GONNA BE A DAD HERE
IN THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS.
- I'D LIKE
A MACANUDO, ROMEO...
- LIKE A ROMEO AND JULIETA?
- YEAH. THEY'RE PRETTY--
- I WOULD TRY A RESERVE.
- I PROBABLY WOULD CONSIDER
MYSELF A CIGAR 'FICIONADO.
- "FISH-CIONADO"?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE [bleep] WORD IS.
- "A-FICIONADO."
NOT "FISH-CIONADO."
- AFICIONADO!
E-FICIONADO?
- THE NUBS ARE ALSO
A REALLY GREAT CIGAR.
THEY LOOK LITTLE, BUT THEY
BURN FOR A REALLY LONG TIME.
IT'S A VERY GOOD ROLL.
BUT IT'S--YEAH,
IT'S A REALLY GOOD--
IT'S, LIKE,
PACKED REALLY TIGHT.
- THAT'S WHAT JIONNI LOOKS LIKE
WITH HIS PANTS OFF.
- I WAS WAITING FOR IT.
I SET HIM UP FOR IT.
- SO IT'S JENNI AND ROGER'S
LAST NIGHT OF FREEDOM
BEFORE THEY HAVE THE BABY.
- LET'S DO SOMETHING.
- WE GOT TO CELEBRATE.
WE GOT TO PARTY IT UP
BEFORE THEY'RE PARENTS.
- YEAH.
AFTER THIS, IT'S DONE.
- IT'S DONEZO.
- DONEZO.
- THEY'RE DONE.
- LET'S GO.
- CARLY IS THE BABYSITTER
FOR THE SUMMER,
AND I NEED HER TO COME
OVER TO WATCH LORENZO.
- YOU GONNA GO
NIGHT NIGHT?
- NO.
- WITH YOUR BLANKET
AND YOUR BA-BA?
- NO!
- I'LL GET THE NAPKINS.
- CHAMPAGNE.
- SPARKLING CIDER.
THAT'S MINE.
POP BOTTLES!
[imitates wolf howling]
- WHAT'S UP, NEIGHBOR?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- RELAXING.
- RELAXING?
- IT'S YOUR LAST NIGHT
OF FREEDOM.
- SCREW THAT [bleep].
WE'RE COMING OVER.
- PARTY'S HERE!
- EW!
SHUT UP, ROGER!
- CONGRATULATIONS,
JENNI AND ROGER.
- YEAH!
YAY!
- THAT HIT THE FENCE, BRO.
THAT WAS A GOOD SHOT.
- TO JENNI AND ROGER.
- CHEERS TO NEW PARENTS.
- YAY.
- LAST NIGHT.
- THANKS, GUYS.
- CHEERS.
- THIS MADE OUR NIGHT.
- WHOO!
I DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE YOUR SHIRT.
THAT'S CUTE.
BEST DAD EVER.
- JENNI BOUGHT IT FOR ME.
- YOU'RE CUTE.
- TELL YOU WHAT, GUYS,
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE IT.
AND YOU'RE GONNA
BE GREAT PARENTS.
- MM-HMM.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
- 'CAUSE WE KNOW.
- 'CAUSE I KNOW.
- I JUST WANT
TO WATCH HER BY MYSELF.
- WELL YOU ARE GONNA BE
THE GODMOTHER, CORRECT?
- YEAH.
- WHO'S THE GODFATHER?
- I HONESTLY DO NOT KNOW YET,
BUT I THINK MY FRIEND LOUIE.
- [clears throat]
HE HAS TWO GIRLS.
HE'S PROBABLY--
OH!
[all laughing]
WILL YOU PROMISE ME ONE THING?
- I'M NOT LOOKING
AT THE PLACENTA.
- PLEASE? PLEASE.
- JUST LOOK AT IT.
- NO!
- IT'S SO LONG.
YOU'RE LIKE,
"THAT WAS IN ME?"
IT'S HUGE.
- IT'S NOT EVEN THAT,
IT'S THE BLOOD THAT COMES OUT.
THEY PUT A BUCKET
UNDER HER LEGS
FOR THE GALLONS OF BLOOD
THAT COMES OUT.
- GALLONS?
- GALLONS OF BLOOD.
HE PUT HIM--
THE BABY'S COMING OUT,
HE'S WEARING
HIS REGULAR CLOTHES.
PLACENTA COMES OUT,
HE PUTS A BIG SMOCK ON.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
HE PUT THE SMOCK ON
BEFORE THE PLACENTA,
NOT THE BABY.
- YOU STILL TALK ABOUT THIS.
YOU'RE HAUNTED BY IT
AND YOU WANT ME TO LOOK AT IT.
YOU TALK ABOUT IT
LIKE YOU DID TIME IN IRAQ,
AND YOU WANT ME
TO LOOK AT IT.
- I'M BEGGING YOU.
- EVERYTHING YOU DESCRIBED,
WHO IN THEIR RIGHT MIND
WOULD WANT TO SEE THAT?
IT'S LIKE SOMETHING
OUT OF THE MOVIE ALIENS.
- WATCH IT.
- I'M GONNA WEAR
A WELDER'S MASK IN THERE.
- TO THE PLACENTA!
- LOOK AT THE PLACENTA.
- I AM NOT CHEERING FOR THAT.
- GOOD TIMES.
- HOW ARE YOU
FEELING THIS MORNING?
- I'M NOT SCARED.
"SCARED" REMINDS ME OF, LIKE,
SCARED OF ALLIGATORS AND STUFF,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE I'M SCARED OF THE DARK,
OR BURGLARS.
- TODAY IS THE DAY.
- AND I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
UM, WE'VE BEEN WAITING
39 WEEKS FOR TODAY.
- I'VE BEEN WAITING
39 YEARS FOR TODAY.
- AW, HOW CUTE IS THAT?
39 WEEKS
AND 39 YEARS.
I THINK SHE'S JUST
GONNA DESTROY ME COMING OUT,
BUT THAT'S FINE.
- IT'S GONNA BE
LIKE COLLEGE FOR YOU.
- YEAH.
IT'S LIKE THAT
FOOTBALL TEAM I TOOK ON.
- LIKE A CHAMPION,
I MIGHT ADD.
A CHAMPION.
- NO, BUT SERIOUSLY.
IS IT WEIRD THAT I'M, LIKE,
SO CURIOUS TO FIND OUT
WHAT THAT PAIN'S LIKE?
I'M KIND OF LIKE,
"I WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S UP."
- YOU'RE GONNA GET
THE OPPORTUNITY TO DO THAT.
- I DON'T WANT
TO POOP ON THE TABLE.
- [sighs]
- THIS ISN'T HELPING.
- [laughs]
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONNA DO YOUR ENEMA THING
BEFORE YOU GO IN.
- YEAH, BUT WE'RE
NOT GOING IN FOR NINE HOURS.
I STILL WANT TO EAT THEN.
I GOT TO HAVE SOME STRENGTH.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST
POOP ON THE TABLE, MAN?
WHAT'S UP?
LIKE, WE'LL GET THE POWER WASHER
OUT OF THE SHED,
JUST IN CASE
IT HAPPENS.
[line ringing]
- HEY, BOO.
- HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- GETTING READY FOR YOU.
- I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE,
WHEN I COME TO GET YOU,
THAT YOU'RE READY,
BECAUSE YOU NEED
TO LOOK PRETTY FOR YOUR BABY
BEFORE YOU GO
TO THE HOSPITAL.
- I AM ACTUALLY ALL READY,
AND IT'S PERFECT,
'CAUSE I DIDN'T
WASH MY HAIR TODAY,
SO I'M SUPER EXCITED.
- I'LL BE THERE
IN AN HOUR.
- BITCH.
- I'M JUST KIDDING.
- LOVE YOU, BYE.
- 'KAY.
LOVE YOU, BYE.
'KAY.
WILL YOU COME
OVER THERE WITH ME?
I WANT TO TAKE MY PICTURE,
'CAUSE I WANT TO TAKE--
- ALL RIGHT.
- I WANT TO TAKE
A PICTURE OF OUR BELLIES
BEFORE SHE GIVES BIRTH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DRIVE.
- YOU'RE DRIVING?
- YEAH.
- ALL THE WAY OVER?
- I CAN'T WALK IN THESE HEELS.
[car horn honking]
- OH, MY GOD, I LOVE THIS SIGN
THAT NICOLE MADE FOR THE PHOTOS.
I REALLY HOPE THAT THEY'RE
GONNA BE BEST FRIENDS.
'CAUSE IF THEY'RE
NOT BEST FRIENDS
AND THEY HATE EACH OTHER--
- IT'S GONNA BE A PROBLEM,
BECAUSE WE'RE
HANGING OUT ALL THE TIME.
THEY'RE GONNA BE
LIKE US.
- YEAH.
- BECAUSE THEY'RE OUR KIDS.
THEY'RE GONNA BE
JUST LIKE US,
AND THEY'RE GONNA
LIKE EACH OTHER.
- YEAH.
IT'LL REALLY PISS ME OFF IF OUR
DAUGHTERS AREN'T BEST FRIENDS.
- I'LL MAKE THEM BEST FRIENDS.
- ME TOO.
- LIKE, "YOU BETTER LIKE HER."
WHAT?
- [laughing]
- WHAT?
- YOUR WHITE PART OF YOUR BOOBS
ARE, LIKE--
- MY WHAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- MY AREOLA?
- [laughs]
- LET'S GET BEAUTIFUL.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
- I DON'T KNOW WHY
I'M WEARING HEELS.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT TO LOOK
PRETTY ON YOUR DELIVERY DAY,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANT YOUR BABY COMING OUT,
AND THEN YOUR BABY'S LIKE,
"EW, THAT'S MY MOM?"
- LISTEN.
BEING NINE MONTHS PREGNANT,
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS
I DON'T DO ANYMORE.
YOU'RE LUCKY I SHOWER.
- SHAVE YOUR VAGINA.
- UGH. THAT'S...
- CAN YOU SEE IT?
- NO.
- [laughs] "CAN YOU SEE IT?"
- SHAVING AT THIS POINT
IS A GUESSING GAME.
I CAN'T LIFT THE LEG.
LIKE...
AND THEN YOU BEND DOWN,
YOU CAN'T BREATHE.
- YEAH.
THEN YOU TRY AND,
LIKE, MOVE YOUR STOMACH
AND PUSH IT IN SO YOU
CAN SEE YOUR VAGINA.
- OH, IT'S SO PAINFUL.
- BUT YOU CAN'T,
SO YOU JUST GOTTA...
- GUESS.
- FEEL IT AND MAKE SURE YOU
DON'T SNIP SOMETHING OFF.
- IF YOU GET A MIRROR--
- GET IT WAXED.
[Snooki and Jwoww gag]
SO WHAT ABOUT AFTER BIRTH?
HOW LONG DO YOU
WAIT TO SHAVE?
- I HAD A LITTLE FOREST,
A LITTLE BIT.
VAGINAS ARE HARD
TO MAINTAIN.
AND THEY'RE GROSS.
VAGINAS ARE GROSS.
- THEY'RE NOT A FLOWER.
- I SHOULD JUST
HAVE A PENIS AND JUST...
- SMACK [bleep] ALL DAY?
[laughing
- WE'RE AWFUL.
I THINK I'M MORE NERVOUS
THAN YOU ARE.
- ARE YOU GONNA
JUST PULL IT OUT?
- NO, I'M NOT
PULLING NO CORD--
- ARE YOU GONNA TOUCH THE HEAD
WHEN THEY WANT YOU TO?
- NO!
- LORENZO'S HEAD WAS HALFWAY
OUT, THEY'RE LIKE,
"FEEL HIM! FEEL HIM!"
I'M LIKE, "NO!
JUST GET HIM OUT!"
I'M NOT GONNA GO THERE.
- I DON'T WANT TO FEEL THAT.
NO.
JUST GET HIM OUT.
'CAUSE HE'S HALFWAY
OUT OF MY VAGINA--
WHY AM I GONNA JUST
LET HIM HANG THERE AND--
- JUST LIKE THIS?
- YEAH, FEEL HIS HEAD.
- THAT'S, LIKE, JUST AS BAD AS,
LIKE, "DO YOU WANT A MIRROR?"
NO, MOTHER[bleep],
I DON'T WANT A MIRROR.
- YEAH. JUST GET MY BABY OUT.
- GET IT OUT.
- JEEZ.
- I COULDN'T SLEEP.
- COULDN'T SLEEP WORTH--
I SHUT THE TV OFF
AT, LIKE, ONE.
AND THEN I COUNTED--
- WHY COULDN'T YOU SLEEP?
YOU'RE JUST EXCITED?
- NO, I JUST PEE
EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
- [laughs]
AW.
- * HERE WE GO
* AND IT'S JUST
THE BEGINNING *
* YEAH,
YOU AND ME *
* WE'RE SPINNING
* THROUGH
A CO-O-OLORFUL WORLD *
* THROUGH A CO-O-OLORFUL
WORLD *
* YEAH
HERE WE GO *
* A COLORFUL WORLD
* THROUGH
A CO-O-OLORFUL WORLD *
- YOU READY, BABE?
TIME TO GO.
- I'M READY.
ARE YOU READY?
- YEAH.
I'LL GO PACK THE CAR.
IS THE KEYS ON THE COUNTER?
- YEAH.
- [sighs]
HER PERFECT LITTLE ROOM.
IT'S THE PRETTIEST ROOM
IN THE WORLD.
WITH THE PRETTIEST COLORS.
THE NEXT TIME I COME HOME,
YOU'LL BE HERE WITH ME.
IN THIS GLIDER.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO NERVOUS.
- CAR'S ALL PACKED.
- I'M NERVOUS.
IT JUST HIT ME.
IT'S 8:00.
- YEAH.
IT'S A GOOD THING.
LET'S GO GET OUR BABY GIRL.
- I GUESS SO, RIGHT?
- THERE'S NO TIME
LIKE THE PRESENT.
- I'M SCARED.
NERVOUS.
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
I THINK THE REALIZATION THAT,
YOU KNOW, TODAY'S THE DAY
IS REALLY SETTING IN FOR JENNI.
SHE IS SCARED.
SHE'S SCARED OUT OF HER MIND.
AND, EVEN FOR ME,
IT'S A LITTLE SURREAL.
YOU KNOW, I'M THE GUY THAT'S
ALWAYS PREPARED FOR ANYTHING,
AND, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
THAT I'M 100% READY.
I'M AS READY AS I CAN BE, AND I
NEED TO BE HER ROCK RIGHT NOW.
- PROMISE TO TEXT ME.
- I WILL.
- GIVE A KISS.
- POUND. KISS.
I LOVE YOU.
- GOOD LUCK, ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
BYE.
- GOOD LUCK, ROGER.
I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
- WE'LL SEE YOU GUYS
REALLY SOON, OKAY?
TOMORROW?
- OKAY.
OH, BABY.
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- BABY.
YOU'LL SEE
A BABY SOON.
- BYE, BABY.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I FEEL COMPLETELY FINE, LIKE
THIS IS GONNA BE EASY PEASY.
- OPEN IT IN THE BACK,
SO THE BUTT'S OUT?
- RIGHT.
- OKAY.
- THAT'S WHAT GOT US
INTO THIS PREDICAMENT.
- SO I'LL PUT EVERYTHING
IN THERE FOR YOU AND, UM,
GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- OKAY.
I'M NERVOUS.
IT'S VERY HARD TO EXPLAIN
THE FEAR OF HAVING A CHILD.
IT'S SCARY.
- SO, WHAT I'M GONNA DO--WE'RE
GONNA PUT THE MONITOR ON YOU,
I'M GONNA START
AN IV IN YOUR ARM.
- IT'S GETTING MORE REAL.
LIKE, WHETHER I LIKE IT OR NOT,
I'M GONNA BE PUSHING MY DAUGHTER
OUT IN THE NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS.
- WE'RE GONNA START
THE INDUCTION,
THEN WE'RE GONNA PUT THAT
MEDICATION INSIDE.
THAT HELPS
SOFTEN UP THAT CERVIX.
IT'S GONNA STAY THERE
TILL TOMORROW MORNING.
YOU'LL WANT TO GET
GOOD REST.
- DR. REZAI IS EXPLAINING THAT
HE'S GONNA STICK CERVIDIL IN ME,
WHICH WILL SOFTEN THE CERVIX
AND GET IT READY FOR DILATION.
BY TOMORROW,
SHE'S HERE.
CRAZY.
- AND PAIN MANAGEMENT'S
COMPLETELY UP TO YOU.
SO WHATEVER YOU WANT
FOR PAIN, YOU CAN HAVE.
- I WANT TO FEEL THESE THINGS.
- ALL RIGHT.
- JUST BECAUSE I'M SO CURIOUS.
I WOULD LOVE TO FEEL
MY FIRST LABOR PAIN.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
BEING A WOMAN
AND HAVING TO EXPERIENCE THAT.
- AND THAT'S WHAT WE
WANT YOU TO DO.
WE WANT YOU TO,
YOU KNOW--
WHEN YOU START THE CONTRACTIONS,
JUST COMMUNICATE THAT WITH US.
SEE HOW UNCOMFORTABLE THEY ARE.
WE'LL CHECK YOUR CERVIX
TO SEE WHERE YOU ARE AND,
YOU KNOW, WHAT YOUR
OPTIONS ARE AT THAT TIME.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- THESE CRAMPS
ARE A MOTHER[bleep],
I'M GONNA BE HONEST.
WHATEVER THEY PUT IN MY VAGINA
IS REALLY MAKING ME CRAMP UP.
- BABE, THE GUY
WAS ELBOW-DEEP UP THERE.
THAT'S GOT TO BE
UNCOMFORTABLE IN ITSELF.
HE SHOOK HANDS
WITH OUR DAUGHTER
AND THEN DID
A DENTAL EXAM AFTER THAT.
- HONESTLY,
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE--
I FEEL OPEN.
- HER TEETH FEEL CLEAN?
[laughter]
- [exhales]
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
WE'RE ABOUT TO GET INTO.
I'M GONNA BE STRAIGHT-UP.
NO IDEA.
- WE'RE ABOUT TO BECOME PARENTS
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
- I CAN'T WAIT FOR MEILANI.
- I CAN'T WAIT, NO.
- I MEAN, SHE'S GONNA BE HERE
IN, LIKE, EIGHT HOURS.
- MAYBE SOONER.
- SOONER, LATER. WHO CARES?
SHE'LL BE HERE
WITHIN THE NEXT 24.
- MM-HMM.
- IT IS INSANE TO ME
THAT, IN THE MORNING,
I WILL BE ONE STEP CLOSER
TO BEING A PARENT.
EVERY DAY, I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR RIGHT NOW, THIS MOMENT.
BUT NOW THAT THIS MOMENT
IS HERE, I'M FREAKING OUT
AND I STILL
CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
CAN YOU TUCK ME IN?
- I LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU TOO.
- I'M PROUD OF YOU.
NO WAY I'M GONNA
FIT ON THIS THING.
- I'M TIRED.
TRYING TO MAKE
A BABY IS HARD WORK.
- HEH!
- [groans]
IT HURTS.
OW.
- WELL, WHEN YOU KEPT
SAYING, "I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT A CONTRACTION IS"--
NOW YOU KNOW.
- OW.
- YOU'RE RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF IT, AND THAT'S GOOD,
'CAUSE IT MEANS IT'S HALFWAY
OVER AND IT'S GONNA GO AWAY.
- POOP. IT'S LONG.
- IT IS A LONG ONE.
IT'S ON ITS WAY DOWN NOW.
- MY VAGINA'S GONNA FALL OUT.
OUCH.
OH, MY GOD,
I'M GONNA DIE.
OH, MY GOD.
THE CONTRACTIONS
ARE GETTING REALLY PAINFUL.
AND I HONESTLY FEEL
LIKE I'M IN A HORROR MOVIE.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I'M
IN THE [bleep] TWILIGHT ZONE,
BECAUSE THIS IS [bleep]
EXCRUCIATING.
IT FEELS LIKE SOMEONE
IS TAKING MY INTESTINES
AND TRYING TO PULL THEM
OUT OF MY ASS[bleep].
YOU KNOW, I'M LIKE,
OH, MY GOD,
I'M, LIKE, HONESTLY
RETHINKING THIS EPIDURAL.
I'M NOT KIDDING. I NEED HELP.
- ALL RIGHT.
- OW.
- YOU'RE OKAY.
- BREATHE.
- WHERE THE [bleep]
IS MY DOCTOR?
OH, MY GOD.
- BREATHE.
- SHE'S TOO BIG.
SHE'S GONNA KILL ME.
SERIOUSLY, MY VAGINA'S
GONNA FALL OUT OF MY ASS[bleep].
I FELT A CONTRACTION.
I'M GOOD.
I CAN'T TAKE
THIS PAIN ANYMORE.
I'VE DECIDED
I NEED AN EPIDURAL.
SO MY ANESTHESIOLOGIST COMES IN.
THANK YOU, JESUS,
BECAUSE IT'S JUST, LIKE--
IT'S TAKING MY BREATH AWAY.
[whispering]
- REMEMBER,
THE MORE STRESSED YOU GET,
THE MORE STRESSED
THE BABY GETS.
SO STAY CALM.
- YEAH, BUT I CAN'T TAKE--
THIS IS, LIKE, BY FAR,
THE WORST PAIN I'VE FELT.
- NOBODY'S GONNA
LET ANYTHING HAPPEN TO YOU.
- SO WE MAY BE GOING
MUCH FASTER--
YOU HAVE TO--
- IT'S GONNA PASS.
REMEMBER, THE LAST ONE PASSED.
THIS ONE WILL PASS.
GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
DON'T WORK YOURSELF UP.
YOU HAVE TO CALM DOWN.
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
- BREATHE.
- YOU HAVE TO STAY CALM.
JUST BREATHE.
STAY CALM.
YOU'RE WORKING YOURSELF UP.
CALM. CALM.
CALM.
- OW.
- CALM.
BREATHE, BABE.
- OH, MY GOD,
I THINK MY WATER JUST BROKE.
- THIS EPISODE
OF SNOOKI AND JWOWW...
- CONTINUES NOW.
- TAKE A BIG BREATH
AND BLOW IT AWAY,
AND TELL YOURSELF,
"I'M DONE WITH ANOTHER ONE."
ONE MORE CLOSER
TO THE BABY COMING.
- REMEMBER WHAT YOU SAID
BEFORE WE GOT HERE?
IT'S ONLY PAIN.
IT WILL GO AWAY.
I KNOW IT WILL END.
IT'S JUST PAIN.
I KNOW IT WILL GO AWAY.
- YOU'RE DILATING
VERY RAPIDLY.
- I'M SCARED.
IT'S JUST THE PEAK
OF THE CONTRACTION
I CAN'T [bleep] TAKE.
- MY DAUGHTER'S
COMING IN MINUTES,
AND I AM JUST IN THE WORST PAIN
I'VE EVER FELT IN MY LIFE.
- YOU'RE GONNA
GET THROUGH THIS.
- SO, DR. REZAI
COMES IN--
VERY CALM, COOL, COLLECTED,
LIKE HE'S ALWAYS BEEN.
- THE BABY'S RIGHT HERE.
I CAN SEE THE BABY'S HEAD.
- OW!
AND HER HEAD'S OUT,
BASICALLY.
LIKE,
SHE'S VISUALLY THERE.
- IT'LL BE
JUST A FEW MINUTES.
- THANKS.
- OKAY?
- HE WALKED IN,
AND HE LOOKS,
AND THEN, HE SAID,
"OKAY, WE'RE DELIVERING NOW.
I'M SCRUBBING UP."
- YEAH.
- THAT'S HOW IT WENT DOWN.
HE JUST THOUGHT
HE WAS GONNA CHECK AND BE LIKE,
"ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW,
20, 30, 40 MINUTES,
MAYBE A COUPLE HOURS"--
NO, SHE'S GONNA
BE HERE IN A COUPLE PUSHES.
[Jwoww groaning]
- YOU KNOW, IT'S--
IT'S BRUTAL TO WATCH,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
YOU'RE WITNESSING,
OUT OF THE CORNER OF YOUR EYE,
THE MIRACLE OF BIRTH.
AND THAT'S TRULY
WHAT IT IS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S--
IT'S AN AMAZING THING.
[overlapping voices]
[Jwoww continues groaning]
EVEN WITH EVERYTHING
THAT I THOUGHT WAS GONNA BE
BLOOD AND GORE, IT WASN'T.
IT WAS--IT WAS AMAZING,
YOU KNOW?
AND IT WAS THE MOST--
AHEM.
IT WAS THE MOST POWERFUL THING
I'VE EVER SEEN, YOU KNOW?
- AND PUSH.
THAT'S IT, COME ON.
COME ON, COME ON,
SQUEEZE, SQUEEZE, SQUEEZE.
HARDER, HARDER, HARDER,
HARDER, HARDER, HARDER.
MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE
MORE, MORE, MORE.
NEED ONE MORE.
COME ON.
AND PUSH.
SQUEEZE THAT BABY OUT.
- [moaning]
OW!
[overlapping voices]
- IT HAPPENED SO FAST.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, JENNI--SHE
LITERALLY PUSHED THREE TIMES,
AND ON THAT THIRD PUSH,
YOU KNOW, OUR BABY--
OUR LITTLE GIRL WAS HERE.
AND--
[chokes up]
- MY WHOLE [bleep] PREGNANCY,
FROM BEGINNING TO END,
AND THE HORRIBLE LABOR
THAT I WENT THROUGH,
LITERALLY
WAS JUST A MEMORY
FROM THE SECOND
I LAID EYES ON MEILANI.
LIKE, SHE WAS ALL WORTH IT.
EVERY SINGLE THING--
I WOULD'VE DONE IT
TEN TIMES MORE AND TEN TIMES
HARDER JUST TO HAVE HER.
- * IF IT'S ALL
I CAN TAKE... *
- TO FINALLY LAY EYES
ON MY DAUGHTER,
AND TO FINALLY MEET HER
AND HOLD HER IN THE FLESH--
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS POSSIBLE
TO LOVE SOMETHING
THAT MUCH IN A--IN A MOMENT.
IT'S--IT'S AN AMAZING THING,
AND SHE'S PERFECT.
SHE'S--
SHE'S LITERALLY PERFECT.
*
- NEXT TIME, ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- YOU HUNGRY?
SHE'S LIKE,
"GIVE ME THE BOOB."
- WELCOME HOME.
WELCOME, MEILANI.
- WELCOME HOME, MEILANI.
- HOT OUT HERE.
WE GOT TO GET HER INSIDE.
- WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
both:
WELCOME HOME, MEILANI.
- BEHAVE.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING DOWN.
PEOPLE ARE JUST LOOKING AT US,
LIKE, "WHO ARE THOSE WEIRDOES
WITH THE KIDS?"
HE'S CHECKED OUT.