- LAST SEASON...
- ON SNOOKI AND JWOWW...
YEAH!
- [laughs]
- HE'’S GONNA WALK.
- OH, MY GOD!
- [squeals]
I WOULD LIKE TO MAKE BABY
NUMBER TWO AFTER OUR WEDDING.
- LIKE, THAT NIGHT?
- YEAH, LIKE, I WANT A BABY.
- GOD.
- I WANT YOU TO BE
AFFECTIONATE
NOT '’CAUSE YOU WANT TO GET
SOME [bleep].
- IT'’S THE LAST THING
ON MY MIND.
KISSES.
- [giggles]
- [humming Richard Wagner'’s
Bridal Chorus]
- [chuckles]
OH, SHE PUT IT ON.
- WOW!
- ROGER'’S GONNA KILL ME.
- I WANT A VEIL!
- [laughs]
- I, NICOLE, TAKE YOU
JIONNI LAVALLE--
OH!
[both laughing]
- WHAT A WAY TO END THE SUMMER.
- YOU GUYS LOOKED SO CUTE
AROUND ALL THE KIDS TODAY.
- I LOVE KIDS.
- YOU COULD HAVE A LITTLE ONE
NEXT YEAR.
- NEVER SAY NEVER.
- YOU COULD TOO.
- YEAH, I COULD.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
- WE HAD AN AWESOME SUMMER,
AND, YOU KNOW,
WE'’RE GLAD WE GOT TO SHARE IT
WITH YOU GUYS.
- LOOK AT HIS TEETH.
- YEAH.
- LOOK AT NICOLE'’S.
- HE'’S LIKE--
[laughter]
YOU'’RE STUPID, ROGER.
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
[baby crying]
- CAN YOU CALM HIM DOWN?
'’CAUSE HE HAS TO TAKE A NAP.
- NAP TIME.
[baby laughs]
- SINCE LAST SUMMER,
I'’M PREGNANT
WITH MY SECOND BABY.
THREE MONTHS BEHIND JENNI WHO IS
SIX MONTHS PREGNANT RIGHT NOW.
- NICOLE, IT'’S GETTING
REALLY CROWDED DOWN HERE.
THIS KID'’S TAKING OVER.
[baby laughing]
- LORENZO,
YOU TOOK OVER OUR BASEMENT.
JUST IMAGINE TWO KIDS DOWN HERE.
I DON'’T THINK IT WOULD WORK.
WHERE WOULD WE PUT HIS BED?
'’CAUSE WE HAVE A CRIB.
- HE'’D SLEEP WITH US.
[baby crying]
- NO.
[laughs]
BEING BACK IN THE BASEMENT,
IT'’S DEFINITELY MORE CROWDER--
OR MORE CROWDIER.
UM, THAT'’S NOT A WORD.
- YOU DIDN'’T TELL JENNI
WE'’RE HAVING ANOTHER BABY,
DID YOU?
- NO.
- I THINK WE SHOULD
SURPRISE HER TOGETHER.
MAYBE LORENZO HAVE,
LIKE, A SHIRT ON OR SOMETHING.
- WE'’RE GONNA GO SHOPPING
FOR HER--
FOR PREGNANT CLOTHES AND I'’M NOT
GONNA TELL HER I'’M PREGNANT TOO?
IT'’S A BIG SECRET.
- WELL, WE'’RE NOT HIDING IT.
WE'’RE JUST WAITING TO TELL HER.
- I TELL HER EVERYTHING.
I FEEL LIKE I'’M GONNA TELL HER
I'’M PREGNANT.
- YOU COULD KEEP ONE SECRET.
- I KNOW, BUT I'’M EXCITED.
MUMMY'’S GONNA GO SEE AUNT JENNI.
WANT ME TO TELL HER YOU SAID HI?
[baby babbles]
NO?
YOU DON'’T EVEN LOOK PREGNANT.
- NO, I AM.
IT'’S CALLED MASKING IT.
- [hums]
- JUST LIKE YOU.
NOTHING FITS ME ANYMORE.
EVERYTHING'’S UNCOMFORTABLE.
I NEED NEW CLOTHES, OBVIOUSLY,
MUUMUUS AND GARBAGE BAGS.
- IT'’S A STRUGGLE.
CAN I SEE YOUR NIPPLES?
- IT LOOKS LIKE--
NO, YOU CAN'’T SEE MY NIPPLES.
- WHY?
- I DIDN'’T LOOK AT YOUR NIPPLES
WHEN YOU WERE PREGNANT.
- BUT I WANT TO SEE
IF THEY LOOK HUGE.
- THEY'’RE--[laughs]
- '’CAUSE YOUR NIPPLES GROW
LIKE--THEY JUST GET
LIKE BIG PEPPERONIS
WHEN YOU'’RE PREGNANT.
- [laughs]
- DO THEY?
IS THAT WHAT YOURS
LOOKS LIKE?
- YES.
MY BOOBS ARE GETTING
OUT OF CONTROL,
BUT IT'’S WEIRD BECAUSE IT'’S LIKE
MY WHOLE BODY'’S CHANGING
THAT MY BOOBS DON'’T EVEN
LOOK THAT BIG UNTIL I TRY
AND PUT ON MY DOUBLE-F BRA
THAT DOESN'’T FIT.
SO I'’M LIKE, "OH!"
- WHAT ARE YOU, A "Z"?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- WHAT ARE YOU WEARING NOW?
- I'’M WEARING A DOUBLE-F BRA,
THEN A STRAP BACK.
- BOING.
- I'’M NOT BUYING A NEW BRA.
MY CHILD IS KILLING ME.
- ISN'’T IT WEIRD?
YOU HAVE, LIKE,
A LITTLE ALIEN INSIDE YOU.
- AN ALIEN
THAT'’S GONNA BE ME ONE DAY.
- MM-HMM.
- AND THEN ROGER, MIXED.
- I FEEL LIKE ROGER
WOULD PRODUCE A GINGER BABY.
[laughs]
- WHAT THE [bleep], DUDE?
- [laughs]
- I HOPE YOU--
- I DON'’T KNOW WHY.
I JUST PICTURE--
- I HOPE YOUR NEXT CHILD
COMES OUT WITH THREE EYEBALLS.
OKAY?
- I JUST PICTURE ROGER--
- WHERE DOES GINGER
COME FROM IN OUR--
- I DON'’T KNOW.
I'’LL NEVER HAVE A GINGER.
- [laughs]
- WOULD YOU BE PISSED?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WOULD I BE PISSED?
[laughs]
YES, I WOULD BE PISSED.
I'’M DONE.
GOOD-BYE.
- I SHOULD HAVE TOLD HER.
- I'’LL MEET YOU
FOR CHEESE BALLS.
- IF I HAD A GINGER BABY,
I WOULD BE SO HAPPY.
- REALLY?
[both laughing]
- YES, I WOULD.
IS ANYONE GINGER HERE?
- THAT'’S HOW--THAT'’S HOW
YOU WOULD MEET IT.
YOU'’D START LAUGHING AT IT,
LIKE, "HA HA HA HA."
- LIKE, "IS THIS MINE?"
- SOMEONE [bleep] IT UP.
WHERE'’S MY BABY?
- THAT'’S NOT MINE.
[both laughing]
- AWFUL.
- WE'’RE TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
THAT WAS FUN.
- YEAH.
- I HONESTLY THINK
YOU LOOK GREAT PREGNANT.
- THANKS. I'’M AFRAID OF,
LIKE, THE NEXT TWO MONTHS.
- I FEEL LIKE I'’M GONNA
THROW UP.
- WHY?
- [coughs]
COULD I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
- YOU CAN TELL ME ANYTHING.
- SO I HAVEN'’T REALLY TOLD JENNI
THAT I'’M PREGNANT YET.
I'’M SCARED THAT SHE MIGHT BE MAD
BECAUSE IT'’S JENNI'’S TIME,
AND IT TOTALLY IS,
BECAUSE IT'’S HER FIRST BABY.
SECOND BABY,
IT'’S LIKE, "OH, WHATEVER.
IT'’S JUST ANOTHER KID."
JIONNI WILL PROBABLY
BE MAD AT ME,
BUT, I MEAN,
HE'’LL GET OVER IT,
'’CAUSE SHE'’S MY BEST FRIEND
AND I HAVE TO TELL HER.
WE'’RE PLANNING THE WEDDING
AND WE'’RE, LIKE,
REALLY STRESSED OUT ABOUT IT.
'’CAUSE, LIKE, THE HOUSE
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
- I'’M NOT GONNA BE PART
OF THE WEDDING?
- BUT THEN--NO, YOU ARE.
- OH.
- BUT WE KIND OF, LIKE,
THREW A WRENCH
IN EVERYTHING THAT'’S GOING ON
AND, UM...
- I DON'’T GET IT.
- I'’M PREGGERS.
- [laughing]
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
- THAT'’S WHY I WANT TO VOMIT,
AND I CAN'’T BREATHE,
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE [bleep].
I'’M THREE MONTHS PREGNANT.
- THERE'’S GONNA BE TWO OF YOU
ON THIS EARTH.
- I KNOW, THAT'’S WHY
I'’M HOPING IT'’S A BOY, BUT--
- IT'’S NOT GONNA BE A BOY.
- YEAH, WELL...
- IT'’S GONNA BE A GIRL.
IT'’S ACTUALLY A GIRL.
- I DON'’T KNOW.
- IT'’S GONNA BE A GIRL.
IT IS ACTUALLY GONNA BE
THE SPAWN...
- I'’M NOT READY FOR A GIRL.
- OF [bleep] SATAN.
- GIRLS ARE SUCH DIVAS.
- I KNOW YOU'’RE GONNA HAVE
A GIRL JUST LIKE ME
'’CAUSE IT'’S KARMA.
I CANNOT BE STRUCK WITH A GIRL
AND HAVE TO RAISE
A SPAWN OF SATAN MYSELF.
YOU'’RE RAISING
THE SPAWN OF SATAN AS WELL.
- NO.
IF I HAVE A GIRL,
MINE'’S GONNA BE A PRINCESS.
- EXACTLY.
[both laughing]
- YOU WANT TO JUST PIG OUT?
CAN WE DO NACHOS GRANDE?
- DO YOU HAVE PIZZA?
- I DO.
- CHEESE BALLS, FRIED PICKLES,
CHICKEN CAESAR WRAP,
CHEESE FRIES, MAC AND CHEESE,
AND MOZZARELLA STICKS.
- DO YOU HAVE BONELESS WINGS?
- YEAH.
- I'’LL TAKE THAT.
- [laughs]
WE'’RE SO FAT.
- I'’M VERY EXCITED
THAT ME AND NICOLE
GET TO BE PREGNANT TOGETHER.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU REALLY
THINK ABOUT IT, WHO,
AS BEST FRIENDS, GET TO REALLY
EXPERIENCE PREGNANCY TOGETHER?
NOT MANY PEOPLE.
- I'’M SO EXCITED.
- WHAT THE [bleep] ARE YOU
GONNA DO IN THE BASEMENT, DUDE?
I CAN'’T IMAGINE BEING
FOUR PEOPLE IN THE BASEMENT.
- STOP.
I'’M FREAKING OUT,
'’CAUSE IT'’S ALREADY--
LORENZO'’S GETTING SO BIG
THAT HE TOOK OVER--
- HE'’S LIKE BAM BAM DOWN THERE.
- HE TOOK OVER HALF THE BASEMENT
WITH JUST HIS PLAYROOM.
AND I CAN ONLY JUST PICTURE,
LIKE, ANOTHER CRIB
WITH ANOTHER BABY.
- YOU GUYS ARE LIKE THIS.
- LITERALLY.
- LIKE, DOES LORENZO JUST
STARE AT YOU WHEN YOU SLEEP?
- YES.
HE ACTUALLY SLEEPS WITH US.
- OH, HE DOES?
- YEAH.
SO I DON'’T GET GOOD SLEEP
AS IT IS.
THAT MEANS TWO BABIES IN BED
IN THE BASEMENT.
I'’M FORCING THE PEOPLE
TO, LIKE, FINISH MY HOUSE AND--
- ARE THEY GONNA BE DONE
IN TIME?
- THAT'’S NOT A DEFINITE.
I DON'’T KNOW.
- I DON'’T KNOW IF THIS HELPS,
BUT THE [bleep] HOUSE RIGHT
NEXT DOOR TO ME IS UP FOR RENT.
- THAT BIG HOUSE?
- YEAH, IT'’S BIG,
IT'’S NICE, IT'’S BEAUTIFUL.
- IT'’S HUGE.
- I MEAN, NO POOL OR ANYTHING,
BUT IF YOU WANT TO MOVE DOWN,
I MEAN--
- THAT HOUSE IS BEAUTIFUL.
- YEAH, I MEAN,
WE'’LL BE PREGNANT TOGETHER.
- MOVE THERE FOR THE SUMMER?
- MOVE THERE FOR THE SUMMER.
I MEAN, IT'’S--
THE RENT'’S NOT EXPENSIVE
AND THEN YOU'’RE GONNA GET
OUT OF THE BASEMENT.
I'’M SURE JANICE
WOULD LOVE HER ATTICS BACK.
- IT'’S ONLY FOR THE SUMMER.
WE DID IT BEFORE.
I'’M DOWN.
I THINK IT'’S A FABULOUS IDEA,
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY,
ME AND JIONNI WANT TO GET
OUT OF THE BASEMENT
FOR THE SUMMER,
AND ALSO, I WANT TO BE THERE
FOR JENNI WHEN,
YOU KNOW,
SHE'’S ABOUT TO GIVE BIRTH, SO...
I THINK IT'’S A GOOD IDEA.
- OH, MY GOD, THAT'’S SO SCARY.
- YOU'’LL BE FINE.
I'’M GONNA HAVE TWO KIDS.
THAT'’S A LITTLE INSANE.
I WANT FOUR,
SO THIS IS A START.
- YOUR TITS ARE GONNA BE
DOWN TO YOUR KNEES BY THAT TIME.
- THEY ALREADY ARE.
I PUT ON A SPORTS BRA
THE OTHER DAY
'’CAUSE I WAS GOING TO THE GYM,
ONE NIPPLE WAS OVER HERE AND
THE OTHER WAS, LIKE, DOWN HERE.
- [laughs]
- YOU SAW THEM BOTH POINTING.
THEY WERE LIKE THIS.
[both laughing]
[Going To The Sun'’s
Out Of The Night]
- ♪ HOLDING ON TO WHAT I GOT
♪ AND YOU CAN'’T TAKE IT FROM ME
WITH MY LOT ♪
- I'’M ACTUALLY NOT NERVOUS
AT ALL.
- [sneezes]
'’CAUSE IT'’S NOT YOUR VAGINA
SHE'’S COMING OUT OF.
- I MEANT BEING A DAD.
- SO TODAY,
I'’M GOING TO THE DOCTOR
AND I'’M ACTUALLY REALLY EXCITED.
LIKE, I'’M NINE MONTHS PREGNANT.
LET'’S GET THE SHOW
ON THE [bleep] ROAD.
- SO HOW'’S THE BABY DOING?
- SHE'’S KICKING.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'’S TAKE A LOOK.
- SHE'’S HUGE.
- NO, SHE'’S GOOD.
THAT'’S THE BABY'’S HEAD,
NICE AND ROUND.
HEARTBEAT'’S RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS THE CHEST RIGHT HERE.
THESE ARE THE RIB SHADOWS
RIGHT THERE.
BUT THAT'’S THE BABY'’S BOTTOM
OVER HERE.
- AW.
- YOU CAN SEE WHAT YOU'’RE HAVING
OVER THERE.
I CAN SEE THE...
GENDER THAT WAY TOO.
THERE IT IS.
- YEAH, LITTLE HAMBURGER.
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
KEEP IT MOVING.
- [laughs]
- KEEP IT MOVING.
- WE DON'’T WANT TO--
[laughs]
- NO ONE'’S EVER GONNA BE ALLOWED
TO SEE THAT.
- THAT'’S RIGHT.
- THIS KID'’S COMING
OUT OF THE BASEMENT
WHEN SHE'’S 34 YEARS OLD.
- THAT'’S RIGHT.
[laughter]
- IT'’S SO HARD
TO PUT IT IN WORDS
WHEN YOU SEE SOMETHING
THAT YOU CREATED IN A 3-D IMAGE.
I'’M SURE IT'’S GONNA
PALE IN COMPARISON
TO WHEN SHE'’S HERE AND
I'’M TOUCHING HER IN THE FLESH
AND SHE'’S IN FRONT OF ME.
THAT'’S GONNA BE, YOU KNOW,
WE'’RE REALLY IN LOVE...
[laughs]
EVEN THINKING ABOUT IT
MAKES ME A LITTLE EMOTIONAL.
BUT IT'’S GONNA BE EMOTIONAL,
YOU KNOW, FOR ME
WHEN THAT HAPPENS,
BUT JUST SEEING HER IN 3-D,
YOU KNOW, IT'’S CRAZY.
JENNI IS VERY CONCERNED
AT THIS POINT
THAT SHE'’S DECIDED THAT SHE
WANTS TO SET AN INDUCE DATE
BECAUSE SHE'’S CONCERNED
THAT THE BABY
COULD ACTUALLY BE TOO BIG.
- THIS WEEK,
SHE'’LL BE 7 1/2 POUNDS.
WE HAVE A CHUBBY MONKEY
ON OUR HANDS.
I'’M JUST WORRIED A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT THE FUTURE
BECAUSE I'’M NOT TRYING
TO PUSH OUT, YOU KNOW...
- GODZILLA.
- GODZILLA OUT OF MY VAGINA.
- THE ONLY THING MORE AGONIZING
FOR JENNI THAN THIS BABY
COMING OUT HER VAGINA
WAS WHEN I [bleep] HER VAGINA.
SHOULD'’VE SEEN HER FACE THEN.
- YOU'’RE A TERRIBLE PERSON.
- WHAT ARE THE NATURAL WAYS
TO INDUCE LABOR?
- WE DON'’T REALLY
KNOW WHAT INDU--
YOU KNOW, STARTS UP LABOR...
- IT'’S ALL [bleep].
- SO THERE'’S, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
THERE'’S NOT
A GOOD WAY TO ANSWER THAT.
HAVING SAID THAT, YOU KNOW,
ONE OF THE WAYS WE INDUCE LABOR
WITH IS, YOU KNOW,
SEXUAL ACTIVITY,
YOU KNOW,
THAT HELPS THAT TOO--
- THAT'’S NOT EVEN PROVEN,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
- I THINK WHAT YOU'’RE SAYING
DOCTOR, IS IT CAN'’T HURT, RIGHT?
- IT CANNOT HURT.
IT CAN ONLY HELP.
LET'’S PUT IT THAT WAY.
- YEAH.
I THINK I'’M CATCHING
YOUR VIBE THERE.
- THERE YOU GO.
- I AM SIX MONTHS PREGNANT
RIGHT NOW,
AND TODAY, WE MEET OUR PRIEST,
AND WE HAVE TO JUST TALK
TO THE PRIEST ABOUT THE WEDDING.
I ALWAYS PICTURED MYSELF
GETTING MARRIED IN A CHURCH.
AND I FEEL LIKE IF I DIDN'’T
GET MARRIED IN A CHURCH,
IT WOULDN'’T BE REAL, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH.
- SO BOTH OF YOU,
WHAT I'’D LIKE TO DO IN A MINUTE
IS BRING YOU INDIVIDUALLY
INTO MY OFFICE,
BECAUSE IN PREPARATION
FOR A WEDDING,
I SPEND A LITTLE TIME
INDIVIDUALLY WITH EACH COUPLE.
- CAN I ASK A STUPID QUESTION?
- YES.
- WHAT IF SOMEONE
CAME TO YOU AND CONFESSED
AND SAID THEY KILLED,
LIKE, TEN PEOPLE?
YOU WOULDN'’T TELL ANYONE?
- I'’M NOT ALLOWED, NO.
- WOW.
- YOU GOT SOMETHING TO TELL US?
- NO, I DIDN'’T KILL ANYONE.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE
A LOT TO CONFESS.
I'’VE BEEN REALLY NASTY LATELY.
AND EVEN, LIKE, GROWING UP,
LIKE, THROUGHOUT HIGH SCHOOL
AND EVERYTHING, I MEAN,
I WASN'’T...THE BEST SEED.
- I THINK AT ONE TIME
YOU WERE A LITTLE BIT
OF A LITTLE BAD GIRL,
WERE YOU?
- I JUST LIKE DRINKING.
- OKAY.
- WHO DOESN'’T?
YOU'’RE IRISH.
- I'’M IRISH, IT'’S TRUE.
[both laughing]
- YEAH,
BUT I HAD MY PARTY STAGE.
YOU KNOW, THE COLLEGE YEARS.
- YEAH.
GOOD.
- AND I STOLE SOME THINGS
WHEN I WAS LITTLE.
- YOU DID?
- LIKE GUM AND SOCKS.
- OKAY, GUM AND SOCKS.
- I WAS 13.
- OKAY, HAVE YOU GIVEN
ANY CONSIDERATION TO COMING
TO CONFESSION
BEFORE THE MARRIAGE?
- PROBABLY NOT.
- WOULD YOU BE WILLING
TO COME TO CONFESSION TO ME
BEFORE THE WEDDING?
- YES.
- TRY NOT TO HAVE PREMARITAL SEX
UNTIL AFTER THE WEDDING.
TRUST ME, IT'’S GOING TO BE
A VERY ENRICHING EXPERIENCE
FOR YOU.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN DO THAT?
- NO.
- OKAY.
- IT'’S WAY TOO LATE.
- DO YOU THINK YOU'’D BE ABLE
TO ABSTAIN FROM HAVING SEX
UNTIL AFTER THE MARRIAGE?
- YES, OF COURSE.
I AM GONNA LISTEN
TO FATHER OWENS.
I AM NOT GONNA HAVE
SEXUAL RELATIONS WITH NICOLE
UNTIL THE WEDDING.
- I THINK IT'’S POINTLESS.
WE'’RE ALREADY PREGNANT,
WE ALREADY HAVE A BABY,
AND WE HAVE SEXUAL RELATIONS
BECAUSE WE LOVE EACH OTHER,
SO...
- IF A PRIEST ASKED YOU
NOT TO DO IT, YOU GOT TO DO IT.
- DO IT OR DON'’T DO IT?
- DO IT.
- SO YOU WANT US TO DO IT?
- NO, DO IT BY NOT DOING IT.
- BEFORE I KNOW IT,
I'’LL BE STANDING BESIDE JIONNI
AT THE ALTAR, AND
HIS LITTLE HEART'’LL BE PUMPING,
AND THEN YOU'’LL WALK
IN THAT DOOR
AS A BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL BRIDE.
- I'’M GONNA CRY.
- I'’M REALLY EXCITED
FOR YOU GUYS.
- I CAN'’T WAIT.
- I DEFINITELY FEEL
NICOLE AND I
ARE READY FOR MARRIAGE.
FATHER OWENS
DEFINITELY FEELS IT.
- I'’VE BEEN WAITING
TO GET MARRIED TO HIM
SINCE I MET HIM, SO--
- SINCE YOU MET ME?
- FOUR YEARS.
- YOU DIDN'’T KNOW MY NAME.
- I--
BUT I KNEW YOU WERE THE ONE.
I KNEW IT.
WHAT'’D YOU SAY WHEN HE SAID
NO "HIBBIDY-DIBBIDY"?
- I COULD DO IT.
- [chuckles]
KNOW WHAT I SAID?
- WHAT?
- IT'’S HARD.
HE'’S HANDSOME.
- HAPPY WITH TODAY?
- VERY HAPPY.
IT'’S GOOD NEWS.
- I CAN'’T REMEMBER
WHAT ELSE INDUCES LABOR.
- I STRONGLY FEEL LIKE SEX
WAS HIGH ON THAT LIST, THOUGH.
- THE PAST FEW TIMES
WAS ENJOYABLE
AND DON'’T EVEN TELL ME
IT WASN'’T.
- I WAS QUITE IMPRESSED,
ACTUALLY.
I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOD."
HONESTLY, DO YOU REMEMBER
ME TURNING THE LIGHTS ON?
I HAD TO SEE IF SOMEONE ELSE
SNUCK IN THE ROOM.
I THINK THAT YOU WERE INTO IT,
BUT IT JUST KIND OF STOPPED
AFTER THAT, SO...
I DIDN'’T KNOW WHAT WAS GOING ON.
THERE WAS SOME REFERENCE
TO HEMORRHOIDS
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT, AND THEN
I FELT--I FELT AWKWARD.
- BEING ALMOST TEN MONTHS
PREGNANT,
I TRIED REALLY HARD TO SPARK--
WHAT IS IT, THE ROMANCE
IN OUR LIFE A LITTLE BIT?
- MM-HMM.
- AND IT WAS WORKING,
UNTIL ONE DAY,
I WOKE UP
WITH A PUFFY BUTTHOLE.
[both laughing]
STOP.
- NOT--THAT'’S NOT
WHAT I EXPECTED YOU TO SAY,
I'’LL BE HONEST WITH YOU.
- WELL, IT'’S ALREADY OUT THERE.
- LITERALLY.
LITERALLY, IT'’S OUT THERE.
- SHUT UP.
- THAT'’S NOT--THAT'’S NOT
WHAT I EXPECTED YOU TO SAY.
WELL, SINCE WE'’RE TALKING
ABOUT IT...
- IT'’S ALREADY BEEN--
- THAT DAY THE REVELATION
HAPPENED, YOU YELLED MY NAME,
AND I WAS DOWNSTAIRS EATING
AN INNOCENT BOWL OF CEREAL,
AND YOU ASKED ME TO COME UP
AND LOOK AT SOMETHING.
AND WHEN I VENTURED
UP THE STAIRS
AND INTO THE BEDROOM,
YOU WERE STANDING THERE NAKED,
AND YOU BEGAN TO TURN AROUND
AND SPREAD YOUR BUTT CHEEKS.
- I DID NOT SPREAD
MY BUTT CHEEKS.
- YOU SAID, "THERE'’S SOMETHING
GOING ON BACK HERE.
CAN YOU LOOK AT IT?"
YOU STARTED TO TURN AROUND,
AND I RAN LIKE A DEER
IN HEADLIGHTS.
I DID.
I RAN OUT OF THERE
LIKE A GAZELLE,
WITH LIGHTNING SPEED,
AND I HAVE NEVER LOOKED,
AND I HAVE NO DESIRE TO,
AND I'’M FINE...
- AND THAT'’S WHY WE HAVEN'’T
HAD SEX YET.
- AND I'’M COOL WITH IT,
MAN, I AM SO COOL WITH IT.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'’S GO UPSTAIRS.
I WANT TO LAY DOWN.
- OH, FOR WHAT?
- SO YOU CAN CHECK OUT
MY '’RHOIDS.
- THAT IS DISGUSTING.
- WELL, IT'’S WHAT YOU GET
FOR BRINGING IT UP.
- YOU WANT TO CHECK OUT
MY '’ROIDS?
BOOM!
- SO STUPID.
- WE'’RE GOING DOWN TO THE SHORE.
WHO'’S EXCITED?
- ME.
NO?
WE'’LL GO SEE AUNT JENNI
AND UNCLE ROGER?
- NO.
- SO NICOLE'’S MOVING IN TODAY.
I'’M SUPER EXCITED.
- I AM TOO.
IT'’S REALLY BECOME
A SUMMERTIME TRADITION FOR US
TO LIVE NEXT TO EACH OTHER,
AND HONESTLY,
IT WOULD BE A WEIRD
AND AWKWARD SUMMER FOR ME
NOT TO LIVE NEXT TO THEM
AT THIS POINT.
- YEAH.
- IT REALLY WOULD.
- I'’M SO EXCITED
THEY'’RE OUR NEIGHBORS TOO.
- YEAH.
- NOW, HELP ME SET THESE UP.
SO WE'’RE SETTING UP
LORENZO'’S PLAYROOM STUFF,
AND OF COURSE, ROGER COMES UP
WITH, "LET'’S PUT SOME WORDS
AND A LITTLE SUBLIMINAL MESSAGE,
OR SOMETHING."
- THERE WAS NOTHING SUBLIMINAL
ABOUT IT.
IT WAS IN-YOUR-FACE.
I THINK NICOLE AND JIONNI
ARE SO USED TO ME MAKING FUN
OF THEIR HEIGHT AND JUST
THEM BEING OF SHORT STATURE.
- I HOPE THEY WON'’T BE MAD.
- OKAY, SO WE GOT "TEENY,"
AND THEN LET'’S DO "TINY."
- DOES IT--HOW THE [bleep]
DO YOU SPELL "TEENY" AND "TINY"?
- T--OH, THIS IS "TINY,"
SO WE WANT "TEENY."
- THAT'’S "TINY."
- WE WANT "TEENY,"
WHICH IS WHAT, T-E--
- T-E-E--
- T-E-E-N-Y?
- I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
HOW YOU SPELL IT.
I KNOW "TINY."
I KNOW "TINY," T-I-N-Y.
"TEENY" IS A TOUGH ONE.
- "TEENY" HAS TO BE T-E--
I-I-I DON'’T PLAY SCRABBLE, "A,"
AND WHEN DO I EVER SAY
THE WORD "TEENY"?
IT'’S GOT TO BE T-E-E-N-Y,
CORRECT?
- YEAH.
- OR IS IT I-E?
- T--
LIKE...
LISTEN, I DON'’T [bleep] KNOW.
DO YOU WANT TO DO "TINY BALLS"?
- THAT'’S NOT EVEN FUNNY, THOUGH.
WHAT'’S FUNNY ABOUT THAT?
I'’VE NEVER MADE FUN
OF HIS BALLS.
I'’VE NEVER SEEN '’EM.
I DON'’T WANT TO SEE '’EM.
- [laughs]
"OH, I NEVER SEEN
JIONNI'’S BALLS.
I DON'’T KNOW IF THEY'’RE SMALL."
- BUT I DIDN'’T GET IT.
WHAT ARE SMALL BALLS?
I DON'’T GET IT.
- I DON'’T--
- HE'’S GOT A SMALL NUT SACK.
- HE DOES?
- I DON'’T KNOW, IT'’S--
- I'’M THE ONE
ON ALL THE STEROIDS.
I HAVE THE SMALL NUT SACK.
- IT'’S A JOKE.
- I DON'’T GET IT.
I DON'’T GET THE BALLS.
- SMALL PENIS.
WOULD THAT HAVE BEEN BETTER?
- THAT WOULD'’VE BEEN BETTER.
SEE?
- WELL, NOBODY CAME UP
WITH SMALL PENIS, NOW, DID THEY?
- COULD'’VE LIVED WITH THAT.
COULD'’VE LIVED WITH THAT.
THAT'’S IT, BABY, WE DID IT.
- PUT A COUPLE TOYS ON IT.
- "SMALL, KIDS, TEENY, TINY."
- YOU'’RE GOING TO HELL.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'’LL WORK.
[Camcorder'’s
A Home I'’ve Never Known]
- ♪ TAKE ME HOME
TO A PLACE I'’VE NEVER KNOWN ♪
- OH, LOOK WHO'’S HERE.
- HOW DO YOU DO, NEIGHBOR?
- HI.
- HI, NEIGHBOR.
- ROUGH RIDE.
- OH, YEAH?
- OH.
- BAD ONE.
- HI, BOO.
- HI.
- MWAH, LOVE YOU.
- MMM.
- MY BELLY'’S BIGGER THAN YOURS.
- NO, IT'’S NOT.
- SHE DOESN'’T EVEN LOOK
PREGNANT.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I'’M REALLY HAPPY
THAT WE'’RE LIVING
NEXT TO JENNI AND ROGER
BECAUSE WE GET TO SEE EACH OTHER
FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER.
- YOU CAN SEE US.
- WOW.
- ISN'’T THIS HOUSE GORGEOUS?
I THINK IT'’S FRICKIN'’ AWESOME.
THANKS, POOP.
- I'’LL BE THE GUY OVER THERE
ON THAT DECK
MOONING YOU GUYS EVERY MORNING.
- THERE'’S GONNA BE
A LOT OF GOOFING OFF.
THERE'’S GONNA BE A LOT
OF FOOLING AROUND, BALL BUSTING.
- WE COULD JUST WALK OVER AND,
YOU KNOW, WE CAN ANNOY THEM.
- WHOA.
- WE WERE WORKING ON THIS
FOR HOURS, JENNI AND I.
- YOU GUYS ARE
THE BEST FRIENDS EVER.
- WE THINK
IT CAME OUT BEAUTIFUL.
- LORENZO, WHAT'’S THAT?
- LORENZO.
OH, MY GOD, HE LOVES GIRAFFES.
- IT'’S A GIRAFFE.
- LORENZO, GIRAFFE.
- GOT HIS GOLF CLUBS.
- THIS IS PERFECT.
SO THIS PLAYROOM
IS GONNA BE PERFECT.
ME AND JIONNI JUST WANT TO GET
AWAY FOR A LITTLE BIT.
WE JUST LOCK HIM IN THE GATE,
KEEP THE BEAST IN THE CRIB,
AND, YOU KNOW--
- YOU CAN DO THAT?
- I WOULDN'’T IN THE BEGINNING.
- BUT NOW, YOU'’RE COOL?
- YEAH.
NOW, I'’M LIKE, I'’M OVER IT.
- OH, GOOD.
- "GO IN THERE."
- I CAN'’T WAIT FOR THAT MOMENT.
- "LET MOMMY LAY DOWN."
LORENZO,
CAN YOU SAY THANK YOU?
- MAYBE DON'’T SAY
THANK YOU TOO QUICK.
- WHY, IS THERE A SURPRISE?
- [laughs]
- WHAT?
- NO.
ONLY IF YOU'’RE LITERATE.
- ARE YOU PRANKING US?
ARE WE DOING PRANKS?
- NO, NO.
- ARE WE GONNA DO
NEIGHBOR PRANKS?
- ONLY IF YOU'’RE LITERATE.
MOST ELABORATE PRANK EVER.
- [laughs]
- ARE WE MISSING SOMETHING?
[laughter]
- YOU ARE.
- WHAT?
[laughter]
- "SMALL, KIDS, TEENY, TINY."
I'’M, LIKE, AN IDIOT.
I DON'’T KNOW ANYTHING,
I DON'’T SEE ANYTHING,
SO I HAVE NO IDEA THAT ROGER
IS SPELLING "TINY, SMALL."
I COULD SEE, YOU KNOW,
IT'’S A JOKE.
WE'’RE SMALL.
WE'’RE TINY.
- HE WAS GONNA DO "TINY BALLS."
- ROGER.
- [laughs]
I WANTED "TINY BALLS,"
'’CAUSE I THOUGHT IT WAS FUNNY,
AND ROGER'’S LIKE, "NO, NO, NO,
NO, WE CAN'’T DO THAT."
- WHY?
- THAT'’S WHAT I SAID.
- I FIGURED ROGER WOULD BE LIKE,
"YEAH, TINY BALLS."
- RIGHT?
- AW.
HE'’S THINKING
ABOUT JIONNI'’S FEELINGS.
- [laughs]
- THAT'’S CUTE.
SEE, ROGER SOFTENED UP ALREADY.
- HE'’S ASSUMING
JIONNI HAS BIG BALLS.
- HE DOES HAVE BIG BALLS.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I KEEP GETTING PREGNANT?
- ALL RIGHT.
DO YOU WANT US TO LET YOU
GET SETTLED
AND WE'’LL START THE...BARBECUE?
- YEAH, WE'’LL GO OVER
TO OUR HOUSE,
LET YOU GUYS SETTLE IN.
- SO WE'’LL JUST PUT SOME STUFF
AWAY AND THEN COME OVER.
- I'’M SURE JIONNI AND NICOLE
GROW,
YOU KNOW, VERY WEARY
AND TIRED...
- THEY DON'’T GROW.
- OF MY SHORT JOKES.
- OR--
[both laughing]
- SOLID POINT.
- WE WOULDN'’T HAVE--
- [imitating rim shot]
- YO, THIS IS AWESOME.
HE CAN'’T GET OUT.
- HUH?
WE SHOULD JUST LOCK HIM
IN THERE.
HE'’S CAGED AGAIN.
HOW AM I GONNA DO MY MAKEUP?
JIONNI?
- WHAT?
- I CAN'’T SEE MY FACE.
- WHY?
- THE MIRROR'’S TOO HIGH.
HOW AM I GONNA DO MY MAKEUP?
- [chuckles]
USE LORENZO'’S STOOL.
- THIS A SICK JOKE?
- GO AHEAD,
HIT THE GOLF BALL.
LET ME SEE.
- NO.
- THAT DOOR WAS OPEN.
- IT WAS OPEN?
- IT WAS OPEN.
- YOU'’RE LYING.
- OKAY.
- BETTER NOT BE LEPRECHAUNS
IN THERE.
IS THERE SOMEBODY IN THERE?
[gasps]
OH!
THERE'’S NOTHING.
THIS REMINDS ME
OF A LEPRECHAUN DOOR
AND THERE'’S A LEPRECHAUN
IN THIS ATTIC,
AND I DON'’T LIKE IT
BECAUSE IT'’S LORENZO'’S PLAYROOM.
IF HE'’S IN THE PLAYROOM
PLAYING BY HIMSELF,
AND A LEPRECHAUN POPS OUT--
- THEY'’LL PLAY TOGETHER.
- NO!
THEY'’RE NOT FRIENDS.
LEPRECHAUNS ARE MEAN.
THEY KILL PEOPLE.
JUST AN ATTIC.
[Panama Wedding'’s
Feels Like Summer]
- ♪ OH, AND I'’M FEELING LAZY ♪
♪ MY HEART IS BEATING NOW
♪
- I'’M EXCITED
THEY'’RE FINALLY HERE.
I FEEL LIKE IT'’S GONNA BE
A FUN SUMMER.
- I HOPE SO.
- UNTIL MY VAGINA RIPS.
THEN THE SUMMER'’S GONNA TAKE
A TURN FOR THE WORSE.
- HELLO, NEIGHBORS.
- OH, HEY.
- LOOK AT THIS SETUP, WOW.
- WE BROUGHT DESSERT.
- FAKE APPLES?
- YES.
- [laughs]
- ARE YOU GONNA BEHAVE?
- SO I'’M GLAD YOU SHOWED UP.
- YEAH, WE JUST WANTED
TO SETTLE IN
AND, YOU KNOW, UNPACK AND...
- THE WHOLE HOUSE?
- REWIND, YEAH.
- REWIND?
- UNWIND.
[both laughing]
- REWIND?
SO WHAT, DID YOU END UP
BACK IN EAST HAMPTON?
- WE WANTED TO UNWIND,
AND, NO, I JUST WANTED
TO GET UNPACKED.
ANY NAMES FOR THE BABY?
- DO YOU REMEMBER
IN YOUR KITCHEN LAST YEAR,
I SAID MEILANI ALEXANDRA?
- YES.
- DID YOU GUYS
THINK OF BABY NAMES?
- I ACTUALLY WROTE DOWN ONE.
- WHAT?
- WAIT A MINUTE, ARE YOU REALLY
DIGGING OUT A LIST RIGHT NOW?
- WOW.
- MEILANI ALEXANDRA MATTHEWS?
- YEAH.
I COULDN'’T GET OVER THAT NAME.
- SO NOT ONLY LAST YEAR,
WERE YOU TWO SAYING YOU WANT
TO BE PREGNANT TOGETHER, YOU HAD
THE NAME PICKED OUT ALREADY?
- IF BY "TWO,"
YOU MEAN JENNI, THEN YES.
- THAT WAS ME, THAT WAS CRAZY,
BUT AT LEAST YOU LIKE IT.
- I DO LIKE IT.
I REALLY DO LIKE IT.
- DO YOU LIKE YOUR OWN NAME?
- MY MOTHER JUST TOLD ME THIS
YESTERDAY.
IF I WAS A BOY,
HARLEY CHARLES FARLEY.
HARLEY CHARLIE FARLEY.
IF MY NAME
WAS HARLEY CHARLIE FARLEY,
I WOULD BE DESTINED TO BE,
LIKE, A PLUMBER
OR A MECHANIC.
- A MECHANIC.
- [whistles]
- I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT MY MOTHER WAS THINKING.
- IT RHYMES.
I HONESTLY DON'’T THINK
YOUR PARENTS WERE THINKING
WHEN THEY WERE DECIDING TO NAME
YOU HARLEY CHARLIE FARLEY.
IT'’S LIKE,
IMAGINE GOING TO SCHOOL,
AND THEN ALL THE KIDS,
AND YOU'’D HAVE NO FRIENDS.
I WOULD BE THERE FOR YOU,
THOUGH.
- YOU WERE A BITCH IN SCHOOL.
- I'’D BE NICE TO YOUR FACE.
- [laughs] THAT'’S--
- AND THEN, I'’D BE LIKE,
"OH, THAT BOY, EW, HE'’S WEIRD."
- WELL, IT'’S JUST
SPEAKING OF [bleep] NAMES,
HARLEY [bleep] CHARLIE.
SMART NAMES--MICHELLE.
- MICHELLE OBAMA.
- YEAH.
- GIOVANNA'’S A SMART NAME.
I AM HAVING A GIRL,
AND WE'’RE GONNA DO
GIOVANNA MARIE LAVALLE.
ITALIAN, IT FLOWS.
WORKS.
GIOVANNA MARIE LAVALLE.
- "GIOVANNA MARIE LAVALLE."
THAT'’S BEAUTIFUL.
- I ENJOY THIS.
- ME TOO.
- THIS'’LL BE A START
TO A BEAUTIFUL SUMMER.
- YEAH, WE HAVE TO DO IT
MORE OFTEN.
- INSTEAD OF CALLING ME
IN THE MORNING, NOW I CAN JUST--
- JUST COME OVER.
- YEAH.
- WITH A CUP OF COFFEE.
- WHAT TIME DO YOU
NORMALLY WAKE UP?
- YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT TO DO?
I WANT TO DO THE TELEPHONES.
- [laughs] YEAH.
- WITH A STRING.
- THAT REALLY DOES WORK?
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THAT WAS [bleep].
- NO, BABE, THAT DOES NOT WORK.
- HAVE YOU EVER TRIED IT?
- NO, BUT I HAVE
A BRAIN IN MY HEAD
AND I KNOW
THAT IT DOES NOT WORK.
- WELL, WE GOT TO TRY IT.
I BET YOU IT WORKS.
- HEY, BOO.
- MY LAST PREGNANCY,
JIONNI HAD TO PUSH MY BUTT
UP THE STAIRS.
WHOA!
THIS IS A BIG-ASS ROOM
FOR A LITTLE BABY.
- I KNOW.
- MY GOD.
THIS IS THE SIZE
OF, LIKE, MY MASTER.
- ARE YOU FIGHTING?
- YOU SHOULD GIVE BIRTH
THAT WAY.
[laughs]
- I ACTUALLY--SWEAR TO GOD,
THIS IS HOW I WANTED
TO GIVE BIRTH.
- AND I'’LL CATCH IT.
[laughs]
- I WANT TO--NO, I WANTED--
IF I'’M NOT GETTING
AN EPIDURAL--
I WATCHED A VIDEO
OF AN EPIDURAL.
- YOU CAN'’T WATCH THAT--
- AND NOW,
I DON'’T WANT AN EPIDURAL.
- I DIDN'’T EVEN WATCH THAT.
- SO I'’M NOT GONNA GET ONE.
- OY...[bleep].
- I TOLD MY DOCTOR,
"DON'’T LET ME GET ONE."
- THIS BITCH ISN'’T GETTING
AN EPIDURAL.
SO FEEL YOUR VAGINA
RIP TO YOUR BUTTHOLE.
- [laughs]
- NO THANKS,
I'’LL TAKE THE EPIDURAL.
- ORIGINALLY,
BECAUSE THEY SAY GRAVITY HELPS,
I WAS GONNA, LIKE, SQUAT
OR, LIKE, BE ON A BIRTHING BALL
UNTIL SHE WAS, LIKE, READY.
- I FEEL LIKE IF YOU JUST
SAT ON THE TOILET AND PUSHED,
IT'’D BE EASIER.
- [groaning]
I THOUGHT YOU HAD TO PUSH--
YOU SAID YOU HAD TO PUSH
LIKE YOU'’RE TAKING A [bleep].
- MM.
IT FEELS LIKE
YOU'’RE TAKING A POOP.
'’CAUSE REMEMBER,
I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,
I GOT TO [bleep].
BRING ME TO THE BATHROOM."
THE DOCTOR WAS LIKE,
"IT'’S TIME."
I WAS LIKE,
"NO, IT'’S A TURD."
HE'’S LIKE,
"NO, IT'’S YOUR BABY."
- ARE YOU GONNA BE MORE RELAXED
THIS TIME AROUND?
- NO, I'’M TERRIFIED.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
YOU HAD JANICE LAST TIME.
YOU'’RE GONNA BE
IN THE NEW HOUSE BY THEN, RIGHT?
- I COULD DO IT MYSELF.
- YEAH? I CAN'’T.
- WE CAN DO IT OURSELVES.
YEAH, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- I DID HIRE A NANNY.
- YOU DID?
- JUST, LIKE, SOMEONE TO HELP.
- AND YOU DIDN'’T TELL ME?
- I KNOW BUT, LIKE--
- WE WERE SUPPOSED TO DO
THAT PROCESS TOGETHER.
- I KNOW, THAT'’S WHY
I FEEL REALLY BAD TELLING YOU.
- YOU'’RE ANNOYING.
- I WANTED NICOLE
TO HELP ME FIND A NANNY
BUT I TOTALLY FLAKED ON THAT.
- I'’M A LITTLE UPSET...
- SORRY.
- THAT JENNI DIDN'’T INVOLVE ME
IN THE NANNY PICKING,
BUT I TRUST HER JUDGMENT,
AND I JUST HOPE THAT I TRUST
THIS GIRL TOO,
BECAUSE IT IS MY BABY ALSO.
- I HOPE SO.
YOU'’RE MY BABY MAMA.
- [laughs]
SO HOW COME YOU DIDN'’T HIRE
ANY OF THE JOEYS?
I FEEL LIKE THEY'’RE GONNA GET
REALLY UPSET
THAT YOU DIDN'’T EVEN
ACKNOWLEDGE THEM.
- THEY ALL LIVE TOO FAR.
- THAT'’S THE REAL REASON?
- AND THEY'’RE CRAZY.
AND THEY'’RE JOEYS.
- THEY WOULD--
- KILL MY CHILD.
- YEAH.
- I KNOW.
BUT MY EXCUSE IS,
"OH, I'’M SORRY,
YOU JUST LIVE TOO FAR."
- I THINK WITH THE JOEYS,
EVEN THOUGH WE DON'’T TRUST THEM,
WE SHOULD JUST BE FUN
WITH THEM ANYWAY.
- I HOPE THE JOEYS AREN'’T
GONNA BE MAD
THAT I DIDN'’T HIRE THEM
AS A NANNY,
BUT THEY'’RE DRUNKS.
I LOVE THEM.
- THEY MIGHT BE A LITTLE UPSET
THAT YOU DIDN'’T CONSIDER THEM,
SO MAYBE WE SHOULD PRETEND
THAT WE CONSIDERED THEM.
- OBVIOUSLY, I HOPE
THEY DON'’T TAKE THAT SERIOUS.
- YEAH.
- WE SHOULD DO SOMETHING
MORE CRAZIER.
- LIKE WHAT?
- WE SHOULD DO, LIKE,
A RELAY RACE WITH THE BABIES,
BUT WITH YOUR NANNY TOO.
SO WE COULD SAY,
"ALL RIGHT, WHOEVER WINS
IS GONNA BE THE NANNY,"
BUT YOUR NANNY IS GONNA WIN,
SO THEY WON'’T FEEL BAD.
- OH, MY GOD,
IF SHE DOESN'’T WIN?
- WHAT IF MY JOEY WINS?
[baby crying]
- I THINK YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET
YOUR TERROR TWO-YEAR-OLD.
- LORENZO.
LORENZO, CLEAN UP, PLEASE.
GIVE MOMMY A BREAK TODAY.
- [laughs]
- PLEASE, I BEG YOU.
- NO.
- NO?
- SURE YOU WANT THIS?
- I HAVE NO CHOICE NOW.
- GIVE HER TO SOMEONE.
- [laughs]
[The Royalty'’s I Want You]
- ♪ NOTHING COULD GO WRONG
WHEN YOU'’RE WITH ME ♪
- WANT TO TAKE A NAP?
- NO.
- YOU HAVE TO, THOUGH.
[baby whines]
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- OBSTACLE COURSE.
- OBSTACLE COURSE!
[baby doll laughing]
ALL RIGHT, NEXT STATION.
I KNOW THE JOEYS
ARE GONNA BE PISSED.
THEY'’RE GONNA BE LIKE,
"WHY DIDN'’T YOU ASK ME
TO BE THE NANNY?"
SO I HAVE THIS GREAT PLAN
THAT WE ARE GONNA DO
A NANNY OBSTACLE COURSE
WITH THE JOEYS, BUT THEN
ALSO WITH THE REAL NANNY.
SO WHOEVER WINS
IS GONNA BE THE NANNY
AND THEN THE JOEYS
WON'’T FEEL SO BAD.
MAYBE WE SHOULD TEST
ON YOU FIRST.
- NO, THAT'’S ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS HAVE FUN.
I'’M ACTUALLY TAKING ROGER
TO A LITTLE DADDY BOOT CAMP.
- OH, HAVE FUN.
HOPE HE DOES WELL.
- GOOD LUCK.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'’S LUBE '’EM.
JUST MAKE IT NICE AND GREASY.
- [laughs]
- EW-IE!
- THEY'’RE GONNA GET [bleep]
ON THIS ONE.
[phone ringing]
OH, [bleep].
HELLO?
- HI, I'’M AT YOUR HOUSE.
- ACTUALLY, WE'’RE GONNA BE
NEXT DOOR AT NICOLE'’S HOUSE.
- NO PROBLEM.
- I'’M GONNA BE A LITTLE WORRIED
IF LINDSAY
CAN'’T HANDLE THE JOEYS,
I'’LL BE HONEST.
- WELL, SHE CAN HANDLE YOU.
THAT'’S A BIG STEP.
- TRUE.
- HMM.
- TRUE, AND SHE'’S HANDLED ME
AT MY BITCHIEST.
- OH, NO.
HELL NO.
I'’D BE LIKE, "[bleep] OFF."
SHE'’S GOT NICE BOOBIES.
HI.
- HELLO.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
- NICOLE, NICE TO MEET YOU.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HI, SWEETHEART.
- HI.
- YOU LOOK GOOD.
READY FOR--
- [laughs]
- UM, READY FOR--
- YOU GOT GREAT BOOBS.
- OH. [laughs]
- IT'’S THE FIRST THING I SAW.
RIGHT WHEN I SEE LINDSAY,
MY EYES GO
STRAIGHT TO HER BOOBS.
SHE HAS GREAT BOOBS.
LIKE, I'’M A LESBIAN.
VERY PRETTY AND SHE TALKS
LIKE FRAN DRESCHER.
[imitating Fran Drescher]
"HEY, YOU GUYS."
YOU'’RE THE NANNY.
YOU'’RE SUPPOSED
TO SOUND LIKE THE NANNY.
- OH, MY GOD, I NEVER
PUT THAT TOGETHER.
- AND SHE'’S A NANNY.
- LIKE, YOU KNOW, I WOULD--
[doorbell ringing]
- [bleep] ARE HERE!
- OH, GOD, I CAN'’T.
- [laughs]
- HI, BOOS!
- [high-pitched voice]
HEY, GIRL!
- ARE YOU WASTED ALREADY?
- I'’M BUMMED.
I DRANK, LIKE,
SEVEN PINOT GRIGIOS.
- OH, I MISSED YOU.
both: MMM.
- BE PREPARED.
SO JOEY, JOEY, JOEY, LINDSAY.
- HI.
- I'’M LINDSAY, NICE TO MEET YOU.
- LINDSAY.
NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
- SHE WILL BE
HELPING ME WITH THE BABY.
- IS SHE YOUR AU PAIR?
ARE YOU THE AU PAIR?
- KIND OF.
IS THAT THE WORD WE USE?
- ASSISTANT, NANNY.
- YEAH.
- ARE YOU GONNA PULL IT
OUT OF HER COOCH?
- [laughs]
- I WOULD, I'’M VOLUNTEERING.
I'’LL PULL IT OUT.
- OH, YOU WILL?
THANK YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WE'’RE HERE TO INDUCE TODAY.
- I'’LL LET YOU TWO CATCH UP.
- WE ARE HERE TO INDUCE LABOR.
- I'’LL GO IN THERE AND GET IT.
I'’M LIKE, "COME ON OUT, GIRL."
- COME.
SO WE INVITED ALL OF YOU HERE
BECAUSE TODAY,
WE'’RE GONNA DO THE NANNY...
both: OBSTACLE COURSE.
- [laughs]
- SO YOU'’RE ALL TRYING OUT
TO BE JENNI'’S NANNY.
- SO WAIT, IF ONE OF US WINS,
THEN LINDSAY GETS THE BOOT?
- WE'’LL THINK ABOUT IT.
- OKAY.
- YEAH, BUT AS OF RIGHT NOW,
LINDSAY'’S THE NANNY.
- HAVE YOU EVER DROPPED
A BABY ON ITS HEAD?
- NO.
- [laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
- SO WHAT EXACTLY CAN I EXPECT
FROM THIS DADDY DAY CARE THING?
- YOU'’RE GONNA GET
SOME GOOD LEARNING EXPERIENCE
ABOUT BEING A DAD.
YOU ARE GONNA BE PHYSICALLY
AND MENTALLY PREPARED
BY THE TIME YOU WALK
OUT OF HERE.
- SO ARE WE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO GET A GYM WORKOUT IN?
- [laughs]
- YOU READY FOR THIS, BUDDY?
- LET'’S DO IT.
- CAN WE HELP YOU?
- THIS--
- HERE FOR DADDY DAY CARE.
IS THIS A GOOD--
- DADDY DAY CARE?
[laughter]
- I SEE A LOT OF WOMEN HERE
FOR DADDY DAY CARE.
- WE'’RE TEACHING
A COMFORT AND LABOR CLASS.
ARE YOU INTERESTED
IN SITTING IN ON THAT?
- THIS DOES NOT LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE A DADDY BOOT CAMP TO ME.
WERE YOU LYING TO ME,
OR DID YOU JUST NOT
DO YOUR HOMEWORK ONCE AGAIN?
- IT SAID DADDY BOOT CAMP, OKAY?
THAT'’S WHAT IT SAID
ON THE BROCHURE.
- DID WE GET THE WRONG ADDRESS?
- I THINK SO.
[both laughing]
- IT'’S KIND OF--IT'’S GONNA
PREPARE YOU TO BE A DAD.
HOW TO HELP, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, WHY NOT?
- WE'’RE HERE.
- ALL RIGHT, COME ON IN.
YOU'’RE GONNA BE PARTNERS, RIGHT?
- LIKE, AS IN ONE HAS TO BE--
- YOU'’RE FULLY COMMITTED.
ONCE YOU SIT DOWN,
YOU'’RE FULLY COMMITTED.
- ONE HAS TO BE THE WOMAN?
YOU'’RE THE WOMAN.
YOU GOT ME INTO THIS.
- WHY I GOTTA BE THE [bleep]?
- '’CAUSE YOU TALKED ME
INTO COMING HERE,
SO THAT MEANS YOU--
- JUST [bleep, indistinct,
bleep]?
- NO, BECAUSE YOU SAID
THIS WAS A DADDY BOOT CAMP,
AND IT CLEARLY IS NOT,
BUT THAT WOULD BE
THE SECONDARY REASON, YES.
- [bleep].
- SO MOMS, IF YOU CAN GET
ON YOUR HANDS AND KNEES.
- [clears throat]
- THIS IS THE EXACT THING
THAT GOT YOU INTO THIS POSITION,
BY THE WAY.
- ONE OF THE BEST WAYS
TO FIND RELIEF
AND MOVE THAT ENERGY THROUGH
IS TO VOCALIZE.
BIG BREATH,
AND JUST LET IT MOVE THROUGH.
- [exhales]
[laughter]
- IT'’S EXACTLY HOW JENNI
SOUNDS WHEN SHE ORGASMS.
[laughter]
SO THE FIRST THING WE DID
UPON ARRIVING AT DADDY BOOT CAMP
WAS IMMEDIATELY
STEAM-PLOW JIONNI'’S [bleep].
[laughter]
[humming]
- ONE, TWO, GOOD, GOOD.
NICE AND DEEP, NICE AND LOW.
- [humming]
[laughs]
- AT THIS POINT,
I'’M VERY VIOLATED.
- YOU'’RE [bleep].
- I FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
- WHEN YOU [bleep] SOMEBODY
LIKE THAT,
HOW CAN IT NOT
BRING YOU CLOSER?
- I STILL FEEL YOU.
[both laughing]
IT NEVER FELT SO GOOD.
- BAD MORNING TO TAKE A VIAGRA.
[laughter]
- ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY?
all: YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'’S START OUR OBSTACLE COURSE.
SO WE HAVE A FEW TABLES
FOR THE NANNY OBSTACLE COURSE.
ONE IS A CHANGING SECTION
WHERE YOU DRESS THE BABY
WHILE CHUGGING VODKA.
THE NEXT TABLE
IS LUBED UP WATERMELON.
- MM-HMM,
IT'’S LIKE A SLIPPERY BABY.
- YOU PUT IN THE BABY BJORN.
AND I FIGURE YOU HAVE TO RUN
LAPS OR DO SOMETHING.
- AND THEN,
THE LAST BUT NOT LEAST IS WHEN
YOU SLIP AND YOU SLIDE,
BUT YOU HAVE TO CATCH A BABY.
AND I FEEL LIKE IT'’S GONNA BE
A [bleep] SHOW.
- HOPE THEY DON'’T GET TOO WEIRD.
ONE, TWO, THREE, GO!
[blows whistle]
- HEY.
- WE'’RE GONNA GO SEE DADDY
IN PRISON, HONEY.
- DRESS THE BABIES.
- BUTTON UP.
A LADY HAS TO BE A LADY.
- YOU'’RE BREAKING HER LEG.
DRESS THE BABY,
DRESS THE BABY.
ALL RIGHT, GO, NEXT STATION.
- THAT IS NOT--JOEY!
- YOU PUT IT ON BACKWARDS!
- THAT IS NOT--YOU'’RE CHEATING.
- NO, THAT'’S FINE.
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, JOEY, VODKA.
YOU DON'’T WANT--
- OH, [bleep]!
- TAKE YOUR VODKA.
YOU GOT TO CHUG IT.
- I DON'’T KNOW HOW TO MAKE THIS.
- YEAH, WHY ARE THERE ONLY TWO?
- NO, YOU GOT TO KEEP
THE NIPPLE ON!
CHUG, CHUG.
OOH, I LIKE HER.
NEXT STATION.
[blows whistle]
ALL RIGHT, PUT THE BABY
IN THE BABY BJORN!
- RUN TWO LAPS.
- OH, MY GOD.
- AROUND THE TABLES.
- ALL RIGHT, RUN TWO LAPS,
LET'’S GO.
- OH, NOW RUN?
- [blows whistle]
- AH!
- RUN AROUND!
GO, JOEY.
RUN FOR YOUR LIFE!
RUN!
- OH, MY GOD.
- YOUR BABY'’S ON FIRE.
- NICOLE, PARTY'’S HERE!
- THAT'’S NOT WHERE
THE BABY GOES!
- ALL RIGHT,
WHAT DO WE GOT TO DO NOW?
- ARE YOUR BOOBS REAL?
- YEAH.
- ARE THEY?
- JEEZ.
BABY BJORN!
[both scream]
- WE GOT BABY GUTS ALL OVER.
[all scream]
- [laughs]
- YOU JUST KILLED THE BABY!
- YEAH.
- MMM.
DROP AND TWERK.
TWERK IT.
- TWERK.
- [laughs]
- NEXT STATION.
[blows whistle]
CATCH A BABY!
[all cheering]
- WHOA!
[laughter]
- CATCH A BABY!
- JOEY! JOEY!
[laughter]
GIVE ME THE BABY.
- OH!
[laughter]
- EW.
- HE'’S LIKE A BEACHED WHALE.
- EW, JOEY!
[all screaming]
[laughter]
- BABY!
- THE OBSTACLE COURSE TODAY
WAS A HUGE [bleep] SHOW,
WHICH I ENJOYED FULLY.
- ALL RIGHT SO WHO WON?
- DO YOU WANT A HOSE?
- JENNI, WHO WON?
WHO'’S THE ULTIMATE NANNY?
- YOU WON.
- SO JOEY'’S YOUR REAL NANNY?
- NO, LINDSAY IS PERFECT
AT WHAT SHE DOES.
- ALL RIGHT, LINDSAY YOU CAN
WATCH THE BABY WHEN WE'’RE DRUNK.
- EXACTLY,
WHICH WILL BE EVERY DAY.
- ALL RIGHT.
[laughs]
- THERE WE GO.
- OKAY, SOUNDS GOOD.
- YOU CAN JUST BE THE UNCLES.
- OH, MY GOD!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, MY GOD, POOR BABY.
- YOU'’RE DEFINITELY GONNA KEEP
THAT BABY NOW.
- YOU'’RE JUST THE UNCLE JOEYS.
- OH, MY GOD.
- IT'’S A BABY BJORN.
IT'’S A NEW DESIGN.
- UGH!
I DIE.
I FEEL LIKE IT'’S NOT A PARTY
UNTIL WE SEE BEAR JOEY'’S PENIS.
- MM-HMM.
- AND PUBES.
YOU GUYS DID GOOD.
I'’M PROUD OF YOU.
- PUT YOUR PENIS AWAY.
- [laughs]
- SO YOU'’RE GONNA PUT IT AROUND
YOUR NECK LIKE A LONG SCARF.
- OHH.
- AND YOU'’RE GOING TO GRAB
ONTO THE SCARF
AS YOU SQUAT DOWN.
- HOLD ON, WAIT.
- THERE YOU GO.
- I'’VE NEVER BEEN
THAT CLOSE TO BRACIOLE.
THAT BRACIOLEWAS
PRETTY MUCH INSIDE ME.
MY HEAD WAS EYE LEVEL
WITH YOUR SACK.
IT WAS A LITTLE UNCOMFORTABLE.
- AM I THE BIGGEST
YOU'’VE EVER HAD?
- BY FAR.
- ONE OF THE MOST
MESMERIZING EXPERIENCES
AND ONE OF THE GREATEST COMFORTS
FOR LABOR
IS STARING
INTO YOUR PARTNER'’S EYES.
SO FACE YOUR PARTNER.
LADIES, THROW YOUR HANDS
AROUND YOUR HUSBAND'’S NECK,
AND I WANT YOU TO LOCK EYES.
AND NOW, WHILE YOU'’RE LOOKING
AT EACH OTHER, BE ENCOURAGING.
YOU SAY THINGS LIKE
"YOU'’RE SO AMAZING.
"YOU'’RE GONNA BE
A WONDERFUL MOTHER.
YOU ARE SO BEAUTIFUL."
[both laughing]
- TELL ME, BUDDY.
- PUSH MY KID OUT.
PUSH.
- WHAT ELSE?
- UM...
I LOVE YOU.
- WHAT ELSE?
- MORE THAN WORDS CAN SAY.
- YOU MAKE ME FEEL
SO COMFORTABLE.
- BABY, THIS SHALL PASS.
WE WILL GET THROUGH THIS.
JUST BITE DOWN
ON YOUR BOTTOM LIP
AND PUSH MY KID OUT.
- [laughs]
COULDN'’T DO IT WITHOUT YOU.
- I KNOW.
I'’M HERE FOR YOU.
- I MEAN, AT ONE POINT,
ROGER WAS TELLING ME,
YOU KNOW, I'’M BEAUTIFUL.
YOU KNOW,
I MAKE HIM FEEL COMFORTABLE,
YOU KNOW, WE DID HAVE
A MOMENT, YOU KNOW, I--
- YOU COMPLETE ME.
- I COMPLETE YOU--
- YOU HAD ME AT HELLO.
- YOU KNOW, THAT WAS KIND OF,
YOU KNOW, SOOTHING.
I KIND OF ENJOYED THAT.
IT WAS PRETTY ROMANTIC
FOR A SECOND.
BUT THEN, YOU KNOW,
I WENT BACK TO REALITY
AND SAW, YOU KNOW,
FELT HIS GUN DIGGING
INTO MY HIP A LITTLE BIT
AND CUT BACK TO WEIRD.
- WE DON'’T TALK ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED BACK THERE, ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH, OKAY.
- EVER.
I DON'’T--DO YOU HAVE
A KNIFE ON YOU?
I'’D LIKE TO--
- SOMETHING,
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- SHAKE ON--
A BLOOD SHAKE THAT WE NEVER
TALK ABOUT THIS
EVER, EVER AGAIN.
- BLOOD SHAKE?
WE ALREADY DID
A PRETTY GOOD SHAKE BEFORE.
- IT'’S TRUE.
BASICALLY, IF I HAVE ANYTHING,
YOU'’VE GOT IT AT THIS POINT,
SO--
[both laughing]
- WE SHAKED GOOD ENOUGH BEFORE.
WE'’RE ABOVE BLOOD BROTHERS,
SO...
WHATEVER HAPPENS
AT DADDY BOOT CAMP--
- WE DON'’T TALK ABOUT.
- YOU ASKED ME WHAT TO EXPECT.
I SAID IT'’S GONNA CHANGE YOU
PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY.
- YEAH, WELL...
- AND IT DID.
- APPARENTLY,
IT TURNED ME GAY AS WELL.
- THIS EPISODE
OF SNOOKI AND JWOWW--
- CONTINUES NOW.
- WHO WANTS SOME ICE CREAM?
LORENZO,
YOU WANT SOME ICE CREAM?
- WHO WANTS ICE CREAM?
ME.
THIS IS LIVING.
I COULD DO THIS EVERY NIGHT.
- MM-HMM, WE SHOULD DO IT.
- WE DO S'’MORES ALL THE TIME.
- PERIODICALLY.
- WE LOVE--
[shatters]
- [laughs]
- SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
- WE LOVE S'’MORES.
- AND WE'’RE BACK.
- IT'’S GONNA BE A LONG SUMMER.
- WE'’RE GONNA NEED
A LOT OF DISHES.
- I STILL CAN'’T GET OVER
WHEN HE TURNS TWO,
WHEREVER WE HAVE HIS BIRTHDAY,
SHE WILL BE THERE.
- SOMETIME SOON WE COULD HAVE
SOME S'’MORES WITH LORENZO AND--
- MEILANI.
all: MEILANI.
- LITTLE MEILANI.
- I HAVE A SERIOUS QUESTION.
- YES.
- WOULD YOU EVER LET MEILANI
GO ON A DATE WITH LORENZO?
- OF COURSE.
- I WOULD ALMOST--
I FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS
ARE MY BROTHERS AND SISTERS.
- I ALMOST--
- I FEEL LIKE THEY'’D BE COUSINS,
RIGHT?
- YEAH, IT'’D BE LIKE INCEST.
I DON'’T KNOW.
- THEY'’D BE CLOSE FRIENDS
THAT ALWAYS HOOK UP.
- OH.
- THAT WOULD--OH, MY GOD.
- NOW YOU'’RE JUST BEING CREEPY.
- NOW I'’M GETTING PISSED.
- I KNOW.
MY DAUGHTER IS A HOOK UP?
- I DON'’T KNOW IF I WANT THAT.
I HONESTLY WOULDN'’T MIND
IF LORENZO AND MEILANI DATED.
- I PICTURE, LIKE, TOM CRUISE
AND KATIE HOLMES, THOUGH.
- YEAH, '’CAUSE HE'’S SO SHORT.
- [laughs]
- MEILANI?
- LORENZO'’S GONNA BE TINY,
AND MEILANI'’S PROBABLY GONNA BE
THIS HUGE MODEL.
WHAT IF WE WALKED IN ON THEM
HOOKING UP FOR THE FIRST TIME?
I WOULD CRY.
[imitates vomiting]
EW.
I CAN'’T EVEN THINK ABOUT THAT.
HE'’S, LIKE, A BABY.
- [laughs]
- STOP.
- STOP. EW.
- EW.
- YOU GOT TO SEE
THE BASEMENT I DESIGNED.
IT'’S PRETTY COOL.
I FOUND SOME INTEREST
IN, LIKE, DOING STUFF LIKE THAT.
- GOOD DEAL, MAN.
MAYBE YOU'’LL BE
AN INTERIOR DESIGNER ONE DAY.
- YOU SHOULD BE A CONSTRUCTOR,
THAT'’S WHAT YOU SHOULD BE.
- I'’M MORE, LIKE--
- A CONSTRUCTOR?
- YEAH.
- WHY'’RE YOU LAUGHING?
- A CONTRACTOR?
[laughter]
- OR YOU SHOULD BE
A CONSTRUCTOR--
- WHAT'’S A CONSTRUCTOR--
- JUST EVERY DAY--
- A CONSTRUCTOR?
- WHAT'’S A CONSTRUCTOR?
- JUST GET OUT LEGOS EVERY DAY.
- OH, MY GOD.
- IS THAT SOMEBODY
THAT DOES THIS?
[laughter]
- I THINK THIS SUMMER'’S
GONNA BE VERY MEMORABLE.
- YEAH, YOU'’RE HAVING A KID.
- YEAH, BUT, LIKE, EVERYTHING,
THE WHOLE SUMMER.
- GONNA BE A GOOD SUMMER, GUYS.
- AW.
- I DON'’T KNOW, YOU THINK
WE CAN TOP LAST SUMMER?
- I THINK SO, EASY.
- LAST SUMMER WAS GOOD.
- THIS SUMMER WILL BE BETTER.
- I FEEL LIKE IT'’S GONNA BE
ONE-OF-A-KIND.
- LORENZO, SAY BYE TO JENNI.
- OKAY.
JUST GOT--
- BYE, BUDDY.
- BYE.
- WHERE YOU GOING?
- SEE YOU LATER.
- LOVE YOU.
HAVE FUN.
- GET HOME SAFE, ALL RIGHT?
IT'’S GONNA BE A GOOD SUMMER.
- YOU GOT IT.
- SAY GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT.
[kissing]
- ♪ THE LIGHT WE GREW UP WITH
- WHEE!
- MMM.
- I LOVE YOU.
♪
♪ OH, OH
- NEXT TIME, ON--
- SNOOKI AND JWOWW...
- OW.
- REMEMBER HOW I ALWAYS WANTED
TO DO PRENATAL YOGA WITH YOU?
- BRING THE HANDS FORWARD.
- I FEEL LIKE THIS COULD
ACTUALLY BRING ON LABOR.
- IT'’S GONNA
POP OUT THAT BABY.
- YOU SHOULD FEEL IT
INSIDE YOUR INNER THIGH.
- OH, I FEEL IT.
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ♪ HUSH, LITTLE BABY
THEY'’RE SO WEIRD.
- BABY'’S SLEEPING.