- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- NOW, WHAT?
YOU'’RE PARENTS.
- I'’M STILL TRYING
TO FIGURE THAT PART OUT.
- WHAT GOES ON
AT BRIDAL SHOWERS?
- STRIPPERS,
WE GET WASTED, YOU KNOW.
- HOW COME I'’M NOT ALLOWED
TO GO?
- WHAT IS NICOLE'’S
FAVORITE THING ABOUT JIONNI?
HIS SENSE OF HUMOR.
- AND HIS WIENER.
[laughter]
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
[alarm clock ringing]
[baby babbling]
- SO TODAY WE'’RE GONNA GO
TO MEILANI'’S
FIRST DOCTOR'’S APPOINTMENT.
DIAPER BAG HAS, LIKE,
TWO WEEKS'’ WORTH
OF [bleep] IN IT.
I'’M ON MOMMY ADRENALINE.
IT'’S CRAZY AND I'’M JUST TIRED.
I WONDER WHAT THEY DO
FIRST VISIT.
IS IT LIKE AN EAR,
NOSE, EYE CHECKUP?
- WE KNOW HER HEARING WORKS,
'’CAUSE WHEN YOU WENT
IN THE BATHROOM LAST NIGHT
AND YOU SHUT THE DOOR,
SHE--SHE WENT...
- [laughs]
- OUR APPOINTMENT TODAY
IS AT 7:45 IN THE MORNING.
HER HEADBAND.
[both laughing]
SHE LOOKS LIKE ME
AFTER A NIGHT AT KARMA.
- I CALLED IT A NIGHT CAP,
BUT THAT'’S NOT IT.
- THAT'’S FUNNY.
[laughs]
- SLEEPING LIKE A BABY.
IT WORKS GOOD.
- AW, LET'’S GET GOING
BEFORE A DOCTOR YELLS AT US
FOR BEING LATE.
- HERE FOR MEILANI?
- YES, YEP.
- ALL RIGHT, I JUST NEED YOU
TO FILL A COUPLE THINGS OUT.
- OKAY.
- A CONSENT TO VACCINATE.
- THAT'’S NOT HAPPENING TODAY
THOUGH, RIGHT?
- IT IS.
- IT WILL BE OKAY.
[both laughing]
- I'’LL BE LEAVING THE ROOM.
- ROGER IS KIND OF BEING A BABY
ABOUT THE SHOTS WITH MEILANI,
BUT I ACTUALLY AM FALLING
IN LOVE WITH HIM MORE OVER THIS,
BECAUSE THIS IS A SIDE OF ROGER
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
THAT I DON'’T THINK ANYONE
IN THE WORLD HAS EVER SEEN.
- LOOK AT DADDY OVER HERE,
WIGGING OUT WITH HIS FINGERS.
- MATTHEWS?
- I WISH I HAD A XANAX FOR YOU.
- I GET IT, I UNDERSTAND
THAT IT'’S A NECESSITY.
I JUST DON'’T WANT
TO SEE IT HAPPEN.
I DON'’T WANT TO SEE
MY LITTLE GIRL CRYING.
ANGEL BABIES DON'’T NEED SHOTS.
THEY'’RE FROM THE HEAVENS.
[baby coughs]
- OH.
WOW-Y.
- HELL.
- [laughs]
[baby groans]
- YEAH.
- HEY.
- HEY, THERE, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- HI.
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
- HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- GREAT, GREAT.
NOW, FIRST THING
I WANT YOU TO DO
IS TO ACTUALLY PICK HER UP
AND HOLD HER FOR ME.
- ALL RIGHT.
MOMMY WANTS THAT THING
TO FALL OFF ALREADY.
GOOD MORNING.
- GREAT, PUT HER UP
ON YOUR SHOULDER
SO I CAN LISTEN TO HER BACK.
- SURE.
OKAY, LITTLE ONE, HERE WE GO.
[baby crying]
- SHH.
AW, SHH.
[baby crying]
GOOD MORNING.
I KNOW.
- SHH.
- ALL RIGHT, ABSOLUTELY,
PERFECTLY HEALTHY BABY.
- WHO'’S GIVING THE SHOT?
- OH, I DON'’T DO THAT.
MY NURSE'’LL DO THAT.
[both laughing]
- THANK YOU.
- I'’M THE GOOD GUY.
GOOD LUCK AGAIN,
WE'’LL SPEAK TO YOU SOON.
- SO I FEEL TERRIBLE
FOR MEILANI AND ROGER RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE MEILANI'’S
ABOUT TO GET HER HEPATITIS SHOT.
- HERE, HERE YOU GO.
- THANK YOU.
- YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
OKAY, I DON'’T LIKE
TO USE BAND-AIDS ON THEM
WHEN THEY'’RE THIS LITTLE...
- I'’LL BE GOING OUT THERE.
- JUST BECAUSE.
- ROGER NEEDS TO LEAVE THE ROOM,
AND I KNOW IT'’S GONNA
BOTHER THE [bleep] OUT OF HIM,
AND NOW, I HAVE TO BE HERE
TO WATCH THE SHOT GO DOWN.
- MOM, DO YOU WANT TO COME OVER
AND JUST HOLD HER LEG
A LITTLE BIT?
SORRY, HONEY.
- I AM LITERALLY GONNA CRY
RIGHT NOW.
- SHE'’S A STRONG ONE.
- YEAH.
- OKAY.
- YOU'’RE LUCKY I WASN'’T THERE,
'’CAUSE I WOULD'’VE BROKEN
THE NURSE'’S LEG.
[baby whines]
- THAT'’S IT.
DONE.
[baby crying]
I'’M DONE.
YOU CAN HOLD HER.
[baby crying]
- I'’M SORRY, I'’M SORRY.
SHH.
- ALL DONE, DADDY.
- OH, WOW, THAT'’S AWESOME.
I'’M SORRY, ANGEL.
- I'’M SO TIRED.
- OOH.
- NICOLE AND I HAVE BEEN
BUILDING THIS HOUSE
FOR OVER A YEAR NOW,
AND AS WE'’RE PULLING UP,
I MEAN, IT'’S JUST AWESOME.
IT REALLY IS
LIKE A DREAM COME TRUE.
YOU KNOW,
WE WENT FROM THE BASEMENT
TO BUILDING OUR OWN HOUSE,
AND I JUST CAN'’T WAIT
TO MOVE IN.
WHAT'’S UP, JOE?
- HEY, JOE.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- LOOKS GREAT.
- WE JUST PUT THE DOOR IN.
- WE'’RE GONNA HAVE WINDOWS,
RIGHT?
- IF YOU'’RE LUCKY.
- AFTER YOU.
- THANK YOU.
WOW.
I LOVE IT.
I LOVE IT, LOVE IT.
- THAT'’S AWESOME.
- IT'’S BEAUTIFUL.
I LOVE THE RAILING.
THE HOUSE LOOKS AMAZING.
CAN'’T WAIT TO COOK.
- NICOLE CAN MAKE SANDWICHES
AND HER DORITO SALAD.
THAT'’S ABOUT IT.
- IS THAT A STOVE?
- STOVETOP, YEAH.
- THAT'’S THE FRIDGE?
I'’M NOT REALLY GOOD WITH OVENS.
- [clicks tongue]
- ESPECIALLY NEW ONES,
OR HIGH-TECH ONES.
IMAGINE IF I BURN IT DOWN?
[gasps]
- OH, MY GOD.
- MM.
- GOD FORBID.
OH.
OUR MASTER BEDROOM IS GORGEOUS.
[gasps]
I LOVE IT.
- WHOA, LOOK AT THIS.
- MY BATHROOM!
OH, MY GOD.
IT'’S DONE.
- I MEAN, NICOLE
PICKED OUT ALL THAT TILE.
IT LOOKS GREAT.
CONNECTED IS HER HUGE CLOSET.
AND YOUR CLOSET.
- MY CLOSET.
I LOVE YOU.
WE'’RE GONNA BE BEST FRIENDS.
OBVIOUSLY,
I LOVE CLOTHES AND SHOES,
AND IT'’S GONNA BE, LIKE,
MY LITTLE SANCTUARY.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WE DID A GOOD JOB.
I'’M REALLY EXCITED
TO RAISE MY FAMILY HERE.
JUST THINKING, LIKE, WHAT IF
WE HAD THIS HOUSE GROWING UP?
LIKE, LORENZO HAS NO IDEA...
- OH, FORGET IT.
- HOW LUCKY HE IS TO HAVE, LIKE,
ALL THIS STUFF AND--YOU KNOW.
- AND WE'’RE LUCKY.
- WE'’RE LUCKY, YEAH,
BUT TO HAVE OUR KIDS GROW UP
IN A HOUSE LIKE THIS,
I'’M JUST REALLY HAPPY
THAT WE COULD DO THAT FOR THEM.
- NICOLE AND I ARE BLESSED
AND WE'’RE VERY FORTUNATE
FOR HAVING A HOUSE LIKE THIS,
AND HOPEFULLY,
WE RAISE OUR FAMILY TO BE,
YOU KNOW, HAPPY.
- [chuckles]
- WHY ARE YOU SO WEIRD?
- YOU'’RE A GOOD KID.
- YOU'’RE A GOOD PERSON.
[laughs]
- THAT REALLY LOOKS AWESOME.
- YEAH.
- GOOD JOB.
- I KNOW.
NOW, WAIT TILL EVERYTHING'’S DONE
AND WE MOVE IN.
- HOME, SWEET HOME.
- BABE, GUESS WHAT I'’M DOING
TODAY?
- WHAT?
- I'’M BRINGING JENNI
TO GO SEE MY DRESS.
- AND YOU'’RE TRYING IT ON?
- YEAH.
CLEARLY, IT'’S NOT GONNA FIT,
BUT SHE'’LL GET THE IDEA.
- ARE YOU GONNA GET MAD
IF IT DOESN'’T FIT?
- NO, '’CAUSE I'’M PREGNANT.
THERE'’S A BABY IN THERE.
I WOULD GET MAD IF IT DIDN'’T FIT
BECAUSE THERE'’S CHEESEBURGERS
IN THERE.
- [laughs]
- I JUST ORDERED MY VEILS,
SO MY WHOLE DRESS IS DONE.
- VEILS?
YOU'’RE WEARING
TWO DIFFERENT VEILS?
- YEAH.
- WHAT ARE YOU,
QUEEN LATIFAH?
- QUEEN LATIFAH?
WHAT?
- WHO WANTS BREAD?
both: ME!
- SO IT'’S, LIKE,
YOUR REAL DRESS?
- YES.
WHY WOULD IT BE A FAKE DRESS?
- I DON'’T KNOW.
DIDN'’T YOU HAVE,
LIKE, TWO DIFFERENT DRESSES
ONE TIME?
- I SHOWED YOU
MY RECEPTION DRESS.
- I'’M ALLOWED TO SEE THAT?
- YOU SAID,
"THAT'’S WHAT YOU'’RE WEARING?"
- [snickers]
- REMEMBER?
- SHUT UP.
I SAID THAT?
- YES.
- '’CAUSE YOU HAD THE BEADS
AROUND YOUR HEAD
WITH SOMETHING HANGING--
- IT'’S GATSBY.
BEADS ARE GATSBY.
- ARE YOU WEARING THAT
WHEN WE SAY, "I DO"?
- NO, WHEN I SAID, "I DO,"
IT'’S A NICE, TRADITIONAL DRESS.
- I MIGHT HESITATE.
- [chuckles]
THAT'’S NOT NICE.
[phone ringing]
- HEY.
- DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO THE CITY?
ARE YOU READY?
- I JUST GOT TO GET CHANGED.
I'’M FINISHING A BOTTLE WITH HER.
- LORENZO'’S BETWEEN MY LEGS
LIKE A WEIRDO.
- [laughs]
- STOP IT.
ALL RIGHT, SO I GOT US A CAB,
WHENEVER YOU'’RE READY.
- OKAY, LOVE YOU.
BYE.
- STOP--THOSE ARE MY SANDALS.
- [laughs]
[car horn honking]
- ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU, GUYS.
- BYE.
SHOW THAT POST BODY, GIRL.
POST BODY.
- THIS IS FANCY.
- I MIGHT HAVE TO TAKE A NAP.
- OH, MY GOD.
IF YOU'’RE TAKING A NAP,
I'’M GONNA SPOON WITH YOU.
ROGER, LIKE,
TELLS ME WHAT TO DO, SO--
- JIONNI USED TO DO THAT,
AND I HATED HIM.
I'’M REALLY EXCITED
TO SHOW YOU MY DRESS.
- I CAN'’T WAIT.
- HELLO.
- YOU WANT TO FOLLOW US?
WE'’RE GONNA BRING YOU
INTO THE SHOWROOM, OKAY?
- YEAH.
LOOK HOW BEAUTIFUL
THIS PLACE IS.
- YEAH.
- IT'’S LIKE BRIDAL HEAVEN.
SHE JUST GAVE BIRTH
EIGHT DAYS AGO AND LOOK AT HER.
- LOOK AT YOU.
- OH, SPACE.
- LOOK AT THAT.
- CONGRATULATIONS TO YOU.
- [bleep].
IT'’S NOT FAIR TO US
NORMAL PREGNANT WOMEN THAT--
- I'’M A NORMAL, PREGNANT WOMAN.
- NO, YOU'’RE NOT.
NOBODY SNAPS BACK LIKE THAT,
NOBODY.
- I DON'’T--
- ANNOYING.
- THINK SHE'’S GONNA BE
SURPRISED?
- SHE KIND OF KNOWS
THE GOWN I WANT.
WE GOT TWO SIZES UP, RIGHT?
JUST IN CASE?
- YES.
- JUST MAKE SURE THEY STAY UP.
[soothing classical music]
♪
- CAN WE USE MY CLIP?
- AS LONG AS YOU
DON'’T HAVE LICE.
- OF COURSE I DON'’T.
♪
- YOU READY, BOO?
- WAKE UP.
- I'’M DYING.
I HAVE TO GET THIS OFF.
- [laughs]
- JUST PICK IT UP.
- [gasps]
- IT'’S CHOKING.
I'’M CHOKING.
- OH, MY GOSH!
IT LOOKS SO PRETTY.
- I CAN'’T BREATHE.
- I'’M GONNA LOOK
SO MUCH SKINNIER THOUGH,
SO DON'’T JUDGE ME.
- WELL, YOU WILL TAKE
THIS MOMENT AND BE HAPPY.
- I CAN'’T BREATHE.
- NOBODY CAN BREATHE
ON THEIR WEDDING DAY.
NICOLE IN HER DRESS, I MEAN,
I HONESTLY HAVE NO WORDS.
SHE IS STUNNING.
SHE'’S EXACTLY
HOW I WOULD PICTURE HER TO BE,
JUST THIS ELEGANT,
BEAUTIFUL BRIDE,
LIKE, YOU KNOW, BREATHTAKING.
LIKE, I KNOW NICOLE ENVISIONED
THIS DRESS HER WHOLE LIFE.
AND--'’CAUSE YOU CAN TELL
BY THE WAY HER FACE IS,
LIKE, THIS IS IT.
OH, MY GOD,
YOU'’RE SO GORGEOUS.
- YOU LIKE IT?
- IT'’S SO PRETTY.
- IT'’S THE SAME DESIGNER.
REMEMBER WHEN WE WENT
TO TRY ON DRESSES?
I LOVE THIS GOWN.
- YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
- THINK JIONNI WILL CRY?
- I'’M GONNA CRY.
- I WANT HIM TO CRY.
LIKE, SEE ME AND BE LIKE,
"SHE'’S SO BEAUTIFUL."
- LISTEN,
I AM NOT A JOY CRIER, SO--
- NEITHER IS HE.
- YEAH.
YOU BOTH SUCK.
- [laughs]
I DIDN'’T THINK ROGER WAS,
AND HE'’S BEEN CRYING
FOR THE PAST WEEK.
- [laughs]
- HE'’S MORE HORMONAL THAN I AM.
OH, MY GOD.
MY BOOBS ARE KILLING ME.
EW, THEY'’RE LEAKING
EVERYWHERE.
EW, THAT'’S SO GROSS
WHEN THEY LEAK.
- I'’M LEAKING RIGHT NOW.
- THEY JUST SPIT EVERYWHERE.
IT'’S LIKE A CAMEL.
- I'’LL SHOW YOU MINE
IF YOU SHOW ME YOURS.
- [laughs]
I COULD LITERALLY
PROBABLY SHOOT YOU
IN THE FACE RIGHT NOW.
IT'’S SQUIRTING
LIKE A WATER FAUCET.
- MINE COMES OUT LIKE TEARDROPS.
- YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE A VIRGIN?
- YEAH, A PREGNANT VIRGIN.
- [laughs]
YOU'’RE GONNA CRY THE WHOLE WAY
DOWN THE AISLE, AREN'’T YOU?
- OH, MY GOD, YES,
LIKE, UGLY KIM K FACE.
- [laughs]
I'’M SORRY I BROUGHT MY BOOBS
INTO THIS CONVERSATION.
- IT'’S OKAY.
MY BOOBS ARE LEAKING TOO.
- [laughs]
I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE A COW
BECAUSE THEY'’RE LITERALLY,
LIKE, 5 POUNDS,
AND THEY'’RE LEAKING
THROUGH MY BRA.
- JENNI, CATCH.
all: YAY!
- I CAN IMAGINE THE DAY,
ACTUALLY, BITCHES
ARE GONNA BE FIGHTING.
- THEY'’RE GONNA BE THROWING
EACH OTHER ON THE FLOOR.
ESPECIALLY MY GIRLS.
- I KNOW.
- WAITING TO GET ENGAGED
AND [bleep].
ALL RIGHT, I'’M GOING IN.
I CAN'’T REALLY BREATHE IN THIS.
I'’M SO HAPPY THAT ME AND JENNI
ARE HAVING THIS MOMENT,
BECAUSE I ALWAYS PICTURED
MYSELF TO BE WITH MY BEST FRIEND
AND SHOWING HER
MY WEDDING DRESS.
- YOU'’RE NOT MY LITTLE GIRL
FROM JERSEY ANYMORE.
- THANK GOD.
- [laughs]
I'’D BE REALLY CONCERNED
IF I STILL WAS, WITH A CHILD.
- YOU SHOULD BE
EXTREMELY PROUD OF YOURSELF.
YOU'’VE COME
A LONG...
- THANKS, BOO.
- LONG WAY.
- AND YOU WOULD NEVER SAY THAT
FOUR YEARS AGO.
- NO, AND I'’M SO PROUD
TO SAY IT NOW.
- MY NIPPLES HURT.
- I COULD'’VE SQUIRTED MY MILK
ACROSS THIS [bleep] ROOM.
- IT'’S COMING OUT, IT'’S CLEAR.
- [laughs]
- DID IT SQUIRT?
WAIT, LET ME SEE!
- NO!
- I SHOWED YOU!
STOP.
DON'’T SQUIRT ME IN THE EYE.
- THANKS FOR THE WONDERFUL DAY.
- THANK YOU FOR COMING.
WHOA!
[baby babbling]
MIGHT POKE SOMEBODY'’S EYE OUT.
- MY TURN!
- SO I GET HOME,
I'’M EXHAUSTED.
IT'’S BEEN A LONG DAY
AND I'’M SO EXCITED JUST
TO LAY DOWN AND GO TO SLEEP,
BUT JIONNI GOT LORENZO
THIS TOY HELICOPTER
THAT THEY'’RE BOTH OBSESSED WITH.
- CAN I TRY?
I WANNA TRY.
- IT'’S JUST A BOY THING.
THAT'’S WHY I CAN'’T WAIT
TO HAVE MY GIRL,
BECAUSE THEN WE CAN PLAY
WITH OUR DOLLS.
- YEAH, LORENZO!
- WHOA!
- GOOD JOB, LORENZO.
- YOU DID IT.
- [cries]
- LORENZO,
YOU CAN'’T THROW THAT.
- [cries]
- [laughs]
YOU STOP.
- [cries]
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER? YOU DID IT.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- TEMPER TANTRUMS
PROBABLY COME FROM ME.
- YEP.
- WHEN HE WHINES--
- THAT'’S ME.
WHEN HE DOES HIS GOOFY FACES,
THAT'’S ME.
- WHEN HE CRIES--
- EVERY BABY CRIES.
- WHEN HE DOESN'’T LISTEN.
WHEN HE POOPS UNDER THE TABLE.
- I DON'’T POOP UNDER THE TABLE.
SICKO.
LORENZO, YOU BROKE IT.
- NO, YOU BROKE IT.
- [cries]
- HAVE A GOOD DAY.
[kisses]
- TAKE CARE OF MY ANGEL BABY.
TODAY'’S A TOUGH DAY FOR ME.
IT'’S GONNA BE
MY FIRST DAY BACK AT WORK,
LEAVING JENNI, LEAVING MEILANI.
- I'’M EXCITED TO BE AT HOME
ALONE WITH MEILANI TODAY.
I MEAN, SHE'’S STILL
JUST A LITTLE MEATBALL.
SHE DOESN'’T REALLY DO MUCH.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO HANDLE
THIS AND TAKE THIS ON,
'’CAUSE HE DOES WORK FULL-TIME,
AND, YOU KNOW,
I WILL BE IN THIS POSITION
FOR A VERY LONG TIME IN MY LIFE.
GET IN THERE.
NOEL.
HEY, DON'’T YOU.
GET--
NOEL!
WANT TO SEE THE BABY?
YOU--
[dog whining]
[grumbles]
HAVEN'’T EVEN BEEN ABLE
TO GET DRESSED YET.
[dog barking]
HEY!
I DON'’T KNOW HOW THE HELL
I'’M GONNA DO THIS,
BUT ALL RIGHT.
[dog barking]
[buzzing]
[dog whining]
YEAH, YOU FEEL THAT?
NO.
IT'’S FOR DIESEL.
WE HAD TO PUT
A STATIC COLLAR ON HIM.
GONNA KEEP THIS ON MY WRIST
ALL DAY.
HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
[dog barking]
BELLA, I SWEAR TO GOD, BELLA.
WHY ISN'’T YOURS WORKING?
BELLA'’S BARK COLLAR
IS NOT WORKING RIGHT NOW,
AND SHE'’S SUCH A LITTLE BITCH.
SHE KNOWS IT,
AND SHE'’S LIKE
"I'’M JUST GONNA TALK [bleep]."
YOU WOKE THE BABY UP.
[dog barking]
THEY NEED TO GO FOR A WALKY.
- SO I THINK LAST NIGHT WAS
JENNI'’S FIRST NIGHT ALONE.
- REALLY?
- '’CAUSE ROGER HAS WORK.
SO SHE, LIKE, DID
THE WHOLE NIGHT SHIFT.
- I REMEMBER FOUR OR FIVE DAYS
OF GETTING,
LIKE, THREE HOURS OF SLEEP.
- MM-HMM.
- WAS THAT RIGHT?
- AND THEN I THINK
WE STARTED THE SHIFT.
- IT'’S HARD FOR HER TO DO
A SHIFT IF ROGER'’S WORKING.
- WELL, YEAH.
SHE IS THE SHIFT.
IT HAPPENS, BUT--
- SHE'’S PROBABLY SO TIRED.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
YOU'’RE A MOM.
[dog barking]
- UGH!
IT DEFINITELY WOULD BE EASIER
IF ROGER WAS THERE TO HELP ME.
I'’M EXHAUSTED ALREADY.
OOH, FANCY.
[rocker clicking]
OH, MY GOSH.
[rocker stops clicking]
JESUS [bleep].
[rocker clicking]
OH, MY GOD.
GOD, YOU'’RE USED TO NOISES.
[rocker clicking]
IF YOU DROP MY KID, I WILL KILL
THE OWNER OF FISHER-PRICE.
[phone ringing]
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HOW DID YOU SHOWER
WHEN LORENZO WAS,
LIKE, TWO WEEKS OLD?
- I DIDN'’T SHOWER.
I SMELLED, I HAD HAIRY ARMPITS,
AND I DIDN'’T EVEN
BRUSH MY TEETH.
[phone ringing]
YOU RANG?
- WHAT IF YOU HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM
AND THEY'’RE, LIKE, WIDE AWAKE?
- THEN YOU BRING HER
IN THE BATHROOM WITH YOU.
- SO LIKE, LORENZO WATCHED YOU
POOP A BUNCH OF TIMES?
- YEAH, AND HE STILL COMES
IN THE BATHROOM WITH ME,
AND HE JUST STARES AT ME.
[both laughing]
AND HE HANDS ME TOILET PAPER.
- YOU'’LL BE HANDING MOMMY
TOILET PAPER ONE DAY.
- EW.
- OKAY, THANK YOU.
I'’M A LITTLE NERVOUS, YOU KNOW,
I GUESS NEW MOM JITTERS.
- I FEEL LIKE ALL FIRST MOMS
GO THROUGH THIS.
- IT'’S LIKE A PARANOID STATE.
- YEAH, IT'’S LIKE,
YOU DON'’T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
YOU DON'’T WANT
TO LEAVE THEM FOR A SECOND
EVEN IF YOU GO TO THE BATHROOM
BECAUSE YOU'’RE SCARED
THEY'’RE NOT BREATHING.
- YEAH, I ALWAYS WAKE UP,
LIKE, FREAKING OUT.
- IT'’S NORMAL.
HELLO?
- HI.
HOW DID YOU HOLD LORENZO...
- WHOA!
- AND DO STUFF AT THE SAME TIME?
- YOU DON'’T HAVE TO HOLD HER.
JUST PUT HER IN THE ROCKER
AND GET YOUR STUFF DONE.
[phone ringing]
- HI AGAIN.
YOU OWN ME.
- CAN YOU COME OVER
SO I CAN WALK THE DOGS?
- I BELONG TO YOU.
HELLO?
I QUIT.
- CAN YOU COME OVER
SO I CAN PUMP?
- ROCKS ARE SO SHARP.
[phone ringing]
- I NEED YOUR HELP AGAIN.
- "OTAY."
TOODLES.
[dog barking]
- BELLA! SHUT UP!
[phone ringing]
- HELLO.
- CAN YOU COME OVER?
- HELLO?
[dog barking]
WHOA, DIESEL!
- HEY, I'’M UP HERE.
- UGH, I'’M OUT OF BREATH.
I'’M SO FAT.
HI, BABY.
HOW'’S YOUR VAGINA?
- MM.
STILL THERE.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- TIRED.
LORENZO WOKE UP
AT 3:00 THIS MORNING.
HE GOES, "I WANT TO GO OUTSIDE."
- DID YOU BRING HIM?
- NO.
- [laughs]
- SO HE CRIED
UNTIL 7:00 IN THE MORNING.
"OUTSIDE, OUTSIDE."
- [laughs]
- BYE.
CALL ME IF YOU NEED ME.
[phone ringing]
WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH MY LIFE?
- CAN YOU COME OVER
SO I CAN COOK?
I'’M SURE NICOLE'’S
GETTING ANNOYED
WITH ME CONSTANTLY CALLING,
BUT SHE MOVED NEXT DOOR TO ME
WHEN I HAD A NEWBORN,
SO SHE HAS TO ACCEPT THIS.
- ALL RIGHT, I'’LL BE BACK, KIDS.
DUTY CALLS.
I THINK MY FEET
ARE GETTING FATTER.
- WHAT ARE YOU MAKING?
- CHICKEN PARM.
- WHAT TIME
DOES ROGER COME HOME?
- 4:00 HE SAID.
- WELL, YOU GOT TWO HOURS.
WANT ME TO SET THE TABLE?
- OH, SURE.
- WHAT IS THIS OCCASION?
JUST--
- DADDY'’S FIRST DAY
BACK TO WORK, MISSING HIS BABY.
- ARE YOU GONNA TOUCHY, TOUCHY?
- NO.
- OH.
- I'’M NOT GONNA HAVE SEX
WITH ROGER AFTER DINNER TONIGHT.
I'’M ONLY TWO WEEKS POST BABY,
AND MY STITCHES ARE STILL
DOWN THERE, AND IT'’S VERY RAW.
IT'’S BEEN TEN DAYS.
- YOU COULD STILL DO SOMETHING.
- OH, '’CAUSE I DIDN'’T
GIVE BIRTH?
HOW ABOUT HIM DO SOMETHING?
I'’M COOKING.
- IF HE [bleep] YOUR NIPPLES,
MILK'’S GONNA COME OUT.
- EW.
THAT'’S EXACTLY WHY
WE SHOULD NOT BE DOING
ANY TOUCHY, TOUCHY.
WELL, I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT DOING SOMETHING
BECAUSE I FEEL TERRIBLE
I MISSED YOUR BRIDAL SHOWER,
SO I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
WITH YOU.
- LIKE WHAT?
- I DON'’T KNOW,
SOMETHING SMALL, INTIMATE,
LIKE A LUNCH.
ME AND YOU, MAYBE THE JOEYS.
- YEAH.
- I WANT TO THROW NICOLE
A BRIDAL LUNCHEON
THAT'’S REALLY CLOSE TO MY HOUSE
BECAUSE I COULDN'’T MAKE
HER BRIDAL SHOWER,
AND I FELT BAD,
AND TO BE HONEST,
I WANT TO DO
SOMETHING NICE FOR HER.
- MMM.
GOOD JOB.
- WE NEED, LIKE, SOMETHING
FANCY, LIKE TEA AND CRUMPETS.
I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
WHAT A CRUMPET IS.
- ISN'’T IT LIKE A CUPCAKE?
A FANCY CUPCAKE?
- I WANT TO MAKE IT
A CLASSY AFFAIR
BECAUSE NICOLE'’S WEDDING
IS GONNA BE CLASSY.
VERY 1920s GATSBY,
YOU KNOW, PINKY UP.
OKAY, I GOT A BED AND BREAKFAST
AND VICTORIAN TEA ROOM.
"DRESS LIKE ROYALTY
AND UPPER CLASS."
YOU KNOW WHAT I'’M TALKING ABOUT?
- AND ACTUALLY WEAR
VICTORIAN [bleep]?
- YEAH, REMEMBER,
WE DID THAT FOR HALLOWEEN
LAST YEAR?
- SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- YEAH.
- LET'’S GO.
- THEY DO DO ETIQUETTE CLASSES.
- THE JOEYS NEED
ETIQUETTE CLASS.
- YOU DON'’T THINK WE DO?
- YEAH, WE DO.
- "HERE ARE A FEW TEA
PARTY ETIQUETTE TIPS.
"AFTER SITTING DOWN,
PUT PURSE ON LAP,
OR BEHIND YOU
AGAINST THE BACK OF THE CHAIR."
- NO, I JUST PUT IT
ON THE TABLE.
- "UNFOLD NAPKIN AND MAKE SURE
TO PLACE IT ON YOUR LAP."
- OH, I KNOW HOW.
- YOU DO?
- I SAW IT ON TITANIC.
- [laughs]
- WATCH.
- THREE?
- NO ELBOWS ON TABLES.
I KNOW THAT ONE.
- "PLEASE EXCUSE YOURSELF
FROM THE TABLE
AND GO TO THE LADIES'’ ROOM."
I ACTUALLY DON'’T KNOW
WHO HAS BETTER ETIQUETTE
BETWEEN ME AND NICOLE.
I THINK SHE EATS BETTER,
BUT SHE ALSO BURPS, SWEARS,
AND ALWAYS SAYS SHE
HAS TO DROP A POOP
IN THE MIDDLE OF HER
CONVERSATIONS AT DINNER,
WHERE I DON'’T DO THAT.
- I GOT TO [bleep].
I'’LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- THIS IS WHY WE NEED
PROPER ETIQUETTE.
[both laughing]
- WE SHOULD GO IN CHARACTERS.
LIKE, AS WE'’RE IN COSTUME,
WE HAVE,
LIKE, THE BRITISH ACCENT
AND WE HAVE A WEIRD NAME.
- I WANT TO BE CINDERELLA.
- SERIOUSLY?
WHAT ARE YOU, FIVE?
I WANT TO BE LATOYA.
- OH.
- NO, WAIT, THAT'’S NOT--
[both laughing]
- I'’LL BE ESTHER
IF YOU BE SOMETHING.
- ESTHER, I'’LL BE BERTHA, '’CAUSE
I HAVE TO GIVE BIRTH SOON.
- ESTHER AND BERTHA.
- LET ME CALL THE TEA ROOM.
- I DARE YOU TO SWEAR.
SAY WE HAVE HORRIBLE
[bleep] MANNERS.
- IT HAS TO BE NATURAL.
[phone ringing]
- OKAY, YOU SAY THE "F" WORD
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- I KNOW, BUT DON'’T ASK ME
TO SAY IT,
THEN I GET ALL FREAKED.
- AFTERNOON, 600 MAIN.
- HI, MY NAME IS ESTHER,
AND I WAS WONDERING
ABOUT PROPER ETIQUETTE CLASSES
AND VISITING YOUR TEA ROOM.
- OKAY, AND SORRY.
YOUR NAME IS ESTHER?
- YES, MA'’AM.
- SAY IT.
SAY "I'’M [bleep] EXCITED.
THANK YOU."
- DO YOU HAVE A LAST NAME,
ESTHER?
- OH.
- "M"--[laughs]
- I'’M SORRY, WHAT IS IT?
- "M"--
[both laughing]
I'’M SORRY, I JUST GOT
REALLY EXCITED.
[both laughing]
SORRY--
MY GIRLFRIEND--
- EXCUSE ME?
- I'’M SORRY, I'’M SORRY.
- M-C-F-A-R-L-E-Y.
- M-C-F-A-R-L-E-Y?
[both laughing]
- YES.
- [laughing] ESTHER MCFARLEY.
- OKAY.
AND IT'’S FOR ETIQUETTE--
- [laughs]
- FOR SOME ETIQUETTE CLASSES
ON MONDAY THE 28TH,
AT 11:00 A.M.
- YEP.
- AND IT'’LL BE THREE WOMEN
AND TWO MEN, OKAY.
- TWO WOMEN.
- YEAH, THAT MAKES SENSE.
- THAT'’S FINE.
- WE'’RE ALL WOMEN.
- OKAY.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- THANK YOU FOR CALLING.
- OKAY, BYE NOW.
- BYE-BYE.
- THAT WAS GOOD.
I ALMOST PEED IN MY PANTS.
- [laughs]
- OKAY, BYE.
- CALL YOU LATER.
- THANK YOU AGAIN.
- MM-HMM.
OW.
SQUIRREL?
[screams]
JIONNI!
EW!
EW! EW!
[shudders]
WALKING INTO THE KITCHEN,
I SEE THIS HUGE SPIDER.
JIONNI ALREADY KNOWS
I HATE SPIDERS.
I WANT NOTHING TO DO WITH THEM,
AND I DON'’T KNOW WHY
YOU SAVED THIS CREATURE.
JUST KILL IT AND GET IT
OUT OF MY KITCHEN.
EW! EW!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'’S GONNA CRAWL IN YOUR HAIR.
UGH.
I'’M ITCHY NOW.
EW!
- I'’M GONNA LET IT GO.
- OH, BABY, STOP.
STOP, DON'’T DO IT.
STOP.
GET IT AWAY.
I'’M NOT KIDDING.
JIONNI!
JIONNI, PLEASE!
- YEE!
- [screams]
- [laughs]
- STOP.
- I'’M GONNA LET IT GO.
- NO, KILL IT.
SQUISH IT.
JIONNI, IT'’S JUST GONNA
COME BACK IN.
IT'’S GONNA BRING
ALL OF HIS FRIENDS.
- YOU'’RE VERY--IT'’S NOT--
THAT'’S NOT HUMANE.
- JIONNI, PLEASE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
HE'’S MOTHER THERESA.
I'’D RATHER JIONNI
JUST KILL THE SPIDER
SO I NEVER HAVE TO
SEE IT AGAIN.
I CAN'’T BELIEVE
A SPIDER THAT BIG EXISTS.
- HELLO, PUPPY DOGS.
BABE?
- HI, BABE.
I'’M IN THE DINING ROOM.
- AH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHERE'’S MY LITTLE ANGEL?
OH, WHAT'’D YOU DO,
MAKE DINNER?
- YEAH.
- NO WAY.
MY FAVORITE.
- YEP.
- AWESOME.
HOW'’S MY ANGEL BABY?
- SHE'’S SLEEPING.
- SLEEPING.
WHAT'’D YOU DO THAT FOR?
THAT'’S AWESOME.
- IT'’S YOUR FIRST DAY
BACK TO WORK.
- THANK YOU,
AND YOU CAN HAVE WINE NOW?
- YEAH.
- AWESOME.
I MIGHT ACTUALLY
GET SOME TONIGHT.
- YOU CAN'’T HAVE ANYTHING,
BESIDES WINE.
THAT'’S AS MUCH AS YOU GET.
ROGER IS SUPER SURPRISED
BY DINNER,
AND THAT MAKES ME HAPPY,
'’CAUSE HE'’S SO HAPPY
THAT I DID THIS FOR HIM.
- THIS IS AWESOME.
WE'’RE, LIKE, DOMESTICATED NOW
OR SOMETHING.
- OH, MY GOD.
- NO, THAT WENT RIGHT
PERFECTLY BETWEEN YOUR BOOBS.
- OH, MY GOD.
- YOU WEAR MORE OF YOUR FOOD
THAN YOU EVER EAT
EVERY TIME WE GO TO DINNER.
- I ALWAYS DROP FOOD
IN MY CLEAVAGE.
THIS IS WHY I HAVE TO GO
TO A PROPER ETIQUETTE CLASS.
I DON'’T EVEN KNOW
HOW THAT HAPPENED.
IT FELL OFF MY FORK.
- MAYBE IF I GET HUNGRY LATER,
I'’LL MAKE LOVE TO YOU.
YOU HAVE A BIG CHUNK
UP ON THE TOPSIDE TOO.
- [laughs]
- HOW DO YOU DO THAT
EVERY TIME, HONESTLY?
- [laughs]
- HONESTLY.
MM-HMM.
- HELLO.
- I'’D BE AFRAID
IF I UNDRESSED YOU,
I'’D FIND HALF A CHICKEN PARM
DOWN YOUR SHIRT.
- [laughs]
both: ONE, TWO, THREE, WHEE!
- WE SCREAM, YOU SCREAM,
WE ALL SCREAM FOR ICE CREAM.
- TONIGHT WE'’RE GONNA BRING
LORENZO TO GET SOME ICE CREAM.
HE LOVES ICE CREAM,
AND IT'’S GONNA BE
A LITTLE FAMILY NIGHT OUT.
- WE'’RE HERE.
YAY, ICE CREAM.
- HERE YOU GO.
- OH, MY GOSH.
- I'’M GONNA PIG OUT.
I'’VE DECIDED.
THIS IS PRETTY BIG
FOR A SMALL.
- GOOD JOB, LORENZO.
- YUMMY.
- THANKS, DADA.
TONIGHT'’S JUST AWESOME.
IT'’S, LIKE, LITERALLY
YOUR TYPICAL
DOWN THE SHORE FAMILY NIGHT.
WHOA.
- WHAT?
- LOOK AT THAT GUY.
- HO!
- HOLY--
- JIONNI, WHAT--
IS THAT A BEETLE?
- YEAH.
- IT'’S FRICKING GROSS.
- ROGER MUST BE
FEEDING IT STEROIDS.
- [laughs]
WE GET HOME, AND THERE IS
A HUMAN/COCKROACH INSECT
ON OUR FRONT PORCH.
- DINOSAUR.
EW, EW, THERE'’S SPIDERS--
[gasps]
DID YOU JUST SQUISH IT?
JIONNI, NOW YOU HAVE TO KILL IT.
IT'’S SUFFERING.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT,
BUT YOU WOULDN'’T KILL A SPIDER?
[crunching]
both: OH!
- GO.
- DO YOU FEEL GUILTY?
YOU SHOULD, '’CAUSE
YOU JUST KILLED A HUMAN BEING.
- THIS HOUSE GIVES ME
THE CREEPS.
- THIS IS DISGUSTING.
- WHOA!
- EW.
- YO, I'’M KIND OF NERVOUS
TO SLEEP NOW.
OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT?
- THERE'’S ANTS
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
UGH!
- EW, LOOK AT THEM ALL.
- THERE'’S AN ANT FARM
LIVING IN OUR KITCHEN.
IT'’S JUST--
- THERE HAS TO BE, LIKE, 50 ANTS
ON THE FLOOR IN THE KITCHEN.
STOP, STOP!
I HATE THIS HOUSE.
STOP.
THIS HOUSE IS NOT LIVABLE.
WHY DON'’T YOU STAY IN HERE
AWAY FROM THE BUGS?
ME AND DADDY ARE GONNA
CLEAN THEM, ALL RIGHT?
OH, I'’M SO ITCHY.
I HATE THIS PLACE.
YOU'’RE MISSING THEM.
YOU'’RE JUST PARANOID.
THERE'’S NOTHING ON YOU.
- THERE WAS SOMETHING
ON MY BACK.
- IT'’S PROBABLY A FLY.
- DADDY!
- OKAY.
- YOU'’RE MAKING ME ITCH.
- SORRY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
NOT ITCH MY ITCHINESS?
- [screams]
I'’M SHOWERING
BEFORE I GO TO BED,
BECAUSE IF WE DON'’T,
I FEEL LIKE
WE'’RE GONNA BRING THE ANTS
INTO OUR BED.
CRACK KILLS!
[laughs]
OOH!
[blubbering]
- WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU WOKE UP WITH A COCKROACH
LITERALLY NEXT TO YOUR HEAD?
- I'’D LEAVE.
I WOULDN'’T COME BACK HERE.
SEE?
WE'’RE JUMPY.
- WELL, YOUR CRACK'’S
OUT ALL THE TIME.
- MY CRACK'’S NEVER OUT.
YOU GOT A NICE CRACK.
- YOU HAVE A HAIRY CRACK.
- YOU HAVE A HAIRY CRACK!
- YOUR MOM'’S GOT A HAIRY CRACK.
- JIONNI!
[doorbell ringing]
- JANICE AND JOE
ARE COMING DOWN FOR THE WEEKEND,
AND I'’M REALLY EXCITED
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I'’M USED TO SEEING JANICE
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
I HAVEN'’T SEEN HER.
both: HELLO!
- [whispering]
LORENZO'’S SLEEPING.
- OH.
- OH!
HI.
- THIS IS NICE.
- HELLO.
- TOLD YOU.
- THIS IS NICE HERE.
- JANIS AND JOE GET HERE,
AND OF COURSE THEY HAVE
TONS OF FOOD TO MAKE.
WHAT'’S THIS?
WHAT THE [bleep] IS THAT?
STOP.
- THIS IS WHAT YOU'’RE
GONNA MAKE.
- STOP, NO, I'’M NOT MA--I'’M NOT.
- COME HERE. COME HERE.
LOOK, YOU HAVE TO,
IT'’S JIONNI'’S FAVORITE.
- OH, NO.
- COME ON.
- I DON'’T DO THAT.
- WHY?
- I'’M NOT COOKING THAT,
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
- [chewing]
- FIRST OF ALL, THEY'’RE ALIVE
WHEN YOU'’RE BOILING THEM,
WHICH IS SO INHUMANE,
AND THEY LOOK LIKE SPIDERS.
- THEY'’RE NOT SPIDERS.
- NO, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
- [humming]
YOU'’LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- YOU'’RE A MURDERER.
- JIONNI, LOOK WHAT I GOT YOU,
HONEY.
both: LOBSTERS.
- OOH.
- I--SHE WON'’T MAKE THEM.
- [laughs]
- OH, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I WOULD NEVER KILL A LOBSTER.
THAT'’S LIKE KILLING A CAT
OR A DOG.
NOT DOING THAT.
COME ON, PUP.
OUTSIDE?
COME ON.
SHOW ME YOUR JUMPY JUMP.
THERE IT IS.
LET'’S SEE.
- OKAY, HEY, WELL
HOW ABOUT HELPING ME
WITH THE FAMILY RECIPE?
- WHAT IS THAT?
- SAUSAGE.
- [chuckles]
- DON'’T START FREAKING OUT
ON THINGS, COME ON.
- [laughs]
I WOULD LOVE TO LEARN
HOW TO COOK LIKE JANIS,
JUST SO, YOU KNOW,
I COULD DO THAT FOR JIONNI,
BUT ALSO IT'’S A NICE, YOU
KNOW, BONDING EXPERIENCE
FOR ME AND JANIS.
- OKAY, CHOP MEAT.
VEAL, PORK, BEEF,
THREE DIFFERENT KINDS.
- OH, WOW.
I WANT TO COOK THINGS
THAT JIONNI LOVES
SO I KNOW THAT HE'’LL EAT IT
AND HE WON'’T THROW UP.
NOT THE STEMS, RIGHT?
- NO STEMS.
HERE, CHOP, CHOP.
- THIS BIG GUY?
- YES.
- WHAT IS THIS AGAIN?
- PARSLEY.
- CAN YOU JUST GET IT
ALREADY MADE?
- KEEP CHOPPING.
- IS THAT GOOD?
- THAT'’S PRETTY GOOD.
PUT YOUR HANDS IN IT.
- EW!
THIS IS A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
RECIPE THAN MY GRANDMA'’S.
- HOW DOES YOUR GRANDMA MAKE IT?
- SHE LIKES A LITTLE BREAD CRUMB
TO MAKE IT DRY.
- NO.
- I GUESS EVERYBODY MAKES
THEIR [bleep] DIFFERENT.
I FEEL LIKE ALL ITALIANS
MAKE MEATBALLS A DIFFERENT WAY.
- GOOD.
DOING GOOD.
- SO WHEN DID YOU START COOKING?
- OH, GOSH.
I COOKED EARLY.
MY GRANDMOTHER USED TO COME OVER
ALL THE TIME
AND COOK WITH MY MOM.
THEY USED TO, LIKE, MAKE
HOMEMADE MACARONIS AND STUFF.
- HOME--LIKE,
MAKE THE DOUGH?
- YEAH.
- WOW.
NOW THAT I'’M PRACTICING
AND I'’M LEARNING HOW TO COOK,
IT'’S ACTUALLY FUN, BECAUSE
I KNOW THAT I CAN PROVIDE
AN EDIBLE MEAL
FOR MY MAN AND MY SON.
IS THAT IT?
THAT WAS EASY.
- OKAY, LET'’S HEAR YOU
REPEAT IT.
- OH.
[laughs]
SO JANIS IS TESTING ME
ON WHAT WE PUT IN THE SAUCE,
BUT I MEAN, YOU CAN'’T ASK ME
WHEN I'’M PREGNANT,
'’CAUSE I HAVE PREGNANCY BRAIN.
- YOU STARTED OUT WITH?
- OIL.
UM, COW MEAT?
EVEN IF I WASN'’T PREGNANT,
I PROBABLY WOULD'’VE FORGOT.
I THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
- MM-HMM.
THEN MAYBE WE'’LL MAKE
LASAGNA TOO?
- YES!
I DON'’T KNOW HOW TO MAKE
LASAGNA, SO--
IS LASAGNA FATTENING?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- ARE YOU SURE?
EVERY TIME I EAT IT,
I FEEL LIKE A WHALE.
- OF COURSE IT IS.
- OH.
YOU GOT POT CHEESE?
- MM-HMM,
SEE, YOU KNOW.
- POT CHEESE IS RICOTTA.
I CALL IT "RICOTTA,"
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
PEOPLE IN JERSEY
CALL IT "POT CHEESE."
HOW MUCH?
- OH, THAT'’S GOOD.
- WAS THAT TOO MUCH?
- NO, THAT WAS OKAY.
THAT WAS OKAY.
- I COULD SCOOP IT OUT.
- NO, IT'’S ALL RIGHT.
- IT COMES OUT QUICK.
- KEEP GOING.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW?
- WELL, '’CAUSE THE SALT'’S
NOT EVEN COMING OUT.
- IT IS.
- KEEP GOING.
- OH, MY GOD.
- [laughs]
I'’M TELLING YOU, KEEP GOING.
OKAY, GOOD.
YOU'’RE GOOD.
- IF I DID THAT MYSELF,
I WOULDN'’T KNOW HOW MUCH.
- OH, YOU WANT AN EXACT NUMBER?
- YEAH.
- YOU'’RE NOT GONNA GET THAT
FROM ME.
- CAN WE TELL JIONNI I MADE IT
AND YOU JUST TOLD ME WHAT TO DO?
- UH-HUH, THE WHOLE THING.
- HE'’LL BE SO PROUD.
- MM-HMM.
OKAY, YOU CAN PUT
A LAYER OF GRAVY DOWN.
OVERLAP THEM A LITTLE BIT.
- CHEESE.
- CHEESE, YUMMY, YUMMY.
- IT'’S HEAVY.
THIS IS SO EASY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE
SO MUCH HARDER,
BUT DUDE, MAKING LASAGNA
IS A PIECE OF CAKE.
- THAT'’S PICTURE PERFECT.
- MORE!
- WHAT?
- LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
- MORE? OKAY.
- MY FIRST LASAGNA.
I PUT IT IN THE FRIDGE?
WE MIGHT NOT HAVE ROOM.
- WE DON'’T HAVE ANY ROOM.
- WELL, I MEAN,
WE CAN USE JENNI'’S FRIDGE.
- ARE THEY UP?
- SHE IS MY NEIGHBOR.
SHE'’S PROBABLY SLEEPING.
WE COULD JUST SNEAK IN THERE
REAL QUICK.
JUST HAVE TO BE QUIET
'’CAUSE WE CAN'’T WAKE THE BABY.
- OH.
CAREFUL, DON'’T FALL.
- I WON'’T FALL.
- YOU GOT LASAGNA, DON'’T FALL.
- OOH, IT'’S DARK OUT.
OH, A LIGHTNING BUG.
WE'’RE BREAKING AND ENTERING.
[laughs]
[whispering]
ALL RIGHT, JUST OPEN IT.
OH YEAH,
HOW DO--ALL HER LIGHTS TURN OFF?
MINE ARE ON ALL NIGHT.
[dog barking]
LET'’S PUT IT [bleep]
AND GET THE [bleep] OUT.
HURRY, HURRY.
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD.
- YOU DIDN'’T TELL ME
SHE HAD A DOG.
- SHE HAS THREE DOGS.
- THREE DOGS.
[dog barking loudly]
ARE YOU KIDDING?
[both laughing]
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- OH, I FORGOT ABOUT THE DOGS.
- GET THE DOOR, OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY--
THAT DIDN'’T WAKE '’EM UP.
[baby crying]
- THIS EPISODE
OF SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- CONTINUES NOW.
- SO I GOT UP EARLY THIS MORNING
TO MAKE BREAKFAST FOR JENNI,
WHO'’S STILL IN BED,
AND, YOU KNOW,
IT'’S JUST I WANT
TO MAKE TODAY SPECIAL.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
- YOU TOO.
- HOW'’S MY ANGEL BABY?
- YOU SMELL GOOD, LIKE FOOD.
- I'’M MAKING BREAKFAST FOR YOU.
GIRLS HAVE SO MANY DIFFERENT
ANNIVERSARIES.
IT'’S OUR...
- THIS IS OUR FIRST DATE
FULL YEAR.
- FOUR YEAR ANNIVERSARY
OF OUR FIRST DATE.
- YES, IT'’S THAT--
- NOT THE DATE
WE GOT ENGAGED, NOT--
- NO, THAT WILL BE
TWO YEARS...
both: IN SEPTEMBER.
- I WAS ACTUALLY JUST GONNA
FIX MY FACE.
I'’LL FIX IT IN THERE
AND I'’LL MEET YOU DOWNSTAIRS?
- WE'’VE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR FOUR YEARS, BABE.
I KNOW WHAT YOUR FACE LOOKS
LIKE WHEN MAKEUP'’S NOT ON IT.
OH, SHE JUST SPIT UP.
SHE'’S SPITTING UP A LOT.
- THERE YOU GO.
- SHE'’S SPITTING UP A LOT.
- IT'’S ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
[baby vomiting]
- OH, MY GOD, BABE.
- JUST KEEP HER--
[baby coughs]
- BABE, SHE IS--
- ALL RIGHT, CALM DOWN.
ROGER'’S FREAKING OUT
A LITTLE BIT
BECAUSE MEILANI'’S SPITTING UP,
BUT I'’M TRYING TO TELL HIM,
JUST CALM DOWN,
YOU DON'’T WANT TO MAKE HER UPSET
BY YOU BEING UPSET.
- YOU DIDN'’T BURP HER.
- SHE CAN STILL BREATHE.
SHE CAN STILL BREATHE.
- AM I FREAKING OUT?
I REALIZE THAT SHE CAN BREATHE.
I GET IT,
BUT SHE'’S SPITTING UP A LOT.
- SHE JUST DRANK THIS.
- THAT WAS, LIKE, THE ENTIRE
BOTTLE SHE JUST SPIT UP.
THE CALMEST ONE WHEN THIS
HAPPENS IS ACTUALLY MEILANI.
IT DOESN'’T SEEM
TO AFFECT HER OR BOTHER HER,
BUT AS A PARENT,
TO WATCH IT, IT'’S SCARY.
THAT WAS SO MUCH SPIT UP, GIRL.
- WELL, SHE'’LL DEFINITELY WANT
HER "BABA" IN A MINUTE, THEN.
- YEAH, MOMMY ALWAYS WANTS
ANOTHER DRINK
WHEN SHE THROWS UP EVERYWHERE...
- SURE DO.
- SHE'’S READY TO GO.
SO WHILE JENNI WAS
IN THE BATHROOM DOING HER MAKEUP
OR WHATEVER IT IS
SHE DOES IN THERE,
YOU KNOW, I'’M GONNA BRING
MEILANI DOWNSTAIRS
AND GIVE HER ANOTHER BOTTLE.
SCARED YOUR DADDY.
PROBABLY READY
FOR ANOTHER BOTTLE IN A MINUTE.
YOU THINK MOMMY AND DADDY
COULD EAT REAL QUICK?
[singing] HI, BABY.
HI, BABY.
OH, I NEVER KNOW WHAT TAKES
YOUR MOTHER SO LONG TO DO STUFF.
SHE'’S GOT TO DO HER MAKEUP
BEFORE SHE CAN COME
HAVE BREAKFAST WITH YOUR DADDY,
SO BREAKFAST IS GETTING COLD.
TRY TO BE ROMANTIC.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'’RE EATING
A COLD BREAKFAST.
DADDY LOVES YOU.
SO AT THIS POINT, HONESTLY,
I'’M JUST OVER BREAKFAST.
[sighs]
I'’M TOO ANNOYED.
I DON'’T EVEN WANT TO EAT,
AND, YOU KNOW, FEELING
DISRESPECTED BY MY FIANCEE.
- OH, YOU MADE A NEW ONE?
- MM-HMM.
- I HAVE THIS ONE TOO.
[laughs]
WHAT?
- I THOUGHT WE COULD HAVE
BREAKFAST FOR OUR ANNIVERSARY
AND IT'’S ALWAYS SOMETHING.
[dog barking]
- ALL RIGHT.
I'’M HERE.
WE HAVE TO STILL FINISH
FEEDING HER.
- I'’M ANNOYED THAT
IT TAKES YOU A HALF AN HOUR
TO DO YOUR MAKEUP
JUST TO COME AND HAVE BREAKFAST.
- WELL, IT SMELLS GOOD.
- WELL, GO EAT.
- NO, I'’M GONNA WAIT FOR YOU.
I DON'’T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'’RE UPSET.
I THOUGHT I ONLY TOOK, LIKE,
SIX OR SEVEN MINUTES UP THERE.
[dog barking]
NOEL, STOP!
- IF YOU DON'’T GET IT...
- HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA TAKE...
- YOU'’RE NOT GONNA GET IT.
- TO GET OVER IT?
- I'’M OVER IT,
BUT WHAT I'’M SAYING IS,
I TRY TO DO SOMETHING
YOU SAY I NEVER DO.
I'’M NEVER ROMANTIC
AND I NEVER DO THIS.
- WAS IT ACTUALLY YOUR IDEA,
THOUGH?
- IT ABSOLUTELY WAS MY IDEA.
- I'’M JUST ASKING.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'’M NOT THAT KNIGHT
IN SHINING ARMOR, UNFORTUNATELY.
I THINK I'’M A GOOD MAN,
BUT THE ONE THING I'’M NOT,
AND JENNI IS RIGHT,
IS I'’M NOT MR. ROMANCE,
AND I NEED TO WORK ON THAT,
AND I THINK, YOU KNOW,
TODAY I MADE AN EFFORT
AT DOING THAT AND IT KIND OF--
THE DOOR GOT SLAMMED IN MY FACE.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU'’RE GONNA TELL SOMEBODY
THAT THEY NEVER DO THOSE THINGS
FOR YOU EVER,
AND THEN YOU SEE SOMEONE
MAKING AN HONEST EFFORT
AND YOU COULD CARE LESS,
YOU KNOW, WOULDN'’T YOU
TAKE THAT PERSONALLY?
I DO.
I'’VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU, JENNI.
- NO, I'’M JUST MAKING SURE.
- WELL, IT WAS.
SO NOW YOU KNOW, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- I'’M NOT ARGUING
IN FRONT OF HER.
- NO, DON'’T.
- THAT'’S WHAT YOU WANTED.
- NO, NO.
- YOU WANTED TO SAY
THAT IT WASN'’T MY IDEA.
- I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE.
- NO, YEAH,
WELL, NOW YOU KNOW.
- NO.
- NOW YOU KNOW.
- OH, GOOD LORD.
NOT ARGUING.
- YOU JUST DID, ACTUALLY.
THAT WAS ALL YOU.
- WELL, I'’M SORRY.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
CERTAIN THINGS.
OH.
I DON'’T LIKE HOW ROGER WENT UP
THE STAIRS AND SLAMMED THE DOOR
BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH I MADE
A SMARTASS COMMENT AND QUESTION,
HE SHOULDN'’T HANDLE THINGS
LIKE THIS.
I APOLOGIZE FOR THAT COMMENT.
- I JUST--I NEED TEN MINUTES.
- I APOLOGIZE FOR THAT COMMENT.
- NOT IN FRONT OF HER.
I NEED TEN MINUTES.
- THAT'’S FINE.
- OKAY, YOU STAY WITH HER, THEN.
- BUT I APOLOGIZE
FOR THAT COMMENT.
UGH.
- UGH.
YOUR DADDY IS ACTUALLY CRAZY.
I DON'’T EVEN UNDERSTAND
WHAT THE HELL
HE'’S SO UPSET ABOUT.
[engine starting]
HE PROBABLY TOOK OFF TO MEXICO.
JUST ME AND YOU, NOW.
- NEXT TIME ON
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- MORE THAN ANYBODY ELSE
ON THIS PLANET,
JENNI KNOWS HOW
TO PUSH MY BUTTONS.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- HE LEFT '’CAUSE HE WAS UPSET.
I THINK HE'’S JUST
LOST HIS DAMN MIND.
TEA ROOM, DARLING.
- [burps]
- THAT'’S PROBABLY
NOT GONNA SWING HERE.
- TELL THE WHOLE TABLE
WHAT IT SMELLS LIKE.
- [bleep].
[laughter]