[Jenni]
Previously on...
[Nicole]
Snooki &amp; JWOWW.
You'’re pregnant
with Satan.
with a stripper.
[Nicole]
She'’s a monster.
[Jenni]
Can we take a picture?
- That'’s like us.
- I know.
[MC]
Is there a bachelorette
in this room somewhere?
We'’re getting married
in three weeks.
- Less than three weeks now.
- Do you regret it?
Like, do you still
want to marry me, or...
[laughs]
What?
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
♪ I don'’t care ♪
♪ I love it
♪ I love it,
I love it ♪
♪I don'’t care ♪
♪ I love it
♪
♪ I don'’t care ♪
[Nicole]
So you know,
since we did the menu tasting
with Jenni and Roger,
we still didn'’t
get our menu done.
I can'’t believe we'’re getting
married in two weeks.
It is almost here.
Finally.
Let'’s just go there
and get this done.
[Nicole]
I'’m ready when you are.
- Hey, what'’s up?
- Knock, knock.
- How we doing?
- How are you?
Welcome.
Good to see you guys.
How'’s everything?
[Jionni]
We'’re going to the Venetian.
We'’re gonna sit down with Carl
and just finalize
our menu,
'’cause it'’s one
of the last things
that we got to get done
before we got to get married.
[Carl]
So we'’re gonna go over
all the stations,
personalize some
of the stations
in that Gatsbystyle
themed items for you.
The cold displays
with different salads,
the bruschetta, garlic breads,
all assorted cheeses.
Israeli couscous?
- Israeli couscous, salad.
- What the hell is that?
It'’s a--
[laughs]
We'’re looking at this list.
- It just keeps going and going.
- A lot.
And I kind of thought
were gonna pick.
He'’s just like, "No, this
is what you'’re getting."
We'’re gonna do
homemade pizzas
with all different
toppings,
mini burger sliders,
luganica sausage,
broccoli rabe, lobster risotto,
zuppa di clams,
mozzarella en carrozza,
orecchiette,
broccoli rabe and sausage,
pasta station,
crepe station--
Wait, what'’s a crepe?
The crepe is the crepe shell.
The gnocchi Bolognese
and shitake mushrooms,
fusilli filetto di pomodoro,
that'’s nice spiral pasta,
chunky tomato sauce.
What is that?
There'’s a lot
of [bleep] on this menu
that I have no idea what it is,
like, all this Italian names.
I don'’t know what these mean.
[Nicole voice-over]
Basically I know
it'’s either pasta or sauce
or something like that.
It'’s got to be
good with some cheese.
Suckling pig?
- The whole roasted pig.
- Oh, my God.
It'’s gonna have the hat
and sunglasses and everything,
so you might not like it.
Are you kidding?
You put a hat and
sunglasses on the pig?
We got to make it look good.
[Nicole]
My God.
What'’s our to-do list?
We need to do invitations.
Hi, Mommy.
What are you doing?
I'’m doing everything
for the baptism.
Oh, yeah?
So I would like
to have a baptism for Meilani.
Roger would like
her to be baptized Episcopalian.
We need invitations,
a guest list.
We need to book the church.
We need decorations.
A baptism is basically
where you--
I don'’t know the word--
baptized the religion.
You get a little holy water
on your head,
the church does some [bleep],
you have a celebration,
and, you know,
you'’re going to heaven.
So I wanted, like,
a huge candy bar display.
I want a huge princess theme.
Do you think you'’re
going a little over the top
with what maybe could be
a private kind of ceremony
for family and friends?
Well, yeah.
I want it private
and, like, 50 people.
No.
I want, like, everyone there.
Even Jesus.
[Roger]
Should we call ahead
and have them order
a bigger baptism altar for her,
to dip her in?
Stop.
We would need
an Olympic-sized swimming pools.
[laughs]
[doorbell rings]
Is that the doorbell?
Mm-hmm.
Hello.
Hi, Squirrel.
- Love you.
- Oh, you smell good.
- Thanks. I showered.
So I need you to help me.
What'’s going on?
I'’m trying to work
on my seating chart
for the wedding,
and I don'’t know where to start.
Do you put Sam and Ron
at the same table?
No.
You have to put them
at opposite sides.
I texted them and like,
"If you fight at my wedding,
I'’ll kill both of you."
- What'’d they say?
- It'’s my day.
Ron goes, "No,
we'’re not like that anymore."
Yeah, okay.
Like, who would you
want to sit with?
The Joeys.
At the gay table?
Maybe put Sam
at that table with me.
What about Deena?
No.
- Okay.
- My Joey doesn'’t have a date.
I don'’t want him
to bring just a random.
I mean, I'’ll help you.
I don'’t know how we should
go about that, though.
What do you think
about speed dating?
I'’ve always wanted
to do that.
I think it'’s a good idea.
We need to find
him a date.
Somebody that we approve of,
for the wedding.
I feel like
that'’s Elton John.
RuPaul.
Eh.
Ricky Martin.
Where are we gonna
find these guys?
Grindr.
- What is that?
- It'’s a gay app.
Like eHarmony?
It'’s eHarmony for
[bleep] sex only, really.
Oh. That'’s nice.
Putting an ad
online is creepy.
It'’s a little weird,
'’cause you never know
who'’s gonna show up.
- But I mean--
- Hopefully no murderers.
- We'’re hoping for the best.
- Yeah.
Bear seeking bear.
[Jenni]
18 to 65, must have job.
18 to 80.
Must be a bottom.
Must be a blue-collar bottom.
I think that'’s good.
- Hey.
- We brought a gift.
Roger thinks he'’s going
to Doctor Rezai'’s with me
to help with Meilani
while I get my exam,
but that'’s not the case.
I'’m taking him so he
can feel childbirth.
- Hey.
- I could not not bring her.
- I knew you guys--
- Oh, oh, she'’s beautiful.
I'’m chopped liver
at this point.
You are not
chopped liver.
- It'’s all about her.
- Well, Jen, when you'’re ready.
I think my vagina'’s okay.
Oh, I hope so.
So, I was actually
wondering if you guys
still own that
labor simulator?
Ooh, yeah.
- You do?
- Oh, yeah.
I would like Roger
to feel the contractions.
- Oh, I love it.
- Yeah.
So I know Doctor Rezai
has this machine
at his office that is basically
a labor simulator,
and I'’m dying to get
Roger to try it
because even though he is
a sympathetic father and fiancé,
he was very, you know,
kind and gentle during my labor,
I still want him
to [bleep] feel it.
We have a little
surprise for you.
For me?
- Yeah, just for you.
- Okay.
[Jenni]
It'’s a new vagina
you'’re getting.
Do you have one of those
fake ones that you show?
- '’Cause I'’ll take that home.
- I do have one. I'’ll show you.
Works better
than the one I got.
I kind of want
to see Roger in pain.
Is that mean?
I don'’t think it'’s mean.
I want to see him in pain.
I want to see him wince.
- Since Jenni had such a...
- Wonderful.
Wonderful, quick labor,
we wanted to see if you
wanted to experience that.
- Labor?
- Yeah.
How do you simulate labor?
Ow!
The pain is only temporary.
Remember, you told me that.
Listen, you had--
you had--oh!
Keep going.
Marge is at the controls
over there
and cranking
the higher button.
I'’m gonna grin and bear it,
but all I can hear is Jenni,
like, hyena-laughing
over there in the corner.
[laughs]
[Marge]
Okay.
We'’re going all
the way to the top.
Oh, ow!
And I feel like Meilani
was even getting
a little bit
of a kick out of this.
Is my stomach moving around?
[Marge]
Yeah, it is.
Oh!
Oh, that'’s going
down my leg now.
It'’s going down my groin.
You want the epidural now?
You'’re gonna
blow a circuit breaker.
[laughter]
- I don'’t want to [bleep] you.
- Oh!
Listen, Marge,
you can take one for the team.
That'’s the most action
he'’ll get in a long time.
Oh!
Oh, right here,
holy [bleep].
Oh!
- [bleep]-A, man.
- You okay?
What should we
ask these guys?
[Jenni]
I think everything
from A to Z.
- Sex.
- Have you ever cheated?
[Jenni]
I don'’t think
they'’ll be honest, but...
My diaper'’s falling out.
[Nicole voice-over]
Today is the day that we'’re
doing Joey'’s speed dating,
just because he doesn'’t have
a date for my wedding,
and I basically found seven,
eight guys.
And we'’re just gonna
pick our favorite guy.
Well, Joey'’s eventually
gonna pick, but, you know.
We'’re gonna pick, too,
who our favorite guy is for Joey
to bring to my wedding.
[whistles blow]
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, guys.
[all]
Hey.
[Jenni]
Thank you all for coming.
We really appreciate it.
[Nicole]
We'’re really
excited about this.
Yes.
Honestly, the first
thing I noticed
is that none
of them are bears.
[Nicole voice-over]
I don'’t see any bears.
I feel like all the bears
are hibernating right now.
- Joey'’s here!
- Hi!
- Yay!
[Jenni]
Our two other Joeys are here
for support and to make sure...
[Nicole]
They'’re taken.
That Joey doesn'’t get so drunk
that he doesn'’t know
what he'’s doing
and makes bad decisions.
Like normal.
- Yes.
I hope--do we have roses
to give to them?
Give them your penis.
I'’ll just give you a penis.
- What is your name?
- Jimmy.
[Jenni]
Jimbo.
Oh, everyone'’s gonna
get a new name today, so.
- Hi.
- Hi. Richard?
- I'’m gonna call you Dickie.
- All right.
Dickie-doo.
- Dickie-doo?
- He was born in Vegas.
- Oh.
[Joey]
I'’m gonna call him Lil Dice.
[Nicole]
Lil Dice.
- You'’re so cute, Jordan.
- Oh, well, thank you.
Your name is Miss Cheesecake.
[laughter]
Je suis espagnol,
mais je parle francais.
Your new name, since
you'’re speaking French,
is Banji Bonjour.
- Banji Bonjour?
- Je l'’aime beaucoup.
- From the South.
- Oh, you are? From where?
Georgia.
Ooh, I'’m gonna
call him...
Peach Cakes.
- Peach Cakes.
- Georgia peach.
Can you turn around
so we can see your cakes?
Oh, my God.
Joey'’s just basically
checking out all the booties
to see what it would
look like if he was--
[bleep] that booty.
[laughing]
Disgusting.
What is your take
on open relationships?
I'’ve been in a few.
How'’d that work out for you?
- Not great.
- No, not at all.
You think it'’s
gonna be amazing,
but then it doesn'’t
really work out.
When was your last boyfriend?
- So I'’ve never had a boyfriend.
- Why?
It'’s not because I'’m a slut,
I swear.
Oh, that'’s good.
When was your last
relationship, if any?
It was actually a "thruple."
See, that'’s not good.
I could not deal
with two Rogers.
I can'’t even deal
with one Roger.
[laughs]
Thank you.
I'’ve never had
a threesome.
Have you?
Yes, you have. Ew!
- Once.
- Poor Meilani.
- She'’s gonna be worse than you.
- No. She'’s gonna have a--
What would you do
if she did that?
I would kill her.
She'’s not gonna be allowed
out of the house till she'’s 40.
What if--
what if Giovanna did it?
I'’d say, "No, no, no!"
[Jenni]
So what do you think?
Which one do you think
is gonna be good for him?
Oh, my God.
Well, I know what one
would be good for me.
- Which one?
- I'’m just saying.
- The dancer.
- I know.
But he'’s a [indistinct].
Is he?
Of course he is.
[Joey]
So I'’m gonna be, like...
[humming]
[laughter]
Should I scream the name
and then grab him?
[Jenni]
No, just take their
hand and leave!
Grab him and go!
- Peach Cakes!
- [all] Yay!
[Nicole]
Whoa!
[Jenni voice-over]
I think Joey'’s
picking his date
on who was most
attractive for tonight.
Guarantee we ain'’t gonna
see Peaches tomorrow.
[Nicole]
Even if Joey doesn'’t
bring Peaches to my wedding,
he'’s gorgeous, he'’s fun,
and...
I feel like he
has a big [bleep].
Don'’t you?
Sorry, guys.
Whoo, daddy'’s got you.
She looks like
a little princess bride.
Today'’s the big day, honey.
It'’s all about her.
So today is our
daughter'’s christening,
and we'’re extremely excited.
It'’s very important
to us as parents.
Let'’s find Auntie Nicole.
We'’re in very
capable hands here,
and I can'’t wait to have
my daughter baptized.
I wonder if they ever
dropped a baby.
It'’s a big day.
Wasn'’t that long ago we were
doing this for this little guy.
Yeah, now he'’s a booger.
[Nicole voice-over]
I'’m really excited for today
just because I am
Meilani'’s godmother,
and, you know, Jenni
went through this process
already with Lorenzo
and baptizing him,
so now it'’s my turn
with Meilani,
and I-I'’m just wondering
if you'’re gonna cry.
Do you have your
godmother prayer?
- A godmother prayer?
- Yeah.
Like, something--
I know I didn'’t
do it for Lorenzo,
but in this church,
like, a nice--
This isn'’t what
I had you do,
so I don'’t understand
why I have to do this.
How long is this prayer?
Just a couple--
just a little bit.
- A little bit?
- Just say something nice.
I don'’t like reading
in front of people.
I, like, stutter,
and I forget how to read.
- Well...
- Like, "Ah-bluh-luh-luh!"
Mom, comfort her.
Nicole'’s duties
as a godmother, I mean,
I don'’t see them
being duties.
I just want you
in our life forever.
Let'’s see if you burn.
[Jenni voice-over]
And God forbid,
if anything
was to happen
to Roger and I,
you would just
raise her the best--
- Take care of her.
- Yeah.
[Nicole]
I'’ll teach her
how to, like,
dance and drink.
Those are not your duties.
[woman]
We welcome everyone
to the baptism of Meilani.
At this time, we'’d like
to ask the godmother, Nicole,
to come up
for the godmother prayer.
Wait, what?
By myself?
- Remember, project your voice.
- Stop.
[Jenni voice-over]
This is a huge moment
in each other'’s lives.
We'’re each other'’s
kids'’ Godparents.
Everyone'’s looking at me.
Can we--
look--
look at these guys.
All right.
[laughing]
Stop. All right.
I can'’t read in front of people.
She didn'’t know
she had to do this.
Just tell me.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
[Nicole]
Oh, Lord Jesus Christ,
you embrace children
with the arms of your mercy
and make them living members
of your church.
[Jenni voice-over]
I mean, it was always Nicole
that was gonna be my firstborn'’s
godmother, never a question.
- Amen.
- Thank you, Nicole.
That'’s special.
Very special.
Let the people
stand as we begin.
Time for a little bathie.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Name this child.
- Meilani...
[both]
Alexandra Matthews.
Meilani Alexandra, I baptize
you in the name of the Father,
and of the Son,
and of the Holy Spirit, amen.
[all]
Amen.
Meilani Alexandra,
you are sealed
by the Holy Spirit in baptism
and marked
as Christ'’s own forever.
- Yay.
- Aww.
- That'’s so good.
- Thank you.
[Roger voice-over]
Here we are celebrating
our daughter'’s baptism,
and it was just so surreal
to realize we'’re parents.
[Producer]
So how do you feel
about this experience,
from Jersey Shore until now?
I think, overall,
this experience
has been amazing
because looking back,
I'’m so glad
I went to the shore
to meet Roger,
to be with Roger,
and to fall in love.
Get the [bleep] out.
[laughs]
I love you.
Will you marry me?
Is that a yes?
[laughs]
How'’s my little baby?
She hasn'’t moved much today.
[Roger voice-over]
I think when I really knew
was when we had Meilani.
You know, I mean,
every time I think about it,
I get a little choked up.
Just bringing Meilani,
you know, into the world.
[Jenni voice-over]
We were, like, a little heart
with a missing piece,
and Meilani was
the missing piece.
- Welcome.
- Yay!
Yay.
[Roger voice-over]
We'’re a work in progress
to this day,
but compared
to where we were five years ago,
I truly have my soul mate
sitting next to me now,
you know?
Good job.
- Hi, how are you?
- Good. You want some Moscato?
[Jenni]
Yes, please.
We'’re having the after party of
Meilani'’s christening at Savor.
It'’s actually next to Karma,
where we met.
Ooh.
Oh, my goodness.
- Hi, Grampy Phil.
- Hi.
[Jenni voice-over]
I think this is
a special moment for Roger,
especially the two generations
that'’s with him,
his mom and his grandmother,
so this is a special
moment for him,
to have four generations
at the party with him.
So this is, like,
where it all began.
- Yeah.
- Way back in the day at Karma.
I was saying that.
When you were peeing
behind the bar.
It'’s below the place
that you peed on, so there--
we may actually get a little wet
in here today, actually.
Yeah.
He went there.
Just thought I'’d get
the record straight.
Dad.
So my dad'’s trying
to make jokes, and I get it.
You and Roger can joke all day,
but do not joke in front
of Roger'’s mom and grandma.
They don'’t get that humor.
We met right over there
for the first time,
but that was it.
I didn'’t see her again
that summer, and--and we--
[Jenni]
We kept in touch.
We loosely kept in touch
here and there,
but I think there was, you know,
some sort of seed planted,
and the rest is history, really.
- That was 4 1/2 years ago now.
- Wow, yeah.
I think you got the timing
a little off
on when the seed
was planted.
- Ew, Dad.
- Oh, God.
That was horrifying.
Let'’s hear it.
[Roger voice-over]
Terry definitely has a way
with words, yeah.
It was one
of those awkward moments.
It was, yeah.
- Is that a Bloody Mary?
- Yeah.
They make really good ones
here, if you want one.
So I'’m drinking a little bit
at the after party,
yes, I must admit.
May I have another Bloody Mary?
That was perfect.
I'’m in, like, three Bloody Marys
in and a couple wines,
but it'’s fine.
It'’s my daughter'’s party.
I'’m not driving,
so it'’s fine.
Oh.
Only I would spill
stuff on me.
It'’s Bloody Mary.
Can'’t take me anywhere.
I already got food spilt
all over me everywhere.
[laughing]
I mean, it is what it is.
I made it.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I'’m so sorry.
- How are you?
I had to manually
pump my boobs.
But I got it out.
[Roger]
I'’ve manually pumped
my [bleep] many times, so.
- Get some food.
- Okay.
- Yeah, help yourself.
- All right.
[Jenni]
We are celebrating
another milestone.
The next thing is to get
married to the love of my life,
and then I can just live life.
[Nicole]
So I'’m excited for that.
I'’m looking forward
to my new boob job.
- I'’m kidding.
- Oh, my God.
I'’m kidding!
Your nipples are
gonna fall off.
You can do the--
the speech
and cut the cake and--
No pressure.
Well, you can set it up as,
"Thank you all for coming,"
thank the godparents.
I got it, babe.
Tell the kids
to go to the candy bar.
You can chime in too.
- No. I hate speeches.
- So do I.
I [bleep] hate
making speeches,
so I'’m gonna stand behind Roger
and make him make the speech.
[clinking glass]
[Nicole]
You have a stain
on your crotch.
I know.
Jenni and I just
want to take a few moments
to thank each and every one
of you for being here today
on Meilani'’s special day.
[whispers]
Thank the Godparents.
Oh,
and a special thank-you to--
[all laugh]
She doesn'’t want
to make the speech,
but she'’s gonna tap me
on the shoulder.
Roger is definitely my puppet
when it comes to speeches.
I tell him what to say
and he does.
A very special thank you,
of course,
to Nicole, the godmother.
Yeah.
Yay.
[applause]
And now we cut the cake.
- Jenni, say something.
- Shut it.
I hate being the center
of attention.
It'’s weird.
You hate being
center of attention?
- You'’re such a liar.
- I swear to God.
All right, so when you walked
into the clubs
with your tits out--
My tits were the center
of attention.
Anything from you,
or do you just want
to tap me on the shoulder
a few more times?
- Say something.
- Stop!
Thank you again, guys.
- I really appreciate it.
- Yeah.
[Jenni]
Thank you all for coming
and spending the day with us.
As a mom, I mean, this moment
is very symbolic to me.
This is her first big party
and celebration of her life.
Four generations.
[Roger voice-over]
Our families are there.
Our good friends are there.
You know, these are people that
we plan on being in our lives
and in Meilani'’s life
forever, you know?
So it was just very nice
that everybody could be here,
and I wanted them to all know
how much that was appreciated.
It'’s a cross.
Yeah.
[Roger]
Now, if I touch this
to your forehead,
will it actually
leave the burn marks?
[Nicole]
It'’ll burn.
Do it to your wife.
She'’s worse.
You said my daughter
was gonna be a stripper.
You'’re worse.
She said Satan.
That'’s worse.
- Are you nervous?
- No. I'’m not nervous yet.
I'’ll be nervous tomorrow.
[Nicole voice-over]
So it'’s the night
before the wedding,
and I'’m really excited
to marry Jionni tomorrow.
I'’ve been waiting
since he proposed to me,
so almost two years, so it--
I'’ve definitely been waiting
for this moment for a while.
Remember to take it all in
because it'’s gonna
go by super fast,
and you'’re gonna wake
up the next morning
and say, "What happened?"
[chuckles]
- '’Kay.
- It'’ll be good.
No more Nicole Polizzi.
Nicole LaValle.
Nicole Elizabeth LaValle.
It'’s gonna be
a very emotional day.
You'’re already crying.
Your eyes are watery.
Please.
I can'’t look at you.
Why?
Do you picture me
as a little girl?
Exactly.
[Nicole voice-over]
So I'’m talking to my mom
about tomorrow,
and it'’s an emotional,
emotional time for her.
I'’m her only child.
I'’m her daughter.
So I understand
why she'’s crying.
I'’ll be fine.
It'’s all good.
It'’s all good stuff.
It'’s good stuff.
Happy times.
I love you.
Hey.
[Jionni]
How does this work?
Do I take her rings?
Or does she--I'’m asking you,
and you'’re answering me.
- Yeah.
- Nicole?
[Jionni voice-over]
Tonight'’s the night
before the wedding,
and pretty much tonight,
I'’m just gonna kind of pack,
get Lorenzo ready,
'’cause Lorenzo and I are gonna
be sleeping at my mom'’s.
You know, I guess traditionally
you'’re not supposed
to see the bride
or hang out with her.
What'’s that?
Do not lose those.
- How do they work?
- What?
You take mine,
and I take yours?
Mom?
Yeah?
Who holds Jionni'’s ring?
- Oh, [bleep].
- It'’s the best man.
- Give me that.
- Lorenzo, please.
Don'’t lose that.
[Helen]
No, I'’m sorry. You'’re right.
Oh, mom.
Oh, my God, Lorenzo.
- It'’s all diamonds.
- Go give that to Da-da.
Why would you give
that to him?
[Nicole]
Lorenzo, please stop
dropping that.
Here. Come here, buddy.
Where'’s the ring, Lorenzo?
- No, baby, I need this.
- Lorenzo, where is it?
That'’s daddy'’s.
Are you kidding?
- Oh, my God.
- Jionni.
Da-da.
- It'’s not in there?
- No.
You'’re lying.
I can tell you'’re lying.
- Not happening.
- Little wedding joke.
It'’s not funny.
You don'’t mess with beautiful,
gorgeous diamond bands
that are my wedding ring.
- Tell Lorenzo that.
- Ha, ha.
- One thing.
- Some orange juice.
Do not be drunk
when we get married.
Why?
Like, I'’m not kidding.
You have to be somewhat
sober to marry me.
I know how boys drink
in the morning and go nuts.
[Jionni voice-over]
So we'’re not even married yet,
and Nicole'’s already
barking orders.
"Don'’t drink, don'’t be drunk."
I mean, is this
what marriage--
I don'’t want you to--
Is this what marriage
is gonna be like?
I just don'’t want you
to be drunk at the wedding.
That'’s, like,
a reasonable thing to want.
My last happy day.
See you in your
white dress tomorrow.
Text me.
Don'’t be drunk
for the church, Jionni.
[Jionni]
All right.
[Nicole]
Bye, Lorenzo.
Morning.
How are you?
[Nicole voice-over]
Waking up,
I walk down in the kitchen,
and all my bridesmaids are here,
all 15 of them.
This moment is everything
I'’ve ever dreamed of.
It was honestly like Christmas.
Let'’s do this.
[Joey]
Leah, can I have a big lash
for Jenni?
[Nicole]
Oh, Jionni goes,
"Have fun, relax, and remember,
I love you."
He said, "You'’re gonna
look beautiful,
and I can'’t wait to say '’I do.'’"
[woman]
That is so cute.
[Nicole]
Like, he'’s never sweet
like that,
so I'’m just
taking this all in right now.
[woman]
Are you even nervous?
You look so calm.
I'’m not nervous yet.
I just--I want it
to, like, happen.
Is that normal?
I don'’t think you'’re
gonna get nervous.
I just feel like
I'’m throwing a party.
- One fabulous one.
- Yeah.
- Is that our big surprise?
- What?
Leonardo DiCaprio
is just gonna be there?
- I wish.
- He'’s gonna come out.
He'’s so hot.
- He wasn'’t hot to me.
- Can you imagine?
We met him, and
he wasn'’t hot to me.
I think he'’s dreamy.
You weren'’t there.
Remember?
I don'’t think he'’s hot.
He'’s, like, sexy.
[woman]
I agree with you in movies
and stuff.
He'’s a good-looking man.
[woman]
Are you pumping today?
Oh, so funny.
Yeah.
Just like at
the bachelorette party.
What'’d I say again?
"Settle, Carly."
[Carly]
No, it was more like,
"If you don'’t settle,
I'’m gonna twist your nipples."
Why did I say that?
Hi.
Hey, J.
- What'’s going on?
- Is everyone in the basement?
Yeah.
Lorenzo and I slept pretty good
last night at my mom'’s,
where everyone'’s gonna
kind of get ready,
relax, have a few drinks,
and just, you know, pretty much
get ready for the church.
All right,
so you and Joe go first.
You ready for a fresh shave?
[man]
Yeah.
My brother surprises
all of us with a barber
to come over and do,
like, you know,
a nice, clean shave, and I
thought it was an awesome idea.
Yeah, how about Dario?
He was saying, leaving my house
after the rehearsal dinner,
he said, "Thank you so much.
The gifts are awesome."
He'’s walking up the stairs,
I'’m like--
he left his gift there.
I said, "Dar, it couldn'’t
have been that good."
He'’s trying not to laugh, like--
I can'’t wait to see Nicole
walk down the aisle in her gown.
I can'’t wait for the moment
we'’re finally,
officially a full family.
- Hey.
- Oh!
Oh, hey, oh, hey!
Hey, why are these bags so long?
Can we talk about that?
I'’m dragging
this thing all over.
Nick, Nick,
the wedding'’s in a couple hours.
Holy [bleep].
He'’s got the [bleep]
bowtie on now?
[Jionni voice-over]
Cali comes walking down
with an hour left.
Typical Cali.
[Cali]
I'’ll tell you
what I didn'’t forget.
[man]
A flask?
Huh?
This is gonna--
I'’m really a little sick.
I need some scotch immediately,
or I won'’t be able to do it.
- I got scotch for you.
- All right.
- - It'’s over there.
I'’m, like, still shaking.
Do I still have time
to back out?
[indistinct chatter]
Your mom--your mom
looks gorgeous.
- You look so amazing.
- You look gorgeous.
Oh, you look pretty, Mama.
We got to take a picture and
put it on your eHarmony page.
[Jenni]
Oh, my God, stop.
I'’m gonna--I'’m gonna have my dad
join you on there real soon.
Imagine?
If our parents banged?
- Ew.
[Nicole]
We would be sisters.
Oh, we'’d be sisters!
I can'’t do that.
That'’d be so cool.
[doorbell rings]
- Thank you.
- Have a good one.
You too.
Aww, Ronnie and Pauly.
Nicole, you got a delivery.
- Who'’s that from?
- You'’ll see.
Aww.
Wait, that'’s not
their handwriting.
- Who wrote this?
- Well, they had it delivered.
Oh.
It says, "Dear Snooks, congrats.
"We are so happy
for you and Jionni
"and couldn'’t be more proud,
"but if he ever does you wrong,
we got you.
Love you, Pauly and Ronnie."
[woman]
Aww.
I love them.
[Jenni voice-over]
I'’m, like, picturing
four or five years ago
at the shore house,
when I look back
at our old selves
and I can'’t believe
how much you'’ve grown.
- Hello!
- Party'’s here.
[Jenni voice-over]
The thing with me and Nicole
is we had an insane early 20s.
Like, no regrets,
balls to the wall.
[yelling]
[Jenni voice-over]
We had the time of our life.
Oh, my God.,
I don'’t want to pay for this.
[Nicole]
Even though when, you know,
you first met me, you hated me.
So where is he going, Jenni?
He'’s running away from you.
[Nicole]
We didn'’t really connect
like I wanted to.
Eventually we did.
Who the [bleep] punches
a girl like that?
[Nicole voice-over]
And we'’ve been
through so much together.
You'’ve always been there for me.
You'’re like my big sister.
[yelling]
Oh, my God!
[both]
Ahh!
I love you, and I wouldn'’t
change it for the world.
Thanks.
So thank you
for being my bestie.
Baby!
She'’s so small.
My nipples hurt so bad.
You look just like your mom.
[Nicole voice-over]
Me and Jenni are literally
gonna be best friends forever.
[Jenni]
Yeah.
[Nicole]
We'’re gonna be
those senile friends in the...
[both]
Nursing home.
- Pinching--
- Poking--
- Pinching old men.
Poking--no, young boys,
young nurses.
Oh, yeah,
the young ones
that are changing
our diapers.
[Nicole]
My dress for the ceremony
I wanted to be very traditional.
Tighter.
Do you want it tighter,
like there?
Very tight.
It'’s poofy, and it'’s princess-y,
and it'’s just gorgeous.
Ready? I'’ll suck in.
- That'’s the tightest one.
- Bingo.
And now it'’s starting
to feel like my wedding day
because I'’m putting my dress on,
and I feel like a bride.
I feel like I'’m gonna
get married.
Is that good?
♪ I feel pretty
[Nicole voice-over]
And I just hope
when Jionni sees me,
I want him to say, "Oh, my God,
my wife is beautiful.
I can'’t wait to kiss her."
I'’m really happy
that my mom'’s here
just because I'’m starting
to feel a little nervous,
walking down the aisle
in this dress with my dad,
so I just need to relax
a little bit.
- Aww, look at you.
- Aww!
[woman]
Is Andy down there?
Hi, baby.
Oh, hi!
[woman]
Where'’s that mama?
Nice to see you.
- Okay.
- She'’s like, "All right."
[Nicole]
You guys ready?
[all]
Yeah.
[Jenni]
I got goose bumps.
Oh, God.
I hope I don'’t fall
down the stairs.
- You look beautiful.
- Beautiful.
- So pretty.
Nicole looks beyond beautiful
in your wedding dress.
- Like a princess.
- Yeah.
[Jenni]
It'’s a perfect moment.
Do I look fat?
- You look beautiful.
- No!
- Are you crazy?
- I feel a little bloated.
[Nicole voice-over]
This has been
a long time coming.
I mean, I feel
like I'’m that type of girl
that has been planning
my wedding for my whole life.
Hi, Dad.
[Nicole voice-over]
I'’ve always dreamed about,
you know,
marrying the love of my life,
and Jionni is very, very sweet.
I'’m very lucky to have him.
So I cannot wait for this.
Read the cards.
Look at the cards, there.
"I love you."
I did the same thing.
[woman]
Oh, don'’t cry!
Once I see that they'’re
from Giovanna and Lorenzo,
I just start losing it.
If I'’m crying with this card,
I know I'’m gonna
be crying all day.
I did the same thing.
- No, makeup.
- Aww.
- Come on. Let'’s--let'’s go.
- It'’s from Lorenzo.
[all]
Aww.
But Lorenzo really
didn'’t do that.
It was Jionni.
[Jenni]
Maybe Lorenzo did,
you don'’t know.
- Yeah, Lorenzo said, "Dad--"
- "Let me get mommy flowers."
No, he didn'’t.
Here, Dad.
This is for you.
Thank you, honey.
[Andy]
"Father of the bride.
I loved her first."
I love you.
[Nicole]
And my dad'’s a very emotional
man, so, you know, he'’s crying.
He can'’t even breathe.
Enough.
Let'’s go have a party.
We didn'’t even start it yet.
[Nicole]
All right,
let'’s get this party started.
I'’m getting married, bitches.
[all]
Whoo!
[Nicole]
Cheers.
Typical.
Vodka on my wedding dress.
[Jionni]
Who did I give the rings to?
What'’d you do with your phone?
It'’s in my pocket.
Your front pocket?
Yeah. Can you see it?
You can'’t see it.
Do you how tight my pants are?
It'’s a nice, slim fit.
Fits me good.
I can'’t bend over.
I'’m gonna rip a seam probably.
My ass is just gonna pop
out of this thing.
It'’s just--
that would be a problem.
So I'’m gonna have Cali
bend over and blow his ass
so he can tie my shoes.
No one cares about his pants.
Wow, you look nice.
Thanks.
- Wow, Aunt Janis, beautiful.
- Thanks.
Do you still need
a plus one, or...
What'’s a "plus one?"
It'’s time to get to the church
and, you know,
I just can'’t wait.
It'’s just--I can'’t wait
to see Nicole
come walking down the aisle.
She'’s been telling me
how good she'’s gonna look,
and now I get to finally see it.
Roadski, you got your flask?
Hey, yo, chief,
you want a flask, or no?
You'’re not drinking in church.
- What are you?
- You'’re not.
You have--
you have an issue, then.
I'’m not--they give you wine.
What are you talking about?
They have a bar there.
- Oh, they have a bar there?
- It'’s wine.
- Okay.
- They have wine. Yeah.
They even give snacks.
[man]
All right, guys, I
need you on the bus now, please.
[man]
All right.
Let'’s go.
[Jionni]
Who has my phone?
I mean, like, pretty much,
like, this is it.
Like, this is really,
like, happening.
Now I'’m getting nervous.
Lorenzo!
[all]
Yay!
[Jionni]
You being a--
you being a good boy?
- Karaoke.
- Thanks for being a good boy.
- Where we going?
- Party.
[Jionni]
A party?
Oh!
Who was on my dress?
I'’ll bite you.
It wasn'’t me.
Mom, do you know
where my coat is?
Where'’s all my stuff?
You'’re so anti-bridezilla
right now.
It'’s cute.
I wanted to be bridezilla,
but I guess I wasn'’t.
Don'’t get me wrong, you are
every other day of the year.
I have no idea why not
this year--this day.
I'’m kind of nervous.
You all right?
I'’m so proud of you.
I'’m kind of nervous.
Stop. I can'’t look at you.
I'’m gonna cry.
You cry?
You'’re human?
No. I don'’t [bleep] cry.
What are you talking about?
No, you cry.
[Jenni voice-over]
I never thought
in a million years
you would have this
gorgeous wedding, though,
and this gorgeous house,
because let'’s be real,
you loved leopard print, and--
Very tacky.
[Jenni]
To see you, like,
as a grown-up.
- A grown-up.
- Yeah.
[Jenni]
It'’s an emotional time.
If any of you fall
down the aisle, I'’ll kill you.
[Jenni]
Hold, hold, hold, hold.
Hold, hold, hold.
- Hello.
- Look at the little red carpet.
Thank you.
Oh, this is so Gatsby.
[Jenni]
Oh, my God.
[Nicole]
Oh, my God, I love this car.
- You'’re in.
- I'’ll see you--
[Jenni]
I'’ll see you at the altar.
No.
[Bleep].
I got to [bleep].
No, just go in there!
[Nicole]
No, I think I have to fart.
Love you!
See you at the altar!
- Let'’s see the dress.
- You ready, Dad?
[Andy]
Yes.
You look beautiful.
You look so handsome.
You are, like,
unbelievable.
You take my breath away.
Thanks, dad.
When you first
came into our lives,
I never thought this
time would ever come.
I mean, just the time
goes by so quick.
I mean, you'’re grown up.
- I'’m not your child anymore?
- You'’re not my baby anymore.
I'’ll always be your baby.
[Andy]
Absolutely.
[Nicole voice-over]
I think my parents are
actually very proud of the fact
that, you know,
I'’m changing my name,
and I'’m gonna be a LaValle now
because I'’m growing up,
and they love the fact
that I grew up into this woman
that they always tell me I am,
so I feel like my parents
are just really proud of me.
This is it.
One and done.
He'’s my husband,
and that'’s it.
Very, very,
very, very proud
of what you'’ve become
and how you'’ve matured.
Just--I don'’t know.
It'’s probably gonna
hit me tonight.
It definitely means a lot
that--you know,
that the church
was packed, you know,
people I haven'’t seen
in a while, friends and family,
it just--everyone'’s out here
for Nicole and I,
and it just, you know,
it meant a lot to me.
[male singer]
♪ I want to keep it moving
♪ Want to keep it going
♪ Never stop for no one
♪ That'’s the way I'’m growing ♪
♪ Hope for the best, yes
♪ It'’s all a test ♪
♪ So keep it coming
Now I'’m starting
to get nervous,
and I'’m like, "I need vodka."
Whoo. How do I look?
[Nicole voice-over]
I cannot wait
to see Jionni up there.
You know, it'’s almost that time
where I'’m gonna be Mrs. LaValle.
Elliott, what is--
- The wedding'’s over.
- Let'’s go.
I'’m missing it!
Jesus [bleep].
Oh, Lorenzo--
he'’s picking his nose.
I just repeat anything
you tell me?
Absolutely.
You just repeat--
whenever I say do, just do it.
It'’s easy.
I'’ll keep an eye on you--
keep two eyes on you.
Sounds good.
Hi, Nani.
[Nicole]
Baby, you look
so handsome.
Okay, Jionni,
I think we'’re ready.
Okay, girls?
Nicole'’s about to be my wife,
and I'’ve been waiting
for this moment,
and it was just more of, like,
a--a happy moment, you know?
I just--
you know, I'’m just happy.
[Nicole voice-over]
I just feel like this is,
like, not real.
Like, it'’s--it'’s so surreal
just because I'’m,
like, picturing myself walking
down the aisle with my dad.
So I'’m just trying to breathe
and not be hysterical.
[Pachelbel'’s Canon in D]
♪
[Nicole]
Oh, my God, we'’re starting.
We'’re starting.
I was so worried
about tripping, like,
hitting the front of
my dress and then the...
- Tops of--
- Coming down?
- Yes.
- That'’d be awesome.
- No.
- That'’d be so great.
No, I was so paranoid.
- Damn it.
- I was like this.
That'’d be so cool
if your tits came out.
Oh, thanks.
In front of Father O.
Yeah.
He'’d get a boner.
- I'’m gonna [bleep] my pants.
- Don'’t do that.
You'’re wearing a dress,
and it'’s white.
- Yeah, and it'’s white.
- You won'’t see it.
There'’s--there'’s lots of layers.
You won'’t see.
[Schubert'’s Ave Maria]
♪
It'’s my eyelash.
[Jionni voice-over]
She looks unbelievable.
The first thing I noticed was,
like, her smile.
Seeing her smile and her awesome
dress walking with her dad,
that definitely
was special and, you know,
something I'’m gonna
remember for a long time.
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son,
and of the Holy Spirit.
[all]
Amen.
What a beautiful day
to gather to celebrate
Nicole and Jionni'’s wedding.
Joined, we pray,
in an inseparable bond.
[Nicole voice-over]
I feel like it'’s, like,
an out-of-body experience.
Like, I feel like, like this
isn'’t my wedding, but it is.
- You know what I mean?
- Were you nervous?
[Nicole]
It'’s weird.
Not nervous,
but I was trying not to cry.
So I'’m, like,
holding back tears,
trying to smile, but,
like, my lip'’s shaking.
I'’m nervous.
I'’m scared.
This is it, I think.
Is this it?
Are we saying, like, "I do"?
- In a minute, you are, yeah.
- Oh, God.
You'’re good.
Take a deep breath.
I feel like Father Owens
didn'’t ask anybody
if they object
to our marriage.
They--they don'’t
say "I object."
It'’s not a courtroom.
It'’s "Speak now or forever
hold your peace."
But he didn'’t say that.
Well, good.
Yeah, but what if--
I feel like you
have to say that.
'’Cause everyone has to
agree on the marriage.
They were all
there for us.
No one'’s gonna disagree.
But it happens.
What if your dad said it?
I'’d punch him.
"I do!"
I'’d be like, "Yeah,
right, dad. Sit down."
Jionni and Nicole,
have you come here freely
and without reservation
to give yourselves
to each other in marriage?
- Yes.
Will you love and honor
each other as man and wife
for the rest of your lives?
[both]
I will.
Will you accept children
lovingly from God
and raise them up
according to the laws
of the Holy Roman
Catholic Church?
- Yes.
- I already did.
I have to compliment,
of course, little Lorenzo
and little Giovanna for being,
at a very young age,
very obedient,
not like their mommy.
But anyway...
[laughter]
- That'’s my bit, Nicole.
- Good, good.
But the question is,
will you try to raise up more?
- Yes.
- Excellent.
And now I invite
you to turn to each other
and hold your right hands.
- I, Jionni.
- Take you, Nicole...
Take you, Nicole...
To be my wife.
I promise to be true to you...
In good times...
And in bad.
- I, Nicole...
- Take you, Jionni...
- Will take you, Jionni...
To be my husband.
I promise to be true to you...
- In good times...
- In good times--look at me!
- And in bad.
[Jionni voice-over]
I look down for one second
at her ring,
she goes, "Look at me,"
in this devil voice.
- I didn'’t say it like that.
- Yeah, you did.
I said, "Look at me."
'’Cause when I see
weddings on TV,
they'’re staring
at each other, like--
I looked down for one second
to make--to just
look at the ring.
I was just making sure that
you were gonna look at me.
This is what marriage
is gonna be like.
Nicole.
- Repeat after me. Nicole...
- Nicole...
Take this ring...
- Take this ring...
- As the sign...
As the sign...
- Of my love...
- And fidelity.
- In the name of the Father...
- And of the Son...
- And of the Holy Spirit.
- Jionni, take this ring...
It was definitely
a special moment.
We'’ve been planning it.
It'’s been two years.
It'’s like, finally.
It feels good.
You'’re a good kid.
Now it'’s my great pleasure
to present to you
Mr. and Mrs. Jionni LaValle.
You may kiss your bride.
[cheers and applause]
[Jionni voice-over]
I thought you, like,
were that excited
that you wanted
to give me a second one.
- Well, I got--
- Oh, my God.
It surprised me.
I'’m like, "Oh, [bleep].
This is our kiss."
When the Father says,
"You may now kiss the bride,"
how'’d I surprise you?
I was thinking of, like,
a lot of things in my head,
so when you kissed me,
I was like, "Oh, my God,
this is our kiss."
So then I--
I kissed you again.
I know.
Is that it?
[Mendelssohn'’s Wedding March]
♪
[Nicole]
This is our vintage car.
[woman]
Oh, love it.
Whoo-hoo!
[Nicole]
We'’re married.
I'’m a LaValle.
Let'’s go to the reception.
[lively swing music]
♪
[Nicole]
So getting to the Venetian,
we walk in,
and everything
just looks beautiful
with all the centerpieces,
all the linens
that I picked out.
- It looks like--
- Chandeliers.
It looks very vintage,
and old-school and 1920s.
So I feel like all of that
just puts everything together
and makes it Gatsby.
[Jionni]
Yeah, they--the Venetian
definitely nailed
our whole Gatsbytheme.
[Nicole]
Yup.
Cheers, husband.
[Jionni]
Cheers, guys.
I have a husband.
[Nicole voice-over]
The cocktail hour
is huge at this place.
[Jionni]
There was 20 stations,
literally 20 food stations.
There'’s seafood stations,
mozzarella station,
there'’s actually
a guy hand-making mozzarella.
I know people
are gonna be talking
about the cocktail
hour forever.
[Roger]
I like the new '’do, man.
- It fits you.
- Thanks, man.
It was time to
switch it up, maybe.
- I had to do it.
- Yeah, it looks good, though.
I had to switch it up.
[Roger]
I think Ronnie just rolled up.
Nice hair, Pauly.
Thank you. Thanks.
- Can I touch it?
- Yeah, of course.
Hey!
How are you?
- How are you?
- Hey, how are you?
- I'’m good.
- Good to see you.
- What'’s going on?
- Not too much.
I texted you!
You wear it really,
really well.
I just wear it better.
[Roger voice-over]
It'’s my suit cut in half.
This is awesome.
Mini-me.
Buy one, get one
half off, literally.
Yes!
My baby did a funny.
I was the only guy here
in white till you showed up.
I thought I was the only
ass[bleep] in white.
Thank God, nobody can see you.
I love weddings!
[Jionni voice-over]
Everyone was downstairs
for a little while eating,
enjoying the cocktail hour while
me and Nicole were upstairs,
you know, getting our--
- Missing it.
- Yeah, pretty much missing it.
[Jionni]
You were getting touched up,
ready to go,
and all of a sudden, like,
a wave of people come in.
[Nicole]
I'’ve got to get changed.
We'’re gonna get started
probably in about 15 minutes.
Oh, [bleep].
I got to go.
And she'’s like,
"All right, we got to--
get in your lines,
we'’re about to go."
I'’m like,
"We'’re already walking out?
"We just missed
cocktail hour.
Unreal."
- Oh, my God.
- It'’s loose. I lost weight.
All right, I'’m sweating again.
- Are you guys practicing?
- Yes, we'’re practicing.
You guys suck!
- You didn'’t practice this?
- Where are my--
[Jenni]
Good-bye!
Let me try it real quick.
Yeah, I can make it.
I go like this.
- Okay.
- Spin.
That didn'’t
work, though.
Can you spin me, though,
from that high?
Yeah, I'’ll jump.
I'’ll do a, "bloop!"
Try and spin me, though.
We can do that.
Okay.
After a few-- after a
little bit of dancing--
Yeah, we dance,
three spins,
dance, dance, dance,
spin out, spin in, dip.
I'’m nervous about
our first dance,
because we kind of, like,
did a little routine.
The night before.
And I don'’t want
to mess it up.
[MC]
All right, ladies
and gentlemen,
it'’s time to bring in
the awesome bridal party.
Everybody have a good time!
This is it.
They'’re going.
[cheers and applause]
[MC]
Here we are. Give it up for
Jenni, Michael, and Anthony.
[Jenni]
Everyone'’s cheering
as I'’m coming down the stairs,
which makes
me more nervous,
'’cause my little
two-step with my twins
is so embarrassing
that I'’m just like, "Oh,
my God, I want this to be over.
"I need a shot. I need a shot.
I need a drink.
I just want this to be over."
[cheering]
[MC]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we need you all to put
your hands together.
Okay, everybody make some noise
out here this evening.
Come on.
Now introducing
Mr. and Mrs. Jionni LaValle.
[Jionni voice-over]
We hear the band yelling,
like, on the top of his
lungs in an awesome voice,
"Now introducing
for the very first time,
Mr. and Mrs.--"
"Jionni LaVaaaalle."
Oh, my God.
I don'’t think
he held it that long.
Yeah, he did.
[Jionni]
I didn'’t know this curtain
was gonna open up and--
- Reveal us.
- So we were like...
- "Let'’s just go."
- "What do we do?"
[Nicole]
There'’s 800 eyeballs
staring at us.
- That'’s--
- That'’s a lot of eyeballs.
Yeah, scary.
Our whole bridal party, like,
made, like, a little bridge,
and then we ran under it,
and I was just giggling
the whole time.
It was so cool.
[Jionni]
I was, like, tapping my friends'’
balls as I was going by.
[Nicole]
What'’s wrong with you?
Who does that?
I was kind of
trying to just,
you know, enjoy
the moment and just--
And so enjoying the moment,
you touch your friends'’ balls?
- You'’re sick.
- That'’s what you just said.
I'’m trying to, like,
loosen up a little bit,
get everyone
not so stressed out.
[cheers and applause]
[MC]
Give a big round of applause.
Let'’s hear it for our bride
and groom this evening.
Come on, let'’s hear it for them.
Just do it.
Again, or no?
Good.
You look good, I promise.
[Jionni voice-over]
I really didn'’t figure myself,
you know, marrying Nicole
after that first night.
Like, were you gonna
figure all this out?
I knew he was the one
because I took his number
from the shore house,
and then I called him,
and I said, "Do you
want to come over?"
And no hesitation,
he was like, "Yeah, sure."
[Jionni]
No, what was the first
thing I said?
[Nicole]
What'’d you say?
I said, "Nicole who?"
How many Nicoles
do you know?
[Jionni]
It was a good summer for me.
[Nicole]
What does that mean?
You had other options?
Don'’t tell me that.
I'’m not kidding.
You don'’t even
remember my name.
Yeah, we'’re good.
[Nicole]
Like, I love him.
I'’m in love.
Like, what the [bleep]?
♪ No matter what
♪ You got me
♪ I'’m never gonna
let you fall ♪
This is it.
I'’ve always wanted a kid,
and he'’s here,
and it'’s with Jionni.
[Jionni]
Love you.
[Nicole]
I love you.
♪ When you'’re feeling down ♪
♪ Just call on me
♪ I'’ll always help you out ♪
♪ It could be something big
♪ It could be something small
[Jionni]
Is it what you
always imagined?
[Nicole]
Better.
[Jionni]
I'’d say we'’re pretty blessed.
♪ It'’s gonna be just fine ♪
♪ I'’m never gonna let you fall ♪
Go, go, get it,
we'’re gonna dip.
♪ Da da da da dum
♪ Da da da da
♪ Da dum
[MC]
I want everybody to put
their hands together for a very,
very proud mom this evening.
Come on.
[Jionni voice-over]
I had my first dance
with my mother.
Just looking around,
there'’s so many memories,
and I think deep down,
my mom'’s gonna be sad--
Getting emotional.
[Jionni]
Oh, and I got to
ask you something.
I swear to God, I got to sit
every time you two talk to me.
What do you want me to do?
Mop the floor.
I'’m not mopping the floor.
You'’re gonna make him
knock over the drink.
Oh, sorry.
You just jinxed me.
[Jionni voice-over]
I think, you know,
she'’s gonna miss us.
You know, I'’m her last child.
Me and my mom get along.
We always joke around.
We bicker, but I'’m definitely
gonna miss her.
- Oh, God.
- Are you [bleep] me?
- This is so--
- Oh, my God.
All right, group hug.
Group hug.
[Jionni]
You know, it'’s just--
not many people get to have
this kind of relationship,
and, you know, it'’s gonna
be tough being without them.
You'’re a good kid.
- You'’re a good kid.
- Grow up.
[MC]
Ladies and gentlemen,
a round of applause
for Janis and her son.
[cheers and applause]
[MC]
This is the time
a father waits a lifetime for,
to dance with his princess
on her wedding day.
What are you doing to me?
Look at the tape.
I'’m doing
the daddy-daughter dance,
and then all of a sudden,
there'’s pictures
of me as a baby.
My dad was crying, so I'’m, like,
holding back tears,
trying to smile.
And then I just started crying.
It was just so emotional
because I'’ve been a Polizzi
for 27 years.
Poppy!
[Nicole]
Seeing my uncle who passed away
and my grandparents, you know,
it kind of made me feel good
because it'’s like--
seeing their pictures,
it'’s kind of like they'’re here.
Eww!
Dad, that'’s freshman prom.
[cheers and applause]
Thanks, Dad.
[Nicole]
Oh, wow!
Babe, it'’s beautiful!
[Jenni]
It'’s insane.
I mean, Nicole always was
looking for love
at the Jersey Shore,
and she found it.
She found it in Bernard,
and she made this crazy
one-night stand the love
of her life, and honestly,
I never would have thought that,
five years ago, we'’d be
standing here today like this.
I am so thankful
to have Nicole in my life.
Blessed as well.
I feel very grateful
that I have her,
and I thank, you know, every day
that I have such a good friend.
What is that?
It'’s snowing!
Ever since I went down
the shore, I always, you know,
wanted to find that guy
who was handsome
and Italian
and his last name
ended in a vowel.
I wanted to have gorgeous, tan
babies with and get married,
and it literally
happened just like that.
Jionni'’s Italian.
He'’s handsome.
His last name
ends in a vowel.
You'’re my dream come true.
Relax, Cinderella.
He'’s stupid.
[Nicole]
This episode of Snooki
&amp; JWOWW...
[Jenni]
Continues now.
[Patent Pending'’s Brighter]
♪ Will you wander
with me to the edge ♪
♪ Take a breath,
tell the world ♪
You look beautiful.
Absolutely gorgeous.
Thank you for coming.
[Jionni]
Hey, that'’s my wife!
[laughs]
- Ew!
- He'’s got a big one.
Good for you.
[Nicole]
You got your flip-flops on.
- Yeah, look. Look.
- Take those off.
Look at my shoe.
[Nicole]
So I'’m dancing, you know,
jumping up and down,
and I broke my [bleep] heel.
Can you get my wedges?
- You want them?
- Yeah.
[Jenni]
You jumped and, "Pfft."
I was dancing so hard
that I broke my damn heel.
♪ Well, this is our time
♪ This is our life
♪ This our song
♪ This is our night
♪ And if the world gives up
♪ We'’ll carry on ♪
♪ Turn the volume up
♪ We'’ll sing along ♪
- ♪ Oh oh oh
- ♪ You'’ve got a home ♪
- ♪ You'’ve got a song ♪
- ♪ Oh oh oh
- ♪ No, you'’re not alone ♪
- ♪ Just sing along
I am having a blast dancing
with our old roommates.
[Nicole]
We can still party.
[Jenni]
It'’s like nothing has changed,
but everything has changed.
We have families.
Pauly has a kid.
I have a kid.
You have two.
You'’re married.
Ronnie lives in L.A.
Deena and Chris
are settling down.
So to come together
like this is super important,
and I know it means the world
to Nicole.
I love the fact
that even though
we don'’t see
each other a lot,
every time
we'’re together,
it'’s just like,
"I love you."
Because I feel like we always
have this special bond.
Want to take a shot?
Sure.
- At the bar?
- Okay.
- Let'’s all go take a shot.
- You want to take a shot?
I want to!
- Come on.
- Let'’s go take a shot.
Nicole and I have experienced
the most craziest life
you could ever imagine
with six other people,
and nothing in this world
can top what we went through.
If there was any way to end
such a beautiful show,
it'’s this way,
'’cause there'’s no other way
to go out besides a...
[Nicole]
Gatsbywedding.
[Jenni]
A Gatsbywedding
and two babies.
Yeah. You'’re almost 30,
so we got to do something--
Shut the [bleep] up.
You have a
30-year-old vagina.
- That'’s--
- Disgusting.
Your vagina had two kids
come out of it,
so it'’s not looking
any better than mine.
No, mine looks still nice
like a little virgin.
♪ Destiny has got us here
♪ Oh, I can'’t believe
how much I feel ♪
♪ Seems like a dream
We love you.
We just want to
say thank you
for enjoying the last
five years with us
and being part
of our crazy-ass lives
and enjoying it just
as much as we have.
Yes.
You'’ve seen us at our best,
you'’ve seen us at our worst--
And at our worst.
- A lot at our worst.
- Our way worst, yup.
But we love you,
and it'’s a good-bye for now.
Yes.
It'’s not good-bye.
It'’s "I'’ll see you later."
You ready, Jionni?
Oh, God.
[cheering]
[producer]
All right, that'’s a wrap!
All right, Jionni,
get down off your box now.
[all laugh]
All right. It'’s done.
It'’s done!
Please.
God.
All right.
It'’s done.
- See you guys.
- That'’s it.
- Love you.
- I love you so much.
So are you still coming
over for Sunday dinner?
- Hell yeah.
- Okay.
Janis'’ chicken cutlets.
Oh, I'’m so excited!
[Roger]
I remember the first time
your dad gave mommy the clap.
[Jenni]
Oh, my God, shut--
- You'’re so stupid.
- You'’re sick.