- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI AND JWOWW...
- ROGER LEFT
BECAUSE HE WAS UPSET.
- WAIT, WHY?
- I THINK HE'’S JUST
LOST HIS DAMN MIND.
I DEFINITELY KNOW ROGER AND I
ARE GONNA FIGHT AGAIN.
I MEAN, ALL COUPLES FIGHT.
IT'’S THE WAY
YOU HANDLE THE FIGHT
THAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
- SO ARE WE OKAY?
- YEAH, WE'’RE FINE.
WE'’LL JUST HIRE NEW PARENTS.
- GUESS WHAT I'’M DOING TODAY.
BRIDESMAID SHOPPING.
I CAN'’T WAIT FOR THE BRIDESMAIDS
TO SEE THE DRESSES,
BECAUSE I'’M GONNA PUT THEM
IN HIDEOUS ONES.
OH, MY GOD!
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT
♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE BLOW THIS COCKROACH JOINT?
THIS INSECT-INFESTED HOUSE.
- LET'’S BLOW
THIS COCKROACH JOINT.
- DADDY, BUH-BYE.
- BUH-BYE, YEAH.
- BUT MAMA BYE.
- MAMA BYE?
NO, SHE'’S COMING WITH.
- I'’M COMING.
DON'’T LEAVE ME HERE BY MYSELF.
- [high-pitched yelp]
- WANT TO LEAVE MOM?
- NO.
- IN THE SPOOKY HOUSE?
- MM-MM.
- DID YOU HAVE FUN THIS SUMMER?
- YES.
- DO YOU THINK THIS SUMMER
WENT BY FASTER THAN LAST SUMMER?
- YEAH, I FEEL LIKE WE WERE HERE
FOR, LIKE, A WEEK.
- YEAH.
- IT WENT BY REALLY QUICK.
- THERE'’S LORENZO.
- LORENZO, WHERE ARE YOU?
THERE YOU ARE!
- LOOK.
- DID YOU SAY,
"LET ME SEE YOUR OUTFIT"?
- LET ME TAKE A PICTURE OF YOU.
- WHEN YOU POSE?
- YEAH.
- GOOD JOB.
I TEACH YOU WELL.
- DON'’T ACT LIKE YOUR MOM.
- IT'’S GOOD FOR HIM
TO POSE AND TAKE PICTURES.
- I DON'’T WANT HIM, LIKE,
LOOKING IN THE MIRROR,
GOING LIKE THIS,
LIKE YOU DO.
- YOU DO THAT ALL THE TIME.
OR YOU GO LIKE THIS.
- YEAH, '’CAUSE I PUCKER MY LIPS.
- YOU DO.
- YEAH, OKAY.
- THERE'’S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH YOU.
- LOSER, I DID THAT
IN EIGHTH GRADE.
- LORENZO, WE KNOW
WHAT YOU'’RE DOING IN THERE.
YOU'’RE TAKING A POOP.
SO TODAY IS THE LAST DAY
OF SUMMER.
WE ARE LEAVING
THE SHORE TONIGHT.
THE HOUSE IS NOT
GONNA BE READY IN TIME,
SO WE'’RE MOVING FROM THIS HOUSE
BACK TO THE BASEMENT,
AND THEN MOVING
TO OUR DREAM HOUSE.
- THIS IS IT.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE'’LL DO THIS NEXT YEAR?
WE'’LL BE TOO BUSY.
- I WOULD LIKE TO CARRY
THE TRADITION ON SOMEHOW.
- MIGHT BE TOUGH.
- I DEFINITELY WANT
TO SEE JENNI AND ROGER
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE, THOUGH,
EVEN IF WE LIVE FAR AWAY.
I'’M DEFINITELY
GONNA MISS THE FACT
THAT WE'’RE NOT SO CLOSE
TO JENNI AND ROGER.
I LOVED BEING NEIGHBORS
WITH THEM THIS SUMMER.
- WATCH OUT FOR COCKROACHES
IN YOUR BAGS.
- UGH.
DISGUSTING.
AM I GONNA MISS THE HOUSE?
I AM NOT GONNA MISS THESE BUGS.
- WHERE'’S ALL YOUR SHOES GOING?
WHY DON'’T YOU PUT YOUR SHOES
IN A GARBAGE BAG?
- I'’M NOT PUTTING MY SHOES
IN A GARBAGE BAG.
- WHY?
THEY'’RE SHOES.
- '’CAUSE YOU HAVE TO TREAT THEM
WITH RESPECT.
SHOES.
- WE'’RE DONE.
- ALL RIGHT, WE'’RE GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT, LORENZO.
BARBECUE, AND THEN WE GO HOME.
- IS IT RAINING?
- DRIZZLING.
- I GOT A DATE TONIGHT.
AND HE'’S MORE HANDSOME
THAN DA-DA.
TONIGHT WE'’RE GOING
TO JENNI AND ROGER'’S
FOR OUR LAST BARBECUE.
THIS IS LORENZO'’S FIRST TIME
MEETING MEILANI,
SO I'’M A LITTLE NERVOUS,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, LORENZO'’S
GONNA HAVE A BABY SISTER,
AND I WANT HIM
TO BE COMFORTABLE.
I HOPE HE'’S JUST CUTE
AND HE'’S EXCITED TO MEET HER.
- OH, HEY.
- WE BROUGHT ICE CREAM.
SAY, "HI, AUNT JENNI."
- HI.
- WHAT'’S UP, BUDDY?
- HOW'’S MY BABY?
IS SHE SLEEPING?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, I GOT HER DRESSED UP
FOR YOU.
- DID YOU?
- BEST AS I COULD FOR A BABY.
- OH, MY GOD.
LOOK AT THE BABY.
- LOOKING BACK
ON THE LAST FIVE YEARS,
I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW THE [...]
WE WENT FROM THAT...
- THAT THING.
- BUNK BEDS AND...
WHATEVER YOU CALL THEM,
LIKE, ROOMMATES
AT THE JERSEY SHORE.
- SMELLY LITTLE DRUNKS.
- SLEEPING WITH VODKA BOTTLES.
- MM.
- FIGHTING.
- AND NOW...
- OUR KIDS ARE GONNA [...] UP.
- YEP.
- IT'’S THE CIRCLE OF LIFE.
- I'’M GONNA KICK THEIR ASS.
- OH, SERIOUSLY.
ARE YOU AWAKENED
SO YOU CAN MEET LORENZO?
WHO'’S AWAKE?
I THOUGHT SHE WAS WAKING UP.
- DAH.
- THAT'’S BABY MEILANI.
- HEY, BABY.
- WHO IS THAT?
[baby cooing]
LOOK
- STRETCH.
- WHO'’S THAT?
IS THAT THE BABY?
SAY, "HI, MEILANI."
SAY, "HI, BABY."
- HI, BABY.
- LORENZO SEEING MEILANI
FOR THE FIRST TIME IS SO CUTE,
AND HE LOOKS REALLY COMFORTABLE
WITH MEILANI.
- AND HE'’S SHY, WHICH IS--
IT'’S JUST MORE CUTE.
LIKE, HOW CUTE
AND, LIKE, SHY HE GETS.
- GONNA BE YOUR BEST FRIEND?
- IS THAT GONNA BE
YOUR BEST FRIEND?
- YES?
- [gasps]
- LOOK HOW TINY.
YOU WERE THAT TINY BEFORE.
WELL, IT'’S DEFINITELY GOOD
THAT LORENZO'’S NOT FREAKING OUT
WITH THE BABY,
BECAUSE HE'’S GONNA
HAVE A SISTER SOON.
SO I REALLY THINK LORENZO'’S
GONNA BE THE BEST BROTHER EVER,
JUST BECAUSE HE'’S REALLY,
REALLY GOOD WITH BABIES,
LIKE MEILANI.
- I'’M REAL EXCITED
TO HAVE A GIRL.
WE GOT THE ONE
OUT OF THE WAY.
SHE'’S GONNA BE
MY LITTLE PRINCESS.
SHE'’S GONNA DO WHAT I--
- I'’M YOUR PRINCESS.
- OH, CHRIST.
- I'’M GONNA GET JEALOUS.
WATCH.
- OH.
- WOW.
- BUONGIORNO.
- DO YOU MEAN BON APPETIT?
- BUONGIORNO?
[laughter]
ROGER, YOU'’RE FUNNY.
IT'’S OUR LAST SUPPER.
- THIS IS IT, GUYS.
- I WAS TELLING HIM EARLIER,
I WOULD REALLY LIKE IT
IF WE COULD SPEND THE NIGHT,
ESPECIALLY WHEN GIOVANNA'’S
FIRST BORN,
FOR--IF YOU GUYS NEED ANY--
- I WOULD LOVE THAT.
- ON A PERSONAL NOTE,
I GOT TO SAY, MAN,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I FEEL LIKE THIS SUMMER
I GOT TO KNOW YOU BETTER
ON A PERSONAL LEVEL
THAN MAYBE ALL THE SUMMERS
IN THE PAST,
JUST BECAUSE WE'’RE DADS NOW,
AND YOU WERE SO HELPFUL TO ME,
AND I'’M VERY APPRECIATIVE
OF THAT.
THANK YOU.
- NOT BECAUSE YOU DRY-HUMPED ME
[...] BUTT?
- WELL, THAT--
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, THAT CERTAINLY
HAS A LOT TO DO WITH IT TOO.
- WHAT A SUMMER.
- ARE YOU GONNA MOVE
RIGHT INTO YOUR NEW HOUSE?
- UNFORTUNATELY, WE HAVE TO MOVE
BACK TO THE BASEMENT.
- IT'’S ONLY GONNA BE
A WEEK OR TWO.
- JUST UNTIL--
I MEAN, I GET IT.
- WE MIGHT AS WELL GO BACK
AND ENJOY THE HELP
OF MY MOTHER THERE.
- YEAH, TRUE.
- YEAH, THE LAST HURRAH
IN THE BASEMENT.
- I COULD USE JANIS'’S HELP
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- YUP.
- YEAH.
- WHAT'’S LORENZO'’S ROOM
LOOK LIKE?
- LORENZO, WHAT COLOR
IS YOUR ROOM?
- BLUE.
- YAY!
DIDN'’T EVEN TELL HIM.
DIDN'’T EVEN TELL YOU.
[laughter]
HE'’S SO SMART.
- WE GOT TO GET GOING SOON,
'’CAUSE WE GOT TO LEAVE TONIGHT.
ALL AROUND,
IT WAS AN AWESOME SUMMER,
BUT NOW IT'’S TIME
TO GO BACK TO THE BASEMENT.
- KISS.
- MWAH.
all: AW!
- THANK YOU.
- IT'’S HER FIRST BOYFRIEND.
- THE SUMMER WAS DEFINITELY
EVERYTHING THAT I HOPED FOR.
IT WAS FRICKIN'’ AWESOME TO BE
PREGNANT WITH MY BEST FRIEND.
NOW SHE'’S A MOM,
AND WE'’RE BOTH MOMS,
AND, YOU KNOW, I'’M GLAD
THAT WE EXPERIENCED THAT.
- I'’M SUPER SAD THAT NICOLE
WON'’T BE MY NEIGHBOR ANYMORE,
YOU KNOW,
JUST HELPING ME BE A NEW MOM
IN EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
I COULDN'’T APPRECIATE THAT MORE
FROM HER.
AND, YOU KNOW, I JUST WANT
TO HELP HER NOW WITH HER WEDDING
AND GIOVANNA.
- THAT'’S WHAT BEST FRIENDS DO.
- MM-HMM.
- LOVE YOU.
- IT'’S NOT GOOD-BYE.
IT'’S, "I'’LL SEE YOU LATER."
- SAYONARA.
- BYE.
- BYE, MEILANI.
- BYE, TAKE CARE.
- I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- DRIVE SAFE.
- CALL US IF YOU NEED ANYTHING.
- I WILL; PLEASE DRIVE SAFE.
- COME OVER!
- IF WE GET DIRTBAG NEIGHBORS
THAT MOVE IN,
YOU'’RE COMING BACK.
- YOU GOT IT.
- LOVE YOU.
- BYE, MEILANI!
SAY, "BYE."
- OH, LORENZO.
- BACK IN THE BASEMENT.
- GOOD MORNING.
- DA-DA.
- WHO'’S PUMPED TO GO
TO THE NEW HOUSE?
- ME!
TODAY WE'’RE HEADING
OVER TO THE HOUSE,
YOU KNOW,
TRYING TO PUT FURNITURE IN
AND DECORATE AS MUCH AS WE CAN.
WE CAN'’T REALLY MOVE
INTO THE HOUSE,
SO IT'’S KIND OF LIKE A TEASE.
- GIVE ME A HUG.
- YOUR BREATH SMELLS.
GO BRUSH YOUR TEETH.
- WHO?
- YOU.
- YOURBREATH SMELLS.
- NO.
[blowing]
- AH!
YOU HAVE, LIKE, SUPER POWERS.
- [giggles]
- HI, BABY.
GONNA HANG OUT
WITH YOUR DADDY TODAY?
- I'’M GETTING
MY HAIR DONE TODAY.
- GETTING YOUR HAIR DID?
- YEAH, I'’M EXCITED.
I DEFINITELY WANT
A MOMMY MAKEOVER
AT THIS POINT IN MY LIFE.
I MEAN, LIKE, I JUST DON'’T LIKE
THE WAY I LOOK RIGHT NOW.
I WAS PREGNANT FOR TEN MONTHS.
MY HAIR'’S ALWAYS UP.
I HAVEN'’T SHOWERED.
LIKE, I DON'’T DO MY MAKEUP.
IT'’S LIKE, SHOULD I TAKE
THE HOUR AND A HALF, TWO HOURS
TO SHOWER, SHAVE?
OR DO I WANT TO [...] IN BED
AND HAVE THE EXTRA TWO HOURS
AND SLEEP?
- "DO I WANT TO GET IN BED
WITH MY FIANCEE
WITH MY WINTER BUSH?"
- [laughs]
YOU SEE?
- FULL PELT.
- BUT YOU UNDERSTAND WHY I WANT
TO CHANGE A LITTLE BIT?
- YEAH.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
YOU KNOW ME; I ALWAYS ENCOURAGE
YOU TO DO WHAT YOU WANT.
- DO YOU LIKE BLONDES, REDHEADS?
PURPLE HAIR, BLUE?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'’M DEBATING.
- YOU ALREADY KNOW
MY PREFERENCE IS BRUNETTE.
BUT...
- THINKING...
I'’M THINKING BLONDE-ISH.
WE'’LL SEE.
I DON'’T CARE WHAT ROGER THINKS.
I JUST WANT SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
AND IT'’S NOT GONNA BE FOREVER.
I JUST WANT SOMETHING LIKE,
"OH, SHE LOOKS GREAT
AS A NEW MOM.
SOMETHING'’S DIFFERENT."
LIKE, I WANT THAT REACTION.
I WANT, LIKE,
"OH, YOU LOOK FRESH."
"YOU LOOK CLEAN."
- I COULD JUST GO TO THE STORE
AND GET YOU SOME SUMMER'’S EVE.
COME HOME A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT GIRL?
- YEAH.
- STRANGER'’S GONNA WALK
BACK INTO MY HOUSE?
- YEAH.
- SHE GONNA BE MORE SEXUAL
THAN THE OTHER ONE?
- NO, BUT I'’LL LOOK MORE SEXUAL.
- IF I PLAY MY CARDS RIGHT
AND TREAT YOU
TO A REALLY NICE DINNER,
WILL YOU HAVE SEX WITH ME
WHEN WE GET HOME?
- UM...
- IS THAT A YES OR NO?
- THINK ABOUT IT.
- ACCORDING TO YOU,
I'’M NOT ROMANTIC ENOUGH,
AND THAT'’S WHY YOU DON'’T
GIVE ME ANY.
SO WOULDN'’T ROMANCE
MAKE A DIFFERENCE IN THAT?
- ROMANCE WOULD,
NOT NECESSARILY
A PLATE FULL OF FOOD.
- WHAT CONSTITUTES ROMANCE?
- HUGS, KISSES, A CARD.
OH, MY GOD.
AH!
THAT TICKLES.
- [whistles]
- SEE?
THIS IS WHAT I GET.
- WELL, HOW IS THAT
SUCH A TOUGH DECISION FOR YOU?
- '’CAUSE WE HAVE A BABY.
WHEN WE'’VE TRIED IT BEFORE AND
SHE'’S WOKEN UP IN THE MIDDLE,
THAT RUINS THE MOOD.
MEILANI HAS ACTUALLY
KILLED THE MOOD A FEW TIMES
DURING OUR SEXUAL ENDEAVORS,
WHEN, IN THE MIDDLE,
ROGER HEARS HER FUSSING,
STOPS AND GOES TO CHECK ON HER.
DON'’T ACT LIKE IT DIDN'’T HAPPEN,
'’CAUSE YOU KNOW IT DID.
- IT DID, BUT YOU MAKE IT SOUND
SO PERVERSE, BUT YES.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN PERVERSE?
IT JUST KILLS THE MOOD.
- I DIDN'’T WALK OVER THERE
WITH A GIANT BONER.
I PUT MY UNDERWEAR ON
AND CLEANED MY HANDS OFF.
- WHO THINKS LIKE THAT?
- YOU SAID IT LIKE THAT.
ALL RIGHT, BREAKFAST WAS GOOD.
I'’M GONNA GO PICK UP
MY LITTLE BABY OVER THERE
THAT I SEE IS AWAKE
AND SNEEZING LIKE A CHAMP.
AND I'’M GONNA WAIT
FOR YOU TO GET HOME
AND MAKE SWEET, SWEET LOVE
TO MY BLONDE MISTRESS.
- UGH.
WE'’RE GONNA HAVE TO HURRY,
THOUGH,
'’CAUSE THEN MY FIANCEE
WILL BE HOME AFTER THAT.
- SO STUPID.
- HOLD ON.
WHOA.
WHOA!
HOME, SWEET HOME.
OOH, OUR POD!
TODAY WE'’RE HEADING
OVER TO THE HOUSE
BECAUSE WE'’RE GONNA START
TO MOVE FURNITURE IN.
THERE WE GO.
RIGHT NOW IT'’S BASICALLY
AN EMPTY HOUSE,
SO I'’M JUST REALLY EXCITED
TO MOVE STUFF IN
AND CHANGE THINGS AROUND.
- AH, THIS IS NICE STUFF.
WHERE DOES THIS GO?
- WE CAN PUT THAT IN THE CHINA.
CAN YOU GET THAT OUT FOR ME?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY CHINA
IS CALLED CHINA.
MAYBE THE CHINESE MADE IT UP.
PRETTY, RIGHT?
- THIS IS JUST FOR DECORATION?
- YEAH.
HAS TO BE SOMETHING
WITH CHINESE PEOPLE,
'’CAUSE THEY'’RE REALLY SMART.
- CAN YOU BRING MY CUP IN?
- YEAH.
[gasps]
DOOR!
JIONNI!
- WHAT?
- I JUST SPILLED
ALL YOUR COFFEE.
- [sighs]
DON'’T GET MARRIED, MARCO.
- [laughs]
- YOU TOLD ME
TO GET YOUR COFFEE.
I SPILLED IT EVERYWHERE.
- I JUST TOLD YOU
TO GET THE COFFEE, NOT THE BOX.
- I WANTED TO BRING
THE BOX IN.
OH, MY GOD.
I JUST RUINED THE LAWN.
- I ASKED YOU TO DO ONE THING.
I'’M SUPPOSED TO CARRY STUFF.
- CARRY YOUR OWN DAMN COFFEE.
- I'’M CARRYING THE BOXES.
- SO AM I.
- APPARENTLY NOT.
- HERE, YOU GOT A SIP LEFT.
- I DON'’T WANT IT.
- I'’M JUST REALLY CLUMSY TODAY.
JESUS.
OH!
[laughing]
- WHAT'’S WRONG WITH YOU?
- I JUST HIT MY CHIN.
- ON WHAT?
- WITH THE PLATE.
- ALL RIGHT, WHY DON'’T YOU
JUST SIT DOWN FOR A LITTLE BIT?
- OW!
I THINK THE WHOLE PROCESS
OF MOVING IS STRESSING ME OUT.
IT'’S JUST HARDER THAN I THOUGHT
IT WAS GOING TO BE.
IT SUCKS.
OH, MY VAGINA HURTS.
- I NO LONGER WANT TO BE BROWN.
- OKAY, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- BLONDE-ISH.
- "BLONDES HAVE MORE FUN"
MAKEOVER KIND OF THING?
- YEAH, I'’M GONNA HAVE
A MOMMY MAKEOVER.
MAKE ME LOOK FAKE SEXY,
LIKE ROGER SAYS,
'’CAUSE I DO NOTHING FOR HIM.
FALSE ADVERTISEMENT.
- OKAY.
SO YOU GUYS CAN ROLE PLAY LATER.
- EW.
- OKAY, READY?
- I REALLY NEVER EVEN LIKED
BLONDE WOMEN,
BUT ROGER'’S NOT INTO BLONDES,
SO HOPEFULLY
IF I DYE MY HAIR BLONDE,
HE WON'’T BE INTO ME
FOR A COUPLE MONTHS,
SO I CAN CONTINUE TO HEAL.
I JUST WANT TO LOOK HOT;
LEAVE ME ALONE.
- READY?
SURPRISE!
- I LOOK DIFFERENT.
- LOVE IT?
- I LOOK LIKE I BELONG
BACK UPSTATE NEW YORK.
I FEEL PRETTY.
[laughter]
I LOVE IT.
I FEEL LIKE A NEW WOMAN.
I'’M OBSESSED WITH MY NEW HAIR.
I FEEL DIFFERENT;
THAT'’S THE THING.
I WANT TO FEEL DIFFERENT
THAN WHEN I WAS PREGNANT.
I DEFINITELY NEEDED
TO FIND MY SEXY BACK.
I REALLY JUST NEEDED IT.
LOVE YOU GUYS, THANK YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
GO HAVE SEX.
- GO TO HELL.
[laughter]
- WHOO!
LET ME GET BACK THERE.
OW.
[grunting]
IT'’S MY BABY JESUS PAINTING.
I REALLY WANTED TO GET
A NICE JESUS PAINTING.
I JUST FEEL LIKE IT'’S IMPORTANT
TO HAVE SOMETHING JESUS
IN YOUR HOUSE.
I WONDER WHERE I SHOULD HANG
BABY JESUS.
IN THE FOYER?
I SHOULD BE
AN INTERIOR DESIGNER.
WHY DON'’T YOU COME IN,
TAKE A BREAK.
GOT A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
OKAY.
BABY JESUS.
- OH, MY GOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT IS THIS?
- IT'’S BABY JESUS.
- THIS ISN'’T SAINT ROSE.
PUT IT AWAY.
- JIONNI, IT'’S BLESSING
OUR BABIES.
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU'’RE LIKE THE ANTICHRIST.
YOU CAN'’T HAVE A PICTURE
OF JESUS IN OUR HOUSE.
- I AM NOT THE ANTICHRIST.
- WHERE YOU GONNA PUT THAT?
I'’M EMBARRASSED TO HANG THAT.
- ME AND JIONNI
HAVE TO COMPROMISE
ON WHERE WE'’RE GONNA
HANG THIS BABY JESUS,
BUT I WOULD LOVE...
- IN THE BEDROOM.
- TO HAVE BABY JESUS SOMEWHERE.
- I WOULD LIKE IT
IN THE BEDROOM.
WHAT'’S WRONG WITH THE BEDROOM?
- I WANT OUR GUESTS TO SEE IT.
- WELL, WHAT IF
SOMEONE'’S JEWISH?
- THIS IS MY HOUSE.
I'’M NOT DECORATING FOR THEM.
- NO JEWISH PEOPLE ALLOWED.
- THAT'’S NOT NICE.
- JUST KIDDING.
- [laughing] THAT'’S NOT NICE.
- ARE YOU--OH, MY GOD.
- JESUS IS BORN.
DID YOU EVER SEE...CHRISTMAS?
- CHRISTMAS?
- THIS IS THE CHRISTMAS PHOTO.
- YOU'’RE SICK.
I LIKE PICTURES
OF JESUS AND GOD.
I JUST DON'’T WANT IT
IN MY LIVING ROOM AND FOYER.
IT'’S A BIG--
WITH SHEEP AND STUFF.
- THERE'’S ONE SHEEP.
- IT DOESN'’T MATTER.
- AND A DONKEY.
- I DIDN'’T SEE A DONKEY.
- THERE'’S A DONKEY.
THERE SHOULD BE A DONKEY.
- I JUST DON'’T WANT IT
IN MY LIVING ROOM
WHILE I'’M WATCHING TV AND SEEING
A BIG PICTURE OF CHRIST.
- JESUS.
CHRIST IS THE FATHER.
WAIT, JESUS CHRIST.
WAIT.
- YOU GOT A PAINTING;
YOU DON'’T EVEN KNOW WHO'’S WHO.
- IT'’S JESUS.
- YOU WANT THE HOLY WATER
IN THE FRONT TOO?
- I WAS THINKING WE COULD
PUT IT SOMEWHERE IN HERE.
WAIT, I'’M TALKING.
BABE.
BABE, I'’M TALKING.
- IT'’S NOT EASY BEING A BABY.
GOT TO POOP ALL DAY.
[baby sneezes]
- OOH, GOD, I GOT IT
RIGHT IN MY EYE BALL.
GOOD ONE, GOOD ONE.
- HELLO?
- OH, MOMMY'’S HERE.
- HELLO.
BABY, WHO IS THAT?
- HOW DO I LOOK?
- WHO'’S THIS STRANGE LADY
IN OUR HOUSE?
WHO ARE YOU?
MY HOPE IS, WITH THIS NEW LOOK,
IS THAT MAYBE IT'’S A WHOLE NEW
OUTLOOK ON EVERYTHING,
MAYBE A NEW OUTLOOK
ON OUR SEX LIFE.
SO, WOW, WE'’LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
WHAT'’S YOUR NAME, LADY?
- SHUT UP.
- CAN YOU BE CASSANDRA?
- ROGER'’S TRYING TO SAY
THAT I'’M CASSANDRA RIGHT NOW
'’CAUSE I HAVE BLONDE HAIR,
AND I DON'’T EVEN LIKE THAT NAME.
IT'’S LIKE A TYPICAL
WHITE GIRL NAME.
- OH, MY GOSH.
IT'’S GONNA BE LIKE SLEEPING
WITH ANOTHER WOMAN.
- YEAH, BUT SAME RESULT.
- NOTHING?
- NOTHING.
- NO?
I THINK THERE GOES MY CHANCES
OF GETTING LUCKY AGAIN TONIGHT.
IT WAS KIND OF LIKE WALKING
INTO A LAMBORGHINI STORE.
YOU'’RE WELCOME TO LOOK,
BUT DON'’T DARE TOUCH,
UNLESS YOU'’VE GOT THE FUNDS
TO BUY THAT RIDE.
AND CLEARLY I DON'’T.
- I'’M HOT NOW.
- COUGAR STYLE.
- COUGAR?
THAT MEANS I'’M [...] OLD!
- COUGAR'’S STILL COMPLIMENTARY.
IT WOULD JUST PUT YOU
IN A LITTLE BIT
OF A HIGHER AGE BRACKET;
THAT'’S ALL.
- 50, 60?
- YEAH.
SO YOU'’LL BE A COUGAR ONE DAY.
YOU'’RE JUST NOT THERE YET.
- THANK YOU.
- YOUR MOTHER WOULD BE SO PISSED
IF SHE KNEW I WAS LETTING
THIS LADY HOLD YOU.
- EXCUSE--
- CASSANDRA,
I'’LL BE HONEST WITH YOU,
THE SEX LIFE
IS A LITTLE LACKING.
- DO YOU HEAR HOW HE'’S TALKING
ABOUT YOUR MOMMY?
- IT'’S TRUE.
BLONDES DO HAVE MORE FUN.
- SEE, BRUNETTES GET
THE JOB DONE, THOUGH.
- NO JOB STARTING
WITH A "B," THOUGH.
- YOU CAN'’T WIN WITH YOUR DAD.
- [laughs]
- SO THIS IS OUR FIRST
TIME OUT, WOMAN.
WE NEED TO BE PREPARED.
MEILANI'’S GONNA COME
TO DINNER WITH US TONIGHT.
IT'’S OUR FIRST
FAMILY DINNER OUT.
IT'’S SUPER CUTE,
AND I'’M EXCITED.
IF ANYONE, LIKE, SNICKERS
OR LOOKS AT ME,
I'’M GONNA BE LIKE,
"YOU ACT LIKE YOU'’VE NEVER SEEN
"A [...] CRYING BABY BEFORE.
"LIKE, GET OVER YOUR [...] SELF.
"EAT YOUR [...] FOOD
"AND STOP LOOKING OVER HERE.
"LIKE, THIS [...] IS NATURAL.
IT HAPPENS, PEOPLE.
GET OVER IT."
- AND THIS IS WHY MY DAUGHTER
WOULD NEVER EMBARRASS ME,
BECAUSE MY FIANCEE
WILL EMBARRASS ME
THREE TIMES AS MUCH.
- HAND WIPES,
EXTRA BABY WIPES,
EXTRA OINTMENT,
SUNSCREEN.
- WHAT DO YOU NEED THAT FOR?
- WE NEED EVERYTHING.
I ALWAYS CARRY EVERYTHING.
FORMULA, TYLENOL INFANT,
NOSE-CLEANER.
- GOOD GOD.
JENNI DEFINITELY
HAS OVERPREPARED.
WHEN YOU GO OUT NOW, IT'’S--
YOU BRING A WHOLE CAR-LOAD
OF STUFF WITH YOU.
- THERMOMETER, BRUSH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE GOT EVERYTHING?
SHOULD I BRING AN EXTRA OUTFIT
OR TWO?
- YOU HAVE MORE THAN ENOUGH,
AS ALWAYS SEEMS TO BE THE CASE.
- RATHER BE OVERPREPARED
THAN UNDERPREPARED.
- HOW AM I GONNA GET THIS
UP OVER THOSE STAIRS?
- I'’LL CARRY.
IT'’S FUNNY AND CUTE
HOW MUCH THINGS HAVE CHANGED
SINCE, YOU KNOW,
WE'’VE BECOME PARENTS.
LIKE, 9:30 AT NIGHT
IS VERY LATE FOR US.
- MAY AS WELL BE 1:00 A.M.
- IT IS.
LIKE, IT'’S LIKE,
I FEEL JUST AS TIRED
AT 9:30 AT NIGHT
THAN I USED TO FEEL
AT 4:00 A.M. LEAVING THE CLUB
AND GOING TO GET
SOME, LIKE, CHEESE BALLS.
- CLUB IS NOW A SANDWICH FOR US.
- YEAH, NO JOKE.
HOW YOU GONNA GO
OUT TO DINNER WITH US
AND PASS OUT?
- NOT A VERY GOOD DINNER DATE.
- JUST WANT TO FEEL SEXY.
- YOU ARE.
I THINK YOU LOOK AMAZING.
I THINK YOU BOUNCED RIGHT BACK.
- I'’M A LITTLE JIGGLY.
EVERYTHING ON ME,
FROM MY HEADS TO MY TOES,
IS JIGGLY.
- YOU DO IT FOR ME STILL,
BUT...
I'’M NOT SURE EXACTLY
WHAT YOU DO.
[laughs]
- I COULD BE BROKEN DOWN THERE.
- RIGHT, SO THE DOCTOR
SAYS SIX WEEKS.
WE ALSO KNOW THAT THE DOCTOR
SAID MANY PEOPLE ARE DOING IT,
YOU KNOW...
- BECAUSE THEY DIDN'’T CARE.
- OKAY.
THE DOCTOR ALSO SAID
YOU CAN'’T DRIVE FOR SIX WEEKS.
HOW MUCH DID YOU LISTEN TO THAT?
- I WAITED SIX HOURS.
- YEAH.
SO YOU USED YOUR ADVANTAGE
AND CONVENIENCE,
WHAT WORKS FOR YOU.
- DRIVING AND MY VAGINA
BEING STITCHED UP
ARE TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
- YEAH, EXACTLY.
[bleep],
YOU WON'’T DIE FROM.
DRIVING, YOU WOULD.
- MY VAGINA
COULD HEMORRHAGE AND DIE.
- I'’VE BEEN HEMORRHAGING
YOUR VAGINA FOR YEARS,
AND YOU HAVEN'’T DIED YET.
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT,
FOR A GUY THAT HAS BEEN
IN A RELATIONSHIP
FOR 4 1/2 YEARS
AND GETS LAID AS MUCH AS I DO,
THERE CAN BE NO QUESTION
OF MY LOVE FOR YOU.
- NO.
- HOWEVER, I DO TAKE
VERY LONG SHOWERS.
- STOP.
GOD.
- MOST PEOPLE CALL, LIKE,
A MOVING COMPANY
WHEN THEY MOVE.
- [laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
- [giggling]
I THINK IT LOOKS
BEAUTIFUL THERE.
WE HAVE TO FIND A HOME
FOR IT SOMEWHERE.
- I'’M NOT PUTTING JESUS CHRIST
ON OUR WALLS.
- WHY DO YOU SAY JESUS CHRIST?
HIS NAME'’S JESUS.
- I GET GOOSEBUMPS
EVERY TIME I LOOK AT JESUS.
- THAT'’S A GOOD THING.
IT MEANS HE'’S CONNECTING
WITH YOU.
- NICOLE, NEXT WEEK,
TUESDAY AND THURSDAY,
WE CAN'’T BE IN HERE.
- WHY?
WHAT HAPPENED?
- FOR INSPECTIONS.
- OH, AND THEN WHAT?
WE CAN MOVE IN?
- THEN WE GET THE C.O.
AFTER THAT.
- A C.O. IS A CERTIFICATE
OF "OPPOCANCY."
[laughter]
OCCUPANCY, OCCUPANCY.
- YES.
- OCCUPANCY.
- SAY IT.
- THAT'’S A WEIRD WORD.
- START OVER, SAY IT.
- CERTIFICATION OF OCCUPANCY.
- A CERTIFICATE.
A C.O. IS A CERTIFICATE
OF OCCUPANCY.
YES!
- NAILED IT.
- INSPECTION'’S NEXT WEEK.
IF EVERYTHING GOES GOOD,
THE STATE GIVES US
THE FINAL PAPERWORK,
AND THEN YOU'’RE GOOD TO GO.
- TWO MORE WEEKS
IN THE BASEMENT.
- NOW IT'’S IN
THE INSPECTOR'’S HANDS.
WE NEED A C.O.
TO MOVE IN THE HOUSE,
AND IF YOU DON'’T HAVE THAT,
YOU CAN'’T MOVE IN,
NO MATTER HOW PERFECT IT LOOKS,
NO MATTER
IF THE WATER'’S RUNNING,
IF THE ELECTRIC'’S RUNNING.
YOU NEED A C.O.
TO PASS INSPECTION
AND TO MOVE IN YOUR HOUSE.
ARE YOU WALKING AROUND
WITH THE GUY?
- YEAH.
- GREAT.
- THANKS.
THE INSPECTOR WON'’T
INSPECT THE HOUSE
WITH THE BABY JESUS POSTER.
HE'’S SACRELIGION.
- SACRILEGIOUS.
- RELIGIOUS.
[laughter]
- HOW DOES SHE--HER WHOLE BODY
HAS TO GO THROUGH THAT?
MY GOD.
THAT'’S WORK.
OH, THIS IS NOT GONNA FIT.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- IT'’S TOO TIGHT.
- I FEEL LIKE MEILANI'’S JUST
GROWING LIKE A BEAST RIGHT NOW,
'’CAUSE LOOK AT HER FATHER.
HE'’S ENORMOUS.
WHAT KIND OF BABY DO I HAVE?
- DON'’T KNOW.
THE FARMER'’S MARKET DOWNTOWN,
SEE IF THEY GOT SOME
BURLAP BAGS LEFTOVER.
- OH, MY GOD.
WE SHOULD PACK FOR DEER RUN
TOO TONIGHT.
- OKAY.
- WE'’RE GOING CAMPING
AT A PLACE I USED TO GO
EVERY SUMMER CALLED DEER RUN.
I'’M VERY EXCITED FOR TOMORROW,
BECAUSE I WANT ROGER AND MEILANI
TO EXPERIENCE
A SMALL PIECE OF MY CHILDHOOD.
IT'’S LIKE BARBECUE, FISHING,
THE CAMPING LIFE.
SO IT'’S REALLY BEEN
A TRADITION IN MY FAMILY,
AND I WOULD LOVE TO MAKE THIS
KIND OF PART
OF WHATEVER TRADITION
WE MAKE FOR OUR FAMILY.
- I CAN'’T WAIT.
I'’VE HEARD ABOUT DEER RUN
FOR YEARS NOW, YOU KNOW?
AND I CAN'’T WAIT
TO SEE WHAT IT'’S ALL ABOUT.
- SEXY BLACK BOOTS,
THIGH-HIGHS.
- THIGH-HIGHS?
FOR WHAT?
- IN CASE I NEED IT.
- WE'’RE GOING TO A CAMPGROUND.
- WHAT ABOUT FUR BOOTS?
- OH, GOD.
I DON'’T MIND ROUGHING IT
A LITTLE BIT.
- HE LIKES SLEEPING IN THE WOODS
NAKED ON A ROCK.
THAT'’S HIS DEFINITION
OF CAMPING.
- I SLEEP NEXT TO A ROCK
EVERY NIGHT.
- [laughs]
MOTHER-[...].
- 42 PAIRS OF SWEATPANTS
AND SOME GRANNY PANTIES.
- NOW JEWELRY.
- YOU'’RE GOING TO A CAMPGROUND.
I DON'’T THINK YOU NEED
ANY JEWELRY.
- I'’M THINKING
KIND OF COUNTRY VINTAGE.
- OH, GOD.
- BABE, WHAT DO YOU THINK,
TOO MUCH?
- WE'’RE GOING TO A CAMPGROUND.
YES.
SHOULD I BRING JEWELRY?
- MAYBE.
- I JUST DROPPED MY [...]
TO GET CLEANED,
SO I DON'’T KNOW
IF IT'’S DONE YET.
- HMM.
BRING, DID YOU--
YOU'’RE A--EW.
- WE GOT A BIG DAY
PLANNED TODAY.
WE'’RE GONNA GO SHOPPING
AND CAMPING.
- YOU WANT TO GO SHOPPING
WITH DADDY
AND BUY STEAKS FOR YOURSELF?
- WE'’RE GONNA HAVE
TO GET YOU SOME TEETH
SO YOU CAN EAT REAL FOOD.
MAYBE WE COULD TALK
TO AUNTIE NICOLE
ABOUT WHERE TO GET
SOME CHOMPERS.
- SO MEAN.
SO TODAY WE'’RE GOING CAMPING
AT DEER RUN,
SO I WOULD LIKE ROGER
TO GO TO LENNY'’S
TO PICK UP, YOU KNOW,
SOME ESSENTIAL GROCERIES
AND BARBECUE STUFF.
YOU KNOW, STEAKS, CHICKEN,
SHISH KABOBS,
ALL THE WORKS.
- WHEN I GET BACK,
IF YOU COULD HAVE EVERYTHING
LITERALLY READY TO PUT
IN THE CAR AND GO.
I'’M NOT GETTING THERE
AT MIDNIGHT.
THAT'’S ALL I'’M SAYING.
- WELL, I HAVE SOAP, FACE WASH.
WHAT DO YOU NEED, JUST DEODORANT
AND YOUR TOOTHBRUSH?
- YOU BROUGHT EVERYTHING
BUT A BALL GOWN.
- DON'’T KNOW IF I BROUGHT THAT.
I PACKED A LOT,
MORE THAN I SHOULD HAVE.
BUT I WANT TO LOOK FANCY
FOR CAMPING.
HE'’LL APPRECIATE IT
LATER IN LIFE
WHEN I'’M STILL HOT.
- HOTNESS IS NO GOOD
UNLESS YOU USE IT
FOR SOME SORT
OF SEXUALITY FEATURE.
IT'’S LIKE HAVING A LAMBORGHINI
WITH NO MOTOR, YOU KNOW?
YOU LOOK GOOD IN A WINDOW,
BUT SUCK OUT ON THE OPEN ROAD.
- DO YOU HEAR HOW HE TALKS
ABOUT YOUR MOMMY?
- [chuckles]
HEY, BABE.
WHAT IS IT?
- HER BASSINETTE THAT GOES
TO HER ORBIT BABY STROLLER.
DO YOU WANT TO PACK MY CAR
OR PACK THE COOLER?
- REMEMBER WHEN I SAID,
"HAVE EVERYTHING READY
WHEN I GET BACK"?
- I JUST GOT--I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO GO OUT THERE.
- TRY TO GET
THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- "REMEMBER WHEN I SAID...
NAH-NAH-NAH-NAH-NAH."
I CAN TELL ROGER'’S AGITATED.
I FEEL LIKE I HAD THE MAJORITY
OF THE STUFF READY FOR ROGER.
I HAD IT ALL BY THE DOOR.
CLEARLY THAT WASN'’T GOOD ENOUGH.
HI, BEAUTIFUL.
HI, BEAUTIFUL, YEAH.
SHE'’S JUST SO...
- I'’M IN A REAL HURRY HERE.
DON'’T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- YOU POOING?
NO.
NOT AFTER THE POO YOU HAD TODAY.
- SO I'’M PRETTY ANNOYED
RIGHT NOW.
I LOADED THE ENTIRE CAR.
I GET HOME, AND IT'’S LIKE
THERE'’S JUST THIS VERY RELAXED,
YOU KNOW,
"I'’M NOT WORRIED ABOUT IT;
YOU'’LL GET EVERYTHING DONE,"
TYPE OF THING.
- ALL RIGHT, I'’M READY.
I WAS WAITING FOR YOU.
- WAITING FOR ME?
I JUST LOADED THE WHOLE CAR.
- I'’M NOT GOING
WITH THIS ATTITUDE.
YOU DON'’T HAVE
TO GET ATTITUDE-Y.
I WOULD HAVE HELPED YOU
IF YOU ASKED.
- HOW ARE YOU WAITING ON ME?
THE CAR'’S DONE.
I'’VE BEEN WAITING ON YOU
TO PUT THE BABY IN THERE.
- JUST THE STROLLER.
- YEAH, I'’LL GET IT.
- OKAY.
THEN I'’M READY.
- I'’M FEELING
A LITTLE DISRESPECTED.
I FEEL LIKE
WHAT I ASKED JENNI TO DO
WAS REALLY PRETTY MINISCULE.
WE ENDED UP LEAVING
ABOUT FOUR HOURS LATER.
IT'’S 6:00, AND WE'’RE
GETTING ON THE ROAD.
I'’M GONNA BE IN THE BACK SEAT
WITH MEILANI,
AND WE'’RE ALREADY
OFF TO A BAD START.
WE'’RE ALREADY ANNOYED.
WE'’RE NOT STOPPING
ON THE WAY UP THERE.
- TO GIVE SOMEONE 40 MINUTES
TO GET READY--
- 40 MINUTES?
I WAS GONE FOR TWO HOURS
TO GO GET HE CAR AND BACK.
- THEY NEEDED A BREAK AT 5:30.
"WE'’RE NOT STOPPING,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH."
- ONLY REQUEST WAS WE GET
ON THE ROAD IN A TIMELY FASHION.
[overlapping arguments]
- AGREEMENT YOU MADE FOR US.
- THE IDEA WAS TO GET
ON THE ROAD AND GET MOVING.
- YEAH, BUT I DIDN'’T REALIZE...
- YOU'’RE JUST
LOLLY-DOLLYING ALONG...
- STOP, SERIOUSLY.
YOU JUST SOUND
LIKE SUCH AN ASS.
HI.
- HEY, LOOK WHO'’S HERE.
HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
- [sighs]
WE'’RE NOT GETTING ALONG.
I'’M JUST GONNA BE HONEST
AND LET YOU KNOW.
- OKAY.
- NOTHING ELSE IS NEW.
- ALL RIGHT, SO LISTEN.
LET'’S LET ALL THIS GO.
SHE'’S WHAT'’S IMPORTANT.
SHE'’S WHAT MATTERS.
- IT'’S SO PETTY.
- IT IS PETTY.
- AND WE GOT UP HERE
AT A REASONABLE HOUR.
- APOLOGIZE.
THE MAIN THING IS
THAT WE'’RE GOOD PARENTS.
WE'’RE UP HERE.
LET'’S TRY TO ENJOY IT.
TOMORROW'’S ANOTHER DAY.
- FAIR ENOUGH.
I DEFINITELY CAN SAY
THAT MEILANI HAS MADE US
BETTER PEOPLE
AND THAT WE'’RE BOTH TRYING
AS PARENTS AND IN A RELATIONSHIP
TO JUST BE BETTER PEOPLE.
AND WE HAD MAJOR PRIDE AND EGO
ISSUES IN OUR RELATIONSHIP,
AND STUBBORNNESS,
AND YOU REALLY CAN'’T HAVE THOSE
WITH A KID.
- YOU'’RE RIGHT.
NOW THAT WE'’RE PARENTS,
NOW THAT WE HAVE A CHILD,
I CAN'’T DO THAT ANYMORE,
YOU KNOW?
IT'’S SAD THAT WE STILL
HAVE THESE FIGHTS
AND WE STILL DO THIS,
AND I WANT TO MAKE THIS
A GOOD WEEKEND.
YOU KNOW, HOPEFULLY TOMORROW
WE WAKE UP
REFRESHED AND FEELING GOOD,
AND I CAN SEE WHAT DEER RUN'’S
ALL ABOUT.
I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- "NO STUPID PEOPLE."
LET'’S KEEP IT MOVING.
NO NEED TO STOP HERE.
CLEARLY WE'’RE NOT WANTED.
- ALL MY FAMILY
HAS MET ROGER,
BUT THEY HAVE NOT MET MEILANI.
SO WE'’RE GOING
TO MY COUSIN APRIL'’S CAMPSITE
SO WE CAN HAVE BREAKFAST
AND SEE MY FAMILY.
GOOD MORNING.
all: GOOD MORNING!
- NEIGHBORS.
- HI.
- OH, YOU GUYS
HAVEN'’T MET HER YET.
- NO, THEY HAVEN'’T.
- SHE GOT BIG, RIGHT?
- SHE EATS ALREADY
MORE THAN DAD DOES.
- DOES SHE REALLY?
- OH, GOD.
- SHE GOT UP THREE TIMES
LAST NIGHT.
8-OUNCE BOTTLES.
- WHERE'’S ALL THE FOOD?
- FOOD!
- YEAH, I KEEP HEARING
ABOUT THIS FRIED DOUGH.
- YEAH.
- IT'’S A BIG TRADITION, I HEAR,
IN THE MORNING UP HERE, HUH?
- THE TRADITION.
- JENNI HAS BEEN TELLING ME
ONE OF HER FAMILY TRADITIONS
IS EATING FRIED DOUGH,
IN THE MORNING, FOR BREAKFAST.
- DAN'’S GOT THE OIL GOING.
I AM READY FOR FRIED DOUGH.
- FRIED DOUGH
IS ALWAYS SPECTACULAR.
IT'’S MY FAVORITE THING.
I ACTUALLY THINK
IT'’S JUST PIZZA DOUGH
DEEP-FRIED WITH BUTTER,
POWDERED SUGAR,
AND CINNAMON ON TOP.
IT'’S AMAZING.
- HAVEN'’T HAD ONE OF THESE
SINCE THE BLUE HILL FAIR
BACK IN MAINE.
- OH, YEAH.
I USED TO EAT,
LIKE, 17 OF THESE.
- [laughs]
I FEEL GUILTY EATING ONE.
- NO GUILT,
NO [...] GIVEN.
I ATE IT AND ENJOYED IT.
- LITERALLY NO [...] GIVEN.
- SHUT--
[...].
WHEN I TEXT A PICTURE
TO MY TRAINER,
HE'’LL BE REALLY PLEASED.
JUST BE LIKE,
"HEY, HERE'’S MY BREAKFAST.
SEE YOU ON SUNDAY.
ALL RIGHT, ONE MORE.
THAT WAS GOOD.
LET ME SEE IF SHE'’S HUNGRY.
- WANT YOUR MAMA?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AWW.
"I'’M SO HUNGRY!"
- WHERE'’S THE BABA?
- "I'’M SO HUNGRY!"
- I'’VE NEVER SEEN A BABY
EAT THAT MUCH, EVER.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR MAYBE YOU.
[laughter]
- OH, YEAH, I WAS
A FRIGGIN'’ BEAST OF A CHILD.
I SAW MY PICTURES.
UP UNTIL, LIKE, 8 YEARS OLD,
I WAS A LITTLE PORKER.
I HAD ROLLS.
- LIKE A LITTLE SUMO WRESTLER.
[laughter]
- THAT'’S WHY THEY CALL IT
DEER RUN,
'’CAUSE THEY SAW YOU.
- WHAT IS THAT EVEN
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
YOUR OWN JOKES AT THIS POINT?
- YOU'’RE HIDEOUS,
AND THEY SAW YOU,
AND THEY RAN THE OTHER WAY.
- I'’M HIDEOUS?
- [laughing]
AS A BABY, YOU WERE.
- I WAS PUDGY.
- THEY THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONNA EAT '’EM.
- THEY PROBABLY DID.
- LET'’S PUT IT LIKE THIS.
I CAN'’T HOLD HER BARE-CHESTED,
'’CAUSE SHE LOOKS FOR A NIPPLE.
- YEAH, SHE DOES.
- SHE STARTS...
[laughter]
- MIKE, WERE YOU GUYS GONNA
COME TO MY HOUSE, OR NO?
ALL RIGHT.
TODAY WE HAVE MORE DELIVERIES
TO COME,
MORE FURNITURE TO PUT TOGETHER,
TAKE OUT OF THE POD.
SO IT'’S TIME TO BRING IN
THE REINFORCEMENTS,
'’CAUSE WE HAVE A LOT
OF STUFF TO DO.
I JUST TALKED TO THE TWINS.
THEY HAVE A BIG TRUCK FOR US.
THEY'’RE GONNA COME TAKE
WHATEVER'’S AT THE HOUSE.
SO THEY HAVE A FEW GUYS
TO HELP.
- OKAY.
- I'’LL GET IT.
- BEFORE JIONNI GETS BACK,
CAN WE PUT BABY JESUS
ON HIS BAR?
I DEFINITELY WANT TO PUT
THE BABY JESUS IN THE MAN CAVE,
JUST TO PISS JIONNI OFF.
AND I FEEL LIKE
IT WAS IN THE MAN CAVE,
THEN JIONNI WOULD THINK TWICE
ABOUT MAYBE GETTING TOO DRUNK.
THINK HE'’LL LIKE IT?
- NOT DOWN HERE.
[laughter]
- MY COUSINS AND FRIENDS
ARE GONNA COME HELP ME OUT.
THIS IS DEFINITELY THE A-TEAM.
I GOT MY COUSIN ALPHONSE,
MY COUSINS ANTHONY AND MICHAEL,
AND MY BROTHER JAMES.
GET OFF THE GRASS!
WE'’RE GONNA GET THIS DONE,
AND FINALLY I GET SOME HELP.
- ARE YOU GUYS GOOD BUILDERS?
- NO.
- OH, MY GOD.
- BABE, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- I'’M TAKING A LUNCH BREAK.
- RIGHT ON TIME.
- HEY, JUST IN TIME.
- WE'’RE HERE; WE'’RE DOING IT.
I BROUGHT YOU THIS,
THE CHRISTENING.
- UH-OH, NOW WE'’RE IN TROUBLE.
NOW THAT I GOT
THE WHOLE CREW THERE,
I'’M GONNA, YOU KNOW,
CHRISTEN THE BAR,
HAVE THE FIRST DRINK WITH THEM.
I'’VE BEEN ENVISIONING
THIS MOMENT,
AND I FINALLY GOT
THE GROUP OF GUYS TO DO IT.
WHO PUT JESUS CHRIST ON MY BAR?
[laughter]
OH, MY GOD.
- GETTING RELIGIOUS DOWN HERE?
- AH, THAT'’S NICOLE.
- OH, OKAY.
- OH.
- WHAT'’S THE PICTURE THING?
- BABY JESUS DRINKS WINE.
EVERYBODY DRINKS WINE.
THAT'’S HIS..."BLOOD."
- YOU'’RE STUPID.
- WANT TO SEE A MAGIC TRICK?
- FOR REAL?
- YEAH.
I'’M GONNA MAKE VODKA DISAPPEAR.
[laughter]
- FIRST PARTY.
I JUST COULDN'’T WAIT
TO SIT THERE,
SERVE MY DRINKS.
AND I GOT RED CUPS
TO DRINK OUT OF.
I DON'’T CARE.
AT THIS POINT, HEY,
IT'’S ALL WORTH IT.
- THIS IS THE FIRST OF
A LOT OF DRINKS DOWN HERE.
- THAT'’S IT.
- LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
GOOD LUCK; BEST OF LUCK.
- I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
I CAN'’T NOT DO ANYTHING.
- THAT'’S PUT TOGETHER.
- NICOLE, DO YOU WANT ME
TO UNWRAP THE COUCHES?
[cheering]
- I COULD SIT DOWN HERE ALL DAY.
AND YOU GOT THE TV.
- TO THE LIGHTS.
THANK GOD.
- THAT'’S IT, OKAY.
- WE NEED ANOTHER BOTTLE.
HERE WE GO.
THAT'’S THE SPIRIT.
NOBODY LIKES TO DRINK ALONE.
ALPHONSE WOULD BE DOING
A WET T-SHIRT CONTEST.
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- WHAT?
[laughter]
WE'’RE MOVING.
- WE'’RE WORKING.
- WE'’RE WORKING ON THE BAR.
- YEAH.
- IT'’S 3:00 IN THE AFTERNOON.
I'’M DEFINITELY ANNOYED
RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE JIONNI IS THE RINGLEADER
OF THIS ALL,
AND HE'’S HAVING EVERYBODY DRINK
AND GO CRAZY,
AND I'’M JUST LIKE, SERIOUSLY,
LIKE, YOU GUYS ARE SUPPOSED
TO COME HERE AND HELP US OUT,
NOT DRINK.
I MEAN, IT'’S NOT EVEN
OUR HOUSE YET.
I DON'’T EVEN THINK WE'’RE
SUPPOSED TO PARTYING HERE YET.
YOU KNOW WE'’RE STILL
MOVING IN, RIGHT?
WE DON'’T LIVE HERE YET.
- OH, WE DON'’T?
- NO.
- WE'’RE TESTING; IT'’S GOOD.
- THEY'’RE DOWNSTAIRS PARTYING.
- NO, THEY HAVE TO GET
THAT STUFF IN.
- I KNOW.
- DOLLAR BEERS.
WHAT IS IT, TUESDAY,
THURSDAY OR SOMETHING?
- I THINK THURSDAY.
- YEAH.
- THE BEST.
[laughter]
- LET'’S GO; BREAK'’S OVER.
- IT'’S NOT A BREAK;
WE DIDN'’T START.
- THE BOSS SPOKE; LET'’S GO.
- AW, DAMN IT.
NOW ALL THE ICE IS GONNA MELT.
COME ON, GUYS.
LET'’S GET THIS OVER WITH.
LIFT IT.
BANG UP THE WHOLE BOTTOM OF IT.
ARE YOU LIFTING?
I HEARD A LOT OF TALKING
BEFORE IN THERE,
BUT WE'’RE THE ONLY ONES
OUT HERE IN THE RAIN.
- LIFT AND TURN.
- LIKE A MAN.
- YOU GOOD?
- YEAH.
- I CAN'’T CARRY THIS.
- BACK.
GOOD JOB, YOU DID REAL GOOD,
I'’M REAL PROUD OF YOU.
THIS WAS A GREAT TIME.
- YOU GOT A FREE LUNCH.
- YOU SHOULD INVITE
ME OVER AGAIN.
- BYE, HOUSE.
- BACK TO THE BASEMENT.
- LAST NIGHT IN THE BASEMENT.
- I KNOW IT'’S NOT GONNA BE
THE LAST NIGHT OR DAY
IN THE BASEMENT,
BECAUSE WE STILL HAVE
A LOT TO DO.
WE HAVE TO MOVE
ALL THE FURNITURE IN.
WE'’RE WAITING FOR OUR C.O.
OUR HOUSE NEEDS
TO GET INSPECTED.
SO IT'’S GONNA BE,
LIKE, A COUPLE WEEKS,
SO I DON'’T KNOW WHY
HE KEEPS SAYING IT.
WAIT, IS THAT NINJA TURTLE THING
RIGHT HERE?
- NINJA TURTLE THING?
- YEAH, THE SEWER.
- OH, MY--
YOU'’RE AN INFANT.
GO, YOU'’RE NOT EVEN CLOSE TO IT.
- WHERE IS IT?
- GO.
- BABE, I'’M GONNA SCRATCH
MY CAR.
- GO, NICOLE, YOU'’RE 17 FEET
AWAY FROM IT.
- I'’M JUST MAKING SURE.
- A NINJA TURTLE THING?
ARE YOU REAL?
- THAT'’S WHERE THEY LIVED.
- OH, MY GOD.
- LORENZO.
WHY DO YOU DO THAT?
- LORENZO, EW.
- LORENZO, DO YOU WANT SOME HAM?
- WHY DO YOU--
- EASY THERE, LORENZO.
- LORENZO, STOP.
- MIGHT PASS OUT.
- STOP.
STOP IT.
LORENZO'’S JUST BEING
SO WEIRD LATELY.
HE JUST ALWAYS PUTS HIS FACE
IN ME AND JIONNI'’S BUTT,
AND IT'’S WEIRD.
ALL RIGHT.
- LAST NIGHT IN THE BASEMENT.
- BYE, MOM, THANK YOU.
- OKAY.
- GOOD NIGHT.
IT LOOKS EMPTY DOWN HERE.
SO, WALKING DOWN
INTO THE BASEMENT,
IT JUST HITS ME, YOU KNOW,
THAT WE'’RE ACTUALLY MOVING OUT
AND WE'’RE NOT GONNA BE LIVING
IN THE BASEMENT ANYMORE.
IT'’S SAD.
I DON'’T WANT TO LEAVE.
- OH, CHRIST, HERE WE GO.
- LET'’S JUST STAY HERE.
- ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR
[bleep] MIND?
- EASY HERE.
WE'’VE BEEN LIVING HERE
FOR TWO YEARS.
IT'’S LIKE WE'’RE MOVING ON TO
THE NEXT CHAPTER IN OUR LIVES.
COME ON, COME ON.
- NO.
- WHY CAN'’T I GO IN THE CRIB?
[Lorenzo whining]
LAST DAY IN THE BASEMENT.
- BUT YOU KNOW YOU'’RE
A LITTLE SAD TO LEAVE.
- NO, I AM NOT EVEN
REMOTELY CLOSE TO SAD.
GOOD NIGHT, LORENZO.
- DADDY CAN'’T SAY BOO?
OKAY.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
- LAST NIGHT IN THE BASEMENT.
- STOP SAYING THAT.
- ♪GOOD MORNING, GOOD MORNING ♪
♪ IT'’S TIME TO START OUR DAY ♪
♪ GOOD MORNING, GOOD MORNING
- IT'’S TIME TO GO HOME.
IT'’S SUPER SAD.
WE DON'’T GET THESE TIMES
VERY OFTEN.
AND I WOULD LOVE
MORE MOMENTS LIKE THIS,
THE SIMPLE THINGS.
IS SOMEONE WAKING?
DO WE HAVE A DIAPY TO CHANGE?
HOLY GREEN [bleep].
MEILANI IS HAVING
AN ASS EXPLOSION TODAY.
THIS IS WHAT WE CALL
AN EVERYWHERE POOP,
WHERE IT'’S UP THE FRONT,
UP THE BACK, IN THE CRACK.
IT IS JUST EVERYWHERE.
OH, SHE'’S STILL [bleep],
SON OF A BITCH.
- OOH, I GOT A WIND OF THAT.
WHEW!
- GOD DAMN IT.
- OPEN THAT WINDOW, WHEW.
DADDY GOT A WHIFF OF THAT ONE.
WHEW, DADDY GOT A WHIFF
OF THAT POOPIES.
WHOO-HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO.
- EW, IT GOT IN IT!
- WHAT?
- COME ON, HER HAND GOT IN IT.
MEILANI HAS DEFINITELY TAKEN
SOME MASSIVE [...] IN HER DAY,
JUST LIKE HER FATHER.
JUST SMELLED LIKE--
IT SMELLED SO BAD.
LIKE, THIS IS--
IT SMELLS LIKE A MAN POOP.
LIKE, MEILANI [...]
LIKE ROGER DOES.
LOOK AT THAT BELLY.
I DON'’T WANT TO GO.
I DON'’T WANT TO GO IN THIS RAIN.
IT'’S SO DEPRESSING.
WE HAD SUCH A GOOD TIME.
NOW WE HEAD HOME.
I DEFINITELY THINK WE'’LL BE
COMING BACK TO DEER RUN SOON.
- YEAH, I THINK SO.
I MEAN, AS LONG AS JENNI'’S
FAMILY IS HERE,
I THINK WE'’LL CONTINUE
TO COME BACK.
I MEAN, IT IS A FAMILY
TRADITION, YOU KNOW?
[baby farts]
- GOOD JOB, BABY.
[laughter]
BABY.
WHEW.
WE'’RE GONNA COME BACK EVERY YEAR
UNTIL YOUR TEETH COME IN,
AND THEN YOU WON'’T BE ALLOWED.
- THAT'’S MEAN.
- [laughing]
- NEXT TIME ON...
- SNOOKI AND JWOWW...
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I'’M GETTING REALLY BAD
CONTRACTIONS.
I'’M HAVING MY CONTRACTIONS,
AND THEY'’RE FIVE,
SIX MINUTES APART.
I CAN'’T SLEEP AT ALL.
WAIT, I'’M CRAMPING.
OW!
THIS PAIN IS NOT GOING AWAY.
- JUST BREATHE.
- I CAN'’T BREATHE.
AH!
GET OUT, GET OUT!
PLEASE HELP ME.
SOMETHING'’S NOT RIGHT.