[Nicole]
Snooki &amp; JWOWW...
I love you.
[coos]
I love my baby.
I love my kids.
It'’s so nice in here.
I forgot what it looked like.
Now that we'’re finally
in the house
and we'’re settled in...
There'’s only one thing
left to do.
Get married.
[Icona Pop'’s I Love It]
♪ I don'’t care ♪
♪ I love it
♪ I love it,
I love it ♪
♪I don'’t care ♪
♪ I love it
♪
♪ I don'’t care ♪
[Jionni]
Nicole,
did you guys ever figure out
what you'’re doing yet for Miami?
[Nicole]
When we get there Friday,
we'’re doing a spa,
and then we'’ll go out to dinner
and go out,
and then Saturday'’s
our pool party.
[Nicole voice-over]
I cannot believe we'’re getting
married in three weeks,
but first we'’re going to Miami
for my bachelorette party,
and so is Jionni,
but it'’s gonna be separate.
Like, he'’s gonna go with
his boys and do his own thing.
I'’m gonna go with my girls
and do my own thing.
[Nicole]
What are you doing?
[Jionni]
I really don'’t know yet.
I would like to do a pool party.
I would like to do a dinner,
maybe a club one night,
maybe golf.
Are we gonna fly together?
- Mm-hmm.
- Sit next to each other?
We'’re gonna cuddle
and have a mimosa together,
and then once we land...
- All bets are off?
- Peace.
Hello? Nonna'’s here.
[Nicole]
Morning.
[Janis]
Hi, Pumpkin. Missed you.
I haven'’t seen you
in two whole days.
So what'’s the plan
for your bachelor party?
I'’m gonna make
some bad decisions.
No, you better not.
I'’m telling you right now,
you guys better behave,
or I swear to God,
I'’ll kill you.
- And you?
- I retired.
I hung up my cup.
- We'’ll see.
[Jionni]
Yeah, we'’ll see.
[Janis]
You might get--go wild.
No.
I don'’t want to hear
any stories when you get back.
- No stories.
- All right.
[Nicole]
Janis is definitely concerned
about me and Jionni
going too crazy, you know,
maybe getting arrested.
I mean, normal things that a mom
would be nervous about.
What if you find someone
in Miami?
Oh, my God.
[woman]
Miami, here we come!
Yeah! Whoo!
[Nicole]
Babe, do I have any rules?
If we see each other,
we can'’t make it bad.
Can we pretend we don'’t
know each other, and be, like--
- Yeah.
- Wink at each other? Yeah.
The one unspoken rule,
just out of common courtesy
to our girls, is wear a rubber,
you know what I mean?
You'’ll be lucky
if I wave to you.
Okay.
[laughs]
I'’m, like, Bridezilla already.
- Good luck.
- Can I have a kiss?
What are you doing?
- Bye, babe.
- Bye.
I love you.
Jionni doesn'’t want
to kiss his wife in the lobby
of his bachelor party...
But I'’m making him.
[woman]
Jeez.
Wow.
[woman]
Oh.
[Jenni]
Oh...my...God.
[woman]
Wow.
[Nicole voice-over]
I just gravitate
towards the outside.
- Because, I mean...
- How gorgeous.
We'’re only gonna be in
this room to sleep and change.
Let'’s be serious.
I'’m single, ready to mingle.
[man]
The key works.
Whoa.
[man laughs]
[man]
Oh, boy.
Ooh-hoo, yup.
[Jionni]
It doesn'’t look like--
do we have a pool?
[Roger]
You can see the beach.
Is that the girls?
[man]
We got a bird'’s-eye view.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, God.
- All the girls are--
- They don'’t--they can'’t see us.
[man]
Oh, that'’s--
They got a whole
outside thing.
- What the--
- What the frig?
- Thanks for coming.
- A good start-off.
[Jionni]
Let'’s make some memories.
Let'’s do some bad decisions.
[cork pops]
[laughter]
[man]
Fill them up.
Come on. Fill them up.
Don'’t--don'’t--yup,
don'’t pick it up.
Just keep slopping it in.
[Jionni]
Let'’s start it off right.
Here'’s to five years
in the making for you, buddy.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Let'’s see how fast
we can get drunk.
Yeah.
- What should I drink?
- Tequila.
I am ready to get wasted
right now, but I'’m just nervous.
I don'’t know what I should drink
right now, and I don'’t want to,
like, drink too fast
to where I black out
and I don'’t even know anything.
Well, that'’s me.
[woman]
Cheers to Nicole.
all: Cheers!
Oh, my God.
[woman]
Bleh! Ew.
[woman groaning]
Oh, my God, rubbing alcohol.
I feel like I have to [bleep]
my pants right now
just because I haven'’t drank
in so long.
- I feel like my--
- Bubble guts.
I feel like my body
is rejecting alcohol
because it'’s, like,
a foreign body.
It doesn'’t know what it is.
Mm-mm. No.
So I kind of want
to take it easy,
but I want to go hard
at the same time.
I'’m four shots in.
I couldn'’t do it that way.
Oh, I'’m gonna throw up.
[laughs]
- Hey, let'’s go.
- Let'’s get out of here.
Let'’s go on the bus now.
- Let'’s go.
- No yelling on the bus.
- Oh, all right.
- Let'’s go.
[screams]
[Jenni]
I did not expect this bus.
It is an insane party bus...
[women cheering]
With smoke and lights
and alcohol,
and I'’m like, "Yup, I'’m really
not making it out tonight."
Holy [bleep].
- In a nightclub right now.
- Oh, my God.
Time out.
There'’s a pole there, guys.
Is that for safety?
[laughs]
Yay.
[Nicole]
Oh, I remember this place.
I used to get drunk and, like,
dance around here by myself
like an ass[bleep].
So right when I get to
Ocean'’s Ten, I mean, I'’m just
having flashback memories
of me drinking, going crazy...
[cheering]
Acting like a fat, drunken slob,
and I'’m like, "This is great.
This is gonna happen again."
Bring it on.
I ordered ten for the table.
Get prepared.
Bulldog, whoo!
Everybody drink.
One, two, three, go!
[woman]
♪ Ready, set, go
♪ We don'’t stop
until we'’re done ♪
Mom, get a big gulp.
♪ Start in three, two, one
Jenni, I want to see
you suck that whole thing down.
[woman]
You gotta drink
for ten seconds.
Ten.
[all]
Nine, eight.
Seven, six.
What are you doing?
Are you chugging?
- One, two.
- Ten!
Ew. You look like an octopus.
[Jenni]
It'’s been well over a year
since I'’ve been this drunk.
I'’m scared of drunk Jenni a
little because a switch goes off
and I like to beat
the [bleep] out of people.
So we shall see.
One!
Will you order another one?
[laughing]
- You'’re gonna be bombed.
- I'’m already drunk.
[laughing]
[Jionni]
Let'’s go, let'’s go,
we'’re here.
[man shouting]
[Jionni]
I'’m starting to rethink
what the hell I got myself into.
[Roger laughs]
- Rog, are you playing golf?
- I could care less about golf.
[overlapping chatter]
Mostly because I'’m a man,
and I don'’t have a vagina
between my legs.
- There you go.
- [laughs]
I'’m not a golfer, all right?
It'’s not something I enjoy.
I don'’t think
it'’s fast-paced enough for me.
But I'’m here to support Jionni.
I'’m here to do
whatever he wants to do.
I mean, if he wants to go
looking at butterflies today,
I will go.
I'’ll make the best of it.
[easy listening music]
♪
It doesn'’t get
better than this.
- This course looks sick.
- It'’s nice. It'’s real nice.
Great job, guys. Great job.
Nice hustle out there.
Nice hustle.
[Roger]
I guess I don'’t consider golf
a sport
because it'’s not a sport.
Let'’s be honest.
[bleep].
I mean, no chick has ever gone,
"I feel safe at night '’cause
I sleep next to a golfer."
[Nicole]
Joey! Joey'’s here!
[women cheering]
- Joey!
- Hi, girls.
- Come sit.
Now it'’s a party,
because now Joey is here.
Whose drink is this?
Does anybody have herpes?
No.
Joey is kind of like
our mascot for the weekend.
And this is when [bleep]'’s
gonna get crazy.
Wait, so the boys
are down here too?
Yeah,
but we'’re not hanging out.
- Sam is here too, right?
- Santa?
Sam.
Oh, yeah.
"Santa?"
[laughing]
[women chatting]
French fries, French fries,
French fries.
[laughing]
Cheers.
[woman]
Jenni? Oh.
- Jenni!
- Whoo!
[women cheering]
- [laughs]
- I love it.
Ah, [bleep]!
I'’m trying to get it
in her mouth.
I almost got it.
I want to try.
I'’m getting beat
by [bleep] French fries.
[laughs]
You'’ve got chicken
in your hair.
You'’ve got chicken in your hair.
[Jenni]
Becoming a mommy
and just not drinking
in God knows how long
has taken away all tolerance.
[Nicole]
Joey, help her. Get it out.
All I know is,
I'’m so drunk right now.
Thank God this ain'’t
my bachelorette, '’cause I'’m just
not gonna be the one to survive
at the end of the night.
[Nicole]
Ew.
[woman]
Are you all right, Jenni?
I want to take a nap.
I think Jenni'’s
the most drunk right now.
I mean, surprisingly, I'’m,
like, really good right now.
Like, I know what'’s going on.
Jenni, no.
She'’s the total opposite.
Can I talk on your phone?
Yeah.
[both laughing]
Hi, baby.
I need to get picked up.
Jenni doesn'’t even know
what planet she'’s on right now.
No.
Ow.
- Oh!
- What was that?
What was that?
You didn'’t even know
your name.
Uh-uh.
I was having a good time though.
I got fries in my crotch.
Oh, my God.
[Joey]
Oh, wait.
I want to show you my outfit.
[Nicole]
Okay.
[Shakti]
♪ Do the thang thang
♪ Freak your body, body
♪ Don'’t hurt nobody, body ♪
♪ You'’s a hottie, hottie ♪
♪ You know you got me,
got me ♪
♪ Let'’s get naughty,
naughty ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da,
da-da-da-da ♪
Oh, my God, look at Joey.
Oh, my God.
[yells]
[screams]
[Nicole]
So we get back to the hotel,
and now we all have to get nice
and pretty
because we'’re going out
to dinner.
And obviously, since I'’m,
like, really drunk right now,
we'’re dancing on the bed,
going nuts.
With his nuts.
- Ew.
- [laughs]
This weekend is about Nicole.
You'’re the best friend
in the entire world.
We'’re gonna have a great time
tonight, right, everybody?
- Whoo!
- Yes?
And here'’s to you.
Who would have thought
on the dance floor
four summers ago?
I agree.
Four summers ago in Seaside...
[overlapping chatter]
- Aw.
That we would end up here
in Miami
looking all as gorgeous
as we do,
'’cause we did not look
the same back then.
We'’ve evolved.
We'’ve all evolved.
- We all looked like [bleep].
- Yeah.
And I can'’t be more proud of
Nicole, and I love you so much.
Her dreams
are finally coming true.
- Aw.
- God bless. I love you.
- Love you.
- Aw.
Joey is the best bridesmaid,
even though
he'’s not a bridesmaid.
Bitch.
[Joey]
We'’re here. Let'’s go.
[Nicole]
This is too fancy for me
right now.
Jionni'’s not answering me.
Can you text him?
I'’m gonna text him my boobs.
We'’re in Miami. There'’s a lot
of [bleep] hot girls around.
There'’s more hot girls
than guys.
Fake boobs, beautiful.
They'’re so pretty.
So I know he'’s gonna
see all these girls,
so I just want to send him--
send him a picture reassuring
him that I'’m pretty too.
- Like, don'’t forget me.
- I don'’t think he will.
I know, but just saying.
I'’m hot too.
[Roger]
How'’s Nicole doing?
You talked to her?
Good. On and off.
[Jionni]
It'’s only one hour in,
first night in Miami,
and I have 20 missed calls,
missed text messages.
We set one rule:
Don'’t call each other.
Don'’t bother each other.
If I ignore her,
she'’s gonna get more mad.
If I reply, I broke the rule.
I can'’t imagine what the rest
of the weekend'’s
gonna be like with her
nagging me, but, you know.
I might just break the rule
and just say,
"Leave me the frig alone."
[chuckles]
Pretend we have accents.
Pretend we'’re from,
like, New England.
Pretend we'’re from New England.
[in accent]
Can we get a dirty martini?
I want it dirty, dirty.
[laughter]
He goes, "Gin or vodka?"
And Nicole goes, "Very dirty."
[Joey]
Yeah, she'’s done. She'’s gone.
Oh, she'’s Drenning.
She'’s Drenning.
- She'’s Drenning?
- Drenning. She'’s Drenning.
Me and Sam are laughing right
now because we can totally tell
that Nicole'’s starting to Dren.
Dren is Nicole'’s alter ego
when she drinks.
She is a crazy bitch.
Is her eyes going like this?
- Yeah. She'’s Drenning.
- Are they?
Oh, I'’m going home.
Whoo!
Dren is the person
that I met in Italy
when Jionni took off
and Nicole was trying
to beat me with her purse.
So where is he going, Jenni?
Where'’s he going?
He'’s running away from you.
Don'’t get near me!
- I'’m not touching--
- Don'’t touch me. I hate you.
Where'’s my boyfriend?
[Jenni]
Normally, I ignore Dren,
but because it'’s
her bachelorette weekend,
I'’ll hog-tie that bitch and lock
her in a [bleep] bathroom.
I'’m not babysitting tonight!
I want to go back
in the party bus and dance.
I called a cab.
I'’m so played out, like--
I hope she doesn'’t get mad
at me when I tell her.
I'’m seeing the writing
on the wall.
I'’m a mom. I can'’t hang.
I'’m tired,
and I just want to go back,
look at videos of Meilani,
and go to bed.
I called a cab.
Is that okay?
You'’re just losers
'’cause you can'’t hang.
- I love you. I love you.
- Love you.
We'’re gonna go to a club
and dance.
Bachelorette party!
See you guys in the morning.
I am so old.
I can'’t stay out.
It'’s not that I don'’t want to.
It'’s I can'’t. I'’m tired.
I'’ve been drunk all day,
and this is the time I'’m going
to bed with my daughter,
so I'’m like grandma in Miami
right now.
[electronic music]
[Nicole]
Miam!
♪
[women cheering]
You know, I haven'’t been
to a club in so long,
and I'’m kind of excited
to go and dance.
Meow, meow.
Jenni already crashed.
If this
wasn'’t my bachelorette party,
I would probably go
and sleep too,
but, I mean, rally.
Samantha Giancola, let'’s go.
This is the last time
that we'’re ever gonna do this,
and we should all just [bleep]
rally.
[bleep] it, and let'’s just go.
[thumping dance music]
[Joey]
Is this a strip club?
Samantha, is this a strip club?
So when we get to E11EVEN,
right away I see boobs--
girls'’ boobies on stage.
And their boobs are, like,
bouncing everywhere,
and I realize
we'’re at a strip club.
[electronic music]
♪
[woman]
They'’re naked. Strippers!
♪
I feel so classy at this club!
[woman]
Oh, my God.
♪
If Giovanna ever ends up
in this [bleep] place,
I'’ll [bleep] rip her throat out.
[woman]
Her tits are out.
♪
[women cheering]
[woman]
That'’s pretty cool!
What if she had her period?
She'’s got her period!
Come on now!
[Nicole]
Her tampon'’s gonna fall out.
[Jionni]
Everyone'’s pumped up to go out
except me and Roger.
I just need to find a second
wind '’cause I am beat right now,
but I don'’t want
to let anybody down.
We'’re gonna keep going.
I told the one guy, like,
"Send every hot broad up here."
It'’s like shooting fish
in a barrel.
[electronic music]
♪
The amount of alcohol being
consumed is--is--yeah.
♪
[Roger]
Girls everywhere, so my first
inclination is no look-ie,
no touch-ie, no see-ie,
no evil.
- I wasn'’t looking.
- It'’s the backdrop.
It was the backdrop
for the environment.
- Yeah.
- For the setting.
♪
Some of my single friends,
they'’re frigging dry humping
on the dance floor.
These guys are going nuts.
♪
I don'’t know the last time
I partied like this.
I'’m, like, banged up.
I'’m hurting.
I'’m tired.
What am I,
some kind of jerk-off?
Like, it'’s my bachelor party,
but I'’m waiting
for the night to be over.
As I look up, there'’s
a "Rest in Peace, Jionni" sign
bannered on the wall.
Who played that sick joke?
I'’m not dead.
You know, I'’m still here.
I didn'’t die.
We'’re about to leave.
[Roger]
I definitely feel like
I can'’t hang like I used to.
When you'’re in a club,
you can'’t hear anything.
[Jionni]
And I'’m on the verge
of blacking out as it is.
We might as well call it
a night and,
you know, start heading back.
[man]
Good night.
[Nicole]
I will twist your nipples.
I'’m gonna pee on somebody.
What time are we going
to the pool?
I don'’t know,
but I'’ll kick you in the face.
All right,
we'’re getting in
'’cause I'’m gonna [bleep] piss
all over your [bleep].
Everybody'’s getting
on the party bus,
and oh, my God,
we'’re all just drunk.
Everybody'’s falling
all over the place.
We'’ve been going so hard today.
Joey, I don'’t know
what'’s going on.
[Joey]
We'’re going home.
[Nicole]
Are you [bleep] kidding me?
Getting back to the hotel,
I mean, it'’s all a blur.
We were all drunk.
- Where are we going?
- We'’re going home.
You don'’t want us to get
new shoes.
I was just a hot mess.
My boobs hurt.
Are you two ser--
are they serious?
- Are you wearing underwear?
- No.
You'’re not?
Get that thing away from me.
[Jionni]
I wake up next to Kali
with no underwear.
He'’s got no shirt on.
It just means
we had a good night.
My head'’s pounding.
I don'’t feel good at all.
I might have
to sleep a little bit.
Waking up this morning,
I just feel sick.
I'’m gonna die.
Like, my stomach'’s turning,
and I feel like I'’m gonna vomit.
[Jenni]
I think I'’m hurting?
I cannot imagine
what these bitches feel like.
I don'’t know how I'’m alive.
I need Jesus.
[Nicole]
I just threw up in the shower.
- You did?
- Yeah.
- Do you feel better?
- Not really.
[Nicole]
I don'’t know
how I'’m gonna drink today.
Why am I so old?
I'’m just projectile vomiting,
like,
chicken wings, vodka, alcohol.
It'’s legit, like,
disgusting puke.
- Never throw up.
- That'’s so weird.
This just shows old age.
[groans]
Every time I sit up,
the world spins,
and I want to, like,
throw up right away,
so I literally need an army
to get me out of bed today.
- I feel so nauseous.
- You'’re gonna be fine.
[woman]
Do you want, like,
Tums or something?
I'’m having vitamin C.
Joey'’s doing my makeup.
Jenni'’s brushing my hair.
You know, I'’m trying
to drink mimosas to feel better
because if you'’re hungover
and you keep drinking,
you'’ll be fine again,
so at this point,
I'’m just trying to able to
get out of the fricking door.
Should I get a bucket
just in case?
No.
[man]
Here we go.
[Roger]
So we pull up,
and this boat is massive.
It looks like
the Titanicsitting there,
and my only hope is that later
I can find a nice, dark room,
and Jionni will let me
paint a picture of him naked.
[chuckles]
- Hi, there. Welcome aboard.
- How you doing?
- How are you?
- How are you doing?
- Beverage, sir?
Let'’s--let'’s go up
to the top.
I don'’t know, I think
I need a little more room.
[Jionni]
Oh, my God. How are you?
Dude, this [bleep] boat
is [bleep]--
Huge.
So we'’re on this amazing yacht,
and you would think that,
you know, there would be girls
in bikinis and, you know,
crazy stuff going on.
No, it'’s just a big--
big sausage fest.
It'’s a Vienna sausage fest
with my little mini Guinea.
For real though,
are you ready?
I got some time.
[laughs]
- Ever think we'’d be here?
- What?
Ever think we'’d be here
doing this five years ago?
Never.
I--I'’ll be
straight-up, man.
I thought--I thought Jenni
was probably a one-night stand.
I'’m sure you thought
the same thing.
And here we are,
you know what I mean?
I mean,
how our lives changed.
You got two beautiful kids.
I'’ve got one.
It'’s crazy, huh?
Yeah, it'’s crazy.
How things turn out.
It made my life better.
It was a long--
[chuckles]
it was a long journey
to get there, but...
Who would have ever thought,
you know what I mean?
[Jionni]
If somebody told me, you know,
five years ago,
my one-night hookup would turn
into this, I'’d call them a liar.
I'’d punch them in the head.
I wouldn'’t want it
any other way.
No. Absolutely.
Standing up here on this yacht
looking at the view.
Yeah.
I love you, Bernard.
Thank you, Mr. Matthews.
[Nicole]
So we'’re getting back
on the party bus
because we'’re going
to the pool party today, and,
you know, I still feel a little
sick, a little nauseous,
but I'’m just gonna keep drinking
because this is my bachelorette
party, and that'’s what you do.
Yeah!
[cheering]
Wow! That'’s enough.
[electronic music]
♪
[screams]
- Whoa!
- Turn.
[Bleep] it.
I thought we hit someth--
Whoa!
[woman]
We'’re running someone over.
- We just killed someone.
- I know.
- Bye.
[Nicole]
We get to the pool party,
and right away,
it'’s just more drinking.
Just more drinking.
This weekend is one big blur.
I don'’t know how I'’m alive.
- Nicole?
- What?
You think I should put on
my bikini to liven things up?
Yeah, put on your bikini.
We need to get this party
started.
Okay.
I'’m gonna go
behind the shed though.
I don'’t want to go
anywhere far.
Joey'’s, like, the mascot
of the bachelorette party.
He just wants everybody
to have a good time.
He keeps the party going,
thank God,
because, you know,
everybody'’s hungover right now.
[indistinct, shrill] bitch!
Let'’s go.
- Lemon drops.
- Thank you.
Spin it, Nicole.
Okay.
I'’m so excited to get married.
I mean,
this is what I'’ve always wanted.
I wanted to find a beautiful
tan Italian boy
to have beautiful
tan babies with.
Obviously, me and Jionni,
we'’re already a family,
but to make it, like,
official and get married,
I just can'’t wait for that.
It'’s my fairy tale.
Hi, everyone.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I just wanted to say
I love you all,
and it means the world to me
that all of you
are here right now because
it means that you love me.
I love you all so much,
and thank you for coming
and experiencing this with me
because I'’m getting
[bleep] married.
[all cheering]
- Salut.
- Cheers.
Salut.
[woman]
Go, Helen!
[all cheering]
[Nicole]
Joey is a hot mess.
He'’s just going crazy like
it'’s his last weekend single.
Yeah.
[all cheering]
Of course,
Joey starts stripping,
and he'’s literally
going crazy.
Joey is wasted right now.
[electronic music]
♪
Wasted.
[women cheering]
♪
I have seen more of Joey'’s ass
in the last day
than I'’ve seen Roger'’s ever.
Yeah. His ass and balls.
Whooh.
[Nicole]
Jell-O shots.
[screams]
So we get to the Clevelander,
and I'’m like, Holy [bleep].
Why weren'’t we here before?
This is, like, a huge party.
They have a DJ.
Everybody'’s drinking,
going crazy.
[high-pitched]
♪ Everybody dance now
This is the perfect place
to be right now.
[electronic music]
Jenni, good for you.
You can still break it down.
I'’m trying to
pull out the old moves.
[Jenni]
I broke a hip.
She broke her hip.
♪
[woman cheering]
Yo, look at this party.
They'’re having a whole party.
Is there a bachelorette
in this room somewhere?
[Joey]
Her name is Nicole Polizzi.
[women cheering]
[man]
We'’re gonna bring Nicole
up on stage.
This is tradition, Nicole.
Who'’s giving me a lap dance?
[man]
We'’re gonna find out.
- Joey...
- Oh, thank God.
- This song is
repeated, my friend.
all: Joey! Joey! Joey!
I'’m not gonna let any man
strip for me unless it'’s Joey.
And I wouldn'’t even call him
a man.
He just has a penis.
[women cheering]
[man]
♪ Shake, shake that ass
♪ Shake that ass
- [squeals]
- ♪ Shake, shake that ass
♪ Shake that ass, girl
♪ Shake that ass, shake
♪ Shake, shake, shake,
shake, shake ♪
[Nicole]
Joey is definitely born
with these moves.
I mean,
you can'’t learn these moves.
[women cheering]
[man]
♪ Shake that ass, girl
[clears throat]
I'’m blushing.
♪
Joey'’s ass is literally
in my face right now.
It'’s just like, "Oh, my God,
a little too close.
I hope
he doesn'’t [bleep] on me."
I hope you don'’t get pinkeye.
God, I'’m gonna get pinkeye.
I'’m gonna.
He'’s gonna fart,
and it'’s gonna--
the particles are gonna
fly right in my eye.
[man]
♪ Shake that ass, girl
[women cheering]
[man]
Peace.
Hey, to Jionni.
[all]
Jionni!
[man]
Congratulations, man.
[Roger]
Any idea what the girls
are doing tonight?
[Jionni]
Not really.
I know Nicole'’s been
having fun and [bleep].
She needed it.
She was real, like,
worried and stuff, like--
but I told her absolutely not.
Right before I left, she
was like, "I don'’t want to go.
I'’m gonna mi--"
I'’m like, "Nicole.
You'’re gonna have one drink."
I miss my kid horribly,
but be a realist.
We'’re here for two days.
My mom'’s with her, you know.
Yeah, that'’s what I said.
I do really, really miss her
though.
Can I have
everybody'’s attention?
[glass clinking]
Jionni, I want to welcome you.
You have brought
so much love into the family,
and our two grandchildren,
Lorenzo and Giovanna.
[Jionni]
I never thought my life
would turn out so good.
Like, my kids are healthy.
They'’re beautiful.
Nicole'’s unbelievable,
and things just--
it'’s crazy how things happen,
and I'’m very, very lucky.
I wish you guys the best.
Health, happiness, and love.
I love you, Son.
[cheers and applause]
Thank you.
After dinner, we have a table
set up downstairs at the lounge,
and it'’s pretty sick right now.
- I mean, it'’s packed.
- It'’s packed.
- There'’s gabagool everywhere.
- [chuckles]
Papa Snooki,
you gonna have some shots?
- I need three.
- Down the hatch.
[electronic music]
♪
Every girl here
is at least 5'’7", 5'’8".
I feel like a child.
I do feel like a child.
Are you wearing
your lift shoes?
No.
[Jionni]
Did you realize that every girl
was a foot and a half taller
than me?
[laughing]
Yes.
Like, now
I'’m just embarrassed.
[woman]
You need to have fun, brother.
[Roger]
The one that was 7 feet tall
with an Adam'’s apple that looked
like a basketball.
She looked at you and said,
"I'’ve got a huge,
hairy pair of balls.
Would you like to touch them?"
That'’s what she said.
[deep voice]
"Do you want to have fun
later?"
[laughing]
[deep voice]
"You want to scratch my balls?
[high-pitched]
Okay.
[indistinct chanting]
[men cheering]
So now we'’re heading
to a club.
We got the party bus,
and we are gonna go even harder.
It'’s our last night, and
we got to make it count, so...
Maybe you shouldn'’t associate
"harder"
with this club we'’re going to.
[electronic music]
♪
This is like
a club-slash-strip club.
This ain'’t your average,
you know, strip-y place.
I always said to Nicole
I wasn'’t going to a strip club,
but, you know,
I went to a regular club,
and the strippers came here.
There'’s a big difference.
This is the bachelor.
Give him a motorboat.
- Motorboat?
- Motorboat.
It'’s your bachelor party.
You'’re very pretty.
I can'’t do that.
- You'’re very pretty though.
- Yeah, that'’s great.
Where'’s Snooki and JWOWW?
Not with us.
[man]
♪ Three, two, one, drink
♪
[Roger]
I can handle a strip club.
It'’s not like I'’m gonna see
boobies
and be like, "Oh, my God,
there'’s other boobies out there.
I got to go be with those."
I feel like that'’s a
lot of choreography
to work out beforehand.
♪
Like, I'’m at that point
of no return.
I'’m hammered, okay?
I didn'’t even see a booby.
I swear to God,
I have no idea of what happened.
You having fun?
My mom told me,
"Don'’t talk to strippers."
[woman]
Whoo!
Party'’s here.
[electronic music]
♪
- I wasn'’t ready for that.
- I was not ready for that.
And everyone'’s just like,
"[bleep].
- Where the [bleep] are we?"
- Yeah.
Look, Snooki!
[screams]
So there'’s this creepy guy
right now in a diaper.
He looks like a baby, and
he has this weird face mask on,
and he'’s trying to party
with us,
and I'’m like, "No, no, no, no.
You'’re [bleep] weird.
Get away from me."
I'’m sorry!
♪
- Hold this.
- I got it.
- Hold it.
- I got it. I got it. Look.
♪
You'’re up next.
No, get the [bleep] out
of here.
It'’s mine.
♪♪
At this point, I feel like
I drank more than I wanted.
Like, I'’m dying.
Oh, yeah, party bus, whoo!
Let'’s go.
[woman]
Thank you.
I would like to say that I
love my best friends right now.
- Very nice, that'’s very nice.
- I have to pee.
[Nicole]
Wait. Can I pee somewhere?
[yelps]
[indistinct chatter]
Amy, I got to pee,
but when I pee,
you'’re gonna hang out
with me.
- Okay.
- Hey, that worked.
We get back to the hotel,
and I mean, at this point,
I'’m bombed.
I have no idea what'’s going on.
I just hope I wake up alive
tomorrow.
Get off.
[laughter]
Get the [bleep] off.
Oh, my God.
You know, I'’m, like,
on another planet.
I have no idea.
Oh, my God, can I get
to these [bleep] strawberries?
I'’m so hungry.
[whimpers]
Please?
Carly?
I got it. I got it.
There you go.
[overlapping murmuring]
You have chocolate
all over your face.
I don'’t care.
No, I--
it looks great on you.
I think I look classy.
With chocolate
all over your face?
- Yeah.
- It'’s a good look for you.
I'’m definitely happy that,
you know, my girls
stayed up with me all night,
even though they were exhausted,
just to celebrate the last night
of my bachelorette party.
Do I have chocolate on my lip?
[woman giggles]
There'’s a huge chunk
on her lip!
It looks like blood.
Just trying to pretend
I'’m dead.
I'’m so dead.
I dead.
[laughs]
- What?
- "I dead."
I meant to say, "I was dead."
"I dead."
The perfect ending
to a perfect weekend.
Oh, you guys win
bridesmaids of the year.
- Yeah, you do.
- Snug as a bug in a rug.
Love you.
We'’re gonna leave her out here
like this?
- Yeah.
- All right.
It'’s warm.
Bridesmaids of the year gone.
Mom?
[snorts]
[Nicole]
This episode of
Snooki &amp; JWOWW...
[Jenni]
Continues now.
Just drinking straight
for two days,
I don'’t know how I'’m gonna get
on this Goddamn plane.
You'’re still drunk.
[cork pops]
- [screams]
[Nicole]
I don'’t know
how I'’m gonna even pack my bag.
I'’m drunk,
but I'’m not a good drunk.
- I'’m, like, throw-up drunk.
- Yeah.
- I--
- Dead?
I dead.
[both laugh]
I'’m glad
to see everyone alive.
[Nicole]
I'’m glad.
[Jenni]
How are you feeling?
Like [bleep] ass [bleep].
Oh, it'’s wet.
What the [bleep]?
[overlapping murmuring]
[woman]
This whole floor is wet.
It'’s all--
Do you want breakfast
and see the boys?
I don'’t want to see the boys.
Oh, my God.
I'’m gonna die.
You'’re hurting, huh?
[Roger]
You look like death. You do.
I'’m--I'’m still drunk.
Like, I'’m not even hungover.
I'’m drunk, like, it'’s--
it'’s--I'’m gonna throw up.
Now I got to go fly
on a plane.
I feel like the walking dead.
- Ah, I look like the [bleep]--
- [groaning]
I feel like if I walk,
I'’m gonna vomit everywhere.
The world is spinning,
and, yeah,
you'’re being
a great bridesmaid right now.
[thud]
- Ow.
Oh, [bleep].
- Hit the key, please.
- Morning.
- Right here or over there.
We'’ll sit here.
[woman]
Oop, oop, oop.
Morning, ladies.
You think that these things
are easy to control,
and they'’re not.
- I'’m gonna go.
- Good morning.
Hey. How you feeling?
I'’m hurting. How are you?
I'’m gonna throw up.
Back to reality.
I miss my kids. I'’m ready.
We'’re getting married
in three weeks.
- Less than three weeks now.
- Do you regret it?
Like, do you still
want to marry me, or...
Or did you find somebody
out here?
I think he'’s trying
not to talk.
It'’s a good bachelor weekend
then.
[laughs]
What? What'’d you do?
- I'’m just laughing.
- Why you laughing?
I had a fun weekend.
I'’m just laughing.
- What?
- Thank you.
- [laughing]
- I'’m just laughing.
What'’d you do?
What didn'’t he do
is more the better question.
[chuckles]
I hate them.
So right when the girls
get down there,
you know the questions
start coming,
and it'’s just like,
"What'’d you do?"
But me and Roger
didn'’t even come close
to doing anything
with girls.
I don'’t even know
if I talked to any girls.
Did you get a lap dance
from anyone?
Jionni!
Jionni, did you get
a [bleep] lap dance?
- Did you?
- Jionni.
No, you sicko.
You know, I can'’t imagine what,
you know,
they'’re thinking in their head.
Bad things.
Like naked strippers on you.
Me and Roger
are just messing with them.
I'’m not asking about your--
I didn'’t care what you did.
Yeah, but if you ask,
I'’ll tell you.
- I want to know what you did.
- I don'’t care.
It'’s supposed to be like that.
It'’s supposed to be a--
I think the concept behind
coming down,
bachelor, bachelorette,
and splitting up was you girls
get to have your fun
and go do what you want to do.
Guys get to--
we don'’t ask questions,
you don'’t ask questions.
- I ask questions.
- No, but there'’s questions.
Well, then why didn'’t
we just have it together?
Why didn'’t we just do everything
together?
What was the point?
We could have.
That would have been
a lot of [bleep] fun.
[laughter]
You'’re so mean.
Did you get a lap dance though?
No, I did not get a lap dance.
Jionni, just tell me.
I'’m not--
I didn'’t get a lap dance.
If you'’re standing,
it'’s not a lap dance.
Did you dance with someone?
- You don'’t even dance with me.
- [laughing]
Jionni, did you dance
with someone?
Nicole, I didn'’t even know
I was at a strip club,
first of all, okay?
I don'’t remember anything
I did.
Oh, you didn'’t see tits
everywhere?
No, I didn'’t see tits.
I don'’t even--I don'’t think
I even saw a stripper.
You saw boobies.
You went to the club I went to.
- No, I didn'’t.
- There are boobs everywhere.
Boobs everywhere, literally.
Boob here, boob there,
boobs, boobs, boobs, boobs.
Why don'’t you ask
some of my friends?
I couldn'’t see, so I literally
couldn'’t look at boobs.
Why, '’cause there were boobs
in your face? Nipples?
No, '’cause I was so drunk.
"Nipples." What?
Did you miss me at all?
No, not even a little bit.
- Did you think about me at all?
- Nope.
[Jionni]
Club E11EVEN apparently
was a good time.
- I don'’t remember--
- Oh, you don'’t remember.
So how do you know
if you didn'’t touch a nipple?
All right, technically I don'’t
know if I didn'’t touch a nipple.
[gasps]
Jionni!
Don'’t say that.
- I didn'’t touch nipple, dude.
- Oh, my God.
If I watch this and
there'’s nipples in your face...
Nicole, if I touched nipple,
I think somebody would tell you.
I'’m gonna find the girl
and kill her.
Ready to get married, babe?
Three more weeks.
We'’re getting married
in three weeks.
I feel like
he'’d be more excited,
but the hangovers
are cutting in.
We'’re getting married.
[cooing]
Get out of here.
It'’s still my bachelor party.
- What?
- It'’s still my bachelor party.
All right,
pretend I'’m a random.
[Roger and Jenni laugh]
Is that what they were doing?
Wait, you'’re wear--you'’re
wearing way too many clothes.
[Roger and Jenni laughing]
Get out of here.
That'’s what they were doing
to you.
I'’m ready to get out of here.
I want to see my baby.
[Roger]
Yeah, I want to go
see my little girl.
Let'’s never attempt
to do this again ever.
No.
Let'’s not leave
our children ever again.
I'’ll come back next year.
Next year? What?
Jionni.
You'’re not ready.
You'’ll be back in nine months
to see your kid.
You'’re not ready
to be a husband.
[Jenni]
Roger!
What'’d he say? What?
He'’ll be back in nine months
to see his kid.
Jionni! Jionni.
Stop.
Stop. Don'’t tell me that.
[Jenni]
Next time on the final episode
of Snooki &amp; JWOWW...
I baptize you
in the name of the Father
and of the Son
and of the Holy Spirit.
Oh, my God, we'’re starting.
We'’re starting.
- Let'’s go.
- I'’m missing it!
Are we saying, like, "I do"?
[Nicole voice-over]
I'’m gonna [bleep] my pants.
You'’re my dream.
It'’s snowing!