- PREVIOUSLY ON...
- SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW.
- I'VE GOT AN INDUCTION DATE.
SATURDAY NIGHT AT 8:00 P.M.
- WHEE!
- GOOD LUCK, ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- BYE.
- BYE, BABY.
- OH, MY GOD,
I THINK MY WATER JUST BROKE.
OW.
- BREATHE, BABE.
- OHH!
- JENNI!
[baby cries]
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
*
* I DON'T CARE
- * OH, YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY
* SUCH A BEAUTIFUL DAY
- WELCOME TO THE BIG GIRL CLUB,
BABE.
SEEING JENNI HOLD OUR DAUGHTER,
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT I HAD ANY PART
IN MAKING SOMETHING SO PERFECT.
I'VE GONE ON RECORD MANY TIMES
AS SAYING I DON'T BELIEVE
IN LOVE AT FIRST SIGHT.
OH, HOW WRONG WAS I?
I AM IN LOVE.
- ARE YOU HUNGRY?
SHE'S JUST LIKE,
"GIVE ME THE BOOB."
CAN YOU CUT MY BACK,
AND I'LL PUT A BLANKET
OVER ME REAL QUICK?
- YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
- SHE'S ALL READY FOR THE BOOB.
- YEAH.
- I'M BREASTFEEDING MEILANI
RIGHT NOW,
AND IT'S GOING REALLY WELL.
SHE'S LATCHING RIGHT ON.
I'M HOPING THAT BECAUSE SHE'S
TAKING TO IT SO AUTOMATIC,
THAT IT'S GONNA BE AN EASY RIDE
FROM HERE ON OUT.
- CAN YOU IMAGINE BEING MEILANI?
IT'S LIKE, COMING OUT
TO AN ALL-YOU-CAN-EAT BUFFET.
- IT REALLY IS.
THEY ARE HUGE.
BUT THEY'RE FAKE HUGE.
- THEY ARE FAKE HUGE.
THERE'S--THEY'RE--
THEY'RE PURCHASED.
- YEAH.
- YOU DID A GREAT JOB.
YOU DID.
- NO, I DID NOT.
I SOUNDED LIKE...
- YOU DID A GREAT JOB.
- A HYENA
THAT WAS GETTING SLAUGHTERED.
- IT HAPPENED FAST, BABE.
IT WENT FAST.
3 1/2 HOURS
FROM YOUR WATER BREAKING
TO THE TIME SHE WAS OUT?
- HER HEAD WAS JUST RIGHT THERE.
- YOU--YOU SAID TO ME
AT ONE POINT, YOU--
NOBODY WAS IN HERE,
NOBODY WAS IN HERE, YOU SAID,
"CAN YOU LOOK?
I THINK HER HEAD IS OUT,"
AND I WENT, "NO, I CAN'T.
I WOULDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO."
YOU HAVE A VERY ACCOMMODATING
VAGINA FOR BIRTH.
- IT IS NOT ACCOMMODATING.
SHE RIPPED THROUGH ME.
- SHE CAME OUT OF THERE
WITH A MARCHING BAND.
- STOP.
- YOU LOOKED LIKE THE EXORCIST
AT ONE POINT.
WHEN MARK CAME IN,
YOU WERE LIKE, "GIVE ME MORE!"
HE WAS LIKE, "I CAN'T.
I GAVE YOU EVERYTHING
I CAN GIVE YOU."
- HE DIDN'T TELL ME
THERE'S A 15-MINUTE DELAY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS--
- YOU'RE LIKE,
"YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S NOT WORKING."
- WE'RE GETTING MARRIED IN,
LIKE, FIVE MONTHS.
- [whistles]
THERE'S STILL TIME
TO BACK OUT.
- I DON'T WANT TO BACK OUT.
- GOOD.
- DO YOU WANT TO BACK OUT?
- NOPE. GREAT ANSWER.
- I'LL KILL YOU.
- GREAT ANSWER.
- I'D BE SO UPSET
IF YOU DIDN'T SHOW UP.
- I WAS--THAT WAS A TEST.
- ME AND JIONNI HAVE A LOT
TO DO BEFORE WE GET MARRIED
IN A COUPLE MONTHS.
THERE'S SO MUCH GOING ON
IN MY LIFE
WITH HAVING TO GET MARRIED
AND HAVE MY SECOND BABY
AND MOVE INTO OUR HOUSE.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE GET EVERYTHING DONE.
I HAVE TO MEET WITH MY FLORIST
AGAIN.
I HAVE TO SEE THE BRIDESMAIDS
ACTUALLY IN THE DRESSES.
- THE MUSIC
TO WALK DOWN THE AISLE.
- OH! I HAVE TO DO MAKEUP
AND HAIR TRIALS.
COULD YOU INVITE
LEONARDO DICAPRIO?
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- WHY?
- HE'S GATSBY. HE'LL FRIGGING
TAKE MY SPOTLIGHT.
YOU KIDDING?
- YEAH, BUT HE COULD TEACH YOU
HOW TO BE GATSBY.
- I AM GATSBY.
- ONE NIGHT, WHEN WE WATCHED
THE GREAT GATSBY MOVIE,
I REALIZED
THAT I LOVE THE THEME,
I LOVE THE MUSIC,
I LOVE THE WHOLE LOOK OF IT.
SO WHY NOT HAVE
A GREAT GATSBY WEDDING?
- DO I HAVE TO DYE
MY HAIR BLOND?
- NO.
THERE'S DEFINITELY MORE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHO WROTE THE GREAT GATSBY BOOK.
I WAS PLANNING ON READING IT,
ACTUALLY.
- WHO WROTE THE GREAT GATSBY?
TOBEY MAGUIRE.
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
SPIDER-MAN?
- HE DID.
HE WROTE THE GREAT GATSBY.
- SPIDER-MAN?
- YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, THIS IS IT?
- OH, [bleep].
WE'VE GOT TO GET OUR RINGS.
ALL RIGHT, MAMA'S GOT A JOB
TO DO.
- NO.
- I GOT TO GO WATCH
THE DOGGIES 'CAUSE
AUNT JENNI'S IN THE HOSPITAL.
- YOU WANT A DOG?
- I'LL TELL THE DOGGIES
YOU SAID HI, OKAY?
- DOGGIE DUTY.
HI, BABIES.
I TOLD JENNI
THAT WHEN SHE'S AT THE HOSPITAL,
I CAN TAKE CARE OF THE DOGS.
SHE HAS A WHOLE LIST
OF WHAT SHE WANTS ME TO DO.
I'M NOT PAMPERING THESE DOGS
LIKE THEY'RE PEOPLE.
THEY'RE DOGS.
FEED THEM TWICE A DAY.
PLAY HIDE-AND-GO-SEEK.
THEY LOVE IT.
I'M NOT DOING THAT.
GIVE DIESEL FIVE ICE CUBES.
YEAH, RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE JENNI
WAS ALWAYS A CRAZY DOG LADY
EVER SINCE SHE HAD BELLA,
AND THEN WITH NOEL AND DIESEL
IT JUST KEEPS GOING.
SIT. SIT.
[dogs yipping]
SEE, LOOK AT BELLA.
SIT. SIT. NOEL, SIT. SIT.
BOTH OF YOU, SIT.
DO YOU LISTEN?
[barking]
I FEEL LIKE ONCE JENNI
HAS HER BABY,
HER REAL BABY IN HER STOMACH,
SHE'S GONNA KNOW THAT SHE WAS
A LITTLE CRAZY WITH THE DOGS.
[growling]
I HAVE AN ACTUAL BABY
TO TAKE CARE OF.
HE'S HUMAN.
HIS NAME'S LORENZO, OKAY?
[growling]
NOW, I'M GONNA CALL YOUR NANNY.
I'M GONNA TELL HER TO COME OVER
AND TAKE CARE OF YOU.
THESE DOGS,
THEY'RE VERY HIGH-MAINTENANCE.
THEY'RE LITERALLY NOT
LISTENING TO ANYTHING
BECAUSE JENNI
TREATS THEM LIKE PEOPLE.
SO I MEAN, AT THIS POINT,
I FEEL LIKE I'VE--I DID MY SHARE
OF TAKING CARE OF THEM,
AND I FEEL LIKE IT'S TIME
FOR LINDSAY TO COME OVER
AND DO HER JOB.
HEY, LINDSAY, IT'S NICOLE,
JUST NEED YOU TO COME
GET THE DOGGIES.
I TOLD JENNI I WOULD WATCH THEM,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
SO PLEASE COME GET THE DOGS.
I'LL BE WAITING.
'KAY, BYE.
[growling]
- HI.
- [laughing] HEY...
JENNI'S DAD,
TERRY, MY DAD, BILL,
AND HIS WIFE, BETTY,
ARE ALL HERE TO VISIT
WITH LITTLE MEILANI.
- WOW.
- GIVE HER HEAD SUPPORT.
ROCK HER A LITTLE BIT.
WE'LL PUT HER IN A BLANKIE.
- HI.
HI, GRANDDAUGHTER.
[Meilani fussing]
AWW, WELCOME TO THE WORLD.
- LOOK, SHE--DON'T BE SCARED.
[Meilani crying]
- JUST ROCK HER A LITTLE BIT,
SHE'LL STOP.
- IT'S OKAY.
- YOU LOOK TERRIFIED.
- I AM.
- IT'S MAYBE A TAD MORE SPECIAL
FOR YOUR DAD, BECAUSE MY DAD
IS ALREADY A GRANDFATHER.
I HAVE A NIECE, BUT YOUR DAD
IS A FIRST-TIME GRANDPA,
AND YOU CAN JUST SEE IN HIS EYES
THAT HE'S--HE'S TERRIFIED.
- SO NERVOUS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE--
I DIDN'T THINK THIS GUY WAS EVER
GONNA GIVE ME ONE OF THESE, HUH?
BUT IT WAS WORTH THE WAIT,
YEAH.
- SEEING MY DAD HOLD MEILANI,
IT'S A LITTLE SURREAL, YOU KNOW?
IT'S SOMETHING I KNOW MY FATHER
DIDN'T THINK WOULD HAPPEN,
SO I'M JUST KIND
OF SITTING BACK AND BASKING
IN THE GLORY OF WATCHING
THAT ACTUALLY HAPPEN.
I KNOW MY FATHER
IS ON CLOUD NINE RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW HE'S JUST A PROUD GRANDPA
AND COULDN'T BE HAPPIER FOR US.
- SHE'S GONNA BE PRETTY
LIKE HER MOM.
- SHE'S JUST PERFECT.
- SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
- JUST PERFECT.
- JUST BEAUTIFUL.
- I THINK THIS LITTLE ONE
IS A KEEPER.
- AND IT WAS SO EASY,
WE EXPECT FIVE OR SIX MORE.
[laughter]
- I'LL UPDATE EVERYBODY
ON HOW YOU'RE DOING.
- MM-HMM.
- TEXTING NICOLE RIGHT NOW.
[phone beeps]
- OH, MY GOD, I'M SO EXCITED.
- YOU.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- I JUST GOT A TEXT FROM ROGER,
AND JENNI HAD MEILANI,
AND I CANNOT WAIT TO MEET HER.
- HELLO?
- HEY, CAR.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- CAN YOU COME OVER RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE JENNI JUST HAD HER BABY,
AND I NEED TO GO SEE HER.
- OH, YAY!
- YEAH, SO--
- I'M READY TO GO,
BE RIGHT THERE.
- ALL RIGHT, BE HERE IN,
LIKE, TWO SECONDS.
- COOL, I'M ON MY WAY RIGHT NOW.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
- I'M SO EXCITED.
I CANNOT WAIT TO SEE
WHAT THIS BABY LOOKS LIKE.
I'M PICTURING A BIG TURKEY BABY,
LIKE A TEN-POUNDER
WITH BIG ROLLS.
I JUST LITERALLY WANT TO RUN
TO THE HOSPITAL
AND MEET THIS BABY.
ARE YOU EXCITED?
- MM-HMM.
- WE'RE GONNA
MEET HER CHILD RIGHT NOW.
WONDER IF ROGER CRIED.
- [chuckling]
I CAN'T STOP LAUGHING.
- IS SHE JUST BEING A LOVE BUG?
- SHE'S JUST BEING PERFECT.
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
DADDY'S LITTLE GIRL.
I LOVE IT
WHEN SHE MAKES NOISES.
- WANT TO SEE YOUR AUNTIE
SOON?
both: COME IN.
- HELLO.
- IT'S THE AUNTIE AND UNCLE.
- BABY!
- SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
SHE'S SO SMALL.
I'M LIKE, "OH, MY GOD."
I SEE THIS LITTLE NUGGET
WITH A LOT
OF HAIR IN A PINK OUTFIT,
AND IT'S JENNI'S BABY.
AND SHE'S NOT A GINGER
LIKE I THOUGHT SHE WOULD BE.
- HOW LONG, HOW HEAVY?
- SHE WAS 20 1/2 INCHES LONG.
SHE WAS 7 POUNDS, 13 OUNCES
AND SHE WAS BORN AT 12:59?
- NOT BAD.
- NO, 49.
- 12:49.
- SHE CAME RIGHT OUT.
- FROM THE TIME
HER WATER BROKE TO THE TIME
SHE WAS OUT, 3 1/2 HOURS.
THAT'S FAST.
- YEAH.
- DUDE, SHE CAME SO QUICKLY,
MY EPIDURAL FAILED ME.
- YOU DIDN'T--
YOU FELT EVERYTHING?
- IF YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT SCREAMING,
I WAS SCREAMING SO LOUD.
- LIKE IN THE MOVIES?
- YES.
I WAS LIKE, "I'M GOING
TO PASS OUT FROM THIS PAIN."
SHE WAS--
- YOU FELT EVERYTHING?
- EVERY--I
LOOKED HIM IN THE FACE
AND I WAS LIKE,
"I'M GONNA PASS OUT."
MY VAGINA IS IN SO MUCH PAIN,
I CAN'T EVEN EXPLAIN TO YOU,
AND THE FACT--
- IT HASN'T HURT
LIKE THAT SINCE COLLEGE.
- SO RUDE.
IT'S TRUE, THOUGH.
- WHAT'D IT FEEL LIKE?
- I--I CAN'T EVEN
EXPLAIN THE PAIN.
- SHE WENT FROM, IN AN HOUR,
BLUSHING WHEN SHE SAID
"FRIG" IN FRONT OF OUR DOCTOR
TO SCREAMING AT HIM,
"IS MY [bleep] FALLING OUT?"
- OH, HOLD HER, HERE.
- YEAH, HOLD HER, BABE.
- CAN I?
- YEAH.
- SHE'S SO CUTE.
I SEE ROGER RIGHT NOW.
- SO DO I.
- I SEE A LITTLE BIT,
BUT I SEE JENNI, TOO.
I DON'T THINK SHE'S REALLY
FIGURED OUT WHO SHE'S GONNA LOOK
LIKE YET.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
WE WERE SCARED YOU WERE GONNA
BE UGLY, BUT YOU'RE NOT UGLY.
- NO, SHE'S SO CUTE.
- SHE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
THAT BAD OF A CONE HEAD
FOR GETTING STUCK.
- SHE LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
- YEAH, MAN.
- I WOULD TELL YOU IF YOU
HAD AN UGLY BABY, TRUST ME.
- THANK YOU.
- I'D BE LIKE, "UM,
THAT'S NOT YOUR BABY."
- YOU'RE AVOIDING THE FACE--
- BUT I COULD SEE EVERYTHING.
- YOU SAW THE--
YOU SAW HER VAGINA?
- OH, YEAH, I SAW EVERYTHING.
- THE BABY COMING OUT?
- YEAH, I SAW THE HEAD
COMING OUT.
I SAW EVERYTHING, YEAH.
I SAW, UH, I SAW A LOT.
UM--
- I STILL WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOUR VISION IS OF WHAT HAPPENED,
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU WERE ABLE TO SEE.
- IT'S JUST--IT'S ALMOST
INCOMPREHENSIBLE TO--
- WILL YOU STILL HAVE SEX
WITH ME?
- YES.
- WELL, WE'RE GONNA
LET YOU GUYS GO,
'CAUSE IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT.
WE ENJOYED SPENDING TIME
WITH YOU.
- MAYBE I COULD COME BY
TOMORROW.
- I WOULD LOVE THAT.
- VISITING HOURS ARE OVER,
AND WE DEFINITELY WANT TO GIVE
ROGER AND JENNI SOME REST
BECAUSE WE DEFINITELY KNOW
HOW TIRING IT IS
TO HAVE THE BABY
FOR THE FIRST DAY.
- THEY'RE PROBABLY NOT GONNA
GET SLEEP TONIGHT, TOMORROW,
OR THE WHOLE WEEK.
- NOPE.
OR THEIR WHOLE LIFE.
- EVER.
ENJOY THE BABY.
- THANK YOU.
- I'M SO PROUD OF YOU GUYS.
- OH, I CAN'T WAIT
TO HAVE A LITTLE BABY NOW.
I REMEMBER HAVING LORENZO
IN THE HOSPITAL,
AND I LOVED GETTING VISITORS
BECAUSE IT TOOK YOUR MIND
OFF THE FACT THAT YOU RIPPED
YOUR VAGINA TO YOUR ASS[bleep].
SO I'M GONNA COME BACK TOMORROW
AND VISIT JENNI.
DO YOU REMEMBER
HOW SMALL THEY ARE?
- YOU'RE A GOOD KID,
I'LL TELL YA.
YOU'RE A GOOD KID.
- LORENZO'S LIKE A BEAST, NOW.
- LORENZO'S A LITTLE WISEASS.
- LORENZO HAS DEFINITELY
CHANGED.
OH, MY GOD,
HE'S NOT MY BABY ANYMORE,
AND THAT'S WHY I'M SO HAPPY
THAT I'M PREGNANT NOW,
BECAUSE NOW I
GET TO HAVE ANOTHER BABY,
AND HOPEFULLY IT'S GONNA BE
THE SAME EXACT BABY AS LORENZO,
JUST LIKE A REALLY,
REALLY GOOD KID,
BUT THAT'S PROBABLY NOT GONNA
HAPPEN.
IT'LL PROBABLY BE, LIKE,
A REALLY BAD BABY.
- THAT'S SO FUNNY THAT
LITERALLY LESS THAN TWO YEARS
AGO THAT WAS HIM.
NOW HE'S A LITTLE WISEASS.
- I KNOW.
- SAYING, "NO, NO, NO."
- DOES SHE GO THIS WAY,
BABE, OR THE OTHER WAY?
- IT'S FINE. YOU CAN PUSH HER UP
NEXT TO ME LIKE THAT.
- YOU ARE THE MOST
PERFECT LITTLE BABY.
- THAT'S YOUR SPERM.
- PRETTY MUCH.
I COULD LOOK AT YOU
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
AND I WILL BE LOOKING AT YOU
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
I SHOULD SAY.
- CAN YOU KISS HER FOR ME?
- AND A KISS FROM MOMMY.
I'M GONNA DIM THOSE LIGHTS
FOR THAT LITTLE BABY TO SLEEP.
YOU KNOW,
AS THE LIGHTS GO OUT ON MY--
MY FIRST NIGHT AS A--AS A DAD,
I'M JUST THINKING, YOU KNOW,
WHY DID I THINK
THAT THIS WASN'T FOR ME?
YOU KNOW, WHY--
WHY DID I EVER THINK THAT?
THIS IS SO FOR ME.
I--I EMBRACE EVERY SECOND OF IT,
AND I JUST CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT TOMORROW BRINGS, YOU KNOW?
[chuckling]
YOU MAKE YOUR DADDY GIGGLE.
NOBODY MAKES YOUR DADDY GIGGLE.
- LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU WITH ALL MY HEART,
BUT YOU JUST DEFINITELY
BECAME NUMBER-TWO BABY.
- GOOD NIGHT, BABE.
- IT SMELLS LIKE BURNT TOAST.
- THIS HAM SMELLS LIKE SACK
RIGHT NOW.
IT REALLY DOES, THAT'S
WHAT THAT SMELL IS, IS THIS HAM.
- WHY ARE YOU GONNA EAT IT
IF IT STINKS LIKE THAT?
- I'M HUNGRY.
IT REALLY SMELLS.
- LET ME SMELL.
- YOU FEEL BAD, NOW.
OH!
ARE YOU CRAZY?
- YEAH, I'M NUTS 'CAUSE
I JUST DID THAT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
SHUT UP.
- I'M TOUCHING MY EYELASH,
AND NOW I SMELL BALLS.
JIONNI, I THINK IT'S VERY RUDE
THAT YOU SLAPPED A COLD CUT
IN MY FACE
THAT SMELLED LIKE BUTTHOLE.
- YOU TRY TO SLAP ME
WITH GREASY STUFF ALL THE TIME.
- I SLAP YOU WITH SALAMI.
THAT DOESN'T SMELL BAD.
- YOU TRY TO DO IT BECAUSE YOU
SAY YOU KNOW I GET PIMPLES.
PRETTY RUDE IF YOU ASK ME.
- I LIKE TO PISS HIM OFF.
I DO WANT TO DO SOMETHING
SPECIAL FOR JENNI.
I WANT TO,
LIKE, DECORATE THE HOUSE.
I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING FOR JENNI AND ROGER
BECAUSE THEY DID SOMETHING FOR
US WHEN WE WERE IN THE HOSPITAL.
I WANT TO GO, LIKE,
WAY OVER TOP OF THAT AND JUST
MAKE THEM SMILE.
- ONE-UP THEM.
- YEAH.
- A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE GONNA COME VISIT.
YOU DON'T WANT TO HAVE NO FOOD
FOR THEM.
- YOU DON'T WANT
TO ORDER [bleep]
AND THEN THEY HAVE [bleep].
- THEY'RE NOT.
LET'S DO IT FOR THEM.
- SO WE CAN, LIKE, ORDER SUBS?
- WE'LL SET EVERYTHING UP.
- LOOK HOW BIG THAT HAWK IS.
- THERE'S TWO--
THERE'S THREE OF THEM.
HOLY PISS BALLS.
- THEY'RE LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
TO EAT. THEY FOUND SOMETHING.
THEY'RE WAITING FOR IT TO DIE.
- BLBLBLBLB!
- THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
WOULD YOU JUST LET THEM EAT ME?
- HOLY COW.
GO LAY ON YOUR BACK.
- NO.
- I'LL PUT KETCHUP ON YOU.
- COME ON, JUST TRY IT.
- NO, JIONNI.
[upbeat music]
*
- DID YOU GET ANY SLEEP
AT ALL LAST NIGHT?
- I WAS UP EVERY HOUR
BETWEEN YOU SNORING TO THE POINT
WHERE I COULD HEAR YOU OUTSIDE,
AND THEN HER WAILING
'CAUSE OF YOUR SNORING,
I WAS LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO."
FIRST NIGHT WITH MEILANI,
I MEAN, I DIDN'T SLEEP.
YOU KNOW, I'M DELUSIONAL.
I'M A NEW MOM.
I'M RECOVERING.
I'M ON MEDICATION.
I HAVE A STITCH-UP VAGINA.
I JUST AM, LIKE, SO BEAT UP.
BUT LIKE, I WOULDN'T HAVE
THAT ANY OTHER WAY.
DO YOU WANT TO GET HER BAG
OVER HERE,
AND LET'S PUT HER IN AN OUTFIT?
- WE GOT TO CHECK
HER DIAPER, TOO.
THIS IS FRONT, CORRECT?
FRONT?
- OH, THAT'S THE BACK.
THE TABS ARE IN THE BACK.
- THEY ARE?
- MM-HMM.
- OH, YEAH, 'CAUSE
THEY COME AROUND, YEAH.
SINCE I'VE NEVER
CHANGED A DIAPER BEFORE,
JENNI KIND OF SHOWS ME
HOW TO DO IT,
AND I AM NOT SCARED AT ALL
OF A POOPY DIAPER.
IT DOES NOT SCARE ME.
JENNI BETTER NOT BE
SCARED OF THEM, EITHER,
'CAUSE I WILL BE IN THEM SOON.
GOD, I FEEL
LIKE I'M GONNA BREAK HER.
- NO, YOU WON'T.
- LIFT HER LIKE THIS?
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T.
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA BREAK HER.
[baby fussing]
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
GET THE CLEAN ONE
UNDER THERE READY.
- MOMMY'S MANHANDLING YOU.
DADDY DOESN'T LIKE IT.
I DEFINITELY
THINK IT'S WEIRD 'CAUSE
I'M KIND OF THE BULL
THAT JUST RUNS THROUGH STUFF,
AND, YOU KNOW, WHATEVER GETS
SMASHED GETS SMASHED,
BUT I THINK I'M ALREADY
THE MORE GENTLE ONE
WITH MEILANI THAN JENNI IS.
SHE JUST KIND OF GRABS HER ARM
AND PULLS IT
THROUGH A SLEEVE HOLE.
I'M JUST KIND OF, LIKE, TRYING
TO MANIPULATE IT
THROUGH REALLY EASY,
AND IT'S PROBABLY JUST 'CAUSE,
YOU KNOW, SHE'S MY LITTLE GIRL,
AND I JUST WANT TO PROTECT HER.
- YOU SAW HOW SHE CAME
OUT OF MY VAGINA.
SHE'S NOT GONNA BREAK EASY.
- MOVE, I--I CAN'T SEE.
- I CAN'T MOVE THE FLOWERS.
- WHY ARE YOU YELLING?
- I SAID, "I CAN'T SEE,"
IN A TONED VOICE.
- I SAID IT IN A TONED VOICE.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T.
- I WAS JUST A LITTLE LOUDER
SO YOU COULD HEAR ME
'CAUSE YOU'RE OLD.
ME AND JIONNI ARE GOING
TO SEE JENNI AND ROGER
AT THE HOSPITAL AGAIN,
AND I'M EXCITED TO SEE THE BABY.
HELLO?
- HEY.
- YAY, I BROUGHT FLOWERS.
- HI!
I'M CHOPPED LIVER
AT THIS POINT, RIGHT?
YOU JUST WANT TO SEE MY BABY?
- YEAH, I REALLY
DON'T CARE ABOUT YOU.
- YEAH, I FIGURED.
- CAN I HOLD HER?
- SURE.
- YEAH.
- ROGER, DO YOU HAVE A CAR SEAT?
- I DO, YEAH.
I GOT TO GO PUT IT IN.
- YOU KNOW HOW TO DO IT?
I'LL COME--
- YEAH, COME--COME WITH ME.
- LET'S GO SET THIS THING
UP, YEAH.
- MY GOOD LITTLE BUDDY HERE,
JIONNI, IS GONNA SUPERVISE
ME PUTTING THE CAR SEAT
IN TO MAKE SURE I DO IT RIGHT.
I'M A FIRST-TIME DAD.
HE'S DONE THIS A MILLION TIMES
AT THIS POINT.
- ALL RIGHT, IT'S TIME TO EAT.
- SEE?
- WHAT?
YOU'RE SUCH A [bleep].
- NO, THAT'S PRETTY GROSS.
MY STOMACH IS KIND
OF FLAT RIGHT NOW.
- YOU'RE SUCH A WHORE!
- IT'S ALL PUFFY.
- IT'S NOT NORMAL.
NOBODY BOUNCES BACK THE WAY
JENNI HAS.
- MY MOM DID.
- AND IT REALLY
PISSES ME THE HELL OFF.
WELL, CLEARLY, YOUR MOM AND YOU,
THE ONLY PEOPLE IN THE WORLD
I'VE EVER SEEN.
SKINNY BITCHES.
- SHUT UP.
- THAT'S WHAT I DO.
- IT'S GONNA BE
THE LONGEST TRIP HOME.
IT TOOK US 20 MINUTES
TO GET HERE.
IT'S GONNA
TAKE US 45 TO GET HOME.
SO I THINK
WHAT MAKES THE MOST SENSE, HERE,
IS ONCE WE INSTALL THE CAR SEAT,
IS THAT YOU CLIMB UP IN THERE,
AND I'LL HELP YOU IN,
THEN I'LL STRAP YOU IN.
I'LL GIVE YOU A PACIFIER.
WE'LL TAKE A RIDE AROUND TOWN
JUST TO MAKE SURE THAT,
YOU KNOW,
I GOT THE HANG OF THIS.
- YOUR HANDS BETTER BE
AT TEN AND TWO.
- WHERE ARE YOUR HANDS
WHEN YOU DRIVE, SIX AND SIX?
- PUT THAT THROUGH THE BOTTOM.
- ALL RIGHT.
READY?
I'M GONNA REEF ON IT.
I FEEL SAFE WITH HER IN THERE.
LET'S JUST PUT THE SEAT ON IT.
- AH, THAT'S GOOD.
EASY TO COME OFF.
- TAKE IT OFF
WITH TWO LITTLE HANDLES.
- AH, RIGHT HERE.
THIS--I GOT ONE ON THIS SIDE.
- YUP.
- ALL RIGHT.
SO IT'S RIGHT THERE.
- I FEEL SAFE WITH HER IN THERE.
IT DOESN'T MOVE BARELY AT ALL.
- ROGER WENT IN TO THE HOSPITAL
ONE OF THE SCARIEST GUYS I KNOW
AND CAME OUT ONE
OF THE SOFTEST GUYS I KNOW.
HE'S JUST A TYPICAL DAD,
AND HE LOVES HIS DAUGHTER, AND,
YOU KNOW, IT'S FOR THE BEST.
- AND THE WEIRD THING ABOUT IT
IS I'M SO COMPLETELY
FINE WITH IT.
I DON'T CARE IF I DON'T HAVE
ANY MORE STREET CRED.
ALL RIGHT?
- YUP, GOOD WORK.
- NICE.
NICE HUSTLE.
- I FEEL LIKE YOU HAD
A REALLY BAD DELIVERY STORY.
- I JUST HAD A FAIR ONE.
- YOU FELT IT.
THAT'S BAD ENOUGH.
- I KNOW.
I HAD A RAPID LABOR.
- IS IT BECAUSE YOU'RE LOOSE?
- NO.
- I FEEL LIKE MY DOCTOR
GAVE ME THAT EXTRA STITCH,
WHERE IT'S JUST...TIGHT.
- I HOPE MINE IS.
I DIDN'T ASK FOR ONE.
- DID YOU GET THE EXTRA STITCH?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS IN TOO MUCH PAIN.
I JUST WANTED IT ALL TO BE DONE.
- WHAT IF HE DIDN'T DO IT,
AND...
- GOOD,
MAYBE THE NEXT ONE WILL--
- THINGS JUST FALL OUT OF THERE?
- MAYBE MY NEXT ONE
WON'T BE SO PAINFUL.
- MM.
SO AFTER THIS WHOLE EXPERIENCE,
YOU STILL WANT ANOTHER ONE?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- OH, MY GOD, ROGER,
HE WAS--LAST NIGHT HE WAS LIKE,
HE SAID SOMETHING,
THE CUTEST THING EVER.
HE WAS LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW
WHY I EVER WANTED A SON."
- LIKE, HE'S SO HAPPY
WITH A DAUGHTER?
- OH, YEAH, HE WAS LIKE,
"I NEEDED A PRECIOUS ANGEL."
- GIVE HIM A BOY ANYWAY.
- OH, YEAH, I WAS LIKE,
"I NEED A BOY."
I DEFINITELY THINK
THAT IF I WAS TO TRY AGAIN,
I WOULD TRY ONE MORE TIME
NATURALLY
TO SEE IF WE COULD JUST, LIKE,
ROLL THE DICE
AND HAVE A BOY ON OUR OWN.
BUT IF WE HAVE TWO GIRLS,
I'M DEFINITELY GONNA GET,
LIKE, ARTIFICIALLY INSEMINATED
FOR A BOY THE THIRD TIME,
'CAUSE THERE IS NO WAY
I'M HAVING THREE GIRLS.
THREE OF ME IN THE HOUSE,
PLUS ME?
I'D BASH MY [bleep] HEAD
UP AGAINST THE WALL.
- MY ANESTHESIOLOGIST DIED.
- WHAT?
- YEAH, HE DIED.
- I MEAN, THEY'RE ALL--
- THAT WAS A GOOD ONE,
LIKE, 'CAUSE HE--
YOU KNOW, HE HIT THE RIGHT SPOT,
EVERYTHING. I FELT NUMB.
WHAT IF THE NEW ONE,
I GO NUMB UP?
I'M LIKE--
- OH, MY GOD.
- IT'D BE AWFUL.
STICK IT TO ME.
I DON'T CARE.
I'D RATHER SLOW IT DOWN
AND NOT FEEL IT
THAN JUST FEEL EVERYTHING.
THIS IS OUR LIVES, NOW.
- MM-HMM.
- WE'RE MOMS.
BUT COOL MOMS.
- SEXY MOMS.
THAT HAPPENS TO PEOPLE.
- YEAH?
- THEY GET NUMB
UP AND THEN THEY'RE LIKE--
THEY FEEL EVERYTHING.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO TODAY,
LORENZO?
WE HAVE A WHOLE DAY
TO DO ANYTHING.
I WAS THINKING
WE CAN GO TO THE ZOO!
- ZOO.
both: YOU WANT TO GO TO THE ZOO?
- YEAH.
- YEAH? JENNI AND MEILANI
ARE STILL RECOVERING
AT THE HOSPITAL, SO WHILE WE
WAIT FOR THEM TO COME HOME,
WE'RE GONNA
HAVE A FAMILY DAY AT THE ZOO.
- WHAT'S AT THE ZOO?
- LIONS.
- LION.
- TIGERS AND BEARS.
- TIGER. BEAR.
- WHAT'S A LION DO?
- ROAR.
- LORENZO LOVES THE ZOO,
AND I CAN'T WAIT
TO TAKE HIM TO THE POPCORN ZOO.
WE TOOK HIM LAST YEAR,
BUT THE FACT THAT,
YOU KNOW, HE'S A LITTLE OLDER,
HE KNOWS A LITTLE MORE ANIMALS,
IT'S GONNA BE AWESOME.
- WILL YOU GO THROW THIS OUT
FOR MAMA?
- NO.
- WILL YOU THROW IT
IN THE GARBAGE?
- NO.
- PLEASE?
- NO!
- DO YOU KNOW HOW TO SAY YES?
- NO.
- SAY YES.
- SAY YES!
- NO.
- SAY YES.
- LORENZO, SAY YES.
- NO.
- SO ANNOYING.
- THIS IS PACKED.
- IT'S THE POPCORN ZOO.
EVERYONE LOVES THE POPCORN ZOO.
- WHERE DO I PARK?
- LORENZO,
YOU WANT SOME POPCORN?
- YEAH.
- YEAH?
- NO.
- IT'S WHAT--
- [mumbles]
- HUH?
CAN YOU SAY POPCORN?
- A PEACOCK.
- PIGGY.
LORENZO, MONKEYS!
DO--DOES THIS ONE THROW POOPY
AT YOU?
- HE'S SCRATCHING HIS BUTT.
- WHOA, IT'S A PANDA.
- WHAT IS THAT?
IS THAT A SEAL?
IS THAT A BEAR?
DUDE, WHAT IS THAT?
- WHOA, LOOK AT ITS TAIL.
- MAYBE IT'S AN ANTEATER.
- AN ANTEATER?
- WHAT IS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- OH, GOD,
THEY'RE VELOCIRAPTORS.
- IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S GONNA
PECK MY HEAD OFF IN TWO SECONDS.
- HERE, LOOK.
- WHOA.
- WHOO!
EAT!
DO IT AGAIN.
[laughter]
[Lorenzo laughing]
[all laughing]
- LORENZO IS CRACKING UP.
- IT'S SO CUTE.
- LIKE, LITERALLY, LIKE, HE'S
JUST CRACKING UP THE WHOLE TIME.
- LORENZO!
- DOES HE GET IT?
THIS WAS ONE OF THE REAL REASONS
WHY I WANTED TO BRING LORENZO
TO THE ZOO, STUFF LIKE THIS.
- HE MAKES US SMILE.
- WHOA, LOOK AT THAT THING.
- WOW.
- DON'T THINK HE WANTS POPCORN.
- DOES IT WANT TO EAT LORENZO?
- PROBABLY.
- HI!
- HEY, NICOLE.
- WHO'S THAT?
OH.
HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- THE OWNER
OF POPCORN ZOO COMES UP TO US,
AND OF COURSE, HE REMEMBERS ME
FROM THE LAST TIME I WAS HERE.
- THIS IS ALL FAMILIAR TO YOU
WHEN YOU USED TO COME
AND CLEAN THESE CAGES?
- YEAH.
- YOU SHOVELED POOP?
- LORENZO, MOMMY ONE TIME
GOT IN TROUBLE WITH THE POLICE,
AND SHE HAD TO COME HERE
AND DO COMMUNITY SERVICE.
I HAD TO DO COMMUNITY SERVICE
BECAUSE I GOT DRUNK
ON THE BEACH,
AND I GOT ARRESTED.
OH, MY VAGINA'S OUT.
AAH!
- NICOLE!
- I JUST WANT TO GO
ON THE BEACH.
WHERE'S THE BEACH?
[carnival music wind down]
I'M A [bleep] GOOD PERSON.
IT HAPPENS.
BUT I DID MY DUTIES.
I DID MY CRIME.
I SERVED MY CRIME.
- DID YOUR TIME?
- I DID MY TIME.
- THAT'S
WHAT YOU WERE LOOKING FOR.
- I DID MY TIME.
- SHE DID A GOOD JOB.
[Lorenzo laughing]
- I HAVE THE BABY'S BIRTH
CERTIFICATE.
- OH, GREAT.
[murmuring]
- WE'RE GONNA GO OVER IT.
I NEED YOU GUYS
TO GO LINE BY LINE,
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING
IS CORRECT FIRST, OKAY?
- OH, I MEANT TO ASK
YOUR FATHER, IS THERE AN "E"?
- CAN YOU TEXT HIM?
- THIS GIRL DOESN'T EVEN KNOW IF
THERE'S A "E" IN THE MIDDLE OF--
AT THE END OF HER MIDDLE NAME.
- YOU KNOW, MY PARENTS
WANTED TO BE DIFFERENT
AND SPELL MY MIDDLE NAME
DIFFERENT, LYNN WITHOUT AN "E".
SO, HONESTLY, I BARELY
USE MY MIDDLE NAME, LIKE IT'S--
- 29 YEARS OLD AND DON'T KNOW
YOUR OWN NAME.
- NO, I ACT--THAT'S TRUE.
I MEAN, LIKE, THIS IS WHAT I GET
FOR BEING WITH A RELAXED FATHER
THAT I HAD FOR SO MANY YEARS.
- YOU CANNOT BLAME YOUR FATHER
FOR THIS ONE.
- I DON'T KNOW IT.
HEY, ON MY BIRTH CERTIFICATE,
LYNN,
L-Y-N-N, NOT L-Y-N-N-E, RIGHT?
- I'M 99% SURE
IT HAS AN "E" ON IT.
- IT IS WITH AN "E"?
- GOOD THING WE WAITED, GIRL.
I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW YOU CAN'T KNOW
HOW TO SPELL YOUR MIDDLE NAME,
AND I'M NOT GONNA
BUY THE WHOLE
"I HAVE PREGNANCY BRAIN"
CRAP ON THIS ONE.
- AT LEAST
I KNOW HOW TO SPELL MY FIRST.
- YEAH?
AWESOME.
THIS KID IS SCREWED.
[pop music]
- * YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
THE REASON *
* I'M AROUND
- LORENZO,
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO EAT?
DON'T EAT THAT.
THAT'S NOT FOR--
- HE'S HUNGRY.
WE GOT CHICKEN WINGS.
- NO, WE'RE GONNA DO PASTA.
YOU HAVE TO SIT.
HONEY, SIT.
CAN YOU SIT DOWN, PLEASE?
- NO.
- SIT,
OR YOU CAN'T PLAY WITH THIS.
- NO.
- OKAY, SIT.
- NO!
- ARE YOU GONNA STAND
AND EAT, THEN?
- OH.
- OH, YOU CAN'T TOUCH THAT.
HEY, YOU'RE NOT GETTING DOWN.
- LET ME.
- NO.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- [murmurs]
- DO YOU WANT MORE?
- NO.
- LET GO OF MY CHAIN.
- LORENZO, MY DRESS.
[Lorenzo fussing]
- HE'S CHECKED OUT.
- I JUST FEEL LIKE MY KID
IS LIKE DENNIS THE MENACE.
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO?
- LET ME EAT THIS REAL QUICK.
- WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO?
- JUST LET HIM GO.
HE'LL COME BACK.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NO ONE ELSE'S KIDS
ARE DOING THIS, JUST OURS.
- IS THIS EMBARRASSING?
- YEAH.
HE'S UNDER THE TABLE LIKE A DOG.
- DO WE LOOK LIKE BAD PARENTS
RIGHT NOW?
- KIND OF.
- I'M STARVING.
- AT THIS POINT,
I THINK PEOPLE ARE JUST LOOKING
AT US LIKE,
"WHO ARE THOSE WEIRDOS
WITH THE KID?"
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"WHAT'S THIS KID DOING?"
I MEAN, HE'S A HANDFUL.
- I THINK THAT'S OUR CUE
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
WE LOOK LIKE DEGENERATE PARENTS.
- HIGH FIVE?
- LORENZO.
[pop music plays]
- * WELL, I'M
* I'M JUST HAVING
A GOOD TIME *
- STEP INTO MY OFFICE.
SO ME AND JIONNI WANT
TO DO SOMETHING REALLY SPECIAL
FOR JENNI AND ROGER WHEN THEY
COME HOME WITH THE BABY,
AND WE JUST DON'T WANT
THEM TO STRESS OUT.
I'LL DO THE DECORATIONS.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE OF THE FOOD.
- I'M GONNA CALL RIVOLI'S,
SET UP A LITTLE MENU FOR THEM.
COCKTAILS?
SHOULD WE GET--FOR CELEBRATION?
LET'S GET WINE/VODKA,
CHASERS.
- ALL YOU THINK
ABOUT IS DRINKING.
YOU'RE AN ALCOHOLIC.
SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH YOU.
- CHASERS.
- YOU HAVE PROBLEMS, DUDE.
- ALL RIGHT, DUDE.
YOU HAVE PROBLEMS.
WHY DON'T YOU BLOW UP
THOSE PICTURES
THAT I TOOK OF YOU AND JENNI?
- I CAN DO THAT, TOO.
WE CAN--
- GET BALLOONS,
A TON OF BALLOONS.
LET'S OVERDO IT WITH BALLOONS.
- ALL RIGHT.
I WANT TO GET A LOT OF, LIKE,
FLAMINGOS, LIKE 100 OF THEM.
OH, MAYBE WE CAN GET
A MARCHING BAND.
- A MARCHING BAND?
WHERE ARE YOU GONNA
GET A MARCHING BAND FROM?
- CALL A SCHOOL.
- IT'S THE SUMMERTIME.
- ALL RIGHT.
MARIACHI BAND,
AND THEY CAN PLAY A NURSERY
RHYME WHILE THEY WALK IN.
I WANT A MARIACHI BAND
BECAUSE THEN
IF SHE SEES THAT, SHE'LL LAUGH,
AND SHE'LL FORGET THAT SHE
POPPED A BABY OUT OF HER VAGINA.
ALL RIGHT,
I THINK WE GOT ALL WE NEED.
- GOOD WORK.
- NOW WE JUST GOT TO GET
THIS STUFF DONE.
TEAMWORK.
JENNI AND ROGER ARE COMING BACK
HOME WITH THE BABY TODAY,
AND I DEFINITELY WANT
THIS TO BE OVER-THE-TOP.
IT'S GONNA BE FRICKING AWESOME.
HI, DO YOU GUYS
HAVE A MARIACHI BAND?
- YO NO HABLO INGLES.
TU HABLAS ESPANOL?
- OKAY, THANKS.
DO YOU GUYS
HAVE A MARIACHI BAND?
- [speaking Spanish]
- I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
I NEED TO LEARN SPANISH.
- PARTY CITY, SHERRIE SPEAKING.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- HI, I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF I CAN ORDER, LIKE,
A MILLION BALLOONS.
I'M JUST CALLING
ALL THESE PEOPLE.
IT'S LITERALLY RIDICULOUS.
DO YOU HAVE A MARIACHI BAND?
- [speaking Spanish]
- A MARIACHI BAND.
- OH, MY GOD, I'M DONE
WITH THIS [bleep] MARIACHI BAND.
- WELL, A MILLION BALLOONS
IS A LOT.
250 IS A NICE AMOUNT.
- [laughs]
IF THAT'S THE HIGHEST
YOU CAN DO, I'LL TAKE THAT.
I DEFINITELY FEEL
LIKE THIS SHOULD BE A LOT EASIER
THAN IT IS RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'M A DUMBASS,
SO WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
- HOW MAY I HELP YOU?
- WELL, MY GIRLFRIEND
IS COMING HOME FROM THE HOSPITAL
WITH HER BABY,
AND I WOULD LIKE A MARIACHI BAND
TO, LIKE, GREET THEM.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU GUYS
PLAY ANY NURSERY RHYMES,
OR IF YOU COULD DRESS UP
LIKE BABIES,
OR, YOU KNOW, LOOK REALLY CUTE.
- EXCUSE ME?
- CAN YOU PLAY NURSERY RHYMES?
- YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, SURE.
- OKAY, PERFECT.
I'M GONNA NEED YOU GUYS
LATER TODAY.
IS THAT OKAY?
- OH, SURE, YES.
- OKAY, COOL.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER TODAY, THEN.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THANK YOU.
ADIOS.
- ADIOS.
- I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHAT HE SAID.
- I'VE NEVER BEEN SO TIRED
IN MY LIFE,
BUT I DON'T REALLY CARE.
IS THAT WEIRD?
SO I'M ABOUT TO TAKE
MY DAUGHTER HOME 'CAUSE
WE'RE GETTING DISCHARGED TODAY,
AND IT'S JUST SO SURREAL,
LIKE, NOW I'M RESPONSIBLE
FOR MY DAUGHTER.
YOU CAN'T PREPARE FOR IT.
YOU JUST HAVE TO LET
THE NATURAL INSTINCTS KICK IN.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
WHY ARE THEY GONNA RELEASE US?
'CAUSE I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'M GONNA DO,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I'M JUST GONNA WING IT.
WE'RE GOING HOME TODAY.
YES, WE ARE.
THEY TRUST ME ENOUGH WITH YOU.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I SAY THEY CRAZY.
THEY CRAZY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
I'M JUST TRYING.
THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
I WOULD LOVE TO STAY
IN THIS HOSPITAL.
I WOULD ACTUALLY LOVE
TO MOVE IN BECAUSE I FEEL SAFE.
I'M A NERVOUS NELLIE TO GO HOME.
WHO THE HELL SAYS THAT?
LIKE, I'M NERVOUS TO GO HOME
WITH A NEWBORN 'CAUSE
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO EXPECT.
THIS IS HARD TO--HARD--SEE?
I'M, LIKE,
STUTTERING STANLEY OVER HERE.
IT'S HARD NOT TO GET NERVOUS.
WHEN DO YOU WANT
TO GET HER EARS PIERCED?
- SHE'S SO PRETTY, SHE
DOESN'T NEED HER EARS PIERCED.
WE WERE WORRIED
THAT SHE WAS GONNA BE UGLY
AND WE WERE GONNA
HAVE TO ACCESSORIZE HER.
SHE DOESN'T NEED EARRINGS.
- I HAVE TO GET A FEW THINGS
AT THIS PARTY STORE,
MAINLY BALLOONS,
SO WHEN SHE COMES HOME,
IT'S LITERALLY,
LIKE, HOLY [bleep], WHERE DID
ALL THESE BALLOONS COME FROM?
- DO YOU HAVE A BIG ENOUGH CAR?
- UM.
- THAT'S A LOT OF BALLOONS.
- YEAH, WE'LL SEE.
- OKAY.
- WE'LL SEE HOW THAT WORKS OUT.
I JUST HOPE ALL OF THE BALLOONS
FIT INTO THE CAR.
GET IN THERE, BABIES.
THERE WE GO.
COME ON, WHORES.
ANNOYING.
OOH!
GOTCHA.
GET IN THERE. SQUEEZE IN THERE.
SUCCESS!
I'M A LITTLE HAPPY I
DIDN'T ORDER A MILLION BALLOONS.
BUT, I MEAN, SERIOUSLY,
A MILLION BALLOONS
WOULD'VE BEEN AWESOME.
SUCCESS.
I CAN'T SEE [bleep]
OUT OF MY MIRRORS.
- LET'S PUT YOU IN HERE.
IF YOU'RE NOT COMFY,
DADDY'LL TAKE YOU
RIGHT BACK OUT.
- OOPS, SHE LOST HER SOCKIE
ALREADY.
- ALL RIGHTY.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- GOT TO PUT THAT SOCKIE ON.
HANG ON.
- DO YOU HOW TO SHUT
THE--WHAT THE [bleep]?
THERE WE GO.
- YOU READY TO GO HOME?
BRINGING MEILANI HOME
FOR THE FIRST TIME IS--IT'S--
YOU CAN'T DESCRIBE THE FEELING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST THAT FEELING
OF ACCOMPLISHMENT,
THAT YOU'RE NOW OFFICIALLY
PARENTS.
YOU'VE WELCOMED A BEAUTIFUL GIRL
INTO THE WORLD,
AND ALL THESE THINGS THAT WE'VE
DONE OVER THE LAST TEN MONTHS
TO PREPARE
MEILANI'S ROOM AND ALL THAT,
NOW SHE GETS TO SEE IT.
SHE GETS TO EXPERIENCE IT
AND GET TO--
TO BE PART
OF THIS HOUSEHOLD, OUR FAMILY.
MEILANI'S FIRST RIDE.
WE'RE GOING HOME.
OH, GOD, THAT'S CRAZY.
- SHE IS PASSED OUT.
TAKING MY DAUGHTER HOME
RIGHT NOW IS 20 BILLION TIMES
MORE NERVE-RACKING
THAN GOING TO THE HOSPITAL.
- WE'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR THIS FOR TEN MONTHS.
HOLD ON, BABY,
THERE'S A LITTLE BUMP.
OOP.
YOU KNOW, I WASN'T WORRIED
AT ALL
ABOUT DRIVING HOME WITH MEILANI
IN THE CAR UNTIL I GOT
BEHIND THE DRIVER'S SEAT,
AND THAT ALL CHANGED.
YOU KNOW, I'M NORMALLY
A LITTLE BIT OF A LEAD FOOT.
- ROGER IS AN INSANE DRIVER,
BUT I'M SURPRISED
WE'RE ACTUALLY MOVING.
- JUST, YOU KNOW,
BEING A CONCERNED DAD.
WE MADE IT UP TO 40.
- I LOVE OUR FIRST RIDE HOME
AS A FAMILY.
YOU ONLY GET ONE FIRST.
ONE FIRST RIDE,
ONE FIRST NIGHT WITH HER,
ONE FIRST LOOK AT HER,
IT'S, YOU KNOW,
I'M LOVING ALL THE FIRSTS.
- TAKING YOU HOME, MEILANI.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
MEET THE CRAZY DOGGIES TODAY,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA MEET THEM SOON.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE THEM,
YOU JUST TELL DADDY,
'CAUSE I'LL DRIVE THEM RIGHT
TO THE POUND FOR YOU.
- I STILL CANNOT BELIEVE
SHE CAME OUT OF MY VAGINA.
- OH, SHE DID.
I SAW HER.
YOU UNHINGED SIMILAR
TO A COBRA'S JAWS.
- STOP.
- YOU DID.
- I'M STITCHED UP.
SO THIS IS
WHAT IT'S LIKE BEING THE MOM
IN THE BACKSEAT.
- OH, THERE'LL BE
PLENTY MORE ROAD TRIPS WITH DAD.
- [bleep] THAT [bleep].
MEILANI, JUST LOOK AT--
YOU KNOW THAT I
AM OFFICIALLY CHOPPED LIVER?
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME, AGAIN,
AND WHY ARE YOU IN THE CAR?
- SPAM.
I'M WORSE THAN CHOPPED LIVER.
I AM SPAM.
I AM CANNED MEAT.
- EXCUSE ME.
DON'T MOVE.
[screams]
[honking]
- HOLY MARY, MOTHER OF GOD.
- BE CAREFUL.
IT'S A LITTLE WINDY.
[balloon pops]
WHAT WAS THAT?
DID YOU POP A BALLOON?
JIONNI!
- NICOLE GOT ENOUGH BALLOONS.
I MEAN,
SHE DEFINITELY OVERDID IT.
I KNEW SHE WAS GONNA OVERDO IT,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE WE'RE
GONNA HANG THESE THINGS.
I'M GONNA TIE THEM ALONG--ALONG
THE DECK AND STUFF, ALL RIGHT?
- WHO CARES WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE?
FOOD'S HERE.
- THANK GOD.
- I JUST HOPE EVERYTHING
WORKS OUT GOOD.
OW.
- WOULD YOU PLEASE RELAX?
- I'M TRYING.
HOW CAN I RELAX WHEN I
HAVE TO DO ALL THIS [bleep]?
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL ABOUT TIMING.
DO WE HAVE TIME FOR YOU TO RUB
MY FEET REAL QUICK?
- NO.
- I, LIKE, WANT HER TO SEE IT
WHEN SHE WALKS IN.
IT'S CUTE.
DON'T FALL.
- GOT IT.
- IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- TELL ME IF IT'S CENTERED.
- PUT IT DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
WHY IS IT SO HOT OUT?
- 'CAUSE IT'S THE SUMMER.
- OH, CUTE.
GREAT, THEY'RE TANGLED.
- WE DID IT.
- NO, WE'RE MISSING
THE MARIACHI BAND.
WE DIDN'T DO IT YET.
WHAT IF THEY COME AND THEN
THE MARIACHI BAND'S NOT HERE?
- THIS EPISODE OF
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- CONTINUES NOW.
- ALL RIGHT, WHERE'S THIS BAND?
ALL WE NEED IS THE BAND,
AND WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
[knocking at door]
THAT'S GOT TO BE
THE MARIACHI BAND.
WHY IS HE KNOCKING SO HARD?
- OH, MY GOD.
[playing mariachi music]
- I'M LITERALLY JUST SO HAPPY
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE EVERYTHING
IS FALLING INTO PLACE.
WE HAVE EVERYTHING DONE,
AND BASICALLY WE JUST
HAVE TO WAIT
FOR JENNI AND ROGER TO GET HERE.
- YAY!
- WE'RE ALMOST HERE, BABY.
- IS THAT THEM?
DID THEY PULL UP?
- OH, [bleep], THEY'RE HERE.
WE SAY WHAT, WELCOME HOME?
YOU'RE GONNA
BE THE FIRST PERSON.
- WELCOME HOME.
- YOU GO.
- IT'S HOT OUT HERE.
WE GOT TO GET HER INSIDE.
- WELCOME HOME, MATTHEWS FAMILY.
NO.
- WELCOME HOME, MEILANI.
- JUST WELCOME HOME.
- RIGHT, THAT'LL DO.
- WELCOME HOME, WELCOME MEILANI.
- WELCOME HOME, MEILANI.
- AFTER MOMMY.
- WAIT TILL--WAIT
TILL THEY GET UP.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
both: WELCOME HOME, MEILANI.
- HEY.
- HI, BABY.
- HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- HERE, LET ME TAKE HER
OFF YOUR HANDS
- YOU GOT HER? YOU SURE?
- COME ON, I GOT HER.
- I'M A LITTLE BIT NERVOUS.
I KNOW YOU'VE DONE IT BEFORE,
THOUGH.
- OH, MY GOD.
HOLY PINK.
THERE ARE, LIKE,
BALLOONS EVERYWHERE.
I AM SO EXCITED, 'CAUSE
THERE'S PICTURES
OF ME AND NICOLE
THAT WE TOOK RIGHT BEFORE I
WENT INTO THE HOSPITAL.
THERE'S A HUGE MEILANI SIGN,
AND I'M JUST LIKE,
"WHAT THE [bleep] IS GOING ON?"
AND THERE'S NICOLE AND JIONNI,
JUST SO WELCOMING.
LIKE, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID ALL THIS FOR ME.
- I GOT YOU A PRESENT OUTSIDE.
- I'M GONNA STAY WITH MEILANI,
GO AHEAD.
- ROGER, COME HERE.
I GOT YOU A PRESENT.
COME HERE, JENNI.
- HOLY CRAP.
YOU GOT A MARIACHI BAND?
[playing Rock-A-Bye Baby]
IT'S A FRICKING MARIACHI BAND.
LIKE, WHO HIRES A MARIACHI BAND?
NO WAY.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT A MARIACHI BAND IS.
HOW DO YOU DANCE
TO MARIACHI MUSIC?
- I DON'T KNOW, BABY.
I'LL JUST HOLD YOU TIGHT.
THAT'S ALL I DO.
- THEY'RE DANCING.
- I CAN'T EVEN EXPLAIN TO YOU,
LIKE, HOW GOOD NICOLE
AND JIONNI HAVE BEEN.
- IT WAS A GREAT WELCOME HOME.
- IT'S SUCH A, LIKE, WARM, KIND
OF LIKE A FUZZY, WARM FEELING
TO HAVE SUCH, LIKE,
GOOD FRIENDS.
- FOR ME, IT JUST
LETS ME KNOW, YOU KNOW,
HOW CLOSE WE--WE REALLY ARE,
AND WHAT THEY
THINK OF US AS PEOPLE,
AND IT'S VERY FLATTERING,
AND I HOPE THAT WE CAN RETURN
THAT FAVOR ONE DAY.
- ARE YOU CRYING?
AWW.
I'M GONNA KILL THEM.
- THAT IS AWESOME.
- WISH I HAD A MARIACHI BAND.
[end notes]
- NEXT TIME ON SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW...
- SEE IF MOMMY NOTICES
IF WE PUT A LITTLE BREAST MILK
CREAMER IN HER COFFEE.
- I WANT THE DOGS
TO MEET MEILANI.
- I HAD FORGOTTEN
WE EVEN HAD THEM.
- OH, SHE GAVE HER KISSES.
- I'M SO EXCITED
FOR MY BRIDAL SHOWER.
LOOK AT ALL MY PRESENTS.
WHEE!
- HERE,
I BOUGHT YOU YOUR LINGERIE
FOR YOUR HONEYMOON.
- WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
I'M GONNA GET PREGNANT AGAIN.