Hi!
Captain Marleau?
- Yeah!
Mario.
- Nice to meet you.
We don't have a head Republican Guard?
You have a head to work in CID?
Me, I don't parade with the
spiked helmets!
Is this my pony?
- No.
We don't let you drive a Formula 1.
That's yours.
Equestrian segregation!
- I see.
Hello. Hi, my bunny! How are you?
Go on!
- Like that?
Yes, facing the horse. The other leg.
Left leg! Left leg.
Left... Left leg.
Left!
In the stirrup. We'll adjust the reins.
- We'll adjust the reins.
Hold onto the mane.
- Like this?
That's it. Foot in the stirrup.
- Like that?
That's right, and:
- Yeah.
grab the raised part at the back of
the saddle and mount.
Yeah, but; you have to push my ass.
You're funny!
- Mount the saddle.!
Really?
- It can't be true.
TWO LIVES
Elodie?
Sorry? Do we know each other?
10 years,
with no news,
and you just show up like that.
I know, I blame myself, when
I couldn't-
Of course you could! You could
pick up a phone!
A call? You really believe that?
Can you imagine what Garance
went through?
And Jonathan?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
As if. But you haven't come
for nothing.
You said you were in love.
What's the problem?
I love my life, but I often feel alone.
OK, so you come to see your
old friend Elodie?
I missed you.
I want to reconnect with this
part of my life.
All right.
And you think that part of your life
wants to reconnect with you?
Hey.
You show up now with no warning?
I didn't want to bother you.
And the photos, are those of birds?
It's my lawyer's idea.
Photos could sway the judge's decision.
Go on, get off my land.
Enjoy your home, Christophe,
on Friday it's over.
Eric was here.
You let him go without saying
anything?
What did you want me to do?
Something, for a change!
I saw you with Eric.
What did he want?
Nothing in particular.
Same puzzle as yesterday, Louise?
Not making much progress!
It's level 5!
Mind your onions.
Are you taking me to the
restaurant tonight?
No, not tonight, sorry.
It would do us good.
- I know, but no.
I have too many things on my mind,
the farm, and all that.
Next time, okay? Yeah?
Should rain. Ground is dry above the barn.
You started sowing in the
northern plot!
Your father always started in
the southern part.
The land is also dry in the south.
- We'll see in 10 days, when nothing
will have sprouted!
- We'll see, yes.
I've seen it all, moron!
Laetitia isn't here?
- Having trouble seeing?
Big ride.
Alright, comrades?
Come on, come on; it's okay,
it's okay.
She's 10?
Thanks, bunny!
So?
Fuck! Was she strangled?
Are you the one in charge?
- I didn't do anything.
Immediately with the prejudice!
Are there indications other
than that?
Yes, bruises all over the place.
- Get me a coffee, please?
Look at her.
On the back, the hips.
- No, that's cellulite. Yeah.
What do you think happened?
Fell on her back: the horse reared,
knocking her off.
The usual yada yada, someone
goes "Waaa!"
The horse goes "Heeee," she goes bang!
Captain Marleau!
Ha ha!
Briere!
- I'm happy to see you again.
What are you doing in Correze?
Had enough of the seaside?
I asked for a transfer after
I got commendations.
The seaside attracts cityfolk. At the
slightest sign of crime,
the Paris guys are on our backs.
"Parigot," calf's head!
That's it.
- Yes.
Saut Balou is my horse-friend.
Now what about this good woman?
Is she baroness-of-the-hunt,
privileged?
No, a farmer's wife.
Mr. Lemaire, companion of the victim.
He found the body.
Dumpling,
er, my condolences.
- No need to force it. Questions?
No. Did she often ride?
- Everyday.
At the same time?
- Mornings.
She liked to start her day on horseback.
Doesn't everyone? Yeah.
Will you excuse me, this is my friend,
I haven't seen him for a long time.
Got something on this guy?
- You suspect he did it?
It's the guys who strangle their
wives, not the horses.
That's true; he's a farmer. According
to my colleagues,
he and his wife were discreet,
the kind of hard workers
dedicated to the family business.
- Okay.
Shall we take him in?
- No, he just lost his wife!
And we don't have any proof.
- It's you who says-
You know me!
Hey...
Where is the widower? Have you seen
a widower with hair?
Captain! There he is.
- Where is he?
Down there, shall I go get him?
- No, I know my widowers!
Sir!
You shouldn't leave a crime scene,
especially when it's your wife.
It's weird.
- It's a shortcut.
And where are you going?
- The farm, to feed the horses.
Yeah? Your wife dies, and you
think of horses?
I also think about my seedlings.
- Do you have combines?
How long have you known her, the deceased?
Her name was Laetitia. Ten years.
We met at a party in Saint-Pessac,
we had a drink.
She slept over at my house
and never left.
What was she doing here?
- She was helping.
She was a farmer's wife.
- How did she help? Cleaning, sweeping,
polishing, shopping, cooking, kids,
not paid, not declared, right?
What were you doing this morning?
Where were you?
- On my tractor.
Alone?
- Tractors aren't for passengers.
Yeah? Like coffins
on the merry-go-round of life.
I have a call, excuse me.
Yeah Briere? Do you already
have something?
What do you mean nowhere?
Really? Thanks, honey.
So, as I was saying.
Your wife: 0 traces, 0 records.
That's impossible.
Is that her bag?
Yeah, it's not mine.
- Why, are bags gendered?
Blue for boys, pink for girls?
You don't really look
upset by what's happening.
Not answering?
"I say, captain, who else should we
talk to, besides these people?"
Back to work. So what's in this bag?
A wallet,
money,
business card.
Thppt.
And what is this?
A loyalty card for Pizza Loca!
We may have a punch for a free pizza.
Or overcooked pasta.
A Neapolitan crime?
Tell me what you're looking for if
you want me to help.
I don't know. I'm looking!
I'm looking for anything.
Something with your wife's
name on it, a passport,
driving license. Even a national health
card would be fine.
Maybe she had them with her
and they were stolen?
- Not stupid.
Killed by the health card gang.
It's not stupid.
No more stupid than a free pizza.
The fact she's not in your files,
is it a problem?
She didn't do anything wrong.
- The problem is a good citizen
is a registered citizen.
Chinese proverb. Now your wife
is not listed anywhere.
Neither social security number
nor date of birth.
It looks like she never existed.
- I don't know what to tell you.
She was very real.
Um, but come on, I know maybe
where you can look.
I'm wearing you down.
It's over there.
What, have you caught the Covid?
I'll let you search. It's your job,
not mine.
Do I do all the work?
We don't talk like that to a captain of
the Gendarmerie!
Louise Lemaire.
Excuse my son. Respect for rank,
he doesn't know.
Apologize!
Don't argue about it, his wife
has just died.
That's not a reason.
- Does she always talk to you like this?
He's my son, I talk to him how I want.
My son, my fight? And to his woman,
how did you talk to her?
Laetitia never caused me no problem.
She was a very nice girl, solid!
You have to be, to work here.
And to stay that long with my son!
And with you, it was going well
also, I imagine?
What was your son doing
this morning?
He was in the fields. He should have
started with the southern plot.
- That doesn't interest the captain.
Yes, it interests me!
I also want to know where you were
this morning, ma'am Louise.
I was making my lunch in the kitchen.
I also went to the vegetable garden to
look for vegetables.
Can they testify?
Who?
- The large local vegetables.
You don't practice soup humor?
Ha ha ha!
No, basically, no.
Hey.
Anyway, life is funny. Your wife
dies in the north
while you were there sowing
little seeds of life.
Does the timing put me at
the scene?
It's not me, it's your mother.
Your mother says that normally you
had to sow the seeds
in the south of the farm.
- What were you doing up north?
- Ouch. - Did you plant settlements?
It hurts?
I took a float from the drain
pump hose.
A float, huh? Show me.
If it will make you happy.
- It's one of the perks of the job.
There.
Disgusting! Do you ever
wear deodorant?
When did it happen?
- This morning. Risks of the business.
Or the risks of attacking someone
who defends themselves.
Like your wife, for example.
- Why would I have killed her?
Exactly, that's what we would
like to know.
To make a bruise like this
takes strength.
And Laetitia was not
a heavyweight.
No need to be strong. We manage
to make babies!
We'll show that to the medical
examiner, OK?
I'm counting on you, Mr. Christophe!
Bye, Louise!
Never do that again!
You didn't tell her anything about Eric,
I hope.
No, what should I have told her?
You really think he came to take
pictures this morning?
He's after our farm! He was
after your wife too!
Open your eyes, you
offal sausage!
Poor kid.
Shame, shame!
We said the 8th.
I can't do anything. What do
I tell my guys?
What's confusing? I didn't say 18.
I'll never be ready, man!
I'll call you back.
What are you doing here?
Wasn't it the farm enough for you?
You wanted Laetitia too!
What are you saying?
- I saw you looking at her!
No way, Christophe! I'd never do
that, the family is sacred!
Why are you here talking to me?
- Laetitia is dead, Eric!
It's not true! When?
- This morning, after you left.
Wait, you don't think...
Stop! Christophe!
Stop! I have nothing to do with
Laetitia's death!
OK?
Hey, guys!
Yeah, Briere?
So, have you found anything on her?
I'm warning you, if you make me
happy I'll adopt you.
It won't be today, I didn't find
anything. And you?
Nothing! No Laetitia Dubus with
the phone carriers.
But! Christophe has two subscriptions
in his name!
That doesn't tell us why we can
find no trace of the victim.
She's not a hologram! Anyway, short of
the Holy Spirit, I figured it out.
It smacks of a voluntary disappearance.
A change of identity.
Find the list of women who have been
missing for 10 years.
OK, when do you need it?
- Now!
Are you stupid or what? Hello!
By dint of working with you, I've
learned to be in your head.
Be careful, it's contagious.
- I knew what you'd ask:
I've already pulled the cases of
disappearance or death
of women of about 30 years of age.
I'll show you what I found.
"Pauline LeBihan"?
It was 10 years ago, near Brive.
Pauline, a researcher
and mother, left her husband and child
like "that" without saying anything.
There was no news for 3 days.
She was found on a bridge.
She took the plunge with too long
a rubber band?
She was helped to jump.
A young man on a moped tried
to snatch her bag,
Pauline resisted. He pushes
her away, she falls.
Splash!
- Who was the youngster?
A certain Arnaud Naudin, AKA "Nono."
Well known to the social services.
We quickly caught him, he was
tried and imprisoned.
We didn't find the corpse?
- No.
Just a shoe, downstream. To investigators
and her family, she was dead.
Of course, sonny. I'll call the
ex-husband.
To ID the body?
I've already done it. He's meeting
you at the morgue.
You are formidable, you know that?
I'm your friend, Briere!
The court has postponed the hearing?
The Covid can take the blame! It's been
8 months, let him hold this file!
I have to leave you.
15 or 20 minutes.
OK, so long.
Mr. LeBihan, Captain Marleau.
Do you know why you here?
You've finally found her?
- Who is that?
Your woman! We don't
know yet.
First, you have to identify the body.
After 10 years, I can't see what
will remain to be identified.
It may be hard. You wanna
have a drink first?
No, I have work waiting for me.
- You sure?
As you wish.
"This way, please."
Well?
Yes, it's Pauline.
That's all? Hide your joy.
- I must identify her, no? It's her.
"It's her, it's her."
You can see it's not a corpse
from 10 years ago!
It's brand new!
In your place-
- You are not in my place.
The wounds there.
She hanged herself?
There? No!
She was killed. The problem is that
we don't know who did it.
What's wrong, sir?
He seems to be thinking.
I have so many questions, I don't
know where to start.
From the beginning.
It's good, the beginning.
And there you go!
- A farm.
It doesn't look like Pauline.
- It looks so different
that she was calling herself
"Laetitia DuBus."
It's unbelievable.
Why did she leave you 10 years ago?
We never knew.
- How's that, "we"?
Me and my daughter Garance.
She was 8.
She pulled herself together,
but it was hard.
"Dad, why did Mum leave?
Dad, why aren't we looking
for her more?"
Then it will be: "Daddy, why did Mom
want us to think she was dead
rather than come home?"
- And especially:
"Daddy, who struck back at mom?"
Do you have any idea who
found mum?
No? Come, I'll show you something.
There it is.
What are we doing here?
- I'll let you guess.
This is where Pauline was killed.
- Is that so? Have you been here?
No. There are remnants of crime scene tape
on the tree.
- Eye of a sphinx!
I'm a criminal lawyer.
- And not myopic.
Where was the body?
The body, where was it?
I don't like to say bullshit;
The body was where you are!
How am I going to tell my
daughter about this?
Call her. A lawyer knows how to
make pretty speeches, right?
This one will not be beautiful.
I can take care of it.
We're used to it at the Gendarmerie,
listening to people cry.
Garance, are you there?
Come here, sweetie.
- What is it?
Garance?
Gendarmerie Nationale,
Captain Marleau.
Did I do something forbidden?
- We'll see. It's about your mother.
Elodie? She's not my mother.
- Not that one, the other one.
The true one. How shall I put it?
You know in Moliere? "The little
cat, it's dead."
No, it's not that. Do you know Camus?
Have you studied him? Do you know
the first sentence of "The Foreigner"?
"Today, my mother is dead."
- That's it.
We got there.
10 years ago, your mother survived
her fall from the bridge.
Instead of coming home, she
invented a new life for herself.
A false name, a false background.
- We found her this morning.
Dead.
You knew that she wasn't dead?
No! I would have told you!
What happened?
Thppt. We don't know. But
this time she's really dead!
Someone killed her.
You are really not delicate.
What did she do all these years?
She lived with a man on a farm,
60 km from here.
- Why didn't she say anything?
I'd like to know that. Was it going
well with your father?
Do you suspect him?
- Should I?
No.
No. But I imagine if he discovered
her, he would
not have been pleased. Nor I.
- Are you also suspicious?
What did my father say?
In fact, not much.
He gave you his Anguished Father
number?
Don't have any illusions,
it's just to make you do his
dirty work for him.
What a big lie.
You can't imagine what he's
been able to achieve
with judges and jurors just
by acting.
No no no, wait a bit before coming
home, you never know.
I said nothing about you and Pauline.
And better keep that to ourselves,
okay?
OK.
Arnaud Naudin, called "Nono."
He did some jail time for the
murder of Pauline LeBihan.
He's been working here for
two weeks.
- That's all? - That's all.
- Let's do it.
Hey!
Nono?
Him?
General tour, cut the engines!
Mr. Nono?
I prefer Arnaud.
- You don't like little robots?
No, that was the old me.
Now it's Arnaud.
Okay Mr. Nono For Now,
we have questions.
On the new life of Mrs. LeBihan?
How do you know that?
She told me. She came to see me.
You didn't know?
- No.
After she fell from the bridge, she was
carried away by the current.
When she woke up, she understood
what fate wanted to tell her.
So she chose to disappear and
start a new life,
somewhere where no one knew
her. But after 10 years-
I don't want to live a lie anymore.
I didn't want you to learn the
truth from someone else.
I promise you, you will be
cleared and compensated.
I just ask that you wait a little longer.
Was it bizarre to see her again?
Alive, and more?
I was relieved and happy. I was
no longer a murderer!
Happy like Ulysses making a long
trip to the slammer,
because of her. Weren't you angry?
Anger, I try to forget. A first
step toward serenity.
Namaste, Nono Rinpoche.
Do you do yoga?
- No, Buddhism
isn't really my thing. I'm just
another man.
Nono would still have ended up
in prison
even without meeting Pauline,
because he was angry.
Angry!
You didn't kill her yesterday morning?
- No, I...
What did you say?
- She's dead!
For good this time. But we don't
know who killed her.
Condemned twice for the murder
of the same woman!
I don't have an alibi for
yesterday morning!
Beautiful in the morning, crow in the
evening; you're really bad luck, you.
Fuck! Mom, what are you doing?
Burning the field!
- Burn the field? You're crazy!
Eric won, our land will be sold.
No one can have it!
Let go of me!
It's not like that, we'll get out of it!
What do you want to do?
Beg your cousin?
Sure, he'll listen to you!
I'll see the banker.
He denied you the loan. Will he
make you another one?
I'll find an argument.
An argument? You only have
one: horses.
Horses? I can't, they're Laetitia's.
She's no longer here.
At 16 she can eat without
being watched.
She wants to go to school!
- Dear...
You don't have to go to class
with what happened.
I prefer going, to think about
something else.
OK.
- Thank you, Elodie.
See you tonight.
- See you tonight.
Garance, what are you doing?
Woo-hoo!
You're crazy!
- Go slowly!
You'll end up planted!
Do you know Pauline LeBihan?
- No.
That's the real name of
your wife.
Come!
Come, I brought croissants and beer!
You never had a flea on your toe?
Laetitia told me she was fed up
with her old life.
I wasn't going to bother her with that.
- No past, no papers,
no Social Security number, no bank account.
You never saw anything?
- I'm not the curious type.
Not curious? To know who they
are: parent, family, friends.
I tried to talk to her about it,
it made her uncomfortable.
So I avoided the subject.
Lying to her boyfriend
for 10 years!
- It's not really a lie.
What is it?
A secret. It respects itself.
Otherwise what?
She could have left.
- So you knew
she was hiding something! You were
afraid she would leave.
How long were you afraid?
- From the first second.
A girl like her who falls in love
with a guy like me,
it doesn't happen.
Yes it does, in Beauty and the Beast.
But since then there has been King
Kong Theory. "Thank you, Ste. Virginia!"
What a con! If I had asked her questions
about her past,
she would be gone but-
- She wouldn't be dead.
Silence kills: my friend Dom,
when she was young,
she was little was raped by her godfather.
She's been wasting away for 62 years
because her family told her:
"Shut up, Dom. Don't say anything!"
By the way,
the coroner said your thingummy was
due to a metal object.
Yes, my grain pipe.
Yeah, sure.
That's it.
On that matter:
a present!
Guy?
No, no not him, not now!
Guy! We're going to be late
for the match!
Jean-Claude, there is no match today.
Huh?
- And Guy is not here.
We're meeting here!
It's not the right day. There is
no match,
and Guy is not here.
I'll take you home.
Let's go!
Magnificent!
You're really magnificent!
- Go cook an egg!
Who's he?
Jean-Claude Merle. He lives
in the village.
Do you want to be a model?
I'm not a model to pursue, I'm a cop.
What are you doing here?
I came to see my friend Guy,
but he's not here.
Tell him I came by?
Yes, yes!
He has memory trouble.
Goodbye sir.
- There's your bike.
Can he go by himself?
Yes, he comes about once a month,
it's always the same.
Fine.
- Yeah.
Who is Guy?
My brother.
- Your brother.
They're beautiful, your vegetables.
You love your land.
Yes. "Your word and the earth
are what is true," that's my motto.
I've always stuck to it.
Not "Your word and the earth
are not to speak"?
Is it the motto of your son too?
Yes, education is like the Earth,
it must be passed down.
But after Christophe all that
will be lost.
Why? He didn't want to have
kids with his wife?
I guess not.
It doesn't look like you
were thrilled.
A woman who doesn't want
children doesn't exist.
Or else Christophe couldn't
convince her.
A woman who doesn't want kids
doesn't exist? What else!
What about me? I must stop
and read "The Weekly Patriarchy"!
You and your son are going strong.
It takes a lot.
- If he's not happy he can leave!
Maybe he wanted to leave with
his wife, leave the farm
his darling mother holds close
to her heart!
Christophe will never leave me alone.
The school called me. Garance
didn't show up this morning.
That's nice of you, thanks. Yes.
I'll keep you informed.
She's not at Baptiste's.
They're not together, his parents say
he was in class.
Shit! She isn't at school or the
hospital, or at her boyfriend's house.
None of her girlfriends know anything.
- Something happened to her.
Listen!
She learned her mother lied
to her for 10 years,
yesterday she was murdered. And
like that she disappears.
I'm calling the gendarme.
Well? The banker?
If we sell the horses, that could
be enough for the downpayment.
Anyway, the decision will be
made upstairs.
Another blow for nothing. It's your
cousin who will be happy!
The banker is optimistic.
The banker doesn't care! He is
paid the same every month!
We struggle all the time!
I struggle-
- Sorry?
I'm the one who fought for the loan!
Begging the banker isn't the end
of the world!
I'm not discussing that with you.
You did what you had to do before.
OK, I'm going to take a shower.
Thank you for acting so quickly.
- That's public service.
Hello madam. Are you the replacement
for Mrs. LeBihan?
Elodie. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
When did your daughter disappear?
She caught her bus at 7:42 am.
Since then, a mystery.
It's the first time she's done this?
Yes. She's a serious girl.
The disappearance and death
of her mother
aren't necessarily linked.
- I wouldn't say that at all.
Where does your daughter sleep?
At the bottom, there.
The door?
Nobody.
Wow!
How you doing, Frida Kahlo?
"I love you like crazy, like a soldier,
like a movie star."
A song by Laurent Fabius.
Say!
A home Big Brother!
How does this work? What do you
have to press?
You talk to it: "Hello, you!"
Hello you!
- No, to the machine.
Ah?
HELLO, YOU!
Hello, Garance. Do you
have a question?
Ha! My name is not Garance.
HELLO, SPEAKER!
Are you pregnant with a beautiful
little robot?
The concept of beauty is subjective.
According to Kant, beauty is what
universally pleases.
She's funny!
Can we please come back to my
daughter's disappearance?
It's OK, relax!
HELLO, SPEAKER,
DID MR. JONATHAN HERE KNOW
THAT HIS WIFE, not you, ma'am,
LED A DOUBLE LIFE?
I do not understand the question.
Me neither, I don't understand.
- Yes!
I questioned the first killer of your wife.
not you, madam.
His name is Mr. Nono, like "little robot."
It seems your ex-wife revealed herself
to him first.
It was expected she would then
see you two.
In any case, she didn't come see me.
- Me neither.
Back on topic, in that case.
HELLO SPEAKER!
WHY DID GARANCE LEAVE HOME?
I do not understand the question.
You never understand anything!
This thing is useless.
So are you! That's crazy!
My daughter is in danger and
you play with a box!
Hello, Speaker?
What is Garance's recent internet
search history?
There. Behind you.
FARMHOUSE MURDER
- Where's that?
Where Pauline lived for 10 years.
And where her murderer lives.
Maybe. Or maybe not.
You-are you Laetitia's daughter?
She was called that?
Yes.
Your parents at least know
where you are?
Yes, yes it's good.
Laetitia also lied very badly.
Says the guy who got fooled
for 10 years.
That's true.
You have the same sense of repartee
as your mother.
I'm not my mother, OK? I have nothing
to do with her.
Don't say that.
- Yes, she was a monster.
She abandoned her husband, her daughter;
what kind of mother does that?
I don't know. You know mine is
still around, so...
Do you know this was her horse?
"Diabolo."
All right?
Listen,
you have a perfect right to be angry
with your mother.
I would be too in your place.
And you, you don't blame her?
Yes, yes, but I tell myself she didn't
lie in order to hurt me.
We can all be pushed to do something
wrong one day.
Depending on context.
- We have to forgive everything?
Not necessarily. Trying to
understand is good.
He's with her, the bastard!
- Yes, I'm taking care of it.
HEY!
For god sake.
- Dad!
Are you OK?
- Yes, fine.
You disappeared.
Why did you leave like that?
You took a big risk.
- What risk?
It's not a safe place.
What isn't a safe place? Huh?
There's a killer on the loose around here.
Go for it, say I killed Laetitia.
That's what I just said, you're too
slow to understand.
I think your wife liked other talents.
You're referring to me?
It's hard to admit she'd rather
live with a louse
than with you!
The louse is going to jail.
- Are you going to fight?
What will that prove? Mom's dead!
She won't go home with the winner
of your pissing match!
Thppt!
QED, I wouldn't have said it better.
A good head on that kid.
Hey presumption-of-innocence,
know a lawyer?
You, we need to talk, come. Him too,
I'll question him:
Yeah, you. Anyway,
what exactly were you doing that day
with her on your back, I'd like to know.
What else is there?
Your wife had trunks full of secrets.
She said nothing to me.
- She told Nono,
Nono was the guy who was with her
the first time she died.
She found him?
What would you have done if you knew
she was going to disclose her secret?
That secret was the glue of
your relationship.
No more secrets, no more couple
or kissy-kissy.
Killing her wouldn't have solved
the problem.
The problem is every 3 days a guy
kills his wife who says
he prefers seeing her dead
than not having her all to himself.
"Hello" Briere.
- Captain.
Come closer.
Are you afraid of a horse?
He's your replacement!
Can I talk to you?
- Yes. You've got him?
What is it?
- Here;
the call history of Christophe Lemaire.
Yes, and?
- This is the phone the victim was using.
Oh?
- And that number.
- Yes?
Do you know whose it is?
No, but you're going to tell me.
Yes, it's Elodie Merchant's.
Merchant of what?
Elodie, the new companion of
Jonathan LeBihan.
You know what? You're the child
I'll never have, Briere.
Captain.
Captain, why have you summoned me?
- Sit down, I'll show you.
Look. Phone bills of Madam Laetitia.
Formerly Madam Pauline.
All calls she made and received.
And look, in yellow:
your number!
Since when did you know she wasn't dead?
A year.
- You failed to tell us.
Really? Ex-best friend, Jonathan's
new wife,
the only one who knows Pauline's
secret: the ideal suspect!
That calculation then
saying nothing is worse.
I didn't kill Pauline!
Don't yell at me! It's not my fault!
How did you know she wasn't dead?
From her, she came to see me.
No, you got married?
Yes, for 3 years.
Who's the lucky guy?
Do I know him?
It's Jonathan.
After your death-
well, your disappearance-we got closer.
He needed someone and I was there.
Thanks for your honesty. I knew.
Is that so? How?
I live on a farm, but I have internet.
Listen,
since we're saying things,
can I ask a question?
Why did you leave 10 years ago?
Because of your job? Because
of Jonathan?
No no because of me.
Pauline confessed to me
that she suffered from absence of
maternal instinct.
She was unable to experience love
for her own daughter,
like a normal mother.
She saw herself as a heartless monster,
and it gnawed at her.
One day she broke down and left
without saying a word.
"Maternal instinct," that's bullshit.
Your friend left her man, and
she said to herself:
"He's going to find someone better
to raise our daughter."
Lots of guys do that, right?
- I don't know.
This is what she was hoping for.
I hid for 3 days.
Without sleeping or eating.
I didn't know if I was going to do
the right thing or not.
I came to a bridge.
And there in front of the sunrise,
I asked myself:
go home, or go for good?
Finally, someone decided for me.
She didn't call you to compare
wedding dresses?
No. At first it was to fill a void.
She was happy, but something
was missing.
What? A friend to confide in?
Because she phoned you a week
before dying.
Yes, she wanted to see me.
It sounded urgent.
You thought about it a lot, what
does that imply?
It's been a month that I've
thought about it.
Garance will be in shock.
- Yes, but it must be done.
Why now?
- It's complicated, I have my reasons.
No, you can't leave me like that
without telling me more.
It regards Christophe. I learned
some things about him.
There are things that need to change.
What needs to change? Are you
going to leave him?
Pauline, answer me.
If you want Jonathan back,
I won't let you do it.
No. I promise you, you know.
- What then?
I can't tell you.
It concerns a man's death.
A man's death? Who was it?
She didn't tell me.
After she saw your husband,
Mr. Jonathan?
She planned to.
- When?
WHEN?
Okay:
the day she got done in.
Guys.
Is he here, the lawyer?
- Yes, in your office.
And he's not happy. He said he's
the victim of police harassment.
I don't care. Good lawyers always
cook things up better.
She's coming.
What the whorehouse is this?
Where's my wife?
Why is she here?
- Hello, maitre.
A whorehouse is a place of work,
but your wife isn't here for
a job interview,
rather for a free hearing: we suspect
her in Pauline's death.
What? Nobody knew she was
still alive!
Is that so? You astonish me. Listen.
All calls she made and received.
And look, in yellow:
your number! Since when did you
know she wasn't dead?
A year.
- You failed to tell us.
We don't record people who are
in court, only those in custody.
I want to be her lawyer.
- We'll see about that later.
There, I'm taking a break.
- Where are you going?
2 hours of hearings so far! Briere!
I'm going to the cafe across the way.
3, 2, 1... enter the lawyer.
What are you playing at?
- Something foamy, maitre?
Not thirsty.
You're right, better to be sober when
preparing your defense.
Especially when suspected of murder.
Me too, I'm a suspect?
- Long suspense:
Your living wife says your dead wife
wanted to see you again.
If she did, you saw her again
and you went crazy,
like "that", like with Mr. Christophe.
You have nothing.
- No.
"Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, you
have nothing on my client here present.
He had no reason to kill his wife!
She left him, she passed herself off
as dead.
For 10 years she left him alone
to raise their poor little 7-year-old girl,
while she lay in the arms of
a toothless farmer-"
What do you say? Crickets?
Shall I continue?
I could never have killed her.
- No.
"He could never have killed
this woman,
this liar, this usurper, this
unworthy mother!
In short, this woman.
'And why, ' you ask me?"
Yes: why, sir?
Because I still loved her.
I've been trying 10 years to forget her.
She's always there.
Guys who kill their wives on
the pretext that they love them:
there are many.
- I know.
Even defended some, people like that.
It's not the most brilliant thing you did.
Mr. Christophe!
Celebrating your wife's funeral?
The bank approved my loan. I can make
an offer to Eric.
Why did they change their mind?
- My contribution. I'm selling the horses.
They're worth a lot?
- Some, yes. Diabolo, especially.
It was good, your wife's death.
- Think what you want,
I don't care. What do you want?
You're boring. A year ago,
your wife saw her former friend again.
You knew that? No, you never
know anything.
If you know my answers,
you don't need me.
Pfft! You've got a short fuse!
Hey Christophe! Your woman, when
she spoke to her friend,
she also said she had learned
something about you.
What I mean to say, or not, is:
how do you figure that
right after saying this, she dies?
Coincidence?
At the Gendarmerie, we have the
Big Golden Book of Coincidences.
Come with me to autograph it.
YOU THERE! No one's going anywhere!
What does this one think,
that she's taking my son in?
Respect for the uniform?
- Put that down, mom.
She knows about Guy's death.
- So what?
Why would she believe us?
- We'll explain it to her.
It was an accident.
Give him the pitchfork,
it might be loaded.
If even my son is against me-
Stop being paranoid,
Come and have a fireside chat, huh?
Your son can come in on his own,
he's a big boy.
We all have our demons. My brother's
was alcohol.
One evening I saw him come back,
he had his belt in his hand.
That time he went after Eric.
And you said nothing? Beautiful family.
That night, Eric wasn't there.
Only Christophe.
And I told him! So he said
"I'll make do with what I have,
with what I find."
So I jumped on him!
- Mom...
I was 7 years old.
I came out of my room, I saw my
uncle wasn't moving.
I realized his head had hit the floor:
whiplash.
- That's hot.
Then?
Then I panicked. My mom, responsible
for my dead uncle,
I saw myself ending my life in care.
But mom told me to grab Guy's feet.
That's not a mother, she's a witch!
Is it Salem here?
You pretended it was an accident?
A serious fall.
And since he was drunk, that sold it.
You're Machiavellian!
- And after,
we promised to take this secret
to our graves.
"My word, the earth!"
Yes, except I broke my promise.
I told Laetitia about it. Captain,
about the pitchfork:
you're not going to file a complaint?
If I filed a complaint against everyone
who can't stand me,
we could do a TV series.
Good! We're going to draft a statement
about your piece-of-work uncle.
It was an accident,
There's mitigation!
- Registering for an insurance check?
What's your damage?
Don't make fun!
Move: in the car, Louise!
"This way."
Captain, will you bring her back?
- Do you see "Uber Gendarme" anywhere?
Don't make fun. By the way-
how did your wife react when
you told her?
I told her I had to speak, to free
myself from the weight.
A bit like her. Can't always
clear your history!
Come on, hot stuff.
Captain.
- Thank you, my dear.
Here we are!
A beautiful, brand new statement!
You read it, then you sign it.
However:
this one is not brand new. 1980.
I struggled to get it, but it
was worth it
because I have a lot of stuff in it:
especially that someone said your
brother is dead
because of a quarrel with you.
"Guy was my friend,
it's that slut Louise who did it."
Who is this witness?
Jean-Claude?
Yes. It doesn't surprise me
that it was him.
He could never blame me.
It was mutual.
What he said wasn't true?
- It's bullshit!
Bullshit! I never had a problem
with my brother. Besides-
And he would surely still be
alive, if what happened
hadn't happened.
I'm done with the mother. Can you
take her back to her son?
Is she confident, or do you plan
to marleauter it?
"Marleauter"? Don't say bad words.
No, you give people some leeway,
You make her believe she's home free,
and when she least expects it: squawk!
I'm not as smart as I look.
In any event,
I would never do that to a helpless woman,
even if she doesn't tell us everything...
the naughty!
Mom?
Well? Is it all good?
What is it? It doesn't seem to be.
Are you seriously asking me?
This story, it was between us.
Why did you need to tell Laetitia?
Have you seen the mess?
- What mess?
It's been eating at us for 40 years.
Don't you feel relieved?
Relieved of what?
Now everyone one will know.
- Will know what?
That you accidentally killed your brother
trying to protect your son?
Mom?
Answer me!
Don't use that tone when you
talk to your mother!
ANSWER ME!
- But...
This is finished!
FINISHED!
The farm is divided into thirds.
I want to sell, my cousin too,
but not Christophe. But he doesn't
have enough to buy back our shares.
Hey, really tight, the cousins.
- You said it, not me.
As it dragged on, we took
the case to court.
"We"? Strange your cousin didn't
tell me about it.
He's ashamed. For people like
him and his mother,
losing their land is worse than anything.
Worse than losing his wife?
Honestly? For them, I think it's equal.
Honestly, it's none of my business,
but a courtroom is not great for
a family reunion.
I don't know. Ask Christophe to
find out what she thinks about it.
And his wife Laetitia, did you
know her well?
Laetitia?
No, not so much.
Not so much? You never spent Christmas Eve,
New Year with her?
- If necessary, a little.
- But we weren't really talking to
each other. -
She was a very discreet person.
Well, I also say that, but super
discreetly.
You look tense. I'm a naturopathic
gendarme,
I'll take your blood pressure.
Ho, what are you doing?
- I'm zealous.
Open Sesame!
What did I do?
- Welcome home, sir!
Go on.
Shouldn't try to smoke me out.
I'm susceptible,
it upset me.
When your cousin came
to rearrange your face,
one of your employees did
the dix-cette.
Your cousin suspects you of
killing his wife?
It's his thing.
- Yeah?
That's crazy too. What's this?
It's my card.
I give them out occasionally.
And on occasion, she put it on her
little heart, in her bag,
to do emergency work.
- Fine. OK, she called me 6 days ago,
to see each other.
So what? You look disappointed.
When my phone rang and I saw
her name, yes,
I didn't care about those things.
But she wanted to postpone
the court date.
And what were her "arguments," 43D?
No. She wanted time to do
geological studies.
It's brave, at her age, to take up
studying Geography.
No: geological. She wanted to
analyze the soil.
The farm land could be worth more
than expected.
That's good! You weren't tickled?
No, it felt like just an
excuse to delay the sale,
the drilling, the experts, the
opposing experts.
- So what?
- If it brings you a big nest egg?
I'm not selling my share for the money.
In fact, my father died there.
An accident.
Every time I go there I think about it.
I don't want to think about it anymore.
Good.
I appreciate it.
So long, comrade.
Good morning!
- You came!
You know me?
- What a beauty! Pose for me!
You work like Kandinsky? Yes, you
answer my questions, OK.
Nude, possibly?
Picasso has already done Guernica,
settle down.
Good! Let's go to the garden,
the light will look better on your face.
As long as it's on my face, there
won't be a problem.
You, you like the nude.
- Yes.
You can strip to paint me,
I don't care. Let's go.
Have you been a model a long time?
I'm not a model, I'm a Gen-dar-me...
Really? A Gendarme! It's not possible!
...and I've come to talk to you
about Mr. Guy Lemaire.
- Guy? He's my friend!
We're like "that", him and me!
Yes?
We play rugby together.
Do you play rugby?
Yes. I'm number 9, and Guy,
he's number 10.
When was the last time you
played with him?
When?
You're putting me on the spot!
I must confess that sometimes
I have memory lapses.
It doesn't stop me from playing!
- Or being friends with Mr Guy.
Yes! Bros! Thoroughly!
- And his sister Louise,
you were friends with her too?
Louise? A big bitch! She can't
stand me.
I think she's in love with me.
I wonder why.
Huh?
- No, I said: "Really?"
Back to Guy and his sister, was
that going well?
Not at all.
The last time I saw a Guy, he
said to me:
"She and I have a long-standing beef.
And if she doesn't agree, it's
the same, what I told her."
The report on the farm.
- What?
A sales report?
- No.
Not a sale! In relation to the land,
a report about the land;
he asked me for advice about the land.
Are you a farmer too?
- No! I'm a geologist!
I set up my business in 1970.
"Soil Expert" it's called!
And it's still active.
It's good to be active. And
who takes care of your business?
Mr. Marechal.
Marechal? What'd he used to be?
Is his number Vichy 40-44?
No, I think not. Wait:
yes, I know him! What was he called?
Wood cross, iron cross, if he comes
back he's going back to hell.
Can I see it?
Here, look.
- Here it is:
Yes, it's similar.
A "Mochetticelli."
- No! Botticelli,
a great Renaissance painter! And
that's your head!
Yes, sadly.
You're early.
- I just got your message.
I'll finish this and then we'll chat.
- I'll help, it will go faster.
Don't ruin your beautiful outfit.
When you weren't walking yet I was
already working in the fields.
50 years old and I never tire of it.
- Yeah.
There are other places as beautiful
as this.
Maybe, but I don't see myself
anywhere else.
Eric, I have to tell you: I'm sorry
about the other day.
Are you kidding? You had just learned
about Laetitia's death.
I would have gone awry too.
Here.
I'll show it to my lawyer. But
for me, it's good.
Gypsy Kings, Barry White, Brigitte-
An iguanodon egg!
A little snail. Damn, it's
beautiful, that one!
There's Marechal!
- Marechal, are you back?
Always so nice to see you.
Let's go, girls...
Calm down, Grandpa Weinstein.
- My real name is Ferrand,
Nicolas Ferrand.
Marleau, Captain Marleau.
- Do you like clinochrysotile?
Looks like coal.
Mr. Jean-Claude, do you remember
the other name
for clinochrysotile?
- Asbestos.
Yes, it tastes like asbestos.
You wanted to see me?
Yes. Do you know Laetitia Lemaire?
Yes, I had the pleasure to make
her lovely acquaintance.
She's dead.
What? What happened?
Just dead.
Shall we take a breath of Correze air?
Mr. Jean-Claude, you still have
your delicious fruit juice?
Yes, I have a little left.
I saw Laetitia for the first time
3 weeks ago.
At Soil Expert, I also cultivate new
clientele, therefore I search.
You're on a search task too?
What are you searching for, soils?
- No, the archives.
Locating old prospecting files to reopen.
Like files for the Lemaire family?
Almost 40 years ago Mr. Jean-Claude
was contacted by Mr. Lemaire.
He wanted to gain an understanding
of his soil,
hoping to find valuable minerals.
But there weren't any, in the end.
I thought it could be worth it
to revisit it.
40 years later?
- In my field, expiration dates are
in millions of years.
And Mr. Lemaire was hoping for
what exactly, gold?
Better: tungsten.
Taxten? He saw the light?
Have you taken your samples?
- No.
Mrs. Lemaire told me her husband
refused our help.
You haven't seen her again?
- No; she came to ask me
if she could search by herself without
her husband knowing.
I told her where to dig to optimize
her chances of a find.
You are truly a Soil Expert.
Mom?
Mom, are you there?
Mom, I-
I wanted to tell you, it's good with Eric.
He accepted the offer.
I was thinking we could
go celebrate it in town.
You know, go to the little restaurant
you like there.
Mom!
You can't treat me like this!
I did it all for you! For you!
So that you're proud of me!
At least one time in your life!
You understand?
Mom!
I understand;
you still blame me for yesterday,
is that it?
I'm sorry. It's this Gendarme who
is bothering me.
Shut your mouth!
I don't want your apologies.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for being hard on you.
I realized yesterday how it felt
to feel humiliated.
I've known that with your grandfather,
I shouldn't have inflicted him on you.
I also apologize for asking you to
hide the truth
about Guy's death.
You were only 7 years old.
You don't do that to a 7-year-old child,
it was filthy.
I also apologize for being angry with you
about being like your father.
No, no...
And I never found the words to tell you
I love you, son.
Me too, I love you mom. You're
my mom. I love you.
OK, that's good.
So long Greg.
- See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Margaux.
- So long Briere.
Hey! Guy Lemaire, when did he die?
I don't remember.
- Show me the folder.
This one.
So what does it say?
There, as I suspected.
- What?
He died on May 18th, 1980.
- Yes.
Two weeks earlier, he called a soil
expert to sample the soil,
to see if there was tungsten.
- And?
Laetitia Lemaire, 3 weeks before her
death, she called a soil expert
to dig to see if there was tungsten.
As soon as they get interested in
the thing, they die.
Yeah.
- That means?
Being their soil expert is an
anteater nest,
there is something rotten in the
kingdom of Lemaire.
Ghosts! Ghosts. Yeah.
This is where I advised Mrs. Lemaire
to do some digging.
Why here?
The soil! It's a little lighter, a
little richer.
That's the clue that it contains sediment.
Proof school.
In any case, there's no proof she
dug somewhere.
There are no holes!
- Did she not have the opportunity?
Maybe.
Or maybe she dug, but didn't
want it to show.
What is this mess?
A horse rack.
For food? Horse dentures? Where?
There.
- 50m from the food?
Why is it wobbling?
And plastic there.
That's not very green! Help me look.
It's hard, it's soft, but it's in the hole!
COURTHOUSE
It's there, right?
Are you going to Mass afterward?
It's a consultation hearing, not
a circuit court trial.
Eric, we need to talk to you.
- What? Your voice sounds funny.
You want more money?
- No, it's not that.
So everything is fine! My lawyer
validated your offer.
I tell the judge, and in 2 hours we
have a drink together, OK?
We're up first. All good?
- Yes, we're coming.
Christophe, we'll talk after. OK?
OK.
All right! First case: Lemaire
vs. Lemaire.
Are both parties present?
Yes madam president.
- Yes, yes madam president.
You don't have representation, Mr. Lemaire?
No. I didn't know I had to have one.
It would have been better.
We will do without. I summarize:
Two-thirds of the co-owners
want to sell.
There's no compromise,
so you request a goods auction.
That's it?
There has been a last-minute change.
Mr. Christophe Lemaire made an offer
to my client,
which we have accepted.
A compromise! It will go quickly-
- Wait, wait.
I have to say something first.
That's not the procedure.
Yes, but; whatever.
Eric, we want you to know something.
40 years ago, your father didn't die
by falling off a ladder.
He'd been drinking.
He was going to come after me.
And my mother-
my mother stopped him;
and killed him, but it was an accident.
That's not trivial!
- You had to know
before accepting my offer.
Well, it seemed to me more honest
for our side.
My father was an asshole.
A violent drunk who hit for pleasure.
It was often my turn to pay the price.
For me, selling this farm means getting
rid of him for good.
But you should have told me, Christophe.
I trusted you. We were like brothers.
I know.
Listen, what are we doing here?
We'll sell to someone else,
but we're selling.
Perfect! A compromise!
And now my decision, sir-
Wait.
- What now?
I just received another buyout proposal,
a buyback.
My client must be informed.
- Considering the stage we're at, proceed!
My client withdraws his request,
we have found a buyer.
The opposite would have surprised me.
You made my day!
Case adjourned, we move on.
Who buys two-thirds of a farm?
It doesn't make sense.
It's OK, we don't mind!
- Come in, make yourself at home.
I don't want to hear your sarcasm
and innuendo.
Sarcasm, pray for us.
What do you say, Soil Expert?
They're the geologists. Laetitia
told me about it.
They want to dig up my fields
to find metal, right?
Yes. Tungsten.
- This story of minerals,
it's a legend.
Nobody has ever found anything
around here.
Yes! Me!
Hold this for me, I'll show you.
Do you know what this is?
It's called wolframite, from the
Latin "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart"
and "moth," as in moth. Inside it's
full of tungsten.
Yup.
Where did you find it?
In a hole, but not in a mine.
Come see.
You see?
I found it here. And it was Soil Expert
who told me
that below here, there was a
big juicy vein.
How did you find out?
- Thank Uncle Guy.
40 years ago, he said to himself:
"there must be tungsten here!"
So he called Soil Expert to
find out where exactly.
Your brother have the idea to turn
your farm
into a kind of Germinal of tungsten.
Like Laetitia.
No kidding? That's crazy! In your family,
as soon as they touch a little
tungsten, they die!
It must be a genetic disease.
Unless someone in your family
doesn't want that for your house.
Huh, Mrs. Louise?
Unbelievable! You don't believe her?
She suspects everyone. I must be
last on the list.
You have no proof!
- No need for proof:
you're a woman of honor, no?
"My word, the earth!
The earth, my word!"
Swear you didn't kill your daughter-in-
law and I'll leave you alone!
But no, it wasn't...
- No. It was to protect our land.
To protect our heritage.
To protect you.
- Yeah?
You kill your brother and your
daughter-in-law
to protect your land? Well done!
You're a woman of honor!
Of great humanity.
There, and there. End of the case of
the woman with two lives.
You don't seem convinced.
- Yes, in two words.
The mother-in-law killed to protect
her land. Ovary rage!
Funny profession. We crack a case, we
should be happy.
But no.
- Nothing to be proud of.
Stopping a killer doesn't bring
the victim back.
A 75-year-old woman in prison!
In 3 days her son loses his wife, his
mother, and his farm!
Well, he still has his wife's horses.
A gift! I'm afraid of those critters.
Is that so? Are you a coward? And
since when?
Last year. We investigated mutilations.
A nervous horse kicked me!
Two weeks in the hospital! I had
something here-
Captain?
- You're a genius.
A horse genius!
- That's a compliment?
You didn't have to bring her to
witness your triumph.
The redneck has lost everything,
your honor is secure.
Garance is at home here.
I have bought your cousin's shares.
It's beyond triumph. You've
won everything!
Nobody's won. We've lost
two women we loved.
I have a proposition.
You pay me an annual rent, and at the
end of a period to be determined,
the farm is yours.
In exchange, you let Garance
spend time here
whenever she wants.
- Why would you do this?
For Garance. She loves this place.
And she likes you.
And also for Pauline: if she loved you,
I can make an effort to get to know you.
Hey! How beautiful it is, the
holy family!
Captain, you'll never guess.
- You too! Do you remember
my theory that your wife hit you?
That's how you got this injury,
from a metal thing, but I didn't
know what. Look!
Horseshoe.
- Yeah.
The truth was under a horse's hoof.
Tell me everything
or I'll smack you with this
good luck charm.
So, you meet men in the middle
of nowhere?
I have a daughter. Her name
is Garance.
It's a pretty first name.
- I wanted to tell you a thousand times.
Why now?
- I want to see her again.
I see; you want to go back to your
old life: if your daughter, her father-
I'm sorting all this out. Then we'll
leave, you and me.
Leave? We have the farm!
We're going to lose the farm,
you know.
Let's take advantage: We buy
a shack for your mother,
and we leave. We rebuild our life.
With Garance?
- If she wants. What do you say?
No, my place is here. I was born
here, I will die here.
This farm is going to kill us!
I'm not leaving. This is my land.
- You'll leave your skin here!
I don't want to see your waste away
without doing anything. I can't.
I'm leaving. I love you, but I'm leaving.
If you love me don't go.
- I'm leaving because I love you.
Don't go!
I panicked. I wasn't myself.
Yeah, panic can make you crazy.
We tell ourselves:
"My wife is too beautiful for me,
she's going to leave."
We prepare for it, but the day it
happens, we go crazy.
She was acting strange for weeks.
She was already elsewhere.
When she told me she was
going to leave,
I came here to the farm, all alone,
with my mother,
with only my thoughts of farming.
And go back to square one: an old
boy and his mom.
Yes, it was, after these 10 years
of happiness.
How could I kill her?
Madness! I killed her!
Passionate love. To love is not to kill.
Take him away.
Watch your head.
You're not the first to confess in order
to protect someone else.
It was a way to redeem myself.
And my regret for the life
I made him lead.
He never trusted himself.
It's my fault.
That's why he killed her.
She loved him.
He couldn't believe it.
Maybe he was right.
- Right? Why?
The idea that 60 km away was
her old life,
maybe she wanted to go back to it.
That we will never know, madam.
Can I see my son?
Maybe, one day.
You should light a candle to
St. Oedipus.
I'm going; good luck, Mrs. Louise.