(THEME SONG PLAYING)
(SPOKE CARD CLICKING)
WAYNE: Yeah, of course I remember.
JIM: Not too long ago?
Ten years is nothing.
I remember everything.
JIM: Well, we can't know.
I mean, what you don't remember,
you don't know you don't remember.
That's some education
in semantics you're giving me.
Hey, let's skip the deposition
and I can just take notes
on your lecture.
I brought my case file.
Thanks for coming in, Wayne.
It's good to see you.
- Alan.
- How's the job?
Still there.
No major cases, but...
Get more time with the wife and kids.
That's good, I guess.
I take time off, inside three days,
my wife tells me, "Get back to work."
(CHUCKLES)
JIM: Well, Detective Hays,
we need you to go back over
the Purcell case. Cases.
Looking to overturn
the conviction, right?
You good with that?
I wouldn't be here otherwise.
Why contest it now,
10 years after the fact?
It's the family doing it,
I know. But why?
JIM: You're having
memory problems, right?
What?
WAYNE: You're having memory problems.
Don't whine about it.
Today's May 20th, 2015.
Henry's coming with
the people from the TV.
You don't like the questions,
or you don't wanna do it,
Henry'll tell them to go screw.
But remember why
you're talking to them.
Figure out how much they know.
You don't need no surprises
this late in the game.
I'm recording this on the 19th.
Today's the 20th.
Look at your pictures.
Take notes. Remember.
Remember the nightstand if you...
If you need it.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
- HENRY: Hey, Dad.
- Hi.
They're all set when you're ready.
Mmm-hmm.
(SIGHS)
ALAN: I think it's a strong case.
You're paid to think that, right?
My wife's publishing a book about it.
Maybe she could help you.
Let's get through this first.
Could you tell us
about November 7th, 1980?
Your “meme of events.
Sure.
(SIGHS)
November 7th, 1980.
Friday.
I remember it was the day
Steve McQueen died.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
Hey, Dad.
Can we ride out to the playground?
What for?
Ronnie's got a new dog
he's bringing out there.
- Home by 5:30.
- WILL: Yes, sir.
Hey, Dad. When's Mom coming home?
I don't know.
- Hey, watch out for your sister.
- Yes, sir.
Home by 5:30. I mean it!
Y'all be back before the sun
goes down, you understand?
- Yes, sir!
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(SPOKE CARD CLICKING)
(DOGS BARKING)
Kids left their house
approximately 4:00 pm.
This from multiple statements.
(PUNK ROCK MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
FREDDY: Come on, let's go!
Let's go.
- Dude, watch the leather, man.
- JASON: Dude, all right.
(SPOKE CARD CLICKING)
-(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
-(MUSIC STOPS)
(CLICKING CONTINUES)
ALAN: And What were you doing
that evening?
I was with my partner at the time.
Roland West.
We were doing our regular shift.
Following up on
a series of thefts, I believe.
Working cases.
ROLAND: You'll get him next time.
Fate spared its shitty rat life,
and it has no clue.
Another way of saying
you're slow on the draw.
ROLAND: Steve McQueen died today.
We should do something.
We could go to Miss Minnie's.
Give me a break.
I can't pay for it, man.
It's more honest
than most relationships.
You never bought no Saigon trim
while you was over there?
Guess I'm a romantic.
I'm a feminist.
They want to sell me a piece
of ass, they got the right.
Shit.
You're gonna pay for it
one way or another.
You see yourself
getting married, Purple?
No, sir.
I'm not a big enough asshole
to put a woman
and children through that.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
Don't.
Shh.
Dick!
Foxes are predatory vermin, son.
Farmers, I was little, they gave
you a dollar, you kill a fox.
I'll give you a dollar
for letting it go.
Let's go ride around.
Listen to some music.
All right.
Maybe we can find somebody
to beat the shit out of.
Boy, that'd be nice.
(ROLAND GRUNT S)
(DOG BARKING)
I don't think so. Let me ask him.
Hey, son? Ronnie?
You seen the Purcell kids?
Will and his sister?
- Were they here?
- No.
Ronnie says they haven't been by.
You heard from them at all?
Were they supposed to come by?
No. I told him he could come by
to see the new puppy sometime.
But he didn't say today.
No, Tom, I'm sorry.
He hasn't heard from them.
Yeah, he's been here
all afternoon, since school.
All right.
I'll let you know if I hear anything.
(PEOPLE CHEERING, LAUGHING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
JEREMY: This fucking piece of shit.
(MAN LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
I don't wanna eat no boar meat, man.
Tracked it for two days.
Had to make my own muzzleloader
for the season.
Why'd you kill a boar, but not a fox?
Well, you eat the boar.
I only had the one shot at him.
If I missed, that was my ass.
Guess I like
a more level playing field.
Except with rats.
You know how many times
rats almost ended civilization?
How many?
I don't know. At least two.
Mate rats.
What about deer? You hunt deer?
Only with a bow.
Never in a stand and never with bait.
OFFICER: (OVER SCANNER)
D-12, over. D-12, do you copy?
(GRUNTS)
D-12 here. Over.
PD in West Finger called for assist.
Missing persons.
That's 5009 Shoepick Lane.
Copy. We got it. Be there in 10.
Fifteen.
Shoepick Lane?
Go towards Devil's Den.
You know how to get to West Finger.
We almost had a clean night, man.
Turn on the light if you want.
(OFFICERS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
It's Tom Purcell.
Two kids, William and Julie,
12 and 10.
Supposed to be home by 5:30,
never arrived.
TOM: They not been home
before the sun goes down.
That part I know.
INTERVIEWER:
Is this setup okay for you?
Uh, yes. This is fine.
So, you caught the case back in '80.
Uh, yes.
Big full moon that night...
And, uh...
I remember the moon.
And Steve McQueen had died.
Will and Julie.
I can't find them anywhere.
Listen, we need a bunch of people
out here right now.
Okay, you need to be on every street,
down in the woods...
All right, Mr. Purcell,
slow down, please.
Take us through what happened,
you could,
so we can know the right thing
to do next.
Went riding their bikes, around 4:00.
Supposed to be home by 5:30.
They were supposed
to go by a friend's house.
Kid says he never saw them.
Never occurred to you
he might be lying?
Of course it did.
General rule is, everybody's lying.
Peflod.
First impression, though, no.
I did not believe he was fabricating.
Not about this.
"About this"?
Yeah. I mean, I checked around
if he was honest about
his overtime or his height.
(SIGHS)
What is this, really?
Y'all know something I don't?
Well, we don't know what you know.
So we can't really answer that.
I was deposed when the man's family
tried getting the conviction
overturned in '90.
Then worked the case again
when it was reopened.
That's when my wife
published the book.
Wish you could've
talked to her. (CHUCKLES)
I used to think back then
it was before 'Nam and after 'Nam.
But more it's
before the Purcell case and after.
And it keeps coming back.
And here we are.
What is it, 2015?
Come back again.
And your wife's book,
which is now, well,
it's considered a classic
of literary nonfiction.
Yeah. Yeah.
She did a good job.
She was a good...
She was a good writer.
Good teacher...
Good investigator, really.
She was good at lots of things.
- I'm sorry for your loss.
- Yeah.
A few years back...
We made plans. I retired and...
It just got me thinking.
(INHALES, EXHALES HEAVILY)
Those kids. My kids. My wife.
I'm sorry.
Guess I'm just missing her today.
Your wife, Mr. Purcell.
She expected back tonight?
I think.
I don't know.
Any chance the kids could be with her?
No. No, no chance.
ROLAND: Have you talked to her?
TOM: Well, not since this morning.
She waitresses down at The Sawhorse.
She's out with her friends now,
and I can't reach her.
Get the APB out right away.
I need as many troopers
as Highway can spare.
K-9 trackers.
If State's isn't available,
check with the sheriffs.
We're gonna search the fields,
the woods,
put patrols on every street.
High beams out.
I wanna light all this up.
TOM: Ain't you gonna call the FBI?
I mean, that's what they do on TV.
Takes 72 hours, sir.
We don't know yet if...
We have to wait on that.
You two. Start canvassing neighbors.
Ask if they saw the kids,
anything unusual.
ROLAND: Any other relatives
the kids might be with?
TOM: No. No, my parents
are in Shreveport, and Lucy's passed.
You know what? Talk to Ronnie Boyle.
Will's friend.
You know, I could take y'all
out to the playground.
Okay, sure.
Mind if we look around the house while
we wait on the other officers?
They're not in the fucking house.
ROLAND: Yes, sir, but sometimes,
might be some kind of clue
where they went,
if they had other plans.
- What? Why would they...
- WAYNE: Just saying, sir.
It's been known to do some good.
We have to consider all possibilities.
TOM: Yeah.
- Whatever. You know, do what you want.
- Mr. Purcell...
Take the house apart, you want.
Flip on the TV. Grab yourself a beer.
I'm going out to find my kids.
I know you want to do that, sir,
but I promise,
we're getting that handled.
We need you nearby,
answering questions
or if somebody calls.
Oh.
You promise?
Huh?
Yes, sir.
Can you take us through the house?
Please?
That's Will's room.
That's Julie's.
That one you and your wife's?
My wife's.
Well, go on. Knock yourself out.
ROLAND: Think his wife left him,
took the kids?
I mean, they ain't together.
Think you're right.
I hope you're right.
Expect she'll call by the morning
if that's the case.
WAYNE: In fact, our first thought was
the Wife had taken off with the kids
and hadn't told the guy.
The marriage wasn't in a good place.
JIM: When'd you drop that theory?
About two minutes later.
LUCY: What the fuck is going on, Tom?
TOM: Let me talk to you.
Lucy! Come here, God damn it.
What happened?
What did you do? What did you do?
Me? Me? You're their fucking mother.
Where were you?
I am entitled to a life!
All you had to do was watch them!
I let them ride bikes
like we done a million times.
All right? Maybe if you were home
and not out looking for dick!
WAYNE: Mrs. Purcell.
I'm Wayne Hays. This is Roland West.
State Police detectives.
We put an APB on your kids.
We got men coming to search now.
Can you think of anywhere
they might have gone?
Friends or relations?
No. We don't have any...
Relatives close or nearby.
I don't understand. What happened?
You dumb-ass! You piece of shit!
- You slut! You slut!
- You stupid piece of shit!
Hey!
You been drinking tonight,
Mrs. Purcell?
What?
So? It's not against the law.
- I'm entitled to a life.
- Of course you are.
But you two getting mad
isn't helping anything right now.
You need to work together, with us.
Okay? For the kids.
God damn it, he's so stupid.
Everything you touch turns to shit.
You been running me down...
You been running me down for 10 years.
Hey!
Why don't we get some coffee going,
all right?
Everybody just calm down.
I'll make the coffee.
Kids headed west down the street,
going to a playground near the school.
I want three two-man teams
going through these fields
between the main roads.
(OFFICERS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
ROLAND: Everybody else,
get spotlights up and down
each one of these streets.
Here, here and here.
Y'all start canvassing.
We're waiting on dogs,
but let's get going.
OFFICER: Yes, sir.
TOM: I ain't never seen these before.
You sure? No judgement.
- I mean, I read it myself.
- Yeah. So do I.
But these are old,
and I never seen them.
He had these?
- It's not unusual.
- No.
Y'all find anything else?
No, sir.
If we could ask their mother,
maybe she could tell us
they have any clothes missing or not.
Might point us if they run off.
No, I don't think
she's in shape for that.
And they didn't run off.
I'm telling you.
Yes, sir. But it needs doing.
Save us time.
NEIGHBOR: I didn't see the children.
But I saw some older boys, teenagers,
in a purple Volkswagen Bug.
I wasn't home until after 7:00.
I saw the two kids
riding out toward the park.
But I didn't see any teenagers.
But I know they hang around
at Devil's Den.
I hear things,
about what they do out there.
NEIGHBOR 2: Yeah, sometimes, like,
out by the ranger tower
at the edge of the park,
people hang out, listen to music.
Um, that Volkswagen is
Freddy Burns', I think.
I seen that "Trash Man" fella.
I don't know his name.
Rides around town in a go-cart,
picking through garbage. (CHUCKLES)
Everybody knows him.
Patty, what's that
"Trash Man" guy's name?
His last name's Woodard, I think.
I saw him riding around
when I was looking for the kids.
He drives a go-cart
and tows this little trailer.
He picks up trash and sells it
at the scrapyard, I guess.
Been around for years.
I never liked him.
Going through other people's trash.
Any idea where he lives?
We're sorry for the personal nature
of these questions,
but we need to know everything we can.
How long you folks
been sleeping separate?
- Few months.
- About six months.
- Since beginning of summer.
- LUCY: Hasn't been that long.
TOM: Yeah, it has. Dan left last May,
then I took the couch.
- Dan?
- He's my cousin.
Stayed with us a few weeks
Iastspflng.
He's like an uncle to the kids.
And what's his last name?
O'Brien. Same as mine. Used to be.
Where's he live?
He's up in Springfield, Missouri.
But he hasn't seen the family
in a long time.
He stayed there on the couch?
No, he stayed in Will's room.
Will was on the couch.
Would you write down his contact info?
Phone number and address.
What for? Been gone since May.
Just have to check out
anything we can.
Sometimes, there's tension
between the parents,
or fighting and whatnot.
Kids'II make like to run away.
They didn't run away, God damn it.
Why don't you go find
that "Trash Man" bastard
and ask him some questions?
- Did you talk to Ronnie Boyle?
- ROLAND: We did.
Hadn't seen Will since school.
Parents said he'd been home
since 3:00.
-(LUCY SOBS)
- TOM: But they didn't run off.
(SOBBING)
WAYNE: Everybody went home
to wait for daylight.
I didn't go to sleep that first night.
I stayed out, trying to find a trail.
I was a tracker, you see.
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
-(BULB BURSTS)
I should stop.
Do I need to stop?
No, uh, we're okay.
Sorry about that.
Please, continue, Mr. Hays.
WAYNE: Uh...
Had maybe 15 guys
out that first night.
They went home after a few hours.
Day would give us better odds.
Get the news to help.
REPORTER: Two children are missing
from a West Finger neighborhood.
Will and Julie Purcell were last seen
riding their bicycles west
on Turpin Road
not far from Devil's Den State Park,
around 4:00 yesterday afternoon.
Police are calling on volunteers
to aid in the search
and are asking all residents
to keep an eye out
and report anything unusual
they might have noticed,
or believe might be relevant
to the case.
The brother and sister are 12 and 10,
and attend the West Finger
school system.
AMELIA: "Tell me a story
"In this century, and moment, of mania
"Tell me a story
"Make it a story of great distances
and starlight
"The name of the story will be Time
"But you must not pronounce its name
"Tell me a story of deep delight"
What do you think
Warren means by that?
Why mustn't you say
the name of the story?
Anybody?
- Riley?
-(KNOCK ON DOOR)
I teach English,
eighth through 12th grade.
Will's a student of mine, too.
You got a boy in your class right now,
a senior, named Freddy Burns?
Yes. He's here today.
We'd like to speak with him.
Okay.
What are you studying?
The quote.
Oh, uh, it's a poem we're discussing.
Huh.
- What?
-"What?"
FREDDY: We were just hanging out,
you know?
Go down to the ranger tower,
mess around.
What time was that?
Um...
Maybe 4:30,
4:45 we got there, I think.
And that was you,
Ryan Peters and this Lampanella boy?
- Anybody drinking?
- No, sir.
See on the news this morning,
about those missing kids?
These two. You recognize them?
Yeah, I seen them around.
I think we saw them.
You saw them?
Riding their bikes.
Yesterday. We passed them
when we were driving.
What time was that?
Maybe 4:15. Before we got to the park.
You saw them riding their bikes
in the neighborhood?
Yes, sir.
Just the once?
You didn't see them again?
- No, sir.
- And they weren't out at the tower?
FREDDY: No. No, sir.
What time y'all leave the park?
RYAN: Uh...
It was about 9:00, I think.
A little after.
Let me ask you.
What's up with this?
I mean, it's... It's just a band.
Black Sabbath, huh?
What's a Black Sabbath?
It's a satanic mass.
Is that true? It's satanic?
I think it's just their name.
You see either of
these children yesterday?
What?
Yeah.
I mean, yes, sir. I...
They were out playing in the park.
You saw them in the park?
Were they up at the tower
when y'all were hanging out?
No.
I mean, I don't think so.
But you don't know.
I don't know all the kids that
were playing out there, you know?
There were other kids out there?
Yeah. They weren't with us.
There were a couple kids
playing with firecrackers
and younger kids just running around,
but we didn't talk to them.
You know any of their names?
No.
Anything you can tell me about Will?
His friends? Family?
Any sense you might've had?
He's a good student.
Quiet, polite in homeroom.
He's very advanced in English.
As far as home, I don't really know.
I don't know either of his parents.
But he's a nice boy.
He has a sensitivity.
You always worry a bit
about the sensitive ones.
Hmm.
There's a few of the older boys here,
you know, they make it hard
on the others.
But I never saw Will
getting any trouble.
I just...
(SIGHS)
Well, I don't think
he got noticed much.
For how long you been teaching?
- About six years.
- All at West Finger?
Yes, sir.
Hey, you say "sir,"
I start looking for my boss.
No, I'm sorry. Just, you know. Police.
How is it here?
You know.
It's fine.
It's good, really, for what it is.
I hear something new and then.
They're all poor around here.
That's the main thing.
What you hear now and then?
You know,
a word in the hallway or something.
They're careful around me.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What about these boys,
Freddy Burns, Ryan Peters
and Jason Lampanella?
I don't know.
They're kinda their own little group.
They posture a lot,
but I'd say they're mostly outcasts.
Tough attitudes, can't talk to girls,
that kind of thing.
And Will's good in English?
Reads at a 12th-grade level,
writes very well,
pays attention in class.
He's a bit shy about speaking up.
And, uh...
You from this area?
Fayetteville.
Still live there.
So do I.
Nice place.
Yep.
All right, um... (CLEARS THROAT)
Thanks very much, Miss Reardon.
Well, now you have me
looking for my mother.
- Yeah, okay.
-(AMELIA CHUCKLES)
- I'm Wayne.
- Amelia.
Okay.
Think you'll find those children?
I've got hope.
I'll let you know
if there's anything else.
Please do.
Anything at all.
Do you have a number?
- I'll be in touch.
- Good.
Think they're lying?
I mean, they're lying.
Think it's just regular teenage lying,
or something else?
I don't know.
The one, Burns, lied about the beer.
- There's lots of reasons to do that.
- Mmm-hmm.
Put a couple guys
tailing Burns and Peters.
Hit this address up
for the trash can guy, Woodard.
Come back on the teenagers,
we need to.
What about that teacher?
You gonna come back on her?
Uh-huh.
WAYNE: After the school, we, uh
checked out that guy
people called "Trash Man."
Brett Woodard.
Used to ride around in his go-cart
collecting garbage.
He wasn't home.
Checked around his place,
the door was open.
Anyways,
you know what happened with him.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
ROLAND: Think the backyard was neater.
A lot of guys have trouble,
they come back.
Mmm-hmm.
ROLAND: I heard
one of my old rodeo buddies
is on the street in Shreveport.
And another buddy
went to prison in Oklahoma.
Killed a dude in a bar fight.
You know guys like that?
Couple.
Put an APB on this guy.
I'm ready to go now.
I don't want to be here.
- I need to stop for today.
- INTERVIEWER: Oh.
Um...
Well, we didn't really
get into the questions.
I understand if it's difficult
to discuss Mr. Woodard...
Not today.
I'm sorry.
- You all right, Pop?
- I think. I don't know.
- Can you get them out of here?
- Yeah, sure.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOGS GROWLING, WHINING)
ROLAND: Wanna thank the volunteers
came out with us today.
It's a tough thing.
(DOGS BARKING)
MAN: Check this spot.
Get those fucking dogs away from me.
MAN 2: Yeah.
(VOLUNTEERS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
What's your partner doing?
He's got his own thing.
Well, how's that help us?
Man was a LRRP in 'Nam.
You know what that is?
Long range reconnaissance.
Drop them in the jungle alone,
come out two or three weeks later,
with scalps.
He's like a pathfinder.
Tracks wild boar for fun.
He wanna look alone, I'm okay with it.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WATER RUSHING IN DISTANCE)
(WATER RUSHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Shit.
(POLICE RADIO CRACKLES)
Roland?
ROLAND: (OVER RADIO) Copy.
I found the boy.
AMELIA: "What is love?
"One name for it is Knowledge."
- HENRY: Dad?
-(KNOCKS AT DOOR)
Crew cleared out. They're gone.
Pop?
(POLICE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
There's another one of them dolls.
Further back.
Right where the trail got sketchy.
- Bag them all.
- Okay.
Leading me.
Like a marker or something.
Kid's head looked injured.
Did a little tunnel work
over there, you know?
Almost couldn't go inside.
All right.
There's no sign of the girl.
We have to get back out there
looking for her.
Okay, man. All right. We will.
WAYNE“. You know what I found.
I don't need to go back over it.
I think I'm done for the day,
unless y'all wanna tell me
what's going on.
What's going on
is the wrong man 10 years ago.
No shit. But tell me why.
Okay, I'll give y'all another
20 minutes some other time,
and that's how we'll do this.
Maybe we'll finish up by next summer.
The girl, Julie.
- Alan, I don't...
- What about her?
Her prints went into the system
when they established the database.
Okay.
An after-hours burglary
in Sallisaw, Oklahoma.
Two months ago.
A Walgreens.
Somebody broke into the pharmacy.
PD worked the store for fingerprints.
Only one set of prints hit.
Julie Purcell's.
Julie.
- She's alive?
- Apparently.
Jesus Christ.
She's out there.
Where you going?
Back out.
We have to find her.
It's too dark, man.
I don't care.