(THEME SONG PLAYING)
It's just like the paperwork says.
Read the report.
DOBKINS: Well, our feeling is that
the prosecution
didn't make a full accounting
or mount a suitable case.
So we have to do that now.
Get the full accounting.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Around the end of the first week,
family got the note.
MAN: Envelope's handwritten.
So, this isn't a brainiac.
Processing stamp's
from a post office in Farmington.
That could have been dropped
in any mailbox.
We're putting men out there
to canvass.
You see this?
MAN: Twiggs said they've been
fielding calls from Martians all day.
What's the Ozark Children's Outreach?
MAN 2: Some charity.
ROLAND: You think it's true?
Girl's alive?
I think she is.
What were you focusing on prior?
Neighborhood surveillance.
Like it says in the report.
Right, yeah. Uh...
"All day." Mmm-hmm.
But you guys didn't get to the house
till after everybody else.
I mean, you'd have got there first
if you were in the neighborhood,
wouldn't you?
Well, might've taken
the call late or...
I'm a little fuzzy.
Wayne probably has a better memory.
The picture doesn't show anything new.
Nothing that suggests a blackout,
and that's good.
Since your CT scan looks clean,
I think the concern
right now is the need
to adjust your lifestyle
to what's happening.
I wasn't...
He explained it wrong.
Didn't drive in my sleep
or any kind of "state."
I mean...
At the time, I...
I believe I did know what I was doing.
It's only I forgot later.
We're just gonna have to do
some things differently. Okay, Dad?
I went up there for a reason.
I just can't remember.
It's not like I'm losing it.
Do you remember
the rest of dinner at my place?
Remember me driving you home?
Yeah.
Heather drove you home.
Now we're playing "gotcha."
DOCTOR: Mr. Hays, your son loves you.
Our only concern
is for your well-being.
I know my son loves me, Doctor.
But thanks for
walking me through that.
The place you found yourself.
Do you know why you might
have wanted to go there?
Does it have any significance?
HENRY: Yeah. It did.
He did a couple interviews
for this show.
Been talking about an old case
took place out there.
- What, you ratting on me?
- What, are you working a case?
It was never fully solved.
People don't remember being babies.
It's good we get to revisit this stage
at the end.
DOCTOR: Mr. Hays, believe me,
I can understand your frustration
with the disease.
A disease
you can't even say what it is.
We can say what it
almost certainly is.
I told you.
You try putting me in a home,
I'll off myself.
Put it out your head.
AMELIA: Don't you want to know?
You do.
And she needs help, doesn't she?
Julie.
WAYNE: Yeah.
You know, it was just a case
when I caught it.
I didn't know it'd be my last.
You with the book these last years...
I feel like I'm tired of this thing
being in our lives.
Like when we met.
I mean, Saturday night,
your mom's got the kids,
got this thing sitting between us.
So what do you want to do?
I don't know.
There was a motel back there.
We could just drink
and have sex all night.
Boy, that'd be great.
Alan said so far
they have her prints on the counter
and some shelves in the main area.
Were there any behind the pharmacy?
He didn't know. Sallisaw PD's got it.
Well, shouldn't you talk to them?
May come back on me.
It's not like if they check,
someone's gonna have my back.
(WAYNE SIGHS)
What if I talk to them?
Sallisaw.
An author with a book about the case.
I have galleys, I'm legitimate,
I bet I could get them
to share with me.
- I doubt it.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'll get done up,
bookish but sexy,
intimidated by those big, tough cops.
(CHUCKLES) This is, like
Afro Hart to Hart? That it?
- Come on.
-(LAUGHS)
Wanna use the pay phone,
we're here? Check on the kids?
Why don't I call from the motel?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(ENGINE STARTS)
We need to walk it back.
Re-examine it all.
It's like a thing's
staring right at us.
Got that feeling myself.
(LAUGHTER)
The Purcells.
Said they were gonna play
with their neighbor,
-the Boyle kid.
- Yeah?
But he said
they didn't have any plans.
Why would the Purcell kids
lie about meeting the Boyle kid?
What were they up to?
What were they really doing?
Back to the kids.
Talk to the parents again,
the Boyle kid, any others knew them.
Go back through the house
again, right?
Yeah, right on.
That's good, man.
Get that teacher
to help with the kids.
ROLAND: Wayne had the idea them kids
would tell him stories.
And he was correct.
You all fucked a good detective there.
You know that, right?
I wouldn't argue with you.
But it wasn't me.
Probably didn't even give you shit
for it, when you saw him?
I can't say he did, no.
Purple Hays. My man.
Tried to get him transferred
over here twice, you know?
Blocked both times
by the major's office.
Told me not to ask again.
Feels like we should stay on point.
I'm making a point, son.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
ROLAND: You played with
Will and Julie 3 lot, huh?
RONNIE: Hmm... Not really. I mean,
I hung out with Will
at school a little.
But y'all hung out after school.
His dad said y'all
played after school.
No, sir. We didn't play much.
I mean, I told him
he could come over sometime
to see the new puppy, but that's it.
He's home after school.
Or at basketball now.
He don't go out playing much.
ROLAND: You said they played a lot,
that neighbor, Ronnie Boyle?
Yeah, well,
three, four times a week.
They're best friends.
Did Ronnie ever come over here
to the house?
Did you ever see him
when the kids get together?
No.
I guess not.
I mean, I know him and his parents
from school.
And they'd go over to his place.
Well, actually, looks like
they didn't really play together.
TOM: What is this...
What's this mean?
Why aren't you out there
looking for her?
That's where she is.
Out there. She's alive.
The letter said she's out there.
Feds are running
a wide search, Mr. Purcell,
and they have a lot more manpower.
We're just trying to focus
on what's personal.
Would you folks be all right
if we started going back
through some of their things?
We're afraid now
we might've overlooked something.
What?
We just don't know, ma'am.
ROLAND: We'll process this stuff,
get it back to you.
Don't lose it, okay?
We won't.
Say, one of you used
to work at Hoyt Foods?
Yeah, I did.
On the chicken line.
Quit a year or two ago.
Make better money in tips
at the Sawhorse.
Why?
Just asking.
Thank you, now.
So Wayne opened up
that the kids weren't doing
what they said they were.
With that big reward,
brought everybody out the woodwork.
ALAN: You see Wayne much anymore?
Not at all, really.
And I don't know why.
No hard feelings, though?
Not between him and me.
We were good friends, as I see it.
I think it was
once we stopped working together,
we just stopped.
Sometimes it's like that with people.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Dad, can I get a Transformer?
No.
Can we get something
from the toys, Dad?
- If it's cheap?
- No.
Where the hell's the charcoal?
- How about if it's only a dollar?
- No.
Stores aren't supposed to be this big.
Can we at least go look at the toys?
No. You guys have to stay with me.
So we're trying to update the book,
if possible.
Hearing about her prints
at the drugstore,
it's very significant.
How'd you hear about that?
My ex-husband.
He's a cop in Arkansas.
Always had a thing for oops, I guess.
OFFICER: We got a few partials
and a lot of fulls.
We verified it
with the state crime lab.
It's definitely a match.
Were any of her prints
found behind the pharmacy?
No. But we didn't get
to keep working the scene, neither.
End of the day,
store just wanted
to get back to business.
- So hers were just the shelves.
- Yes, ma'am.
We only focused on the robbery,
and that was months ago.
I'm about to clock out.
You wanna grab a bite?
We can talk more about it?
All right.
Hey, I think we're done.
That was awful, right?
Since you guys were so good,
I'll let you get one thing.
- Yes!
- Feel better, sad guy?
Where's your sister?
She was right behind me. I don't know.
Come on.
- Becca!
Becca!
Becca! Becca!
WOMAN: (ON PA)
please come to customer service.
Look for the nearest
Wat-Mart representative
and ask them to bring you
to customer service.
Rebecca Hays.
It's been 10 minutes.
Need to lock down the store.
Shut all the doors, nobody in or out.
Listen to me. I'm a cop. State Police.
Lock down the store now. I'll make
an announcement, give me the mic.
Sir, I don't think that you...
- Give me the mic!
- BECCA: Hi.
- Where were you?
- I don't know.
They were giving out chips
in one place,
and I stopped to eat some,
and y'all were gone.
God damn it, you can't do that!
You hear me?
Don't fucking do that, Rebecca!
(CRYING)
Okay. Okay.
Let's go. Let's just go home.
MANAGER: We were happy to help.
Especially once we heard
she was a former employee of ours.
Just, it led to a lot of false tips.
You know, it's better
to coordinate this kind of thing
between our offices.
But we did.
The board cleared it with
the county prosecutor's office.
I don't see any pictures of you all
putting up rewards for anybody.
MANAGER: Up till now, we've tended
to help families
with children that needed
medical treatment.
But with it all over the news,
and knowing the mother
used to be in our family of workers,
the board voted to contribute.
When did this outreach start?
Mr. Hoyt endowed the foundation
after they lost their granddaughter
a couple of years ago.
Mother worked on the chicken line.
Where's that building?
Oh. Let's see.
It would be one
of those two.
WAYNE: You know what would help?
Names and dates of hire
for every employee
that works at this plant.
That's nearly 700 people.
Faster we get them back, the better.
All right. Sure. Of course.
We'll start getting it together
right now.
And the big man, Mr. Hoyt,
he ever here?
Well, hardly, no. Mr. Hoyt's
been in Africa since mid-October.
- Safari.
- Oh, yeah?
My partner's
a bit of a hunter himself.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
State PD. Task Force.
Uh-huh.
The girl's being held
at a snake farm in Huntsville?
And how do you know this, ma'am?
Listen, we closed right now,
but do me a favor,
call back in the morning.
This number,
and ask for Agents Bowen or Diller.
FBI.
Tell them what you're telling me.
All right, now.
(HANGS UP)
Lady seen Julie Purcell in a dream.
She say her dreams always come true.
All this stuff's about that game.
Couldn't find his dice,
but I'm not seeing anything.
Except he played a lot,
and them other kids
didn't play with him, huh?
Who gave Julie the doll,
met them in the woods?
Who played the game with Will?
Where'd they go after school?
They were meant to be
with that neighbor.
So what was your next move?
ROLAND: Shut down the park,
except for search parties.
They were still doing them
every day. Mostly volunteer.
State park's about 2,500 acres.
AMELIA: So, how does it work?
Spot patterns.
Disturbance, flattening.
It's there, you just
have to look for it.
Bent grass, compressed ground.
You tracked men in the war?
I did.
Did you march?
Funny how the protests stopped
once the draft ended.
Hey, that poem you were teaching...
Yeah. You had some thoughts about it?
He says you call the story "Time,"
but you can't say its name.
Why is that?
I think it's because
we're in time and of time,
but to name...
You separate yourself from
something when you name it,
and I think he means
we can't be separated from time.
Ah.
I thought he meant
it was like the name of God.
You know, how the Hebrews
weren't supposed to say God's name.
Huh.
Think maybe we should
have dinner sometime?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- AMELIA: Hey.
- Hi.
Those Sallisaw boys
couldn't stop telling me stuff.
I was pretty tremendous.
I think I have a future at this.
(CHUCKLES)
- You're reading it! Finally.
- Not really.
Keep seeing my name.
Are you drunk?
No, I'm...
I had a drink at dinner.
This detective took me out to eat.
- Ah, terrific.
- No, actually,
I got a lot of info from him.
Listen, her fingerprints were found
just on the shelves
in the cosmetics aisle.
Looks like she was
probably a customer.
They had the prior week's
surveillance footage.
I think they're gonna let me
take a look at it.
I didn't get any of the shit you want.
At Wal-Mart.
Okay.
Did something happen?
- Are the kids all right?
- The kids are fine.
- Are you all right?
- I'm all right.
But one thing. One favor.
Do not come bouncing in here,
half in the bag,
all giddy about this shit.
Can you do that?
Can you summon the mental resolve
to shut up about this shit with me?
If you feel this way,
you don't have to talk
to me like that.
- You could just tell me.
- You've been told.
Why don't you go check on your kids
since you haven't seen them all day.
- They're supposed to be in bed.
- Fuck off.
I'm with them five times
the amount you are
for a job that treats you like shit.
I don't really feel
like trading curses.
I said my piece.
I'm not gonna stop, Wayne.
Patrol's got the scene.
Forensics is on the way.
That's where the boy died.
Somebody carried him to the cave.
The office checked the field reports.
Nobody talked to this guy.
And the farm road's not on our maps.
I already talked to your people.
Man came here the next day.
What man?
Was he police? Sheriff's?
Man in a suit. Showed me a badge.
Asked me about those missing kids,
if I'd seen anything.
Can you describe him?
A normal guy. White. A suit.
Showed me a badge.
What'd you tell him?
Did you see anything?
I told him I seen those kids before.
Two or three times.
They come down my road
and into the woods.
Couple afternoons I seen them.
- You see anybody else?
- Yeah.
Told him I seen a car
out here a couple times.
Nice one. Brown. Man and woman.
But it wasn't the same day.
What'd they look like?
The man and woman.
Like y'all.
Black and white.
Man was Negro.
I couldn't see faces.
Now, most times,
you gotta be looking for our place,
but sometimes people come out here.
WAYNE: Sir?
You mind we search your property?
Yes, sir, I mind.
Don't you need a warrant
for something like that?
If you make us get one.
I think you'll have to, son.
ELISA: Can I ask, do you feel
there was sufficient coverage
of the neighborhood
during the canvassing?
Yes, I do.
We brought whatever we had.
General rule is, you start close,
then work your way out.
ELISA: Did officers conduct
multiple interviews
-with all potential witnesses?
- Yes. Mmm-hmm.
And I feel like, honestly,
everyone was giving
everything they had.
Well, we have people who say they were
never questioned by the police,
although they remember
the officers going door to door.
WAYNE: Hmm.
I don't know.
If anyone got overlooked,
it was a mistake.
We had over 100
law enforcement officers out there.
ELISA: Some residents
did get talked to three or four times.
But nobody spoke to these people.
And we found two who both
separately claim to have witnessed
a very nice brown sedan
driving around the neighborhoods,
and later, away from Devil's Den
on the day of the murder.
Brown sedan?
ELISA: A witness said police
talked to him once,
and he told them about the car,
but they never came back.
And there's no mention of the sedan
in the field reports.
Another said police
never took a statement,
but they both noticed the car
because it was new and upscale,
and that was unusual for the area.
And that the vehicle
kept driving around.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Treads.
I remember. Treads.
Another former resident,
Charles Snyder,
said two weeks before,
he reported that his boy and a friend
had told of a black man
with a soar, in a suit,
at the cul-de-sac where the kids
played near Devil's Den.
No one ever came back to question him.
None of this is mentioned
in the official reports.
This alone, don't you think,
points to serious flaws
in the investigation
from the beginning?
What's going on?
Really.
You have some new evidence?
Are you looking for Julie?
You find something?
- HENRY: That's enough for today.
- No, I'm all right.
- I think we're doing well.
- I'm sure you do.
You see his distress?
This man is ill, Elisa.
- Henry...
- That is enough.
For today.
WAYNE: Over there.
Other side of the tree line.
It's hard to find. Kind of hidden.
That's where they played.
MAN: Now,
we need to process these toys.
You bag the toys, but we need pictures
to show the parents.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HORN HONKING)
(HONKING CONTINUES)
MAN 1: Hey.
(TRUCK DOORS CLOSING)
Get up.
What's going on?
MAN 1: What are you doing,
skulking around here?
What...
We got kids playing out here,
and we don't need you
lurking around them.
My kids and two others
say you keep coming around that field
where they all play.
What are you coming around
the kids for?
I'm not.
I don't.
- I have kids.
- MAN 2: No, you don't.
And we don't want you around,
you hear?
I live here! I have rights!
I fought for your fucking rights,
you asshole... (GROANING)
MAN 3: You're a goddamn bum.
You stay away from these kids.
MAN 4: And stay out of
our neighborhood!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
You hear me now, boy?
You don't come around here no more.
We don't see you,
and God help you if you talk
to another child out here.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Get the fuck out of here!
(EXHALES)
So how's life in charge?
(SIGHS)
It's got its good and bad.
You talked to them? Alan's firm?
Yeah, they approached me.
The guy's kids hired them, he said.
But you support it?
Reopening it?
They tell you about the fingerprints?
Yeah.
You have any idea
what that means to me?
I have to imagine,
but, yes, sir.
You know, I...
I think of Lucy.
I wish she was still around
to hear this.
Two years ago now.
Alan had her file.
I had the body brought back
from Vegas.
What about you?
How you doing with all this now?
I'm still sober.
Five years.
I know.
I'm proud of you, man.
So I got my Higher Power,
and he's putting this
in front of me now.
Cream and extra sugar, still?
Yes, sir. Like a dessert.
How about the other one?
Your partner. He still around?
He's on the job.
Hasn't been in major crimes
in a long time.
Anyways, yeah, me and him
kind of lost touch.
You didn't have to check on me,
Lieutenant West.
You've done more for me
than just about anybody.
Pulled me out of that hole
five years ago.
No.
You done good.
Can I ask you for something?
You can ask.
Would you pray with me?
God,
save me from anger.
God, save me from resentment.
God, save me from myjudgments
and prophecies,
my need to control.
I have known you
by the hawk and the dove
and I live at
your infinite compassion.
Lord,
guard what I hold dear,
and let me never hold too dearly
anything of this world.
Amen.
(RECORDER BEEPS)
Brown sedan.
Farmer talked about
a brown sedan,
'80...
We knew.
Was that who they played with?
She wrote a bit about
how the games we found
got people worried that
kids were getting killed
playing this stuff
or something.
Henry was
five or six, I think,
when she started writing.
Becca would have been
three or four.
(RECORDER BEEPS)
AMELIA: Scientists now theorize
an infinite number
of dimensions outside our own.
Einstein said past, present and future
are all a stubbornly
persistent illusion.
Oh...
Oh, God.
And are you waking up
to that illusion?
Now, while things fall apart,
are you starting to see them clearly?
And at the end of all things,
are you awakening
to what you withheld?
Did you confuse reacting with feeling?
Did you mistake
compulsion for freedom?
(STAMMERING) Please, not like this.
And even so,
did you harden your heart
against what loved you most?
Not like this.
Oh, sweetheart.
Did you think you could just go on
and never once have to look back?
Please, I...
I don't deserve this. I...
Whatever's happening,
I don't deserve this.
No, you don't.
But it's happening anyway.
I'm so sorry.
-(BECCA AND HENRY GIGGLING)
-(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Where is it? I...
How much do I have to lose?
Everything.
Same as everybody else.
I lost Becca.
No, you didn't.
Not the way you think.
You're worried what they'll find.
What you left in the woods.
Finish it.
(TYPEWRITERS CLACKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Got a message, maybe the lieutenant
wanted to meet you.
Moving up in the world.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
TOM: No. I don't recognize them.
I think. I mean...
I know I didn't buy any of these.
Ma'am?
I don't think so.
I don't really remember.
I'm the one bought them toys.
I don't recognize any of those.
This about the reward?
Someone called us.
What's it have to do with?
Where'd you find these?
ROLAND: (SIGHS) Looks like
the kids had this kind of
play area hidden out in the forest.
Found these toys there.
TOM: They could be anybody's.
ROLAND: Had the kids' prints on them.
Another set of prints we can't ID.
And more of those straw dolls.
They were meeting somebody?
Like some adult?
Maybe. Yes, sir.
What are these?
We haven't seen this.
It's an old baby album.
He brought it out. I...
I can't look at it.
Roland?
It's the same.
What's this one from?
That's Will's First Communion.
He was 10.
What?
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
Purple Hays.
How you been, killer?
Just making my rounds.
Places I'm not wanted.
- Dub 8000.
- You served?
- Every day of my life.
- Yeah? What war?
Motherfucker, get me two fingers
of Southern Comfort.
He's a lieutenant with State Police.
Could've told him
you were fixing jeeps
while the rest of us
was getting shot at.
Could've slapped my dick
on the bar, too.
Nine years, you're still
talking about your dick.
Well, I don't mean to.
It just keeps coming up.
New task force.
I'm in charge.
Good for you, Lieutenant.
Say,
that promotion for merit
or did it come with the pigmentation?
Well, I think, unlike some others,
I lacked a big fucking mouth.
Hell, with affirmative action,
you could've been my boss by now.
Guess if I'd been
clumsy enough to get shot,
I'd be playing golf most days
and calling old buddies
like I'm doing them a favor.
Guess you had a few before I got here.
Could be avoiding home.
I was gonna keep going, some race bit.
You never been very funny.
You feel like maybe
being a detective again?
'Cause that, you were okay at.
Purcell case?
State's reopening it.
They want me to steer.
Look at you.
Can't stop this rocket. Mmm-mmm.
You wanna get back to work or not?
I, uh...
I'm sorry about the pigmentation line.
No, you're not.
Half sorry.