(THEME SONG PLAYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
WAYNE: You have the autopsy report.
I don't need to go over that.
Blunt force trauma
and a cervical fracture.
Somebody broke his neck.
Brought him to that cave.
Folded his hands, I guess.
Alan.
Talk to me about Oklahoma.
You have to, man.
- Wayne, this isn't the time...
- How many sets of prints were taken?
Do they know she was
one of the robbers and not a customer?
If they found her, you wouldn't
even be talking to me, right?
Do they have video surveillance?
Mr. Hays,
the purpose of this deposition
is to give your statement,
not to extract one from us.
I'm pretty easygoing,
but go away already.
I don't think I Will.
Look, we're not at liberty
to divulge details
of an ongoing police investigation,
nor to share discovery items
with anyone
other than the prosecutor's office.
Now, you can talk to them,
if they'll talk to you...
Hey, hey, hey. All right, stop.
Wayne.
Finish up today, all right?
Then after, we'll speak.
I'm saying, we'll talk. Okay?
Now, you were saying.
You questioned people
during this time. Right?
Do you know another way to do it?
The father worked
at Wilson Body Works,
where they used to make parts
for school buses.
We talked to everybody there.
Employed about 100 people
from West Finger.
The dolls were their own thing.
Wasn't getting us anywhere, either.
Thank you very much.
WAYNE: That guy who collected garbage,
Woodard. We talked to him, too.
I saw the kids.
They were pedaling into the sun.
Headed west?
We went by your place.
You sort of collect things, huh?
I salvage trash that I can sell.
You don't need to make it
sound better than that.
You got any other properties?
Anywhere you keep things?
I don't have anyplace else.
What'd you do before this?
Before you collected scrap.
Uh, came back from overseas. '72.
Did some carpentry.
Construction dropped off.
Things didn't work out.
My marriage. Stuff.
I was gone too long.
About four years ago, she left me.
Took the kids.
I was motor pool.
My man here was a LRRP. Two tours.
Detective Hays.
They called him "Purple Hays"
over there.
You miss your family?
I... Yeah.
I miss being someone that way...
A way I could have a family.
You were recon?
75th Infantry.
Sergeant.
You must be pretty insane,
volunteering for that.
I didn't think about it much,
to tell you the truth.
I ain't one of them burnouts.
You know, comes back busting guys up,
getting high.
And I ain't a bum.
I keep a house. I pay my way.
Hey. I ain'tjudging, man.
Look, I punch in and out.
I put on a suit in the morning.
And being honest,
I don't have much of a life.
So why? Why punch in?
Why the suit? Why...
I don't ask myself
questions like that.
Could be I'm too chickenshit,
Mr. Woodard.
It ain't my world.
Less than yours, even.
But I did pretty good
at following orders.
Now...
You ever do this?
I miss when "Don't get killed"
was the only thing on my to-do list.
It's hard to unplug from that.
I spent a year coming down.
(ROLAND CLEARS THROAT)
Just to go back over it,
you sure you didn't see anything?
I told you.
I saw the teenagers out there, too.
I was going in the other direction.
You like kids, generally?
Do...
What the fuck's
the right answer to that?
You think I...
Listen, I got two kids, okay?
Where are they?
I don't know. She didn't tell me.
And I haven't gone looking.
If I'd never left,
I think it'd have been fine.
But to go, and come back...
I just couldn't put myself
back in that old story, that's all.
And I couldn't leave it, either.
You know?
You ever been some place
you couldn't leave,
and you couldn't stay,
both at the same time?
HENRY: Do you remember the place?
I remember.
GREG: I can tell you all
that none of us will rest
until we achieve justice
in the matter.
Our detectives are hard at work,
and this is priority one
for law enforcement
in Washington County
and Northwest Arkansas.
Now, it's temporary,
but we're gonna have to
have a curfew for a little while.
It's important that we keep
an eye on our kids right now,
and we want to make sure
you know where they are at all times,
and that they're indoors by 8:00.
Now, we can't really say
too much about the investigation,
but I'm here to answer
any questions I can.
Well, I don't let mine
go near Devil's Den.
Everybody knows you got
something happening in it.
Bums, junkies.
Queers meet up out there.
You have a question, sir?
I wanna know what y'all are doing
to break up that stuff.
Clean up that park!
What about these junkies?
You got heroin in Arkansas now.
Right now, our focus is trying
to find this little girl
and bring her home.
We're considering every possibility.
MAN 2: And what about that fella
always digging through
everybody's trash?
Mr. Kindt, can you tell us
if they think the girl is still alive?
It's our hope that she's alive, yes.
But again, I really can't discuss
any of the details
of the investigation.
Now, our detectives
have a pair of Xeroxes to pass out.
One is a picture of Julie Purcell.
The other is the kind of backpack
that the boy, Will, had.
It's red and has his name on it.
Now, if anyone has any information
of potential interest,
no matter how far afield,
share it with us.
And trust that we will not
let this terrible,
cowardly act go unpunished.
WAYNE: Your old boss got real vocal
around then.
Gerald Kindt had an election
coming up the next year.
I know.
Guess that works
to some point in your petition.
It's worth noting,
I think, his motivations.
Well, now he's fucking
State Attorney General.
But we didn't work for him.
He was your boss.
Oh, not for a good while now.
The broken neck is clear.
But the way the arms were folded...
- I know.
- And the other thing.
- The hell are those dolls for?
- Correct. Look familiar, some way.
Like the kind of thing
at country fairs.
What do you get
from that crowd in there?
They're worried.
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Could be thinking
it could have been a neighbor.
Had them sign in.
Saw some shifty eyes in there,
but may be my redneck radar.
I don't know.
Excuse me.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You found him, didn't you?
You look like you haven't
slept in a couple days.
Work to do. How's it at school?
Sad.
People are scared.
Uh...
Been asking about this.
We haven't gotten anything.
I don't know,
you knowing the kids and such.
You ever seen anything like this?
Seen a kid with a doll like this?
Uh, maybe. I don't know.
But looks like something you'd find
in a craft store or something.
I haven't seen
any of the kids with them.
Can I keep this?
Uh, sure.
I'll ask around with the kids,
maybe check with the other teachers.
All right. Thanks.
Uh...
MAN: Amelia.
- Okay, I gotta go.
- All right.
Be safe.
HENRY: NOW, this family,
haven't we spent enough time
with this?
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
It's helping me.
Bringing things back.
How's that?
Your mother.
I, um...
I have trouble seeing her sometimes.
Or I know who she is,
but the parts of our lives, pieces,
I can't picture them.
You think Mom wants you
to keep doing this?
It's bringing things back,
going over the case.
I'm remembering things.
My life. Your sister.
You know when the last time
I saw Rebecca?
(SIGHS)
Mom's funeral?
I think you talked
on the phone a few months back.
You sure you wanna
keep talking to the TV people?
That woman, the director,
I wanna know what she's after.
What they might know now.
She said she'd, uh, show me something
next time.
She's baiting you, Dad.
Do you think she cares at all
about you or who did it?
She just wants people
to watch her shitty show.
And I think
Mom would want you to move on.
Enjoy the family you have around you.
Well,
she and I always had different ideas.
-(HENRY SCOFFS)
- I remember that.
WARREN: Wayne. Roland.
Special Agents Burt Diller
and John Bowen.
BURT: Thanks, Detective.
We'll get these back ASAP.
Want you to know we have no intention
of impeding or usurping
your investigation.
This is a Task Force.
One unit with a common goal.
Feds are gonna take the lead
with the kidnapping.
You two are still point
on the death investigation.
Both of which will hopefully
lead to the same solution.
Everybody shares everything.
We'll be doing debriefs
first thing every morning.
Everybody turns in dailies.
How you guys wanna go forward?
We got a mum-state APB
out on the gm.
Checkpoints along state lines.
Agents advised.
Let's get caught up.
We'll figure our next move.
Time?
You two have somewhere to be?
We got a funeral to get to.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
I know we spoke on the phone,
but we want to touch base
on a couple of things.
What's that?
I haven't been out here
since last May.
You stayed
in the boy Will's room, right?
Yeah. Told you I did.
Leave a couple magazines behind?
Under the mattress?
(SIGHS) Damn. Yeah, maybe I did.
Uh, should I...
Never mind.
You recall anything from the time
you spent in the house
might be worth mentioning?
Like, you ever see anybody
talking to the kids?
Any adults you didn't recognize?
Nah. Nah.
Can't say I recall anything like that.
Them kids, they kept
to themselves a lot, you know.
The house was a pretty tense place.
I mean, you can probably tell,
Lucy and Tom, they aren't real happy.
Before any of this.
Will and Julie,
they play outside the house a lot?
Yeah. I think so.
I don't think they liked
being around there.
You know, Mom and Dad
angry all the time.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(COUPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Were you pretty close
to Will and Julie?
I don't know. We got along.
I played with them a couple times.
They didn't see me much
before I stayed here.
But they were good kids.
What do you think of Tom?
He's an all right guy.
I feel sorry for him.
I felt for him even before all this.
I mean, in my opinion,
Lucy always needed,
like, a strong male.
Staying in town long?
Nah, I gotta get back to work.
Family could probably use you around.
I can't get the time off.
It's not like there's a lot
I can do for them.
And the night of?
Your neighbor can confirm
you were at home?
I don't know if they can or not.
But you could check
with the Starlight Bar in Springfield.
I had a couple there after work,
and then I went home
and watched CHIPS.
- You wanna search my place?
- Would that be okay?
(SCOFFS)
Sure.
But maybe you should be out there
trying to find my niece.
I'm gonna get back to Lucy.
ROY: Like we said over the phone,
we hadn't seen or talked
with the kids since last Christmas.
ELOISE: Nearly a year ago.
- She doesn't like us.
- That's Lucy, you mean?
ROY: Eloise, let's don't, now.
Why not now?
Why not just say it?
The children are lost.
Yes, I mean Lucy.
She runs around on Tom, you know.
Every marriage has its own story.
Nobody knows except the two involved.
Bull. She was a terrible...
(ELOISE SIGHS)
You know, there's been
some wondering about Julie.
Don't. Not today.
ELOISE: Tom was working offshore.
Could have been welding in Texas
when Julie was conceived.
- Now, I've wondered...
- God damn it!
Not today, Eloise. Not today.
(SOBS)
TOM: Hey.
Why don't the two of y'all
get out of my house for today?
Mom, Dad.
- CREWMEMBER: Yeah, I got it now.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
ELISA: There's a web forum
that posts
about real-life criminal cases,
things that are unsolved
or unresolved.
They have a whole section
on the Purcell case.
This is what people do now?
ELISA: They go in lots of directions.
Did you know at various times since,
large-scale pedophile rings
connected to people of influence
were uncovered in
the surrounding areas?
Do you know about
the Franklin scandal?
WAYNE: No.
It's been theorized
that the straw dolls
are a sign of pedophile groups,
like the crooked spiral.
I don't think that's right.
Can I ask, with what happened in 1990
and you leaving the force,
did you ever feel
your leads and theories
were discounted because of your race?
Not particularly. No, why?
I'm interested
in the intersectionality
of marginalized groups
within authoritarian
and systemic racist structures.
Anyways, those dolls from the scene,
they were a significant lead.
Amelia. She's the one
helped us out with that.
Got us that lead.
(CHILDREN YELLING, PLAYING)
Have you seen a do”
that looks like this?
No.
Not you?
Okay, well, you let me know
if you do, okay?
(VIDEO GAME BEEPING)
Mike, have you seen this doll before?
MIKE: Halloween.
Somebody was passing them out
at trick-or-treat, I think.
Julie, she got one.
This Halloween you went
trick-or-treating with her?
We met her and her brother
and... And some other kids.
We live on the next street over.
It's okay.
Tom?
(AIR HISSING LOUDLY)
Tom! Tom!
Hey, what you doing
back up here, brother?
Talking about?
This is my usual shift. Four years.
What's your fucking problem?
My dick showing?
ERNEST: Hey, Tom.
You sure you wanna be back
at work today?
I've been working full-time
since I was 14 years old.
You want me to sit at home
with this shit in my head now?
(SHOUTING) How long
are you motherfuckers
gonna stare at me?
Somebody got something
to say about me? My family?
Huh? Somebody know
something I don't...
Tom? Hi.
We didn't plan on
having you back this soon.
Well, I gotta earn a living.
Well, the thing is,
we, uh... We put you on leave.
Well, I didn't ask for that, okay?
Now, I gotta work.
You telling me I can't work?
Look, with everything
that's happening,
it's a little disruptive.
People have other things
on their mind.
These machines.
That's how accidents happen.
You know that, Tom.
(VOICE BREAKING) I'm the guy
nobody wants to be, huh?
I'm a fucking joke, right?
You shouldn't look at it like that.
But you ain't coming back
to work right now, Tom.
Well, fuck everything, anyway!
Yeah, fuck each of you! I quit!
ROLAND: You remember which house
was giving these out?
Who else got one?
Mike, did you see her get the doll?
MIKE: No, ma'am.
When did you see she had it?
It was like at the end.
We were all showing what we got,
and she had the doll
in her trick-or-treat bag.
Did you stay in the neighborhood,
or did you drive somewhere?
We just walked.
Thanks, Mike. You're really helping.
Hey. What'd you go as for Halloween?
Luke Skywalker.
Cool, man.
My partner, he loved that movie.
(MIMICS LIGHTSABER)
(WAYNE SIGHS)
Say, uh,
were you with Julie and her brother
the whole night?
Or was there ever a time
y'all went different ways?
Yeah.
They'd been to a couple houses
before we met up.
But I don't think
she had the doll then.
How about the rest of the night?
We might have split up once or twice.
But not for long.
I saw her talking to people.
Adults, maybe.
They were two ghosts.
Just in big sheets.
You don't know who the ghosts were?
Can you show us
where it was y'all went?
Here.
You must have had some good times.
When y'all meet?
Thirteen years back.
We got married
'cause she was pregnant.
ROLAND: How long you knew her before?
Not long.
Got married three months after we met.
The Fort Smith courthouse.
Me and Lucy,
we never really knew each other,
we just...
Well, had the kids.
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
(VOICE BREAKING) My kids. Will and...
(BOTTLE CAP UNSCREWING)
(COUGHS)
Are we gonna find Julie, or what?
'Cause I can't live through this, man.
Neither of us can.
If we're not gonna find her,
I just need to know now.
I can't go to sleep,
and I can't wake up.
BURT: Now, you're saying
last week, Halloween,
girl got one of these dolls,
and then you found two of them
at the crime scene?
It's an identifier, boss.
So what do you want to do?
We wondered, maybe
let's put it out on the TV or paper.
Ask everybody
if they seen one of those,
or know who makes them around here.
But that'd tip our hand.
We're not ready for that.
What's better...
There's 114 households
in the marked area
and the subdivision near it.
We do total surveillance.
We have people searching
every single house.
Oh, come on. You don't have enough
for one warrant, much less 100.
No warrants.
Say, two days, maybe three.
Every detective we have.
Pull in more Feds, you want.
Everybody just knocks
and asks if they can search.
Say it'll help with the Purcell case.
People won't like it,
but a lot, I bet...
A lot of people let us look around.
ROLAND: We keep surveillance.
See if somebody starts acting hinky.
Nobody escapes the net.
Our guy panics or something,
we do it fast, without announcement.
Even if you find anything,
it could be problematic at trial.
- This is about the girl, not a trial.
-(GERALD SIGHS)
WAYNE: Something happened
on Halloween, that night.
She gets that doll.
A week later,
she and her brother are gone,
and you got two of those things
on the scene.
JOHN: Maybe the perp's
just brought them somewhere.
You know?
Maybe the dolls belonged to the girl.
ROLAND: It's all maybes, man.
You do the maybe
that gives you a shot.
No, it's thin.
I mean, our constituents here,
they value privacy
and property rights.
They aren't just gonna acquiesce
to random searches of their homes.
There's other ways to approach it.
ROLAND: If we bring in the public,
it stirs up the town
and lets our guy know
what we're thinking.
Maybe he takes off.
Maybe he just kills her,
if he hasn't already.
We can just do it fast.
People will get over it.
Warren.
Just give us some time, Roland.
(LIGHTS BUZZING)
Been running this sting.
Truck stop next door.
Prosts and drugs.
I was gonna check this guy out
at some point.
He asked one of the working girls
if they had any younger friends.
And another said he asked her, too.
Came in here looking
for special magazines.
Ted LaGrange. Pulled his file.
He got outta Wrightsville
a while back.
Carnal knowledge of a minor.
Enticing a minor. Bunch of shit.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
Calling himself
"Robert" something now.
ROLAND: Thanks, Rich.
Man, you gotta come in here every day?
Welcome to Vice.
(JAZZY MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
I haven't seen you here before,
havel?
I'm usually at the VFW.
Want to thank you for everything
you did today with the kid.
He wasn't talking to us
fill you opened him up.
Real grateful for that.
He was broken up about it.
I think he had a crush on Julie.
Why'd you give me that picture?
The doll.
Instinct, I guess.
I knew the kids weren't talking to us.
You were in the war?
You're a cop,
so you want to know
more about a person,
you just look them up, huh?
Pretty much.
Did you look me up?
Thought about it, though.
I was born here.
I went to U ofA.
Dropped out my junior year.
Went west with a friend.
We got in with some people.
I was in this scene, San Francisco.
Anti-war,
kind of fringe Panther stuff.
Some things happened, not good.
And then I was alone.
'74, I came back home, got my degree.
I grew up in Conway.
My mom worked on a farm.
I spent two years in the jungle.
A lot of it I was alone.
I hunt a lot now. Alone.
I'm a vegetarian.
(CHUCKLES)
That's a real shame.
If you're a Democrat, don't tell me.
You like teaching?
Sometimes.
I want to be a writer.
Write books.
I don't read enough.
I like Batman and Silver Surfer.
I had this sort of
dyslexic thing growing up.
Was that hard?
They said I was dumb.
My mom wasn't having any of that.
That poem you were teaching,
IIookeditup.
- Oh, yeah?
- I read it.
I'm not ready to talk about it yet,
but I have thoughts.
- Share when you want.
-(CHUCKLES) All right.
You ever been married?
No.
You?
I was engaged. Seven months.
I broke it off.
I didn't want to be married,
I realized.
- I don't wanna get married.
- No?
Guy the other day
said I must be crazy.
Thing is, and I've thought
of this for a while,
I think I might be.
Like how?
I wear clip-on ties
'cause I'm preoccupied
with this idea
of getting strangled with one.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Is that too much?
This year, twice,
I've been to St. Louis,
and I've stayed at this hotel,
and I've pretended I'm someone else.
I go out, meet new people,
and I am someone else.
Different name,
different background, different job.
Twice.
(CHUCKLES)
You drink too much?
I don't know.
I might get drunk twice a month.
Three times.
I like to laugh, is the thing.
Hey. Raise it up.
Hurry. Quick.
NEWSCASTER: ...information
in the Purcell murder-kidnapping,
we go to the Washington County
courthouse earlier this afternoon.
Don't do it.
GREG: We believe the missing girl,
Julie Purcell,
was contacted by her abductor
while she participated
in Halloween last week.
We're sharing a graphic of the area
where she and her brother
went trick-or-treating.
Now, our investigation suggests
that someone who saw her on Halloween
has special knowledge of this case.
Giving it away.
GREG: Anyone who saw
anything suspicious...
- What's wrong?
-(SIGHS) I'm sorry. I...
I gotta go. God damn it.
REPORTER: Are you saying the children
knew their kidnapper?
GREG: I'm not at liberty to, uh,
reveal that at this time. Thank you.
WAYNE: I knew
they wouldn't listen to me.
But you should have stopped that.
Me? What am I supposed to do?
You were there.
I'm saying, I talk,
it don't mean anything.
Don't matter if I'm right.
You, at least, you talk,
it means something to them.
Might consider what you're saying.
You might have stopped them
from doing that.
Bullshit.
Who knew until it was on the TV?
Why didn't you stop them?
They ain't my tribe, man.
Take care of your shit.
Tribe?
Where you think you are, asshole?
- I know where I am.
- Do you? It don't sound like it.
Son, I know where I am in a way
you will never understand.
Are you high, "Purple" Hays?
'Cause you're making
about as much goddamn sense
as my grandmother's dementia.
No, I'm saying I know where I am.
Hey, good for you.
(SCOFFS)
Was all I could think of.
You got something else?
Vice gave me a dude
near Fort Smith to look at.
I pulled his file.
What is it?
You can read for yourself.
You wanna go get him?
Iwanna go get him.
We might as well keep watch out here.
Check the guy out in the morning.
Toss his place first.
(SIGHS)
We should get bennies.
Staying up all night.
Glove box. Red and blue ones.
Prosecuting attorney decided
best thing was to take our single clue
and spread it all over the town.
And that got us a few hundred
false tips the first couple of days.
That's when it all started
with the town.
Just panic.
WAYNE: Lived in their
imaginations now, you see?
Everybody was scared.
That included us.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Hi.
Morning.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You gonna eat?
Me neither.
We need you to come with us, sir.
-(STAMMERING) What's the...
- We'll tell you on the way.
- No! Please!
-(BOTH GRUNTING)
(TED SOBBING)
No, it's not me, I swear to God!
You're wrong about this.
You shouldn't have brought me here.
This get you off, mister, huh?
You entertain fantasies
of strapping white men to posts?
- Now and then, yeah.
- Really?
(GRUNTS, SOBS)
Talk about your fantasies.
Then he'll tell you his.
Theodore LaGrange.
It's Ted, yeah?
Ted, you been out
a bit over two years.
I haven't done anything.
I know what you're doing,
and I haven't done anything.
Released from Wrightsville.
You got Little Rock up the road.
Why'd you come way out here, Ted?
And why are you calling yourself
Robert Hebert?
(STAMMERING) I...
I wanted a new start.
They keep you in protective custody
in Wrightsville?
(CHUCKLES)
Figured.
Guys who mess with kids,
they don't usually make it out
with all their parts.
Tell me how you mess with kids.
WAYNE: The boy and the girl.
Your landlady said you
didn't come home last Friday night.
- What?
- The 7th.
That's not... I was out.
I was just out.
Help me understand what it was like
for you in the moment.
Let me feel your side of it. Okay?
- Tell me why you killed the boy.
- I didn't!
I never seen him
before he was on the news.
(GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
You'll wanna explain to me
where you were that night.
Help me see your side of things.
What'd you do on Halloween night?
Where were you?
Well,
we're here to listen
when you want to share.
-(GRUNTS)
-(YELLS)
(SOBBING)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING, PLAYING)
Yes. He's here Mondays and Fridays.
We do story time twice a week
in the evenings,
and he plays guitar for it.
But his name's Robert Hebert,
not what you said.
And he worked on the 7th? Last Friday?
Yes, mmm-hmm.
You know what time he left that night?
Probably about 8:00 or after.
He helped us put up
the tables and chairs.
Did he do something?
You're not gonna see this guy anymore.
If you do, give us a call, okay?
ALAN: Robbery
was a couple of months ago.
All I know for sure
is that her prints showed up.
It's like you said...
They don't know if she was a customer
or part of the break-in.
Was it a partial or a full?
Full.
It was her.
They had video surveillance?
Oh, they smashed the camera
in the pharmacy.
Store's got footage
going back three days prior.
We subpoenaed it, but we have to wait.
Somebody watching the store
in case she comes back?
My understanding,
Sallisaw PD's focused on the robbery.
And I wouldn't say the locals
are a crackerjack investigative team
or anything...
So nothing.
Man's family didn't have
the resources for an investigator.
But obviously, we'd like to find her.
What about Arkansas PD?
They looking for her?
There's nobody on the case yet.
Kindt's office will have to look at it
since they'll be defending
our motion to overturn,
but right now, no.
I don't think so.
You all right going up
against your old boss?
It's overdue.
Talk to Roland?
We have an appointment.
He's done well.
He has.
You wanna execute him?
We can bury him right out here.
I don't give a shit.
Throw him off a bridge...
Nobody'II care.
-(TED MOANING)
- Put him in holding,
get his parole violated.
He'll be back
in Wrightsville tomorrow.
- Full sentence.
- If you say so.
Talk shit about us...
I'll have monstrous niggers
fuck him to death in his cell.
(MUFFLED SPEECH)
Do you hear me, boy?
You will bleed black cock.
(MOANING, SOBBING)
Gotta catch up, man.
Just spent the day on this bullshit.
That was a vivid description
of prison rape. Jesus.
Could tell he had the racial thing.
Remember what he said in the barn?
Still, it's gonna haunt me.
(POLICE RADIO BEEPS)
DISPATCH: (OVER RADIO)
D-12, do you copy?
Copy, dispatch.
Lieutenant Twiggs wants y'all
at the Purcell place.
What's up?
Said the family got a note.
Copy. On the way.
(CARTOON PLAYING ON TV)
- HENRY: Hey, Dad.
- Hi.
Hey. Hey.
Did you see? They sent me the galleys.
That's great.
You got a little loose after work?
How was the deposition?
It was fine.
(SIGHS)
WAYNE: It's as much about us
as anything.
And I think her and me,
it was as close as she could give
the thing a happy ending.
ELISA: After the events of 1990,
and what happened
with Julie and her father,
you left the PD.
Did you believe
that concluded the case?
Did you feel the investigation
ended too abruptly?
She wrote six novels after.
This was her first.
Uh, very...
To a cop,
very impressive eye for detail.
Have you read it?
Mr. Hays, did you have theories
after what happened
with Julie Purcell
and her father in '90?
Theories that weren't in line
with your superior's directives?
I heard what you asked.
The answer is...
I never stopped coming up
with theories about that case.
And I hit Todd and Dave into a home,
and when I went over, we won.
Coach saw, and came and talked
to me about baseball
when I get older.
- That's fantastic, Henry.
- HENRY: Mmm-hmm.
You're gonna be very athletic.
You already are.
(HENRY CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
The publisher said we can
issue an update for the paperback
once this appeal goes to trial.
Yeah?
You're a bit out of it tonight.
The kids noticed.
You can't be that way
in front of them.
- I'm not drunk.
- What's going on?
What happened with the deposition?
Are they overturning the conviction?
Julie Purcell is alive.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LUCY SOBBING)
Thought for sure
you'd all beat us here.
TOM: What is that, huh?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What's that mean?
Well, what's it mean?
Hmm?
HEATHER: You want more chicken, Wayne?
Uh...
Thanks for the spread, Heather.
This is wonderful.
Are you feeling all right?
He's been going back
through that case. Mom's book.
I never read the whole thing.
Couldn't stand I was in it so much.
Going back over the story,
it's good...
Making me work my brain, I mean.
Leading me to other stuff.
Maybe you guys could see
about getting Rebecca out here.
I'd like to see her.
She's in LA, Dad.
When did that happen?
What's she doing out there?
She's playing music, Wayne.
She okay? You talk to her?
HEATHER: I talked to her
a few weeks ago.
Think she'd come back home
for a visit?
She don't like it here, Dad.
Why not?
(SIGHS)
I just don't think it suits her.
- She never liked it.
- She didn't?
-(BOY LAUGHS)
- Hey!
One more time, okay?
(BOY LAUGHS)
HEATHER: Shh, eat. (CHUCKLES)
It's going by pretty quick.
Don't I know it.
Maybe you guys could see
about getting Rebecca out here.
I'd like to see her.