(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Hell of a day when a gunfight's
the second most exciting thing
happens to you.
I was trying to hold out.
Make you wait a bit.
You seem like the type
that kind of thing matters.
You don't have to do that.
What?
Check and see if I'm judging you.
I'm not.
I was so glad you weren't hurt.
Came close.
First time I fired my weapon
on the job.
You fired your weapon before,
in the war?
I wanna hear about your stuff.
How you got here, your past.
Honestly, I never give it thought.
One thing I learned, the war?
Life happens now.
And Iater's now, you know?
It's never behind you.
And I'm not avoiding the question,
just really don't spend time
remembering stuff.
That's like a superpower to me.
I can't even understand that,
how you do it.
Just lucky, I guess.
WOMAN: (OVER RECORDER)
Tell him to leave me alone.
- I know What he did.
- MAN: (OVER RECORDER) Who?
WOMAN: The man on TV
acting like my father.
MAN: Can you tell me
Where you're calling from?
WOMAN: Where's my brother, Will?
I don't know what he did with him.
That certainly sounds like
an indictment.
And according to the file,
he didn't have an alibi the night of.
You two never kicked that very hard,
did you?
You ignored that?
(BLEVINS SIGHS)
We need to go at him, hard.
Freddy Burns saw the boy alone
out in them woods,
when we still had Tom
working on his car.
BLEVINS: Me and Ted can take a shot.
Y'all wanna observe?
No. We'll do it.
I don't know what that call was,
but no way we could be that wrong.
(SIGHS)
Wanna give it to Morelli?
No.
Them others will eat him alive.
What's it mean?
- That was her, wasn't it?
- Sit down, Tom.
- I don't wanna sit down right now.
- ROLAND: It's not a request.
What are you looking like that for?
Something you wanna tell us,
Mr. Purcell?
What?
However long it's been,
it's the time,
while you're talking
to a couple of friends.
'Cause they bring in the other guys,
it's gonna get bad.
Tell us your side.
We can help. Make a case for you.
My side?
Everybody knows my side.
You think me?
Back in '80,
the night of the incident,
couple of neighbors saw you
working in the garage, early evening.
Don't have anybody saw you after 6:30.
Saw me?
Roland...
Lieutenant West.
You go somewhere back then?
You leave the house
and forgot to tell us?
No.
No. Iwent back inside,
I had a couple beers
and listened to the Cardinals game,
same as I told you.
Julie's room...
There's a little hole in her wall
came out back of Will's closet.
A what?
Like a peephole. For spying.
Ever look in on her? Julie?
Maybe while she was getting dressed?
Some question, wasn't there,
whether she was yours?
Lucy passed it around a lot,
what we hear.
Listen, she...
I held...
I fed her, got up in the night.
She's mine. That child is mine.
How could you,
after everything you know,
you think I could
do something like that?
Do you? You?
- Did you give her to somebody, Tom?
- What?
- Was she trying to get away from you?
Somebody helping her
out of a situation with you?
- What? Why?
- Did Will know? Did he catch you?
Why? Why? Goddamn, why would I...
WAYNE: You know they weren't playing
with that neighbor kid.
Who were they meeting at Devil's Den?
I don't know. I don't know
anything you're talking about.
No, no, no, no...
ROLAND: Tell us about it.
We wanna help you,
but we can't if you don't talk to us.
(YELLING)
WAYNE“. I don't know.
Usually, I do, but I don't know.
I can't believe we missed this.
I mean, could he have
colluded with Woodard?
Come to that, could he have planted
the items in Woodard's house?
There's no evidence
right now for an arrest.
Hold him for the 24.
Start digging for anything
that points in his direction.
I'm gonna give you a warrant
for his place.
We need to check out
where that call came from, too.
Get busy.
We missed it once,
we're not losing him now.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
ELISA: The phone call was viewed
as a major turn, correct?
Law enforcement seemed to
consider it as an indictment,
particularly in light of
what happened.
What happened?
Huh?
After questioning,
Tom Purcell was held in jail.
What did investigators do
after that phone call?
That was her, wasn't it? Julie?
Mmm-hmm.
Call came from a truck stop
outside Russellville.
We pulled a partial
off of a payphone.
Hers.
You didn't wanna tell the bosses
about the backpack?
You were pretty convinced
it was planted.
It was planted.
I didn't wanna give them that
to use on him yet.
Hey.
Had to change. Gotta go back out.
Okay.
Missing my old clip-ons.
Shit.
You're not
in elementary school anymore.
Where you going?
I have things to do.
New book.
What new book?
Sequel
It's about the current investigation.
I thought you wanted
to work on a novel next.
The publisher wants this bad.
They think
it's too good an opportunity.
I get troubled calling what happened
an "opportunity."
That's their word.
You can't expect the world to conform
to Wayne Hays's moral semantics.
Right.
Well, it's an opportunity for you,
isn't it?
Back to Major Crimes.
Keeping your own hours.
We get clear on this,
I'll be home more.
Will you?
Seems like this suits you better.
Running free.
Just trying to do my job right.
So, that's my imagination,
seeing you
like you can't breathe in here?
Yeah, it's your imagination.
Telling yourself stories about me,
my motives.
I could tell stories.
Why you're all of a sudden
working on a book you already wrote.
What you looking for out there,
you're not finding here.
WAYNE: We dug into Tom.
The father, yeah.
His place. Talked to his bosses.
I remember talking to y'all back then.
Yeah, he quit before
the school bus factory closed.
Tell you the truth,
he was on his way out
even before what happened.
Why's that?
Caught him drinking on the job
more than once.
Machines are dangerous
around that shit.
Always asking for a loan.
And, you know,
didn't quite get along
with the rest of the guys.
How do you mean?
I didn't wanna say anything back then,
but a few of the boys had around
saw him going into a queer club.
They got on him a lot, after.
So, he's not
the saint of all suffering.
Everybody's got weaknesses.
Don't mean he did that to his kids.
Looking less and less to me
like they were his kids.
Devil's Den was a homo cruising spot.
The kids weren't
supposed to be out there.
- If Tom was...
- Fuck off.
We know they were meeting
somebody else out there.
Tom wouldn't do that.
- This.
- Hey.
If he wouldn't, then we'll clear him.
But we gotta get this right.
You saw at the station.
Kindt and Blevins are hot for it.
If it's not him,
we clear him.
But we don't stop.
Take it all the way this time.
I remember 1980.
You're supposed to be at home.
Detective Hays.
Your shooting cleared. No surprise.
What's the latest on Roland?
Gets to keep the leg.
Won't be the same,
but it's a lot better
than Diller and Bowen got.
WARREN: They found the boy's backpack.
Girl's shirt.
Both at Woodard's place.
KINDT: Yeah, it was him.
What?
No, something's wrong here.
If it was him, that ain't all of it.
Other people involved.
Kids were meeting somebody.
KINDT: Jesus Christ, you were there.
WARREN: Wayne.
You see what's happening out here?
Press is making the county
3 Hee Haw sideshow.
May have gotten some help with that.
Okay, Detective,
stick to the evidence.
And it only goes one way.
Even makes sense for the kidnap note.
Cut-out words, misspelling.
It was Woodard.
Then where's the girl?
He had a couple of oil drums
he made into an incinerator.
Evidence suggests he burned the body.
- Are we sure?
- KINDT: She's dead.
Let's not draw out
the family's pain any longer.
Our official position is
Woodard murdered both children.
That's it. Take some time.
- Probably a medal in this.
- Warren, I don't wanna take time.
I don't give a shit about medals.
I'm telling you...
Enough. He killed 10 people, Wayne.
You were there.
It's done.
This community needs to heal,
Detective. We're the first step.
And state law allows conviction in
absentia under special circumstances.
Our offices are gonna need
all evidence,
your investigative records,
everything.
Twelve people.
What?
You putting the kids on him,
that means he killed 12 people,
not 10.
Just so you keep
your stories straight.
ELISA: The cousin, Dan O'Brien,
his remains were found in a drained
quarry in southern Missouri.
Do you think
this could connect to Tom?
I don't know.
Couldn't say.
Well, what happened with Tom,
Lucy, now her cousin Dan...
We also had to talk to all the cops
who worked the Woodard scene
backin'80.
I believe that's what we did next,
or around then.
Because the thought was that Tom
may have planted the evidence there?
Well, we had to look
at the possibility.
Or maybe they worked together,
him and Woodard.
You know, it's terrible
what this work makes you ponder.
Don't you think?
Might've seen him. Hard to say.
Had a lot of Iookie-loos
around the place.
And you're the one found the backpack?
Yeah. Yeah, I found it.
Then Harris said
looked like that boy's.
- That's Harris James?
- Yeah.
Says he left the force.
Oh, yeah, 3 long time ago.
You know what he's doing now?
"Chief Security Officer."
How do I get something like that?
Well, I moonlighted security
at the plant
for about five years
when I was a patrolman.
When the spot opened up here,
I was in the right place.
I don't know why a lieutenant
would wanna switch careers.
That matter, I don't know I ever heard
a lieutenant working the field.
It's a special situation.
If I get your salary,
I'll switch to any career they say.
What, you look at my paycheck?
Pretty depressing from my end.
(CHUCKLES)
ROLAND: You took the job May '81?
That's right.
We're backtracking. The Purcell case.
Got it down you were the one
spotted the bag.
JAMES: NO, I didn't find it.
I was the first to think
I recognized it, off the APB.
Well, we've been wondering why it took
two days to find that backpack.
Took God six days to make the world.
I can believe it took a bunch of GEDs
two days to find a backpack.
The kids' father.
You ever see him out there
when you were processing the scene?
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I saw him
in the field across the street.
Watching.
ROLAND: What was he doing?
Just staring.
Stood there looking at the house,
or what was left of it.
Long time.
You know, the kids' mother
used to work up here.
Back in '79.
Well, unless she worked
10:00 to 6:00 in the morning,
I never saw her.
That was y'all, right? The shootout?
That's my fucking limp.
Why'd you leave Highway Patrol?
Why'd I give up hemorrhoids
and 15K 3 year? I don't know.
That question keeps me up nights.
What's the job involve?
Money like that.
Hog thieves?
People trying to steal
the secret chicken recipe?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
"Securing without compromise
"the integrity of corporate assets
"while guarding against hazards
to daily operations."
But I'll admit, now and then,
I miss whiling away my days,
cruising around, eating donuts.
I don't eat donuts.
I can tell.
You got a good body, Detective.
ROLAND: Appreciate your time.
We'll get outta your hair.
ROLAND: I thought it took God
seven days to make the world.
He rested on the seventh.
I always thought he should've
put the extra day in,
instead of half-assing it.
ELISA: Harris James?
He was one of the officers
who processed the Woodard scene.
He disappeared
during the 1990 investigation.
Huh.
Know what happened to him?
No. But the mother, the father,
the cousin's body being found now,
all the dead at Woodard's,
this former cop worked the scene.
I wonder if one day
they'll drain a quarry with him in it.
I wouldn't know, miss.
But what you just did
is called speculation.
That leads to projection, we call it.
Twists what you see, obfuscates truth.
Have you sat back at any point
over the last two decades
and thought about the sheer number
of fatalities surrounding this case?
(SIGHS)
I'm afraid I need to stop for today.
I'm sorry, can you give us
five more minutes?
I didn't mean to press.
You're fine. I'm just done.
All I meant...
Doesn't the simple body count
point toward something bigger...
- Stop. He's done.
- ELISA: I'm getting to the point.
HENRY: Then you should have
gotten to it sooner. Okay?
AMELIA: Thanks so much for your help.
Do you work with a lot of young girls?
We get a fair amount.
Runaways, girls trying
to get away from bad homes.
We just lose so many.
I can't say I recognize her.
But that's not the best picture,
is it?
The idea is
maybe it's this little girl, grown up.
Here we are.
Yeah, we were in the same group.
That was four or five months ago,
I think?
Why did she leave?
Things had gotten kind of shaky.
Drugs.
One of the guys had gotten
some of the girls to trick.
Just got ugly.
I dropped out
a couple weeks after Mary.
She called herself "Mary"?
Sometimes.
Or Mary-Julie.
And sometimes Mary-July,
like Julie, but July.
"Like summertime," she said.
She had different names.
(CLANGING)
AMELIA: She ever talk about herself?
Talk about home?
Where she came from?
She mentioned something about,
"Living in the pink rooms"?
Or "A queen in a pink castle."
You know what I think?
I think she didn't know who she was.
I think she just pretended.
You oughta write a book.
Write about what happens
to kids out here.
What happens to girls.
OPERATOR: (ON RADIO)
D-12, you around? Over.
D-12. We're here.
Got a call on the hotline.
Guy says he wants to talk
to Lieutenant West.
Says he knows him.
What guy? Who?
Gave us a number to call.
Go ahead.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MAN CHUCKLES)
Y'all still together?
Right on.
You're a hard man to find.
Where you been?
Time being what it is,
I imagine you boys
would rather I stick
to what's relevant.
Which is thatjustice might
finally be done for Lucy and her kids.
Gonna need you to make
your fucking point, Dan.
My point is Tom going on TV,
Julie being alive.
Now, there are questions
that you cannot answer
without what information I know.
You know something you're not saying,
we can put you away right now.
Or we can take you somewhere,
kick the hell out of you
till we're convinced that you're
as full of shit as you look to me.
- I want $7,000.
- I want a boat.
It's clear from the news
that y'all don't know any more now
than you did then.
But when you can
deliver to me that amount,
hey, you're gonna know
a whole lot more.
I imagine a whole lot of your
confusion's just gonna clear right up.
You're working on getting your head
bounced off that fucking curb.
I been getting the shit beat outta me
since I was two years old.
Way before Lucy came to live with us.
- Live with you?
- Yeah.
She moved in, she was four.
After her mama passed.
Her and I, we sort of shared
a lot of milestones, growing up.
First time we talked,
it was clear that
you can't speak without lying.
Why should we believe you now?
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, you ignore me if you want.
But if you guys try muscling me,
this ain't gonna work out for anyone.
Hmm?
Look, I got you out here
because you looking for Julie again,
that means that right now,
there are people trying to make sure
that none of your questions
can ever be answered.
What people?
People who do not renegotiate.
People who it was in their interest
to make Lucy look like she OD'd.
What, you saying she was murdered?
Lucy, she had this problem,
self-defeating.
She didn't know when to stop pushing.
She'd push till she got
what she wanted,
and then she'd keep on pushing
till she got what she didn't want.
Y'all ever know anybody like that?
Let's throw him in the hole
for a week,
-see what he remembers then.
- You think she has a week? Hmm?
I'll just remember that
I'm a sick person who got called away,
carried up in his imagination,
telling stories to the police.
And while y'all are threatening me
and beating me and whatnot,
what you're really doing
is making sure
that the truth of what happened
vanishes from the face
of the fucking planet.
What happened to her
have anything to do with Tom?
Man, y'all are really far off,
aren't you?
You think that I'd be scared
of sticking my head above ground
'cause of that little cocksucker?
Shit.
The people you're saying hurt Lucy,
that involve the kids?
What am I... Yes, God damn it. Yes.
It's all about the kids.
And my way is the only way
this works for us.
Now, you procure my funds,
we meet back here,
say, tomorrow, maybe the next day,
you're gonna see the solution
to your problems.
It's gonna take more than couple days
to put that money together.
DAN: You ain't got
much longer than that.
Like I keep saying, you ain't
the only ones looking for Julie.
(DOOR OPENS)
You can't be so fucked in the head
where you're thinking
we're gonna let you walk outta here.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, maybe I misspoke, hmm?
I mean, look at me.
This basket case junkie,
can't tell night from day,
taking up your valuable time.
I mean, probably I'm just a crazy man
you should ignore.
I speak crazy. I'm fucking fluent.
Tick-took. Clock's ticking
for our girl out there, Detectives.
And them others
that are looking for her,
they got a serious head start
on you all.
Look, I'll call you
day after tomorrow.
Unless you all would rather we keep
having this fucking staring contest.
Maybe I'm a nervous Nellie,
but I catch any cops following me,
this shit's Off.
Thanks for breakfast.
ROLAND: Believe this?
Think he's telling the truth?
WAYNE: I think we need to get
the phone records from Lucy's hotel.
Two years back. Yeah.
Think we need to figure out exactly
where Tom was when she died.
He didn't like Tom for it.
Well, I also think we oughta see about
requisitioning that seven thou.
Keep eyes on this trash.
Go on. You're getting out.
I wanna see Lieutenant West.
That's not my problem.
OFFICER 1: That was the lieutenant.
They just had lunch with our dirtbag.
- How's that?
- The uncle or whatever. Dan O'Brien.
Met him some diner.
Says he has the whole story,
wants a payout.
Fuck that. Give me an hour
in a room with him.
And they want us to get phone records.
Diamond Cactus Motel
in Paradise, Nevada.
Two years back.
Lucy's phone records.
Yeah, that's good use
of our time, huh?
Where's O'Brien now?
OFFICER 1:
They gave us a plate to run,
but sounds like
he's still in the wind.
ELISA: You're acting like a child.
HENRY: I'm not acting like a child.
You don't give a shit
about anybody but yourself!
ELISA: You're acting like a child.
Okay, forget it! This was a mistake.
Hey.
You're smoking now?
Seemed like time
to stop depriving myself.
You gonna keep going on with her,
after she's done filming?
What do you mean?
Have a hard time
seeing you in New York City.
How'd you know?
I'm still your daddy, boy.
Additionally, I was once
a fair-to-middling detective.
I feel bad.
And Heather, I mean, she's...
She's a good woman, you know?
She know about it?
I gotta tell her, huh?
Are you leaving her?
No.
You're ending the other thing.
There's something to be said
for truth just hurting her,
causing pain 'cause you feel guilty.
Is that fair?
You feeling better, she feeling worse?
I never did anything like this before,
Pop, I want you to know that.
I didn't plan it.
You know, shejust...
She was exciting.
They're exciting, all right.
And me and Heather,
it's not like it used to be.
Nothing stays like it used to be.
I been looking at myself a lot.
And I'm asking this question for me,
so I know.
What?
Did you find that I...
Did I teach you to withhold?
I don't understand the question.
I didn't intend that.
I didn't realize it was happening.
I got those addresses you wanted.
The names.
What are you planning?
Before you ever knew me,
Iwasn't scared much.
Iwasn't a fearful man.
I did things some people
even called brave.
Y'all made a coward of me.
I been terrified since
the day you were born.
Maybe you know when mean.
Can't shrink from it.
Can't be stingy, son.
People you love,
can't hold it back, see?
Can't hold back anything.
I gotta make a phone call, Pop.
KINDT: Due to the shocking
and horrific events three days ago,
our offices have reached a conclusion
in the case of Will and Julie Purcell.
New evidence suggests that
Brett Woodard murdered both children.
Now, we will pursue
a conviction in absentia,
due to the terrible nature
of his crimes,
and it is our hope
that the community will begin to heal
from these events
which have shaken us all.
REPORTER 1: Have they found
the girl's remains?
We have evidence,
but I don't wish to say more
under the present circumstances.
REPORTER 2:
Was Woodard under investigation?
He was very much a person of interest.
We were looking at him.
REPORTER 2: Were you close
to an arrest, is that why he snapped?
KINDT:
Well, I believe it's very likely
that the pressure, maybe the guilt,
drove him to explode
before he could be brought to trial.
But make no mistake,
that was an act of suicide
where he wanted to take
as many with him as he could.
REPORTER 3: Brett Woodard
was interrogated early on, correct?
Why wasn't he held
during the time of questioning?
KINDT: A lack of evidence.
We are bound by our common law,
which preserve the rights of all men,
even those as malignant
and as vicious as Mr. Woodard.
Mrs. Purcell.
Do you have a statement at this time?
"Leave me the fuck alone"
is my statement.
- Do you feel justice has been done?
- Justice?
The fuck are you talking about?
What's that even mean, huh?
- Here? Now?
- Mrs. Purcell...
Just leave her alone.
This is harassment.
It's my job. I'm just trying
to get the story right.
If I don't,
someone else'II get it wrong.
That is no excuse.
The fuck do you want, teacher?
I just wanna apologize
for how we left things...
Don't apologize to me.
Ever. For anything.
You two bitches,
you talk to each other.
Make up a story on your own.
Be ironic, that shitbird clears Tom.
It's something, isn't it?
How quick this town died.
Didn't die. Got murdered.
We oughta look at who else might've
planted the backpack and shirt.
Could've been anybody.
But I wouldn't clear Tom just yet.
The man has secrets.
Get back to the office,
wanna look up that church program,
more co-workers.
Wait. Where we going?
I'm taking you home. What you think?
I'm not going home. I'm working.
It'll still be there in the morning.
Come on, man. O'Brien?
We got the scent.
Let's get back, strategize,
maybe talk to somebody in Vice
about the queer underground.
Just stop, all right?
You don't wanna go home,
don't go home.
But don't make it the job.
Maybe we just work it different.
Oh, yeah, we work it different.
- I just said.
- And I agreed.
That's why I'm where I'm at,
and you...
What?
Me, what?
You're you.
- Pull over.
- What?
Stop the fucking car.
What are you, a prom queen?
I hurt your feelings,
you're just gonna storm off?
Are you fucking kidding me?
This kindergarten shit?
Where do you think you're going?
I don't care so much
about my timecard.
I'm working.
People see your black ass
skulking around,
you're gonna get yourself shot.
Prick.
Tommy Purses.
The fuck you doing here?
Smart mouth.
For a smart guy, you're awful sloppy.
Same place you used to
come to slam meth
when you weren't leeching off of us.
Don't really feel like
catching up just now, Tommy.
Hey, you know,
there's a rest stop up the road.
Saw a glory hole in the back stall,
if you need something to do.
Heard you're wanting a payout.
Let's pretend each of these bullets
is a thousand bucks.
Hold on now, Tom. Now,
you ain't got no problem with me.
Look, I know we ain't been buddies,
but you got no call for this here.
You know something,
you son of a bitch!
What is it?
What are you selling the cops?
Just point that gun down now, Tom.
Please.
You're making me real nervous here.
(PANTING)
You been drinking, man?
I thought you quit that.
- What do you know?
- Nothing! Just nothing!
- Bullshit!
- Okay, hold on, hold on.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
Hold on.
(GRUNTING)
Get up, motherfucker.
(GROANS)
I'm gonna shoot your dick off.
And then your knees,
and then maybe your ears...
What the fuck are you
talking about, man?
Julie! When you were staying
in Will's room,
you were spying on her.
Made a peephole in Will's closet,
so you could watch her get dressed.
I never... I would never...
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I'll figure out where to put
the last bullet when I get there.
God damn it, listen to me.
Listen to me!
I don't know nothing
about no peephole.
All right?
I'd never do nothing like that.
- Julie? She was...
- Where is she?
- I don't know!
- Where's my daughter?
- You lying motherfucker!
You ever ask yourself
where Lucy got the money to run off?
Or what she was living off for all
them eight years before she died? Hmm?
Say what you're saying, God damn it!
I'm saying,
I know who was paying her.
Listen, man,
I know who was paying her
and who would have a problem
if she asked for more.
That's all I was gonna
give the cops, man.
That's all I was gonna give the cops.
A name. Shit.
Just a man's name.
All right, you dumbshit.
Give me a reason not to murder you.
WAYNE: They were passing notes.
Little notes with the kids.
The hole in the wall,
that's what it was for.
That's right. That's correct.
Yeah, that director woman.
She mentioned Harris James. Again.
(SIGHS)
Are you sure you know
what you're doing with her?
Well, if I don't...
What'd O'Brien tell us?
"I'm just a sick man."
(SCOFFS)
I got a list of the names, addresses.
A former domestic, Hoyt's house.
Harris James' widow.
What you think we're gonna do?
Take a leak.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(DOOR OPENS)
Roland?
Hey, man.
How you doing?
Good, man.
All right.
You been spending a lot of time
in here, I guess.
I don't think I sleep much.
What?
Do me a favor.
Go to the window.
See if there's a dark sedan
idling down the street.
Okay.
No, man.
Nothing out there.
All right.
You been seeing a car?
How you been, Roland?
Been doing some reading.
Oh. Yeah.
I never read it all the way.
She never minded.
Good-looking woman.
That she was.
Yeah.
It's 2015, isn't it?
That's right, pal.
AMELIA: "A lost child is a void
"that echoes backwards
and forwards in time.
"It encompasses not just
the rooms you were in with them
"and are no longer,
"or even those rooms
you will never enter together.
"The negation is deeper.
"It is the knowledge
that in every room you enter
"for the rest of your life,
"they should be there, and are not.
"And your memories of them
become totems to that absence.
"A lost child
"is a story
that's never allowed to end."
MAN: Mrs. Hays will answer
a few questions,
and afterward
she'll be signing copies right here.
Thank you.
Are there any questions?
MAN: They saying
the girl alive now?
There were fingerprints
found recently, yes.
I'm writing about
the new investigation now.
You got any idea where she is?
Do they?
Uh, no. Nobody does.
- Are you...
- And what about your book?
You got any theory here?
You got some idea
about where she's at?
Well, this...
I wrote it
when she was believed dead.
So, you don't know nothing?
You just...
You're just making your money
and milking their pain.
Sir, the author has never claimed...
Shame on you, woman!
Dolls.
The hell?
Julie?